Hey, what up everybody? We're doing the Mario Kart Tournament. I may have started late. We were waiting for some people.
What's going on? How are you? I'm hearing a hundred voices in my ear. Let's deafen it for a second. Hello. How are you?
I am currently participating
in the Ludwig
Mario Kart
Invitational
It's going to be set up in two different ways. We're going to do the first thing we're going to listen to me
The first thing we're going to do. I can't see chat. Fuck. Hold on. There we go. Now I can see
What happened to bitcoin? I don't know. I haven't I have looked at it in like a day or two days. What happened?
I don't know. Whatever. I'm playing Mario Kart. Whatever
If you guys don't know the rules, wait, you got there's like 50 people streaming this right now
But you're staying here
Uh, we're gonna do the draft. It's gonna be teams
6v6, I believe then we're gonna do a free-for-all. I'm just gonna jump in. We'll see see what happens
Good luck
rock paper scissors shoot go for it
both competitors
Terribly desync cutie goes with rock alinity goes with paper. That is one point alinity. Obviously best of three class
shoot rules
Okay, let's go for one more rock paper scissors shoot
Paper paper. Okay, let's go again
rock paper scissors shoot
All right. We got scissors versus paper. It is one one. It's game point now next rps win wins it all
Yeah, right rock paper scissors shoot
uh
Yeah
Ty who are we waiting on? Yo
rock paper scissors shoot
Hi last one. Let's go
Cutie you win. Yay
Got a linear every time
What a match
That was uh, it's probably better than the mario kart match. We're gonna see
Um, great
So now when you win cutie, which means you get the first pick
Who would you like to pick?
Okay, cutie come on cutie come on cutie
Absolutely not miss kiff. I'm gonna go ahead and say clint come over to team butt stuff
Is clint the only person here with more than five hours in this game
But
Have you ever played this online miss didn't you just have your mom like set up an account for you just to play online
Dude, I just turned 13. So everyone's saying same shirt. Andy. What are you talking about? This is this this is mint
Was I wearing this mint shirt? No, I wasn't I was wearing blue look
We got the draft going i'm gonna i'm gonna end up being like the last kid picked at the basketball game
I already know it. I think connor is cute and I think he looks like he's good. So i'm gonna go with connor
Team alinity it is
Do you want me to tell you to pick no clint I want mango
You're so dumb. You're so dumb. Oh, that's a little nasty
I'm gonna be the last person picked. I already know it is mango on that team alinity. You get a pick again
Oh, by the way, uh, did you want to see the scores?
I think i'm gonna i'm gonna give my child just in case I need to help him with something else again
Cutie you get another pick who'd you like? Uh charlie anyone
Right now, um, let's go with a germa
There it is
Welcome to the attraction. All right, it came back around cutie
You know what you want to do to not get picked last with five hours in that's a skill alone
Come on, you gotta take preso on this dream team. That's what I was afraid of
Oh, no
Wait, we got german. We're pretty good. All right, your options are to be clear there. It's wubby preso stans or simply
Yo, i'm pretty crap
Wubby
terrible call
what
Really if I had to guess who's good
I would probably I really just don't want to listen to simply's mike. So I don't know. It's up to you
Okay, who is left sentence you ever said out loud who is left tell her anything
No, he's definitely talking more useless things. We have a wubby preso
simply in the
I think that's it. Well cutie
Well
Come on simply preso and stans. I said what what character am I? I i'm i'm the one going like this
I i've seen simply play and he's absolutely garbage
Dude, I beat you half the time we play. All right. Is that paymady wubby talking?
I I you really sound the same as him. He sounds very similar
Your mic is fucking I can use my better mic if you want. Wait, why would you choose to use your worst mic?
What is that decision? Does this sound any better?
Thank you. That was night and day actually on that mike. I think we choose preso
All right. Oh
Simply your stance cutie. Hey preso's legit as fuck. I'm so fucking
I was gonna take preso. I definitely don't want stans
What is going on? I'm so good. You've got the game today. Okay. Hey
I choose simply. All right, you're dead to me, which means a limited you get stans to recap the teams are team first up cutie clint
mango charlie wubby simply
Team alinity is alinity connor ms kiff jerma preso stands winning team gets 69 gifted
It's 12 races a good team tracking the point. That's a good team
It's gonna run like a free-for-all
So you're gonna have to learn your teammates faces in their carts because you will be able to hit them friendly fire is
Oh shit, what friendly fire is on friendly fire is on so make sure you know what your teammate looks like and don't shoot
A red shell at him. Oh fuck you guys do have your own voice channels
You can hop to team cutie and team alinity
You guys need to talk strategy and say hey don't hit me with a fucking red shell ms
Kiff by the way guys if if you get a blue shell and you're on my team do not throw it
Okay, don't hurt me. It doesn't hate your teammates. You're not gonna be in first. I'm terrified. I think i'm
Hurt everybody your teammates. Good luck to all
And then yeah, I need like a two minutes like a like a two minute
I'll be right back hop into your calls and just talk shop
Are you not playing no i'm casting oh you got the easy job
If we're in the if we're in the different calls though, how are you gonna see the
Uh, oh you guys are you guys saying sabotage sabotage the whole team
But you want me to literally not get not get invited to anything ever again
You want me to get like stared at by like like 25 people at twitchcon all going like this. Oh, yeah
It's that fucking guy. Oh, we're network andy now. All right, I gotta move. Hell. Yeah. All right
What are we thinking in terms of making sure we don't kill each other?
Uh wild idea. We all play donkey kong. Okay. I actually fuck with that so hard. Wait. Yes the character
Oh shit, it's a good idea. So we don't hit each other, you know, holy shit. That's brilliant
That's the last pick right here. Everybody's on
For sure
Don't go to the tauren though. He takes up too much of the screen doesn't he?
Uh, yeah, but he's fast like big characters are fast. He's the leader of the bunch. You know him well
Yeah, he's finally back to kick some tail, you know, okay. Do we have everybody in the lobby? Do we know?
Uh, definitely not one two, three, four five six seven eight nine. No, we're missing two
So just don't attack donkey kong. I got it. So how do I join?
You get a friend's eye. Oh, I see. Okay. Okay. Yeah, I got it. This is fucking brilliant strategy, by the way
Absolutely flawless strategy. They're not gonna do this shit. We're gonna fucking roll them
Go to online for multiplayer online and then friends. Oh, okay
Oh, no, I don't have my buggy
That's tough. No buggy. I don't have my yeah, because they're a new account. So we don't have oh you got a new account
Oh, that's tough. Yeah people are saying shitty build. Why? Yeah. Oh, no, I don't have my bug
The bug is actually godlike shit. No, I I want I want like I want a bunch of traction
Oh donkey kong weighs too much. Fuck. Hold on
Shit, I want like a full bar of traction
I'm worried that we have people in here that shouldn't be in here. Oh, we might we could do a we could do a check
I'm gonna say are you guys in here? Are you giving my best shot that they're all in?
I feel like there are people in here that are not supposed to be here. Well, it should only be 12
So if you guys are all in and they're all in that it's fine. Yeah, I'm joining right now. Are you in?
Yeah, it says i'm spectating guys. You gotta turn a bunch of shit off. Don't you?
Why are we doing this like a tournament by the way?
We're gonna have to remake it because people join that weren't supposed to be here
Why are we doing it like a tournament and connor just uh,
invite
Uh who invite uh clint last in mango, okay, because I think they have people in their friends lists
I I got I got booted this qualification by the way. Yeah
Yeah, they should deduct some points for that. You'd be crazy to you guys. Anybody else get booted from that lobby?
Yeah, I had to make a new one. Oh shit. Okay
Wait, how do you go offline? I don't think you need to I as long as you have no friends in your friends list
You should be okay or no friends. You've never played a game essentially if you have friends just try to join less
Yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna wait. I want to use this thing. This thing's so ugly though. Okay. I'm picking the dog again a band
All right. I'm with you connor. Oh shit. Okay, so
All right. I'm joining dude. Who the fuck's billy eilish. Should we just be the same car cutie?
Uh, well, it depends on if you like using a certain car
The beetles kind of nice with doing that. I think the beetle is really is one of the best cars, but we don't have it
Wait, no, you start with the beetle. Yeah, everybody had to make a new account. Yes of the friends thing
No, I think you start with the the beetle you're thinking of the other one
What beetle are you are you talking about? I I I don't see the car. It kind of looks like a hot dog
It's like a hercules beetle
Brown
I don't see it. Oh tilt controls. Oh, is that good?
Yeah, I think it's good the the beetle with the red tires and the clouds i'm going nuts
So you might not have clouds now. Are you sure that is that top meta?
No chat, I don't know ask chat if it's top meta is it good they're saying it's good. It's really good
I'm pretty sure it's the other deal though. There's still people here. That's enough. Who is the little guy?
Okay with the cloud. No, I think we're getting scammed. Yeah, like who's grease hole? That's charlie. So
The swell braces little guy is who's we do have that person's name
Who is not here? We have mizzy. I'm here. I'm missing his clint and germa preso. Yeah, i'm here. Yeah, i'm in there
In the game. Okay. Okay. Cool. I think we should be over here. Okay turn off smart sharing. Did I not?
Uh, okay. Ludwig. There's someone that keeps joining that. I don't know whose friends list they're on but they're
Small little me. I think okay somebody keeps like joining the game. I don't know if anybody knows who's fucking nintendo
I don't think so. I haven't seen their name. They need to speak so I can see their name
We all had to make like new accounts new nintendo like online accounts for this
I feel like it might be yours though. Oh, it might be my I have people on my friends list, but
All right. Let's just have stan's way to join
If your account's clean then just join so like miz is clear. Yeah, i'm clear. It's okay
Your name is Pedro. Who is Pedro on their friends list?
I gotta clean account. If you're on my friends list, i'm about to fuck you up and then this guy who is this?
This other guy keeps trying to join too. Hey germa. What's up guys? I have an idea
Would you like to come on my show one day? I think I can set it up. Yeah
Okay, you guys do you guys let me set it up because it anybody's who joins their friends can join
Okay, it wasn't any one of my I actually have a clear account. I have a clear account germa
You're proud. Can you join a friend if they're in a tournament though? I don't think so. Oh, they got good taste
I don't know about that. I mean they watch me. All right, try it again. Shit. That's right
All right. Oh you you you got yeah, I like your stream a lot. You got a great stream
No one ever says that man. You do have a good stream. Don't don't beat yourself up about that shit
You mean that I do Pedro and maybe he is one of me
I hope one of you guys isn't Pedro. I'm gonna say networking andy. Um, what are you talking about? Yeah
Yeah rejoin especially if you have a fresh account. Yeah, I'm good advice on how to fix it if it happens again
Donkey kong so there's no online if I use a random account, right?
You know what? Sure. I'm gonna mod you my chat. I gave mod. Are you serious? Yeah, I modded you. Oh shit
Yeah
It's like it's like 2000. It's like 2012
Tell them to join quick
Well, you I'm on your back person is back in but no greasy holes charlie. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. Who's the other?
Who's the green shirt on the left? Oh, that's definitely something simply would wear. We just lost preso
Oh, that was preso. Oh shit. Do you have it set to 12 races?
Yeah, I set it up after this screen. Oh, please simp god for sure. That's simply okay. Okay, there's one
Who's nate? That's you. I am stance and that actually just looks like you what the fuck. I know that's pretty good
Huh? Wait, this looks right, right? Is everybody in we just need you guys all in I mean, I mean
Yeah, there's a germ is not making the stream late this time
Well when I went networking andy man, I can't be the one that everybody knows is the late one
I've been here for an hour just ready drinking coffee. Just getting ready to do this shit
You can't hold it up. And everyone was remember I told you oh we got somewhere to be like yeah
We got like a thing. We'll go have an appointment. We're going to yeah, it's nice to see you the end. Germa though. Oh my god
Switch accounts, but then I had to link my account and shit. I was like scared that people were joining off me vrv
So that might actually be the case i'm not using tilt control. I was preso
Okay, what what is the least on the last one that's good on the character select thing when you're doing the uh the tires in the
Chassis, what's the glider is the third the lighter? No, no, no
The lyr what is what is the one on the way? They're right. Oh, what does that one mean?
I can't remember what they mean. All right, we got it, right?
I think we got everybody everybody in the other team is in I don't know what it means. I'm just like auto accelerate did
All right, boot it up. It's 12 races 150 cc
no teams
No, we're putting teams right now, right?
Yeah, but this is going to be set as a free for all so that um, yeah 12 races
Yeah, all right 12 races. That's good. All right, let's do it. Wait, can I come over this week?
Uh, yeah, cool. Wait, are you getting any new boxes lately?
Uh, I got them pokemon ones and i'm fucking i'm tapped out bro. You know, you know those boxes
Wait, so we need to remember who isn't our team so we don't hit them don't hit don't hit don't hit
Okay, we voting
What is your guys's character's name?
Listen to me mario kart stadium. I get first place every time every time I never lose
Okay, all right. I picked it for you. What the fuck is barry? What is that?
It's the first. Do we all pick the same?
Level it's i'm telling you I I farm that place
Sorry, what are we choosing? I chose it doesn't matter. I picked the first one
All right, just don't hit donkey kong, right? Yeah, don't hit don't go now. What if they are all donkey kong?
Are you not?
I'm peach i'm peach i'm go
Okay, oh sorry, we were supposed to not go donkey kong. No, we're just that we were supposed to go
Okay, I know I was going to and then I ran out of time. It's on your first place
Okay, i'm actually to start being serious for you guys. Let's go. Okay, so don't hit don't hit donkey kong
What if they have what if they have a donkey kong? Oh, then we're fucked
There is a mod meeting
Oh, they're all wario. Yep. Yeah, they're all wario. You have a mod meeting at 11. All right, i'll be there
Good start
Oh shit
Oh, wait, you're donkey kong. Oh, I got red shell. Did you red show me? I'm lucky. I'm lucky. I'm lucky
Are you son of a bitch?
Oh fuck
How do we get the other people's names off the screen?
No way
All right, you're peach you're peach. I'm right behind you. I got a red shell
Yeah, don't worry. I'm holding up the rear team. Okay. I'm at a cutie. That is such a gamer dude. This car sucks
Oh shit, the the left side has a speed boost
Okay
Come here connor don't drop that behind you, okay
All right. Hey, who's in first place? Who's in first place? I got I got a blue shell who's
I don't think any of us
All right, I got a bullet bill get out of my way, okay
Okay, i'll stay out of the middle
It did not work. I got hit
Wait, I I tried to avoid you. All right donkey kong boys
I fucked up. I got scared about the blue shit. I fucked up. Oh, oh i'm done. Oh, I got one of them
I just spammed item
I don't play as donkey kong man donkey kong sucks. Nice job connor
My boy
Good we did good. We did good. No, we we won that for sure. We won that
Okay, go donkey kong
Yeah, please go dong that was that was confusing. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Who was black yosh? Who dare enter black yosh?
Wait, well, i'm my team, right? Uh, just general rule do not pick the same map
unfair
So that way we just don't spam it because I was literally going to pick the same map. Yeah
I just big donkey kong by the way
Your perspective
I I haven't dropped any frames
I have zero drop frames
Wait, what's going on? Is it you mean like on like here? Oh shit where we're picking?
uh
Wait, where we're picking what we're doing? Yeah, I think it should work
I'm really proud of you guys. That was a good race. No, that was good. Yeah
Yeah, I I don't have any drop frames on uh on obs I don't know where it's coming from
First of all, okay. I got six so I fucked up. I got 11. Okay. Oh, I got 10
You're gonna have oh look at this in the lead. We have out of we have four out of that's so good
Four dongs at a sixth place. That's really good. And what do we get if we win this again?
Thousand 69 subs
Oh, wow, is your game plan all donkey kong here for so you don't forget almost all
Okay, who did go donkey kong?
Uh, literally didn't at first but we just owned her. I am I am donkey kong now. Okay. All right
Oh, okay
Okay, that was that was bad charlie's my nemesis. Got it. Gotta just pass him
That's the trick
Not last. Okay. I'm missing everything
I did all my practicing on dry bones not on donkey kong. Okay, we can hey we can switch
I'm such an idiot
Oh shit, oh, sorry. He knocked you into me. Oh
Oh fuck
Oh, who's the first i blue shell? Uh clint is i'm gonna go back. I'm gonna rip it
Ripped it
All right. I got i'm i'm lost. That's that
Yeah, i'm where is everybody? You got this
I have dude. I have a star and i'm not even going faster than the people driving normal speed
Just the worst things are happening to me. I need miracle rng jesus
I can't even hear that shell
First to last baby
Actually first to last. Hey, who's in first place?
Uh, nana, send it. I made it back to the pack
Okay
I got bowl bill careful stay in the middle stay in the middle. Sorry preso. Oh my god. He went to the middle my friend
No, no, no, I didn't get hit. I didn't get hit
Come on just hit somebody
Oh shit
That's big miss. That's big. No, you see me
Seven okay, what do we get? What do we get?
Oh, I don't know. I got they got one two and three one two three. Who's wait? Who's one one one, dude?
This like i've i've played this game for like two hours of my whole life and i've never played floating around going two miles per hour
Screws me up. I couldn't hear the items. All right, can I please if we got yeah
Yeah, change. Okay, we dry bones
Dude, it is so important for us to get first. It's so
First place literally the five or something like that. It's it's like we need first
We got this though. You got this
I mean, they're mostly warios and black yoshi. I feel like we can remember who they are if you want to change characters, you know
All right, if it picks my map we win
Buffering is insane. I'm not seeing any of that
I wonder why
Skill-based map. All right. I I always i'm just gonna take it slow. I hate this map. I always lose though always
I do really bad in this map. We're winning by the way. We're winning. We're winning 48 points. Yep
Well after the first race we're winning, but I don't know about second. No, we're winning we are
All right, love that we go here we go much better
Yeah, you should do the dry bones. Oh this place sucks
Yeah, this one's
Not my favorite
No, i'm sorry
Dude charlie hit me
You guys killing each other
Yep. Oh, did one of you hit me?
Miss
Somebody hit me and there's only doggie cogs behind me
I feel like it might have been one of you
Oh
Wow, why was that what's the look on that fucking squirt me and just like crawl on your wall?
No, this oh my god this they stole a blue
Abu. Oh my god. That was ridiculous rng
I hate simply man
Oh, who's the first? Hey, who's the first?
All right, i'm ripping it fuck it
Oh god
Oh, all right. I got a lightning bolt. Are you guys ready?
Do it. I mean we can't dodge it, right?
Yeah
Oh, I should have done that
I got a bullet bill coming in
Oh fucking played bad
This is not gonna be anywhere
Not for me
Go on i'm gonna hit you guys. Oh fuck. That was me. Sorry. I got two the two yoshis behind you though. Are you?
Yeah, you did
Sorry
No, oh dodge corner. Nice job. Oh shit. Give me it. Give me it
Nope. Oh, i'm about to get my shelf
Dude, I have the worst luck i've ever seen they literally a ghost stole my shelf and the second he stole my shell
I lost I I just got decimated
So he struck my lightning, sorry
We hit each other a lot
My stream is fucked on what this
Doesn't i'm not dropping any frames
Lagging hold on. What if I go like this?
Fix it. I was had out and then I got hit
And then I just what oh you this bad. I've played mario kart 8 one time ever
Like an hour or two
Is it a slideshow? I'm I I don't understand. This doesn't make any sense
Anybody else buffering right now? Like I I
Everyone's saying the stream is buffering. I got no drop frames though
Uh, no, my mine's feeling good. Somebody's pretty happy. Wait, wait, wait, stop, stop, guys
We are still in the lead. It is 84 to 80
All right. All right. Good. Good. We got this. We had a big first race
Okay, this this map you need to make sure that you're ahead. Otherwise, you're gonna get fucked because it is a
Very difficult map to have abilities on. Yep
No shit really we're in rainbow road
So try to make sure you're not in last because if you get abilities you're gonna you're gonna fall so far behind
I actually feel like i'm gonna pull through on this one. Okay, that's what they say about you a rainbow road, andy
So they called me
I'm actually fucking
racing like
I got something to race for dude
I feel like that dbz character that thinks he's really fucking strong and then realizes that everybody is a thousand times stronger
No matter how much you try
Like I just kind of had one of you guys in the chest and you were just like, oh, let's get by a fucking mosquito
Reza i'm with you
I'm hoping for a blue shell. All right. I have the worst luck great
Reza if you want to throw a go for it i'm on one behind you
Uh, no, i'm scared of blue shells. Oh wait third lap just i'm back with this fucking thing. I swear to god
Reza throw it chuck it
Fuck I thought the b button was like the slow down button. Is that not the case it is
work
All right, second and third nice good. I should try to destroy clintmore
Yeah, it's fine
No, that's good. You and I you and I that was good. I got
So far back dude, I I fucked my items the that was good stuff that wasn't even met for me was hitting me it
Ahead it's just impossible to fall behind. It really is
That's why I was just telling you to chuck chuck reds because I don't know if that was
Idea what's going on?
My my obs says zero drop frames. My game looks perfect. It looks through obs too. I don't understand
I don't I have no idea what's going on
Stop streaming to discord. I'm not I turn that off
I have no idea what's going on. So what what is what is happening? What is it doing?
Hold on. What if I do this?
Is it restart the stream?
I have I have absolutely no idea why this is happening. Oh, there's two black yoshis now
What's there always do please? No
The legend of the black yosh goes far back
Just drove right into that banana
Oh, is there a shortcut these guys are?
All right. I'm in first right now
Sorry second. That was on me
I was aiming for someone else
It's okay. We're all really close
We're doing good this race so far
Fuck you, bitch. Oh
I took simply out
I literally watched out. I'm right next to you
Okay, don't use that. Don't use that. Don't don't don't don't who's in first place. Who's in first right now. I'm in first
Hold on. All right. I'm not gonna throw it
I'm a second
Oh, you're a second. Oh, I threw a fucking red
All right, tell me you tell me hold this hold this boys if you hold it germa, I think no other blues was spawned
All right, good. I'll be useful for one goddamn round
I think I could have changed my like tires or something. I'm going like fucking two miles per hour right behind me man
It's right behind me
Mango's now ahead of me
Oh my god, i'm gonna get my fucking everything
Watch out. He's got three red shells. Yep. That's luck
What's up? Will it bill coming?
Dude connor's way ahead
sick
shit connor
All right. I got first
All right
Let's go. Oh, that was huge. I do not feel like i'm running on a fucking tricycle. Why am I so slow?
Oh, that was huge
Changing right there. That was a team too. That's the best germa. You are a god there you chuck. Thank you
Thank you. I'm gonna change cars
It did it knocked them out first. Let me just get blue shells hold them
Yeah
I sniped three of them at the end
Like two before the last turn and somebody right at the end as well. Like I took three of them
Fucking look at the speed. I on discord so I can see your perspective
Um
Or present that would be very difficult. Yeah, i'm live you
Let me see if I can figure it out
No worries. I don't know what's going on
But I think from trying to stream my perspective like i'm buffering my stream, but i'm not dropping any frames. It's weird
That's oh sometimes it does that and if it does that just back out. It's fine
I'm just trying to get a problem on this map mrs. Your stream's blocked so you can turn it off. Oh shit
Really? Yeah, I don't know why
Wait, is everybody's stream fucked right now?
And now I got mine is good. Look at these dongs, baby. This is great connor. Damn. Look at that top four. Oh my god
By the way, get behind other dongs and use them so you can get some speed
Genius
Clint has a red shell in front. I'm behind you connor
Clint. Oh, it's red. It's red
You know trying to take simply here. Can you move a little bit to your left brussels?
Yep, huh? Am I too late now? I'm at 11
Give me the purple. Give me the purple. We need to catch up a little in germa
Wait clinton eighth. Okay. No, i'm an eighth
Oh, he's yeah, he's in seven. I'm about to pass him
Hey mango's in first. Somebody has a blue
Fuck no, i'm not
Lost i'm so sorry shit. Oh, you're fine
Will you get lightning uh coordinate so people that stars can use it? I'm gonna make fun of you nice
or uh
We should we should be able to get mango out of here
Oh jeez, okay, uh
Okay
Watch out nate. I'm sorry. Oh, no, you're fine. You're fine. I dodged it. No, I dodged it. We're good. We're good
I'm in first right so hold that banana. Let's go
I have blue at blue
Hold it. Tell me when it's clear. I've got a red
Or when you finish so I can just knock someone out in front of me
Let's go. Oh my god
Oh shit
Let's go, baby. What a clutch. What a clutch. I knew that mushroom was there. I went for it. Oh
We're getting up there
Oh god, i'm gonna drop call and come right back
Great. I'm gonna read you on the call because I have no idea why this happened. He's just
I stream I don't I don't get it
This is very distracting
Not 12th and I thank god. I I wish I knew what the fuck is happening
I gotta go
We got first and second
How am I doing? Am I top two?
Uh, like all people I was in ninth man. I was I was I didn't
That's no that's good. That's good
That's still good. This track kind of sucks. It's kind of a bit of a free for all who is the highest point?
Uh quick update. They're up like we're up by 20. Yeah, we've been killing these last erasers
You're literally underwater. Wait, my mic is no you're good. Now. You're gonna. Okay. What'd you say? The score was?
You guys are one of the one of the warios just choked
I caught him back here. Don't throw the banana
Don't on the mud fuck
Oh, what the fuck was hitting?
Yeah, that might fucked me up
I'm in first by the way
I'm in last by the way
It's all right. Oh shit
This track isn't honest anything you should count
So true so brave of you to say that too
Oh jesus may go clear top two the dream team
Oh that thing just fucks you. Oh my god, i'm so sorry. I think I think it actually helped you
Oh, I have I have the thing where I have everything i'm not trying to throw it at you if I do
Hey, who's in first? Oh my god, I can just throw in the boomerang. Wait, do we got first place?
We're not done yet
Going up. Oh shit
I got second. Oh my god
Oh
Okay
Hey really clutch end game there missy
Yeah
This is getting that track is awful that track does suck but you guys i'm gonna try something here. Let me tell me if this fixes it
I'm i'm i'm very distracted right now trying to fix this problem, but I don't I don't even know what the problem is
Tell me if this does anything. Oh shit. I think I just turned off my console
Oh god, wait
That oh
I just like refreshed my thing. Let's see if this does anything. All right, i'm back first then you got the six
Yeah, yeah, you know you sniped him at the end
nice
Lag went away by the way saw that ninth place. Don't think we didn't see it
Did anyone on our team get 12th place no
Nice nice. What about 11? That's 11. Yeah, we did get 11th. I will say that i'm not gonna name names
But one of us got 11. Okay. Yeah, we don't want to talk about it. All right
This track is yeah exactly it is such a short map so it just that's it this fucking it dies immediately
Okay, 16 points
Dude, I feel like this this my beetle's not that good because the boost on the beetle is really bad
Hey, feel free to switch it up. You should go with the wiggler. I might
I don't think he has the wiggler. I'm trying as hard as I can right now. This is my worst mat
You're donkey pong. You can build up speed behind me. Yeah, there you go. Wait, I got a red who's ever in second
I can throw the cut
Yeah
Fuck
It's so hard to coordinate who to throw things to
What the fuck's that thing?
Oh, yeah, you have to dodge it the the the scary boy. Who's uh, who's the first they have um, they have blue
Oh, he's a blue germa. I'm a whole blue ante. That's what you call me. All right, there you go
I'm gonna like click click get in front and you throw a germa. Okay, throw it throw it throw it got it
Oh, I got bombed
No, wait, I just lost I just lost I just lost I just lost I got hit off the eye
No, you're good. No, I'm not good
I'm terrible. Okay. I don't touch anybody. I'm sorry. Oh, that's all right. We are all in last place. This is really bad
Yeah
You got triple reds in second fuck you quinn
I have a blue shell. I have a blue shell. Should I throw it? Oh, yeah
Wait, that's over. Oh, I got second. Damn it. We got rocked
I'm, I was literally on the edge. I got hit knocked off. It was over
That was a great play earlier though germa when you threw the blue
I I triple tapped somebody with green shells. That was my fault. I'm sorry
It worked out it worked. It just clinked out double reds behind me in second. I couldn't do anything
We should still be first. I think
Keep the morale up. All right, is it big on a favorite track?
Baby mark the baby one the baby. I've been
We could gamble with babies. Let's run. Let's run baby park. Fuck it. Which one is it in?
Dude
I had that man. That's what it's in at the leaf the animal crossing one
Yeah, baby park is pure rng. That is a is that is that the did they update it already?
I'm down for baby park or yoshi. So the baby park is it is a gamble
Yoshi, you don't want that. That's the best track
Really? I oh, I love that track
Yeah, i've never seen clint lose them stream looks good. No. Yeah, i'm sorry guys. I have no idea why that was happening
This is bizarre. Sorry
Seems like it's fixed now. Let's go. Oh shit. We're we're ahead by like seven points only six points
Okay, if you get a mushroom go through the middle, you're probably gonna get a mushroom
So just be wary and go through the middle. It can literally make or break you. Okay
Hold the mushroom for the middle
What hit me?
Uh, I think I just popped I have shells circling me and I think I got too close
Okay
Oh
This is what mario cries like now, huh?
It's fun
I mean like that
It's 10 coins for max speed, right?
Yeah. All right. Nice
I deserve that. Oh jesus. Oh, okay
I just ruined mango's life
Okay, i'm right behind mango now
nice
Oh alinity, i'm sorry. Oh wait, never mind
All right
All right. I'm in third. Oh my god
If anybody gets a blue call it out and matt can go behind
Got him
I got a bullet to careful
Clint has a red shell in first
They must wait good blue good blue
Blue's coming matt blue's coming coming guys. Fuck i'm good
I'm pulling from the back
Please swear god. Yeah, you should have used it
Who was in first?
me
You need to go behind clinton in the blue. I couldn't I was too far ahead
It looked like you were that far ahead. Oh shit. I was
I was getting first
I was doing good, too
I couldn't I literally stopped. Oh, wait, apparently that's a tough one. Clint saw it coming and clint stopped too. That's what happened
That's all right. We got second third and fourth. That's good. Oh, that's good. We got yeah, we got second
Overall, yeah
Oh, yeah, that was overall. So someone must have told clint that that was coming and clint stopped as well
So
What should I get for a car for something that has no idea what's going on?
What should I do? I'm trying to drift i'm trying to learn
What do I do?
drifting too much
What car should I have?
drift more often
I don't even remember. No, we definitely didn't win that round. We definitely lost points. I don't want to talk about it
I think we lost alan we need to just go through our g here. Yeah, we're probably tied
We're probably tied. Yeah, we were up seven. So I think it's going to be very close
Do you guys want to comment on why you are so adamant on going to baby park?
Rng, baby, what do you like? Okay, you want the gamble? Yeah, actually i'm now suede i'm on your side
It's all it's okay. It's track twice. It's been clint's track twice in a row
That is you want to talk about this you want to talk about a little weird a little weird. Um, okay
It's updated. We are oh
We're losing by two points guys. Okay. Okay. I can't come in last place. I'm trying i'm trying not to have that happen
No, no, you got
On the side early because then you get full coins
Oh, do you?
Yes
I didn't take your advice
Yeah, me neither. I forgot where it was. Okay. I'm with you preso in third
I'm with you preso. He's got he's got a bomb
He's always got bombs man
No, it pushed me. I'm sorry. I forgot i'm like live on your guys channels. I'm sorry
What the hell just happened i'm getting
Fucked up a bit. I'm in third behind you preso. Let me get hit by it
Uh preso, I have a red if you want to toss that i'll get in front and toss it again
Sure
Let me get oh
Wow
Guys guys guys, uh
Connecting time so this is a four fun race
Wait, what happened?
Wubbies thing disconnected, uh, he's in the in the lobby still he just for some reason it loaded longer than everyone else
So this is purely for fun race it won't count and if it happens again, we'll just remove like bottom two scores for exhibition
Dude, I I hate people that just make us like lap the weight all the time. It just drives me nuts
Like I don't know
I actually just get him out of here
Oh, yeah, that's right, that's right
Ha ha ha
Taking out connor holding me back because you guys man taking out connor part two
He wasn't expecting that one. It worked second time
No, you suck hurry up, why am I so slow? Uh, go same map go same map
Remember you're trying so hard. I really am I don't want to come in last place every time
Because now the final score is fucked
That was weird though, because I saw paid money right next to me the whole time so yeah, was it a bot or
Wait, wait, why do you want us to all just click the path zero, right?
Oh, I didn't do that. Might be
Oh, I thought we had to hit f0. Yeah, you're right. No, you're you're right. I wasn't paying attention. Neither was preso
Where's f0?
Oh shit, I didn't know why I'm listening to directions once dude. This is fun. It's fuck. We should just like once a week
Yeah, the problem is that we selected 12 races so even though we want to play another we'll have to
So he said this guy sucks
I i've played mario kart like three times
It is this is a very close winner loss like these teams are pretty tight
We need to just get first first second and third because it just powers you we need we need to get top two
All right top two right here. I got you. I'm going and are currently top two
Germa, this is all you okay?
Um, yeah
Get that bullbill make us win top three. All right, you got it
God damn first place is so far ahead
Let's go
Oh, that's you preso. Yeah. Hell. Yeah
Hey, jesus christ clint
Oh, I got bumped off the stage
Oh, I lost my audio right behind you
All right
I hit clint
Almost followed them off. I got two reds in first as long as I drive good. I should be fine
Okay
How should I be on the points?
I'm right in front of clint or mine clint
Clint has a thing so he's safe right now. I can't do anything to him. Okay, he used it aggressive
Who's in fifth?
Me and illy i'm getting destroyed
Oh my god, i'm raising my heart out and i'm not making any progress anyone on six secured 12th
Wait, wait, who's in 10th? Is it one of us?
Is one of us in 10th?
Speak now i'm about to grip it
Fuck. All right, clint got first. I got second
Uh simply got third
I hit him with the red shell really fucking strategically, but he just got ahead. I got forward
I I very strategically fucking smacked him
That was a tough one
That was bad. That was bad. Hey for for both of us though
Damn
I even got hit from behind by a red shell. I'm all in on the baby park idea
Yeah, I said, you know, let's do it. It's all right
What people said i'm wicked embarrassed for you
Stop it
I'm probably like bright red
I'm amazed honestly, like I may as well have my fucking pants and underwear down right here in front of everybody
Where are we going?
Baby, baby park. Oh baby park. It is pure rng. Like how are we gonna uh run the next race because
Two more races. We're just gonna boot up the next one. Uh as like uh, like an individual race
Okay, I got it because you can just keep the lobby. Yeah
So just boot up one more after this it might make you do four but that's we'll just back out. All right
Here we go, baby
This is how they're gonna be really good or really bad
We are 20 points behind yeah, we need top four here we need we need crazy numbers here
Okay, the problem is our last we're getting last place too much
We need like the middles. I'm sorry
That's okay. Yeah, I know that's a little bit of me. No, it's okay. It's okay
We'll save it right here me and connor
I've got a red watch out
What place you in?
How did that hit I don't know who that hit this is a disaster i'm just not getting anything
Fuck I do like I do like the music a lot
I got bowl bill going from 10. Oh weird
I don't know
Like a miracle
No, I'll give you a fucking miracle
A little bit of a hole
We lost we lost we lost
Oh
Decent I got I got literally I got
Wario's got top three
That sucks that's bad
That's over it's over that was america's funniest home videos all we gotta do is go one two three four five six in the next race
We got one more race
What in that map if you get hit? No to me that that was that was like uh
it was like an a leslie nielsen movie where he's
He somehow got into being like a conductor at an orchestra and he's trying to find the person that's in the audience
That's like the criminal and he's like
He's trying to like find a place like he's trying to find the guy
Is a boomer reference, that's a great. He's a great actor. What's our best track?
Uh
Where are we going on baby part? We need a miracle to get all of us in pop six. Oh, yeah
baby park
I mean, I don't know what the best way is
Depressed
Oh, there's no way we can win this no, there's not we went for the hail mary
I think if you get her second third fourth fifth and sixth you might
That's what I said
I picked baby park again somehow
You wanted it bad I get well, maybe we're going there I should go there
But harbor I fuck with it gotta be the best race of your life. All right
I'm gonna get first the cart that they're using is definitely better. This thing doesn't get nearly like look how fast clink goes out
I just saw a bunch of people go that way and I just fucking yeah
Oh my god, this car sucks. What was I thinking? All right, i'm in first. I'm second
nine second
Yeah, i'm third now
Oh god, it's going pretty. All right so far. Oh, I got bold. Wow simply double fired bald me
I've never seen that happen before. Yeah, that sucks
Let me get let me get second. Oh fuck
Damn it
I should just keep going
Got it i'm not trying to hit you
What a bounce what a fucking bounce that was what are these fireballs coming around the corner what yeah
Okay, I got sixth. You guys just gotta get first and fifth
Yeah, this isn't amazing. Okay
No the trolley
Fourth what happened? I've got two yoshi in front right behind you miss just hit him
I'll just take some bites
So I just told uh, I just told my chat this but i'll just say it's all yours
This is like as embarrassing if I was to pull my fucking pants down. I might be in my underwear
And i'm on stage and you're all there
This is like i'm gonna dream
Yeah, this wasn't good. This wasn't great. Um
Oh, I was racing so well. I was doing so well
uh
Is it possible to end the race early connor
Holy shit, that was bad. I uh
I severely severely underestimated how much better everybody at mario car was in this call
I thought we were just I thought that like we were gonna be driving backwards. We're driving into people
People were good
This is good
I don't want to skip free for all
Do this again another week, but we are moving over to free for all
Uh, and conor you can just close out this lobby make a new one
So we lost new lobby are they gonna come in here and shit on us?
You did lose. I don't know if they'll shit on you, but they did beat you change character
Should I change my so we go to we go to the free for all chat or what?
Yeah
Go to the free for all chat and this lobby make a new one enjoy the new lobby. I'm gonna
I'm gonna go with a new character
It was a bad character
No offense. I mean this with peace and love jerma. You suck
yeah, I'm
Like is it 75 of my in-game time in mario kart 8 has been with you
All of you
So what should I do? How should how do I pull this back?
More speed. All right, so I should get more speed
Well, let me unlock some of this stuff because like I we had to make new accounts
longer drifts
What should I what should I play with what character?
Goals to get first place. Yeah
The thing is I like played a little bit off stream and I was like, oh, okay. This is going well
No, no, not at all
All right, I gotta join this thing
But some of us are still playing
It says you're playing
Yeah, I didn't leave. I think we're supposed to leave but no I
I'm making a new group
Okay, okay. You connor i'm gonna go to the bathroom real fast. Did it close the entire lobby?
So who's who's a good character then what should I play as character? Oh wait, that was like advice
Character any level three heavy such as bar bowser wario or morton
Pipe frame card blue falcon and streetl are ideal. All right streetl. I'm gonna go with
Morton and streetl because I don't think I have the other one unlocked. All right, you're not good enough for heavies
Well, I mean I just i've literally come in in in ninth through 12th place every single time
It's not I don't have those unlocked
You can also press the button to make the car move
All right, i'll try this the streetl and like
Morton use a bike. I was like kind of good with the bike, but I had like I had different tires unlocked
Wood I was using wood tires and little scooter. All right, well i'm gonna go for it. I don't have wood right now
I don't have it unlocked. You're so annoying
If it makes you feel any better. I have a lot of fun doing it. So you're you're making my
My time better. Oh, excuse me. Oh, you're welcome buddy. Thank you. Is he like that yoshi circuit, dude
What I literally I told them they were all picking yoshi
If there was no items I was gonna win
That is
What kind of wheels should I get
I could be in there like oh let's have a little bit of fun banter. No, what what hey guys what do I do?
What wheels should I get?
rollers
like this
a roller
like that
And then what should I get?
Parachute any glider doesn't matter. Okay, it's fine. All right
I mean
All right. Looks like we still need me a clint. I think I have entered the building
I don't want to wait just because I feel like people join off me. Yeah, you should join last
What does slick? What do you guys mean slick wheels? What does slick wheels mean?
slick wheels
How do I do that?
Slick slick slick slicks don't do slick. They're called slick
Slim, I don't think I have them. I'm gonna go with this. This looks pretty balanced
Whoever's the best by league in the end of june. Oh, yeah
All right. So this is hey, yeah, let's do that
So this race is going to be three thousand dollars in the line fifteen hundred dollars for first
Uh 750 for second 500 for third and 250 for fourth. We also have a secret prize for 11th place
That's me
Uh-huh. Well, legally, that's me
I think I got 11th seven times for whatever reason you happen to be in the back for a lot of the teams event
11th does have a special prize so will be worth your while to a fight for not dead last
Yeah
Uh, it'll also be 12 races. Okay. Yep
It should go about an hour and uh, everyone if you can get the streams going everyone who had it in the last time
Get them going again
Yeah, I can't I couldn't figure out how to do that
No worries. A lot of you did get it and they were sick honors was fire. Love these
How do how do you guys stream from like your like a capture card though
I just share I use a two computer set up
I can't I use a two pc set up so I I won't be able to do that
I do not want to talk with all of you guys here. Can I go in my own little lobby?
Defen just defen, okay
Is there any rulings on voting maps?
Uh vote for whatever map you want and uh, that's totally legal because it's a one in 12 chance
You're fighting for yourself. I'm not I wasn't ready. Uh, oh
Just don't run a repeat
I picked the wrong bike. That's okay. I don't need it
all right, so
Let's go
Let's go. Let's go right? Like come on. I can't like i've got a
I can't be the guy that's like the two-year-old
But you just lie to me and tell me that I got in like fourth place
It's the little brother. It's it's the little brother. Hey, yeah. No, what place did I get you got fourth?
You came in last every time. All right, let's go. Let's go. All right, i'm i'm not i'm in my own thing
Let's do it. I'm ready
Come on
Oh shit
I gotta get mixed up. I gotta make some ground up here. I'm just throw a fucking cone at me
That just fucked me up so bad. It was just a huge like a nuke on the screen
Let's go boys. I just
Right at the end I do not know how I did that mango threw a bomb at you. Oh my mango
Thank you, buddy. Thank you
Dude you got me from the first the third you did I got I got from I went from eight to second
Just with the mushrooms in the corner
Dude i felt like crap man
That was the first i've been in 12th place the entire time we've been playing
Hey not that one my friend
I know it is big
All right, buddy. It's okay
It makes me feel any better. I got third. I got still a fifth. I'm not out. No, that's good. That is pretty good
Whoever did that lightning at the end is a hero
That saved mango mango was about to get hit by a blue shell the lightning was a dr
Perfect timing mango. Did you drop the bomb? Yeah, that was my bum mango. You fucked me so bad
That was sick
All right. Quiet. Okay. I got I need peace and quiet. I need quiet. My brain can't function without it
What the fuck was that?
God damn it. I think that drift right. I only have one coin
Damn it, man. Oh god
And I got lightning bolt use it now
I thought it's funny. Oh my god, my hands are sweating so much. Thank you so much
And then mango just kept going
Literally you literally I told you about it. I'm very sorry. Well, I actually didn't do that on purpose
It's been all day
Yeah, clint's looking a little lost without his supporters in there
Looking a little lost
Okay
I haven't seen you all game. I didn't add at all
I'm so fucked
Everybody's saying I don't deserve fifth. I know I don't but isn't that how mario kart works
That is how it works using the word deserve when there's a giant blue shell that goes from 12th to first to lift light them up
It's a little clean. What did you get that round?
seven
Seventh is respectable. I like that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's pretty it's not bad at all, right?
But you know, it gets the job done. They were you saying stop tryharding. Did I have to at least not come in last place, man?
Simply was nasty in teams. What's going on?
I i'm set up right now. I don't want to fuck with that at all
Talking into the boost
Come on. Uh, come on. Give me a I need both coins now
Shit already a lightning bolt
Where's the way they're going i'm going this way i'm fucking somebody right now. I'm just gonna screw somebody over
How am I still in the 11th place? What the fuck is this thing?
Whoa
All right. Come on. Let's go
Give me another like guaranteed victory. Oh get away from me. Get away. Get away. Come on. Give me a bullet bill right here
my god
Jesus i'm getting fucked i'm getting i'm so fucking sad
i'm getting fucked
I got green shells. I'm in 11. I'm in 11 first the whole time. Yeah, I got fucked. I got fucked. Yeah
I think I got three. I think I got three blue shells that time. I'm sorry everybody. Sorry, brother
Oh, man, clint had a lead for a year got hit by a blue shell red shell and it was gg
He bought it out. Yeah, dude
Prezo had a channel bet whether you would get first place or not and uh 90 people lost all their channel points
Let's go
What the fuck did you press you got first?
Yeah, I got first. The prediction was literally will prezo get first
Dude, this shit will double my bank account. Just let me have this. Oh god, not this map
I was just wondering what the sand that has the succ in the middle
Yes
All right, i've got this
Do you think that quicksand would give a good like blowjob? What the fuck? Oh, yeah. I'm so sorry
I thought I was muted. I thought I was talking to my chair
I just fucked up
Oh my goodness
Oh my goodness, this thing sucks
You just hear arnold
All I hear is hey
Wow, that's all I hear arnold's fortune dagger
Oh my fucking god. Are you kidding me?
All right, it's not over
Get out of the sand
There's so many bullet bills
Damn it. Don't hit me. Don't hit me. Please don't hit me. You're behind me. Please don't hit me. Please. Please. Please don't do it
Oh
Don't fuck it was done for oh
Somebody said somebody's using a hacked switch going for 11th place
I guess i'm going for it now one and i'm
Hit by everything starting with the simply dodging grabbing my double double items hitting me with it
Yeah, did those fireballs hit you by chance? I threw a couple back
Shut up fireballs hit me when I was in fourth at the end and I finished 11th
I'm desperately just trying to
Not be in the last place
Dude, it's this bike. I'm not playing with it anymore
Oh my god, that was dreadful
It's definitely bike for sure
You sound like a flustered grandma
I could I probably couldn't be your grandma right now. I mean, i'm probably like old enough to be your grandma
And i'm kind of flustered so it makes a little sense
Just get away from me
I don't like to go near you at all. It's you
Wait, what place did you get second? Let's go. Let's do it. All right
All right concentration
Let me try to get first. I can't believe I had first the first game
What happened? What the fuck was that?
Oh shit, that could have been me
That could have been me
Oh shit
I have zero fucking coins
I need to collect coins right now
It's coin collection time. Give me those. I fucking missed all the coins
Holy shit that went right by me
Get out of the way
Why i'm so slow hurry up
Dude charlie got mega fucked
Dead air i'm trying so hard to concentrate
Uh, this is the worst moment of my life. I'll take that
Wait, how did how did I just got first place if i'm in if I got fifth is it because everybody that was ahead of me
Just got screwed over
Yeah, there was non-stop bumper cars at the end. That was pure luck. Whoever got top five
Yeah
I will say clint had no competition for first on that one. No, he didn't he did not. I mean
charlie was close and then
I hit him like three times
And we're having fun. Stop stressing
I'm just fucking around. Don't worry
He never ever talked his manner known him. That was fucked up dude. Wait alivia
You're like you dropped that bomb in the first round. What do you want from me?
You paint it back
Wait, who's in first who's in first right now alivia is in first place with
I mean you guys do understand that the last game
What if we play i'm gonna i'm gonna drive the wrong way and just try to drive into the person in first place
And you understand that right?
Become inaccurate if someone drops or something
Oh, no
That's such vm like I don't think I could get away with it
In the race for the money who are
In eleven
Sixth place is prezzo and he's tied with connor or no one behind connor who's the seventh?
Uh charlie
Yeah, that's 12th place lead uh hit me pretty hard
I need coins
Bananas everywhere jesus, there is a lot of bananas. I know they're everywhere. It's insane
Dude, baby park is the one map where I like lean with every turn like my body
Holding the controller can't stay still
Oh, don't touch me and there I go there goes my lead what the fuck
There goes everything I worked for in life. It's over
Oh my god, that was a perfect time
That was perfect timing to use the star
I I played that so well and I still got ninth like I I clutched every turn and then one red hits me
We just got a new spot coming in. There's a secret gift for random placing between fifth and twelfth
Oh, what? Oh, that's big random number generator five through twelve and then one of them you're scared
Uh, no, no, I wouldn't do that clint. Can you do a placey one? What's the shittiest one grumble volcano, right?
Last one in what way the grumble volcano is like the worst course grumble. I like it actually. Oh, all right
Cool clan pick boom metals are scared thousands castles. I think people are pretty bad
Toad's turnpike. Oh shit. Is it actually gonna do it? No, let jex play
I've definitely improved. Okay, like the first like four or five races, especially I literally had blindfold on
All right, I got I got at least place in the top six. Let's go. Hold on eyes eyes my eyes
That's what you get. You gotta knock somebody out right at the beginning
This one hurts my head. Oh
It's fine. Relax like five people just did that
Oh fuck that. No
Whoa
I'm fine. What did me? Uh, oh watch this shit
How do I how do I cycle between items? How do you cycle between items?
I'm gonna hold this to the very end
How do you cycle between items? You can't
What what's fucking happen? What is that? It's gonna same two items again
Just use it. Whatever
Seventh fucking place whatever height squeeze
Brutal just keep getting last place man. It's really unfortunate. Why did you sit there?
Simply he's coming for a long time. I saw him my controller
I'm just gonna start waiting non-stop. How many more races do we have? I believe that was
Five more. All right. All right. Oh, wow. Holy fuck. There's still plenty of time to uh to pull this back
Oh plenty of time. That's what I was thinking. I'm gonna get first place every time now. I'm actually gonna start playing
Whoever used lightning in the last game is a fucking hero
Thank you clint. Didn't you have a a star during that too?
I did that I had a star during that. Oh, are you trying to imply that I don't deserve to get second because I get a star
Yes, I I think third is more up your alley, you know, I will see on this one
What does it do the imposter is sus face? No, just go google it. That's okay. I'm still in eighth place
So I think both of us are great
Really? Yeah, I don't know why everything's so cocky
Oh, that's a trap jam
Turn into a mud bath immediately
Oh fuck. Oh, that was a scary thing
Okay, goodness. This place is ridiculous
Okay
Oh, I hit his hand. I just jumped over that. Oh, I can't believe I jumped over
This map is wacky
shit
All right back in it
How am I so far away?
It's absurd
Karma, no, no, no turn
I I lost I lost
How'd you get a first this one?
Okay, fuck karma
Clint, where are you?
He's first. He's in first, but he's me
If you just keep asking him questions, he'll get rattled
Me and manga are going after him
Come on no get away from me
Slow down. Oh, oh you juked me. Oh my god. Are you fucking kidding me? How did you dodge that bomb?
Charlie you are the worst
You robbed me, man
Did clint drive off the level? What happened there? Yeah, I drove off the level
Unnecessary place of all time and then drove off the level charlie. That was so unnecessary. You rammed me
Wait, how did I get second?
Is this my first time playing mario kart? No, but come on
Indeed i'm getting fucked and i'm still in third
man
You know the the little teddy bears you guys sent for schooled
Yeah, no, so my dog you don't well you guys sent these really cute teddy bears, but my dog just
Ate his face cool
You asked me to send you a new one i'll send you next time we do school
Okay
He has no nose right now. I did almost rage quit accidentally that would have been bad
Charlie that was not needed
I I my eyes were red. I I just full of rage. I'm, sorry
I do one impression and this happens that was so unneeded rage quit at the ninth race
I think it was actually me that hit you miss. It's race where I drove. No, it's charlie
I literally saw charlie rammed me at the star and I hit you with fireballs on my screen
No, he he I did not deserve that at all. He's he saw me. Yeah, you're a good man. Don't take it personally
That wasn't the real charlie. I would never do that. Okay. Oh wait, this is my map
Okay, let's do it. Let's go. Come on
This is the one i'm gonna get top four in this one. I have to I have to
I got I got screwed right there. Sorry
I just drove into a fucking tree. I drove into a tree
Oh
Oh, you gotta drift. Oh
Whoever isn't first. I'm so sorry you dead
Uh, no don't
Oh
Jesus I gotta hit somebody in the air
No, come on right when I got the star off
Give me a fucking break
I need a fucking christmas miracle right now if I want to stay in this
i'm so
angry
I was in third place
I what joke wouldn't be choked. I'm gonna get in 11th place
What happened?
Who was who was just in 11th place? I also made you and you made me dude if I didn't you made me a president 12th place
uh
Meg you guys are tied for first two races left
Moo-moo meadows are dying. I swear do it. Holy fuck. I've gotten so many three races past few races and still managed to get like four through fifth
I tried my hard out. You guys are just absurdly good. I can't not get last place
Yeah, I feel like who's battling for that 11th spot right now
Uh, i'm in 11. It's a solid 11
Dan's cutie and simply are all fighting and no one else is close really
Okay, next match everyone. Please do moo-moo meadows. Fuck you. Sure. All right
Yeah, no, I get I get it. I do caught up. Let's make a five get the sub bet right here that I beat you
Okay
You already owe me like
In the hole
How do I think i've ever played this one? Have I what's the airport one right?
Oh, don't go off the edge
Holy shit. I went why did I go so fast?
Oh, it's a bomb. I'm gonna fucking screw everybody over. I just killed like three people
I just did not I freaked out. I can't play this game
I need to play double dash where I just am the one that throws the items and somebody else drives the car
Gotta hit these fuck off two wheels. You fucking idiot
Oh
How do you take that turn with a fucking didn't? Yeah
Oh, this is too hard for me
Come on hit those things
I didn't even get a chance to fly
Go, what are you doing?
How does this keep happening?
Connor i'm gonna share my one year anniversary by the way, so there's a yo so that's four subs. I owe you now
Well, it's more like 70
Play cheers to you
Okay
I want to move on see if it helps. Well, let me what place are you now?
I'm getting fucked. Okay. Are you guys targeting me on purpose? It really feels that way. Yes
It a hundred percent feels that way what you're about to hear your mom coming for your ass, bitch
What? Hey, why what are you single? They just ninth place. I don't care about 11th anymore. Why are you coming for me?
What I do? I'm well, you're one place ahead of me. You're gonna kick a man while he's down reach
Down you're ahead of me
All right. Let's go. All right moomoom cells are dying
Here we go
I don't fuck around with this one
What you're about to hear is encouragement and praise with cheering applause
Just for you
Acknowledging you for a variety of reasons
Oh fuck. I lost the other head. There's a situation that does not apply to you. Why how the headphones came on
I'm using two different headphones how you feel
So sit back get ready
Here it comes
We want to thank you for all your hard work
You're the one who steps up and gets things done around you
You keep your word
You deliver what you promise
And then you go the extra mile
You're doing a great job
a great job
If anyone asks we'll tell them
This one's too hard where to go. Where's the fucking cheers get out of my fucking way
You're probably wondering why yeah
It's impossible to be able to have cheers to you play with this is the second time you probably played this map
And you don't play mario kart. Oh, well, this is the last one miss kip. You do have a good chance for a top four
This is the actual last lap right now
It's top four wait
Who is fourth and how many points my way
Uh president, why would you ever bet for me? I've come in
Seventh through last place every single game. I am not gonna ever get past like fourth
You know what i'm saying? Like that's just free money
One or two. Yeah
All right. Last one. Good luck everyone
Okay, good luck everybody. Have fun
By the way, i'm gonna i'm gonna drive the wrong way the whole game by the way, okay
Okay, respectable wait don't do that. I don't know if it disconnects
I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna do it. Okay. I I don't know if it disconnects. No, you'll be fine. Oh
Oh my god
Oh that shell is a such a bad spot
Oh my god, I can't believe it. I'll give you a sub if you just stop moving
You've got to stop throwing shells someone whoever's doing you gotta stop. I feel really bad on that one. Whoever's nate
Yeah, well
My mother raised me better, I don't know why I did that
You should all destroy connery's pants yeah do it
Oh, oh my god fucking cows
Oh
Lucky prezzo
First or second that just chucked a red shell at me. No, I didn't make
Who was in first or second that just you got fucked at the end
Wait, did you get hit by a red shell in second that threw a red shell? It was me
I threw it backwards like right after I finished or right before I put it did not place top four
You literally just stopped me from getting top four hundred and thirty feels good feels real good
Good job. I'm happy with top four
I think it was clint clint mango me and then
Yeah
To the dream team 11th place who won that simply got it by two points
Yes night 11th
It was a coincidence
All right
That was a lot of fun
I suck absolute asshole at this game, but that was a lot of fun. I was fun to play
That was fun
Not change it and then one person ran pretty much the same thing 12. I'm gonna give 69 gifted. Oh shit
Wait, i'm fifth
Yeah
So I thought I should charge. Okay. All right, let's go 10th
I'm feeling eighth place
Uh-huh a little 10th there for my knife. You do it
Let's pull it up for the fans. Wait, who got first place?
clint
Who got second mango?
Yeah
Dude mango's dirty at this game. I was not expecting that
Mm-hmm
I probably should considering it's a nintendo game. Oh, no
No
Okay, i'm angry. Hey reroll though. Imagine who won you won miss
That's no way
Baby, so I got what if what if what if fourth place get more money than you got more money than fourth place
You got work. I can't lose man, which is 350
I can't lose. You're welcome. Thank you clint. Thank you. Good friend. Good friend. I got you
I just want to give me like 20 boys. I got nothing else for you. Thank you all for playing
Hope you guys had fun and shit
Making this even happen
Organizing it. It was so much fun
Next week, let's say ban clint put him in the hall of fame. He's too goaded
Uh, you're dead to me. Have you ever thrown another shell in this town again?
I already am going to fucking confessional about it. I feel bad
Our next event is a 16 man battleship tournament, uh that me and germa are throwing on that'll come that'll have some time in the next couple weeks
Yeah, of course. Absolutely
German totally knows what you're talking about board game battleship 16. Are you talking about a video game?
Battleship. Yeah battleship the game
You mean like the one where you pick like b4 squares and stuff exactly. Oh shit, that's fun
I used to play that when I was little tournament
So is it like everyone against everyone and this is a real thing
I don't even know what competitive battleship is. That's unbelievable clint clint's not invited to this right because he won
Uh, why would I be excluded from the battleship?
Yeah
Um, but anyway boys, thank you so much. That's all I got. Uh, have a good rest of your days and shit. Yeah
Let me write you have a yoshi. Let's go take it easy guys
Nice to meet you, uh
Meet a lot of you for the first time. Yeah, everyone nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you. Love you clint connors
Nice to meet you man
Hey, thanks. Nice to meet you big moist. It was a pleasure man. Nice meeting you
Nice to meet you as well miss and uh, hey miss i'll be at that mod meeting
Uh, i'll be at the mod meeting at 11, right? You're yeah 45 minutes to be there. Okay. Okay. Yep. All right. Bye guys
Bye
Well, there it is
That was the uh
whoo
Uh, I must say I didn't realize I was gonna get smoked that bad
But that was still a lot of fun
sorry for the I don't
know why
The stream was so fucked up. I think it was good because I we were pulling perspectives into lidwig stream
so
but
Yeah, I if you came here thinking you were gonna get good mario kart gameplay. I have to apologize. I did not make that clear
um
Fuck I really thought I thought I was gonna do really good
I
Man, i'm in my own little world where me coming in first place at like 50 cc is like really good
When I saw 150 cc, I was like, oh
That sounds fun
I like play on 50 or 100
It was a lot of fun though. I look this is just for fun. So live on a tuesday
Well, just because this is just a fun thing. Ludwig was just like you want to do it and i'm like, yeah, sure
Why not? That sounds like fun. And oh, yeah best 16
uh 16
Person battleship meta to a twitch tournament. I I let's I let's go that sounds like a perfect thing to do
We'll work on that
The next stream is gonna be on
Uh, we're gonna do tuesday again. I have some stuff I gotta do this weekend
Actually have a lot of things going on this weekend
So we're gonna do tuesday of next week exactly one week from right now
And then after that we're gonna go back to normal. Let's go back to normal with sunday saturday and sunday
Uh, yeah, we've been doing a lot of um, kind of coast up streams, right?
The last like three or four streams in a row. Uh, we're gonna go back to some solo stuff for a little while
But it's it was a pleasure to even be invited to something like this. It's a lot of fun
And it was cool networking andy, right? I hope it was at least somewhat enjoyable
You could there was a lot of other perspectives to watch if you wanted to watch somebody not get their ass kicked
But it's all right, uh, and that's gonna be it. I'm gonna i'm gonna close it out here
I'll see you guys on tuesday of next week. Have a good rest of your night. Let's get the subs in
Let's do it here
And here they go what time? Uh
Like 2 pm pacific on uh this coming next tuesday
And hopefully in the next couple of weeks the next like two or three weeks
I will have a lot more stuff to share with you guys because I did mention this a few times
In august and september are two
Monster streams. I mean like monster streams one in august and one in september
So I will have a lot more to share about that soon because I have to because we're getting there
It's coming in close. Uh, who of that group is streaming? Let's see
Who's still going?
Do we just don't everybody is who is like continue who's gonna continue to stream? Let's see charlie's gonna keep streaming
Yeah, we can rate charlie. He's playing smash brothers
He's going right from uh, right to smash brothers. All right, cool
Battleship tournament would be actually great. Oh, I know that when I when he just said that i'm like, oh shit
Let's go. Yeah, well i'll dump you guys on charlie. So what are we? What am I streaming next?
I'm gonna have to pull out some stuff
I have to go back. I've got a lot of single player things things I have to go back to
Okay, cheers to you. Yeah, too bad. Cheers to you didn't work
It's all right. Thank you everybody. I will see you later. Good night. Goodbye
Take care of yourselves
You