You know, before we play a game like this, I think it's safe to say I should take a little swig of whiskey.
This is free-for-all? Is that how this works?
Oh, you use a kick too? I think it's just free-for-all.
Dude, I just blew that guy's head open.
Wanna go? Wanna go a shit-shooter, McGee?
This guy over here. Don't worry, don't worry.
Oh! Bang! Shit!
Oh, I got fists. I got a knife too, right?
Yeah, I got a knife. Oh, you can throw knives!
There's an explosion over here.
Shit! I'm gonna get...
What? Oh, he's still alive!
Not anymore!
Oh, dude, you can have two things at the same time?
This is just like the old West!
Where is somebody? I need to kill someone.
Come here, you bastard!
Wee-hoo! Wee-hoo!
Somebody behind me, right?
Uh, don't kill me.
This one has six shots? Yeah, six shooter.
Somebody behind me too! Shit! No!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
That was a pretty good arcing knife throw.
That's fun. That's cool. I really like that.
That's a really cool feature.
Get out of the way! Get out of the way! Don't block me, bro!
Where is he? Where are you? Where'd you go?
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it! Let me out of here!
I'm gonna throw this and turn around and just blast this dude.
Come on! Yes! Nice.
Gotta keep the streak going. Gotta keep the streak going.
It's all about those streaks.
Guys on my team. That guy ain't.
Whatever. Screw this.
Death from above. You don't even know him right here.
You have no idea. You have no clue what's about to happen to you.
Yeah, you did. It's a team deathmatch, right?
Yeah, I'm on your team.
Don't go to shoot. Don't shoot. Hold your fire.
There you go. Nice teamwork. Nice teamwork.
We got another bastard coming in here.
I only got two shots left.
I didn't get him.
And now I got a long ass reload here.
Good save.
Good save, dude.
It didn't even matter. It was for nothing.
So I heard you wanted to fuck with the guy with dynamite in his hand.
Is that true?
You gotta be kidding me. I did not really mean to do that.
You can hold it for a long time.
I can hold this for a long time.
Come on. Walk down these stairs.
Yes!
I can hold this dynamite for a long ass time.
Oh, that's a doof-er.
That's a doof-er.
Special. $2.99.
See you in the checkout lane.
Never turn your back on a spy.
We're gonna go for a Hail Mary here.
I'm gonna try just to destroy this guy when he comes through.
Hail Mary!
Got him. You like that Hail Mary?
That knife throw is one of the funnest things. I love it.
Damn.
Crouch. He can't hit you.
That guy's on my team. Why is he shooting me?
I don't think I have any more knives left.
This single shot shooter thing is awesome.
This game's pretty fun.
This trajectory is very odd.
Come on up the stairs.
Where is he? Yeah, up there.
Watch your head. You're a little too tall for this ride.
I took his hat flew off.
Did you see that?
This thing goes so fast.
It is such a fast moving projectile.
It's crazy.
Bites going on. I can hear dynamite.
I can hear all kinds of stuff.
That was too unkillable. Good.
Dynamite! Jesus!
This hatchet is scary business, man.
Nobody even understands.
The hatchet wielder is coming.
What? Okay.
He's dead. It's alright. We're good.
I hit him in the nuts.
I hit that guy right in the balls with the hatchet.
And I don't have a weapon now. I gotta go recover that.
Kick his side right through the fucking window.
I'll take his weapon.
I wanna get a little minigun.
I want to use my little cute guns.
I feel like I have two little toys in my hand.
I wonder how dangerous they are.
I wonder if they shoot BBs.
I'm gonna shoot you with my little BB gun.
Where is anybody? They're pretty dangerous.
That's pretty dangerous.
This guy's in a lot of trouble now.
That's how you hatchet.
That's how you horror movie somebody.
Can we horror movie anybody else?
Yeah, this guy.
Get horror movie'd. We both have the exact same idea.
He's gonna get his and I'm gonna get mine.
We're gonna do it all over again.
Shit.
No. Please.
I just wanna play the horror movie game.
That's the end of the movie.
Horror movie villain died.
Movie's over.