Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with Scare Saturdays.
Gonna be playing Candles tonight. Heard it's pretty ridiculous, a lot of jumpscares.
So if you don't like jumpscares then, well that's too bad, you're gonna get scared. Scare Saturdays.
Bang! Alright, Candles. Get a nice little bonfire here, we're out camping.
Enter the forest. Why is my mouse still on the screen? Oh there we go, it's gone now.
Okay, here we go. Playing Candles.
Ooh, um, I can't see anything. Wait, can I go down here? Yeah, I can.
So the whole purpose of this game is I'm supposed to light candles in my haunted house.
That's the only thing I read about. Just gonna follow the path.
What a weird path. Am I gonna like fall off the edge of the world here?
Oh, there's a jump button, okay. Jump. Jump!
What kind of house does this person live in? Are you serious? Where do you park your car?
Can I go in?
This is small text.
While you've been away, your basement generator must have run out of fuel,
thus your house has been overrun with the dark, loving night imps that scour these parts of the coastline.
As you know, they usually like fish, and what they... I don't... I cursive...
You know what? Gotta turn on lights. That's all I need to know, right?
Oh dear. It is really dark in here. Turn it on!
Come on, the game's called Candles! Turn the light on!
Oh, my game just like froze. Why can I not turn this on?
The game is called freaking Candles. I should be able to turn the candles on.
Oh, okay. There's one candle lit.
God, this game keeps like freezing! Quit freezing on me, bro!
There's a candle in this room. Where is it right here? Lit.
There's another one. Hey, look at that. There's another one in the corner.
And one more, right? Yes.
Hey, we lit up the room! Is that like a picture of like... Who is that?
Is that Larry Bird from the Boston Celtics?
No, it's like Grover Cleveland.
All right. Is it gonna freeze again?
Hmm. I think I'll need to get my key to this door from my bedroom.
Easy. And this one.
Oh! Oh, whoa!
There's a person in there! There's like a demon in this room!
Oh! What am I supposed to do?
What am I supposed to do? Do I have to walk in there?
I don't have to walk in this room, do I? Are you kidding me?
Oh, dear Lord!
Candle! There's a candle in here! He can't get me.
He can't get me. There's a candle in the room.
You piece of crap!
I thought that... No, that's just the shadow of the chair.
I thought that because he was a horned being. He was a horned beast.
See how it looks like a horned beast?
Oh, sh... Turn on! Turn on the candle!
Dear God! Is that the only candle?
I think that's the only one in this room.
Looking... Can I open the fridge? Is that blood?
I hate this game already.
Oh! Oh! I'm going this way.
These candles are lit.
Damn it, man! Damn it!
Something tells me I have to go in here.
Well, true. We'll go back. If I need to, I'll go back.
There's no light in this hallway.
Jeez! Oh!
I figured it out. I gotta bring these mother effers to the light.
That's how you kill them.
So I gotta drag that one dude that's in that... Oh, the key's in here.
Where's the key? It's a pretty huge key!
This is the key to my house.
Sick like giant three-foot wooden key.
I can get into the cellar.
I gotta get this guy. This one guy in here.
Alright, come on out. Come on out, you son of a bitch.
Come on. Come on out!
Come on! Did I die?
This is the bedroom.
Wasn't there a dude in here?
I forget. I forget. I forget.
Okay, all these are turned on.
Get the key again.
Oh, god.
Where's the light? Oh!
Oh, my...
This one was so easy last time.
Give me the giant wooden key.
Come on.
Why are the doors closed behind you?
Alright, come on.
Come on, man. Just come over to me.
There's a candle right to the left. Can I do it?
There's one more room.
There's a guy right here.
Come on. Come out. Come out, you piece of crap.
Come out. I'm gonna have to run to the desk.
Three, two, one, go!
What? He should have died from the light.
Oh, you...
Turn on.
Thank you. Alright, I'm back here.
Made it back safely.
I gotta get this guy out of this room.
Get out of that room.
You butthole.
I'm not the cellar, but there's one imp left in this room.
I don't know how to get rid of this guy.
I'm jumping onto the desk.
Okay, guys.
I have no idea how I'm gonna get out of this one.
It's on. It's lit.
How are you not dead?
Explain that to me.
The candle is on.
You should not be alive.
Okay, I'm gonna go for like a jump over his head.
Here we go. Jump over his head.
That didn't work.
Shit.
Here we are again.
Can I get this guy to chase me out here into this light?
Come on, man.
Come on. Look, I'm like a nice, like, succulent human.
Don't you want to eat me?
Yeah, you do.
You son of a bitch.
Need anything in here?
That's it.
All right.
Well, that does that.
Now I can go in the cellar, turn on the generator.
And I know that's what I have to do.
You can't get me in this light.
Come on.
Yeah.
Yes.
The last light.
Where is this, like, supposed generator?
In here?
Damn it.
I can't see.
I can't see anything.
There's definitely one in here, and I'm just, like, locking myself in here with them.
Turn the light on.
Can I turn that on?
Turn on the damn generator.
How do I, like, turn it on?
Is it, like, a tool over here I can use?
There it is.
Why is this not turning on?
Come on, generator.
Generate some electricity.
I just, like, flung it on.
Can I, like, fling it?
Why?
It started to move.
Hold on.
Spin.
I command you to spin.
There we go.
I'm doing it.
Maybe not.
What the hell?
What kind of generator is this?
Not really working, are you?
Oh!
I got two lights on.
I'm almost...
I'm almost got the generator on.
I can't believe this is how you do this.
This is the most, like, awkward way.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
Spin.
Spin, you fool.
Yes!
Yeah!
Oh!
Did I do it?
Oh, yeah.
Generator's on, baby.
That's how we do it.
All the lights are on, right?
If I get out of the cellar?
Oh!
Perfect!
See you later, monsters.
That's Candles.
If you want to go...
It's free.
Link will be in the description.
It's a jump fest, as you saw.
A lot of crazy screams that I'm not that proud of right now.
But anyways, guys, I'll see you all next time.
And, of course, take care, everybody.
Light the candles!
Bye!