This is gonna be you want to get bake-stabbed part two. Do you want to go to sleep a little bit?
Hey, you want to go to sleep? You want to go to sleep? You want to get sleep slabs?
Hey, you want to get sleep-stabbed?
You want to get sleep-stabbed? I don't want to get sleep-stabbed. Is it like when you go to sleep,
but a spy was like actually disguised as your bed?
I can't even like play because you just said that. Come here, I got you.
You want to get sleep-stabbed? I don't want to get sleep-stabbed.
The spy is just like a big square. I don't know how he does it. What am I voting for?
What are you singing? Is that copyright? Is that copyright? Yes. Then are you singing a
copyrighted song? You're gonna get me arrested. Hey, I only copyright when I'm Fourth of July.
I can't believe I got that guy. Actually, you know what? I can believe that because I should
have got him. Yeah, you had it in you the whole time. I hope I did. What are you playing as right
now? The snipper rifle guy, the Australian long shoot man. Oh, the guy with like the
elephant hunting rifle? Yeah. Well, you can take down a wildebeest with this. When are they gonna
put in a hunting rifle in TF2? Damn it. When are you gonna make a new huntsman with changed stats?
When are you gonna make a crossbow that on headshot does 700,000% more damage than the
huntsman and on body shot, you fucking EXE crash out of TF2? That would be actually really cool.
I like that idea. Yeah, you don't get a headshot, you HL2.EXE crash if you don't get a headshot.
What happens if you miss? Like you don't get a body shot, but you miss? Does it still crash?
No. What happens? Does your FPS drop by 10 every time you miss? Yeah, your FPS drops by 10 every
time you miss. And if you land a headshot, it goes back up. Oh, I'm just like walking around.
It's the skill based mechanic. The periwinkle. Insert funny name here because I'm tired and I
don't know funny names. Periwinkle. No, but periwinkle. No, that sounds like a Christmas toy.
Are you saying that it's not a Christmas toy? It has like festive lights on it.
Touche. Touche. Gotcha. Touche. God, Hamlet's headshot him in the air. Kill me.
Oh, crashed the desktop. No, my FPS is just dropping. Oh, body shot.
How about a rocket launcher that has one shot, that has one bullet in it, and it moves like
two miles per hour. When you shoot it, it moves incredibly slow. It's like a turtle,
but wherever it lands or wherever it hits, explodes the size. Hey, hold on before you go
any further with this. Why is everyone always going to make fun of turtles? What's what we mean?
Oh, it's so slow. It's like a turtle. Because turtles are frigging slow. Not all of them.
You've met a fast turtle? Yeah. What's his name? That's my grandfather. How is that not a headshot?
That was like a shoulder shot. I tell you my grandfather's a turtle and all you have to say
is, oh, how was that not a headshot? You're very supportive, Jerma. Your grandfather was really a
turtle? Yes. What was his name? Longbeard. Longbeard the turtle. Yeah, he was a pirate too. So he had
like a pirate name, like Longbeard. Because every pirate is named after their beard. You got red
beard, long beard, yellow beard, gold beard, Johnny Locks beard. We're going to have to call
Burger Boy Cheese Crumbs because that's what is always in his beard. That's actually a really good
pirate name. Hey, Cheese Crumbs, get over here. The same scout has hit me with every single move.
You know, how about that one? Yeah. Oh, right when I was like starting to do like decent and by
decent, I mean like luckily shoot one dude in the face. Oh, get me. You're not going to get me.
Too bad. You're not going to get me. I'm standing right behind him. You don't even have, you have no
idea. You have no idea. You're not going to get me. What team was I just, what's going on here?
I'm so confused. What was happening? If you have reserve slot, I think you do. They can't kill you
at the end of the round. Oh, yo, Merry Christmas. That's that. Why is your server have yo Merry
Christmas? It's festive and shit. Yeah, but it's not Christmas anymore. Anymore. It's always
Christmas. You just had like the Huntsman with the lights on it. Yeah, but that's, but I didn't mean
to. Christmas isn't a holiday. It's a way of life. I guess you're right. Cause you wake up in the
morning. You're like, yo, Merry Christmas. Yo, Merry Christmas. Is that what you do when you wake
up? That's the first thing I say. I wake up, I look at the ceiling and I go, yo, Merry Christmas.
And then I diarrhea every single morning. Let's edit that part out. Cause I don't want people to
know that I diarrhea every morning. I think they know. I think they, they can just guess. Oh, you
know that guy German? Oh yeah. He diaries every morning. How did I not kill that scout? No,
you Swayze son of a bitch. Hi, I have ham. Tyco RC is about to charge up his batteries for his race
car and have the battery only last 15 minutes after like a six hour charge. What is this guy
doing over here? Are you, what are you hiding from? Are you protecting this rock? All right.
Yeah, I guess he was protected. We are at the last point. It makes a little bit of sense. I guess
got to protect that rock because once you lose the rock, everyone could just walk into mortar
mortar. All right. New, new tests to see if I can do this. I have to stay alive on star server for
more than 15 seconds. See if I can do it. Is that you? Are you the pyro? Nope. Nope. Oh, your,
your pathetic little grenades just bounce off my manly chest. Come on. Shoot me again. Didn't work.
It didn't even work. Oh, I didn't know it protects it against that. I am completely protected. Okay.
Let's see how long you stay alive at the mid fight. Okay. If I die at this mid fight, I have to like
drink the rest of my ice coffee as fast as I can. That'll hurt your head. God damn it. Why did I
just say that? That was not a good idea. That means I have to stay alive. That'll hurt your head.
Don't hide in the corner either. No, I'm going, I'm going up balls to the wall. This is happening.
I cannot die here. Mid fight. Here we go, baby. Smoke it. That was a terrible jump. Smoke it.
No, get this pyro out of here. I lived. I don't have to drink my ice coffee as fast as I can.
I'm going to come kill you like right now though. No, you're not. Oh, I thought you didn't have
that much health. It's okay. It's okay. I've died from like 30 scouts since hitting F9.
I have like jello vision right now. Did you do something to me? No, I didn't do anything.
Did you like give me drugs? What's going on? Oh my God. This is bad. This is real bad.
It's serious. Hey, tell me when you respawn. All right. You guys can have a comeback.
Are you about to give me like 100% corrects and no clip? Are you, are you respawn? I am spawned.
I am spawned. Good luck. What is this thing? Oh no, do it again. I walked into like a freaking
resupply. Oh, what does this thing mean? What does this thing do? Just have fun. Just shoot a guy.
Oh dear Lord. Oh boy. Oh no. People are going to think I'm a legitimate hacker.
I got killed. Some pyro blew the rocket back. I went spy because I was going to try and kill
you while you were like that, but. Dude, I died within 10 seconds of me having that thing.
Can I have it again? I don't know. I don't know if I can trust you.
Let me have it again. All right. This time I promise I'll make use of it. Yay. What is it? Oh,
right. God, no. Oh, that's you. Stabbed you in the back. Now I'm Swayze. Just give yourself
the valve rocket launcher. I could no clip. Just no clip and stop backstabbing people.
You know what? You know what, Jerma? You know what? That's a good idea. I just want to see this.
Waiting. Oh damn it. I was like waiting to watch and I got friggin' cabred. I actually died.
Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. I feel bad for that Angie.
Like of all the ways for your sentry to go down, the spy who just came through the wall
was probably like the worst. Can we have just like another no clip fight?