Dear Tom, new paragraph. Can you please send me the images we talked about yesterday?
Question mark. I would appreciate it. Period. New paragraph. Thanks, new line.
Germa. Tosh Meston. That's close enough. It's time to control Team Fortress 2, only by talking.
Walk. Walk. Left. Right. Walk. Strafe right. Back. Strafe right. Strafe right. No, left.
Left. Left. Straight. Walk. Walk. Left. Right. Right. Shoot. Shoot. Back. Back. Back. Shoot. Back.
Strafe right. Turn left. Left. Shoot. Back. Shoot. Hopefully I reload. Okay, good.
I'm gonna have to just stand here. I'm not gonna be able to kill any person, by the way, doing this.
Right. Right. Walk. Strafe left. Shoot. Shoot. Strafe left. Strafe left. God damn it.
Walk. Shoot. Up. Shoot. Shoot. Shoot. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Left. Shoot. Left. Shoot.
Shoot. Back. Back. Up. Back. Back. Detonate.
I'm pretty much a bot on easy at this point. No, I'm doing worse. I'm doing worse than a bot would do on easy in this game.
I'm essentially the kitty cone of Team Fortress 2 right now. You wouldn't even sell me to an adult.
This is gonna be the one. Cloak. Walk. Stab. Right. Left. Walk. Stab. Yes! I got two people.
And all it took was to be a cloak and dagger in the corner.
Walk. Up. Fire. Fire. Back. Left. Shoot. Right. Right. Strafe left. Strafe left. God damn it. Listen to me.
Don't crit-screak me. Do not crit-screak me. That's a big mistake.
If you crit-screak me, you're gonna be real damn sad, I'll tell you that.
Strafe right. Left. Strafe right. Walk. Right. Walk. Fire. Left. Left. Left. Right. Fire. Up. Shoot. Right. Right. Fire. Down. Shoot.
God, that happened so much later. I'm gonna have to do that as if I'm shooting a Huntsman bow at somebody.
Shoot. Oh, come on. Shoot. Right. Right. Zoom in. Right click. Why did I- I'm forgetting my commands. Right click. Right click. Left. Shoot.
Fuck. Right. Left. This is a fucking da- Stop. This is really dangerous. Right. Right. Right. I'm gonna fall off. Bugs. Stop. Duh. Walk. Stop.
Stop. I knew it. I knew I was gonna fall. There's no way I could have made it past that.
Because the delay is long enough where it doesn't matter what I say. Stop. Back. Tree. Shoot. Good job. Good job. You shot the fucking stairwell.
Down. Oh, fuck. Walk. Stop. Fire. Left. Left. Left. Left. Left. He's dead. He's already dead. Left. Left. Cloak. Walk. Stab. Got ya. I got him.
I'm so excited about that. Oh, yes. I got that one person. Awesome. We're about to lose the game.
...to make sure you know that I tried to make a fun video. Unfortunately, comma, unfortunately, that didn't turn out so well.
My hypothesis and my experimentations were not happening as well as I planned. And I'm really sorry it'll never happen again, Tom. Please don't fire me. I hope we can still be best friends.
Your...your...thank you again. Comma. Period. New paragraph. Cherma. 900-800-500. Your favorite employee.