Hi. Good to see you. Hope you're having a good day. How are you? I was sleeping. Well, wake up.
What time is it? God is here. I am not God. No. You guys remember Bruce Almighty,
when he sits down to the prayer email thing, and he presses yes to everybody? I couldn't do it.
I love that movie. That's a good movie. You need to grant my wish.
What if I did a genie stream where I was a genie and I was granting wishes to people?
I feel like... I don't know if that would work. You would dare ignore my prayers? How's your day
going? It's going well. It's going really well. I feel like the only thing I would be able to do...
No, this wouldn't work because we would have to have people kind of pre-screen their genie wishes.
Because realistically, genie, can I have some money? Yes, absolutely. I could give you money.
That's the extent of what I can do. I can't really do anything else.
Genie, I really need my driveway paved. I guess I could try. What else would I be able to do?
I wouldn't be able to do anything else. I guess you could wish for someone to power wash your
driveway and I would come do it. I don't think this idea doesn't work. You have to
interpret the wishes like a genie does. Okay, so how I would interpret that one? Oh, great,
powerful genie, German985. I would love for you to power wash my driveway. Your wish is my command,
but then I send you an invoice. It's a service that you're paying for.
It's on Groupon. So you being a genie means you just become a contract labor worker.
I mean, what else would you do? Oh, great and powerful genie, I wish for you to go
down a hill, a big hill in the neighborhood on a sled. Okay, I could probably do that,
right? But I couldn't do much else. You could wish for me to... Oh, great and powerful genie,
I wish for you to go to David Buster's and have a fun two-hour evening. I guess I could do that.
There's not much I can really do. What are these wishes? I have to say, I wouldn't be able to fix
very many things. It's like, oh, I wish for this, I wish for that. Oh, Joe, great. You wouldn't be
able to wish for world peace or anything with me. I wouldn't be able to do it. I'm not a genie.
You can wish for me to power wash your driveway for the stream would be kind of fun, but I don't
think I could do anything else. Fake selfish genie. I just don't, I wouldn't be able to.
Okay, I wish for emote only mode. Yeah, I could do that. Oh, great powerful genie, I wish for you to
end the stream. These could be kind of fun, but that's not really, I mean, this could be fun for
like 10 minutes, not for like three hours. Anyways, here's the plan. We are going to be playing
House Flipper. Their pets update came out. I want to check it out for a little bit.
There's also the possibility to play multi-versus. I got access to the alpha. If I want to play that
for a little bit, I can. I don't, maybe I just play House Flipper and we'll play multi-versus
soon because I think that is the alpha. I don't think the alpha is permanent.
Yeah, the alpha ends in two days. Well, yeah, whatever. I'll figure it out. Alpha ends in two
hours. No, it doesn't. Wait, does the alpha actually end in two days? Does it? When does
the alpha end on Friday? It ends in two hours. No, it doesn't. Shut up. It does not end in two hours.
It's still the 20th. All right, somebody just had a helpful message and it got eaten by the automod.
It's on, okay, the 27th. When on the 27th? Why does your microphone sound so weird today? I like
it covered it in Vaseline and covered it in like oils and olive oil and stuff. I was trying to get
like a nice smoother sound. I don't think it worked. Automod removes all helpful messages.
May 27th at 5 p.m. Pacific. All right. So if I don't play it today, then on Friday,
I'll play it for like 40 minutes. So that's fine. It's going to be a good stream. I'll play it for
like 40 minutes. Whatever. I don't think you guys, nothing helpful was automoded. That's all right.
Yeah, we'll play Multi Versus on Friday for an hour and a half, maybe an hour, maybe 30 minutes,
or I'll play it tonight if I feel like it. It does look kind of cool though. May 27th. Yeah.
Can you do a Street Fighter KO combo? It seems like the game plays identically to Smash Brothers
with one kind of major change. It's more team-based, right? You have team recovery moves
and stuff, isn't it? Otherwise, it's essentially very much the same game, isn't it? It isn't. It's
balanced around 2v2. Oh, okay. I knew that they... No, it's not even close. There's no shields. Okay.
Multi Versus is going to be free to play. Oh, that's fine. General, please wish my best friend,
my silly fluffball, a happy birthday for the 27th. Please, they are your biggest fan,
and it's all they want for their birthday. Happy birthday, silly fluffball. It's me,
JerkBot985, Neil's birthday man. It's my birthday too. Happy birthday to everybody's birthday. I
can't do them all. Here, if you have a birthday within the next three to six business months,
happy birthday to all those May birthdays, happy birthday to all those June birthdays,
happy birthday to all those July and August and September and Donor and Vixen, and then we're
going to wrap back around and take back the White House. Yeah. There. Did I cover it all?
That's an old meme. Do any of you know what that is? Chat's way too young to know what that is.
You kind of are. Maybe you are. You are way... That's way too young for... Yeah. Does anybody
in the chat know who Howard Dean is? You have to, right? Who? Whatever. Is that the funny scream
guy? He didn't even... All right. He went like, yeah. Everybody fucking freaked out. Like what?
Really think about that. He became this meme joke guy because he literally said,
we're going to go to Michigan and Oregon and I'm doing a pump up speech and we're going to go and
we're going to win next time. Yeah. This guy's a fucking Looney Tune. This guy's fucked up.
Huh? All he did was cheer. It was absurd. What am I turning it to here? My mic. I know my mic's
fucked up right now, but I definitely had time to sit down and fix it. Compressor Andy. Are you like
40 years old or something? No, not yet. So what? Hold on. I haven't heard this in a long time.
You know something? You know something? We're going to South Carolina and Oklahoma and Arizona
and North Dakota and New Mexico. We're going to California and Texas and New York and we're
going to South Dakota and Oregon and Washington and Michigan. And then we're going to Washington
D.C. to take back the White House. Yeah! But what? Was that that big? Was that that bad?
What? Because he has he has like a really great like WWE promotion voice. What? He was just
yelling. Is that big of a deal? Boomer humor. All right. Fine. We'll get to the zoomer humor.
We'll get to the zoomer humor. Here we go. Hi guys. Hi. What's going on here? All right. So
the word this is pets DLC. It's time to flip some houses. I don't. So there's new shit here.
Here's my computer. Okay. So I have to do I have to do like the pets tutorial DLC. Okay. Because
I can't touch this yet. I also have. All right. I remember this is the house that me and Ludwig
when we competed. So I got I can sell a lot of this stuff. I can just sell all this and just
get a bunch of money. Are there new pet houses? I don't see any new pet houses. I thought there
were more houses. Maybe I do have to unlock them. I think I have to unlock them. It's easy money.
Okay. All right. So let's let's just go. Let's do this. This is pet house full of pets. Can you
guys hear it? Is it too low? I can't even hear it. Okay. I thought that was it. I thought that was
animals. So what is going? What? What? What? This is like one of those children's play mats.
Where am I? The training didn't make any sounds. All right. Alice Finbar always wanted to see the
world. After graduating from university, she decided to satisfy her one of us. Three years later,
while on a motor race, found a hungry and sick bunny. Eventually became her travel mate. Alice
has bought her first house recently. She wants to move in with Jesper the bunny as soon as possible.
Settling down will be something new for both of them. This is freaking me out. This is freaking
me out. I don't know why. Okay. So we have, we have to take care of the bunny rabbit. So what
do I have to do? Am I high right now? No. The voice acting. And driven a dog sled in Alaska,
but house renovation is not really my thing. This is funny. I've heard you can do wonders
and I want my home to be one right now. It's in a worse state than Machu Picchu.
What's that? Something more than just my base camp. What's that? A place I can work from,
live in, rest. How many animals are in this house? Wait, there's like, why are there tracks?
For me and my bunny. And to be happy here too. Let's go out with the old and in with the new.
Okay. So I need to do this job to unlock the pet stuff and watch out for that train. Okay. Get rid
of that trash. This is a nice house. Is that a, this is pets DLC. Look at this. They added animals.
Look at this pets DLC. Why am I still fucking Santa Claus? No, I don't have to do any of this.
I actually don't have to do any of this. No, I don't. Wait, remove weeds. Do I really have to
do this? All right. I guess I'll remove the weeds. Eat the bugs. Oh, look at that giraffe. This is
cool. All right. So just to clean up the trash. Oh, can you step in dog shit in this game? Oh,
that's too bad. It would've been kind of funny if it was like, and then you could just walk around
and just track dog shit through the house. Again, I've said, this is a very relevant time for me to
bring this up. I have to say it again. When was the last time you stepped in dog shit? It hasn't. I
don't think it's happened since I was probably like 13. It's never happened to me. I don't think it's
maybe like ever, maybe once or twice ever. Never, right? It's always like such a trope, but I feel
like it never happens to anybody. Wait, where's my, what are my tools? Oh, I just smeared that
around. I wouldn't put this on the counter. Is that a fucking owl? Can you hear this? There's an
owl in here. That's all sounding like fucking toilet sounds. All right. This sounds way too fucking
high. That's freaky. I don't like that. What happened in here? Why are there bird feathers
everywhere? It's a pigeon. Well, where? Why did the, is this place, were there like animal parties
in here or something? Why, there's dog tracks, there's bird feathers everywhere. There's like
piss on the ground. Were they just hanging out in here? No, that's not, those aren't dog prints,
are they? What were they doing up here? Okay. I was going to pick up all the trash. What the fuck?
What's happening? Who's calling me? Why is there a dog up here? Why is there a dog up in the box in
the attic? Ah, this is going to be my puppy. But do I have, yes, of course. But yes. I can't do that.
Why does it have a weird hat on? What do I do with the dog now? Um, what am I supposed to do with
the dog? Uh, you want to sit down over here? Hey, um, you're kind of, you're kind of dirty. How do I
clean the dog? Do we have to like go to a dog like groomer or something? This, no, that's not how you
do it. Why is there blood up here? What is this? Use, what's this? Bunnies are very lively animals
and need a lot of space to have fun. The best option is a free roam room, but sometimes they
will be safer in a closed one, especially when we have other animals at home or unsecured stairs.
I don't know. Free roam room, I guess, is what I'm deciding on. Are you okay? Okay. That was just like
freaked me out for a second. I was like, what happened? Unsafe rabbit room. Unsafe. Really? Um,
what? This puppy's name is Lassie. Helper, energetic, and is a fussy eater. Okay. So let's,
um, you want some food? Oh, all right. I want a treat. You actually throw them. Okay. What about
clean? What is tug of war? Like pet is busy. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. Slow down. Fetch. Oh, go get it. Where'd it go? Will you catch it in the air? I got it. I
got it. I got it. I got it. Don't go up there. Please don't go up there. All right. All right.
Let me see it. All right. Fetch. Wait, how many things can I use? Will they catch it? You all
right? Are you okay? Now we're going to get rid of these. I need to give you a bath or something.
Don't, how do I remove these? Just remove it. I don't want to throw it over the fucking fence.
Okay. How are we doing up here with, uh, with the cleaning? It's good. Looks good. Looks good.
I clean these, uh, windows. It's good. I, I literally, I would look, watch. I thought,
okay. So when I went like this, he jumped in the air. He jumped in the air at one time,
didn't he? He went like this. I thought he was going to jump up and grab it. I don't know.
Don't be sad here. Just take another one. Look, this is there. They're all made out of like soft
rubber or something. Ready? See? Look, I thought that he was going to catch it. Do you want this?
And there we go. Okay. All right. You're good up here. Just be careful. Anything else to clean?
All right. It's clean, clean. It's going to be nice and clean. The dog can't understand you.
Come with me. Maybe you shouldn't come down here. It's probably kind of dangerous.
Look at all this. We're not playing thief simulator. What is it? What even is that then?
I thought this was a painting. I didn't think it was a rug. Okay. Looks pretty good. Looks pretty
good. That was an eagle. How many different animals are here? Did you hear that? That was a
literal eagle. Oh, wait. Where's the dog? How do I call the dog? Should I get the dog like a spray,
like a spray down or something? Come on down here. Is that, should I go take like a bath or
something? Go play with the water? I don't know. Follow me. Okay. Follow me. I wonder if this will
work. Come on. Let's go. Come on. Let's go. All right. Well, get over here. Let's go. We're going
to give you a little bath. What's the temperature outside? It's nice and hot. It's a nice hot day,
right? Okay. Here we go. Do you want to, do you want some of this? Do you want to play with them?
Okay. There's a fucking bald eagle in this neighborhood. Like this, this is freaking me
out. There's a bald eagle here. Okay. Should I do this? We think this is like fun. How do I
wash the dog? I don't think this works. I don't like the fact that you're over here. I don't,
I don't like this. I don't like the fact that there's a fucking train over here.
No, you're going to the house. Uh, uh, put them in the bathtub. All right. Well, first of all,
let me figure. All right. I'm almost done with the cleaning. Oh, come here. This way. No. What
am I? How do I? Okay. Well, just be careful. How are we looking? We look pretty clean. Is there
a basement? They're probably, this is pretty clean already. What else is dirty? Oh, you want
the other stuff. Okay. So you want a magna leather soft, magna leather left corner sofa, 1500 bucks.
Actually, this thing's huge. Okay. Jell-o coffee table and, uh, pom-pompa's grass. There you go.
Here, boy. Here, boy. All right. Let's go. The boring color. It's a girl. Oh shit. Here, girl.
Close the front door. All right. So now what do I unlock? What do I unlock? The eagle is going to
get her. Oh, this is our house. No, no, no, no. This can't be our house. Wait, you have a, you,
oh, food. This place is a fucking dump. I need to fix this place up. No, no,
filled with more food. No, stop. No, no, no. Don't eat that. Don't eat this. Get rid of this. How do
I get rid of this? All right. How you doing? You okay? How about with water? Does that look good?
You okay? I need a dog bed. Next to cement bags. This is fucked up. This is fucked up. Okay. This
is really not okay. This is not okay. Get rid of this shit. I can't have my precious puppy here.
Get rid of this. We'll get a, we'll get to a better house. This is dangerous. Okay. It's not,
it's not dangerous over here anymore. Okay. That looks fine. All right. All right. All right. I
just want to get all the immediate problems over here. Okay. All right. That's cool. Needs hygiene.
How do I do that? What, what do I, is there really like a dog hygiene thing? Dog, dog chew toy,
dog mat. Here we go. Washing tub for large dogs. All right. Washing tub for small dogs. All right.
Come here. What's this thing on my face? I don't know. Okay. Here we go. Now it's, can I do that
a little more gently? Wow. Look at the difference. Okay. Here, have a treat. Oh, I just threw it away.
Have a treat. No, come out of the, no, get out of there. Look at, she's so cute. Okay. Go right here
and here, have a treat. Here you go. You want this? Oh, good catch. Nice catch. All right. Let's go.
You want some water? Come on, please. I want to hear it. Nice. Okay. So you, are you okay? You just
sit here by yourself. These, all right. These birds are fucking annoying. I'm just going to be
honest. I feel like they're in my head and why are there, what kind of bird is that? Why are there
tropical birds here? All right. I'm going to, let's, where's the laptop? What birds? You know,
how do you not hear the birds? All right. Where's the laptop? Okay. Morgan's pet care. Bunnies,
rodents, reptiles. You mean to tell me that I could have just a house full of birds, reptiles,
snakes and spiders? Hold on. Can I just have like a hundred spiders? No, I can't. All right. But wait
a minute. Okay. Snakes. Should I make a snake house? How about a bird house? Does it have parrots
everywhere? Oh, look at the cats. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. A little Bengal. A Norwegian. Bragg doll.
How about a little Bengal? But wait, what's the pet hotel? Pets at home. Oh, find a new, move to
hotel. Pet hotel. What's the tutorial? I can't fucking think of the birds. Okay. Choose an
enclosure for small animals. You have a, there's a pet panel. You have pets and jobs. You can take
cats and dogs on a job with you. Okay. You'll pet, we'll get a hat, which will turn off its needs.
It's magic. That's cool. Different traits. Different. Okay. The helper traits. Oh, they can, they can
help. Don't put your mouth in that. It'll dig holes when needed and can carry the paint for you.
Okay. Playing, feeding, sleep, bath time, going potty. The pet hotel. All right. So they can,
I get it. I need a place to go first. So let's go back and let me see the browser for purchase.
All right. Here we go. There's this house here. I can buy this. The blue snuggery. This is the house
I was just at. All right. I'm going to go, I'm going to go sell some of these houses that I don't
really want. Fix up your house first. That can be my house. Watch. I'm just going to sell this. Watch
this. I'm literally, I'm going to sell this place right now. Yeah. Just we're selling this right now.
Sell. Sell as is. Nah, you can do better than that. I want at least what I paid for it. I want at
least what I paid for it. At least 150. That's fine. I can negotiate. Now that's all right. I'll
take it. I'll negotiate a little bit though. I want another five grand. All right. There we go.
Yeah. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Appreciate it. Accept the offer. I didn't do anything to
this house. I didn't even care. Holy shit. These are not the photos you want to put on the Realtor
website, but it's all right. I sold it. Art of the deal. Now let's, ah, this is like so, I hate this.
We're not staying here though. I'm moving to another house. The microphone shadow makes it
look like you have a black eye. Whatever. Okay. All right. Now we're going to go sell the other
house. Is there a stain on your webcam? No, it's a shadow and there's gunk in my ear or something
because it feels weird in there. What was that? Okay. Browse. Um, this is the man cave. I'm just
going to sell it. I don't even know what this is. Sell it. $268,000. I just want what I paid for it.
Turn the ambience down. I will. This person wants a sauna in their house. I should have
sold them the other ones. Okay. $184,000. All right. Let me negotiate a little bit here.
I'll lose like a thousand bucks. Whatever. Okay. All right. I lost a thousand. It doesn't matter.
Fine. I just need, I need capital. That's a handshake deal if I've ever seen one.
It just got a little darker. The time of day changed. That's the only difference.
Oh my God. What happened to the driveway? I got to sell the, uh, the versus Ludwig house.
I feel like I might get some good money for that one. I got $450,000 bucks. We're going to do
another couple of animal jobs because I want to unlock some, I want to unlock some animal houses.
Okay. Owned. This is where I am right now. So I'm going to sell this one and then I'll buy another
one eventually here. No more birds, please. I'll fix it in a minute. It's even like still too loud
at 0.08. We are down to one cent and I can still hear them. Okay. That's fine. That better. That's
fine right there. All right. So I saw I'm going to sell this house, put it on auction. Oh, this
is going to be a big profit. I forget what happened in this one. I'll take it. Not bad.
You took it from the bed, which is weird. Not much change there.
TV. All right. Good. I got like six or $700,000 now. I got a lot of money. I can take that and
I can buy a huge like half a million dollar house and I'm going to have snakes. I'm going to have
spiders. I'm going to have other animals. We're not going to stay here for very long. Oh no,
you puked. No, that's grass. What did you, what is going on here? What is all this? Oh my God. Watch
out. Watch out. Watch out. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. All right. We
got to get out of here. We got to find, we got to get a new place. We got to get a new place.
All right. What's the, I need to do one more. I need to do another animal job to unlock some
more animal stuff. Terrified of moles. I don't want the mole to attack my puppy. It looked like
they were, it looked like he was about to start fighting. Okay. Let's see. We did that one. I want
to unlock shit. What's this one? Animal caretaker. There is the only one I can do. All right. I can
do this one. Okay. So what do I have to do? Do I have to help with, oh, is this the animal hospital
area or something? There is this saying about changing the world. I'm sure you know it. When
started with myself, now it's time for my home. So what do you need? Structure and order. They
are crucial for my plans. This is how I see it. Cats and dogs will have their rooms downstairs.
Got it. The other pets in the attic. Okay. Yes. I know it's such a nice room, but it's worth it.
It's nothing compared to what they went through. Okay. What so many stray pets experience every
day? Can't save them all, but a few is more than none, right? Was that, that was a rubber chicken.
Okay. The animal caretaker. So what's the job? That eagle is going to freak me. I swear to God,
it's going to come attack me. All right. What do you need? What do you want me to do?
What are we looking for? This, your house is wonderful. This is a beautiful home.
What do you need me to do? I mean, you want me to pick up shit and rearrange it and,
okay. Upstairs, right? Look at all this. Where are all the animals?
All right. You want this new. Sell the drawers, sell this, sell the whole room, sell everything.
Okay. That can go. That can go. What else do you need? Picture birch. Yeah. Okay. I could see that.
Painting of a forest road. Yeah. Okay. So now you want a dog. Oh, this is where the dog
stuff is. All right. I got you. Dog bed. This is the one you want. Looks good. Right here. No,
that's too close to the radiator. How about in the corner? That looks good. Okay. We don't want them
to be too, okay. Like there, that looks all right right there. All right. You want a light under
bowl mat. That looks fine. Yep. Right there. It looks all right to me. Everybody's going to get
their own mats to eat and drink off of. Two automatic food dispensers. Yes. House flipper.
Yes. Okay. Two water dispensers. All right. I'm just doing this to unlock. Rubber chicken,
chew toy, tennis ball, a big cat tree. Put it right here so they can look out the window.
Cats really like looking out windows, right? That's all right. Okay. Mouse cat toy. You got it.
Okay. Okay. One of these over here. Okay. Litter box. All right. That can go right here. Looks
good. Now I need two of these. All right. That's fine. Right there. Okay. I need a pee pad. There's
a lot of shit going in this room. Pee pad. All right. I need a pee pants. Put it right. Let's
put it over. I don't like over here. No, not near the food. Like right here. This needs to move.
There's toys everywhere. You're messing with the feng shui. All right. Pee pad will go right here
and then this litter box will go right here. Okay. That's fine. All right. Now this is a dog carpet.
Really cool. Okay. And then we're going to do a double foot stool or what is this? What's this
for? What is this for? You can't fit all this shit in this room. Okay. Automatic cat water feeder.
There's too many. They're all going to be in this room at the same time. What? Dog enclosure.
Interior dog enclosure. Like this? Just little dividers. That's fine. Put it down. I can't put
this down. Why? There's so much shit in this room. Oh, okay. It doesn't matter. There's so much shit
in this room. Breed chat. What? He said the attic too. Use the other rooms. I thought it was...
The game usually is whatever room you're in, it tells you what to do. That's usually how the game
works, right? It's whatever room you're currently in. These are the objects that you need to put in
here. That's how it's been the whole time. Forever. For like five years. Floor tiles. I'll move it.
It's been like that forever. It's whatever room you're currently in. For the missions, at least.
Yeah, no. It is this room. See, room 37M2. It is this room. Yeah, I was right. Put the food
under the mats. All right. Bon appétit. Can I? He can rearrange this however much he wants. There we
go. Okay. See? That's better. Toys need to go in the corner. This is not even my house. I don't want
to put that much time into this because I want to do my own. This is not my house. I'm just trying
to make some money so I can buy my own animal house. If you want to come in here and rearrange
it, that's fine. You can come in and do it. This is a home designing game. Bro, House Flipper is my
number one most played game on stream. You don't think I know what I'm supposed... I'm just trying
to do the missions quickly to be able to buy the house, bro. Now we've got to go to the attic.
Where are the mats? I just want to do the mission so I can unlock the stuff because I want to make
my own. I didn't say sell. My awesome entertainment center, dude. Oh, you didn't? Oh, okay.
Oops. Actually, you did want me to do that. All right. Bunny enclosure. Yeah, it is the same room.
All right. So we should just go like in the corner over here. I'm thinking it doesn't matter. I'm
going to do my own. Okay. This is for a... this is for a guinea pig. Whoa. That's huge. Okay. Let's
put this one over here. Turtle aquarium. I want to do this so bad. I don't care about this other
person's house. I want a bunch of turtles. I want a bunch of... There's hamsters, too. Hamsters.
Look at how cool this is. Okay. Furry carpet. A big pantry. Sure thing. And poof. Poof over there.
Poof over here. And a poof over here. Sounds good. Awesome. All right. Cool. I'm gonna give
you that money so I can do my own. There was one more down here, right? This is... yeah,
the house is already pretty nice. What are the rooms? It was downstairs, right? Yeah,
this room looks like shit. I know. But I... I'm just trying... where do I need to go? The bathroom.
Bathroom. The upstairs bathroom or downstairs bathroom? Wasn't that the attic that I was just
in? Yeah, I did the attic already. It's whatever bathroom I just was in. I don't fucking know.
This is the bathroom. Bathroom? Where is there another bathroom on this floor? You have a
bathroom in the backyard? No. There's another bathroom. First floor bathroom. Yeah. But how
come this says 11 meters by second power, not 12? Where is it? Oh, okay. Here it is. All right.
Let's go. Bathtub plumbing system. I want to get rid of that. All right. Okay. All right.
Arrange the ceiling tiles. Oh, that's right. You can do ceilings now. Right. That's part of the
update. You can paint ceilings. You can tile ceilings now. Big update. Big deal. All right.
I did it. That's fine. I don't need to do anything else. Goodbye. I just... I'm just trying to unlock
the stuff. I didn't... all that trash. I didn't do that. This dude has no passion in his work.
I'm... you'll... you want to see passion, you'll see it. Just wait. I think I probably unlocked
another house. Okay. Browse for purchase. All right. I just unlocked that house. Should I try
to find another one that's bigger? I think I want a bigger house than that. I want a huge house.
That one looks all right. No. That one looks... this one looks pretty big. I want... okay. This
one's huge. This one's huge. And it's right on the water. Let's... let's... let's get this one.
I need a man-sized house. Actually, this is not that big.
The inspiration has been hitting me pretty hard lately. My creative spark feels kind of
damn great out. Colors, fluffy blankets, and lots of cozy furniture. This is what I truly need.
I always imagined myself in my skelly cutie in a lakeside house with a wooden terrace,
maybe even a small sauna. Somewhere I would be able to flourish as a writer.
But I don't... this is not big enough. I could have different houses for different animals.
And you need a man-sized dinosaur park. This is a huge yard though. Okay. This is a lot of work.
You can change the stairs. I think this is a lot of work. Oh, this is a... this is big though. Yeah,
this is big. This is huge. Look at how big this is. There's a lot of downstairs real estate there.
All right. All right. I think I want this one. I think I want this one. Is it available now,
or do I have to do the mission first? Build this house with spiders. What do you mean I can't have
it? Why not? I wonder if it's unlocked. If I have to do the mission first, that sucks. You have to
clean this whole house. I'm gonna have to clean the house twice. I'm gonna have to clean the whole...
Okay, I'm gonna do speed run it. I'll speed run it. Okay, I'm gonna speed run it. I'm just gonna do
the bare minimum. I want this house. I want this house. All right, here we go. Time to speed run.
Go. Fast. Very fast. Fuck that. I'm just gonna do the... this is gonna take too long. I'm going in.
There's just shit everywhere. I want to be... I'm gonna have a different enclosures for different
animals. Okay, looks good. Let's get the broom out here quick. And then I'm just gonna start
placing objects. Do you want to play the game? That's what I'm doing. I want to just do this
mission real quick. Because here's the thing. I'm gonna buy this house and I'm gonna have to
do this all over again. Don't you understand? I don't want to sit here and just waste time
if I'm gonna have to do the whole thing again anyways. You want this. I wouldn't pick this,
but that's your choice. I'm just trying to fill the progress meter. Uh-huh. Looks good. You want
it in the whole thing, right? All right, beautiful. I wouldn't... I don't know. I wouldn't do this.
Play breakcore. No, it's way too early to do that. It's way too early to start playing breakcore
during the stream. Just keep... you have to wait a few minutes. I need this. It does not matter
where the fuck it goes. I don't care. The dump sink that you want. That's fine. Okay. I'm just
going for completion. Trust me when I say I'm not. This is just to get... so I can get in the house.
I put the cabinets on the ceiling. I'm... trust me. I know people are like, dude, just fucking play,
but I have to do this all over again. I feel like I'm a moving company that just brought all the
shit in here, put it in there, and just left. Wait, I thought... wasn't part of the charge that you
were gonna help me assemble? Nope. It's like if an AI played the game. It does look like that.
It does. The AI just knows it has to do one specific task. That's fucking funny. Whatever.
That progress meter is gonna... this would take like six fucking hours if I were to do this legit.
Don't you want those six hours to be spent making our own house? Not somebody else's? Don't you get
it? What is this? Oh my god. Where... can this go in the other room? It can't go in another room.
Fucking iguana enclosure has to go in here. Oh my goodness. Whatever. I keep running out of room.
You want two of these? Where do you want me to put them? It doesn't matter. It does not matter.
Can I put it... this would have taken so fucking long and you all know it. It's sort of taken
four hours to do all this. You have to trust me on this. Just please trust me. Just please trust me.
Okay? And you want your TV... I don't care where your TV goes. I really don't. All right. Pretty
good. Now I should do the rest of the house. This would have taken me fucking six hours.
Okay. Where's the terrace? Garden. You want me to do all this shit out in the garden? This would have
taken forever. I will spend time on mine. Okay. This is going to get a lot of progress. Yep. That
progress meter is going up. Okay. Terrace. Clean the dirt. Do you sound like a Dr. Seuss book?
What? All right. I need to do... oh this is gonna be nice. Okay. You want these out here. I know
there's puke everywhere. It's fine. We're just going for progress. Again, I would reiterate a
million times if I have to. I want a nice hangout zone out here. Okay. Decorative puke. It kind of...
it does look like decorative puke. You're right. Can you imagine? I thought that cannon just shot
at me. So you hire somebody to come clean and rearrange your whole house and the whole time
they're going, I gotta hurry the fuck up. I gotta clean my house. I gotta take care of my house. I
gotta rearrange my furniture. So they do a half-assed job on your house. That's kind of unfair,
isn't it? Is this the terrace too? That progress needs to go up. Is this helping? Kind of. Okay.
Clean that up. I think we're almost halfway there. Get the spray. Close that up. Looks nice. Good,
good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good. Clean. How much is the progress of the windows
giving me, I wonder? That always feels so good. Nice. Okay. Remove weeds. Only 10%. This is really
dragging the progress down. Yeah, definitely. This shouldn't take too long to get all these.
Yeah, that's definitely filling up fast. Use the flamethrower? I don't even have it. I think this
is slower. This is slower. 70, 80%. Let's go. 97%. 98%. Dirt. Where? Okay. All right. We're good.
There's one here. 99. Just give me the fucking house already. There's a few more windows to clean.
Watch. New basement entrance. Oh, that went away. That's gone. Okay. Well, sorry. You have no access
to your house anymore. Very nice. Okay. Halfway there. Can I not climb in through the window?
You gotta be kidding me. Okay. Here we go. Buy this shit. It's already there. This, this, this
chair, light switch, three of these, six of these candles. Where's the passion? I don't have any
passion for this. I need to get to my house. I don't have, what do you mean? I don't have, why?
I don't have any passion. I have lots of passion for my own space. I'll show it to you. This is
just to get the money to fucking, he's, there's no passion. I will show it to you. You want to see,
I will show you passion. I promise. This is going to be a long stream. So don't worry. It's fine.
I don't know how many they wanted, but that's enough. And then cigars or something. All right.
Here we go. All right. Cool. Look at that progress. Almost done. There's still some trash that needs
to come out of this room. Clean that up. It doesn't matter. All right. Let's go in this room. What do
you want in here? Okay. Here we go. We're good. That's an ugly bed. I'm sorry that that actually,
I think is an ugly bed. See, I don't care about this shit. It's not my house. How are you supposed
to fit all this shit? People put way too much stuff in their bedrooms. You know what you need
in your bedroom? Here's what you need in your bedroom. You need a bed, an end table, a lamp,
and that's it. And maybe draw like this for your clothes. There's too much shit in their bedrooms.
You need maybe like a painting above the bed or something, right? Or like on the wall, like over
here. I don't know. People put way too much shit in their bedroom. Like I don't, I'm sorry. I don't
want this. I don't want a fucking gigantic tropical plant next to me when I sleep. I just don't want
one. I feel like I'm just going to get in the way. I'm going to get annoyed by it. Ceiling fans. I'm
scared of ceiling fans. I feel like I don't want to ceiling people. Oh man, ceiling fans are no.
Ceiling fans. I feel like they're going to spin and drop and kill me and they're going to chop
me up in a thousand pieces. I actually think that when I pull the lever and I see a ceiling fan
spinning, it always freaks me out. I don't like it. I, it's just, I don't know. Sometimes some
ceiling fans aren't really screwed on all the way and they kind of go like this while they spin
really fast. And it's just like, that doesn't look, I want that to be secured with a bolt.
I don't like it. Oh, these are pictures. I was like, what is it on these? That's supposed to
happen. That's not, no, I don't, I don't like it. I don't care if it's supposed to happen or not.
I don't want to be looking straight up at a thing that is going like this spinning really fast
because if I, I'm afraid to close my eyes under that. I don't like it. Something about it freaks
me out. What can I even put this on? What is this supposed to go on? A shelf or something?
Okay. There we go. Okay. Almost done. You want the same carpet everywhere. Two of them. Really?
Why do you want this in your room? This is a swing. You're putting way too much shit in
your bedroom. That your bedroom for me, I mean, that's a place to sleep. You go sleep. I don't
want a bunch of distractions and just shit everywhere. Okay. Almost done. And plus we're
taking down some walls as well. I'm not, this is not the way that I want my house to be. Okay.
What do you want? Paint the ceiling with lime cream. All right. Okay. Mountable oval bathtub.
You want these on the wall? Is that what I'm assuming? Yeah. Okay. Here we go. We're almost
there. Santa's got way more important shit to be doing right now. You guys understand? I think,
you know what's bullshit? We treat Santa like a Madden release. This motherfucker has to prepare
Christmas for just a one year. No, no, no. They should, it should be, Christmas should be every
two years. So Santa has more time to fucking deal with the presents. I think, I don't know. I feel
like he doesn't have enough time. It takes a whole, at least a fucking year to get the shit
ready. Santa's not real. Madden isn't real either. What are you talking about? Start, um, start
timing people off for that. Like, I don't know what the fuck they're talking about. That's annoying
though. Where does this go? Are you sponsored by Santa? No. How dare you say Madden isn't real?
Every new Madden game, is it? What are you talking about? All right. We're almost there.
There it is. Okay. Put it together. Like all the WWE games, all the NBA games, they come out once
a year and come on, Gwen. I'm sad that the court stream never happened. Me too. That joke is long,
long dead though. Unfortunately. Okay. What's going to put it over the edge here? One of the
showers, multiple sink. That's right here. Explain? Um, oh, there's probably a lot of you that don't
know what I'm talking about or what Chad is talking about either. Uh, years ago, um, I killed Santa on
stream. Like, I don't know, it was like 2016 or something, 2017. And the joke was I was going to go
to court for it and get tried for the murder of Santa. And Santa, we were going to have lawyers.
Santa's lawyer was going to sing all the prosecution. I was going to be up, he was going to be cross
examining witnesses and stuff and he was going to be singing the whole thing. Um, at the end,
it was going to be up to you guys if I was guilty or innocent. And the punishment was going to be
the judge was going to smash the gavel down and say, like, I sentenced you to three Minecraft
streams in a row. And he's going to smash the thing and everyone's going to freak out. Everyone's
going to be fucking screaming. Everyone's going to start crying and stuff. Um, and that was going
to be the joke. And I had to play Minecraft three times. There you go. There's the whole thing
because there's just no way it's happening. Like ever guilty. Yeah. Everyone would have said guilty.
There's no way you would have made me innocent. Not even remotely a chance though. Can you just
play Minecraft for real? No, I can't. I don't play. I can't play Minecraft. I can't. I, every time I
play Minecraft, especially if I make a video or stream Minecraft, I do the same thing every time.
I start to build a dirt house. I make a wooden floor. I make a cobblestone wall. The ceiling
is half cobblestone, half dirt with five to 10 holes in it. And then I go dig down and I make
what I'm going to say is I'm going to make a mine down here that connects to the bottom of the house
and then I die at the bottom and I uninstall the game. It happens every single time. I don't think
I've ever gotten past the making a fully cobblestone enclosed house. I don't think
I've ever gotten. I've gotten like iron in my inventory. Do you still consider yourself a
Bostonian? Of course I do, kid. We're so close. And then I can finally start playing. Are those
lights? I don't know. AI controlled placement. It's right there. Come on. One more. Okay. This is
almost done. Here we go. Look at that. One more little tick and that's it. I can probably just do
it by cleaning. Oh hell yeah. Yeah. I can do it by cleaning for sure. Come on. It's right there.
It's so close. Look at it. It's so dirty. It's definitely going to be it, right? Okay. Come on.
Finish. Just finish. Destroy the walls. I knew it was going to be so loud. I just, I barely prepared
for it. I realized what was happening before. There we go. Okay. Which wall do you want me to
break? Build the walls. Okay. I turned this house into a hidden object game. They didn't even want
to show you the living room. That's too bad. You should play a hidden object game. I have. Okay.
Are you ready? Let's go. Here it is. Our cozy haven. Let's buy it. And I want to go there
right now. Hey, remember all this shit that I just did? Hope you're ready to see it again.
Why does my camera lag every time? All right. Actually, this is going to go much faster. What?
I have to buy a new one? That was so much faster. That was so much faster. I'm so glad that I can
do that. He's looking for a spy. Where is he? And I fly fucking forward. He backstabs me after all
this bullshit. I finally like get fucking stabbed. Have you seen the save TF2 thing? A little bit.
A little bit. I'll give my take on it. I would love to see valve. The thing about TF2 is TF2
is an old game, right? But if there are official valve servers, if you're going to keep official
servers turned on, I think that they need to support the game somehow, right? And if there
are official valve servers, valve servers, that means that they're still officially technically
supporting the game. I would like to see some more updates to TF2. Forget about bug fixes or
problems with the game or whatever, right? But I would really like to see them at least sometimes
go in and just kind of fiddle with some knobs, right? That would be great. I don't know. I don't
know. What is valve doing now? What is valve up to? What's like in the pipeline for valve?
Steam Deck? The game's currently unplayable right now. Yeah, I just think they kind of need to do
something, right? So, I mean, I support anything to get and I love that game. I think the game's
as one as literally the reason why I'm sitting in this chair is because of that game. So absolutely,
I support them coming in and fixing some of the problems that the game has, especially if they're
going to officially support it. But on top of that, I would, like I said, I'd like to see at
least something else or even, I mean, it's so easy to sit here and be like, I would love to do this.
They should do this. I want the pirate to do this. I want the heavy to get this. But even just small
little fixes just to support the game. Will they do anything? I don't know. I don't know. I can't
say that I would expect them to do very much, but it would be nice if they tried to do something
with the game. But I don't think Valve is really in the business of video game making anymore.
Video game stuff. They're more hardware related and business related. Steam and their hardware
shit is, I think, when almost all their focus is completely 100%. I don't know if that's going to
change. I mean, obviously they're doing really, really well. Steam is the platform for pretty
much everything. So I don't know if they're ever going to get back into trying to do game stuff.
Will they actually come out with something besides? I mean, Alex came out a couple of years ago,
right? But I don't know. The games that they have currently that they kind of are operating as a
service in a way. I mean, like Counter, they still, what about like CSGO? Dota 2 still gets updates.
CSGO still gets updates, right? Doesn't, like, CSGO, yeah. Dota 2 is still really supported.
Yeah, I really do hope that they can at least support the games that they officially have,
especially official servers for. I guess that's take on it, I guess. I mean, I love that game.
I love everything about it. That's the huge reason why I am in the position I'm in today,
because I decided to make TF2 videos fucking 10 years ago. Without those games, I don't think I
would be sitting here. I really don't think so. Whatever happens, happens, I guess. And I guess
hopefully they can come up with some kind of solution as I burn this whole fucking place to
the ground. It should just let the game die. I mean, the hard part with that is if they want
to just turn it off, then okay, turn it off then, right? If you want to turn the game off,
and that's it, we're not supporting servers anymore, then at least give some closure to everybody.
As much as I don't want to see that happen, right? It's almost like, give us some closure.
Give everybody closure. And oh, hey, look, we're not doing official supported servers anymore.
We're our focus is in other places. But by all means, if you want to run community servers,
blah, blah, blah, right? But if you want to pull the plug officially on it, then you got to do it.
Like, well, closure for what? Closure just for, I think people expect, or not expect, but people
really want them to be involved, to help and do things and fix things and stuff. But if they
don't want to, and there's been no real, I guess, communication to do so, then I don't know, right?
Like, I don't know what their plans or goals are long term, but we'll see. TF2 is the blueprint.
You've been walking in circles for 10 minutes. Yeah, go watch my Minecraft video. My Minecraft
videos where I went like this and talked about like what happened at my house today. I literally
went like this before, I think three or four hours going like this. And when it was brought
to my attention, I was going to, I think I was going to delete the video because I was embarrassed.
I was like, holy fuck, what am I doing? I remember MLC Stealth told me long time ago, he said, dude,
I watched your Minecraft video and you built and took down the same wall for about 12 minutes
straight. It was, you did it like 15 times. So I just, my brain just gets, when I have talking,
I can't fucking do anything. All right, let's go. I don't want to buy any, I'm going to buy shit
little fuel, but I will leave you with this. I do not really play TF2 anymore. I don't, I'm not really,
I'm not into it anymore, but if you are, then I really hope that some kind of solution can happen
because it's a great game. It's a fucking fantastic game. It's one of the best FPSs to ever release.
So time for Smite Sundays. Time for Omega Lull Overwatch Wednesdays. No, I'm not, I'm, no.
Think of all the bugs in the grass you are killing right now. I'm just trying to get to square one.
Bug killer. Oh, stop. I'm not, I'm not killing bugs. I checked, I checked before I started
because there's going to be, it's going to be stuff out here, animal stuff. I got, it's got to be clean.
Holy shit. That hurt my chest. That's good enough for now. All right, let's clean. Hey, I, come on.
I was the, I was the master at being able to fake sick so I didn't have to go to school.
I feel, I just like feel terrible. Oh fuck. Oh, you don't feel good? No, I can't go to school.
You said fuck to your mom. No, I'm just saying I was, oh fuck. Oh fucking. So as you see here,
this theory of the triangle and the circle, the Pythagorean theorem is fucking, it's got the angle
in the middle here you had to solve for that is. Remember that joke? That was a good one.
I'm going to put new windows on. Don't worry. I need to clean. I remember that. Yeah. So I don't
have any more water. Where's the, where's my water? Where's, where's water? Excuse me. This,
I got to change this outside as well. You should play that. Play where's my water. What are you
fucking an iPad gamer from 2012? What are you talking about? Play iPad games. You know what
I wanted to do? I wanted to watch a shitload of mobile ads, but we're going to have to do that
in really small doses because they are insane. I don't think we could do that for three hours.
I think we would all have, it would make us sick as an avid iPad game connoisseur. Let me tell you
that some of the most ridiculous, insane bullshit that I've ever seen in my whole life happened
while I was watching an iPad game ad or a phone ad. You want to talk about a computer generating
random shit? This is it. But some of them are so goddamn funny. They're so funny that I think it
deserves a stream night. Okay. I always get it. What's that? Oh, that's a bugs. Didn't I just
burn this whole room? I thought I burnt this room. Why is there blood? I don't think it's blood.
I think it's rust or something. All right. This looks fine. I'm now look, I'd look at the passion
here. You see, see the passion here. There's no natural light. I'm going to put windows in.
First of all. Nope. Don't want one of those in the house. Front door. Okay. This is the front door.
Well, that's the side door. Yeah. All of this wood needs to change. Yeah. This all this looks
artable ceiling fan phobia. I really do with that. They're weird. I don't really don't like them.
They're weird. No, we're doing it from scratch. We're building this house from scratch. All right.
How do I want this to play out here? Let's pray. All right. Take all these walls down.
We're building the house from scratch. Where's the dog? I think at the other house.
Holy shit. That was inside of my head. This is a load bearing wall.
Jerry. These are load bearing walls. Whoa. Have you doing a Seinfeld thing where they build a
house or something? I feel like that. Wait, didn't this happen in Drake and Josh? No,
it's a load bearing wall, Josh. How was I supposed to? They really are Jerry and fucking George.
What the fuck? I'm just realizing this right now. How was I supposed to know that a door was
supposed to be there, Josh? No, other one. Other way around. There's supposed to be a door over
there. That's George. Holy shit. Damn. Okay. He knows too much. I want another Seinfeld episode.
You know what I was thinking? In a hundred years, will I know that, okay, like media has a tendency
to kind of repeat itself, right? Are we going to see in 50 to a hundred years, just Seinfeld,
but it's they just kind of redoing it. Will there be a Breaking Bad remake in 50 years?
Do you think so? I wonder. I'm actually genuinely curious about that. All the most popular media
right now, will they redo it? I mean, Seinfeld ended 20 years ago though. I think, I don't know.
Maybe like another 50 years, but would they call it Seinfeld and just have some guy that's not
Jerry Seinfeld just be pretending to be Jerry Seinfeld. They're just going to call it Jerry.
Okay. I want this. I want, trust me when I say, why are you taking all the rooms out? I'm not.
When are you going to get remade? See, I'm a, well, see I'm doing all of Jim Carrey's
sound effects. So like I already am a remake. You know what I mean? Like I am essentially a three
stoge stooges. Why can't I, I can't talk when loud sounds are exploding in my head. I mean,
I'm sort of, I am like one of the stooges or all of them combined maybe. Sometimes I feel like Moa.
Sometimes I feel like, like, not Gary, Curly. Sometimes I wake up and feel like one of the
stooges each day. Each day. I prefer, I prefer the remake. You're the fourth stooges. Okay. So
let's get rid of this. I need some light in here because this is what, where even am I?
Where's the door? Oh no. Drake, you forgot to put the door on. Where, actually, where's the door?
Oh, I fucking deleted it. Right. I forgot. Where are the stairs? Where is there a door? Okay. This
is temporary. Where did it go? Oh, what? What the fuck just happened? Oh my goodness. Somebody
punched me in the face. I got punched in the face. Why is it fucking Walgreens now?
All right. Just whatever. I am very, very stunned right now. That just stunned me. That was, that
actually stunned me. I hope everyone's all right. Let's get some lights in here. Jesus. What the
fuck? Why is caps lock on? Oh, okay. I just need a light. Pools? No. What the fuck is this? Stop.
I'm concussed. Here we go. Just temporary. Just to get light in here. Where's the light switch?
Turn it on. There we go. Now I can see. All right. Let's get, let's keep going. I don't know where I
want the bathrooms yet. We'll get that figured out. Relax. I am getting blocked by this, aren't I?
It's all right. All right. I hope this doesn't explode anymore. Okay. I cannot take this wall
down. This is, this is a load bearing wall. You're ruining your house. I am not even beginning it.
I have not even started. Okay. Good beginning. Um, clean. Let's get this situated. Clean this shit
up. Let's make this look like, uh, less of a haunted house and more of a animal sanctuary.
Animal, uh, foster home or something, right? Or to that. Okay. Get rid of that and get rid of this
and get rid of these. I don't want that. All right. What? This is down to the other floor. Okay.
We're going to keep, should we get the bugs downstairs? I want, where should the bugs be?
Where should I put all the bugs? All right. We'll do the bugs later. First of all, I need a bedroom.
So we're going to have the bedroom be, this is the front door. Is this the front door? Where the hell
am I? This is the, okay. This is where the front door is supposed to be. Right here. I'll take care
of that right now. Turn your, turn your sound down. Same shit's going to happen. Turn your sound down.
I mean it. Thank God I did that. Thank God. That was almost a disaster. There's the front door.
It's temporary. Don't worry. Everyone calling me a shitty front door Andy. I've seen those comments
and I, this is greasy. I can't fix it. That's really greasy. Is it still greasy? This shit is
greasy. All right. Let's clean. I know. Every time these steaks, they're not greasy. And just
right when you go to the pizza shop, be careful. The pizza's greasy. How fast can you do that?
Fuck out of here. No one can compare. Not one person. Dominate that market. Okay. Let's do it.
I need to figure out where I want to put my room. There's no upstairs. I think my, so this is the
front door. That's the, technically the back door. That could be like a little living room area. This
front door. You come in, maybe like right over here. I'm going to say I want my bedroom to be
right here. Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, right here. Yeah. I think that's a good
idea. So let's say from here we can, I don't know, we can just put like a fucking weird clock here or
something, right? This is the front door. I don't, okay. This is the front door. Bedroom is going to
be right here. Right here. That looks good to me. Right there. Make a little hallway. Shut up. I'm
working on it. So you come in. This is a little hallway. There'll be a little, uh, maybe a closet
right here. Um, but should I have the bed, yeah, the bedroom entrance be here or right here? I feel
like the door being right there would be weird, wouldn't it? This is kind of a hallway. Then this
can be the entrance right here. Yeah. I think that makes more sense. Yeah, that makes more sense.
Looks good. Put a window in there. Yeah, I will. This is fine for a bedroom. Look, I didn't, I just
need to sleep and wake up and have a light and have like a painting and that's it. I don't care
about anything else. I need a bedroom door. Ooh. What's a decent door for the bedroom? These
refrigerators? Okay. This is fine. What color should the door be? Um, how about like a beige?
Maybe like a birch? These are front doors. Oh my God. Does it really matter though? Luxury? Pets.
These are the new ones. Let's get some new ones. Okay. Interior door. Here you go. This one looks
fine. Maybe like a nice, um, like a nice cedar. Yeah, that's fine. Okay. Uh, please. Thank you.
Looks good. Now we have to build the little things up here. This game is so relaxing. Where's the
passion? I, you don't see the passion in my voice right here. I'm working on it. This is just,
I want a ton of room for the animals. No window. Yeah. God, I get it. I got to be at lightning
speed apparently. Where's the bed going to go? We'll do like one here and one. Okay. There's the
window. Put two windows in here. There it is. Nice. All right. That looks fine. The walls aren't
going to look like this. Don't worry. In fact, let's figure that out now. Let me get some good,
good, good lighting, lights. Although I should probably have some cool stuff in here. Why are
the walls two feet thick? Because that's the way they made the game. Okay. I didn't do that.
Should I have some weird shit? Oh, this thing look cool. That's fine. Get a dog. I need to
have this place be available. I need to be okay to have a dog or a cat or a rabbit or a horse
or a tarantula or an iguana. I'm not just going to bring them in here. It's dangerous.
It's really off center. I just need the light. All right. Floor. Carpet. Definitely carpets.
Ooh. How's this look? Looks nice. I like carpets. I like carpets up in a bedroom. I like carpets down
in the bedroom. I like in a bedroom. I don't know how many times I have to say that for you to get
it. It's comfortable. It feels nice on your feet. It gets really nice and warm and stuff. I don't
get this carpet hatred that everybody seems to have. All right. Walls. What do I want this to be?
I don't care. My bedroom is small. I want more room for the animals. Yeah. Really? I'm not going
to do that. Cool. But wait. Check this out. People are going to be very... No. I'm not going to burn
it down. He's making a pet sanctuary. That's what I'm doing. That's the pet DLC. Of course,
I'm going to make a big pet sanctuary. What do you got? Do you mind? Here's the design.
This is where the design comes in. Watch this. Check this out, everybody. Okay. Watch this.
Here we go. There we go. Now it looks like an old Nickelodeon ad. It doesn't work. Oh, I hate it.
Just an accent wall. Okay. I'll do... Yeah. Something else. I hate it. Let's do paint.
We'll keep that as the accent wall, though. What should I paint it? Crystal? The Milky Way?
Let's try the Milky Way. Is it ugly? Too plain? It's a little too plain. Yeah, too plain. I don't
want to go too crazy, though. How about morning celadon? Fresh morning. Fresh morning would
probably be good here. Let's test it. I like it. I think it goes with the accent. Oh, yeah,
this will work fine. Yeah, for sure. It's the same thing. It's not the same thing. That's not...
Look at it under the light. That's not the same thing. This is way nicer. I am a shadow in the
dark, okay? I need to... Hold on a second. Hi. You can see me again. This is different and it
looks much better. There we go. All right. Yeah. Much, much better. It's just gray. I'm going to
change the carpet, so it's not so boring, but I'm very boring. I swear to God. People think I
might be making this up. Like, oh man, I bet you he has really crazy taste. I bet you have wicked
expensive taste and shit. He probably has a chandelier in his house. Guys, I would be so
happy. At my most happiness. Just sitting in a bedroom that just has a bed, a table, and a lamp
on it. I don't care. That's at my most happy. I don't want a bunch of shit in the way. I don't
want a bunch of stuff everywhere. All I need is, yeah, I need my iPad sitting here on my chest,
a bed, a light, and good company. This door looks like shit. You're an iPad kid. No, I'm not an iPad
kid. Sometimes Holly will take a funny picture because I fall asleep a lot when I'm with my iPad
on my chest. In the pictures I'm about to show you, I am asleep. Asleep. One of these in particular
is really funny. This happens all the fucking time. I just sit there. I have this little thing
that sits on my chest. Let's go through a couple of these. Maybe one or two of them. Okay, hold on.
Let me make sure I can get this on the screen. So this is a picture of me. This is the kind,
I don't know what I was even watching. Auto play just takes over, guys. A lot of the time. Okay,
that's me asleep. Be aware of that. I am asleep. And apparently I'm watching free money to quit
your job. I don't know where this came from. Getting rich on government money. I was sleeping.
It gets better though. It does get better. I promise that this does get a little better,
and I'm going to show you another one. Don't be, don't, nobody freak out about this, okay?
But I just have, it's too funny to not show. It really is too funny to not show this. This is,
and I, I just fall asleep to stuff and I watch stuff. It could be anything. There's more.
There's more. There's more of these. There's one of, here's the other one. I think this is from the
same video, but it's just funny. Guys, I'm telling you, I will fall asleep to shit and just, it'll be
on for six hours and I'll, I will absorb it. I've fallen asleep to six hours. I, oh my God,
what a perfect opportunity to talk about this. So today, what I fell asleep to as an iPad kid Andy,
I fell asleep to, I don't know, was a food eating video? One of those videos of people eating food
and I, I guess I fell asleep and I woke, I kind of woke up because Otto was in the bed and I heard
like crunching shit and I'm like, Otto's eating something. What's he eating? No, he's not. What's
he getting into? And I open my eyes and look at the dog and he's fine. He's just sitting there sleeping
and the audio stopped. There were no more eating sounds. So I was like, what the fuck was that? I
must've been having like a weird dream. So I didn't care and I went back to bed and I heard it again.
I heard this crazy eating sounds and I'm like, Otto's getting into like the trash.
What's happening? And no, it was over here. The iPad was on the other end of the bed,
just Otto playing shit. And I kept thinking it was Otto eating food in the bed. It had to have been
going on for at least four or five hours because it was dark when it happened the first time and
the sun was shining the second time. I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me. I don't know what
I, what's, I don't know why I keep doing this, but it doesn't matter. It could be anything.
The YouTube recommendation autoplay is terrible. Here's another one. We'll do this last one.
I think this is from the quit your job for money thing. By the way, if you want to know who that
is, that's, that's Matthew Lesko, who he's actually like a really, really nice guy. Really, really
like awesome, awesome dude. Really just wanted to like help people and shit. He is a great person.
That little documentary that Vice did is wonderful. I really recommend you watch it. I've seen it.
I didn't fall asleep to it. I've seen it. It's he's actually, it was actually a really,
really good guy. All right. You have broken neck. No, I don't. I'm propped up on a pillow.
I'm propped up on a pillow, man. I'm, that's not a TV. There's an iPad. You have streamer neck in
your sleep. Sometimes though that's dangerous because I will be like this and I'll move a
certain way and the iPad will go and start falling down and I'll feel it. And I'll be like,
I'll grab it and okay. And then I leave it there and I go back to bed. It's move it. Just move it
off of your fucking body. I do that three or four times a night. I almost get smashed in the mouth
by my iPad and I don't care. I put it right back where it was. One of these days it's going to
knock out one of my front teeth. Anyways, this is too funny. I could, I had to share it.
Ceiling is still wood. I'm working on it. Okay. So it's, is this real? Is this a,
Holly? Is this real? Is this a real one? Is this real? I don't think this is,
did I fall asleep to this? I might've. I don't know. I really don't know. I don't know.
I truly don't know. Why is this image so huge? What the fuck? Where is it? I'm so confused.
Oh, there we go. Okay. I may, I might've, I actually might've. This is, this could be a real
photo. I really probably did. Oh, it's not real. It could be. I, I, it actually could be. This is
no way. That's edited. It's fake. Okay. But it's definitely real because I've definitely
fallen asleep to watching that video. I'm not even kidding. Like I sometimes it was like eating
videos and he's like, watch one. I go, whoa, what this, whoa. And then I just,
and they all play. It's real. I'm serious. I don't know. I, I'm very weird when it comes to media
and consuming media. A lot of people probably like, dude, what the fuck? Why are you doing that?
What's wrong with you? I don't know. I like watching odd media, just like interesting stuff.
I don't watch TV shows. I watched four straight hours of ASMR eating videos. I don't, I just,
because, because it's interesting. It's very, it's fascinating. It's interesting to me.
It's interesting. I will watch like four hours of log cutting videos. It's just, it's fascinating
somehow. It's very interesting. You know what I'm saying? It's ADHD that's doing it. It probably,
it could be. It actually could be. All right. Can I paint the ceiling please? I think it can
just be this. This is fine. Now you could paint a wall. Good. Is this the wrong color? No. Is
this too weird looking? I can't tell. I love doing interior car cleaning videos. Yeah. You
don't have to watch, you know, oh, the new season of Breaking Bad or whatever. We're just,
I like watching random shit. I will watch old commercials. It's interesting. Really old
commercials. I'm happy with this room. I'm done with it. Okay. Now I need a bathroom,
which would be right here. You missed a spot. I can go to finishing touches later. Bathroom
can be here. Ooh, the door is going to be close, isn't it? It's fine. Change the weird door.
It is a fucking weird door. I know you're right. That is a weird door. Maybe I could just have
like an open concept here. It's probably, it's got to be here instead. Right there. There it is.
Okay. So the bathroom's right here. Open concept into a bedroom. I don't know. It's just going to
be, it's going to be me and all my dogs and lizards and shit. I think right, right there
should be fine. That should be fine right here, I think. What does your YouTube recommended look
like? It's a, it's crazy. I actually have to go in and delete all of my search history and watch
history because eventually it gets to be fucking nightmares. It's just crazy, the recommendations
I get. If I don't reset it, it's just all over the place. Just wild, wild shit from every genre.
YouTube is fundamentally broken. Show us your YouTube. I'm not, you want to see my YouTube
searches? Let me screen that first. I'll screen that first. Show us. I don't have to show you
anything. You need to show us right now. No, I don't have to show you. I don't, I don't know.
I don't know if you guys know what videos I've watched. It's freaking me out because I'm not
embarrassed by like something weird showing up. I'm embarrassed by the volume of eating videos
that are going to be there. And I, that's kind of, I don't, I don't know if I like that. The volume
of like people eating or like drinking liquids really fast. It's going to be, it's going to be
predominantly there. I'm done. I'm done. Thanks for participating. We're going to move on.
We won't judge you. Oh, please. That's, you guys are in the game. You guys are in the business
of judging me. You guys, that's what you are here for. That's, you are in the business of judging me,
especially with things like this. Maybe I'll do it. I'll go look and see if it's like weird.
Not today though. Maybe like on Friday. Nah, give me a new door because I have to get my
iPads like not fucking, no, my iPads are not even charged. It's no, not going to happen. You'll see
maybe on Friday. If I, you know, decided to do that. Nothing to hide, nothing to fear. We'll see
on Friday. We'll, we'll see if I do it. I'm watching this on my iPad. No, you're just going
to watch normal videos on Thursday. You will know if it's full of shit, if it's regular ass videos.
Okay. I just told you the, all the fucking stuff that I watch. And if on Friday I'm like, hey,
take a look at my YouTube recommended. Yeah, it's normal. See, it's like, oh, how to build a
birdhouse and, oh, top 10 Marvel characters who you could be like, you're going to be like full of
shit. You guys know what I was looking at. So I can't hide that. Yeah. If my recommended is like,
but I don't know why you'd even want this. Oh, the end of far from home explained.
You would know that I, I'm full of shit. There's going to be a lot of infomercials. Do liked videos.
I don't, I don't do that. I just let the automatic recommend to just throw up into my face. I don't
do, I don't like videos. I don't save them. I don't bookmark them. I just watch. I just pick
a random one and just go and just go for like four hours. I've never liked a video. I don't think
since like, maybe like, I don't know. God damn fucking decade ago. I have no idea. I don't think
I even did. He hates videos. I don't, I just don't. Okay. Please, we need to get a door in here.
You're fucking with me. It's going to be like Kathy Mitchell, Express 101, Kathy Mitchell,
the turbo cooker, Kathy Mitchell, the snack master, Kathy Mitchell, infomercial,
Kathy Murch Mitchell, infomercial, long version. I swear Kathy Mitchell, DVD turbo cooker,
because it was like three hours and it's her just doing recipes for the turbo cooker.
It's not the infomercial. They go, I just read you the last, I read you the last six. I'm never
going to get this house done. Thanks a lot. All right. These, these doors were too weird.
So give me a normal one. Just a regular interior door. Just a regular ass door. Just a regular
interior. There's a ton of stuff in mod chat right now. Oh God. I'm never going to finish
this house. I don't know. Why am I, what is this from? What the fuck is this? When did I do this?
Huh? Why am I naked? When did I do that? What the fuck is this? What is this from? Why am I nude?
Why would I be watching this? I don't know. Somebody said, why are your nipples so high?
I need to investigate. Hold on. I need to investigate this. I need this to be investigated.
This is so confusing. Yeah. What the fuck? Like up here. That doesn't look right. That doesn't look
right. Where's your mic? Dude, I, uh, look at how, oh my God. Why would I be watching this?
There's so many of these. I will never be able to get through them. No. All right. You, you know,
go to the, the, the sub stream is doing a whole lot of shit. Go check it out. It's funny. There's
going to be watching baby sensory videos. Me watching what I am that. I'm assuming it's like
porn or something. There's me watching this stream. Top 10 son. No, I don't, I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's go. Let's go. I'm out.
That was a lot of fun. Thanks for participating. I don't care. It doesn't matter what this door is.
I don't care. Let me just finish the fucking house already. I knocked down five walls. Stop
you. Bring me back to my Minecraft days. It's been three hours. I'll fix it later. I need to
put animals in here. This is a mouth like you want. This is the one everyone's talking about.
I don't why would I be fucking watching this? You don't have to show it. Oh God. No. All right.
I'm knocking this wall down right now and nothing's going to stop me. Nothing's going to stop me.
I'm knocking this wall down. Nothing is going to stop me. I'm a 36 year old man. Let's relax.
I'm a 36 year old man. It's time for you to start acting like one. That was so loud. Why is it? Why
did this get louder? How did this get even louder? I don't know how that got so loud. Okay. So let's
continue. This is going to be the bathroom very quickly, very quickly. Let's get it done. Let's
get it done. Bathroom right here. It's fine. It doesn't need to be big. I just need it to exist.
I don't care. I'm not going to watch the video right now. Give it a rest. Okay. This goes to the
bedroom. This is going to go to the bathroom right here. There it is. Excellent. Looking good. It's
a small bathroom, but it doesn't need to be large. This needs to be small enough, big enough to
go in there and do whatever you need to do. And then here we go. This is where the iguana
is going to live. The doors can be replaced later. I don't care if they're ugly. They just have to
exist. I don't care. Oh, my eyes are so irritated. Why are my eyes so irritated? There's just a lot
of irritation right now. It's good. Yeah, it looks fine. All right. Speaking of in the bathroom,
my eyes are so itchy. All right. I need floors. We'll do the walls first. Well, it's a nice
bathroom one. How about, I don't know, green? Let's go. Let's get wild with it. Let's get wild
with it, right? Why not? Should we get wild with it? Green? Let's get wild with it. All right. This
is some Wizard of Oz munchkin land shit. Should I leave it? Oh, Emerald City. That's what I was
thinking of. Well, wasn't it munchkin land as well? It was all that green, wasn't it? Emerald City,
not munchkin land. It's a Yoda bathroom. I think it should be. If I put this, whatever,
I'm sticking with it. I second guess too much. Okay. We need some, you know what I'm saying?
We need, we need floors. Floor and ceiling tiles. How about this one? I've got to brighten it up a
little. Okay. Let's make this a little nicer looking. The ceiling should be, let's just make
it white. Put some nice lights in here too. Okay. Get rid of that. We need some nice bathroom
lights. It's a green screen room. Lights. Something nice. Something really nice. Really brighten it
up too. I need something to brighten it up. I actually, these would be all right. These are
nice and clean. Yeah. These are clean. Yeah. These are clean. Those are clean. There are no fire
escapes. Just wait. Why? What do you mean fire escape? Oh dude, our jacuzzi is definitely going
back there somewhere. I don't know. No windows in the bathroom. No. I don't want that. Zero. No
windows in my fucking bathroom. I don't want a window in the bathroom. What? So the window
in the curtains can be closed permanently and never ever opened ever for any reason ever.
Never opened. Why would I want a bathroom window? What are you talking about? Ever. You want me to
put a window here for it to permanently be closed and never have the curtains opened ever. I don't
like that. I don't like that. Maybe you'd get a frosted window. They have them. They don't have
frosted windows. Yeah. No. Fuck that. Fuck this. Yeah. Fuck this. Why would you want a window here?
I don't want a window in my bathroom. Loud. Careful. Yeah. I don't like that. I don't like
this shit, but whatever. Get some air in here. Why is my eye so itchy? It's fucking making me
mad. Am I like, I have allergies or something? What's going on here? This feels like a room on
a spaceship or something, but whatever. It's like an escape pod. All right. I got my window. I need
my installations for the bathroom. Okay. Bathroom. I want toilet plumbing system. Toilet is going to
go right. Okay. I also want a shower. Yeah. No bathtub. Shower plumbing system. Shower can be
in the corner over here. Can I not move it up? There we go. All right. That's fine. Let's go.
No bathtub. I don't need a bathtub. Did you actually put lemon juice in your eye?
Where'd I get the lemon juice from? This is kind of lemony. It's kind of lemony. Okay. Shower.
Say it with me now. Oh, none of you are fucking going to do it. That's surprising. Okay. There's
the shower. That looks fine. Let's watch out for the door. What is this? Oh, a toilet needs to go
here. Toilet. Okay. Suspended toilet. I was like, what? I was like, is this a toilet? Standing toilet
paper. All right. How about this one? Now I just need a sink. I need some toilet paper there. See?
Okay. Now I need to sink and a mirror and a painting. I need a weight. I need a mountable
sink. Right there. Why am I so itchy? Rotate the shower. You can do that in your game. All right.
I need a mountable sink. Oh, I like that. I like this one. I like that kind of basin style. The
water always comes out of these really cool. Let me see if I can describe. You know what I mean?
When it's like, it's this weird, there's no bubbles in the water. It's just this really see-through
stream. Do you know what I'm talking about? When you turn on a faucet and it goes,
it's called laminar flow. Yeah. What is that called? Cause I want it. Laminar flow. Okay.
I want that. I love that so much. It's like my favorite thing in the world.
There are microplastics in it. I don't have one. There are microplastics all over your body right
now. We'll get them off. I don't want them on me. Put a trash can in here. Yep. This looks fine.
There. Now I just need a painting. I need a bathroom painting. Like a lemon. I just need a lemon.
Something lemony. Something lemony. That's kind of lemony. That one was the most lemony, I think.
This one looks pretty lemony, I think. This one is way too fucking big. Why are these so huge?
Okay. Now I need a mirror. Just a basic one. Oh, all right. I like that. Bigger than that,
though. Is that too high? Is that too low? Okay. That's fine. Look at that. The bathroom is done
and it's a beautiful one. I need a little rug. This one's a lemony. Oh, and I don't know anything
about design. I don't know anything about how the world works. Look at that. Take a look. That's a
nice bathroom. It's fine. There's nothing wrong with it. Oh, but you need to rotate the shower
and start banning them. Okay. So that's cool. Now we can start to think about where I want
the animals to be. Here's the front door. Okay. Front door. Coming in here. What do I want the
painting on the walls to be? And is there going to be another room? I think so. All right. Yeah.
Watch. Let's get rid of this. That's the bathroom. This is the bedroom. And then I need, this will
be a nice enclosure here. Right here. I can maybe do some fish tanks and shit. I am so ready. This
is going to be so fun. Are you guys ready? It's going to be so fun. It's going to be so cool.
Okay. So the wall should be there. Just we'll go straight across from here to there. What's wrong?
And my axe and my bow. And my axe and my bow. Activate sleeper agent. Code onion ring.
Whatever. Okay. I need the walls again. Onion ring. It's actually kind of fun and funny that
I will, I will spend hundreds of thousands of dollars on shows. And the biggest memes that come
out of these, this channel is like, I found an onion ring in my French fries. And I'm the guy
from the Among Us guy. I'm the serial killer AI guy. That's so funny. They're uneven. What do you,
I'm fixing it right now, but they have to be uneven because I want it to be flush to the door
here. It doesn't have to be flush to the door. Okay. That's actually annoying. It can be flush
with this. So whatever. So this now can go here because I want this to be the wall. This is going
to be our first enclosure. Here we go. Let's go. Here we go. Let's do it. All right. So what should
I put in here? I'm wondering, what do you guys think? I need lights. First of all, chickens.
What can you actually put in here? I just want a lamp. There's a cat treadmill. I just want lights,
ceiling lamps, just something basic for now. I can play with it later. Just basic, basic,
just to get light in here. It doesn't have to be exact. Everyone's going to be pissed that they're
not lined up correctly. It's just to get light in here. Okay. So this is animal room one. Let's
see what I want to do here. Pets. Wellen freshwater aquarium. Snake terrarium. Should
I do some snakes? What should be up here? Birds? Hamsters? Just do a bunch of reptiles. Spider
terrarium. Spiders will go downstairs. Okay. Let's do a bunch of iguanas and lizards. All right. Let's
do lizards. This thing is huge. This thing is actually too big. No, it's not. All right. Here's
our iguana terrarium. It fits perfectly in this spot. I can put some little decorations around it.
Nice. Okay. Buy two to fill the wall. I don't think two will fit. All right. Now we can do
like a snake and a snake. What are the small reptiles going to do? Do aquarium. What about,
yeah, snakes maybe. Oh yeah. We can do four. All right. Let me put this on a counter. Is it like
a table or a counter or something that I can build it on top of? Do a turtle. Well, let's do snakes
over here and then turtles over there. I don't even do I have access to a snake? Or am I access
to a turtle? Hamster? Where's turtle? Turtle's not here. Oh, there we go. Okay. How big is this?
All right. This is huge. It can just, I think, can it just sit on the ground, right? It can just
sit there, right? That's fine. Should I just do two turtles or should I do two snakes over here?
Turtle, iguana, and two snakes. You look like a fish. Yeah, whatever. I'll do two snakes,
but I need to be up off the ground. What is it? Because my mouth goes like this? Because my mouth
goes like that. My lips. I have like these, I have like a fish mouth. Yeah. You don't think I know
that? You don't think I know I have like a mouth that like goes like too far this way? You don't
think I've ever seen that before? You don't think I've never looked at that before? I can breathe
underwater. You can't. What if I just lifted up my like neck over here and it was just gills? Just
like bing bing bing bing bing. Okay, Jim Carrey, settle down. Okay, I need a counter. This is
probably big enough, right? I don't want it to be like that though. Here we go. I think that's fine.
Yeah, that's like kind of snake themed, isn't it? I need a longer than that. There's a shorter one,
right? Look at that. Perfect. Can I fit two? I can. No, I can't. Yes, I can. There we go.
Okay, we got two snakes. I got a turtle and an iguana. Pretty cool. All right. Now what?
Let's do this while I'm here. This room needs to be a little bit more inviting too. What should be
what should go on the ground? I don't know what to put on the ground. Put a snake skin rug on the
ground. Excuse me? All right, I need to do um the walls are just so awful looking. Oh, let's go back
to pets. What else is here? There's no bunnies in here. Don't do that. What is this? Holy shit.
How do I get out of here? I'm stuck here. That's going right here. Oh my god. That's so annoyingly
large. Where? How? What are you supposed to do with this? What are you actually supposed to do
with this? Why is this floating? Oh, it goes against the corner. Okay, what's what does this
go to? Oh, fuck it. Whatever. I don't care. What does this go to? It's the bathroom shit. Um,
we can go over here. That works. What is that? It is a cat aggro crag. It's the bedroom. I'll do
that later. Bathroom is fine. All right, here's the let's go back in here. Take care of this.
I need to do this. Where do you eat? I'll make a little kitchenette over here. Kitchenette can
exist over there. I think it should be fine. I got three hundred thirteen thousand bucks. I'm fine.
Get rid of this too. I don't want this. Here's the back entrance. We're going to do a little
we're going to do a huge patio here and there's going to be a ton of play areas for the dogs,
the cats. Just let me how much does it cost to buy like 40 animals? Is it more than three hundred
thousand dollars? It's probably a lot. Yeah, it's probably a lot. We're going to find out
if I need to go sell the other house. I will. Okay, back to this room is the reptile den.
I'm going to think of the night if the reptile den is going to be green. It's going to be green,
light green, dark green on the floor. Yeah. Oh, that's kind of cool. It could be green,
green and brown. Let's just do some paint. Yeah, something like this. Strong green maybe for the
see for the walls. Now that's too dark. Here we go. How about like spring grass or ripe hair?
We'll try spring grass. I feel like this is going to be it. My god, my eyeball is going to fall out
of my head. Let's do a sample. I mean, it's the reptile room. That's what's happening. This is
the reptile room. You spoke too much. No, I did not. I like that. That's cute. I can put some
paintings up. We will dress it up a little bit so it doesn't look so plain. It's too light. We'll
dress it up. Don't worry. No one's going to see this wall, so who cares? It's good. Paint it.
Landlord special. Don't paint behind the furniture. I don't know. I feel like if I was a landlord,
I feel like I would be constantly just, is everything okay over there? Things going good?
Something break? Does something need fixing? I would want it to be like really good over there.
I don't understand that concept. I would be so concerned that you can't tell if this doesn't
look good. If I was like, hey, my sink is broken and I need someone to come fix it. I'd be like,
you stay right there. I'll be over in five minutes and I get out of my pajamas and go over.
I don't know. That's because I want to make sure this shit's fucking taken care of. I own this
property. If I own this fucking place, what am I just going to hang up? Yeah, I don't care.
What the fuck are you talking about? I'll be over there in five minutes. Okay, so that's the green.
This is a nice green reptile room. They do do that. Could you fix it? I would get the appropriate
person that could or try. You need to be there. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Actually, I kind of like this
wood for the reptile room, don't you? I think it's kind of like the Jurassic Park kind of.
I kind of like it. I don't mind this. Okay, we're going to leave that for now. I'll come back to
this. Okay, so now I need to figure out where I'm going to have my leisure time. And I think
this is going to be an aquarium in here, by the way. That's going to be the aquarium room.
In fact, let's get this started right now. Okay, I need counters. Counter. Okay.
My fucking eye, it's fucked up. All right, I need this. I need a long counter. Are you allergic
to reptiles? No, I'm fine. This is way too short, like a shoe rack. Dude, you blink like a reptile.
I also go like this every 15 seconds. I probably am a reptile. That has to be a little bit higher.
I blink a lot. I go, I look my lips all the time. I don't know. This is going to be so sick coming
in. Oh, this is basic. This has been facing the wrong way the whole time, hasn't it? Has it? It
has been. Oops. I got to go. Shit. I got to fix that. The other ones in there are backwards.
It's okay. Light. They all have lights. Well, that's cool. Okay. Well, these have to flip.
Just leave them. At this point, I really don't care. Those are not flush fish tanks. Okay.
Fresh water. We'll do fresh water over here. Whoa, that's a lot. This is huge. I can't. All right.
I got to rethink this. Oh my god. This is too big. This is way too fucking big. Maybe not. It's not
going to be big if I have a smaller door. Nice. Is this facing the wrong way? I can't really tell.
Oh, this looks like a PetSmart. It kind of does. It does look like a PetSmart. Stack them. Can I do
that? I can't stack them. That's fine. I don't need more than that. That's a nice entryway.
It's the Rainforest Cafe. Where's the iguana? Oh, I didn't finish that. Something reptilian.
This is kind of reptilian. Oh, some of these are pretty reptilian. This feels like a really big
afterthought. This is fine. I like the kind of, yeah, these are like kind of leaves and shit.
I don't know. People do weird shit like that with paintings, don't they? All right, that's fine. I
don't put a little table here. Cat aviary? What's a cat aviary? Where's the dog? I haven't gotten
there yet. I just need like a, yeah, like one of these is fine. No, that's in the way. I don't care.
That's fine. This is as good as it's going to get because I need to get the animals in here.
All right. This is the front door. You got your cat tree thing here that can stay open. I need a
little kitchen. Kitchen's going to have to be right here. Just a little kitchenette because this goes
into the bathroom. This is the bedroom. We're going to move this to here because I need this
to be a kitchen. So that's what's going to happen. I need this to be, this has to be a little kitchen
area. Otherwise, how am I going to cook? That's better. Okay, so now this can be a little kitchen
corner. I'm thinking, I want tile. See how this looks. No passion. That looks stupid. If this was
a kitchen area, I didn't see the whole thing. It looks like a pizza parlor. Why do I know what
you mean? But it's, I don't secret room, secret room. Why do you keep saying secret room? What
do you mean secret room? There's a room on your map. Huh? What is this? What the fuck is this?
What is this? Um, oh, well, okay, I can take this down. So now this can be the little kitchenette
in here. That's okay. That's much better because then I can do a little kitchen in here.
Okay, I get it. Nice. That makes sense. Okay, so now let's do, uh, what do I, I don't like the way
that looked. Something nice and kitchen-y. This is kind of kitchen-y. That's kind of kitchen-y,
isn't it? It looks like a chocolate bar. It just looks like a new Hershey's chocolate s'more thing.
Maybe it works. I need to see the whole thing. Nah, I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like
it. I'm not a huge fan, so I'm taking it down. What about this one? It's grandma wallpaper. Let's
try this one. A little bit lighter though. Yeah, like a light biscuit. Let's try that. Light biscuits
should be good. That's better. That's fine. Yeah, that's, that looks cute. What's wrong with that?
This should, I have it go all the way out though. Yeah, probably like that. I'll change this. Okay,
that floor has got to go. Please add trim. I just want to get rid of these. So, I need a better
floor for here. What should I put in here? Tile? A nicer tile. A nice tile. I like tile. What's
wrong with tile? One of these looks good. I like that. Let's try this. What's wrong with that? I
need a stopping point for this though, and I don't like it being here. Oh, it's the same thing that's
in the bathroom. Is that fine? I think that's okay. Isn't this, I think that's fine. It's a
fucking ballroom. It's going too far into the living room. Well, I got to figure out what I want
in the living room. What the fuck happened? Why did this fall? Why did that fall? I was worried.
Okay, so I know the kitchen is going to be here, so we're going to do kitchen stuff. I need a fridge.
Uh, I like this. Fridge, and then a counter, an oven. Okay, let's do a fucking double oven.
Triple oven. Okay, triple oven. And then I'll do some cabinets with a washing machine. Dishwasher.
Just good old stainless, stainless steel. That right here. Part of that. We'll get some cabinets
here too. I need a sink. Why, I don't know, why are they so small? That's weird. Fucking horrible.
What kind of, I want just a kitchen sink. I just want a kitchen sink. Okay, here we go. Thank you.
Give me this one. Does this even match? Yeah, that's fine. Okay, we'll do a counter this way.
One counter, one counter. Whoa! Give me this thing. Oh my god, it's already done. I don't have to do
anything. It's already ready. That's so much better. Okay, cool. That sink is trash. It's fine. Okay,
looks fine. Let's make one of these over on the other side. I'll be honest, I don't care. I don't
give a shit. I tell you, I don't care. Zero passion. I'm passionate about the animals, not about what
the kitchen looks like. That doesn't even look that bad. All right, so now I can, let's clean this up.
Cat, tower, aquarium, and then the bugs and the bugs will be down here. Okay, cool. Let's get that
started. All right, I need some dog stuff and cat stuff. Here's the little kitchen, living room.
Oops. I'll put stairs somewhere else. Stairs will be, where the hell the stairs gonna go?
I think they need to be down like over here. Over here in this corner? Where am I gonna put the
stairs? Maybe they can, I thought maybe they can only be in that spot. This works. This actually
kind of works. Come on, really? Give me a break. Okay, this is scary. I need it there temporarily.
I can't even go down this. There's so many more. Okay, but it takes up so much less space.
This takes up so much less room. The other one is this big. It's so massive. Evil cellar. Not,
just wait. It's less cute. What do the other stairs look like? Garden stairs. Okay, wait,
stairs. All right, this is way better. Yeah, yep, yep, yep. We'll make it a little darker.
Okay, that's better. Oh my god, it's so, it's too huge. Look at how huge this fucking thing is.
It's the whole house. I'm keeping the attic stairs. Look at this. This is not gonna work.
Put it on the side. It's too big. The spiral takes up less space. I want a little one. Yeah,
less space. Really? This is the whole house. This is the entire house. All right, this is kind of
stupid, but whatever. Do I really need the cat thing? Are you trying to tell me to get rid of
the cat thing? I can't put it anywhere else. Maybe over here? There's no other corner where this can
go. No, this has to stay. I can't move that. I think that's fine, although the color is awful.
This just needs to be a little more unassuming. Okay, that's a little better. I think that's fine.
It doesn't matter. Look, it's not gonna be a TV. I'm putting the couch right here to watch the cats.
That's more interesting than television anyways. It looks like shit, but there's no other place I
can put this unless I get rid of this corner, but then I'd have to make the bathroom entrance here.
Let's try it. Bathroom right in front of the fridge. This shit is way too fucking big.
It's so enormous. It can't go anywhere. Build another room. I can't. You cannot build out.
You cannot build out. You can only build in. I can't build. Where am I supposed to put it?
The only thing I can think of is... Let's see if this does it. Ready? Let's try this. I have an idea.
I have an idea. Let's see if it works. This would be fine. Not big enough. I could do one here,
which that's fine. That's fine. That's okay. We don't need two snakes. I'll find a place for it,
but let me see if I can put the staircase here. Give me a small staircase. Is there a small one
I can put right here? Right there. Come on. Really? There's no place to go down the stairs?
I gotta go down there and I gotta break a bunch of shit. Hold on. Fucking dump down here. Yeah,
I want this here. Okay. I think that should do it. There's just stuff in the way. Is it construction
lights or something I can put down here? There's a bright ass construction light. I just want to
be able to see. Okay. Now I should theoretically be able to move this into this corner. At least
I hope so. Let's find out. Why is there a handprint down here? I don't know. I just bought this place.
Okay. Now can I move? Hopefully the lights aren't going to be in the way they might though.
Okay. It looks good. Can I move those over here? Here. Even if it has to be the attic, I don't care.
It just needs to fit there. I just need a way to get down the stairs. And really? Is this, is it a
wall there or something? I don't get it. It's a wall here. It's a wall, wall, wall, wall, wall.
Where's that fucking wall? Where? Oh, bullshit. Why is the house wider? That should be able to
go right there. Turn it around. I don't think that's going to work. I'll try it. No, no. Switch sides.
Oh shit. Is it going to fit? Yes. Okay. Can the regular staircase fit here though? No, not really.
Kind of. No, but it's messing up my view. I guess I could do this with something else over here
because now I can move this down. I'll do this wall. Will that fit over here? All the snakes can fit
now. Nice. Okay. Yes. All right. We're good. I want to be a little bit more unassuming though. I don't
like the light. That looks good. That's fine. Okay. The light switches above the stairs. I'll fix it
later. Okay. So now that does that. Reptile room is still fine. I can fix the green paint. I can
weigh down. Where does this end up? Actually, perfect. I'm actually really happy with that.
We're gonna keep it. Okay. Let's get some animals in here. Where do I get animals? Where do I get
animals? Where's my dog? Oh, I have to go to the menu. Okay. Okay. Let's get... Where's my dog?
Where's my dog? Come here. All right. There's dog. So now let's get some reptiles. Iguana. Whoa.
Turtle. We need a turtle. Okay. We need it. One turtle. Name. Crunch. Oh, there you are. Okay.
Where's crunch? There's crunch. Okay. Crunch looks good. You're gonna go eat? Very cool. All
right. I'm happy. Now I need... Here. How's the treat? Delicious. Okay. Now I need an iguana. How
many iguanas can I put in here? Just one, right? Iguana's name. I want... How many iguanas should I
get? Oh, it needs its own enclosure. Let's go look at Fred. Whoa. Hey, Fred. What do you eat?
Deviled eggs and lettuce? Okay. Very cool. Fred doesn't come out. What a dinosaur. I don't think
they come out. That's so cool. Okay. Well, have fun in there, Fred. What are you up to? Let's leave
it open. I'm not gonna leave the enclosure open. You guys want all the... You know, I'm sorry. No,
that's not happening. All right. Now we need some cats. Back to the laptop. I need like bunnies and
cats. Spiders. All right. What about rodents? All right. We need some... I need a cat. I think
the Bengal kitten. Scrumptious. Very scrumptious. How many cats should I get? This is a ragdoll. This
is chevious or mischievous. Chevious. Okay. This is chevious. Where are you going? Wait, do I need
to like make sure there's nothing dangerous in here? Don't go out the window, please. Oh my God.
You're so cute. Okay. Let's go get some more. Now go play. How's everybody doing? All right. Let's
get some more. This is a sphinx. Perfect. Little perfect. Except I should have spelled it with a
U. Okay. There's perfect. And then there's... This is a European. European? Okay. Eiffel. For the
Eiffel Tower. Okay. Okay. There's a lot of cats. I need cat food. I need a cat food thing. Let me
take care of this right now. I'm working on it. All this stuff is for rabbits. I don't want rabbit
shit. I want cat food stuff. All right. We need a dog bowl. Okay. Automatic dog food feeder. That
looks good. Now I need an automatic cat food feeder. Does one not exist? Automatic dog water?
Okay. I thought that was just cats eating the dog food. Make sure the dog doesn't eat the cat food.
Okay. Cats. Automatic cat food feeder. We'll put one here. We should probably do two and then we'll
do a cat water. Sounds good to me. Wait, this is for dogs. All right. How are you guys? How's
everybody doing? You guys having a good time? Another rag doll. Doll. You need a litter box.
Peaches. I like that. Peaches. Okay. All right. There's only a few more cats. Sweetie. Hello,
sweetie. Okay. You have too many cats? I got enough room. Let's get some beds.
It's going to be very nice. It's going to be comfortable. It's going to be tons of activities.
There's going to be toys and shit everywhere. I need cat beds. Okay. How many cats do I have? Five?
Ooh. Look at these. These are nice. Yeah. These are perfect. One for everybody. That can be
scrumptiouses. This is, um, I don't know. Somebody else's. Hi. What can I do for you? You want a
treat? Oh, have some water. Very good. This one's very mischievous. Who is this one? Oh, wait. Isn't
that like fucking iguanas back here? There it is. Don't go in there. Oh shit. This is a terrarium
over here. Just delete it. I don't want it. Okay. Now we need, I got, there's a couple of beds.
I got food stations. All right. David. I don't know. Just random names. Name one Morbius. Is
there a, is there an auto? There's no auto. Octavius. Morbius. All right. Hold on. I don't
want to have too many pets. I don't want to have too many pets. I need to make sure that there's
enough. Okay. We need to go with the downstairs because I need to make sure there's enough room.
Where is it downstairs? Okay. This is going to be bugs, but okay. This would be the bug room.
I need more room. This would be the designated insect room. What was that? We need rodents too.
All right. One step at a time. This would be the rodent room. These would be the bug room. This
would be the rodent room. This will be more downstairs play area for the cats, dogs and
wherever. So let me get this. Let me do this first. How much should I feed? The downstairs is for
gross animals. That's not what I said. Where's the, where, where's, where's the turtle? Are you all
right? Oh, hello. Hello. Octavius. Oh, a little bit of a rascal. Come here. Come play. Now leave
the turtle alone. All right. Tug of war. Doesn't care. All right. Everybody. What? Everybody get
out of here. Everybody come out of this room. You're my favorite, but don't tell anybody.
Okay. There are just birds. Flight. Nevermind. Ooh, look at this one. How about one of these
bunny houses right here? Bugs. All right. Bugs. You can be over. Where should I put bugs? Over
here in the corner. This is a fun spot. This is cute. Oh, there you are. What can you do with the
bunny? Oh, that's so cute. Here. Want a treat? Oh, I need a litter box. Okay. I got to feed the fish,
don't I? Are there any fish even in here? How do you, I got to feed the fish. Okay. They got a
little box now. Is it, is it pee on the ground? Oh, there's like a little, yeah, there's poop
right here. All right. I got, I have a little box now, so I'm fine. I don't have to pick it up.
Get rid of that. Okay. I need a new floor. The floor is shit colored. The floor. It's, I can't
tell. Okay. Will they, will they actually use the litter boxes? Do not go outside. No, no, no, no.
Nobody's going outside. Everyone's staying right here. And how come no one's used the fun cat
thing? There's a shit in the sink. There is not a shit in the sink. Uh, okay. Wait, maybe I should
let them go out. Yeah. You need to go out, right? It's a big yard. You guys want to go hang out?
Look, there's, just be careful. The eagle. Is there a fence? I don't think their programming
will make them, I don't, this is a invisible wall, I think. Yeah. It's an, it's not an invisible wall.
I don't think they can even come down here. I really, I really doubt it. This is my cat.
Oh, come here. Go get the yarn. They're having so much fun. Okay. Everyone's having such a good
time. Put a fence? I don't, it's a fence even exist? This is for a bunny enclosure. There. Now
they can't go over here. There. Okay. That's good. This looks like shit. It just needs to be
practical. It doesn't look all right. Very cool. All right. Uh, this one has, there's a fence around
here. They're good. I messed it up. Just wait. Look, it's fine. They can't get out this way.
They can't get out over here. They can get out over here though. Let me fix this. Watch out. Watch
out. Get over the other way. You're not supposed to be over here. Please go over there. Here. Look
what I got. The fucking bunny went to go get it and you didn't. I'm here. Get over here. I need to
pick you up. Stay here. Oh, you got the, nice. You got the ball. Good. There you go. All right. Go,
go, go, go, go, go, go. Now stay away from me for a minute. I cannot put a fence here. I actually
can't put a fence up. Um, I think it's fine. Okay. Well now I can't get over here. All right. I can
get through that. What's this? All right. Everyone's having a good time. We're all just hanging out.
Everyone's got put. What are you doing over here? Okay. Are we missing anybody? All right.
Everybody's in. We got a big yard now. We're ready to go. I need a dog bed. Oh, you look at you.
Here. Have some deviled eggs and carrots. You need to buy fish. Goldfish. Angel fish. Goldfish.
Guppy. Discus. Yeah. Get some more fish. Fishy. What about a guppy? Okay. All right. That's all
I can do. Um, I got a huge yard so I can still. All right. I should get some puppy golden retriever.
I already have a golden retriever. Labrador. Uh, doofus. Stop rubbing your eyes. I can't help it.
I need some beds. Um, let's put some new flooring in here. Look, everyone's having such a good time.
How's the iguana doing? All right. Build food. Get some eye drops. I'm currently streaming right
now. Is anybody even in here? There's nobody in. What's supposed to go in here? Don't go over there.
The snake got out. There's no snake. I didn't buy one. I didn't buy a snake. I didn't buy a snake.
Come get it. Come get it. Oh, they're all trying to get it. Who's gonna get it? Here. Have one of
these. Okay. Cool. How are you doing? Okay. I need, um, why is there so much shit over here?
What's happening? How come nobody's using their litter boxes? There's a shit directly
next to the litter box. All right. We're fine. Let's get the downstairs rolling because that's
where a lot of beds are going to go for the dogs. Oh, cool. Look at this. Oh my goodness.
Do I have to? How do I feed them? Yeah. Look, doofus. It's fishes. Good dog, doofus. He got it.
I love doofus. Oh no. What's wrong? Why do you look so sad? What's wrong? Yeah. Want a biscuit?
We need some more recreation down here. All right. We need recreation. Everybody watch out.
Careful. Not everybody come in here at the same time. All right. Let's just dog beds. I need some
beds. Let's make it a little more comfortable down here too. Carpets. I know people are going to go,
what are you talking about? I want to be nice and comfortable. I'll get steam cleaned once a fucking
week. There's going to be beds down here. There'd be toys. It's going to be awesome. This is where
there's going to be tons of space. Okay. Looks good so far. So this is going to be another
different animal room. Get it up to the wall here. There's so much room down here as well. All right.
So now we're going to do, please have the rats in the basement. Yeah. The rats are going to be in
here, but if I'm going to have like five dogs, I need a ton of space. So let's go ahead and get
some dog stuff. Okay. Sleeping mat. Here we go. Yeah. Everybody's going to have a little spot.
There we go. Right there. Everybody's going to get a little space. We'll go with a little smaller
one. Some dogs like the little beds. They don't want the huge ones. That was stereo. Yeah. Like
a little one. Yeah. Like this. Some dogs like just like the mat, right? Perfect. Okay. Sleeping
quarters here. That's good. He's clueless. What do we mean? They can't go down the stairs. Why not?
Follow me. Can you not go down the stairs? They can't go downstairs. What? So when it's time for
bed, I have to pick each one of them up individually and bring them down to bed? Swap the reptiles for
the dog beds. Okay. Maybe I should do that. Should I swap the dog beds? I didn't leave them down
there. I'm going to go get them. Yeah. I'm going to have to swap. Why are you a different color?
The iguana is a different color. All right. I'm going, I'm swapping. You dope. This is just
temporary until I get everything down here. Do not, don't go in there. What are you eating? Don't eat.
What are you eating? All right. Come with me. He's going to jump in. Doofus ate the iguana.
No, the iguana is up in there. Fine. Let's move the beds. I'm going to make this more comfortable
because it shouldn't be a wooden floor. Let's go with some carpet. Let me get nice and comfy.
I can stay with that gray. That's fine. I'm going to repaint this whole room. All right. Yeah. I'm
going to make this a little comfier. What do you mean? This is not carpet. Gray fitted carpet.
That's carpet. What are you talking about? This is ugly. Yeah. Well, it's, this doesn't, it's not
going to be this insanely. What is that? I can stay. Okay. Dog beds coming up. Perfect spot.
And the cat beds can come in here too, probably. Right there. All right. Bring a couple of cat
beds in here. Oh, okay. I'll come back. Change the color of the room. I will. I don't need this.
Okay. How are we doing? Plenty of food, plenty of water. Does anyone want to play with this?
Why won't anybody go up here? The house keeps getting worse. I'm in the middle of
handling it. I just didn't understand. Hidden room off the kitchen. Where is this hidden room?
There's no way. This is my fucking bedroom, dude. Do I even need a bedroom? What was the,
what's the point of the bedroom? Okay. And put some toys in here. That can stay there.
I should just sleep on the floor. Who cares? Where did you get this? You don't have any needs.
Somebody has needs over here. Who is it? Needs sleep. Oh, we'll go to bed. Go in the,
go lie down over here. Look, come here. In here. Get some sleep. Right there. That's just like Otto.
Otto does that too. Little Otto. Okay. Let's put a few toys in there. Is this rabbit shit or is
this cat shit? I don't know. This floor has to be a different color than shit brown. It's kind of,
it's changing right now. These? Okay. At least I can see the shit on the ground. The door doesn't
go anywhere. I know. I haven't fixed it yet. I'm in the process of getting this done. My game is
lagging. There's too many animals in this house. We have some comfortable living space now. Tons
of room over here. Did you just? Go in the dog bed. So now let's see. What else do I want?
You need more animals. I mean, I want, I need space to accommodate them. Okay. Rodents. Hamster.
There's no rats. I think the game is having trouble loading any more animals. The game does
not want to load any more animals. It doesn't like that I have 10 already. Fill the house with
spiders. All right. Let me move this out of the way. Can I not put any more? That's kind of annoying.
What's wrong with this? Excuse me. How is that not enough room? I don't, I don't get it. There's
plenty of room. Ceiling is too low. Light. Can I not put any more animals in? Dude, what is the
problem with nothing on the wall? Whatever. Can I go back to the, I want to get some, um, spiders
and rats and stuff. Oh, there we go. Okay. So let's see. Spiders. Spidey. So somebody said,
I love how you're putting the gross animals down here. Where? Ah, he's right there. I see him. Oh,
what the fuck? Oh, I don't like that. Don't let it out. Don't let it out. Why is it on the floor?
Cause I need to, I'm just temporarily, I just want to see if it did. All right. I have a snake
room. Okay. This one's fine. I have one already. Slimy. Morbius. Fine. It's the only time you're
going to get that. All right. Where's the, where is he? There's a snake. Oh, there you are. You eat
eggs. That's cool. All right. It's the turtle. I can probably put a few turtles down here if I
wanted to. Okay. There's the iguana. Spiders. I need the computer down here. You can go out there.
It's fine. You can go outside. Go for it. Stop shitting next to the food. It's not happy. Here.
Look, go get it. Come here. How do I, how about play with yarn? You want to play with yarn? Oh,
there you go. You're happy now. Okay. People are happy. Yeah, they have litter box. Somebody,
what's wrong with you? What's going on? You need, you're not happy and you just sleep. Well,
go lie down. Nice catch. Go lie down over here. There's a nice bed just waiting for you and you
go lie in it. Go to sleep. So cute. I know, I know that's your favorite bone, but you need to go lie
down. It doesn't want to go to sleep. All right. Who else is here? Who else needs something? No
needs. No needs. So then we'll, oh, they were hungry. Okay. You still need to go to sleep.
Go to bed. Everyone else is fine except for you. No, you're fine too. So what's wrong with you?
What's going on here? No needs. Okay. So you need to go to sleep. All right. Let's go. Um,
it's kind of dirty over here, isn't it? It's dirty as hell over here. I think it's outside the house.
The beds are backwards. I don't know how that's possible by the way. I don't know what you mean.
Like you were right. What? There is no backwards. It's a rectangle actually backwards. That's
ridiculous. Okay. Well, whatever. I'm going to move this temporarily out here. So there's an extra
bed back down here. You look good. I need to organize this area. So I want, let's put like,
I should go down there. I'm taking the computer downstairs. Be good. Okay. How much money do I
have? Birds. Should I have birds down here? No. How many more spiders should I have? 50? I don't
think I can have 50. There are no more spiders left to buy. Okay. What about rodents? Hamster? Yep.
Definitely going to have a hamster. Oh my God. That's big. Um, we'll put some hamsters in here.
Oh, all right. You need a light. I'm definitely going to not have the snake be in this room.
No, that's not happening. Are you in here? Okay. You're in here and you have an egg, right? Yep.
You're good. It's dark down here. I'm going to put some lights in here. There's the turtle. There's
the hamster. It's too dark in here. Let's get some light. Get a guinea pig. Yeah, I'll get a
guinea pig. Just something basic. Yeah, this is fine. Just basic shit. Just like Minecraft
fucking torches. It doesn't matter. There we go. Can I play with the hamster? I think I can just
watch. So cute. Okay. There are the three spiders. There is my snake, the iguana. All right. What
else can I buy? Okay. Let's guinea pig. Uh, this one looks good. Um, frumpy. Oh my God. This is way
too big. This is a children's playground. This is not an enclosure for a guinea pig. Cool. Well,
have fun in here. Oh, fucking alien. They need, they need way more space than people think.
Did they really? This is a huge enclosure. I hope, I hope they're very happy. Okay. What else? I don't
need any more turtles. Another hamster? No. How about another, how about a husky? Um, husko. No
rats? Yeah, there's no rats. How about some birds? I think I've, should I put birds? Okay. I'm going
to get some birds in here. Guys, I haven't slept in five days. I need to, I need to fix the bedroom.
Where can this even go? Holy shit. Guys, I, this can't go anywhere. Wait, do they actually want
to be outside though? Okay. Let's get some birds. What are you doing down here? Okay. Here's a parrot.
Tweety. Thanks to your good care, your pet David is growing up. Please remember that all pets,
regardless of age, need much attention. Who? Who's David? Oh, it's David. Hey, you look,
you're an adult cat. Oh, that was so fun. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I need to, I need to, I need to buy a few more
birds and then I got to take care of everybody. Um, they're all just parrots, flappy and slippy.
All right. I need you to come with me. What are you looking at? Okay. You're good. Come with me.
I thought that was a huge shit log. I was about to say, oh my God, are you okay? You've been in here
for a long time. You all right? What's going on? Why can't I, um, what's happening? What's
going on? Why do you just, do you don't want to treat? Oh no. What's happening? How do I fix this?
Come with me. Come with me. I can't pick the cat up. What do I do? Well, how do I fix this?
Too many pets of room is still walled off. Um, okay. They're fine. Did they actually, would they
want to come out? No, right? No, no, no. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let's take care
of everybody. Everyone seems to be okay. What can I do for you? Uh, watch out. Okay. Come here.
There you go. Okay. You look like you're having a good time. Here, have some yarn. How are you
doing? You need to go to sleep. Get some sleep. There's tons of bed over here. Go check the beds
out over here. There's like three that are over here. Everybody's happy. They just, one of them
is a little tired. How are you doing? Everybody's relatively happy. Have some food. So now we'll go
get some sleep. Where are you going? What do you need? Come here. All right. Now we're going to
give four or five of them to the animal person, right? Cause he's like, you take care of them
for a while and then I can come get them, right? What's going on over here? They need to go to,
okay. Some of you need to go to sleep. How are you doing? You're doing good. You're holding so much
shit in your pocket. You got plenty of food. You do too. How are you guys doing? Oh, there you go.
Delicious water. Do I, I don't have to fill food on this one. How are you doing? You still have
food, right? Was the whole ground just food? No. Hay is food. Get another guinea pig. No,
I'm not, there's no, I'm not getting any more animals. I am at capacity. How are you doing?
Good. Snake is taking a little rest. No, I'm not getting any more. There's no, this is it.
You've got your salad there. Okay. How are you doing over here? I can't put food in here. I think
it's just automatic. How are you doing? Yeah. Everyone that has needs needs to sleep, but they
won't go in the bed. Okay. So now where's my laptop? The guinea pig needs a friend. No,
I'm not getting any more. No more animals. No, no more. This is it. This is what I can reliably
take care of. So now, so now what some of them can go. Cause I took them from his hotel, right?
I was like housing them for a little while. The doorways are too small. Adopt a child. Okay.
Where are my animals? Oh, here we go. Okay. So then somebody comes in and adopts them.
Who, where's David? Oh, this is kind of cool. All right. So David, you want to find a new
home for David? Yeah. Let's get David a nice home. Did I do it? I think Fred needs a nice home too.
Okay. Scrumptious is going to stick around. Who else needs like, I've been, I've been taking care
of them and I want them to have good homes. Perfect. I think perfect could get a new, a good home.
Bugs. Oh, I was like, what, why are they bugs? We'll get bugs should probably have a new home.
Yeah. I'm like an adoption place, right? I'm like helping the guy with like his adoption stuff.
Okay. Octavius, you've been a very, very good, good dog. Let's get you a new home. Who should
I stick around with? Fishy can stay. I think, I think doofus. Don't sell them. I'm not selling
them. What are you talking about? You're deleting them. I'm not, I'm not deleting them. They're
finding new homes. What are you talking about? Yeah. I want to make sure they have good homes.
I don't want to have too many that I can't take care of. I want them to have good homes.
Okay. Let's pick this up. They have plenty of food, right? All right. Let's take,
let's do some playtime. So I think somebody grew up. Yeah. All, all the needs are just sleep,
sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep. Come over here and play with the mouse. Go get it. Adopt. Yeah. I'm,
I thought I was like a foster house and then they would come and I would put them up for adoption.
That's what I'm doing. How are you doing? Sleep. Let me guess. They, okay. They, they don't sleep
and then they get unhappy because they're tired. Do I need more beds? I need more litter boxes.
Okay. I'm going to add two more litter boxes over here. The dogs don't, the dogs just go out,
right? You're happy. Everybody seems pretty happy over here. Hungry. Okay. You're really bored. I
keep, hold on. Come here. Come over here. Go get it. Go get it. Yeah. Who's going to get the ball?
Oh, the bunny, bunny got adopted, right? What's wrong? Do you want a treat? There we go. Okay.
Very good. You have the same eyes as the Among Us guy because we're the same person. Okay. Everyone
seems to be in pretty good spirits. I think you guys are just tired. Yes. Okay. You're tired and
I think you're tired too. Yes. All right. So let me clean up your area here. I think, I think it's
time for Doofus to get adopted. Doofus needs a little bit more room. Yeah. Doofus needs some
more room. You want a treat? No, please. No, no. Someone else. Oh, look. Lassie, uh, grew up. You
need to get some sleep. Please. Not Doofus. What about, um, what about Husko? I think Husko needs,
Husko needs a lot of room. Yep. All right, Husko. We're going to get you a good family. Okay.
Where's Husko? All right, everybody. Let's find Husko a home. Oh, let me go to the birds. Birds
need a little bit of, uh, a little bit of care, I think. Right. I want to get out of the, please
let me get out of the laptop. You monster. What? I'm getting them in better homes. Here you go. Have
some food. Copium. What do you mean? What? I'm taking care of them until we can find them. I'm
fostering them until we can find them better homes. I'm not deleting them. It does not say
delete this dog. It says find a home. I'm not, nobody, what are you talking about? Here, have
some. Oh, you already have, do you already have food? Yeah, you're tired. Are you tired too? Yeah,
they're both just tired. Home. Copium. Huh? It says have them find a better, a new home. Look,
that's what it says. Morgan's Pet Care. I'm currently fostering animals and it says, okay,
so here's who is at my house. Find a new home. It doesn't, I didn't, move to hotel. Move to hotel
would be, no, this is, they come in and they, that's not what it says. It's not a funeral home.
Stop. You guys are fucked. Show us the homes. I don't, there's not that much in this. What?
Oh shit, I just went to sleep. Ah, bugs. Do you actually see the people? This one's really cool
looking. It's blue and orange. That's crazy. You're good. You're happy. Fill up your hay again.
Give you some more food. You still have leaves there. Hello. What's this guy's name? Fred.
What's turtle's name? Hello. I like doofus more than I like lassie. Oh, that was crunch. Right.
I wish I could take you out and kind of let you run around a little in a safe enclosed space.
You're doing good. How are you doing in here? It's filled. Oh, right. Fred got adopted. That's
right. Fred got adopted. Hope you're having a good time, Fred, in your new home. Uh, I just fed you.
How are you doing? Tired? You want to play here? I love how the dogs want to play with the cat toys
too. Are you tired doofus? No needs. All right. I think it's time to send out some more. I think
you're just tired. Yeah. You doofus just won't go to bed. How come doofus won't sleep? He just won't
go to bed. Fish. Uh, I don't, you don't feed the fish. They just kind of hang out. There's no
mechanic to feed them. Yeah. These guys are all full up with food. They're all good. How are you?
Maybe we should get some adoptions going here. Uh, you were adopted so I can get rid of that.
I, I want to adopt crunch. I want crunch to be adopted from me and I want scrumptious and doofus.
The rest are going to have good homes. Crunch. I'm keeping crunch. Actually, I'll keep lassie too.
I'll keep doofus. Uh, it's kind of glitched out. Okay. So I'm going to, I want crunch. I could keep
scrumptious. Oh, chivius would be so wonderful. Let's get chivius a new home. Eiffel. Eiffel will
do so good in a new home. Come on in. Adopt. Well, sweetie, we'll keep sweetie. Oh, the fish.
That's cool. We'll keep doofus. I, we'll keep spidey. We'll adopt out. Uh, we'll keep morbius.
All right. We have some, anybody want to come in and get the spiders? Oh, that's a hamster. I
feel like somebody would have a lot of fun with this hamster. Frumpy would have a lot of fun with
the new owner too. Keep spider four. This is, this is all temporary. I wanted to make sure that I
could house them. All right. Flappy. I'm going to, I'll keep one of the parrots. I'm going to keep
tweety. Some of these spiders though, I'll keep the blue spider. We'll find a new home for you.
The fish can all stay. And I think, I think I'm good. I think, wait, what about peaches?
They're going to a new home. A new home. This doesn't say a new death. This doesn't say a new
shelter. They're going to a new home. Home. H-O-M-E. H-O-M-E. H-O-M-E. H-O-M-E. H-O-M-E.
It doesn't say heaven. It doesn't say, no, it'll find a new H-O-M-E. Home. It says home. How come
you're adopting animals to give them away? No, I'm working with the pet adoption center. I'm working
with the adoption center. The new, oh my God. Isn't that guy, that's not adoption center.
You're being so gaslit right now. I know. And they deserve to be fucking yelled at.
Okay. So I got rid of this. These are all adopted. Very cool. The only thing, yeah, there was just
this, you were the only one. Hi. This chat is fucked. He's role playing. Yeah, I'm just,
I'm role playing. I'm role playing as a person that's like fostering animals and adopting them.
You deleted them. Where are all the huge dogs? What is the title of this fucking stream? I mean,
technically this was a huge dog house. So here we go. We've got two dogs, two cats, and our bird
friend out here. Perfect. Hello. Everyone is happy. Don't need these because I just need one. I don't
think Doofus has slept since he got here. Okay. Do you want a bigger bed? I wonder if it's, is it
the size? Does he, do you want a bigger bed? You're kind of a big dog. Are they big beds?
Open the bedroom. Okay. There we go. I don't even need a bedroom. This can just be another, okay.
Will you sleep in here if I put a, like a big bed in here? I wanted to get some sleep. Light dog
sleeping mat. Dog sleeping mat. Dog bed. Dog bed with legs. One of these big ones. Dog, dark dog
couch woof. Okay. This is extra large. How is that extra large? This doesn't look like an extra large
bed. That looks like a small bed. Why are these all so small? Okay. Hi. Yeah. He's not on follow.
Yeah. Get some, go get some rest. How are you doing? You doing happy? Doing good? Hey, look,
look at this. Oh, oh, are you gonna get it? Are you gonna get it? A little scrumptious. Are you
gonna go to bed? Finally? Good cat. I think you grew up. No, he's not on follow. Oh, snoozing. Keep
it open for now. You're doing okay. You're doing all right, but you're probably hungry. Yeah, come
over here. Want to play some yarn? Get it. Yeah, I don't, he's not on follow. Come here. Come with me.
I know you're very excited. It's very exciting stuff, but come over here. We'll put you in. It's
gonna be a quiet little space right over here. I know it's very exciting, but you should go
lie right in here. It's very exciting. There you go. Go on, lie down. Oh, no, get out of here.
He's trying to sleep. He doesn't want to go to bed. He's not on follow. Look, you just turn the
lights off. He's just too excited. Okay. Come over here and go lie in bed. I'm telling you.
Follow me. Okay. Follow me. Have they all been on follow me the whole time? Every single one?
I thought it was, I thought I had to click the follow me or click this. Really? What? No,
I didn't know that. I thought it was, but their default set to follow me. Okay. So in my brain,
this is not follow me, right? It's, he's under stay. See? I thought it was just,
now he's following me. He's so happy. I'm so happy. Thank God. Okay. So there you go.
You may have been the light switch. I think this room was off for a while too though.
How's everybody doing? Good. Just checking on everybody down here. Looking good. You still
have your egg. How are you anyways? How are you doing? Good. Just chilling. Don't do any more
adoptions. What? What are you talking about? He is not. He's fine. I think he's, I don't think
he's dead. I don't think he's dead. No, I don't think so. No, right? I think he's just sitting
there. I've been coming down here and putting food in and stuff. No, I don't, I don't think
they can die like that. No, I don't think so. No, look, look. Ready? Watch this. Watch. Ready?
Crunch is fine. He's fine. Look, this is him right here. It says he's fine. That's just an image.
No, why would I be able to move him around if he was? I think he's just bugged. I really do.
I honestly think he's bugged. Watch. Ready? Here's what we'll do. I'll prove it. Check this out.
Move to the hotel, okay? Pets in the hotel, okay? Pick from the hotel. Go back into your aquarium.
All these motherfuckers telling me that Crunch was dead. All these motherfuckers telling me
Crunch was dead. Everybody telling me Crunch was dead. I've been coming down here and been,
it's fine. Crunch just was, AI just walked into a wall for a second. Dude, you posted Crunch.
I've been feeding them. I've been having, I was right. I've been hanging out with them. How are
you doing? Good. I think you're sleeping down here. I think you're asleep down here. Oh no,
they were adopted. Yeah, everyone trying to tell me that Crunch, Crunch is perfectly fine. In fact,
let's get, because I know I'm keeping you, I can, you know, I'm going to bring you into the bedroom.
I think that's, I mean, I don't, nevermind. No, I'm not. Okay. How you doing? Doing good.
Everyone's doing good. I did, this hamster got adopted. So I can put you back over here in this
spot right here. Very cool. All right. Look at how happy you are. Very cool. Wanna play? Doofus.
Why do you hate doofus? How are you? It looks like you both have grown up. Need some sleep.
Make sure you're not on like follow, wait, so when it says follow me, that means it,
that they're staying, right? That's correct. So I have to click that. Happy, happy. Here, you wanna
play? Come, let's come, come outside. Let's get some exercise. Go get it. No, not doofus. Dude,
of course doofus is going to go get it. All right, doofus. Let's get you some exercise.
Doofus. There we go. All right. Come on out. Good catch. They don't, they're not really dirty. Yeah,
they look really clean. I'll get a cleaning station there right here. And then I'm probably
going to end the stream soon. I feel like I've done everything I wanted to do. You want to,
oh, well, okay. Well, now you're dirty. That you did not look like this before. Here you go.
You ready? Let's get clean. Very good. Do you need to clean? I don't think, I don't think you
do anything with the cats. You want to play? All right, here we go. Ready? This is for you.
I know I joked about the house, but I hope you had fun making it and the animals are very cute. Yeah,
it was fun. That's definitely a cool addition to the game. Go get it. Nice patch of grass.
It's fine. Don't worry. Everybody seems happy. I think, is doofus clean? Do you need to be clean?
No, you're fine. Fish is doing good. Very good. You don't feed the fish though. Everyone's having
such a good time. The fish are starving. I can't feed them. They're just, I think there's like an
auto feeder or something. They never used the cat wall. Yeah, they didn't. How do you, I wonder how
you get them to use it? Can you put them on it? Um, let me see if anyone will think it's fun.
Well, you're too tired. I don't want to do that. Where's uh, where's scrumptious? Scrumptious?
Where's scrumptious? How are you doing out here? You need food? No, you got, they got plenty of food.
Um, you might be stuck somehow. I think the game maybe has you stuck. Okay, I don't know. How did
that happen? He's going insane. I'm, hold on. All right. Tweety, we'll, we'll get Tweety adopted.
I don't, I can't, I can't fix Tweety. Tweety was stuck in the, on the seat or whatever it is. What?
I'm finding them new homes. You guys are fucked. All right. I think that's probably it. That was
fun. I didn't want to go too overboard because there's no way I, that was the limit of the
amount of animals I was able to reliably even take care of in the game. So I didn't want to
keep adding animals. How could you? Get them all adopted? Well, I, I, I can, I can take care of all
these. Two dogs, two cats, a couple of lizards. I'm okay with this. I'm not, no, I'm keeping them.
No, these, these are, these are my best friends. All the other ones were my good friends too, but
we got them new homes. If you turn the game off, they die. That's not true. They continue to live
here and have fun. This is a substantial update. I did not think there was going to be this much
stuff in it. There's a lot. This is really cute. It is really, that was really funny. That was really
cute. Start a dog sanctuary. Well, that's why I wanted to make sure I had enough beds and enough
food bowls. Once we got to like three, four dogs in the house, it was like, no more, no more. I
cannot take care of any more. The cat wall. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Who's, um, can I see you
for a second? Your fridge is so ugly. All right. Will you want to hang out on this? I don't think
so. No, I just don't think they want to use it. I just don't think they like it. No, they're on
follow. Are they? Well, these two were playing, so we were just playing. Can I go to bed? Okay.
It does look cool. All right. Goodbye, Doofus. It has been fun. Goodbye, Scrumptious. Goodbye,
Doofus. Goodbye, David. Goodbye, Husko. Goodbye, Disc. Goodbye, Flappy. Goodbye, Lassie. Goodbye,
Crunch. Goodbye, Peaches. Goodnight, Morbius. Goodnight, the other ones, all the other animals.
Perfect. Goodnight, Fred. Goodnight, Morbius. All right. Yeah, that's it. That's it. That was fun.
That was a back stretch. Oh yeah, multiverses. Okay. So on Friday, we're going to play multiverses
for like 40 minutes and then we'll move on to something else. Was that a good stretch? That was
a really good stretch, actually. I feel great. They're not going to leave the hard drive.
It's fine. I'll see you guys on Friday. We're going to start with multiverses. I'm going to stream
earlier than four because if the, if it actually turns off at five o'clock Pacific,
I want to play for at least a couple hours. We'll start at like three, at least three-ish,
because I want at least an hour or two. Your arms look really small. Get a little of that.
Do they? Yeah. What'd you say? Would you excuse, say that again if you could? All right. Goodbye.
I'll see you guys Friday. That was House Flipper Pets DLC. I didn't even pee for five and a half
hours. That's kind of weird. It's fun taking care of pets. Who was your favorite? My favorite was
probably Doofus and Crunch. Mainly Crunch because everybody said he was dead, but he wasn't. He's
alive and I proved it. So they're my favorites. Scrumptious? Yeah. David? Yeah. So everyone was
so convinced that Crunch was dead. Unanimous in the chat. Unanimous. Now, see you Friday. We'll
start with multiverses and then from there, because I'm not going to be able to play that
game for more than an hour or two, from there we'll probably do, I don't know. I'll take a look at
the recommended. There's a ton of stuff in there. We'll probably do a pre-stream poll if you're
around. But yeah, take care of yourselves. Thanks for watching. See you again, hopefully. This stream
started kind of absurd, but I think we chilled out a little bit halfway through, but it's fun.
It's fun just to hang out. You should play Ultrakill. Yeah, I mean, if it's not in the
recommended already, toss it in there. I'll go take a look. What about more infomercials? Yeah,
we'll do that too. You're in the hospital today. Thanks for cheering me up. Hopefully you're
all right. Hopefully there's nothing serious or anything. When's the green screen? Green screen
in front of the green screen night. I'll let you know early this coming week. It's not, I'm not
going to get in front of the green screen for at least a couple weeks because I want some time
for people to do actions and I want some time for me to figure out when I want to get in front of
it. So it'll be at least a week or two from right now at least. Where can we submit actions? So
in the discord right now we have a channel. It is imminently about to be used. We're going to set
up a discussion channel to talk about actions. What you want me to do in front of the screen.
I think it's going to open probably soon. It is a public discord with some sub only channels.
It is the submissions green screen channel. Go please read the rules. There are a lot of them.
There are a lot of rules. I will give some more info on this. Well actually we'll talk in detail
about the kind of what I'm expecting on Friday. Yeah and also check on the already done actions
before you submit. We've done this two times now. This is the third time. I'm not going to do,
for instance, I mean maybe I will for my own sake for my own amusement. But if something,
if it's if I've already done it in front of the screen I'm not going to do it again in a week or
two. If we already have that footage then if it's already been submitted then think of something
else. Is it sub only submissions? No it is not. Yeah take care of yourselves. Thanks for watching.
Take care of your pets. Give your dog and cat some love or if you have any other pets too.
And I'll see you guys on Friday. And always of course call your mother of course.
All right good night guys. See you soon.