Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here, and if you're wondering why I'm being
a little bit on the quiet side, it's because Jeremy doesn't know I'm in here. And I saw
him play this game the other day, and I asked him nicely if I could play it, and he told
me, no, Grandpa, you can't do that, because your heart is too, you're gonna have a heart
attack. And I told him, fuck you, and he said, fuck me, and then I said, fuck you to fuck me,
and that's how it ended. But I'm not supposed to be in his room, so don't fucking say anything.
If I hear any of you guys tell him that I did this, I'm gonna be really mad. But I wanna play
anyways, I think I'll be okay. This looks like a pretty easy level, because it's like all pink
and cottony, so I figured I won't get that mad at this. But let's just go, let's get started here.
Cotton Ellie. Okay, now, if I remember correctly,
you're supposed to jump over these shovel legs, just like this. God, this controller sucks!
Oh, oh no. Whoa, whoa, whoa, what was that? Are you all right? I just heard a crash. Are
you okay? What happened? Oh, no, yeah, I'm okay. Yeah, the seagull just
rammed into the window. It was ridiculous. What? He went full speed. He was looking at
me right in my eyes, and I said, you better not come over here, seagull, or I'm gonna get
really fucking mad at you. And he said, yeah, I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna bite you. And he
flew into the window and broke it. Can't believe it. Hold on, a bird flew into the window? That's...
Yeah. What is my controller doing over here on the ground?
Yeah, you did that. You must have done that. I didn't do anything.
You threw this into the window. No, this is not what you're talking about.
We live in the woods. There's no seagulls. Get up. Go get a broom.
I'll clean it up. Geez, what do you want? I'll get the fucking broom.
I can't believe you did this. You've never broken a fucking window
before because you're super mean boy. Everybody's done that for Christ's sake.
Thank you. Thank you for proving the reason why I banned you from this room.
What throws a controller into a window?