Hey what's going on everybody, Jerma here. We're going to do a live commentary tonight.
I'm going to be real relaxed, real laid back with this one.
I've got a lot of things on my mind, and we'll talk about them very, very briefly.
Nothing too big, don't worry. Nothing crazy, guys.
It's just the fact that I have a wedding that I'm the best man of.
Is that a spy? All the way, whatever.
I'm going to be the best man at my brother's wedding in two days.
And I have to make a speech and everything, and that's not what I'm concerned about.
It's just weird, people growing up.
Friends, family. It's really odd.
And it's not really depressing, but it's something that's in the back of my mind now.
It's just odd. I don't know really what to say about it, but it's going to be a great, fun, exciting day.
And hopefully it turns out...
Well, is that a cake on the ground?
The TF2 birthday stuff. Okay, I get it.
How did that not hit? Oh my god, dude, he's standing still.
Oh god. So I have a wedding.
And it should be a lot of fun. It's just really weird seeing your family grow up.
And seeing your friends grow up around you.
Some of you guys are too young to realize what I'm talking about.
But some of you guys are a little older.
And you'll know what I'm talking about soon enough.
Watching everybody get married, watching everybody around you.
But this is a live com. I wanted to get it out here tonight.
Because I'm not going to be able to do a video, obviously, in the next couple of days.
Because we're leaving tomorrow.
So I wanted to... I didn't even mean to do that.
Oh, come on.
No. Get the assist.
This is on Gold Rush. This is on Leptor's server.
Technically it's mine and Leptor's server, but Leptor's really the executive producer of this server.
Are you a spy? Yes, you are.
Oh, get caught in that! Oh!
Yeah, Leptor's in this game. So Leptor, if you're watching, what's up, dude?
There you are.
Oh, come on. Come on.
Oh, come on.
So yeah, that's mainly what I wanted to talk about.
Is the fact that Brother's getting married.
And I'm scared.
Give me some ammo.
Playing as a demo man. Just because I feel like it.
A lot of people... A lot of spies on our team, huh?
Well, not really. Only two. Seven on seven.
A lot of spies in general.
Let me catch somebody with one of these.
Let me catch somebody with this.
Oh, come here.
Come here now.
Oh, yeah.
This is a battle of wits.
A battle of wits right here.
Oh, I got you done.
Admirable attempt, though, my friend.
I thought you were going to get me.
So birthday cakes. This is Valve's birthday.
I guess this is their...
Well, not today, but it was.
Oh, boy.
Oh, come on. I'm going to die.
Nope.
There we go.
Get some stickies out.
See if I can't catch somebody coming around this corner.
And also, I'm still working on the livestreaming, guys.
I'm still working on getting that ready.
Getting that out to go.
I've had a lot of tips from a couple of dudes.
Oh, my God. Get away from me.
Oh, that was Leptor.
Leptor, you're a real son of a bitch.
I'm live-comming, by the way.
So...
If you don't know Leptor, you should.
Get off that cart!
Oh, come on.
Nice, nice.
Oh, question is, can I finish him off?
Question is, can I finish him off?
Question is, can I...
No, I'm not going to be able to do this, guys.
Somebody left in the comments before,
they said,
we want to see you fail,
because you never show gameplays where you fail.
And usually in my live stuff,
I don't do too great.
I usually get
beat up pretty hardcore
in my live commentaries.
Because I have like a problem with
doing two things at once.
My brain can't really function that well
when I have to do two things at once.
So if I have to talk, then I have to talk.
If I have to play,
then I have to play.
And why am I just letting him get away with this?
So pretty much when I speak,
I can't play.
And when I play, I can't speak.
My mind is one track.
Oh, come on now.
You're a spy. Come on.
Yeah, great. Nice job.
Nice job, spy.
Oh, can I finish him off?
I couldn't do it last time.
Oh, son of a bee. Here we go.
Four more minutes, lads.
Let's get some...
Oh, I think that's lepter right there.
Oh, I missed.
He did too, though.
Oh, god.
Nice. Nice shot.
But if anybody else in the comments
could just let me know
if you had a family member get married.
My sister got married a couple of years ago.
But what was your experience
with somebody in your family
getting married or somebody you know,
a close friend getting married or something?
I'd really like to know because it's really interesting to me.
No, they're going to win.
Uh-oh.
Better get these on the card.
Three minutes and 57 seconds.
Question is, can we do it?
Doesn't really look like it.
It looks like they're getting pretty close to winning.
What do we got right now?
Actually, we're doing all right.
Oh, spy.
Fine. You want to play that game?
Where'd you go?
Oh, god damn it.
I knew that was going to happen.
Like, I guaranteed myself coming around that corner.
Somebody, two scouts on the card.
Somebody do something.
Oh, can I?
Kaboom.
By the way, see my new hat?
If you didn't see my new hat, I'll show you.
I finally got the towering pillar of hats.
It is the stupidest,
most funny, entertaining thing in the game,
I think, and I'm so glad
that I finally have this
really dumb hat.
The thing is, I hate when people wear this hat.
It's so obnoxious.
It's just like, dude, will you take that thing off?
The thing's annoying.
What? Oh.
I was going to say.
Lag, huh?
But yeah, I'm still working on the live stream
thing, guys, and my first game
that I'm going to live stream is probably
going to be obviously TF2.
The other game
is probably going to be Deus Ex.
Because I bought Deus Ex.
I was really, really raring to go to play Deus Ex.
And now I have it, and I haven't
played it yet, so I figured that's a good outlet for it.
And if you guys don't want that,
let me know, because I will
take it into consideration, but it's definitely
something I want to do. My live stream, I think
I want it to be, because some of you
might remember, a lot of you newer subscribers don't remember,
but about three or
four weeks ago, I came out with a new
Let's Play series of The Witcher 2.
And it didn't really go over
so well with people.
Didn't really get too many views.
I can understand, because I know that people
don't want to sit through a
freaking 500 hour game
and all these cutscenes and stuff.
But I figured, what a good place for a live stream
to do that.
So if you guys don't mind, during my live stream
hopefully I can play some of those games
and you won't be too annoyed.
Oh boy, right out of the gate.
Oh, where'd it go?
Where'd the Uber go? There it is.
Oh, that was...
I don't think they had a century console.
I'm not going to call that a fail Uber.
Yeah, they only have a level one.
That's not a fail Uber.
Maybe it was, but you know.
Like I said, talking and playing at the same time.
Live comms are not my strong point.
But they are a lot of fun.
Because you get to see the real, raw Jerma.
Oh, by the way
speaking of my videos
Jerma, whatever.
Go watch the video that's up on Pixel Enemy right now, guys.
It's out there now. Scout, Milkman.
It's getting a pretty good response so far.
Hopefully you guys enjoy that.
Oh boy, I heard stab. Yes, I knew it. I knew it.
No!
I'm going... Oh god.
Oh wow, I can't believe I...
Hey, this is a tip for you guys.
Especially for those new guys.
If you are on a cart
or you're on a point and you hear
a stabbing sound, if you hear that like
it sounds like a...
Make sure to turn around because most of the time
that's somebody getting stabbed on your team.
So listen for that.
Listen for that stabbing noise.
Oh my god, I'm getting owned.
What am I? Eleven and ten.
One for one.
Whatever. I'm having fun.
Yeah, eight on seven.
Playing with my boy Leptor.
Yeah, let's see.
We've got to move this cart.
We've got to move to get this cart moving.
There we go. Oh...
No, don't you dare.
Don't you dare.
Give me the help. Nice.
Oh come on, come on.
What? He just got backstabbed by nothing.
Did you guys see that?
If you're watching right now, go back
like five seconds to when that
soldier just got backstabbed.
He didn't get hit by anybody.
He just magically died from a backstab.
Oh, I better sticky jump.
Oh god, this is nonsense.
Hear that stab? There he is.
Oh, I didn't save the medic.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Wow.
Oh my goodness.
I'm the only one left.
And then there was one.
Oh, Christ.
Oh, I'm done.
Might as well just sacrifice myself.
You know, let's...
I need an engineer.
An engineer is my favorite class, as you know.
I'm going to wake up for a loadout right now.
No, I don't want to
use that. Stick with this.
Actually, you know
what? Why not? I'm going to use it.
It's not what I really
want to do, but not very many
gameplays with this thing, so I figured why not?
I'll try it.
Got the spies. Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. That thing. Wow.
That thing's really bad.
That thing is really bad.
Man.
Wow, I shot twice. I didn't...
I hit him. I'm going to have to look
back at that and see how much ammo I actually got.
That was really bad.
Wow. Oh, somebody got a
collateral. I got to get like a
heat shot on somebody. That's not going to work.
No. I'm just going to get myself killed.
Oh, come on.
You're going to do what we like that? You're going to do what we like that?
Oh, this is...
You know what? Forget it. Not working out.
I'm not even going to pretend like I'm going to try and use this thing.
I said there's a...
Oh, nobody does this. There's no gameplays with this thing.
Maybe that's because it sucks.
They'll buff it, don't worry.
Watch out, spy. Spy, turn around, turn around, turn around.
I got you. I saved you.
I saved you, Johnny.
Not really, because he was a dead ringer.
Oh, you're done.
You're going to come around that corner and you're going to get yourself killed.
I told you.
Give me that crit.
Spy. Just bumped into a spy.
Can we just please win this game? Oh my god.
That's not a good place for that.
It has to go right here.
Get killed. Nice.
Destroy it. Put it right back.
Oh, come on.
Are you serious?
I saw that. That was not a bad...
Oh, god.
Alright.
Might as well put a teleporter down.
That's probably going to get sapped and destroyed anyways.
Not like it matters.
What the...
No assist. Crap.
Oh my god, leave me alone.
You know what? You're dead.
I'm going to punch you in the face.
God damn it.
We got a pyro on the team.
Oh, this is not looking so good.
Livecom.
Me getting my ass kicked.
Now, I could just stop talking and probably play
ten times better.
But, as you know,
that's not the fun of a livecom.
Alright, I can't be an engineer.
I got to be a power class.
This is not working out.
This is not working out at all.
Power class. Let's do it.
For the love of god.
They have this spawn camping.
Oh, man.
Okay, time to change this.
Alright.
Okay, got the scout.
Where is he? Where is he?
No, no. Alright, they're gone.
Where's that spy? Keep running into him.
Spy at spawn. Be careful, guys.
Oh, crap. I can get it.
Yeah, we got it. It's all good.
Get out of here, dude.
Somebody has to kill that guy.
Pyro time.
Yep, you saw it here.
You saw it here first, guys.
Rage pyros. Rage pyro.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's go with the default.
Default flamethrower.
Default shotgun.
I'm going to do it like this.
I'm doing it like this right now.
Yeah, we're doing it like this now.
Oh, the question is, yeah, he's going to kill me.
No, you're a spy again.
Spy's all over the place.
So what was that? Four classes
in five minutes?
Jerma, get it together here.
Jeez. Medic.
Come with me. We'll make this happen.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
Dude.
Oh, I would play
not...
Alright, whatever.
We are getting absolutely dominated
right now. This is just ugly.
This is really ugly.
Yeah, get out of here. Get out of town,
buddy. Check for spies.
Yeah, get out of here. Get out of town.
Where is he? There he is. Yeah, get out of town.
There's more of you.
I'm going to eat this sandwich. I'm going to die.
He's definitely a dead ringer.
I just don't know where he is.
I got to get up here. I'm going to do some...
Oh, yeah, of course. Of course
that's what's going on. Give me a break.
Oh, die, you little
squirrely mother... effer.
I get you. I got you.
You ain't getting away. You're dead.
Oh, come on.
Where's that medic?
Get out of here. Alright, alright.
You're good. You're cool. I just totally
stole you. Let's go.
You want to do this? Uh-oh.
Server's lagging out. What does it say?
Pyro. Hey, take the sandwich. Take the sandwich.
I'm going to get backstabbed in three, two, one.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it, guys.
I knew it.
Had to get rid of that soldier though.
Wow. This is bad.
Don't matter. Because I'm going to get out here
right now and I'm going to win the game. Ready?
Watch this. Ready?
No more screwing around. Are you a...
Okay. Okay. Yep.
So many spies.
Alright. Let's do it. We got it.
Alright. Stick with it, guys. Stick with it. We got this.
I need to heal. There we go.
Oh, I'm not winning this fight.
Get up there, Pyro. Come on. Get some damage.
There it is. There it is.
Oh, spy. Where are you?
Yeah. Yeah.
Get out of town. Oh, spy going to spawn.
Watch it. Gotta get on that cart.
But I have no life because the spy just took it.
Give me that birthday cake.
Oh, brass beast heavy.
No.
Oh.
God.
I want to take it back
and watch this and see how many times
I get killed by that spy.
I bet you it's...
I've died 23 times in this server.
I bet you
it's at least like a couple... I bet you it's at least
a dozen times I've died from that spy. Same spy.
We'll find out if I look.
Alright, I'm going to do some bird of prey
crap here. Here we go.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my
God.
I'm going to name this livecom
Spies Are Insane.
No, don't give them the satisfaction.
Alright, well, hopefully you guys enjoyed this
livecom. Check out my video on Pixel Enemy
and wish me luck at this wedding, guys.
It should be interesting.
I gotta do a speech and everything like I said before, so...
Take care, everybody.
See you all soon and take care, everybody.