Hi, you gotta go with that. I was I was thinking you were gonna say something to it just be like
My name is drama and this is my youtube channel and I'm playing with star. He's a fun friend
I'm actually also Gerber. I'm playing with Gerber. Yeah, I am
Hey, are you are you the room? Hey, you're not supposed to blow yourself up until the round starts. Oh
I
Was getting healed. That's why I'll do it right this time. I'm putting all eight of these friggin things right here
What the hell is that?
What the fuck is that? Hold on. Wait a second fun. You've been spawn quick. Here we go. Sticky jump, baby
What? Oh god tip. I was so confused. Oh
Okay, I was looking at the kill feed and I saw German 985
Somebody and I with a rocket I was like I didn't kill anybody with what the hell's going on
I was standing still and died. You have to understand something very important is you're not the real German
I really am I'm not you are the real German right now. That was the worst sticky jump
I think I've anyone could have ever done. I gotta get behind somebody now or get on the car. That works too. Bye
No, pyro. Yeah, come on spawn spawn spawn spawn spawn spawn health pack. Yeah
No
No, I'm not on the goddamn pyro
First wait take one second. I want you to look at how many spies we have on our team. Hold on
I killed y'all you shot that rocket and he reflected it into me and now you're dead
Look how many spies are on our team?
I was watching all five of them fighting a spy from the other team. It was brilliant
Just I gotta say it
Why the blue team's been losing five spies
There you go
I'm happy that in the fact that I killed you. I was awesome. That was pretty friggin hilarious
I think I might have to change classes. I'm not doing anything as a demo man right now. Let's go
What do you have? What do you have for a load-up right now? I dead ringer knife
Pretty much stock except dead ringer. All right
So are we gonna like try to fool the other team or something that guy's gonna I don't think they're gonna fall for it
I think they pretty much just no. Oh my god. There's I'm dead down down. I knew it. I knew this guy
No, no, I can't I can't in good conscience. I can't I can't do this anymore
They know why did why did like two people jump after me a teammate and an enemy just both jumped off the cliff after me
Off the cliff. Oh, yeah, they know I'm a spy. They're coming probably gonna win
I mean, it's taking a while, but we're getting there. I have confidence gotta have confidence. You have to have confidence
I mean, you know, it's like about fanboy moment
What's going on? Don't over why did I get uber'd?
Exactly. There's no one there. Um, oh he's behind
All you fools up there are done pyro get out of my face. All right, here we go. Here we go. You ready?
Where are you? Oh, I got I got uh, I'm up in their grill space. You're up in the grill space
What's gonna baby make it work make it happen. Make it happen, baby. Make it happen. It's just pyros everywhere
You and the cat make it happen
There's another pyro back here where they where these guys come in from every time I kill one
There's immediately one to replace it. It doesn't matter how many I've killed
It's a little ridiculous, please. Heal me, please. Please. Heal me. Oh
He heard me good. Did my voice chat work? Yeah, get get launched
Launched you prick. I almost got another buff. What the hell keeps doing that
Am I just going crazy and like hitting myself on the screen pyros three pyros? I counted three
Should just go pyro and pyro the pyros could also I could go heavy too. That's a pretty big counter to pyro
Hold the button down on their face
Walking backwards is pretty good, too. Yeah. Well, we're on it. We're on it. Could we win this kid? No
Oh, no, we got two pyros coming up the backside. You're uh, John. You don't do it. I'm joining him going pyro
Get off that point spy. Here we go. Let's do it. Get out of here pyro. All right time to play the pyro counter
I'm going heavy weapons. No play pyro. What the hell happened here next time you get a chance to come out of spawn
Just take a look at what take a look at that like scene. That's right out in front of the spawn
What's that? What would I there was like a heavy taunting out there? Yeah, he's dead. He stays
This is a dead heavy body next to the teleporter. Oh, hey pyro. How you doing? Oh, they have a sentry destroy the sentry destroy the sector
Oh, hey, what's up another pyro? No, shut up. Destroy the sector. It's dead. I got it. Hey
Hey, what's up three pyros moving as one?
What what was that?
They were like inside of each other. Is this guy like multi boxing like five pyros?
It's just one guy playing the game really well. Oh, we got this. We got it. Oh, baby. Boom
German 95 number one. Yeah, see I top score. You're so good pyro heavy pyro
I'm amazed. All right, when you've respawned we're gonna try to move as the same person. Okay, we'll be the same guy
We need to you know, when you have like three legged races, that's us
Okay, you ready? This is going to be so difficult, right? I can't even see you. I guess you're okay
I'm like I'm trying to like stay into you. That's a spy trotty trotty trotty
I don't know where he went trying to shoot at the same time as you. Yeah, we got him
Okay, back up back up getting the small health kit. Oh spy. Yeah, you punk get out of here. Where'd you go?
I died. He spied me. Oh, he did I died for you. You have two legs once again
I want four legs. We'd just like to draw attention this match to how many snipers we have. Oh, we I keep seeing snipers
I'm like, oh, hey, what is this guy doing? What the hell was that?
That guy was standing behind me as a pyro. I almost freaked me out
I felt like I was on the other team
You ever have that happen where like somebody's just like not doing anything that is a walking around around you and you think you're on
The other team. Yeah, I feel like we're playing call of duty right now
I feel like the spawns are all over the place. I feel like everyone just appears behind me
A lot of spies just doing their thing like this scout. The scouts just like behind everybody. This guy's dead
The spy got me again. I just every time. Oh, come on. That wasn't a headshot both. Yeah
That would have been such an amazing shot. Too bad. I'm not good enough
I wish you could have saw that that was great. Oh
That's a highlight and that's a spy and that's a goddamn pyro and that's another
Where are these people coming from? Really? I see what you mean
He's dead. No, he's right. Oh, yeah, you want to get body blocked. Is that what you want to have happen?
You want to get clubbed? Oh, that's you can jump wherever you want. Oh
What do you know about that slam dunk slam dunk? You want some peanut butter with that jam? Oh
Mike man, that's how I walk off the bram. Oh, there's a pyro behind me. Okay
No more sniper. It's serious business time. Yeah, I think I've stayed alive
I don't think I've stayed alive for more than 15 seconds. That's okay
Half this video is going to be the respawn time in the top corner. Just just slice that just cut it
Just cut it up crop. It didn't happen. Oh, they've got a heavy pocketed. I just want to win
No backstab by this same guy every time. Leave me alone, dude. There are other people here
Give me the health just