Hello, hello, hello. Hi. Yes, we're here. Well, that was what we'd like to call an adventure.
So for those of you that don't know, I had a plan today. I was thinking of starting the ace attorney.
See, no, I'm not gonna wait. I'm gonna wait. I'm gonna wait because there are people probably
coming in. Remember, we're watching the Super Bowl. So am I. There's a long list of what's
going on today. First of all, free nothing. Patriots just scored. I don't have a TV.
I don't have cable that can watch this game and I'm not watching it right now a lot.
I'm getting the like website updates on what happened. That's bad. I forgot today was the
Super Bowl. Okay. I had, I did not know this last night, late last night when we were like,
oh yeah, tomorrow we're gonna do ace attorney. That sounds like a good idea. Let's do ace
attorney tomorrow during the Super Bowl. I was like, ah, I woke up this morning and two things
happened. First thing that happened is the Super Bowl is today. Do you know how I knew that?
Because my entire family sent me messages telling me how excited they are. And I was
like, what are they excited for? It was like, I have like 40 messages from my family
and they all, they're all dressed in Patriots. This is all the Super Bowl is today.
I forgot. And so the plan was gonna play ace attorney, but you know, that's just the way it
is. Ace attorney, Phoenix Wright. And that didn't turn out the way that I wanted to for two
reasons. One, yes, Super Bowl. And I wanted to pay attention to it because the Patriots
are in it. That's my team. You know, until the Raiders get here, that's my team. Problem
two, uh, ace attorney. I have, I bought them all on the iPad. So iPad comes in sick. There's my iPad
got a crack in it, but it still works. My splitter. Okay. Yeah. I packed that one. Remember
I packed that one. I don't have the audio splitter, so I couldn't capture the audio
from my iPad. Somehow it got lost in the move, got lost in the mail. Thought about potentially
emulating like, all right, I bought them all. I have them all on iPad. Let's whatever. Like
this idea came out last night, right? Like ace attorney. I didn't really plan that much on it.
It was like last night I bought them and like, I'm going to try it this morning and
you see how it went. Um, the emulators, they're, they're all removed from the internet,
at least on a couple of the places that I thought. Cause you know, I all, I own the
titles maybe out of desperation. I've bought them, I own them. And then I heard that there's
going to be a PC remaster of ace attorney coming out very soon. So I'm sitting here going,
Oh God damn it. What the fuck? When are those coming out? So what I've decided to do today
is I still own ace attorney and I can still get it to work. And so we have to get a
new audio splitter. Here's an emulation. I don't want to talk about emulators,
no emulation. Not yet. I'm not talking about that yet. So what I've decided to do is because
Super Bowls today, I went through, I jumped through a bunch of hoops and I was able to
get this. Well, hold on. There's like a logo on here. I don't want, I don't want like a,
hold on. There's like a, I don't want to show this thing. Oh, give me a second.
It's like two logos on here. All right. Well, you know what? We'll just show the back.
No, I was going to go like this. So this is what I was able to get today. Like let's rewind.
Okay. So after all, I was going to play a ace attorney and I jumped through a bunch of hoops
and I was able to get this. I just blitzed the league too. One of my favorite games of
all time on the old generation console. So you're probably asking yourself, I mean it is,
it is Patriots Day, right? It is like the Patriots are like gone. So I made sure to get
my Patriots clothes on today. Hey, can you tell? I knew it was a fucking goddamn Superbowl.
10% of my wardrobe guys. Do you understand? Go Patriots. It's desynced, which shouldn't be.
What? You're going to desync me? Oh, it is desync. What a piece of crap. Hold on. But
yeah, uh, blitz the league too. It even blitz the league. If you guys didn't know,
this is where Mortal Kombat got their horrible, break the person's neck closeup blood comes out
of their mouth animations. This is not a regular football game by a long shot.
This is the game where all those crazy brutal things that happen in Mortal Kombat,
this is where they came from. Same company. This game is fucking hilarious. It's amazing.
And I got it today. I got this today. I activated Jax powers and I got, well, I had some help,
but you know. How do I put this in? I don't believe you. Is it Mortal Kombat older?
Mortal Kombat's zoom in. You'll see what I'm talking about. Once I like punch a guy in the
nuts and like his balls explode, like that, I'm not, I'm just saying that that happens in
this game because it does. You'll understand. How do I, I'm not used to this PlayStation.
This is all very quick. We got this set up immediately. Who scored? Nobody. It's still
three down. I don't know how to put the disc inside of this PlayStation. I'm not kidding.
This is bad. How do I open this? Does this have discs? Anybody know how to do this?
Where do I put the disc in? It's on the left. Just push it in. It's not on the left.
Wait a minute. Hold on. Somebody help me. Hold on. I gotta move some stuff.
Is there a disc in there? No, there's no disc in there already. For a second, I thought
stupid invaders was in here. Where's the, wait, wait, wait. Let's go. Okay. No, I got it.
No. All right. I'm turning the fucking webcam on. You guys have to help me here.
I don't get it. I don't get it. You ready? How do I, how the fuck do I put a disc in
here? Where does it go? There's nothing here. There's nothing there. Slide it. I've never
seen a PlayStation like that. I'll slide the top open. No way. Slide it open. Oh, fuck my
camera. We had to activate Jax this morning. I have a controller, right? Okay. Let's delete
two going in into the weird like Willy Wonka machine. What? I've owned like three different
PlayStation 3s. I've never seen a slide the top. Here we go. Welcome to Blitz the League.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't do that. Welcome to Blitz the League 2,
right? If there's something wrong with this disc, the last hour was jumping through hoops
to get this. Oh, thank God. Anybody score? Who has the ball? A mandatory game data install
is required for Blitz. Yeah. Please don't turn off the fucking PlayStation. Oops. Wait, what?
Oh, shit. I forgot. Where's this camera even pointing? This camera sucks. You know who's
got a real monopoly on the video camera industry? Logitech. They are, they are the
Kleenex of cameras. It's bullshit. There's like four cameras stalling. No, I got 17%. I don't
want you to, I don't want you guys to know what the percentage is. Just use a cam link
and a real camera. I don't want to like hook up a DSLR up here. I don't, I don't,
do you guys think I, what would you think? I want you to see my face in like 4k.
You think sometimes I look fucked up now. Imagine what I would look like in every
pore, every pocket of my face being shown. No, you're not getting the Ren and Stimpy
close-up camera on my face. I'm sorry, guys. What are we at? 31. Who has the ball? The,
I can't believe I forgot the fucking Super Bowl was today. And it was like a perfect,
it was a perfect opportunity. So I streamed the last two days in a row. This is three
days in a row, right? I was gonna, oh, maybe I'll take today off. I would have like
probably watched the Super Bowl, but I can't even watch the Super Bowl. So uneven side
brides. That's not true. I tried as hard as I could in the morning to shape them. See,
look one, two, right in the right spot. I mean, I may have ripped, I may have butchered
this side a little. They're not uneven. They're just unorganized. There's a difference.
They're actually uneven. No, they're just unorganized. They're uneven as fuck. No,
they're not. They are, they're just, they just don't look right because I need a haircut.
And when I get a haircut, they just, they take them out. Speaking of haircuts,
I need to get one of those too. They actually are uneven. I can't buy, I can't buy,
the camera's right here. You guys are right here. Video game is here. OBS preview is over
here right now. I can't, there's no way I can fucking do this. I'd have to go into the
bathroom, cut your own hair. What's the percentage? 65. He shouldn't, I don't know.
I think it might have something, you know what I think it is? So I don't know about you
guys, but I have like, I have like an uneven face. So when I'm like turning and looking
this way, going like this, my eyes are in a different, this eye is not in the right
position. It's like squished in. Then my nose is like bigger on this side. So when
I'm like shaving over here, I'm like blocking my view. When I'm shaving over here,
I have like two different viewpoints because my face is uneven. Your face is fucked up.
Yeah? So? Your face is fucked. No one's face is completely even. Thank you Dr. Phil.
Second quarter? When is the Super Bowl halftime show? Is that free? Is it free to see,
to watch the halftime show? Don't, doesn't every TV channel all at the same time turn
on the halftime show? I thought that was like legally what happens. Like you're
in the middle of law and order or something and it's just like,
you're in the right stuff baby I was born. It just goes to it, right? Every network.
Installation complete. Please quit the game through the PS button and restart. Blitz League
2. You got it. I hope there's enough battery in this. What am I doing? Okay, quit game. Yes.
It's free on the CBS website, but I'll go to jail if I play that, right?
On stream. You can't do that on stream. That's the quickest way to go to jail.
Look at those pores. Shut up. Any score? Who has the ball? Patriots have the ball. It's
3-0. Did they get a field goal? I need play-by-play from you guys. High definition HD gaming.
Here we go. I'm so excited. This game is amazing. Touchdown? Can you get 100% of
the trophies from me? Blitz League 2. Not rated. Interaction's not rated by the ESRB.
So they're talking about when guys get like punched in the balls and they explode. That's
what they're talking about. They can't rate that. By the way, there's no actual NFL teams in this
game. It's like the Boston Brew House. It's like the Cincinnati Steelers. There's no actual
licensed teams. I can't wait to play this. Okay, so let's go ahead. We're probably
going to get this whole thing claimed from the... We probably need to turn that off.
Yeah, we have to turn this. We have to turn this off. I'm sorry, guys,
but the whole VOD's going to get muted. The rest of this is fine. Difficulty? Yeah,
no vibration. Get that out of here. Video? Brightness is fine. I don't remember exactly how
to play, but I know some things. We can do training camp. No, I gotta do the Super Bowl
right now. It's going on right now. No, training camp. Receiving defense. Yeah, you
have to stick syringes in your players and stuff. All right, we're going to do
watch and learn how to be a pro. Rushing. It's a game of inches. Let's just... I gotta remind
my brain. You got like three hours. That shit's going to go on forever. No, dude,
it's already almost halftime. This stream can only be as long as the Super Bowl.
And then I gotta get off all my Super Bowl Patriots gear and turn the stream off.
It won't look right. All right, superstar, you look ready to go. This should be easy
enough. Just take the handoff and bang out a few yards. Press X to hike the ball,
gain 10 yards. That's a burst down. That is the way to execute. I think some people are
going to come to the stream and not understand. Power move. How do you do a power move?
And that's what we call a top down. This game is so good. Evade.
Let's see if you can juke the pros. Looking good. Don't let up now.
I'm so sad they didn't make a new one. It's freestyle time. So that's a freestyle.
So right stick is... Good job. It's almost showtime, baby.
Just wait. Just wait. It doesn't matter. I don't know anything about football. All I
know is the Patriots are good. Tom Brady's cool. Tom Brady wins. Rings. That's all I
know. I don't know anything else. I know first down means that they get to play it again,
right? It's like getting... It's like re-spins. I just made a casino reference. Why did I do that?
I don't even like the casino. The casino sucks. Okay, how do I do that? First down.
Okay, hold down L2 to enter clash mode and use evade or power to make a clash move. This
is what we're talking about here. Yep. See? I can slow down time and shit.
Each clash icon adds a pip to your unleash meter. Finish filling your unleash meter
by performing a two-move combo in clash. There's one. There's two. There's three.
Look at the dumb shit you can do. So now I can break somebody's neck.
Every damn penny. Get out there and unleash on the first offender that gets in your way.
Score a rushing touchdown and then enter the following code. X, X, X, circle.
That guy dove from all the way across the fucking map. Oh! What's the code? I told you
that's nothing. Oh god. This is... Outstanding. I want five more just like that.
That guy just landed on his back very, very... It was like pillows. He had other issues going on.
I didn't do that. All right, let's do some passing training. If I jumped as high as I could and
landed directly on my back as flat as I could, that wouldn't happen to me. My stomach wouldn't
explode. Yeah, it's so fun to... Time to test out that arm of yours. Keep it simple. Just hit
the first open receiver you see. Tap as a lob. Hold it down for a bullet. That's not bad. He knows
what he's doing. Clash after your quarterback evade blitzes. Run it by gaining yards and scoring
on offense. Yeah. Gain 30 yards to fill part of the clash meter. That was poetry in motion.
Keep it up. This sounds like young German. Okay, so you have a good arm, but how are
your feet? I am young. Think you can avoid getting planted during the blitz?
Pressing L2 to enter clash. When defenders are in range,
arrows will appear. Move the right stick towards an arrow to evade.
You can do better than that? Oh, it sounds like young you. What? That was weak sauce and you
know it. Give me something better, something spicy. Yeah, he sounds like young.
Weak sauce and you know it. Give me something better, something spicy. This is John Travolta.
No, um, what's his name? There it is. All right.
That was just what I was looking for. Not John. What's his name? John Cusack. You've got the D pissed
off now and they're coming for you. All right, execute QB, unleash evade and move the right
stick towards an arrow when a defender's in range. Maybe you should try out for basketball.
I think I'm gonna snap this guy's neck. When you get unleashed, that's how you do the
horrible shit. This isn't college anymore, kid. You have to produce.
Show me what you've got. Towards the, towards the rusher, right?
This isn't college anymore, kid. You have to produce.
You're not even going to make the practice squad at this rate. How the fuck do I do that?
I mean, it's probably a really strange time. I know you can do better than that.
It's Jay Moore. Who did I say? I said somebody completely wrong. Who did I say this was?
The arrow? Yeah, I gotta wait for the arrow, but it's like, it pops up in a tenth of a second.
I gotta go towards the arrow. Like, I hit him so hard that I electrocuted his brain.
I didn't get tackled. Looking good. Don't let up now. You're looking like
the real deal, kid. All right, square passing touchdown. Now it's time to put all the pieces
together and give the fans a real show. Get in that end zone. Oh shit, I have to catch it.
What? Oh, I didn't do the code. I got tackled. Square, square, triangle, triangle.
That's a touchdown though. All right. Square, square.
Why am I doing this to my own teammate? That wasn't my own teammate.
It was like cartoon and punches. All right. Rushing, passing. We got that pretty much down.
This is very quick. They don't make games like this anymore. You know, when you could
just punch people on the other team or on your own team for that matter.
51 seconds left in the second quarter. And oh boy, third and two at the LA 40.
Like anyone cares. Word around here is you have hands like flypaper. Well,
put the ball in the air and show me what you can do.
An open receiver. That's what I'm seeing here, kid. That was a nice catch, but let's see how
you do under real pressure. So you do a clash catch. Take some of your clash energy and
make sure you come down with the pass. Catch must be at least 20 yards. Okay. Got it.
And I broke the tackle too. I'm still good. Now that is the way to execute. It's fourth
and long here. So what are we going to do? Press and hold L2 while the ball is in the air
to enter clash. Catch that deep ball. Yeah, it's a guaranteed catch if you have full meter.
Don't let up now. That end zone is calling to you. Haul ass downfield and give the
networks their play of the week. Hold L2, the ball's in the air, press triangle to make
the intended receiver do an unleashed catch when the ball is in range.
Uh, I didn't do it. These guys have made out of peanut brittle. These bones have made it a
candy floss. It's so delayed. The bones break like five seconds later. They have pretty bad
lag. All right. So I have to make them do it. So like this.
There we go. No, I was trying to hurt that guy. Freaking standing. What's a touchdown without
a good celebration? We're receiving touchdown then do XX circle circle. Get in the end zone,
pick a spot and show the fans your moves. No. Is it halftime? All right. Who's the
halftime show? Oh, it's halftime. No, that's going to be embarrassing. Nevermind.
And then what was it? XX square square? I don't remember what it was. Give us a
halftime show. Uh, I can't, I can't do a, I don't, I'm not prepared for this.
That's a fail. Why? XX circle circle, not square. Damn it. Beer chuck.
That's a $50,000 penalty. That one's a keeper. Great job.
Is that allowed in football? Uh, no, no, and none of it is actually.
Pain, injuries, glory. This is where we get to see the real pain.
The whole point of blitz the league is you're trying to make the other team injured.
You're trying to put people out, hurt them to a point where they can't play in the game anymore.
That's the point of this game. That's not the point of American football.
Looks like the offense is trying to pass on you. Are you going to take that?
X while tackling the ball carrier. Don't show those receivers what happens when they
try and catch a pass in your territory. I'm sorry. I thought you said you had skills.
Well, I need to know how to select a guy. Press X while tackling the ball carrier. So
where's my character? Hey, why don't you get your damn head in the game and try again?
Um, I, you need to tell me who I'm, where my character is. How do I select a new character?
Real deal. Looks like the switch into the run.
Press and hold L2 and press X to execute a dirty hit. That's what we want right here.
Dirty hit. That is the way to execute. Those fat linemen are trying to get in your face.
Like the lard asses they are.
That's a success. Nothing brings in the ratings like a sack.
Damn it. I didn't get any more kid. You have to produce.
It's not going to be ready. You got to go run right through.
You had skills. Now prove it. I'm also trying to do it. I don't have any time.
He's too good. He like gets rid of the ball immediately.
I know I'm the defender, but look at how quickly he gets rid of the ball.
Sack him. Sack him. That counts.
Give me this guy.
All right, he throws the ball. By the time my character takes a step, the ball's gone.
Are you using L2? Oh yeah. Jesus Christ.
Guys, I'm doing it correctly. I'm holding L2 and press. I've played this game before.
The tutorial. How is that a fail? I sack the quarterback.
It's just the tutorial. They forgot to program the
quarterback to hold the ball for more than a tenth of a second.
I'm sorry. I thought you said you had skills. Now prove it.
What the fuck?
I'm going to go with another guy. I don't know. Why am I getting failures for sacking
the quarterback? All right. Do you see how fast he's throwing this ball?
And she's in a nursing home. Pathetic. That counts. That's a dirty hit. Jesus.
Christ. Time to make the ball carrier cry for his mama. Unleash on him with everything you've got.
All right. Unleash all the ball character press. Yeah, I got it. Suplex him on his head.
Oh, that guy's. You nailed that one. Keep going.
We didn't break any bones or hurt him. All right. Last thing.
And then we're going to do career mode. I'm going to do the whole career in the time
to take for. Who is the halftime show? Have we figured it out? SpongeBob.
It's not SpongeBob. Although that would be great if it was.
If you're going to play dirty, you need to learn to call your shots.
Hit the ball carrier hard. Pick the body part of your choice and make sure he doesn't get.
Oh, yeah. SpongeBob is the halftime show. That is absolute bullshit.
Perform dirty hit. Pick an injury using left and then pump it up by rapidly pressing X.
Step on it. Oh, OK. Right. I see. I see. That was weak.
I remember this. You have to, like, pick a place and then spam X.
You should try out for basketball. That guy ran into his own teammate.
Yeah. Bruce, those ribs. That was poetry in motion. Keep it up. Injuries happen.
That's why the training staff has a ready supply of juice.
Take aim, find the vein and get your comrade back on the field.
Position your syringe using left and then juice the injured player by pressing X.
Get a 50% or better result.
Here we go. Yes. You get steroids.
OK, here we go. Use a left stick to place the needle as close to the middle of target as
possible. The closer you get to the center, the quicker your player will get back into the
game. That was just what I was looking for. Sometimes the Jews just get in the middle.
You got to grab hold of what's broken and wrench it back into place.
Allow your player to get in and pull left and right to prepare for a bone set.
Then move left and right in indicated directions when prompted. Get a 50% or better.
Oh, that's a broken shoulder portion.
OK, move the left stick and right stick to their respected targets.
Once the targets are in place, mimic the arrows that appear to snap the bone back into place.
Sorry, dude. Sorry, dude.
Great intensity on that one. Keep going.
So I know how to play. Let's do it.
He's ready. So there are lots of things. We got campaign.
Oh, God. That's a whole storyline here.
Battaglia levels the quarterback. It's a fumble.
Football was coach thinking. Ten seconds left in a tie game.
And the Nightmare cough up the football on their own 20.
Frank Kelly. Is that the John Madden guy?
Got this one in the bag, sunshine.
The quarterback is down.
Looks like Battaglia may have ended his career.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Quit your whining.
Just stick him with a syringe.
Seamless transition into gameplay. Let's go.
I don't know how to kick a ball, though.
I have no idea how to kick a ball. There wasn't a tutorial for that.
Oh, yeah. It's a fumble.
It's a fumble.
Neck break. So face mask running the whole time.
You'd be thrown out of the league to see Kingpin up in the...
Kid, you're going to be huge.
The first two-way player this league's ever seen.
I've got every Fortune 500 company panting to get into bed with you.
Like horny bridesmaids at the wedding of the century.
Do you really want to rock the boat?
Okay, kid, we're fucking on.
Excuse me, commissioner.
I wanted to introduce you to my new client.
Great to meet you, son.
Boys, take a look at our next big star.
Big star?
Is this like the opening GTA cinematic?
He's a one-man-walking franchise.
Hey, you know what? That's his new nickname, franchise.
Well, it's the evil mafia guy.
Franchise. I dig that.
Well, you'll certainly be the franchise player for the riot.
L.A. traded up to the number one pick to take you.
I don't like that voice.
I'm sorry, sir.
Not evil.
I won't be able to play for L.A.
Good one, sir. Good one.
It's no joke.
The only place I'm going to be able to play is in my hometown.
You'll play for the team that drafts you.
I'm sorry about this, but my mind's made up.
SpongeBob is not home.
Then he'll go play center field for New York.
They just offered him $17 million a year for seven years, guaranteed.
That's the kind of athlete you're looking at here.
Look, everybody knows you expanded your league too quickly.
I mean, six teams in five years.
Come on.
Now you're choking on it.
And your so-called owners raised the money for those new teams.
So you had to offer stock to the public.
And now you get a once in a lifetime cash cow who could save your league.
SpongeBob.
All he's asking for is to play for his hometown team.
SpongeBob is in the halftime.
They're doing sweet victory.
Thank you all for coming.
Today's a special day.
Are you kidding me?
My client.
I thought you guys were just fucking around.
Most of you have been following his career as he smashed multiple collegiate records.
Now he's poised through the sand in the league.
So let's get the questions rolling.
Fogs one at a time.
Scott Smith, League Tribune.
How do you feel your presence on offense affects your teammates?
I like to go out there and deliver good passes and let my playmakers do the work.
As a running back, I know that I need to go out there and control the game.
They can rely on me to make the big catch.
I have the versatility to line up and block or split out wide.
What do I want to do?
I think isn't quarterback the most fun?
Quarterbacks like the most fun in a football game.
I'd go out there and deliver the passes.
I like to go out there and deliver good passes and let my playmakers do the work.
The man is a playmaker.
Pure and simple.
Next question.
Now you're going to play offense and defense.
I'm a threat to the quarterback every play.
Uh, they can't contain me.
Any run or short yardage pass that enters my territory is going to be,
they're going to pay a price.
I'm the general of the secondary.
I'm everywhere I need to be.
I want that safety.
I'm the ultimate shutdown corner throwing to my receiver.
Nobody, I, I don't know what any of this means,
but I know that I want to be a safety.
I want to be the general.
I want to be the quarterback and I want to be the general.
And I want to be done safely.
I'm the general of the secondary.
I'm everywhere I need to be.
As you can see, confidence isn't an issue.
Who's next?
How about the looker in the front row?
Jennifer Mendez.
My readers are wondering what did you do for fun in your youth?
Uh, does running from the, I was best dodgeball mostly.
Um, what do I want?
Speed?
Strength?
I want agility.
I was the best dodgeball player in my neighborhood.
Plus two agility.
Little did the old neighborhood know they had a future super store on their hands.
Okay.
How about the gentleman in the back with his hand up?
Thanks.
Did you play any other sports in college?
Uh, we got base.
My curveball could have gotten me in pros.
Collegiate champion wrestler.
Track and field.
I played rugby as well as football.
Twice the pain.
Ooh.
Yep.
I play rugby as well as football.
Twice the pain.
You know, I want a good tackle.
I want to be able to hurt people.
This kid could have gone pro in a half dozen sports.
He's just that type of athlete.
Okay.
Next.
Jeff Jones, Midwest One News.
What's the thing most opponents don't realize about you?
I'm a team player.
I'll do the dirty work.
Glory doesn't matter.
Just the win.
I studied martial arts.
I know just where to hit them to make it hurt.
I think that's the one.
My hands are like flypaper once I've got the ball.
I'm holding on to it.
Catching me is one thing.
Bring me down is a whole different story.
I studied martial arts.
So I know just where to hit them to make it hurt.
They'll be learning soon enough, huh?
Let's get someone who has not been called on yet.
I watch anime.
What have you been focusing on in the off season?
Hitting the blocking sled.
Full contact drills.
Running the obstacle course on a one-on-one.
Maybe.
I think any more strength.
Oh, no, maybe full contact.
Block, tackle.
No, what's BKT?
Back tackle?
I'm all about the full contact drills.
Got to train hard to play hard.
Take it from me.
This kid has been working his ass off all summer.
You're a QB with full tackle points.
He'll be ready to start day one.
Who's next?
Ms. Mendez, you have another question?
If you had to give yourself a nickname, what would it be?
Nickname.
The playmaker, the enforcer, the freak of the wall.
The enforcer.
Same as in college.
Folks can call me the enforcer.
Can we quote you on that?
Yeah, yeah, kid.
The laughing?
All right.
Looks like we only have time for a few more questions.
OK, Scott, go.
Which current player do you model your game after?
The speed demon.
Wide receiver.
The bullhawk.
Full stop.
Ezekiel.
The enforcer.
Me.
Laughback.
Running back.
The enforcer.
Don't hate me for this,
but I model my game after my boy, Bruno Bataglia.
We're just about out of time here.
Let's get in one final question.
Do an archer build.
Right there.
What do you want people to say about you five years from now?
I was one of the quickest guys to ever put on a pair of cleats.
Everything that I put my hands on, I'd bring it.
That kid could sure pack one hell of a punch.
You need a jet pack to be able to keep up with that guy.
Punching.
Five years, huh?
That kid sure packs one hell of a punch.
Ladies and gentlemen, that's all we have time for today.
And I want to thank you all for coming.
And I hope that you are as safe as I am about seeing him this coming season.
Why does it taunt me in every game?
Do I have to get taunted in every fucking game I play?
I don't know why.
Blazing fast scrambler with a lot of tackle.
First name, kid.
First name, Jax?
Overall, C.
I don't know if this is a Jax.
Frank?
Name him Pizza.
Mr. Super Bowl.
I like that.
The last name already is Franchise.
Oh, there he is.
Mr. Dave Super Bowl.
That's perfect.
But what if you never get to the Super Bowl?
Select your city.
All right.
Where is it?
Nope.
There it is.
Las Vegas.
The Las Vegas.
Oh, I get to name the team.
The Las Vegas Aces.
No, the Las...
Eat this one.
The Las Vegas Dealers.
Yeah, the Vegas Dealers.
The Vegas Boomers.
Terrible Boomer.
I'm not going to be the fucking Boomers.
The Las Vegas Super Bowlers.
No, this is so dumb.
Las Vegas Super Bowlers.
I can't even fit it.
Mr. Super Bowl of the Super Bowlers.
That word doesn't look right.
Is that correct?
Bowlingles?
Is that weird?
All right.
The Las Vegas Super Bowls.
Mr. Super Bowl on the team.
Anyway, that's a pretty...
That's pretty Vegas.
Is it just a bowl?
It has to just be like a bowl, right?
A middle finger.
Mr. Super Bowl of the Super Bowlers.
All right.
These two images?
This is just evolved version of George Washington.
This is Super Saiyan Washington.
We got a club.
What the fuck is that thing?
There are too many icons.
How about just a terrible default one?
I mean, come on.
How many icons?
Okay, we got to the end.
We got to do dice.
We're in Las Vegas.
And the team colors.
We've got to be the German 985 official colors.
A little darker, I think.
Maybe a little bit lighter.
Like the light is bouncing in the right spot, you know?
Here's the uniform.
Holy fuck, that's ugly.
It's not.
That is very ugly.
Home uniform.
Helmet style.
And this is just like a...
I need to swap it so it doesn't look...
What did italics say?
Polly Pocket?
Shut up!
No, this needs to be like that.
This is fine.
Like the...
Okay, that looks cool.
I'll keep that one.
All right.
Now, how do I...
Okay. Jersey.
That looks a lot better.
Right there.
Jersey font.
Super Bowl?
What?
Oh, right.
That's the name of the team.
I thought that...
I was like, what the fuck?
I like that.
Pants?
No.
I gotta break it up a little bit.
It's got...
I gotta break it up a little.
It looks so bad.
Socks?
Where's the Star Wars socks, please?
So we got...
Mr. Super Bowl.
Captain of the Super Bowls.
He's pistachio ice cream, man.
Are we still at the halftime show?
How long is this shit?
Agent.
Keep them on the best supplements you can afford.
And don't forget about socializing.
Hit the club scene.
Make a name for yourself off the field as well.
All right.
So we got the trainer.
Roster stats.
Lifestyle.
I think you can go to jail in this game, if I remember.
You can get arrested for breaking stuff and punching people.
All right.
Wins to advance five.
Need...
I got seven division games remaining.
$100,000.
Trainer.
Juicing.
Oh, you can take drugs.
Now, okay.
Training.
Train your starting players yourself or have the team's trainer take care of it.
It's your call.
I want to do the training myself.
No, I don't.
This is way too many people.
Assign the trainers automatically.
Juicing.
You can juice up to three players each week
and different juices are more suited to different positions.
Keep an eye on your risk meter when buying illegal drugs.
As risk gets higher, so do the chances of getting busted by the league.
So should I take drugs?
No, not...
We don't need to do this.
Not yet.
Upgrades.
All right.
So for tackle, it's $105,000.
I don't have enough money.
We're just going to do it.
We're just going to play.
Lifestyle.
Girlfriends and sponsors.
These...
I haven't even made a name for myself.
Cheap Helm.
These cheaply made lids are as old as the league helmet policy.
They barely offer more protection than your skull.
So I don't have any sponsors.
Not yet.
I got to make a name for myself.
I got to...
Let's go.
Las Vegas must stay within five points at the final score to win.
I can bet money on my own team.
Max bet.
The Philadelphia Brawlers live up to their names with their style of play.
They cheat as much as they can and get away with far more than they should.
Defensive end, H.J. Latchaw was just another unruly Philly fan last year.
Until a fight spilled onto the field and Latchaw beat his ass to earn himself a child on the ball.
Pressed his history.
Just like a fat guy fan that came and beat everybody up.
Just the WWE NFL.
No, this is not an NFL.
This is the Blitz the League League.
There he is.
They got dirty defense, but they have very poor offense.
So they play dirty and they cheat, but they don't score very many points.
Remember, it's 30 yards for a first down.
You know, I was hanging out the pool this morning before the game.
There he is.
What?
Why?
Maybe I had a diaper.
Oh, I love this game.
All right, we're going to go with uh, we're going to go with a
world record trail.
Passing play.
All right, got some yards.
Got a little yardage.
Seven yards.
Las Vegas diapers.
Boy, HP float.
One of them thinks we know what the hell we're why I didn't make the away uniform.
Watch this.
I didn't do it early enough.
There's no nudity.
What are you talking about nudity?
Oh, there's people dancing in the background.
Oops.
It's all right.
This is the hotline Miami team.
Oh, you dumb ass.
God damn it.
No, I'm going for it.
I'm going for it.
And they bring him down.
Las Vegas exploits an opening in the defense for some real yardage on that play.
We'll go with speed.
Uh, let's do uh, half back, double back.
Big series of downs upcoming.
All in about the 24.
All right.
That was bullshit.
What are you guys supposed to be?
Please tell me that wasn't his knee.
Hail Mary into the end zone.
And watch this.
I'm gonna fuck his wrong quarterback.
Perfect example of why they call him whatever it is they call him.
All right.
Now I gotta, I gotta kick it.
I gotta get a field goal here.
Field goal.
Fake field goal pass.
I need, I want two points.
That's a two point conversion, ladies and gentlemen.
Regular kickoff.
I don't know how to do this though.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, take him down.
Okay.
So I'm on defense now.
We're going to go with uh, we're going to make cover plays.
Man up.
I'm the man in the back.
No, not very many yardage.
I'm good.
First, the first quarter's already over.
The first quarter as Las Vegas leads by eight.
Why does someone's balls explode?
You just, wait.
They'll happen very shortly.
Oh fuck.
Delphia gets some monster yardage on that play.
Don't forget about the bet.
I gotta be within five points.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
I almost got the quarterback too.
Shit.
Goal line.
Just bump.
Everybody fucking just get in there.
This one thing has the safety.
It's all right.
They're only going to get one point.
No, they're going for it.
All right.
No, you don't get it.
No such thing as pass interference in this game.
Oh, we're going to catch this.
Why doesn't everybody just get it?
Shit.
I got a time loop there.
Philadelphia has a super move where they're going to be able to hurt me real soon.
This one right here.
First down and 30.
I gotta be careful.
They could...
Something bad could happen right now.
What the fuck just happened?
Oh no.
I was trying to...
Okay.
I thought that was a running play.
Fuck.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going to have to kick a field ball.
Oh yeah.
We're tearing up the field here.
Let's do a trick play.
How about slip and dip?
I'm going with a slip and dip.
Oh no.
What did you do to my brain?
Am I dead?
Oh come on.
He turned off my brain.
It's all right.
He's only up three plays.
I brought it back to life.
All right.
I got to be careful.
I got to get...
I got to make a play here.
What?
Oh, how about stream?
Why did I do that?
Because I can.
No game.
They're taking a timeout.
What down is it?
Third down.
All right.
Let's stay...
Let's crush them with chaos.
I'm going to stay back.
Really?
You got to be kidding me.
That was two tackles that he...
He dodged them both.
He dodged two tackles?
Just fucking block it.
Get in there.
Don't mind.
All I need is one...
I need to touch it.
I need to touch it and I win the game.
All right.
Is there...
Oh no.
No.
They keep turning my brain off.
It's going to be another fumble.
Isn't it?
No.
Hold him still.
Hang on, buddy.
Only have three plays.
Only one stamina loss.
I need one more blip.
I got to...
Okay.
I got to get some yards here.
I want someone to knock that jackhole out of the game.
Perry.
We're going with this.
I'm going to go run and play.
I have to...
I have to get a good hit here.
Ow.
Oh, damn.
Timeout.
I'm going to go with the guy on the left.
I got it.
I have to get like an end zone pass right now.
We have to go for it.
Ah.
Triple nines.
Oh my god.
I did it.
All right.
Just kick a field goal.
I don't know how to kick a field goal though.
Just a field goal.
How do you do it?
Okay.
You just have to tap it.
On top.
Who gets the ball?
It's good.
All right.
That was a good kick.
I got a full meter, by the way.
I'm not going to use it until I need to.
Thank you.
Yeah, I can sprint with R2 instead of using the meter, right?
All right.
We're going to stay balanced.
The offense looking at first and 30.
I want...
Should I try to break through his neck?
I wonder.
No hurt.
He didn't get hurt.
Ah.
I thought I was going to hurt him.
I was trying to like break his body.
What the fuck are you doing?
Hello?
All right.
Anticipate.
I'm going to stay back.
I don't think so, buddy.
I'm going to pull this bullshit on me.
Fourth down.
What are you going to do?
Let's do prevention.
Just prevent.
No.
Just balance it up.
Lockdown.
They...
Oh, they can't...
They're punting it.
He's actually punting it in this game.
You go for it every time in this game.
What are you doing?
It's fake.
It's not fake.
Oh, god damn it.
It's all right.
Is that good?
That's a good question.
All right.
I got to get...
I have to get a parry here.
I have to.
I didn't think that that would work, but I just did it.
Franchise.
Corner look.
You can taunt.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, I got some...
I got two points there.
Right there.
Two points there.
Got it.
Now, they need to score.
13, 14...
They get a score.
So I can get my money.
Right?
That's all right.
I'm gonna fucking hurt somebody.
I tried.
I tried to hurt somebody.
Am I actually...
So I just...
I have to be more than five.
I love the incomprehensible fake John Madden.
Yeah.
Three hits.
Uh...
How about zone?
I don't know what any of these mean.
I'm not gonna lie.
I don't know a thing about this.
All I know is that you punch people and you can suplex them on their back.
And they break their neck.
But wait for it.
Man, that's ugly.
I mean, you got your pretty and then you got your...
Can't get a date to the prom ugly.
And that's what that was.
But hey, what do you think about it?
I'm not the best looking corsage on lapel.
So in a way...
Yeah, think about it.
It's kind of beautiful.
Hard class.
It's the kind of ugly only a mother could find beautiful.
Oh, that's it.
Does that make sense?
What the hell is he saying?
As we reach the end of the third quarter,
Las Vegas leads by 10.
How was that?
How's the Super Bowl going?
Patriots have the ball.
Still three nothing.
Not the same bullshit.
Somebody get him!
First down yardage right there.
Give me a break.
How did nobody get him?
Super Bowl.
Nope.
Defender made sure there was no receiver there to make the catch.
Let's go with the lockdown.
Spongebob is singing the Doom OST.
Oh!
I got a full meter.
I'm going for it.
I'm going for the kill shot here.
I gotta get that ball.
We're going with the...
We're going with the fucking total blitz here.
I...
Someone's...
I gotta go for it.
It's all right.
Still ahead.
I need to get another touchdown.
Are they gonna kick on sides?
They might.
Are they?
Oh, no.
That's my...
I...
Okay.
So...
Fuck this.
Hail Mary all the way down.
And I'm gonna do an unleash catch and catch it.
Why would you turn around?
Balance.
We're gonna do...
Okay.
I need to get a good...
I'm not gonna unleash this yet.
Let's throw the clock out.
All right.
That's the first down.
They're doing a timeout.
I'm gonna run again.
It would probably make people sick.
Especially me.
But I still wish I could do it.
Red zone offense here.
We gotta say about that.
See you later.
Oh!
What the hell are you talking about?
They don't have a meter either.
It's over.
Zero meter.
That's my game today.
Yeah!
Just kick it off normally.
I just don't really feel comfortable in my pants.
I don't know what it is.
I know I'm supposed to wear them.
I'm expected to wear them.
Something keeps telling me not to trust them.
See if I can get an injury here.
That was fucking pretty good.
But didn't...
I didn't injure him.
Just took his stamina down.
Who the hell is this?
It's supposed to be John Madden.
But not John Madden.
It's like fake John Madden.
I have to injure somebody.
Why did you fall down?
Break us back in half!
Yeah!
Why am I excited about that?
Break us back in half!
It's the game.
It's the video game doing it to me.
Now we're just going for something more dire than that.
Jerma wants blood.
I'm gonna get it.
You'll see it.
I'm gonna tear somebody's leg off.
I can't do nothing.
Let's do balance.
Coming back in.
All right.
I got one more opportunity to really hurt somebody.
Get a pass.
That would have been it probably.
This is the last attempt.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
Game over.
I'll take my money too.
Can I still hurt somebody you think?
Let's try to hurt somebody.
Come here.
Come on!
You can do it!
You can do another touchdown.
Taunt!
So Las Vegas wins the game.
37 to 1.
I'll take it.
Beat Philadelphia.
Passing yards.
Rushing yards.
Return yards.
Sacks.
Fumbles.
Recovered.
22 times 2.
Okay.
5k.
Unleash dirty hits.
That's how you make money.
Wager.
Winner.
$207,000.
You've unlocked concept art.
Movies.
Jackpot trophy.
This game's very fun.
What's your trophy level now?
I have no idea.
Phone.
We're off to a good start.
Keep it up and you'll be drawing all the right kinds of attention.
I'm talking sponsors, of course.
The better you play, the more sponsors will come looking for your endorsement.
And that means some sweet new equipment for you and your team.
Jerma agent.
Oh, it's Kim.
Kim, what's up?
Hi franchise.
This is Kim.
I'm acting on behalf of your agent to explore your marketing potential.
You are already generating major interest.
If you can put in a strong performance this Sunday,
I can work my magic with the sponsors.
Okay.
Franchise must gain over 200 combined yards.
Wow.
What a game.
How many yards did you rack up?
Hell, I stopped counting.
But whatever.
As it gave our new sponsor a major hard-on.
They couldn't wait to sign on the dotted line.
You're awarded the protector helmet by value tech.
Sponsor's protector is plus two to resist injury.
The name on the helmet says it all.
It isn't the most comfortable headgear in the world,
but it will certainly protect your players from wide variety of injuries
that other helmets would not.
All right, nice.
Is it on?
It's just on, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
So I want, let's see here.
I got money, right?
Let's see.
It's 125,000 for the first level.
I need some better speed.
I think so.
Put ankle weights on.
Provides a little extra resistance in training sessions
to really strengthen those quad and calf muscles.
Tackling.
This will keep all the offensive players healthy
and practice and allow defenders to unleash on some helpless pads.
Tackle.
And this is why I'm not parrying well.
Because it's break tackle.
It was so low.
That's why.
I think there was only like 11 points.
Breaking tackles.
I can't do them.
I need to, I have to put this on.
That's all right, but no.
Who's injured?
Each staff subtracts one week.
Broken collarbone.
Okay.
So he's out for one game.
Upgrade facilities.
Purchase adds two additional staff of 15 grand.
Yeah, just do it.
One as well.
All right.
Now who should illegally juice?
Offense.
I'm going to juice this week.
Choose drop.
Reduce the stamina loss from tackles by 25%.
It's one of the cheapest over-the-counter drugs in the market,
but it's very effective in keeping the body healthy for a long haul.
Trilafine.
Decreases class drains by 25%.
I just spit all over myself.
Everyone's so like sad about this.
Just taking a shitload of drugs.
Increases the stamina loss to opponents by 50%.
Speed up, speeds up the heart rate and delivers enormous amounts of energy.
Turbo bar drains 50% slower.
Reduces the chance and severity of injuries.
Regenerate two stamina each play they're on the field.
Reduce stamina loss from tackles.
Let's do, I like this one.
Increases the stamina loss to opponents.
We're not going to go too crazy here.
The team, team risk is, I don't want to get it any higher than that.
Mr. Super Bowl.
Go crazy.
No, no, why would I do that?
All right.
So I have to get a lot of yards here, right?
Max bet.
No, I don't know.
Let's do a $5,000 bet.
I'm not going to be crazy.
Minus 16.
Las Vegas must win by more than 16 points.
No, that's not going to happen.
That's a lot.
I'll give $1,000 to it.
They're a better team anyways.
Their stats are just overall better than mine.
So I got to play good here.
You're taking this game seriously.
It's really fun.
He's a warrior and the spearhead of the Bearcat offense.
There's only one man to fear.
So defend the spirit attack by aiming for him.
Okay.
Pazzi's taken a lot of pounding, but he's still as sharp and lethal as ever.
Baltimore.
Watch the offense.
Still three nothing Patriots in the Super Bowl.
Welcome to the Super Bowl party.
There's no party.
It's just me and NFL, not NFL.
It's just blitz the league too.
We'll be having a party time.
Get extra money.
I get extra money for injuring.
Oh my God.
Those are ugly.
That's an eyesore.
He didn't even catch it.
Bench that guy.
Do I need to get the yards or how does it work?
Oh, that was two though.
That was two stiff arms.
Good thing I trained it.
They're not gonna do the same play again.
They're not even gonna fucking see it coming.
Are you kidding me?
How is that possible?
This is the guy.
That's the guy.
Nice tackle and beat the shit out of him too.
This is the guy.
Oh, he fought me off.
That's the guy though.
I got a, I got a power.
I'm going for it.
It's going to go.
We're going to go anticipate.
I'm going to, I'm going to injure this dude.
I'm going right for his legs.
He's done.
Got him.
You're out of here.
Out for 10 games.
10 games.
He's gone.
Ruptured Spleen.
That was the guy.
That was the intro cinematic.
Just ruined his career.
Well, that's up.
Oh, they're punting it.
Shit.
Why would you punt from here?
You don't have that far to go.
Okay.
So we got the ball again.
We're going to go with a empty.
They cross over the field.
We're going to try to catch them and cross over.
Ball at the 17 yard line.
There.
Got it.
Las Vegas with a nice game there.
Oh, I didn't get the first down.
I can run that.
Let's just go.
For some.
No, boat left.
I had to step over.
Oh, damn.
Okay.
He really took a shot.
Okay, fine.
Whatever.
I'm just going to be going for it again.
Take it.
That was some exhibition of raw running ability.
You can't teach that kind of talent.
All right.
Let's go with balance.
I'm going to pass play.
Brash out.
We're going for the guy on the right.
Wait, fourth down.
And so at the end of one quarter of play.
Didn't I get a first down?
We're scoreless.
No, that wasn't a first down.
What can we do?
We got to boot it.
Open.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
To the right side.
Got it.
That's a first down.
Stopped at the 21 yard line.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
Open the link.
What are you doing?
What is happening?
Oh, my God.
That is.
Okay, cool.
That's good.
I'll do it the other way.
I want to see it from both sides.
I want the bottom to be me and the top to be him.
That's wonderful though.
Do it the other way.
First down yardage right there.
The offense is looking good.
I got a first down.
They're driving.
I'm going for.
I like this one.
This fade.
Touchdown.
Here we go.
And I should have full meter for the next.
We can go ready.
Watch.
Watch X.
That's a beautiful catch.
I'm going to play it safe.
I'm just going to kick it.
Just get the.
The extra point is good.
Just regular kickoff.
No messy stuff.
Now let's try to hurt someone.
First chance I get right here.
Oh, that's 13.
Just give me another one for free.
You ever had that acid reflux, you know, with the heart burden,
and then, you know, with the rest of it, all that kind of stuff.
14 nothing.
And the extra point is good.
Hey, another thing we just did.
Let's do it again.
Do I have full meter?
I don't have full meter, but I can still hurt somebody.
There it is.
All right.
Stomp on his head.
I got meter again.
Let's go for it.
They are actual garbage without their crutch player.
Yeah, we're going to get the ball back again.
First down, 30 yards.
Really good thing.
I took him up.
See if I can get the ball back.
What just happened?
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Hold on.
New one.
Jesus.
Oh, what is that?
Oh, this is a ready player one avatar.
I don't like this.
That's me going in the Oasis and hanging out.
All right.
Uh, show us.
Hold on.
I need to.
Yeah, this is worth saving.
This is what I'm talking about.
And I'm going to take a piss break, by the way, while you stare at this image.
This is what I'm talking about when I say my ready player one avatar.
How the hell did you even do this?
All right, I'll be right back.
All right, hold on.
Hold on.
Before I go, you know what this reminds me of?
This looks like.
This looks like this is supposed to be here.
Do you know what I mean by that?
How this is like what?
German 985 stream.
I'll be right back.
It's like a cartoon kind of 3D version of me, like a YouTuber kind of thing.
This looks like it's I'm supposed to have this here.
All right, I hate this image.
What am I looking at?
Oh, no, let me like do like, let me deep dive this.
Hold on.
How did you even make this?
That's so weird and scary that this is possible.
Welcome back to the show.
It's German 985.
Oops, hold on.
Welcome back.
It's me, German.
Welcome back to the show.
How do I get this off?
His teeth aren't showing.
Side by side.
No, I.
Oh, don't limit it.
Don't just crush me.
That's so loud.
Oh, I look at OBS and I crack a tab and it blows out the audio every time.
It's a Coke.
I'm going to prove it.
There, proved it.
Now, hopefully the game didn't crash.
Me trying to prove it.
All right, so I got to beat by more than,
I got to win by more than 16 points.
Should have bet fucking max bet on this.
I'm going to get it.
Can we test the sync here, by the way?
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
We good?
All right, I get the ball, right?
How the Patriots do it?
Oh, fuck, it's tied up.
It's tie game.
Three to three.
They got a field goal.
What in the name of fucking God just happened?
They just Donkey Kong barreled.
They with the barrels.
The ball was Donkey Kong.
Offense with a long way to go here on third down.
Take his helmet off.
All right, this is fourth down.
Are they going to punt it?
15 yards to go.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're going to punt, aren't they?
Punt return.
Yeah, they are.
I don't have any meter though.
He didn't even catch that.
It just bounced in his hands.
Sheds a tackle and he's brought down.
I got something for shedding that tackle, didn't I?
Another one.
Hold on.
What is this one?
These are all so...
I just looked at the other one.
This one is also as detailed.
And there are more.
Okay, guys.
It's getting to a point where people, when they search me,
they're not going to know what the real one is.
Let's just put them all up on the screen eventually here.
Let me just like, let me get to the end of this.
I got it.
Okay, that's scaring me.
I need to close that.
End of the third quarter in the Super Bowl, by the way.
All right, let's go.
Let's do a pass play.
Big cross here.
I have 200 images of your face.
No one should have that many faces.
Got it.
Yes.
And that's a full meter.
Without their, without that player there, they are absolutely worthless.
That's it.
Fuck it.
We're just going to run it.
I got a full meter.
We're going to do an HP crush.
The version is good.
Speaking of full meter.
Got it back.
And so at halftime, Las Vegas leads by 22.
It's a good thing that you killed that guy.
Jerma actually knows that he's...
Jerma actually sounds like he knows what he's talking about.
I know some sports stuff.
Some.
Oops.
I know that this first one.
You know, I know what that is.
Crank his fucking neck.
Really?
That's too bad.
Is it 85% though?
I don't really follow football that well considering, if you think about it.
First and 30.
The New England Patriots are in the Super Bowl right now.
And I have a browser tab open just seeing how the score is.
So, I mean, I'm not that much of a big fan.
Of the sport.
I do think it's interesting sometimes.
Baltimore leads by 22.
Let's see if I can make something happen here.
I got a long way to go.
Cheerleaders.
They really are doing just that kind of the dumbest dances.
To me, this is mocap.
Okay.
That was a fumble.
This is a big fourth down coming up.
Are they going to punt it?
You need to shut them down.
They had to punt it.
Am I going to shut this team up?
Again, I didn't even catch it.
Holy fuck.
I ran out of gas.
It's okay.
Let's go with...
Let's do it.
Let's do our own Donkey Kong barrel play.
Bring it back.
I gotta be careful.
Don't run it.
I gotta pass it.
I could get a fumble here or somebody get hurt.
Oh.
Okay.
Trick play.
Break delay.
No.
Snowflake.
Maniac.
They just go all over the place.
How's this for a maniac?
Wide open.
Just land.
Land, land.
I'm not getting unleashed.
If you don't know, if he uses Unleashed,
there's a high chance that he'll break my neck or will fumble.
So I need to just down myself.
No!
That's what I'm talking about.
I survived.
The rambling boomer is the best part of the game.
Everything is a boomer.
All adults over the age of like 30 are boomers.
God damn it.
And it's a touchback.
Shit.
A boomer in the background.
Get it back!
No!
Shit!
That was so abrupt.
Oh, man.
He just bounced off the ropes.
And I just...
Why won't they make another one of these?
Seriously.
I don't even give a shit about football, really.
Oh, God.
I would play this all day.
Fourth down still.
Are they gonna punt?
You can't punt.
You have to go for it.
Fourth and long.
They really need a big play here.
Come back, come back, come back.
All right.
Let's go for a shutout.
He doesn't have any meter or anything.
That's just getting embarrassing.
That's embarrassing.
There's a new image.
What the hell is going on?
Wait, just wait, wait.
I need to put that on.
I'll get a conversion here.
Let's add an insult to injury here.
Yeah, should have made that bet, right?
I'll try to injure him.
No, I wanted that tackle.
Not you.
Shutout.
Give me the achievement for the shutout.
That's a fumble.
I just like spinning wheelhouse kicked him.
Can I do a 40-point shutout or 38-point shutout?
Oh, my God.
I got it.
Across the clean.
Let's go for a...
I'm going to try to get the guy in the middle right.
He's going to turn around.
That square is going to turn around right now.
You dickhead game.
No, I'm not going to 36 points.
Pain, pain, pain.
Make him hurt.
Light hit.
Get it.
Step on his head.
Now I can actually do an injury here.
New link.
It's going by too fast.
Oh, my God.
The offense looking at first and 30.
What the fuck are these?
97% accuracy.
Really?
I have another one.
I want to go for the quarterback, though.
I don't even care about the play.
I want to hurt the quarterback.
He's not injured, though.
The quarterback is the paint.
And the paint was all over the canvas.
I mean, it's like the paint all over the entire paint canvas.
And the receiver gets taken out before the ball gets near him.
I don't think he knows what hit him.
Let's stop him right here, right here.
Let's do it again.
Oh, he's coming back in.
It's all right.
Good?
You good to go?
Go get him.
Is the announcer drunk?
No, the announcer is doing a John Madden impersonation.
John Madden was unknown at...
side.
Okay.
I can't.
Damn it.
No fucking shut up.
Give me the penalty.
I don't even care.
I'm fucking hurting someone.
I can't go across.
They're doing an onside kick, aren't they?
Nothing matters.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Yeah, it's Frank Caliendo.
He was on Mad TV.
First down and 30.
And he did a perfect one-to-one John Madden impression.
It was pretty ridiculous.
What was that pass?
What did...
Is there a replay feature?
What the hell was this?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Go back.
I underhanded that ball like 45 yards.
50 yards.
Okay.
Bowling ball that...
What are we doing for?
How about manning?
No.
Razzle go.
Into the end zone.
It's all right.
Game over.
Should have bet the money.
It's the fourth quarter of the Super Bowl tied at three.
That's going to be a lot of money.
Turnovers caused touchdowns.
Wager $1,000 to $256,000.
That's pretty damn good.
New link.
During the cutscene, I'm going to get these saved.
We'll put them on screen.
Have a seat.
Just have a seat.
What's this about?
You're going to go play with that new hotshot, Franchise.
Why the fuck would I want to play there?
His team's in division three.
Because I happen to know that the nightmare is going to cut you at the end of this season.
Let's put them up here.
Along with that big contract of yours.
That's why they traded up to draft Max Carson.
Oh man, fuck them.
You might get picked up by another team for a fraction of your current salary.
Or you can go play with Franchise.
They keep your deal as is.
Just tell me one thing.
What's in it for you?
There's too many of these.
There are too many of them.
Okay, I swear to God.
I'm not kidding.
I don't know.
Call me like a weirdo if you want.
But I feel like I look in the mirror and this is what I look like sometimes.
I'll take a selfie with an iPhone and this is what the image will be.
I swear.
All right, it's Kim.
Wow, what a football.
You and I need to get together this evening and discuss our options.
It's the front-facing camera.
You'll find me a flexible negotiator.
Okay.
You and I need to get together this evening.
It's time to go on a date.
Apparently.
Darling, you dressed to kill.
Have time to talk a little business?
Whatever you like, beautiful.
We have the opportunity to land the biggest sporting goods company in North America.
And you need me to do a little meet and greet.
Their reps will be at the game this Sunday.
I need you to give me a top-notch performance.
That's the only kind I ever give.
Get it done on the field, hotshot.
And perhaps we can celebrate afterwards.
That one's not even.
This one is not even.
You didn't even try to change it to the other photo.
You just mutated my face.
Okay, this one is the agent.
This one's the agent too.
You're getting a little weird.
And this one is just slowly turning into a gnome.
All right, roster.
I think there's some changes here.
I got a new player, right?
All right, I got offense, quarterback.
I'm a C plus.
Defense, defense.
Anybody like, do I have any Ds?
All right, I don't know.
You might have, you guys might have to go here.
D plus.
They're all Cs and Ds.
Lifestyle.
Sponsors again.
Protector.
Crunch pads plus two tackle.
Crunch pads help defenders pack a little extra punch in their hits.
Cool.
Oh, let's see.
Trainer.
Training.
Assign the training automatically.
Upgrades.
More tackle.
255 grand.
Yep.
I want to be unstoppable.
What is going on?
Okay, I'm standing looking into a pond in a dramatic part of the movie,
and somebody dropped a pebble right in the middle of my face in the water.
That's fucking ridiculous.
All right, tackle.
Two tackle.
I need some, okay, better hands.
No, I don't have enough money.
Do I have enough money for anything else?
Ice bath.
Get rid of all the swelling.
You still have to be careful of shrinkage.
Oh, that's funny.
I've seen the fireman.
Oh, we got old boomer hands.
No, I'm gonna hold the money.
Let's take some more drugs.
For me, I like this turbo bar drain.
Slower.
Reduce the chance of severity of injuries.
Game plus two stamina for every successful clash or unleash move.
Yeah.
And let's have the halfback.
Clash drains for the halfback.
Yeah, I think so.
All right, easy with the drug risk.
I gotta do halfback plays here.
All right, any, what's this one?
I just got gnomed.
Well, there are a million images in the,
but that's what happens when people are just putting in links.
All right, let's go.
Las Vegas must win by more than 17 points.
I need better stats than this.
Train already.
Fourth quarter.
What a boring Super Bowl.
Oh, Patriots scored.
I was gonna say what a boring Super Bowl.
Three to three for the whole game.
Patriots up 10-3.
Seven minutes remaining in the last quarter.
I mean, Tom Bladey really is just so unbelievable.
5,000.
The Houston rioters have been the Division 3 punching bag
since they joined the league three years ago.
That might be changing this year
since they drafted running back Don L. Sullivan
in the first round.
Running back.
That's the target.
The guy's got an effective one-two punch.
His wicked first to speed followed by his stiff arm jab.
And he ain't afraid to hit below the belt.
So if we want to shut down Houston,
we need to knock out Sullivan.
Time to kill this guy.
Who is this in real life?
It's all fictional.
No, people.
There are no real people in the game, I don't believe.
This is not a licensed NFL video game.
Pro, they got a strong running game.
But their con is their speed.
How does that make any sense?
How can you have a slow, strong running team?
Good evening, everyone.
It begins.
It's a dirty hit right off the bat.
And I can, let's go.
What's the name of the drink?
All right, I got two blips so far.
Good breath back.
So we're going to stop the running game.
First down and 30.
Stop him.
Oh, that's him.
Any other questions this guy's leadership
may can just look to a play like that.
All right, I got to take him out.
I'm going to say crush.
There he is.
I see you.
You see that?
That was me.
That's called me waiting for you.
And now I got a meter.
Same deal.
You want to go for the same guy?
Go for it.
Oh, I had an opportunity.
He didn't make it through though.
Let's forward down.
They're going to punt it.
Where are the refs?
Yeah, where are the refs?
Why would you do that?
I have punt return and oh, God.
Keeps his feet moving.
You guys are fucking kidding me.
All right.
Now we taunt.
Dream of as a special teams player.
That was really, really good.
Went right during that return.
A punt punt returned from the end zone
that the guy didn't catch to run back for a touchdown.
Welcome to hell.
Catch it.
I got it.
I actually got it.
I still have a full meter to new image.
Watch the guy in the bottom right.
Twenty eight.
That's the captain.
I am not going to select anybody else
because if he gets through it's a touchdown.
So I'm staying back.
Is it actually cursed image in chat right now?
I can't.
That's going to make the throw up.
I can't look at that.
I actually just hurt my head looking at that.
That's all I see now.
I don't see anything else.
Third down.
Let's do the flip.
Twenty eight right there.
They're going to twenty eight.
I'm going to crush him.
Ravity goes up the middle.
No.
Quarter ran out.
And that's the end of the first quarter as Las Vegas leads by eight.
Yeah.
Watch that picture.
Be easy on that picture.
If you have you're sensitive to light rays
and sensitive to wacky images.
I advise you not to click it
because I just got like a headache for five seconds.
Fourth down.
Same deal.
Oh fuck.
They're punting.
Shit.
Somebody catch it.
I always figure they're not going to do it.
All right.
There's an opportunity here.
Couldn't couldn't plow through it.
He's got better stats than I do.
Let's go.
Let's go straight up.
I might try to do a big no no no let's run it run it.
Crush.
Halfback crush.
I have the drug.
My halfback is on drugs.
Can't plow through that even with drugs.
That sucks.
Do it again.
I like their chances here on third and short.
Damn it.
I promise you he's gonna feel that one tomorrow.
Shit he actually got through.
Fuck it.
I'm going for it.
Franchise gives his team a new set of downs.
Fake punt.
No I'm just going right.
I just have to get the first down.
That's all I care about.
Now I have to be very careful.
I gotta get a touchdown right here.
He lets it fly.
The ball gets there too late.
Or should I say the defender got there.
Oh I just got clotheslined.
Shit.
Second I gotta get this now.
Houston comes up with the turnover.
Sorry here comes this is they got one play.
At least he blew his uh unleash.
They got one play.
I'm staying all the way back.
I ain't gonna let somebody just get across here.
The first half of the books.
Las Vegas leads by eight.
Four minutes.
In the Super Bowl Patriots up 10-3.
He's actually playing safety.
Yeah um yeah sometimes you have to play the game where you're supposed to.
These dirty hits.
First and 30.
Oh I can't look at that right.
Wait.
Hey hey hey Herbert thanks for the five community subs.
The links.
Thank you for the community subs Herbert.
Oh well there's too many people coming at me.
Got the first down.
All right we're kind of at the.
Let's do a goal line here.
First and goal.
This is not I mean it is goal.
Cut out to the left.
There it is.
These guys are very the defense is very good.
It's hard to break through.
Second down down.
Hey uh what we got him at the team breakfast this morning.
Get in there.
I got an unleash.
Las Vegas gives themselves some more breathing room with that score.
No let's just be smart because they still have their star player.
The extra point is good.
First and 10 at New England 4.
I'm getting live updates here.
All right somebody just said.
Break.
Come on.
Injury.
Yeah.
Somebody just said who would ever move to Las Vegas.
It's a fucking wasteland.
Well hey Vegas is great.
What are you talking about.
That was another touchdown by the way.
Those are paying attention.
Nobody has made or anything.
So it's a couple of late hits.
Step on the helmet.
Why would you move to Vegas.
Why would you move anywhere.
Why did I just get that.
You can get a chance to move.
And you're angry.
He's they can tell I'm angry.
That back here it is.
Got it.
Thank God.
I don't know.
I don't know by law.
As we reach the end of the third quarter.
Las Vegas leads by 21.
That's this.
By the way t-shirts are available.
If you want a German 985 officially licensed t-shirt.
They are.
There's a new t-shirt store.
It's on taste frame.
Go ahead and if you want it is the night sky is now available.
And blue man is back.
Please include that image on a shirt.
That's no.
I don't want to put that on.
Why.
Stop him at the 29 yard line.
I hope you enjoyed your popcorn folks.
Because you just saw quite a show.
What a run.
Let's get here.
Crucial series of downs here.
Ball spotted the 29 yard line.
Holy shit.
They're going to get a touchdown.
That was wild.
I know.
I have to kill that guy.
But it's easier said than done.
I almost blocked it.
The extra point is good.
And he got.
And it looks like they'll try it on sidekick.
They got to get two more full possessions.
They're not going to get two full possessions.
In a minute.
Damn that was a hit.
I don't see any new kids in his future.
Oh what.
Flush inside.
I'm going to go for a run.
First down and 30.
Damn it.
Who was that?
Robbie.
No not Robbie.
Anybody but Robbie.
Listen this isn't working.
Let's go with.
What else have you got?
Let's go with mom.
Second down and about a mile.
They don't have any meter.
Looking for the big play.
Got it.
Oh there it is.
Now it's out of reach.
Pretty much completely.
Let's go with a little dog shit pass.
Right here.
The conversion is good.
29.7.
What's the colors?
The colors are supposed to be.
The German 985 Twitch YouTuber colors.
They don't really look that good on.
They look like it's an ice cream cone.
But that's okay.
Right into my guy.
They don't look good on anything.
Well it looks good on a digital screen.
As like a character.
Oh god damn it.
Oh nice juke.
Houston exploits an opening in the defense for some real yardage.
All right this is my opportunity here.
It's time to crush.
First down.
30 yards to go.
I have an unleash.
I'm going to try to hurt somebody here.
Let's go.
They're going to go to the running back here.
You stopped my unleash.
How would you stop my unleash?
I was holding L2.
He stopped my unleash.
How?
He stopped it.
Don't matter.
It's legitimately impossible for them to get in this game.
It's impossible.
Stop my unleash.
You got to be kidding me.
We can try to.
There you go.
You're all right buddy.
All right Robbie get back in here.
Goes way down field.
And it's caught at the 15 yard line.
He turns on a dime.
Full line.
Touchdown.
Las Vegas.
Okay I'm trying to get a random code.
20.
Yeah Robbie comes in the game.
Let me see what happens.
Get out there and start.
It's no good.
It's okay.
It's 30 seconds in the game.
There's no way they're going to have this.
They might get one more touchdown.
Maybe.
They still get that guy in the game.
So I'm going to hang back.
Oh you got to hold on to that.
Quick kill someone before it ends.
I might not be able to.
Let's go for a chaos run.
Patriots win Super Bowl.
Did they?
Like there's still like a minute left right?
No he used his unleashed.
I'm gonna get it.
Game over.
And as time expires Las Vegas will take this one.
Beat Houston.
Two minute warning for the Super Bowl.
What a party.
No injuries unfortunately.
A lot of touchdowns.
They did get the wager right?
Because it was 17 points right?
Concept art.
Who am I rooting for in the Super Bowl?
I mean I'm from Massachusetts.
I lived there for 30 years.
So the Patriots probably.
If I were to have to sell you.
Is this?
Hey yourself.
Quick cut the stream.
How we doing on training?
Stats.
Power rankings.
League standings.
Girlfriends.
Kim provides exclusive sponsor equipment.
Marketing professional who specializes
in getting superstar athletes together
with top sports brands.
Did I get any new sponsors?
No new sponsors.
Training.
Upgrades.
I don't have enough.
What do I need?
I need better hands.
No more fumbles.
Or strength.
I'm going to say hands.
Hands and strength.
I got one.
Yeah I got enough.
It's just hand moisturizer.
Maybe speed too.
No I'll do strength.
All right.
Because my training is doing good.
Assigned training automatically.
So what do we got here?
I got two more games to advance.
Three and all right now.
Forty two thousand dollars in the bank.
And let's see where we're at now.
I have gained stats.
Our overall is two notches.
I went up in defense.
How do you spend a hundred grand
on hand moisturizer?
Win by more than 20 points.
I've done it two games in a row.
But that's a lot of money to bet.
Fuck it.
The Milwaukee Hounds used to be
a bunch of semi-pro misfits.
But quarterback Conrad Damon
has made them the high caliber team
to beat in division three.
Not bad for a guy who drives
a military assault vehicle.
He just ruined the whole field.
Conrad's got a cannon for an arm.
And a damn good receiver call.
Make no mistake.
This guy's a deadly bastard.
So hit him hard and hit him off.
All right.
Okay.
Easy there.
Guy.
What?
What is this shitty twisted metal reject?
We have to get rid of him.
Look at how long his body is.
He has an exceptionally long body.
Good evening, everyone.
So ugly.
Every time.
All right.
We got to go up to the quarterback.
That's the target.
And that's a fucking touchdown
right at the beginning of the game.
So nobody on their defense
is particularly terrifying.
Oh, almost.
Almost.
Oh!
That deserves a taunt.
How do I taunt?
That should have been a taunt.
No, I'm going to go safe.
Here we go.
Three extra points.
How's Super Bowl going?
One minute left.
Patriots have the ball.
4-1 at L.A. 24, really.
I don't know how up to date that is.
It is a nice dirty hit.
That was nice.
So they have an amazing quarterback.
So I got to be aware of that.
I got to try to injure him.
I don't want to do that for safety, though.
Maybe I do.
He's at 86%.
And I have an unleash.
Field goal for the Patriots.
Okay.
Caught that right at the very end.
So the Rams have one minute
to...
It's almost impossible, isn't it?
They're going to have to get a touchdown
and then an onside kick.
Damn.
Well, it's not impossible.
It's just improbable.
Ooh, nice interception.
See you later.
Identity.
Am I rooting for Rams?
I mean, I'm from New England.
The Patriots are the team
that I should be rooting for.
So I don't know.
Yeah, but right in the fucking head.
Cox chugged all the frames.
Oh, geez.
I don't know what that was.
What did I just hurt?
Broken rib.
You're up a two plays.
That's it.
See you in like two and a half minutes.
No game.
Only three yards.
I just broke a few ribs.
Just get in there.
Oh.
Not only is that illegal,
but that's how you find yourself in a jail cell.
Let's go back to balance.
He's going to be throwing it.
All right.
You're all right.
Let me see here.
Good.
You're good to go.
Go get him.
Actually illegal.
Oh, no.
He's still going.
I almost had it too.
He's close.
Crucial series of downs here.
Stuff him here.
Stuff him.
Don't give him a chance.
Ah, pick up one more.
That's the end of the first quarter
as Las Vegas leads by 15.
Tom Brady just grew an extra finger
to put on his sixth spring.
Is it actually over?
Damn it.
Ah, what was I trying to do there?
Sorry.
No, it's not time yet.
I'm still streaming.
My Super Bowl's not over yet.
What the heck?
My eight foot sub cater order
didn't even get here yet.
Holy shit.
You fucked up bad.
Okay, I don't even want to hear that kind of.
What the hell are you saying?
The deep pass.
And it's complete at the seven yard line.
Hurt him.
No injury there.
Oh, the signature.
Look at me.
What are we hurting?
Uh-oh.
Nope.
I thought it was, uh.
I thought it was something else.
We still have not seen the worst.
The offense looking at first and 30.
Which is the defense.
God, he's outbound.
Prevent.
Deep zones.
He passes all the time.
That's not what I call prevention.
That's not prevention.
So that's it.
Patriots win the Super Bowl.
That's it.
The New England Patriots
have won the Super Bowl
for the tenth time in a row.
There it is.
They did it.
I can't believe they did it.
But, uh.
Yeah, congratulations to Tom Brady.
You can now.
Essentially now Tom Brady is the one.
When Tom Brady eventually like dies.
Like in, you know, 50 years.
He's won so many Super Bowls.
They're gonna like future Ramaham.
He'll be doing like press conferences still.
Oh, that one hit.
Got it.
Perception.
Oh.
He fell down and turned his braid off.
No.
No, that was me.
Oh, shit.
That's bad.
Hen's game of the loss.
That sucks.
It's fucking shaggy.
All right.
We both have unleashed.
Eaves it deep.
Out of bounds at the 47 yard line.
I actually caught it.
Holy shit.
Hold on.
I don't think I caught that.
I think I caught that out of bound.
I can't do like slow motion.
Is one foot?
Nope.
Whatever.
It's in my favor.
I don't care.
Brady now has the final stone for this bump.
Yeah, you guys.
Everyone should be concerned about this.
Oh, look at me.
Look at me.
I thought I was gonna get really hurt.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Stop pausing.
And so at halftime.
Leads by 16.
Sorry for the YouTuber scream.
I'm sorry.
He's gone for like the rest of the year.
It's always the spleen.
You're gone forever.
See you in eight games the whole season.
That's what you get for making me lose and be stupid and taunt you.
That's what you get from me taunting you.
I gotta get in there and get that.
Quarterback.
I gotta get in there.
He recovered from the concussion.
I almost got it.
We'll do spy man.
One more good dirty hit.
And I'll have enough to try to take up.
What?
My guy just stopped moving.
Oh, fuck the button.
Oh, stay up.
Stay up.
Uh, what about the sling?
Let's go with the sling.
I don't, I'm not going to use my own leads here.
Give me a cut.
There he is.
Let's go for a bolt.
Bolt pass.
Cut right.
What an unbelievable catch but not good enough.
Dammit.
He's gonna come back and haunt me.
The crowd is twitch chat.
Yeah, I could see that.
How did you not catch that?
Honest to god.
How did you not get that?
Wait, where's this guy going?
Beautiful move.
Beautiful fumble.
Why did he run that way?
I ran him that way.
Fuck me.
Not this time.
How the fuck?
This quarterback is too good.
I have to win by 20 points.
I'm trying to do a not terrible.
What if Jerma was one of us?
The Super Bowls are gonna win.
I can't believe the Patriots won the Super Bowl again.
How'd you run out of bounds there?
There's no reason for you to run out of bounds.
You had an opportunity to run.
Damn.
Turnover on downs.
Didn't get it.
It's third.
All right, it's my opportunity to make it.
My $15,000 bet.
Let's run it.
First down and 30.
I'll take it.
Uh, is this game online or is he playing against himself?
I'm just playing against you.
As we reach the end of the third quarter,
Las Vegas leads by 22.
This is an old PlayStation 3 game.
What's the League 2?
It is.
Sometimes I wish I was just sitting down there with a...
This was definitely one of the best.
Sit down with like a buddy.
And just shit talk to each other and play again.
Lofts one.
And the defender gets a hand on it and it's incomplete.
Sit down with a buddy.
Doesn't bounce, right?
Looks like they'll have four more downs to work with.
All right, here it is.
Red zone.
We're gonna go run right up the middle.
Let's see if the offense can keep it going here in the red zone.
Oh, did I lose yards?
I don't think I'm fighting right now.
Again.
Fifth play of the drive.
Touchdown!
Las Vegas refuses to call off the dogs as they add to their lead.
And I got a big bet riding on this.
Just field goal.
I want to keep my unleash.
It's good.
Just gotta hold him.
If you remember, I was there when rage quit Jets sent radio.
Were you there when I exploded the guy's balls?
It didn't happen, but.
44.
I'm stroying with now.
This is not even a contest anymore.
He's very injured, too.
Look at this guy.
This guy's in pain.
Oh, wrong guy.
This is the guy standing next to him.
More like dumb luck.
That one's already been used.
All right, I got an unleash.
Let's take the quarterback out of the game.
And out of the seat.
And now I'm in.
Oh, he's gonna be funny about it.
Yeah, you get a little prize.
You got 13 points.
Good for you.
Get it!
I'm caring so much about trying to
kill the quarterback.
Let's turn off the announcer.
Do you really want me to turn him off?
It's all right.
He was resilient.
Okay, our new mantra is run the ball, burn the clock.
Yeah, run the ball, burn the clock.
Oh, I punched him so hard in the face.
Oh, look at me!
I punched him.
I punched him so bad.
Very nice run.
His legs never stop moving and his eyes never stop looking for Dayla.
Let's go with the pass.
I have 50 points.
Well, I thought it was going to be circle weather.
Look, when you're up by 50 points, you kind of just...
Can I take off my starters?
Let's go with the PS.
My controller turned off.
Is that a battery?
I need a battery right now.
The offense looking at first and 30.
I need a plug.
This one fits, right?
It does.
Where's the USB?
It's right here.
The offense has a ways to go here on second down.
How do you get the USB in here?
All right, I'm plugged back in.
We're good, I think.
It's just blinking.
How do I do this?
Why is it not just syncing?
Why does it have to sync?
Got it.
Okay, it's back, it's back.
Hey, yeah, that's not fair.
That's fine, yeah.
You get to play against a non-opponent for a minute.
What?
I intercepted the ball?
Did he throw it in?
I don't...
No.
How do...
I wish I could slow this down.
There's no way to slow it down, huh?
I don't know.
Nice work.
All right, let's just throw an end zone pass.
See if I can get to 58 points.
You're not on code again.
58 points, let's get it.
Oh my god, what are you doing?
What?
Oh, this poor guy.
And so, Las Vegas is your winner here tonight.
For the wrong code, joke isn't a joke.
No, I'm just trying to find other codes.
I'm just doing random buttons to try to find other codes.
Because there's a shitload of them.
All right, I got...
I'm gonna get a lot of money.
I had a lot of points, a lot of dirty hits, a lot of flashes.
Touchdowns.
Yeah, 400 grand.
Uh, I got some movies.
Very cool.
What's my sweat like?
But I'm not...
I'm fine.
We're about to make it into the next...
We're about to win.
Agent.
Franchise, main man, you feeling pumped?
Because I'm feeling...
This is it, the big bucks, baby.
Your first commercial shoot.
You just suit up and do everything I tell you.
And let the cameraman do the rest.
You nail this and we will have the sponsors eating out of our hands.
Okay, I got to score at least three touchdowns against Detroit.
No new sponsors.
Training.
Let's take a look.
I want to take a look at how everybody's doing, too.
So I got 400 grand.
Resist injury is probably a good idea.
Speed.
Passing.
Grip master, more strength.
I'm gonna do speed.
Speed and...
Speed and passing.
I might be able to do one more.
And resist injury.
Big spender.
All right, so we're doing all right.
75 tackle.
People are ranking up.
Oh, I have to actually...
Okay, train the attributes now.
So this is me.
Oh, I gotta set it to automatic.
It's on automatic, isn't it?
Pass and kick plus five.
Hands, strength.
Break tackle is so bad.
Yeah, just keep it there.
That's fine.
Yeah, it is doing it.
It's doing it automatically.
I see.
Okay, we're good.
How about drugs?
I got 50 grand.
Let's go with turbo bar.
Reduce the...
Turbo bar drain.
Let's reduce the stamina loss.
Let's also give this again.
Turbo bar to the halfback.
I don't want to get arrested,
so I'm gonna keep it like that.
Although, let's go to defense.
I'm gonna get in trouble.
All right, let's go.
This is the Detroit Devils.
4-0.
Las Vegas must win by more than 23 points.
Max bet.
This week, we've got the Detroit Devils.
Once upon a time,
this was a pretty good team.
But there's a cancer in that locker room,
and his name is Cookie Wallace.
On a good day,
Cookie is one of the best receivers in the game.
Thing is,
he ain't having as many good days as he used to.
And of course,
he blames everyone else for his screw-ups.
So the team sucks,
but he's...
I don't understand.
So maybe I should leave him in the game.
Should I just not try to hurt him?
If the team sucks when he's on it,
I should leave him be.
Selfish and undisciplined.
Okay.
Go after everyone else.
Thanks for joining us.
We're partway through the Division 3 season,
and this team has been making some noise.
Let's hope they can keep it up.
And now let's get ready for the kickoff.
Come on.
Why does that keep happening?
Looks like a fumble shoot.
Okay.
Whoever that is.
82?
Fuck you, 82.
That was ridiculous.
Come on, now.
Damn.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's a neck cleat.
There's Robbie.
That guy's on drugs, too.
I gotta get him back in.
Hold on, buddy.
Look at the run in the background.
Hey, get the cart out here.
I gotta make this good.
Take it easy, buddy.
It'll be over in a second.
That's all right.
Take it easy, buddy.
Three plays and one stamina boost.
All right.
This team is kind of hurting me.
That's smart.
Just like those are the reason that man needs to be a big part of this offense.
Exemplary catch.
I'm not doing any running plays.
I don't have my hat back.
And he's the one on drugs.
I gotta keep him okay.
Cut it.
Somebody cut it.
Just short of the first.
All right.
I gotta run.
I have to.
I'm gonna do a QB sneak.
No, he made it here on time.
I'm just running.
I'm gonna walk over the...
I'm walking over the line right now.
Three, two, one, go.
God damn it.
It's all right.
It's because my halfback got hurt.
I would have ran with the halfback.
Kill somebody already.
I...
I got killed.
My guy was injured.
I...
Guys.
Oh, I had an opportunity.
But it's okay.
As long as I keep him.
Third down.
Let's do some zones here.
Oh, damn it.
He unleashed to catch it.
It's a free catch if you unleash.
Fuck.
God damn halfback got injured in the first play.
And then I fumbled the ball.
It's still early.
Is Vegas falling from grace?
No, not yet.
I'll take it back here.
I'm gonna get my halfback.
He's gonna come back.
This is the turnaround right here.
They're pretty rough.
Holy...
Good thing he's got insurance.
There he is.
There you go.
You're all right, buddy.
Robbie's back.
Next play.
There it is.
Let's bring it back.
Don't taunt.
Just score the fucking touchdown.
I gotta take the lead.
Let's go.
Take the lead.
Yes!
Across the plane.
Look up codes.
I mean, I'm...
Oh, no.
No.
Look up codes.
I was looking at chat.
I got it.
Killed Cookie.
I know.
There's gonna be a back and forth here.
And all I need is a touchdown.
I got the two.
They didn't get a two-point conversion.
I did.
All right.
They got an unleash.
I'm about to have one.
I gotta...
I gotta run it out.
I gotta pass and run out of bounds.
I have to get that.
Otherwise, I'm gonna get fumbled again.
Let's hug the right side.
Stay!
No!
Out of bounds, please.
Yeah!
Yes!
And so at the end of one quarter...
Wow, that was lucky.
Leads by six.
Aren't you guys lotioning up your hands?
I need to upgrade the hands.
It's bad.
It's very bad.
I need to upgrade hands.
First and goal.
It's gut check time.
Ball at the 22-yard line.
Goes way downfield.
He's got it.
Touchdown.
So I have an unleash.
It's tied up.
Oh, should I be safe?
Okay, we got the set.
We're picking up the trail
and we'll check up like the dogs they are.
Okay, tie game.
Injury time.
No, I wanted to select it,
but I couldn't get it.
Cycles through like everybody on the team.
No, I...
Let me hit him.
Stop getting in my way.
Did that just happen?
That just happened.
It just comes easy to this guy.
Sure, he works hard.
He has talent.
I can't believe it.
But that's what makes these sorts of plays so easy for him.
Bravo.
Or injury.
Heart.
He lets it fly.
And he makes the grab.
Oh, man!
Hookie Wallace.
If they would just get out of my way
and let me tackle them,
I would have tackled them two plays ago.
He was right in my line of sight.
I have an unleash
and some guy bumped into it.
They're making this hard for me, guys.
Get out of my fucking way.
I'm the captain.
I say what I say goes.
Who gets the ball?
That's who.
You got the smelling salts?
Yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
You know what?
Never mind.
Let's just get the card out here.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, bring it up.
Oh, no.
Oh, that's not good.
That's not good.
Actually dead.
Oh, God.
This is not going well.
He's going long.
And it's complete at the 46 yard line.
Two unleashed just ran into each other.
That's what happens.
Oh, nice pass.
Wish I had that.
Get over that first down.
Did you get it?
I didn't get it.
No, that's not.
No, it's not what I said.
I said if it was up to me.
It's not.
But the offense is looking at third and short.
Get it.
First down.
We're doing all right.
Everything's going fine.
Let's try to run it here.
Who wins in the unleashed fight?
Who wins?
Time out.
I still have my unleashed.
I got it.
You've got to be kidding me.
And so at halftime Detroit leads by seven.
That was an unleashed catch.
It's supposed to be guaranteed.
All right.
Injured.
Injury.
No.
Why?
It's not fair.
Kill it.
Break is back.
Yes.
He's too good.
Get rid of him.
Oh, my God.
I think it's separated.
Stay down.
Cookie has made every single play.
He's made every single touchdown.
Not anymore.
You're out.
And everyone on the same page there.
And they are rewarded with a very nice game.
You only have five plays.
It's all right.
That's an entire.
I'm so amped up right now.
I've got to win.
I've got to go five and up.
I just fucked it up.
Oh, the receiver's taken out of the play.
And that's incomplete.
He falls on him.
Here's my guy.
He's just serious to let him get by you.
How could you let you hat you?
You were holding onto him.
How did you let that happen?
You tackled him.
And he just walked off.
This team's training.
I'm going to fucking close the door on this.
These idiots can't do anything on defense.
I'm just like pissed off.
At like Cookie, whatever his name is.
It's all right.
Keep it going.
Let's run it.
How have I not found a random code?
Okay.
I need this two point conversion.
I need it bad.
Very, very badly.
Very badly.
Let's go.
Cookie hurt him.
He's back in.
He's injured.
Make it work.
Make it happen.
Look at that stamina.
It's terrible.
And I have a...
I'm going to...
Let's go for him again.
Anticipate.
Cookie's coming over here.
There he is.
Nice try.
That was like a ballet move.
I don't think he knows what hit him.
That was a big sack.
Third and 39.
We're going to play cover.
I'm just man up in the zones.
There's no way you're going to get 40 goddamn yards there.
See you later.
My ball.
Fourth and 26.
They're definitely going to punt.
And I've got an unleash.
As we reach the end of the third quarter, Detroit leads by eight.
Now I need a two point conversion.
Yeah, I do.
I do now.
Down again.
You explained to me how during an unleash,
this guy is able to dirty hit me still.
All right, I've got to make the plays here.
Let's go for a run.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm entering my unleash.
My unleash.
Why does it get stopped every time?
That was a default.
Oh, fuck.
That guy did a default tackle and I'm in a goddamn unleash.
I can't believe it.
It's okay.
Way to go here on third down for the big play.
Lots of quarterbacks can make a great pass in practice,
but it's out here during the game when the pros
really step forward with throws like that.
This is it.
I got to get that fucking ball back.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I'm so involved.
Done.
Out for the season.
I'm going to call it card.
Okay.
I got to get this ball back.
Yeah.
Get it out here.
I'm getting too amped up over this game.
First and goal.
I have to stop them right now.
Crucial series of downs here.
They can't get a touchdown.
Stay back.
Get that fucking ball.
Fumble it.
I got an unleash.
I have to use it somehow.
Just pass into the end zone if there is.
I got to activate it and try to catch it.
There it is.
Fumble it.
How on earth did you not recover the fumble?
Oh, that's unbelievable.
I can't.
How?
Those three of you.
Running around in a circle around it.
Pick it up.
The offense might want to mix it up here.
They've been a little predictable the first two downs.
Take him.
He's out of bounds.
All right.
Don't let him run up the middle.
Yes.
Okay.
This is bad though.
This is very bad.
I'm in my own end zone.
I got to get out of my own end zone now.
I got two timeouts.
Oh, shit.
I have no meter.
Oops.
I know.
That's okay.
Okay.
I got one more play.
I got one last play.
Get in the end zone.
Yes.
Okay.
Just kick it.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I'm so happy.
I'm still, I'm going to be undefeated.
I'm getting way too invested in this.
They got one attempt here.
They have to run it back or touch it right now.
They don't have a meter.
Play smart.
Goodbye.
Right way.
God damn.
Oh, I felt that one in my bones.
I didn't cause a turnover at all.
I lost the wager.
It's all right.
I'm just happy to be undefeated.
That was better than the actual Super Bowl.
Killed a man and won the game.
All right.
We got a call.
Hey there.
I just got off the phone with the sponsor.
They love what they saw doing the commercial shoot.
We did a little negotiating and they're throwing
in some additional gear for your team.
You can thank me later.
It was killing a man worth that money.
Franchise.
Good news.
I've been working my magic and I've lined up another big name sponsor.
All we need to do to seal the deal is have you make that end zone your bitch this Sunday.
Think you can do that?
What am I saying?
Of course you can do that.
You're the franchise.
God.
So I have to get a gain of 50 plus yards on a single play.
Currently 5-0 against the Crusaders.
Let's see what we got for sponsors.
Impact.
Plus two tackle.
Plus two break tackle.
Plus two hands.
Plus two speed.
All right.
Cool.
Exclusive sponsor equipment.
Upgrades.
Hands.
280.
I don't have enough money.
Damn it.
Do I just hold on to the money?
What can I do?
I can do blocking.
Probably need it.
Resist injury.
Turbo jets inside of the massage pool.
Agility maybe.
I'm going to hold on to the money.
Agility block.
I need no block.
Yeah.
Get everything to one.
That's not a bad idea.
What about drugs?
What can I take for drugs?
Okay.
I just accidentally took them.
I don't even know what they are.
What are those?
I don't know.
I just took a handful of random drugs and I don't know what they do.
Okay.
5-0.
I got five grand versus Cincinnati Crusaders.
I don't know.
After that last one, I can't believe I got to get my shit together, right?
Let me take a piss and grab another Coke.
I'll be right back.
Everyone says again.
Yeah.
I slammed that last Coke and now I got to pee it out.
I just realized something.
Holy shit.
Is it a good time to be a Boston sports fan?
The Red Sox just won the World Series.
Patriots just won the Super Bowl.
Wow.
I just realized that right now.
Let me know you didn't.
Well, I mean, what am I just realizing this yet?
Because the Patriots just like 40 minutes ago won the Super Bowl.
It's better to be a Las Vegas fan.
Well, not yet.
Not yet.
Not till like 2020.
But let's go.
The Cincinnati Crusaders.
Oh, must mean by more than 15 points.
I don't even have any.
No, no bet.
I don't have any fucking money.
This team's terrible.
They're one in four.
You're going to go up against the Las Vegas.
What's the team name?
I forget.
We're playing the Cincinnati Crusaders this week.
Hallelujah.
Their best player by far is free safety Ezekiel Freeman.
Ezekiel could be playing division one ball,
but he claims God told him to be a Crusader.
Come Sunday morning, he's reveling in the good book.
Sunday afternoon, he raises hell.
Okay.
So he's a safety.
Are you waiting for the Raiders?
No, not particularly.
That's going to be really interesting.
But I'm more of a baseball fan than I am a football fan.
So if Las Vegas gets itself a Las Vegas baseball team,
I'll be very, very excited.
All right, I have to make a 50 yard play.
That'll count for 50 yards.
I think.
Oh, there he is.
The Crusader himself.
Just shut it down.
God, come on.
He was a lightning bolt.
That was ridiculous.
That was so fast.
Where is he?
Top left.
He's the safety over there.
Hey, I'm supposed to be down there playing this game.
I really let myself go.
What happened to me?
I got to get away from that safety.
Let's go.
Let's go with a shimmy.
Two blockers on the right.
Try to go right between them.
Well, if you were there, that would have been a great run,
but you weren't there.
He was just blocking that guy.
Let's see if I can get a hook.
He's so fast.
Got it.
Now, let's go for a run.
Shimmy, shimmy right again.
Let's go make a cross.
Oh, okay.
I was going to go for a juke.
Didn't get it.
Same deal.
Let's go right in the middle.
That wasn't very cordial.
No, right here.
Just go across.
Oh, shit.
I got stuffed.
I just got stuffed.
No two-pointer version.
Just get the field done.
As he gets Greg Caliendo in a booth
and tell him to do every John Madden stumble he's ever done.
Actual via.
Dirty hit.
All right.
Keep the defense up.
Lock it down.
He's not on offense.
So don't have to worry about it here.
Good play.
And that's the end of the first quarter
Las Vegas leads by seven.
What is that commentary?
It is very odd.
Oh, let's stay.
Let's stay back.
I feel like you're going for a pass play.
Magnetized to his back.
Third down.
You know what?
Just blitz them.
Defense will be coming here on third and long.
Get it.
No, what a play they did to me.
Cincinnati gets some monster yardage on that play.
Defense in solid field position here inside the red zone.
There it is.
Broken neck.
What did I do?
No, he just went bent.
That was a little more than I thought.
That was a helmet to skull.
Sixth play of this drive.
Wow.
It's a neck and neck and two.
I was there.
I made the right play.
Watch this.
Huh?
Keep the arm on this young man.
Not to mention the accuracy.
Tug him.
And the extra point is good.
And that ties it up.
Jesus.
Jesus said so.
Nobody's got an unleashed meter.
So should be good.
Mistake.
But still got me.
Son of a bitch.
Out of the way.
Just make it there.
You got it.
Don't do any taunting.
Just get it.
I think it's gonna be codes.
I think he's got insurance.
I'm not.
Just get it.
Stay ahead.
Blocked it.
And the extra point is good.
Is that a new sponsor?
Did I get the 50 yards?
I think I did, right?
He's gonna have a meter in a second.
So am I though.
That this guy's back in the game?
Oh, don't let him in there.
Knock him down.
See an ankle.
Oh, the fluid.
That frog fin.
That was a frog.
That wasn't even a person.
And that wasn't even an unleash.
I still have one.
Intercept him.
Perfect.
Turn it around.
Watch this.
Bingo.
Still have an unleash.
I still have an unleash.
I'm not gonna use it.
Nothing here.
The guy, I didn't want to throw it a square.
It was like, what the fuck?
Oh well.
It's okay.
It's still up.
I still have an unleash.
I'll get it back right now.
Give me that ball back.
I'm running the clock out.
Watch this guy on the left.
This guy's coming up.
How many does it take?
You're gonna have to do a timeout.
I don't see a timeout.
Do you have any timeouts?
I'll take it.
One second.
Give me a break.
And with the first half of the books,
Las Vegas leads by seven.
Why would you not do a timeout here?
Did they not have any timeouts?
Oh, you just gave yourself worse position with the ball.
Unless he activates his thing.
Which he just did.
Okay, this is not good.
That's a fumble, isn't it?
All right, I thought he fumbled it.
Apparently not.
First and 30.
This is not good.
They're gonna get it.
Unless I can get an interception or something or a good hit.
That was pretty good.
Building meter slowly.
Please don't hurt them.
Oh, I'm not hurting them.
They are.
How did you?
He was right to you.
Get some more lotion ordered.
I'm doing hands no matter how much it is next.
Third and let's just call it third.
We're putting into a vigorous hand training.
Where's it going?
It's just salmon jumping out of water.
They gotta kick a field goal.
They're going for a field goal right now.
I'll take it.
I'm still ahead.
Oh, shit.
Did I get it?
The field goal is good.
They're chipping away at the lead.
Can they come all the way back?
God, fuck.
All right, don't burn it.
He let go.
He had it up to him.
Let's go for a run to the left here.
What a catch that was.
That reception all the way into the end zone.
Nice yards after the catch.
I'm going for it.
Knees that bad.
The conversion is good.
Now the game's out of reach.
They never win.
22.
What do I have to win by?
No, I didn't make any bets.
Deep zones.
The offense looking at first and 30.
The Super Bowlers.
They're about to win the Super Bowl.
Normal bowl.
That was a big hit.
10% stamina.
Back off, bitch.
That was a good counter.
The normal bowl.
Let's do some jamming.
Watch this right side.
Las Vegas.
What?
Did I just scoop slam somebody and they dropped the ball?
Quite trailing late in the game and giving it up.
I need to see that again.
What happened here?
So he's he backs up.
Okay, so he just kind of flicks the ball
from his left hand.
I was supposed to go to the guy right in the middle
and I'm in the middle of doing like a slam to some guy.
That, what a hero.
Not only does he belly to back soup like somebody,
he also recovers the football.
Nice job.
QB.
That was quick.
Trick play.
Look at this one.
Check this out.
This is going to be all over the place.
That was perfectly executed.
Even Crusader guy couldn't stop me.
Is he alive?
He actually got up.
I'm very surprised.
Cincinnati needs to make this a scoring drive.
They are one and four.
Looks like a fumble.
Las Vegas comes up with the turnover.
Oh, I was trying to shoot him.
These fellows may have just seen their chances
of winning fly out the window.
And so with three quarters gone,
Las Vegas leads by 20.
Hey, that is bullshit.
I got a play for you, buddy.
Under pressure.
And it's intercepted.
Ezekiel Freeman is hard to stop once the QB's in his sights.
He does that game in and game out.
Just consistent, great play.
Why pass?
Passing on first and goal.
I was going to run,
but then I got scared because he had an unleash
and I was scared he was going to hurt my quarterback,
which is the main player of the campaign.
And I thought I was going to be up for like five games
and then I had panicked.
I panicked.
Oh, it was right.
Get them.
What shitty hands.
Get a punt.
The receiver couldn't hang on to it.
You have to punt.
Fuck, how did I?
I thought I had the guy back there to receive the punt.
The 34 yard line.
And so they're forced to turn the ball over.
The offense not able to move the sticks this time.
First down, 30 yards to go.
Ball spotted at the 34 yard line.
Touchdown.
Thanks a lot.
Good job, Robbie.
Robbie.
A really outstanding run.
He blew past defenders and found some room to run.
Excellent work.
Robbie's good.
Let's take the field going.
No, we're so far ahead.
Who cares?
No, I don't want to.
What are you doing?
I'm getting booed.
Whatever.
The extra point is good.
Is Robbie juicing?
I don't think Robbie's on drugs this game.
He was on drugs last game.
Let's go for an injury.
How's the ribs?
How do those feel?
Here we go.
Hold on, man.
I'll give you a hand.
Come on.
You actually want to buy this?
I don't blame you.
It's a very, it's a very fun game regardless if it's a football game.
One of those franchises that kind of disappeared.
Because they did Blitz, Blitz the League, the Blitz 2.
It was in the arcades too.
Not this, but I remember Blitz being in the arcade.
I would love another Blitz from Midway, which then, which now turned into Netherrealm, right?
Or are they different companies?
No.
Owned by, does he own it?
I would love them to take a year off Mortal Kombat.
Okay, our new mantra is run the ball, burn the clock.
And make, well not a year, I mean like instead of a new Mortal Kombat cycle,
which is about 24 years sometimes, two years, that's wide open.
Looking for the big play and it's complete at the 30-yard line.
The ball comes loose.
Cincinnati makes the recovery and that hit drops him like a rock.
Every two years?
Yeah.
So they took a break from Mortal Kombat and made another Blitz.
Good, you good to go?
There was some great arcade sports games.
I don't like the simulation games.
Get up.
Don't let them have this.
Never gonna happen.
Yeah, there was the bigs, there was Blitz.
NBA Street was another amazing game.
Why do they only make these simulation games now?
What happened to the fun arcade sports games?
Wait, has anybody made one?
The receiver never had a chance.
He got pummeled before the ball arrived.
Because of the licensing?
Well, there's no license for this game at all.
There's no NFL teams.
There's no license here.
These are all made up teams.
Or should I say the defender got there early.
Big fourth down coming up.
They're not going to do it, are they?
We need to shut them down.
Nah, they are going for it.
NBA Street volume two is the best sports game ever made.
I might agree with you on that.
Feeling the rush.
Incomplete.
The quarterback needs to make sure his throw gets there before the defender, I think.
That's fairly accurate.
That's a turnover.
First down, 30 yards to go.
Blood Bowl.
Eaves it deep.
Oh no, please don't catch that.
And the defender says nothing doing.
And so, Las Vegas will take this one.
Oh, I didn't even do any timeouts.
It doesn't matter.
I went by a lot.
Mario Strikers was a great soccer game.
It was.
All these games lived in like the PlayStation 3 Wii era.
PS2, PS3.
Why has there been no none?
Next Gen has so much opportunity to make one of those.
And make them way better.
A new NBA Street.
Look at like the technology increases and the amount of things.
It'd be so much better.
Slogfest was awesome.
All right, we're going to get a cut scene.
Nice game you played today, kid.
Nice.
It was fucking awesome.
Sure thing, beautiful.
Where would you like for me to stand?
Don't undo it.
Hey, hold this, partner.
Hey, I want one too.
She a wraith.
Uh-oh, here comes the jealousy arc.
Oh, franchise, you're unstoppable.
Oh yeah, you just unstoppable.
Got that right.
Un-fucking-stoppable.
What the fuck?
Did this poison me?
What was it?
What happened?
Hey there, franchise.
I've been watching you since draft day.
You're good, but I can do things for you.
Your coaches and trainers can't.
Ask around in the locker room.
They'll know who I am.
Keep that body of yours healthy and I'll be in touch.
I can do things for you, okay?
Ask around in the locker room.
They'll know who I am.
Keep that.
All right.
What did I tell everyone?
I told them all that my main man delivers.
That was beautiful, franchise.
You and me, we're going to conquer the world.
Don't cheat on Kim.
I'm not gonna.
See, Kim's the only girlfriend.
New sponsor stuff.
Crazy grip.
Superior ball control.
I need more hands.
I told you that's what we're going to do.
First things first.
Take my 276, go to hands.
Passing, I could make my passing better break.
Tackle, break tackle.
That means I just have to make more money.
I got to make $250, $260,000 right now.
Is there another image?
What the hell?
That's amazing.
All right.
So we got training and everything's fine.
Juicing.
Let's go.
What do I got?
20,000 class drain by statement of loss to opponents.
No, no, no.
I want to give this to somebody on defense.
I mean, I am on defense, but do I get this on?
I get it on defense too, right?
Because I need to make tackles with myself.
Let's give Robbie something.
Reduce the chance of severity of injury sustained or stamina loss from tackles.
Let's go for it.
All right.
This is against the Cleveland Steamers.
Currently 6-0.
We are.
We have increased our stats here pretty even.
Besides, I got a little bit better defense.
Got to win by more than 23 points.
I don't have any money, so don't bet at all.
Why 6-0?
Can we make it 7-0?
We play the Cleveland Steamers on Sunday.
The best player they've got is wide receiver extraordinaire, Henry Cho.
Cho is like the bad guy in a Hong Kong action movie.
Hong Kong action moves off video too.
Cho's got style, but he has one problem.
Half the team is doing his wire.
What?
That's how you're going to end that?
Okay.
So wide receiver, a good thing I'm a safety.
Because obviously, you know, I can cover big play secondary and there's bad pass consistency.
Good evening and welcome.
Well, we all know what's at stake here for this team.
Another win and they're going to the division three championship.
Both teams are ready.
That's right.
Championship.
I got a championship incoming here on his head.
Right off the bat.
Two clips.
Good.
All right.
So I need to cover.
Where is that receiver?
Wide receiver, right?
I cannot let him catch a pass.
That's him.
Pretty worthless enough.
There you go.
I got you.
You don't think I'd see you?
Don't even give him a chance.
I know.
Shut up.
Thunderstorm.
Nothing.
That could have been a big play if the ball would have gotten to him before the defender.
Here comes the punt.
I get the ball.
Why does your team look like bubblegum?
Because I tried to make it my stupid colors.
It looks awful on the home and the away jersey.
It looks bad everywhere.
What?
Did he go through?
That's weird.
All right.
So he is not on the field anymore.
Pumping into each other.
Don't please.
Don't catch it.
No.
What the fuck did I do?
How is that such a bad throw?
Calm down.
No.
What the heck did I do?
Really?
Look at that play they just did to me.
Thank God.
He just sniffed on two people.
That's the guy.
Crucial series of downs here.
Thankfully somebody caught him.
Stamina has been decreased.
He's at 80%.
I had my target.
I picked the target.
It's time to put him up for good.
Put him out.
Third and goal.
Not the fourth down.
And he's brought down at the eight yard line.
Are you going to go for field goal?
I would assume probably.
Yeah.
And that's the end of the first quarter.
And we're scoreless.
Nice snap.
I don't know.
Goal line.
Special field goal block.
I can make it in there.
The field goal is good.
And a little more juice.
Touchdown incoming.
Blocked my unleash.
Dick.
I'm going for it.
See ya.
I had to go for that.
And I got a choke slam.
Nothing fancy.
Who gets the ball at the half?
Never in the bigs you can break the scoreboard.
Yeah.
You can do a lot of cool shit.
This is making me want to go back and play all those old.
All my old.
I mean like 10 years, 12 years.
Not that old.
Catch that.
I don't know.
That was inhuman.
No game.
Bigs didn't have a story mode.
Yeah, this is weird.
It has takes itself.
What the fuck?
I would have had it too if I wasn't trying to get a sack.
An opening in the defense for some real yardage on that play.
Big series of downs upcoming.
I thought I could have sacked him.
It was a risk.
Okay.
Second and goal.
I'm going to stay hydrated.
I agree.
Drink one glass of water per eight ounces of activity.
Third down.
Got it.
What?
That was insane.
I can't fucking believe that.
Tackled him.
He fumbled the ball to a teammate that was standing in the end zone.
Sorry, I was still in the game.
I got timeouts.
Nobody just decides to go get that.
That was a waste of an unleash because it didn't do anything.
Oh, eat shit video game.
Big play.
Field goal.
Just stay ahead.
The steamers eat shit.
We'll have one attempt here.
They don't have an unleash, do they?
No.
They have nothing actually.
They're not going to get anywhere.
That'd be a good injury opportunity.
I got like one or two plays.
Just watch that receiver.
Double coverage.
Don't let him get anywhere.
Robbie is my MVP.
Yeah.
I can see that.
All right.
No, I'm staying back.
Then you can pass it all you want.
You got nothing here.
I fucking can't believe that shit.
What the hell happened there?
You've got to be kidding me.
What?
I want to see it.
What happened?
How did he even get that?
All right.
We're going to have to talk about this, guys.
About this stupid nudge.
Sorry, I'm not going to have that happen.
Let's go with the sizzle.
Steamers.
And the ball gets there too late.
Or should I say the defender got there early.
This screamer is steaming mad.
I'm getting really unlucky here.
All these turnovers are a main reason why these guys are losing side of this game.
Unlucky.
I got a first and goal.
It's gut check time.
Ball at the 17 yard line.
This is my house.
Look, I'm going to do this shit again.
Play third down.
Watch this.
Watch this shit.
You're done.
No, I'm 6 and 0 right now.
It's a fake.
That's the best possible thing that could have happened.
Choke slam.
No!
Wrong button!
Get up!
Oh, I was trying to circle.
God damn it.
I'm so angry about that.
That was a touchdown right there.
And I had to press square.
I was trying to press circle.
Las Vegas gets it back.
I'm not doing that again.
Get it to Robbie.
He knows what to do.
Get it to Robbie every time.
Same thing, Robbie.
You do it.
My friend's trying to punch an 8 here.
Robbie, same deal.
Let's get it to Robbie every time.
They're not there yet catching up.
That was a hit!
I don't see any new kids in his future.
Get in there.
What's with all the fumbles?
Oh, I so badly need to upgrade those hands.
I should have just kept the money.
I should have saved the money.
That's like the third fumble I've done in this game.
Still plenty of football.
It's because of the rain?
Yeah, but where's their fumble?
Got it.
Fucking can't be serious.
I tried to select him.
Apparently, he wasn't the closest person.
I would have selected him and pressed triangle.
Bringing his man down.
That was a questionable hit.
If I get a conversion here, then I'm on a good spot.
I can't get a first down here.
All right.
Played smart.
I was just going to do Hail Mary.
That would not be smart.
First down and 30.
Got it.
It's okay.
I got like four blips for that.
I really, really need those.
Look at that.
I almost have a full meter again.
Let's get it out of range of field goal.
Just get a field goal.
Then I got to get the ball back with my meter.
I've watched more of this today than the actual Super Bowl.
This is a pretty cool game.
Thank you for joining me.
Those of you that are in post Super Bowl mode right now.
If you've watched.
Get that fumble!
Who's got it?
Look at how far back we are though.
I got a full meter.
I'm going to get this ball back.
I'm going to go touch down right here.
Look at how far the ball is.
He has it unleashed as well.
All right.
That's a good spot to be in.
Do I let the receiver catch it and try to hurt him?
He wasted it.
Fumble.
Okay.
Unfortunate but okay.
Honda!
It's a big hit.
Where are my points for this?
How come I'm not getting any meter?
Those aren't dirty.
Apparently they're not dirty enough.
Fourth down.
What do you got?
One minute.
Defender made sure there was no receiver there to make the catch.
Are they going to punt or are they going to go for it?
No.
They're punting.
If I get a touchdown here the game is going to be fairly out of reach.
And then I'll be seven and up.
No meter.
So I'm just going to get a solid run here.
That is bullshit.
Oh I got to play for you buddy.
First down.
Let's get it to Robbie.
30 yards to go.
Oh no.
Okay.
It's nothing serious.
It is though.
That was really good.
Only have three plays.
Three standard hits.
This dude is out every game.
Oh no!
Please tell me that wasn't.
He gets injured every single game.
Steve is taking the time out.
Third and 13.
Hmm.
Lightning.
Bastards.
Am I in field goal range?
My three.
Field goal?
How close am I?
I can get it.
No good.
That's no good.
That was a perfect kick.
What happened?
It didn't aim.
I thought the game aims for you doesn't it?
I don't think you can even aim it can you?
Shit.
He's got an unleash.
This is not this is very very bad.
Well there was no kicking tutorial.
Come on.
He jumped over the ball.
This is where I put the game away right here.
I can do nothing.
Just stay in the zone.
Outside of the zone.
In the zone.
Get in the zone.
Fuck.
That was an unleash catch.
Oh bad bad bad.
Come on.
Defense.
No!
What?
How do you catch it?
How is that possible?
Right up your ass.
I was right up your ass.
I can't believe it.
Why did I just do that?
I just tipped it.
I just tipped.
I just timed up.
That's not what I wanted to do though.
So game over.
Out of bounds.
I'm fucking believable.
I gotta make this.
I gotta have it happen.
Seven.
28.
29.
30.
I just need.
I gotta run it back for a touchdown.
No.
I can't do it.
I have to run it back.
I have no meter.
I have to instantly run out of bounds.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
I just hiccuped and almost threw up.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh my first loss this season.
I gave them a timeout.
Hey, but my character was like poisoned, right?
So that's why he wasn't as good.
It's scripted.
I'm supposed to lose that one.
Uh-oh.
Do I answer this call?
I got the championship.
We'll put Damon in his place during this game.
Okay.
I got to land a dirty hit on Damon
during the division three championship.
This is the championship game.
I made it to the championship versus the Hunts.
All right.
I don't know.
I guess everyone's on drugs this game.
How are we doing?
Somebody's a broken neck.
All right.
I gotta take a bunch of drugs.
Regenerate two stamina each play that they're on the field.
Yep.
Robbie.
Resistant to injury and wide receiver.
Shepherd is going to take.
Removes the cooldown effect from clash.
No, you're going to take a turbo bar terrain.
Good luck, everybody.
This is the championship game.
Look at how much better of a team I am.
Max bet.
It's the fucking goddamn Super Bowl.
Win by 16 points.
I'm going to just, I'm going to crush them.
Yeah.
You can only take three drugs at a time.
I wasn't poisoned last game.
I'm ready to go.
This is it.
It's the quarterback.
I got to land a hit on the quarterback.
Only three drugs.
What is this?
Oblivion?
Hello, everybody.
I got to land a hit on Conrad Daniels.
I'm excited to bring you the division three championship game.
Now I'd like to throw it over to my colleague.
By the way, this is like the Pee-wee leagues.
I don't know about you, but I'm ready to watch the football.
I mean, guys brought in the ball and other guys trying to attack.
This is the division three Pee-wee Super Bowl.
In that case, they tried to tackle the guy.
Nice start.
8%.
Am I dropping frames?
What the hell?
Shouldn't be happening.
All right.
So this is the, it's the quarterback that I need to work on.
First down and 30.
He's a very good quarterback.
It's gonna be hard to do that.
That was a good fucking pass.
He just got him by goddamn weight.
Get him.
You're not going to actually.
Who's, who's foot is that?
Is that my foot?
What?
What happened to me?
Why?
That's unfucking believable.
He'll be back.
I lost to a poop joke.
That's so, oh, what a, what a dog shit.
That's unbelievable.
How did you do that?
His first is a straw.
Oh, I know I'm behind already.
First goddamn exchange.
I'm going to lose the championship.
Oh, what is he doing?
Oh, that was so fucking funny.
First and 30.
He lets it fly at the 12 yard line.
It's okay.
That was a beautiful play.
Red zone.
We're going to go for a run.
Power it in there.
Offense goes into their red zone package.
No, what?
Didn't I take resistant drugs?
Why is everybody getting hurt?
Shattered tibia.
Everybody took too many drugs.
Last game.
So now they're all fucked up because they're on drugs.
It's going to be a miracle if I win this game.
I don't even know what to say.
Speaking of disaster, let's might as well just do it.
Bingo.
Got it.
Pop.
I'll take it.
That's fine.
What a beautiful pass.
You see that spiral?
I can't throw a spiral for the life of me.
Nothing.
We had, we both had unleashed.
What a video game, Choi.
Come on, man.
We got to do this all day.
Okay.
Kick off.
Tie game.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Not good.
I still got a guy in the back.
No.
Cardiff.
Why?
This is so unfair.
At what point am I going to have not enough people
to play the game?
It really might be that they're on too many drugs.
By the way, the guy in the back fell down on his own.
Dude just tripped in the snow.
This really is the Pee Wee League.
I got all my sponsor gear on too.
It's like bullshit.
I'm going to let you get that one.
I am closer to a special than he is.
All right.
Come on back in.
Good.
You good to go?
The rollback.
Whatever that is.
Throw it down.
There's no way you can catch that ball.
There within 30.
It's time to put up or shut up.
I got to get a dirty hit on him.
Here it comes.
Dirty hit.
I wish I could run like that.
I mean, if that were me.
It fell down in the snow.
I got a bunch of like random dudes
from like the AA leagues in my lineup right now.
It's not me.
Not a bad return.
Let's do crosses.
All right.
Finally.
Robbie's back in.
The offense looking at first and 30.
There it is.
That's what they call a textbook execution.
Still haven't seen x-ray ball crush.
Resident sleeper.
He'll go.
Just tie it up.
I haven't unleashed.
Let's see if I can get the ball back.
Give me that ball back.
Bump.
And so at the end of one quarter of play.
We're tied.
You thought I was making the beer chugging sound effect?
That'd be pretty cool if I was.
Where are we going?
It's that damn quarterback.
Can't see them go to shit their pants.
Yeah, we do.
He's got a lot of viewers coming.
Is there a raid?
Did a raid just come in?
There's the dirty hit, right?
The quarterback is the paint and the paint.
Whoever is hosting or rating or whatever.
Thank you so much.
That's a shitload of people.
Oh, this is blitz the league.
Nice.
That's exactly what I needed to have happen.
They're going to punt it.
Oh, shit.
They're putting it.
They had a long way to go.
That's right.
Good run here.
Come on.
We're good.
Everything's fine.
First down and 30.
Get a good play here.
That was a good play.
I still got plenty of time in the quarter.
Trick play.
Razzle dazzle.
Razzle go.
One minute left in the half.
We're all tied up.
Wide open.
Beautiful.
Don't even need to use an unleash.
Defense lost track of it.
End zone.
Nice catch towards turning into a touchdown.
Nicely done.
We got them just where we want them.
Let's keep twisting the tournament.
No, just go for field goal.
No reason.
The extra point is good.
In a good position.
Can you do anything else besides the beer chug?
Yeah, you can.
I just don't know the code.
And the codes, it gives you a blip.
So that's why I'm doing it.
By the way, speaking of blips, injury incoming.
Yes.
Las Vegas makes the recovery.
Thank God.
It's going my way.
Championship game.
OK.
Oh, close call.
Tough guy didn't break a nail getting the ball back.
Let's go for a run.
Crucial series of downs here.
That's OK.
I still got plenty of time.
Run the clock out.
Oh, no.
Please tell me that wasn't his knee.
Looking for the big play.
And the defender says nothing doing.
PS4 or is this PS3?
OK, I'm thinking maybe we should.
Why the hell is the team's sideline?
The offense might want to mix it up here.
They've been a little predictable the first two downs.
All right, I can get a field goal.
Just don't screw it up.
Field goal.
OK, so am I going to aim this in the right place?
Triangle square X circle.
All right, you got that was a good lay hit.
Incoming.
Wrong guy, but it's fine.
We've been a little frame droppy today.
I apologize about that.
First down, 30 yards to go.
Just don't let them get a touchdown.
There's 11 seconds left.
That didn't count as a dirty hit.
Milwaukee really executed on that big step down the field.
Nice work.
That didn't count as a late hit.
Sorry, just ended.
And so at halftime, Las Vegas leads by 10.
I get the ball.
What the fuck is this clown shit?
This is blitz the lead.
I'm running it out of bounds.
No, I'm not.
I'm running it into the end zone.
Oh, come on.
That would have been perfect.
All right.
I got to I got to play the the boundaries here.
Because first and 30 very we're in snow weather vulnerable.
He cannot fumble the ball to play the outside.
Fine.
I'm okay with that.
Get in there.
This same guy a second injury.
Robbie is out again.
That was not good, but it's okay.
This guy is made out of jelly.
There's no way he's made out of like rubber bands or something.
Fourth and one.
I'm not confident.
Go.
Just right through the middle.
Nice.
Let's go lightning.
First down and 30.
Caught it.
Jelly rubber bands.
You see the blonde on the sideline?
See her?
Huh?
That's a nice piece of ass.
All right.
Right side.
Too fat to push him over.
All right.
Robbie's back.
Circle circle square.
X triangle.
Did I actually just do that?
Fuck.
Go for it.
I don't care.
What the fuck is happening?
Get up.
Touchdown.
Snow.
Stupid snow.
Trying to get squished.
I didn't have an opportunity to do it.
We're printed out of reach in the championship game.
We might see an entire...
That guy wasn't even hard to play.
Uh, it's...
I don't know.
We're gonna have to...
I'm not sure you're gonna be able to see the testicles.
Sorry, guys.
I'm trying.
Damn.
That guy got hit for it.
Sometimes they...
You knock the quarterback in the next Tuesday.
Was that before or after when this game came out?
I don't know.
Goes way downfield.
And it's complete after 35.
Sorry.
We're still waiting.
Wrestling run after the catch for the score.
That's what I was trying to get a hit on the quarterback.
I would have had that guy.
I'm the safety.
I shouldn't be doing that play.
But I was doing it anyways, I guess.
Whatever.
I got it!
I actually fucking blocked the field goal.
Yes!
Oh, I've...
My...
Okay, that's a weight off my shoulders.
By the way, I understand that that reaction was as if somebody was dropping a couch.
And I was on the other side.
I got...
I got it!
First down.
30 yards to go.
Bad yardage.
Onside kick.
See, now they're just getting desperate.
Because I got the ball.
I got plenty of time.
All right, now I'm just being an asshole.
What?
Robbie, no!
He tried so hard.
He tried.
He was such an integral part of the team.
He's dead.
We gotta win this one.
Can I make this field goal?
Robbie's dead.
It's all right.
His memory will live on when we beat...
When we win the championship game.
To get out of Peewee leagues.
And to go into like...
Baby division.
Oops.
Do it for Robbie.
I'm gonna do it for Robbie.
From Peewee...
From Peewee to Weewee.
Yep.
He's a good player, too.
This is it!
Oh, no!
That's the...
That's the quarterback.
Out for the season.
Got it.
Nah, this game is unwinnable for them.
They have a backup quarterback in right now.
Why don't we kill him too?
We gotta get revenge for...
Robbie, what are you talking about?
Don't do that.
You don't want revenge.
For the broken, shattered neck that they gave to Robbie.
What the hell was that?
Flocky tears up a good chunk of field there.
And you can see him getting revved up.
First and goal.
It's gut check time.
What the fuck was that?
What the...
He could have fixed the receiver's eyesight at that time.
He could have garnered his name with a receiver's helmet.
He could have leveled the receiver's bookshelf.
Lasers are amazing things!
Okay.
Well, now this just became a game.
So, I have to run the clock out.
And the extra point is good.
They need a touchdown and a two-pointer version.
And as long as I can get a field goal.
It looks like they'll try an on-side kick here.
Uh-oh, Cox.
I don't have my all-star half-back though.
Pick it up.
Las Vegas gets it back.
Oh, the defense can taste that.
Game over if I can get an end-zoner.
I should get it because I have the unleashed championship.
Comes to Las Vegas.
Beer chug again!
27-40.
Fourth quarter game over.
I win.
Want to see something funny?
Oh, this doesn't run the clock out.
Oh.
Right.
Never mind.
I'm getting booed.
Yeah, on their home turf.
Good job.
I forgot that I thought the clock was going to run out.
That should have been a safety.
I'm not looking for wagers.
I'm looking for...
Wait, how many points do I have to win by?
That was such a bomb pass.
That's your last play.
Don't matter.
Might as well just give you a touchdown.
Fun.
And I got one second.
Quick, quick, quick.
I want to hurt somebody.
Let's game over.
Championship wins.
So Las Vegas wins the Division III championship and will move up to Division II.
That's it.
I win the game.
Robbie's dead.
Out forever.
I didn't get the $20,000 wager.
Silver trophy for a rookie.
Very nice.
I miss Robbie.
Both your A&B samples came back positive, son.
This is bullshit.
He's never used steroids in his life.
You're trying to bend him over because he wouldn't play for your precious LA Riot.
You know, franchise, I can make this go away.
If you play for the Riot and sign a six-year contract.
Oh, I got...
I got...
Fuck you.
No deal.
They're conspiring against me.
This is what's going on.
Last, if the sponsors hear you flunked a drug test.
Man, I ain't flunked no fucking drug test.
Except you probably did because we've been taking drugs the whole season.
Oh, shit.
Ultranull is on the FBI's banned substance list.
In fact, you've probably taken a drug every other game, franchise.
Sir, you're under arrest.
What the hell?
No time to explain.
Gotta get you a lawyer.
You give up that right.
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
Quick, dive out the window.
Is this the prison?
From the Newtown State Correctional Facility, Mr. Franchise.
Ordinarily, I don't like having celebrities in my prison.
However, you're a happy exception.
Man, what's this?
Well, it just so happens that next month we're having our annual football game
against the Supermax facility down the road.
And you just became my ringer, son.
That ain't no movie.
I ain't playing in some prison game.
You can play and be out of here in time for training camp.
Or you can refuse.
And piss away the next two years making license plates.
Or have to win.
So what do you say?
Super Bowl II.
Get out of jail.
Sounds good to me.
What time is practice?
Milltown Correctional versus the Supermax prison team.
There's a reason we've never beaten the Supermax prison team.
Oh, God.
It's guys like Carl Turpitz that have made that hell hole their home.
Turpitz is serving time for 23 counts of aggravated assault.
No helmets either.
Too bad we can't beat Shackle.
This is wild.
All right.
So, yeah, I think I know how to play the game.
What are the rules?
Is it just a game?
Is anybody watching?
No, this is it.
We're just out here.
Who are my teammates?
Oh, God.
This is ridiculous.
Okay.
So there's no kickoff.
There he is.
All right.
Watch out for the guy on the left.
First and 45.
Got it.
Touchdown right there.
First play of the game.
Get it.
Got it.
It's 45 yards from first down.
Muscle?
I got a new playbook.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
There's no...
There's no field goal.
You have to do a two-point conversion?
And now, okay, there's no kickoff.
There's no special teams.
This is ridiculous.
All right.
Not bad.
Well, let's go with...
Let's stay with cover.
That guy's not on the field right now.
Take the shoulder off.
That's always the most devastating one.
That guy gonna get up?
Nobody comes and even picks him up.
Is this it?
What?
Forgot how fucking awful that was.
Ooh.
All right.
We're good.
That's a turnover.
Let's go.
Let's go with the slant play.
Got it.
I'm still...
No.
Nobody touch me.
Oh, what's it?
Oh, beer chug.
All right.
I got...
It's...
It's all right.
Nice.
14-0.
Come on, man.
We gotta do this all day.
Let's get up, man.
Come on.
That's not the same voice actor.
That's a completely different voice.
Come on, man.
We gotta do this all day.
Is he going with it?
Nice.
That's a fumble recovery.
That's a...
56.
Play hit.
No helmets.
Let's go with zone blitz.
Cox.
Oh, Cox.
Cox is being stupid.
Fuck.
I was trying to knock him down.
I was trying to just jump into him.
Now, everybody does like the shit emote.
Oh.
Shit.
That's a safety.
Where are we?
What the...
Where was that?
Oh, my God.
That was bad.
This is bad.
Oh, the game's...
The game broke.
This is...
This is all glitched out.
Dude, I just intercepted the fucking football.
I can't get out of here.
Wow.
Okay.
Can we maybe relax here a second and...
Something is fucked up with this controller, I think.
Something's going on.
Weird.
I lost...
I don't see any player icons.
Shit.
See what I'm saying?
What the hell's going on?
Who's...
You guys know what I'm talking about.
Like, this is weird.
Did I win?
Yeah, something ain't right.
Ain't right.
I won.
I won the game, too.
That's unfortunate.
I'm gonna call that a win.
Did I save the game?
I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure save is on by default, isn't it?
Your current game progress would be lost.
Yeah, I got soft-locked somehow.
I knew something weird was going on.
I lost the player icons.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's annoying.
See if it's still there.
Everything got really fucky after the ghost interception.
It soft-locked the whole game.
That was going so well, too.
Okay, here we go.
Should be back to normal, right?
Yes.
Now I see icons again.
That was very weird.
I'll just beat him again.
Just win.
Is it snowy outside or...
I don't understand.
We're gonna...
His hand...
There goes his wrist.
And his forearm.
Let's hope he was right-handed.
Yeah.
I agree.
Another exploded collar bone.
And we're gonna make it even.
Was that the arm?
Was that the arm that he did that with?
That was with the busted...
That was with the fucked up shoulder, too.
That's so funny.
All right, let's do some muscle here.
Belly.
We got some weird movement there.
And go wide open.
Touchdown.
I couldn't punch into code.
Go right up the middle.
There are no...
Yeah, there's no kicker.
There's no punts.
There's no kicking.
It's just...
Play.
No field goals.
That was beautiful.
He anticipated that dough
for the exact moment that he needed to.
And this should get another touchdown right here.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Watch this.
No, that's me.
My back hurts after that.
Oh, come on.
That was fucking ridiculous.
I was gonna go for a QB sneak
and get another free touchdown.
Up in the old end zone in the sky.
This is like doing it for me somehow.
I'm like fucking...
What the hell was that?
Oh, not safety.
No.
How big is this field?
This is the second time.
First time, I had a ghost interception
and it fucked up the game
and I was up by like 14 points.
Now, I was up by 14 points again
and they broke my neck and ruined my career.
And I'm like, what the fuck is going on here?
I'm like, what the fuck is going on here?
Okay, I need to get these off.
It's a 50-yard field.
You only get one possession.
I can't get over that.
Stupid.
How did they have 10?
Me.
I love this game.
So that's man crush knockout
is square, square, triangle, triangle.
All right.
Can somebody explain to me why
we just both did the same thing
and they have two extra points?
I don't get it.
What happened?
Oh, the safety.
Right, the safety in the beginning of the game.
Right, right, right.
Of course.
Go for the elbow.
Oh, it was the forearm again.
You gotta watch this.
There it is.
Another shoulder.
Yeah, kick him in the shoulder.
We see that one all the time.
The exploded collarbone.
It's very, very loud.
Burn left.
Oh, no, they're going up the middle.
They're going right up the middle.
Mortal Kombat wishes it was this gross.
Well, this is what I was talking about.
When I was talking about how the new Mortal Kombat games,
after this game came out,
they started doing that, like disgusting stuff.
Listen, why?
This dude didn't have to do it.
He just fell.
Oh, I fucking don't even know what to say.
The dude just fucking rolled over
and his collarbone exploded.
What is it?
Was Ed Boon the dev?
I don't actually don't know.
This is an old Midway game.
I'm not sure if Ed had anything to do with it,
but watch out for the guy on the left.
Perfect.
Take it to him.
That's all it is.
Just keep your head in the game.
All right.
Can I actually win this one?
No, I don't even know what I did.
I tried to.
No, no.
The same guy.
Same guy, same shoulder.
They got the ball back.
We're going to go to overtime.
Oh, is that just the first quarter?
Third and 31.
No, we just keep going.
Second quarter.
No, I don't think I could see that.
I could smell you from a mile away.
I knew exactly what the hell you were doing.
I'll tell you what.
Thank you.
We got a ball spike.
That's the worst one.
I'm going muscle.
I'm going to go.
I have meter.
Let's go right in the middle.
I'm up.
No, Jeremy.
What the heck are you doing?
Just try to catch it.
I'm so hell bent on da.
Whatever.
Fuck.
I was trying to like dive into him and it's okay.
Now we are on a completely even playing field.
Safety in the beginning of the game does not matter now.
They've got an he's got a goddamn power here.
All right, we both have unleash.
Red zone.
We're going to go.
I don't want to use my unleash.
I want him to.
Wait, is that me?
No, thank God.
That's not me.
Okay.
I thought that was the end of the career again.
Thank God.
So now I have it.
See if I can convert this.
Nice play.
That's exactly what I wanted.
No.
It was for the team.
You did it for the team.
That was the guy that did the super tackle.
Triangle, square, square, triangle.
I'll try it next time.
Oops.
No.
Can I just play a game of football without having one of my bones explode?
Can I play everybody?
It's just like a 40% chance that if you get tackled,
your collarbone is going to blow up.
Just I got it.
He's the quarterback.
I'm the quarterback and I'm the safety.
Can I put him on the bench for the game?
God damn it.
I have to keep him away completely away from harm's way.
That means more runs.
Yeah, that bone heals in like five rounds.
If you get any injury, it's over.
Now I'm so terrified to even get involved in a play
because if I roll over out of bed like an old lady,
I'm going to get hurt.
That was good.
No.
He's the quarterback.
Okay, seriously.
How am I with the quarterback?
I just had to...
Oh, come on.
He keeps dying.
Okay, so I'm going to run at every play.
I'm just going to hand it off to...
And they're going to take the fall for me.
Don't run it.
When I pass it, if I get hit, it's over.
I need to have my like halfback run and do like quick little slant plays
with these little things right here.
See, like it's everyone's made out of fucking paper.
Oh, no, it's that mean guy.
Who cares about this, dude?
Just get the touchdown.
Was it the square triangle, square triangle, triangle, square, triangle, square.
All right.
And the quarters, they're lasting a long time.
Triangle, square, square, triangle.
Okay, it was triangle, square, triangle.
It was triangle, square, square, triangle.
Okay, triangle, square, square, triangle.
There he is again.
That guy.
Inmate 274594866252784.
Doing a great job.
Now you're out forever.
Fourth down.
I'll use it if I have to.
Oh, turnover.
Good.
Just don't do a big pass.
See, like that, that's me.
That's me right now.
If that were...
If I had the ball still.
Who cares?
Forget about like the jobbers.
Like the...
Hulk Hogan used to fight.
Like a nameless dude.
Don't catch that.
Who cares about like the warm-up matches?
Down shit.
Oh man, we got to do this all day.
Let's get up, man.
Come on.
All right.
See, everyone's getting their skull fractured.
What are they feeding us in here?
Whatever it is, it's not nutritious at all.
Nice catch, Tucker.
My character cannot put his hands on the ball.
I'm serious at this point.
I just have to run the clock out and try to play defense.
Didn't work.
I think I have to unlock them or something.
It's all right.
I'm up by 12 points.
And on defense too.
I can fall the wrong way.
I can roll the wrong way.
There's so many ways this goes wrong.
Clean.
Stay alive.
I got unleash.
Stay up.
That's probably only two halves.
Fumble.
Oh, I got squished.
Yes.
Okay.
Don't.
Just run.
Just run it.
I am up by a lot.
This long.
I don't.
I don't have to play.
I just have to survive.
This quarterback survived.
I could potentially turn it over.
No, I'm not going to do that.
I think it's like a half, right?
Okay.
18 to zero.
First quarter time.
All they have to do is kill me.
But as long as I keep myself out of harm's way, it's not going to happen.
Let's try to get the ball converted here.
I'm so concerned.
I got to kill that guy.
I know.
I know I got to kill this guy.
Doesn't matter.
Just always stay one step ahead.
Use it.
I don't remember using my unleash.
And Jeremy, why are you passing?
Thank God it wasn't.
It was this random asshole.
Classic beer chug.
Let's go.
I don't care about my team.
No, I don't.
Because there's no...
Nothing happened.
This is not my team.
I need to stay alive.
Okay.
Like this is probably the one.
We're not going to get any phantom players.
We're not going to get any broken necks.
He jumped over me.
Don't do any unnecessary dives with that character.
Let's go with the muscle again just to fake around.
That...
They have an unleash.
This is a guaranteed injury.
See?
They didn't use it.
Nice.
Okay.
Things are looking up.
Rushing attack.
Get rid of the ball!
Just don't be right.
Oh my God.
If I had to do this again.
I might have just had a heart attack.
I seriously thought I was going to have to do this all over again.
Look at how far we are into the game.
Where are my...
It's getting weird again.
I don't have...
No, it's getting weird.
People are walking in random directions and shit.
Okay.
I got to stop him here and that should be game.
Bingo.
Just run the ball.
Just run the clock out.
Just do balanced.
Just...
Just run it.
Who cares?
Pretty sick.
No timeouts.
I don't know.
What did I just do?
What play was that?
It's actually halftime.
He just was like,
Oh shit, I'm not supposed to have this ball.
You take it.
You actually have to play through all four quarters like this.
All I need is just to keep...
Stay ahead.
This is why you spec tank.
Yeah, I did not do that.
You're right.
All of my points went into tackling and what?
Like strength.
All right.
They don't get a touchdown in this game.
No, it's not true.
It's close.
We're number one down.
Perfect.
Dermot is so stressed.
He hasn't made a joke in like an hour.
Yeah, because I want to get out of the prison arc.
Oh, I broke his spine by punching him in the face.
How do you play?
That was some Mortal Kombat uppercut shit there.
That was Scorpion does that.
Doesn't that move that Scorpion does?
Self is a better player than me.
Well, I'm playing very timidly because I don't want to die.
No, I haven't passed the ball.
Self doing the work.
That's great.
Self, he almost had it.
No, was that?
No, that wasn't self.
All right.
I was going for a little bit of a play there.
Turnover.
They can't get by the defense.
This is good.
Same deal.
Hubert.
I'm not quite a lot though.
No.
Boomer overconfident.
Wait, is that?
No, I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
I'm up by so much.
I don't want this.
Right to self.
Okay, just right through the middle.
Fourth quarter.
We're almost done.
No, no, no.
Give me something easy right here.
Really?
That was kind of stupid.
Let's go.
That guy's dead.
I was trying to taunt, run, and it's the same stick as juke.
If it doesn't show up on the screen, you juke instead.
Made that look so good.
But holy shit, was it bad.
I got this.
That looked real cool for how bad it actually was.
All right.
I need to stop this nonsense and fucking win the goddamn game.
Again, he jumped up again and missed it again.
It's all right.
He needs like two more touchdowns.
It's not going to happen.
See, it's not going to happen.
My patrol officer says I got to control my anger.
Fuck that.
I'm going to get one right here.
Oh my god, what a fucking hero.
Don't do it.
I got it.
He ran out of gas.
It's okay.
We're going right up the middle.
Same thing, dude.
Again, exact same play.
They're not ready for it.
I got it.
Across the plane.
Now it's impossible for them to win.
Imagine if I broke my back there.
I would have shit my pants.
I got to kill the quarterback.
I have to.
Okay, I don't.
The play doesn't matter.
Just get rid of it.
I win.
It's over.
Early release.
The warden is pleased with your good behavior
and has arranged for your sentence to be reduced to time served.
You're free.
That was the real Super Bowl.
What about self?
Can self get out too?
Trade offer to be traded.
Hey, Ashwin.
Oh, what?
Oh, I can get Cho from.
All right.
That's insane.
Why would you want this?
Why would you give this to me?
Oh, I can pick anybody from.
I see.
From the last division.
All right, who do I got?
What do I got?
B minus for wide receiver.
What do I need improvement here?
Halfback.
Robbie died.
So wide receiver.
Wallace.
Look at that.
That's a huge upgrade.
We're going to go with Wallace.
Or Sullivan.
No, Wallace definitely.
Wait, hold on.
This is Cookie.
Wasn't he bad?
Doesn't Cookie bring the whole team down?
The only thing that will happen if I bring on Cho
is everybody will sleep with his wife, right?
That's what happened the last time.
Something like that.
It's tough to get rid of a B minus for an A minus.
I'd rather get rid of like a C for an A.
What about Sullivan?
No, we got to keep Robbie back from the dead.
Defensive.
What a latch off.
This is a defensive tackle.
Kind of necessary.
96 strength.
82 tackle.
I'm going to take Cho.
Or the tackle.
C plus versus an A minus.
Way more strength.
Yeah, we need some more defense.
I'm going for Latcho.
Robbie's dead.
We get rid of him.
Dump Robbie's corpse.
I mean, this is true.
He's dead.
Was Sullivan a team player?
We have to bury him.
He died.
Plus, an A minus halfback is ridiculous.
Done.
I know we're going to keep him for the meme,
but guys, the halfback is one of the most important players in the whole field.
Robbie's gone.
An A minus halfback.
You saw his neck explode.
That's good news.
Listen, you should know.
It's going to take a while to rebuild relationships,
both with sponsors and with me,
but I'm willing to stick with it if you are.
And hey, I just want to make sure that everyone's aware of this.
Robbie got injured every five plays.
So he was actually really on the field,
maybe like 50 to 60 percent of the time.
So did you really like Robbie?
He did make a few good plays,
but I mean, very though.
I'm going to pick you up busy trying to line you up some news.
You do know all the old sponsors bailed when you were convicted, right?
I didn't even know the sponsors.
But don't worry, because you work your magic on the field,
I'll do mine off the field and I will be forgiven.
Okay, so I got a question for those of you
that are in the stream hanging out here still.
Would anybody be against me beating this campaign?
Maybe not necessarily tonight,
but like next stream?
Would anybody think that that was a bad idea?
Because I forgot just how much fun this was.
Okay, so next stream, we're going to continue this.
I'm not stopping yet, by the way.
I just know that I'm not going to be able to get it done this stream.
So sorry, I couldn't pick you up from the slam.
Franchise must perform three different touchdown celebrations.
Next game, I got to do three different celebrations.
Do I unlock them?
Oh, okay, hold on a second.
Let me look at this.
Ace Attorney next year.
No, no, no.
So we got it was half back, right?
That's me and I'm a B right now.
There's Sullivan, the new halfback.
Bernie Cox.
How do I delete this character?
How do I trade this one?
Can I just delete them?
All right, we got a good halfback.
Fullback, not so good.
This guy's terrible.
I need some better receivers.
Ashwin's, that's why I didn't want to get rid of Ashwin.
Because B minus is the only, all these other guys suck.
Tight end.
Did this back up the B minus?
That's not bad.
Punter, my punter's not, the kicker's not bad.
I have a pretty decent kicker in punter.
I could have got Cookie,
but Cookie would have brought the whole team down.
Let's go to the trainer upgrades.
So I have 400, I need hands.
I told you this is the first thing I was going to do.
Grip master.
Do it.
Which leaves me with turbo jets.
I can't, I can't put anything else.
We can take drugs.
Train automatically.
What do we got?
So let me give, where is Sullivan?
There we go.
Okay, Sullivan's going to take decreased clash drain.
That sounds pretty good for a halfback.
Turbo bar drain slower.
That's really good for a halfback.
Yeah.
Wait, what's with the team risk?
Oh no, I just got in trouble for taking drugs.
How do I take those off?
Fuck.
I just got out of prison and I can't remove it.
I am going back to jail, I think.
Los Angeles riot is the next game.
Need to win five games to advance.
They're a much better team.
Las Vegas must stay within 11 points at the final score.
Look at how much better of a team they are.
Let's go.
Finally, we get to play the Los Angeles riot.
Our beloved commissioner's dream team.
The captain of this gang of all-stars is Bruno Bataglia.
Veteran linebacker and all-around asshole.
Bataglia surgically upgraded his elbow with a titanium replacement.
Not good considering the man already wrote the book on cheap shots.
Every Sunday he writes another chapter.
All right, be careful.
Titanium bionic elbow guy.
Titanium people's elbow.
Helmets become mandatory.
It's weird because this game actually still holds up pretty well.
Hi and thanks for joining us.
Nearly, what, 10, 15 years later?
It's a nice field.
Does it?
Yeah, I think it does.
Elbow.
Good luck.
See you later.
Fractured wrist out for eight games.
Say goodbye to your special teams.
So we're going to get a balanced defense here.
I got to be careful on offense because that's their captain.
Blocked it.
Still got it.
That was a 10% hit too.
Is this my new guy?
I think that, is that the new guy?
No, no, no, no.
He's a halfback.
Never mind.
This is where I gotta be careful.
So we have, he's right up the middle.
Holy shit, you still got it.
Better hands.
We've seen bounces.
Yeah, Madden's back.
We'll fake Madden.
Thank God I got away from him.
And there he is.
There's Sullivan.
Worth the pick up for sure.
You see how well he dodged there?
Team captain.
Nah, he's gonna field goal.
I almost just blew that one.
Very different celebrations.
Yep.
I think I have to unlock them somehow.
When's the next bathroom break?
There probably will not be a bathroom break.
Oh my goodness.
There will probably be an end of the stream for the next break, technically.
Bathroom's closed.
No game, good.
End of the stream P.
Haha.
Really kept that.
Still no first down.
Kill the other team captain odd.
Gotta get the ball first.
He's on defense.
Where you at?
He's got all the time in the world.
Kill him.
Kill their quarterback.
Yes.
Bruce Kinney out of the game.
Out for five plays.
That sucks.
Well, and they're punting.
And he's tackled at the 35th and so at the end of one quarter play.
I could have turned that into something crazy.
Las Vegas leads by seven.
That was a pretty decent play.
I have to get into that end zone.
He goes way downfield and he makes the crack.
And they make the attack.
Las Vegas with a nice game there thanks to some key downfield blocks.
Just pissing a draw?
What pissing a draw?
Let's get the ball to Sullivan.
New halfback.
What's going on?
Sullivan with a fucking beautiful catch.
We're pretty close.
Let's hit the end zone.
He should be able to run it right in.
It's okay.
Tongue?
You see that?
I've seen more gains in my mutual fun.
Not really.
That's just as pathetic.
Looks like his tongue is hanging out.
Do you see that?
Las Vegas covers it up.
Fuck.
Thank god for that guy.
I can get there.
Damn!
That wasn't very cordial.
Get in there.
He's your brother?
Big series of downs upcoming.
Touchdown!
Different celebrations!
Las Vegas now leads by 13.
Dead.
Sorry, I got too confused there.
Point is good.
That was awesome.
LA Riot.
Better team.
You don't get the chemistry that I do.
You got the stats on paper,
but you don't get the heart I do.
See you in the second half.
And with the first half of the books,
Las Vegas leads by 14.
Should have made the bet.
Yeah, look at the stat difference though.
I figured it was going to be difficult.
It was like a one and 14 that I had trouble with.
Not like the LA Riot.
Somehow.
Oh, he should be careful.
Stay back.
I'm gonna bingo.
Did I just break that tackle?
Oh no!
It's just a sprained neck.
It's not a broken neck.
I was about to be very sad.
83% hit being in two places.
Oh man, if this was a neck and shadow,
that would have been so sad.
I would have actually been so sad.
We got a new half back in.
First down.
Don't really care about.
He almost died.
No, he didn't.
He's going boys.
Okay, four new downs to play with.
It's just tight stretch.
Oh, it is caught.
He's going long.
Who the hell was that?
Whoever they are, they're getting a raise.
Touchdown!
Las Vegas increases their lead.
Who is it?
Number 80.
Let's get a two-point conversion here.
He is going.
They can't even score any points.
I need to celebrate.
I couldn't.
I got tackled.
If you get tackled in the end zone,
you can't celebrate.
I might not be able to get it this game.
Prison arc worked.
Well, what's this?
Las Vegas?
Better than LA?
Quarterback is in the game again.
This is...
Oh, that's why.
That's why.
I get it.
They haven't been doing shit because of that.
Envy football.
L-U-L.
The prison was the pit.
In the dark night.
Could I have gotten up potentially and caught that ball?
All right.
Let's do...
We're going to deep zones.
At today's section.
Let's try it.
The only other thing I can think of is that the quarterback must have thought
it was opposite day on that.
Tackle again.
Now people say,
sorry, I guess today must be opposite day when they screw up.
But for it really to be opposite day,
wouldn't it have to be?
Probably back in the game.
Crucial series of downs here.
He lets it fly.
Complete.
Un-voided, but I didn't even need to do my meter.
I wish I bet on this game.
Ever had that acid reflux, you know, with the heartburn and then,
you know, with the rest of it?
What are you going to do?
The extra point is good.
That's Ashwin, yeah.
Glad I didn't get rid of him.
I'm going to fail the challenge.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
You're going to see an injury.
That was just me.
The bet was to win by 11.
Holy shit.
10 community subs from Great Canadian FK Club.
This one's for you.
Thank you so much for the 10 subs.
Now that, that's a, that's a pog champ scenario, I think.
Could have caught it.
That meter.
Third down.
Bounce it out, little boys and girls.
Another 10 community subs from AmScoots.
10 community subs.
Back to back.
Thank you to the both of you.
10 community.
You guys are fucking amazing.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Why did he run that way?
I got an unleashed.
I got a sonic unleashed.
They do too.
Here comes the end of the third quarter.
Last play of the quarter.
And...
I didn't catch that.
I did not catch that ball.
And yeah, they should be chanting bullshit.
I would too.
Let's go for a run.
See if I can get it in the end zone.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, he's out for four games.
Come on.
That's, they're only like five, seven games in a season.
That's not good.
Now my 80 is going to have to step up.
That's Ashwin.
Ashwin really pulling it up here.
Miles on some more points.
The halfback Kirk.
Who's the halfback right now?
Cox?
All right, let's hope he gets his...
Let's hope he gets like his...
No, don't do an onside kick.
How do I change that?
It's all right.
I'm going to put 35 to nothing.
Everything's going to be just fine.
I, I'm going to put...
I'm going to go in the medical tent or whatever.
Put him in there.
I'm digging it deep.
They're getting desperate.
Is this the last game of the night?
This is going to be the last game of the night.
That is what's going to happen.
Figured it's probably a pretty good stopping place to beat Los Angeles as Las Vegas.
We will pick back up with this game because I, I am having a blast.
I love it.
And we're probably about...
We probably beat the halfway point of the campaign in the next game or two.
So, might as well just keep it going and...
Okay.
Have they haven't unleashed this whole game?
Well, they haven't really had possession of the ball for very long.
No conversion for you.
Did I get a ball crush yet?
Yes, I did.
Few times now.
That's not good.
He held onto it and he's not injured.
Good.
Got his revenge.
Two ball crushes.
Yeah.
Looking for, looking for, looking for somebody, looking for somebody.
Just go!
Cox getting in there.
Do it again.
Wow, that was fucking cool.
Um, um, hold on.
What is it?
I need to do one more, right?
I haven't done knockout.
Square, square, triangle, triangle.
That should be it.
Got it, right?
Do it again.
Just beat the fuck out of your own teammate.
Yeah, I thought I could stop him.
I thought I could stop him but I couldn't.
This game's over.
Start of the season 1-0.
It was a big hit but not enough to do an injury.
I think franchise has to do the celebrations.
Oh.
Well that, I don't think that's gonna happen then.
First and third.
Don't think so.
Do the philosophy mode.
Dirty hit on the floor.
That sack.
Well here's the injury potential right here.
Let's just go for a super blitz.
Just like a blitz.
Everybody.
All in.
You know what?
Like fucking field goal block.
He got it again.
Well I think I can stop it right here.
What a beautiful turnaround.
And there goes another broken frog wrist.
And that's the end of the game.
See you.
I'll see you in hell.
I get one more play here.
Hail Mary into the end zone.
See if I can win by like 50 points.
Cox!
Get in there Cox!
Too bad.
There's a lot of yards though.
There's a lot of achievements.
Probably a decent amount of money too.
No wager.
Oh well.
392.
Awesome.
Magic hands trophy.
And that's I think they're like the division leader.
I'm pretty sure I think that's like the antagonist in the whole game.
You just lost.
The ones that lost.
Slow down.
That's two shots in a row.
Slow down!
That's four shots of vodka?
He doesn't know.
Punch.
Three.
Two.
I'm gonna get fined.
Uh oh.
Franchise I gotta tell you this is not the way to endear yourself to potential new clients.
Sponsors are willing to overlook an arrest record but they still want winners!
Um dude I'm like fucking eight and one.
Hey man I hear you got a call from Tara a while back.
I know what she sounds like but trust me you're gonna want to meet with this girl.
She can hook you up with all kinds of shit.
And if she really likes what she sees she could be a real freak.
I think that's Cox.
You know what I mean.
Oh it's Bruno calling me now.
Hey punk how's it hanging?
Sorry I broke up your little love fest with sands but you know what they say the truth hurts.
When you're ready to leave that piece of shit team of yours and join the riot
give me a call.
Yeah I know the right people.
Hey Franchise got time for a meeting today?
I've got some paperwork for you to sign but trust me you're gonna like it.
You racked up over 200 yards on offense last Sunday and that got another big sponsor
beating down our door for your endorsement.
Award the pro cleats shoes by turf pros.
Let's take a look.
Protector, impact, crazy grip.
Pro cleats plus two speed.
Well I need them.
How much money do I have?
$392,000.
All right injuries.
I need this is where we need to.
Okay I need uh D Sullivan's got a broken collarbone.
Two games out.
One game out.
Get as many staff on him as I can.
Okay so now he's only gonna be up with one game.
What do we got for upgrades?
I think I want to do hands again.
No probably speed.
Yeah let's get speed to two.
I have no money now but it was worth it.
Girlfriends.
Kim provides exclusive sponsor equipment.
I got uh nobody else here.
Maybe training?
Do I have to meet with her or something?
Is there another place for me to do that?
Roster?
No.
This loser only has one girlfriend.
Nah I don't need to do this.
All right that's uh I think that's a good stopping point for now.
She's in the roster.
You have to equip the sponsored stuff.
So it's not just on.
So this actually this has to be equipped.
You sure?
I don't think so.
Yeah it's not here.
I think it's just on.
Shoes?
First name number oh I need a number nine.
Number is it double zero?
Or is 99 as high as you can go?
Change his colors.
90 is it?
85.
Yeah all right.
No I can't.
There's somebody on my team that's 85.
Then I can't do 69 either guys.
How about 50?
48.
Yeah I think it's just already equipped.
But that's going to be it for tonight.
I am going to take the next couple days off.
We went three days in a row here.
So I was going to take one or two days off.
I got some stuff I need to take care of in the house.
So I will see you guys on say Sunday.
I will probably see you guys on Wednesday.
And I'm sorry to all the Ace Attorney fans.
But I kind of want I think I want to beat this.
It's so fun.
I had what a blast this was.
The last couple of streams is like Space Channel.
They've been great.
Not that not that other streams haven't been.
But game selection wise I think I've been having a lot of fun with the game selection.
The last like four or five straight.
Larry Resnick will two into like Crazy Taxi and Space Channel into this.
What a great selection of video games in the last two weeks.
After this Ace Attorney yes I will try to get that to work.
I'll get my audio splitter.
But that's going to be the end of tonight's stream.
So thank you all for watching.
Really appreciate it.
See you guys on Wednesday.
For those of you that came in late.
Yeah there's a you probably have no idea what this is.
But that's all right.
I'll see you guys on Wednesday.
Thanks for joining me.
And Patriots won the Super Bowl.
That's I guess that's as a Boston and New England guy.
Tom Brady now can put a ring in every one of his bedrooms.
Implying that Tom Brady probably doesn't have like a 12 bedroom house.
So he has to win at least six more Super Bowls.
His bathrooms.
He probably doesn't have more than six bathrooms in his house right.
So we can have a ring in each bathroom.
They can just like hang it on the like on the shower or something.
But anyways let's go through the bits.
See you guys Wednesday.
Thanks for hanging out.
That was Blitz the League 2 for PlayStation 3.
It is a very very very fun game.
Highly recommended.
And we will complete it.
Hopefully on Wednesday.
And stadium seating.
Thanks for four dollars stadium seating.
Hey Jerm, I just want to say you've helped me through so much
throughout these past years whenever I'm feeling down.
I've always been able to tune into the streams.
Or watch your videos on the old channel and laugh.
And you've helped me through tons.
Just want to say thank you bro.
Thank you stadium seating for the four dollars.
And I'm I'm fucking honored that I'm somebody you can say that about.
So thank you so much.
Much love to you.
Thanks for the four dollars.
That was a really good photo ship.
Yeah a lot of them work.
Some guy nine thanks for the five bucks.
All right it's almost 2 a.m here.
I got to get up early so I got to post this meme video.
And go the fuck to bed.
What's what's what's what's what the meme videos lately.
My audio is in the wrong spot.
I just scratched my monitor didn't I?
God damn it.
Oh I can buff that up.
Something's what is it?
If this is Phantom of the Opera.
I'm deleting my YouTube account.
Oh it's the it's the.
See YouTube.com slash German 95 gone.
Deleted.
Just did it.
I clicked the two buttons.
Guys you don't understand.
There's a red button on on every desk I've ever owned.
That was delete all YouTube videos.
Every YouTuber has one.
You know just in case like they come for that.
They just give the they come for the files you know.
Somebody get like where are those videos?
Like in Mission Impossible.
The button didn't work.
Oh well and I got scammed out of like forty five thousand dollars.
Like they they're coming for like my secret codes.
You know what if somebody wants to take control of my channel.
Nope I haven't got the kill switch in there.
Thank you Jess for the one dollar.
Could you give me a new username change?
I can't think of anything.
I want to keep the Jess part.
Um how about uh how about Jess you got it.
Jess you got it.
It's a real that's a real firm handshake of the name I think.
Why is German so stinky?
Laughing my ass off.
You don't know what I smell like.
No idea.
Hopefully you like that new name.
Thank you Flugboy for the five dollars.
Super Bowl Sunday big love to you.
German thank you for being so great.
Also I'm gonna be the big 20 tomorrow.
Can't believe I've made it this far.
Hope you have a great night.
Happy birthday.
Yeah probably not sure what time zone you're in but happy birthday.
Big 20.
Two zero.
Thank you so much Flugboy.
Hope you have a good one.
Thank you creation the cyborg for the one dollar.
Hey German my grandfather died on January 30th.
Even though I never met him I was able to see photos.
Also the Wii died on the 30th and I bought my last Wii game.
Have a great day and let the Super Bowl begin.
I'm terribly sorry to hear that.
Rest in peace to your grandfather.
Sorry to hear that.
But yeah the Super Bowl began the Super Bowl ended.
Patriots won.
Thank you Alec for the one dollar.
Hey German how do you like your steak cooked?
Medium.
Depending on what kind of cut of meat.
I don't really eat a whole lot of red meat.
I don't really eat a whole lot of steak because it upsets my stomach sometimes.
But like a medium to medium well depending on what the cut of meat it is.
But it's it's it for hamburgers though if you'd like a cheeseburger.
I liked my cheeseburgers cooked all the way through.
So if I get a steak I'd want it done medium.
But if I get a McDonald's hamburger it's not medium rare.
If I order a burger I usually just say whatever like you know medium or medium well.
But I like it usually cooked all the way through for a burger.
Medium wet.
So burgers medium well steak medium to chef's choice.
Hope that answers your question.
Tingy thanks for the one dollar.
The audio splitter got lost in the mail.
Probably got lost in the same place as the Pikachu socks.
Yeah I don't know something about the mail.
I don't know what it is mail.
Fucking mail.
You guys are gonna be like everyone's gonna laugh.
When I finally get that mail.
Thank you Beck PNG for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma I'm here to force you to look at fan art.
Sorry.
Sorry what?
I wanted to make you something a little more polished in color.
So here's there's here it is.
You stream the perfect background noise for drawing.
Though sometimes I end up laughing so hard I can't see the screen.
Thanks for that.
Also you need to know your hair is extremely fun to draw.
As is the rest of you.
Keep up the clownery.
Look at that.
All right they're like here I'm gonna put this like.
Look at this.
This is just like there are a lot of talented people.
That watch these streams.
I want to get it on the screen.
How do I do this?
Oh there we go.
Yeah there's a lot of there's a lot of talented.
Even just like the photoshop manipulation shit.
You guys are so quick with the art the artwork and the the edits and it's great.
I gotta turn this off.
Hold on.
I gotta put my gotta put my feet in the microwave.
There we go.
There it is.
Why would you do that?
Take a look at that.
This is this is just wonderful.
You guys are so talented.
Yeah make sure we get the Beck PNG right there.
This is like Jerma is Jerma the Disney character.
It's got that like old school Disney animated feel.
I love it.
Well done.
Thank you so much Beck.
That is absolutely phenomenal.
Thank you.
Now you're gonna be in Kingdom Hearts.
Yeah that's Beck PNG.
I don't know if Beck if you have.
Because you linked me like a Google Drive.
I don't know if you have a art page or something.
But go ahead if you if you have it link it.
But thank you.
Fantastic stuff.
Thank you Mr. Sneak Man for the dollar 30.
Hey Jerma been getting a lot of Dunkin Donuts ice coffees in the last three years
and I want and I want you to know that the one birthday TF2 video where you drank
blueberry iced coffee fueled my iced coffee spendings for three years and counting.
I especially like the five percent of the time when the coffee actually tastes good.
Favorite flavor of coffee.
Well that that's Dunkin Donuts.
Dunkin Donuts is like a doll of 60 for a coffee.
For like a medium iced coffee right.
But it's Dunkin Donuts.
My favorite flavor of Dunkin Donuts is blueberry.
Just that's what I used to drink it all the time.
But now I'm more of a I think I'm more of a classical English toffee kind of guy now.
But there you go.
Dunkin Donuts I do miss Dunkin Donuts though.
It was just so easy to grab like a fucking dunks
because he knew nobody was going to give a shit.
It's like oh he's just drinking dunks.
It sucks.
But everybody it's good because there's no expectations and it's just delicious.
It is the it is like such a low expectation.
Cheap comfort drink I think.
I'm not even sure there's a Dunkin Donuts in Las Vegas.
I don't think I've even looked but I haven't seen them.
They're not as prevalent as they are in Massachusetts that's for sure.
But thank you Mr. Sneakman.
Thank you Divus for the two bucks.
Divus always coming in with a feud.
Holla's every stream.
Thank you Divus.
Grimoire for the five dollars and five cents.
Thank you Grimoire.
Hey Jerma I work at a vet in Vegas and like a year ago
when you announced your move I dreamed that I saw Otto at work
and instantly recognized him because I've seen Otto's big adventure one and two dozens of times.
What?
Wait we're spamming a link here?
What's going on?
This is another.
I would put this on the stream but I don't I want people to be able to go to bed tonight.
You know I would really love it if people could like be able to go to sleep tonight.
I can't even like save this link.
This link is like unsavable.
It's a video.
This is this is an mp4.
How do I pull an mp what?
Let's see if I can get this on the screen.
I apologize to anybody that oh wanted to go to sleep because here is here's a strange video.
It's over on both monitors now and it's freaking me out.
I have to take it off.
That's my transition into the green goblin.
Holy hell.
But thank you Grimoire.
Las local Las Vegas vet.
Little Otto.
Hey robot mentality thanks for the five dollars blood for the blood god.
Thank you for the five dollars.
I'm something of a goblin myself yeah.
Hey scar thanks for the one dollar so I'm not sure if I should tell you this
but this man approached me and said he was a top 1000 streamer or something
and he threatened to snap my back in half.
It's just that fucking image of my face and that it's that's it's like this one.
No it's this one.
It's this one.
It's not that one it's this one.
But with like the other guy's face whatever.
That didn't happen.
I made the original one and the reverse one.
This is so fucked up.
This one doesn't this looks like a different person.
All the other ones have looked like me
but it's weird how the bottom of my face doesn't even look like a face.
This doesn't even look like it could be me.
This is some weird cousin.
Thank you scar for your multiple manipulations of photos.
Thank you.
We also have Freudian weapon five dollars.
Thank you Freudian weapon.
Appreciate the five dollars.
Code man.
Thank you code man for the one dollar.
German looking like Handsome Jack from Borderlands 2.
Borderlands 2.
Thank you smarky.
Thank you smarky for the five dollars.
German I didn't know you were in a band.
What is this band?
What band is this?
Is that um I don't know what band that is.
Booger eating stream.
Why did I read that?
They did a song on Tony Hawk 2.
Oh okay.
Lit bulb thanks for the one dollar.
Oh I get it because today is the Super Bowl.
Yeah see there you go.
You got it.
You get it see.
And a Wednesday is not the Super Bowl but we're playing it again.
This is a four day long Super Bowl routine.
Thank you creation the cyborg for the one dollar.
I promise I will get the internet box.
I have no idea what you're talking about but thank you for the one dollar.
Timmy Timtan thanks for the one dollar.
Video games really do make people violent Jeremy.
You're gonna go run down to the Super Bowl
and punch no.
Thank you flank tank for the three dollars.
Now the Dreamcast is over.
Ever think you would do Nintendo 64 set of streams?
Some 90s Nintendo nostalgia if you ever do my vote is for Kirby 64
excluding the obvious Mario, DK, and Goldeneye.
Yeah I think all the old consoles should show up eventually
but I think we really need to take a break from them once they're done
because there's so many games to play
and so many things to see on the old consoles
that I don't want to just all right Dreamcast
we just played like 15 Dreamcast games.
Bring on the 64 next week.
I'd like to do them maybe once every six months to a year.
So because the last time we did the when we did the big PlayStation 2 and
PlayStation 3 I mean this is a PS3 game
but this is obviously this I played this game for six hours today
but usually once like every six to twelve months or so I like to really
because it is expensive too you know I think just get emulator
but I really I'd rather I'd rather play it the way it's intended to be played.
So you know buying a Dreamcast in 15 games I mean that's it's I think the total bill
for the Dreamcast stuff was at least like seven or eight hundred dollars for everything
so you can't really I can't really do those like once a week
GameCube like the plate I've spent probably thousands of dollars over the last couple years
on just old console stuff.
Sega CD those were very expensive just because they're so old and rare.
That's a lot of bits.
Do I still have the Sega CD?
Uh I do.
I do it's in a box somewhere do I?
I think it's in like a box somewhere did I get rid of it maybe I did.
Stop flexing.
No well I'm just explaining why um on top of I don't want to just have every
those streams are really fun to do and they're really fun
but once they're done they're done.
You know if you do like let's go back and play a bunch of random 64 games
there we go here it is all right that we I can't really do that again
you know it's pretty much a one hand a poker.
Now there are some great games that I maybe want to play through
but once you play through them that they're it's it they're over.
Like for instance Dreamcast I can't like go back and do Space Channel 5 part 2
that it's done it was a three or four hour experience and that's it.
So I want to like save them for uh times when I know that I want to complete something
or when I want to do it full week dedicated for N64.
I kind of did that for Dreamcast and PlayStation 2 we did Dreamcast games
for like three streams in a row or at least three out of the four
and there are some experiences that I didn't get a hand of
that I want to do still for some of those old consoles.
There's still PlayStation 2 games behind me that I never did just kind of ran out of
time slots to put them in but yes N64 you will definitely see it eventually
I just can't really tell you when but thank you Flank Tank for the three dollars as well.
Hey creation the cyborg thanks for the one dollar it's 9.43
meaning not a lot of time of time for what am I missing something here?
Thank you Dirty Margaret for the one dollar I really thought you were going to lose to Detroit.
Jax does it again uh thank you creation the cyborg for the two dollars here
uh you missed a Sega Dreamcast exclusive uh Star Wars collection on Etsy for 15 dollars
do not get Halo for the Dreamcast it sucks.
They did a halo for the Dreamcast they did like a modded halo for Dreamcast
well uh is it like an is it like a black market Etsy video game modded community?
Do people make like Dreamcast games still is it is this that's pretty interesting I didn't
even know that but I think like the old console stuff is probably done uh for Dreamcast at least
like for a while probably revisit revisited is neither this name sneak I don't know what the
sneak means um but the last sentence didn't come out correctly the key was in the lock
but the key wasn't all the way in and I turned it anyways and I couldn't turn the
door and open the door so the key went back in all the way and I was able to unlock the door
we're fine uh thank you Dr. Clay for the one dollar if you're looking for a recent
modern blitz type game you should try out the mutant league football it's on steam and switch
is it like this because if it's like blitz I would definitely give it a try
now isn't there like a turn-based football game is that what this is
I know this is a turn-based kind of like x-com football game isn't there
is that what this is so it's not like kind of madden style with you know passing and running
with the analog it's more of like a strategy game right no okay so mutant league football
is different okay so that's blood bowl okay I will definitely check it out because I love
blitz blood blow is the warhammer one okay yeah that makes sense uh thank you to
me for the one dollar your drummer started an nhl meme page about three months ago just wanted
you to know that the success I've had couldn't have come without your inspiration and motivation
it's already gained nearly 7 000 followers in just a few months and I know it doesn't seem
like many followers yes that's a lot but it really feels like once in my life I have a
serious influence in voice and things I care about anyways love you germa if you want to
go check out the page it is it is kaylor dot me me me mateo me motto me motto me me moto
oh okay I see uh they say fuck some I don't know what that is but 7 000 followers is a
lot of people that's 7 000 people would ever play the bigs or nhl hits probably
because I remember the bigs being one of my favorite baseball games we'll see one game at
a time but thank you uh kaylor me a moto and congratulations on the followers and
hope you having fun thank you oh muffin for the one dollar they say gay rights
absolutely thank you the one dollar thank you gucci for the five dollars uh nothing just no
message just five dollars dr epic frag thanks for the one dollar streamer gets cleveland
steamed on stream oh no forgot I forgot about that thank you for the one dollar thank you
dirty margaret for the one dollar the blitz cut scene is just a gta4 movie maker I think
for their time they're pretty good that opening cinematic is very well made
remember this is the modal combat guys they know animation they know movement they
know exploding testicles some of the best work they've done thank you sly 161 for the one dollar
thanks to this game I now know that the human collarbone is a ticking time bomb that can
explode at any moment thank you effectator what's up effectator thanks for the one dollar
I was born with glass bones and paper skin every morning I break my collarbone
and every afternoon I break my collarbone thank you for the one dollar and sorry to hear
uh smashly thanks for the five dollars beer chug is greater than default fortnight dance
yes it is it is it is you just made you that was a correct statement you just said
uh thank you windar for the one dollar can't wait for this to be a major motion picture
selling millions worldwide and telling us the amazing and very true story of the la riot team
they even have to bring a tissue for how much I cry shaded thoughts thanks for the dollar
bro luck thanks for the nine dollars and 85 cents 985 thank you so much bro luck I'm sorry
I've been tardy here's the bits you asked for well a perfect amount of bits right uh thank you
so much bro luck thanks for the nine dollars and 85 cents uh Nile Orion thanks for the one
dollar firm handshakes all around all around all around the table hey binary man thanks for
the one dollar hey Jeremy no stupid video this time I just want to point out that the past
few have been audio from left 4 dead 2 and not anything creepy so that last video from the last
stream was not me leaning into the microphone being a weirdo that was left 4 dead 2 sound
effects well you you fooled me but thank you for the one dollar thank you hans beats for the
one dollar they say blip blop blip blip blip thank you hans beats shawnee noodles thanks
for the five bucks and and who they're probably out drinking right now that's a stellar
reference to the jurassic park slippery arm game which I wish I could delete my memory and go back
and play that one again that's like one of my favorite video games I've ever played on stream
thank you for the five dollars though shawnee uh mom oh the peach thanks for two bucks couldn't
see much of the stream because my dnd session I want to stop by and say hi thanks for stopping
by maybe we'll see you next time thank you so much for the two dollars and hopefully dnd went
hopefully you cross the point of uh the field of action whatever it's called I hope you cross
that field of action and you rolled a d plus six I don't know what's called when you cross
over somebody you'd like going next to them and they have to attack them or they have to attack
you the field of act what is it called action of opportunity what's it called attack of
opportunity there you go hopefully you got the attack of opportunity and you you're saved the
day thank you so much uh bro luck thanks for the five dollars and 15 cents I can't believe
you admitted this on stream I promise it's not a snort I did purchase seaman and the mic
I did I I bought seaman and the mic and the mic didn't come in the box so I had to return it
and I have to even check to make sure that I got like the credit for that because that was
fucking expensive that was almost a hundred dollars yes you heard me right you cannot buy
seaman or the mic the mic for the dreamcast is like 80 dollars and it's the only way you can
play these games on dreamcast that was a hundred fucking dollar purchase it's so rare apparently
seaman is expensive incredibly for some reason the disc isn't but when they bunt they they get
you just buy the disc why would you sell just the disc maybe I guess maybe if you
assume that you just have the microphone nobody has that the game requires a lot of time too I
figured maybe we could spend a long time on it at least like a few hours on stream
desperately trying to make a fish friend but we'll have to wait uh always make you always
check your amazon orders because that was two out of I believe 14 purchases that weren't correct
they either were missing items yeah they were just missed disc one not in stupid invaders
and mike not in box clearly explicitly stating mike included I wouldn't have paid that much money
if it didn't say that unbelievable but uh thank you brawler to the five dollars and only a few
more uh james stir thanks for the one dollar no message just one dollar thank you uh we had
creation cyborg for one dollar what actually was going on a few hours ago uh your your
mother was gonna take the internet you listen you gotta listen to your mother uh I don't
know why you don't you don't disobey your mother you gotta listen to your mother your mother
asks you to do something you gotta do it it's your mother sorry mom yeah you gotta listen
to your mother but thank you for the one dollar and I hope you're doing well uh just you got
it there it is just you got it one dollar I now realize this could be read as just you go
tit but that's fine too no it's just you got it name change there it is and that's gonna bring
us to the end of the bits thank you all of you credits are gonna roll by which will lead us to
the next few days like I said no stream over the next couple days Wednesday we're gonna finish
maybe no I don't know we'll see at least we'll see how far we get in blitz the league but I
am immensely enjoying myself hopefully you are too take care much love to you all let's
roll those credits they're not on screen why is that oh it's because there we go all the
resubs of the new subs you guys are amazing thank you so much all of you roll them creation
the cyborg thanks for the one dollar you're right I'm sorry uh you got all f's and do I
have fan mail I do not have a p.o box that are not accept any mail but um take take care
of your schoolwork you know you gotta be you gotta take care of your schoolwork you gotta
take listen to mom take care of your schoolwork hopefully that's not true hopefully that doesn't
sound very good hopefully you can work out on that and get um some better performance in school
because it is pretty important did you take care of your schoolwork I took care of enough
of my schoolwork like I said you don't have to get a pluses just you as long as you show
up and do the work and you give a shit enough to take care of it you can you can be a c
plus streamer like me that hurt me no don't listen to any of my advice ever unless it's
like the five percent of the time when I'm like dead serious mode uh but thank you effectator for
the one dollar mod unmod timeout then ban effectator and permanently delete their twitch account
wait uh can we welcome the new moderator of the channel uh effectator if we could that'd be nice
I think I was supposed to do that like two months ago hey creation the cyborg thanks for
the one dollar I'll do it jerma I promise I'll do it for you and mom also tell sega and
shito I said bye they say goodbye and shito especially says hope you do well on that schoolwork
listen to your mother now I gotta unmod you effectator and then I gotta ban you so well
we'll how about this I won't we'll wait a little bit you didn't give me a time frame for
this so I modded you I'm gonna unmod you in like eight months and then I'm gonna ban you
like a year after that and then I'll delete your twitch account like three years later
we don't have a time frame all right that's my time see you a stalling streamer do me next
no uh have a great rest of the night everybody and uh mr manager you just came in with a new
subscription right when I'm about to turn it off look at that see you guys wednesday
cheers and congrats to the new england patriots on winning the super bowl your new
england patriots good night everybody