What's up? How's it going?
What are you doing?
Yeah, today we're going to be continuing the Resident Evil 4 Remake playthrough.
Last thing we did, if you're trying to avoid any spoilers or something.
We killed the, uh...
How do I say it? I don't want to spoil it.
Big body of water.
Something there.
I don't want to spoil it for anybody.
We killed the big monster in the lake.
That was the last thing we did.
And we moved on a little bit. We did like another couple of areas.
I spoiled it.
It's okay.
Crap.
Yeah, how you doing?
Not going to waste too much time in the intro because I really want to play.
I've been wanting to play this game.
I was considering reverse delaying yesterday.
I was like, you know what?
I don't think I'm going to do it.
And Holly and I looked at the clock.
It was one o'clock in the morning.
It's like, well, I can't do that now.
I can't do that.
It's like, oh, man.
No, reverse delay?
Maybe.
What time is it?
1 a.m.
Oh, never mind.
Yeah, let's just go.
I don't got very much to talk about besides this.
Stop staying up so late.
I don't really stay up that late.
Well, that's a lie.
Recently I've been staying up pretty late.
But I...
I want to say the last few years,
I've really tried to go to bed before 3 a.m.
Really, really try to do it.
It can be so hard, though.
I try to get to bed somewhere between 2 and 4,
which will reliably allow me to wake up at some point in the morning into the...
Because I don't like waking up early in the morning.
It doesn't matter if I have seven or eight hours of sleep
and I wake up at 8 a.m., 7 a.m.,
I feel fucked up.
And it's been like that forever.
Since I was a kid, all through school,
all through my early adult life into my kind of mid-stage adult life here.
I just cannot operate at 7 to 8 o'clock in the morning.
I can't...
I feel like that's forever.
But you move that forward
instead of going to bed at 10, 11, 12, waking up at 7, 6, 7, 8.
I don't know what, you move it forward two hours.
I go to bed at 2 or 3 in the morning, wake up at like 10, 11, 3 a.m. to 10.
It just works better for me. I don't know why.
You're a vampire, huh?
Oh, I don't think so.
Is he going to play the game?
I just turn...
I know you just fuck with me.
You're trying to get me to go off.
And I'm going to be better about that.
I can tell now.
You know how you guys can tell when I'm doing a bit...
Oh, here comes the bit voice.
I can tell now when you guys are writing the LOL Vitamix blender.
Like, oh, hey, what blender should I get?
I'm aware of that now.
You don't think I started to sense this?
It only took you like six years.
I mean, I'm...
Yeah, that's true.
Can you play Project Zomboid?
I wanted to.
I wanted... There's too many things I want to do.
Sorry, I didn't say anything.
I was just stirring up this fucking tea.
All right.
You guys ready?
Resident Evil 4?
You guys good?
Oh, also, there's a new Grotto Beast video talking about deck building.
You want to...
The Grotto Beast YouTube has a new video.
If you want to go check it out, if you're not into that,
then hey, Resident Evil 4 is about to begin.
Let me link it so you can see it.
Yeah, our game designer is making these.
Grotto Beast has a YouTube if you want to check it out.
It's part two of a series.
There you are.
Why is my chat going so slow?
No, not like my chat is going so slow.
Like, computer is going slow.
Why is my chat going so slow?
That sounds like egomania.
No, I'm saying like my computer is slow right now.
Why?
All right, you guys ready?
Resident Evil 4 headphones are going in.
I got my drink.
I've tweeted and I'm ready to play.
I've been waiting for this.
What's up?
How are you?
Both headphones are in.
I can't turn the lights off.
I'm on the West Coast.
I'm on Pacific time.
So it's it's almost six o'clock Pacific, but I can't turn the lights off.
They already are off.
When it gets darker, I will turn off some things and we will have a nice scary environment.
I promise.
What about your you have blinds?
They don't they don't lock out everything.
It doesn't matter.
You know what?
I've thought about getting but I actually don't want you know those hotel complete blackout curtains.
Those things those things are so dangerous.
I don't really want those because when it gets to be 7 8 9 10 11 12 o'clock if it's still pitch black in your room
and you kind of wake up for a second, it's like oh, it's still nighttime.
I'm so tired.
It's sleep time.
Having natural sunlight kind of come in.
Otherwise, I will sleep till 5 o'clock in the afternoon.
If I have blackout curtains, it throws me off big time big time.
Okay, they are nice though.
They are they are nice.
I have them and to be honest, it does make it harder.
You know, I want to get a sleep mask.
I want to get one of those eye things.
Is it bogus that that actually makes you sleep a little better?
Is that for real?
Those things work.
It blocks out light.
Well, it's the same.
Wait, it's the same thing.
It's having blackout curtains in front of your face.
So that would probably be bad for me.
If I don't want blackout curtains, then I shouldn't do like blackout thing on my eyes.
That would be bad.
No, whatever just wear sunglasses to bed.
All right, let's go curtains work better than a sleep mask.
I'm going to give you a black eye.
All right.
All right, dude.
All right, settle down.
Next game.
No, get out of here.
All right.
What was I doing?
I got another gem for this, didn't I?
Ruby's all rubbish.
It makes no difference.
The price will.
That's our choice to make.
Is it okay if I gamble?
To suit your specific...
I don't know.
Are you old enough?
It's a thing of beauty.
Wait, I don't know.
I can't answer that question.
I don't know.
The answer is probably no.
Are you using it for entertainment value only?
Okay.
Let's see.
Yes.
Okay.
The answer is no.
Don't.
That's all there is to it.
This is the new pistol I got and this thing is unbelievable.
I think I...
All right.
Should I sell the other pistol and just dump it into this?
The game's a little quiet.
I'll fix that.
I probably should.
This is like the best gun.
Not seeing anything you like, stranger.
I'm selling the thing that I was using.
Nineteen thousand.
I'll buy almost anything.
This is not stupid, right?
Because then I'm going to dump it all into the...
Because this weapon is awesome.
This is the play.
This is what you do.
I'm selling it.
And people...
Whatever.
I've ruined my playthrough.
A deal well struck.
Okay.
I want ammo capacity.
There you are.
I want power.
Dazzled.
And I want...
Our craftsmanship demands no less.
Ammo capacity again.
There we go.
We're starting to get an idea of your taste, friend.
I know.
I'm stalling.
I am.
This is like one of the best games ever made.
I'm going to stall a little.
Lack of skew, friend.
I'll have a knife too.
I should do this.
All right.
Well, this thing is awesome.
I'm going to use it.
It's going to be so deadly.
Everyone's going to be so jealous that they don't have this.
Because I knew where it was.
Why am I sinking?
That was weird, wasn't it?
Was that weird to anybody else?
That was kind of weird, wasn't it?
Did I just lose my mind?
That was weird.
I felt like my character was sinking into the ground.
I don't know.
That was...
Oh, it's because there's an incline here.
Okay.
I was wondering.
I was like, why can I...
Why am I like at eye level with the save thing with the typewriter?
What?
All right.
So the last thing we were doing, we're going now to two locations.
I got to get in the boat and go down here.
But we're going to be a hundred percent completion, Andy.
And I think I'm going to go this way.
Can I even get there from here?
And where's the boat?
The boat's down here.
I got to go down the stairs.
Okay.
I already tried that.
Sell the crown.
I'm not selling the crown until I have all gems fully socketed.
I'm not selling until I get it fully socketed.
Why do you look so angry?
It's just my face, man.
I'm sorry.
This is my face.
All right.
So did I try to go?
I don't think I docked here.
Let me try it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I can go this way.
What do I have for a weapon right now?
There it is.
This thing is awesome.
Can't go that way.
I've been so waiting to play this too.
Both headphones go in.
Watch out.
There's no jump.
I don't know why I just tried to jump with spacebar.
Not bad, right?
This gun's awesome.
Oh man.
What the fuck just happened?
Can you parry these things?
Oh my God, please.
The glasses.
The glasses is staying on permanently.
I want to put on all the other stuff too, but you know, whatever.
We'll see what happens.
I've been playing on stream for a while tonight.
So hmm.
But he looks so lame.
You can't even see.
You don't even know that he has sunglasses on right now.
You don't even know that.
You can't even see it.
It's only when he talks and the camera zooms in on his face that everybody gets mad.
Okay, go up.
Shortcut.
How do I turn it around again?
Q.
Nope.
Like I just threw it behind his head.
What?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I like coughing?
Like I threw that shit backwards.
That was...
Oh my God.
I'm gonna fucking die.
Oh shit, that works.
Okay, that does work.
I don't know why he threw a Molotov at me and my throat hurt.
Okay, that's good.
Let's go.
There's more shit over here though.
Back here.
Oh, I could have done that.
It's all right.
Whatever.
I'm going to go that way though.
Good.
I don't want to miss anything.
Heard somebody.
What the hell is this guy?
You know what we haven't heard yet?
We haven't heard that one.
The really grungy, gravelly one.
That was one of my favorites.
What is this guy doing?
Is this a zombie or is this a guy also playing Resident Evil?
Oh, it's a zombie.
Hi.
Okay.
Well, I'm taking this.
Running out of ammo.
He's playing the game better than you.
Well, he's gone and I'm still here.
So, sorry.
Oh, that was...
That's him.
Don't put it down.
Don't get up.
Shit.
What the fuck?
I'm getting hit way too many times.
And for being a hardcore gamer playing on standard,
I got to be better than that.
All right, let's go.
Wait, I probably shouldn't have dropped down.
It's okay.
You're over 35.
Yeah, that's right.
What's the route to get over here?
Right across?
Oh, I don't...
What is this one?
Is this written down somewhere?
Let me get some brain fluid.
Okay.
So, it's that one, that one.
But what order?
I don't remember this puzzle.
I seem to not remember anything from this game
because I keep saying that.
All right.
How do I know?
Do I just have to present any order
or just the ones that are shown?
Let me walk around.
All right.
So, this is like a circle of the line.
There's like a double...
Like a DNA thing.
There is a floating...
Whatever.
He's not remembering this?
No, I don't.
All right.
So, it's the circle on the line underneath the DNA symbol.
The two, like, Pisces, whatever it is.
Anything else?
It's really awesome meeting you at PAX East.
Somebody lied to you.
Okay.
Well, let me see if I can deduce it from that.
Was there any over here?
Let me just check.
Any other symbols besides those ones?
Or am I just overthinking this
and it actually is just so easy?
I'm probably overthinking this.
All right.
Then there's like the two birds.
That's four.
I think I got it.
Two birds.
So, we got this one.
Why can I not press it?
Okay.
No, it's this one.
Then this one.
This one.
Wait, what?
Does that mean a certain...
Wait.
Well, I couldn't do it.
Is it this one or this one?
Is it not this one?
No, I didn't want to do that.
Cancel.
That's not it.
This is going to take you 20 minutes.
Oh, this one had...
Okay, this one had that.
This one had that.
And this one had...
And this is correct.
Why?
It was like two...
The two bird ones.
Does that mean an order?
Because, I mean, this one was absolutely there.
This one was absolutely there.
I don't...
It was only one.
It was the circle of the line underneath it.
This one obviously doesn't count.
What's going on here?
Check it again.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is one.
Okay.
So, this is just one of them.
So, it's this one.
And then this one.
Okay.
I thought they were separate.
I was like, wait...
I thought this was just the double helix one.
We're good.
I just...
I got it.
I got a head.
Did you do a video of you fighting a bear?
No.
That would be incredibly dangerous.
You can't carry a grenade.
It's going to just explode on you.
What am I doing?
All right.
I'm just...
There's one of those things in this guy's head.
Almost out of bullets, by the way.
Cool.
Okay.
I got what I needed.
Time to go to the other one.
Oh, nice.
All right.
This is the...
This is going back.
I...
Hold on a second, though.
I want to explore.
I'm exploring.
Sorry.
There's a lot to explore.
Yes, there is.
Unfortunately, this...
Can this go in there?
Oh, it can.
It's a very big box for...
Wait.
There's other ones.
Does that work?
That works.
I'm going to go back to the other ones.
There's like two or three.
I'm going to try to remember what those are.
It was a 30-hour playthrough.
Now it's a hundred and...
You know what?
I played Elden Ring for a full straight month.
So it's all right.
I think I'm going to be...
I think I'll be fine.
That's all there is over here, though.
I'm not going to play this game for a month.
I'm just saying.
I'm taking my time.
It was definitely more than that.
It was probably like two months straight.
I...
Yeah, I want to...
I want to go back.
Maybe not right now, but eventually I want to go back to the other areas.
Bro, what are you doing?
Somebody just said that into their screen.
Their teeth, they were close.
What are you doing?
Relax.
All right.
Wait, I didn't get this.
What is that?
I got to check it.
I already...
I was just here, though.
Did I not get...
I'm confused.
How did I not see that?
Where is this?
Just past it.
Oh, is it there?
Is it that right there?
That's kind of weird.
I don't...
Is it really that?
Where is this thing?
I think it actually is that barrel.
My ceiling, ceiling, ceiling.
Oh, I thought that was a...
I thought that was a stalagmite.
Nice.
Bro just shot the rope.
I don't know.
I thought maybe it would...
Now we're good.
All that for a silver coin.
All right, I promise I'm going to move on.
We're going to continue through...
I'm going over here.
What are you doing?
What is he...
What is he doing?
He hates this chat.
No, you guys are fine.
Okay, we're good.
All right.
Now we're doing game progress.
Let's go.
What were they thinking?
All right.
So I need to put the head here
and I need to put something else there, which...
Oh, so he's got to go through the lake
and then just keep going.
Any other shit over here?
No, this is the boathouse.
Just check the outskirts.
Yep.
Let's go.
Check everything.
A lot of chickens here.
Ooh.
Wait, any golden eggs?
Any golden eggs?
I need it.
That's for a quest.
Oh, that's not a golden egg.
What do you have the golden egg?
Yep.
Gold chicken egg.
That's a quest.
Anything else here?
Oh, no.
Very good.
All right.
That's why we explore.
Got everything.
Now I'm going to go...
Oh, man.
Look at all this.
Look at all these fucking goodies.
I'm going over there.
What's this?
Oh, that's progress.
We're not doing game progress right now.
We're going to get goodies.
Anything over here?
Yeah, trinkets and all that stuff.
Okay, we're good.
This is the one and only time
you're going to see me walk around
in a circle collecting things.
Maybe one more time after this.
All right, let's go
clean out this place.
Block?
No.
Oh, God.
Shit.
It needs a regular key.
What?
You're alive.
This room feels booby trapped.
I don't think I want to go in here.
Do I have to shoot those?
Wait, I was already in here before.
Why are there more enemies now?
All right, this was one of those things
I know there was.
Where was it?
Did I bite my toenails?
No, I did not.
I don't bite my nails really either.
Not that I would bite my toenails,
but I don't bite my nails
because it kind of...
I always feel like it hurts
my teeth or something.
Like going like this would be like a bite.
Like it messes up my teeth.
It kind of hurts my teeth.
That's not very XQCL of you.
Yeah, there it is.
Nice.
Pearl bangle.
You have weak teeth?
Probably.
All right, I can't get that one,
but I can try these two.
Oh, I can open this.
Is this game progress?
I don't know, but I can go in here.
I thought game progress was going with the boat.
Apparently not.
Into the tunnel.
Someone catch me the gigantic fish
that lives in the lake for me.
Fish oil has many uses.
This photo should help you find it.
Oh, we're going back and doing that.
In front of the big shed thing.
Oh, yeah, let's get it.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Let's go get it.
There is something in here though.
Is it hanging? There it is.
Spinal.
Paper wolf.
Omega 3 Andy.
Very good for you.
There was one more and it's over here.
I want to go over here.
Where is it?
For the nest?
Right here.
Ooh.
All right, now let's go get the fish.
That's all I can do here for now.
Pretty sick.
All right, let's go get the fish.
Shoot the nest.
Shoot the nest, you dummy.
What do you mean?
Is that going to do something?
God, the backseaters today.
God, God.
All that for five handgun ammo
and I just destroyed a nest.
God, backseating today.
All right, let's go.
I want to get the fish.
You know what?
Mods, put it in no chat only today.
It would be so weird to scream without a chat.
I'll give you a little bit of inside info.
Back in the day making YouTube videos.
A lot of times I would just open up the game.
I would just kind of sit here like this
and I would be talking and making jokes
and trying to find funny things to do.
And it's so much easier to do this
with the people that you know are here right now.
I remember talking to nobody sometimes
and that's why I would always kind of be hanging out
on a call.
A lot of those old videos had, you know,
like stir, italics, boo, stealth.
We were kind of always just hanging out on a call
and she's like, all right, I'm just going to record.
A lot of times they would just be in the videos
because they were just in the call.
Which is, wait, what's in here?
Ooh, there's something else in here.
What's this?
Is this game progress?
No, there's something else in here.
Is it game progress?
All right, three squiggly lines.
Red herb.
P3, whatever that is.
And then the three fishes.
That's not going to help.
It's locked.
Where's P3?
Oh, there it is.
Ooh, it is game progress.
I needed one of those too.
I'm not going to pick that up yet because it's going to spawn
like 30 people.
So I'm not getting it yet.
Anything else I can get here?
I got everything besides the thing that's in the, wait,
what?
The other head.
Now get the key to the church.
There's still something behind me.
Hanging?
Very nice.
All righty.
It's time.
It is now time to, I'm not going to go back this way.
I'm going to go over here because I want to go.
Where was that other?
It was over here, wasn't it?
Where I could go.
I could go down.
Where was that part that I was at?
Oh, is this game progress?
It was up here, wasn't it?
I need the shed.
Yep.
Bang, all right.
All right, fish.
I think the fish is over here.
Move that like shed.
There it is.
There's it.
Uh-oh.
It's a little too big.
Um, I already did this, right?
How big is this fish?
I think that's big enough, right?
All right, cool.
A rare Lunker size bass measuring over 18 inches
can be sold at a high price or used.
And is that the, that's the right one, right?
Okay, yeah, let's go.
Let me go do this.
What was over here?
Was it just a chest, a regular chest?
I need to go back to the merchant.
Need to go do the hexagon puzzle.
Yeah, that was pretty early on, wasn't it?
Okay, now I got to go right.
I go down.
Because this is, jeez.
What the hell is going on here?
I was trying to do the jump scare
and then have it get jump scared like three seconds later.
Like I, I don't know, like I had lag on my computer
or you had lag to your computer.
This is wicked funny.
You just didn't get to see it.
Oh, this is a key.
I can go open up a drawer now.
All right, I, I love doing this.
I, yeah, I'm having fun.
I don't care.
Now I got to go open up one of those drawers
and that's all that's here.
Any other things to do?
Nope.
What the fuck is that?
No, honestly, like what is that?
Why is the predator out here?
Great.
What the hell?
What button?
I just pressed every button on my keyboard.
It's V.
Oh no.
No way.
See ya.
No, it don't even.
Oh.
Oops.
Okay, we're good.
All right, there is a draw in here.
Let's go open it.
Where, right here, right?
All right, what do we get?
I got a gold bar.
This is a, how much this is worth?
Where is it?
A gold bar?
It's 10,000.
I got a lot of money.
I need more of these jewels though.
The rectangle ones.
So I can do this now.
$46,000.
This thing is, I'm going to be able to buy something ridiculous.
Very cool.
I need more of these.
I found tons of these, but not a lot of these.
Now I will sell this.
I'm going to make a lot of money.
Okay, very cool.
Good.
Worth it.
Glad I came back here.
Now we're going to go to the merchant.
Because I have to turn in a bunch of shit and I want to make sure I get.
What is going on up here?
I didn't get, that's gunpowder?
I got to get it.
How did I miss this?
Remember, it's a Resident Evil game.
You have to pick up everything.
Everything must be picked up.
Okay.
Got everything.
Very good.
Very cool.
So happy.
I'm excited.
I had to go put like $70,000 into one gun.
Think that the merchant is down here.
Here.
All right.
That's going to go straight.
Take the boat east.
You can find a McDonald's.
I wonder if they'll be, should I go to the merchant or will there be one like right here?
There's one right across.
Yeah, just go.
I'm going to be mad that if I don't.
Can we please go?
This area is very important to explore.
Maybe I should have used the key here, but I got a gold bar.
I'm happy.
All right.
Turn in the quests.
Sell a bunch of shit.
Welcome.
I've got something new for you.
Where's the um, how come I didn't get the turn in?
Oh, sell a Lunker bass.
Okay.
I need to sell the Lunker.
Sell the egg.
Welcome.
Anything perfect.
You're a real professional.
A job well done deserves payment in kind.
Will that be all then?
All right.
Pearl bangle.
This is just for selling only.
Rubies or bar makes no difference.
The price is just for selling.
Cool.
That's our choice to make.
Seventy three thousand and this key is done, right?
This is a done key.
Nice.
All right.
This is like seventy five thousand.
Thank you.
Got a selection of good things on sale stranger.
Why not try your hand?
I'm going to buy the rocket launcher.
I'm not buying the rocket launcher.
I should probably get this because I have the.
Crossbow.
It's twenty percent off.
Knowledge is power.
Case upgrade is just important.
I'm getting it.
All right.
Now hold on.
I don't think I really care about the rifle.
That cash in your pocket or your life.
What else do you got?
Anything else?
What's that?
Have we procured eight curiosities?
Increase the drop rate of resources large elegant mask.
Oh, yeah.
I'm getting the mask.
You can't go wrong.
I'm getting the Punisher.
No, no, no, no.
Get the map to don't already have it.
I guess I get is it going to help?
Treasure.
I'm going to get one of these two.
All right.
Now hold on.
Hold on a second.
I could do three reds in this right now.
Is that better than we'll find out?
All right.
Triple Reds is one point four times nineteen six.
What about three?
Way more.
Twenty four seven.
All right.
Put those in.
Sell this.
Welcome.
Where would it?
What can I do you for a deal?
Well, don't get yourself killed here.
I'm going to put this in here.
A ton of money.
Now, what do I want?
Fix the knife.
Good luck to you.
Strange.
I think I'm doing durability on the knife and I'm doing.
Yeah, it sucks when you don't have it.
I got tons of money.
I'm fine.
Dirty.
Yeah, this kind of work is about finesse.
Strange.
Little bit goes a long way.
You'll see.
See how that feels.
Better like yourself should notice the difference right away.
Dazzled are you?
Our craftsmanship demands.
All right.
Slow down.
I am.
I am disgusting right now.
Killing me.
You come back any time.
How come you're not using the rocket launcher?
Because the rocket launcher is going to sit in the storage box until the last encounter
and I'm going to take it out and I'm going to have three shots for it.
I'm going to miss the first one.
It's going to right by the boss's head.
I'm going to scream and be pissed.
I'm going to shoot one more time.
It's going to hit the chest.
Boom, big explosion.
Do it again.
And then I'm going to have to take out every magazine and every clip anyways of every weapon
to beat it anyways.
So no, I think I'm going to put this one back on.
I want because my handgun is the best thing I have.
I want more ammo for it.
I'm running kind of low.
I could make another three bolts, but do I really care?
Let's do this.
Then I need a yellow and we're good.
What's the case look like now?
I'm happy with it so far.
I'm happy.
I do want to get another shotgun eventually though.
Shotguns are so good in these games.
Cool.
All right.
I am ready to progress the game.
It's time to do it.
Finally.
So in the boat, straight right.
There it is.
Bro Twitch didn't notify.
Oh shit.
I'm sorry about that.
Okay.
I have that hexagon puzzle too though.
Where was that?
Church insignia.
I got to go back to the church.
That just something is wrong with my video card.
Condor one to roost.
I found the key to the church.
Copy that.
Now go get baby eagle.
Right.
No time to chat.
I'm going in condor one out by the fishing farm.
I got to go back here.
Bang a left down here.
And then wait, how do I get back there fish farm?
Here it is.
I need to go here.
Okay, so I got to go to this way.
I missed some treasures.
Yeah, I did.
It's okay though.
Can't get everything.
Where did I just come out?
Interesting.
I'm going the wrong way.
I got to go back to the boat.
Why did they dump me out here?
I guess I could have not gone this way.
Am I going to stream today?
I was thinking about it.
It depends.
I was going to start at like 8 or 9 p.m. Pacific again.
I haven't pressed the button yet though.
I hope you do stream today.
Eh, I don't know.
I'm not really feeling it today.
So probably not.
Maybe like in a few days or something.
All right, I need to go here.
I'm going the wrong way again.
I'm so bad with directions.
Wait, didn't I just, hold on.
All right, I can't look over at chat for a minute.
I need to, it's over here, right?
Because this is connecting.
Now it's back where the merchant is.
Back where the merchant is, back where the merchant is.
I don't know what the fuck I was doing.
Wait, is it actually, can I actually go from here?
Why am I looking over here?
I just said I wasn't going to do that.
Because I like, I'm in the game,
and then I take myself out of the game.
And then I just hold W, and I'm still,
I'm going in a complete, and then I'm like, where am I?
I gotta stop looking over here.
I found it.
Stop looking over there.
Stop!
This is like doing a Rubik's Cube.
Shit, I gotta bring this up, the whole thing.
This shit's fucking hard.
I wish I could move the, all the top left.
I can't.
You could have done this in like four turns.
You know, here's the thing, everybody.
Some of you are good at puzzles.
Some of you are very strong.
Some of you are very smart.
Some of you are very funny.
Some of you are very, some of you are very fast.
Some of you are very slow.
Some of you are slow and strong,
and, and we're all different, okay?
We're all different people.
I'm not very good at puzzles,
but I do other stuff pretty good.
We're all different people.
Some of you are really good at this kind of shit,
but it's good.
I'm glad that you are.
Not me.
Not me, if I could do that though,
oh, you didn't see me, did you?
This hurt my ankle.
Maybe if I do it with one eye.
I fucking can't do this shit.
I hate these more than anything.
You want people to go, I can't, why can he not do this?
Every time I've ever seen a puzzle like this,
I don't do it.
I just don't, and where would I do these, by the way?
It's not, it's not like in the,
this is not like the Sunday fucking comics.
It's not like, oh yeah, let me do the fucking weird
three triangle slide puzzle today.
I've, where do you do these,
if not only in Resident Evil 4?
I've, this is the only time I've ever,
I don't do Rubik's Cube.
If you give me a Rubik's Cube,
I'm gonna go fuck this, man.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm not gonna do this.
Somebody else do it.
I'm not doing this.
It's only, these are only in Resident Evil.
I've never completed,
I've gone like this with a Rubik's Cube.
Oh, there's green on the top,
and there's yellow down there.
I got one row.
It's gone, I don't, into the trash.
Well, not into the trash, into the, you know,
on the shelf somewhere.
But you get, all right, all right.
Everyone stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Why would I buy a Rubik's Cube to throw it in the trash?
Fuck you!
I wanna move these ones on the top right.
Hey, this needs to be on the bottom.
How do you get it to be that way?
No, this has to, this is, it's on the top.
This has to go on the top.
Those ones up there are the bottom.
I don't fucking know, guys.
I don't care.
Is this the bottom?
No, it's not.
It's the right side?
What side is that shit?
Get me in there!
I don't care, shoot it open!
Give me a crowbar, I'll get in there in one minute.
Give me a crowbar, I'm in here in less than 30 seconds.
I'll just,
and open it.
Give me a crowbar, I'll get in there in one minute.
All right, so that's, this is the right,
this has to go over to the right.
It's because it's all circles and shit.
I can't do it.
My four-year-old got this in six minutes.
You're a bad parent for letting your four-year-old
play Resident Evil 4, there's blood and guts in this.
2020 Jerma would have gotten this, no.
2020 Jerma would have stopped playing Resident Evil 4
after the first stream, and you know that's accurate.
Yeah, oh yeah, 2017 Jerma, no, 2017 Jerma
would have played Resident Evil 3, 4, for three hours,
and then played a different game the next day.
He was so, he was so much smarter than me.
Yeah, 2018 Jerma would not have been,
not even gotten this far.
2018 Jerma would have thrown a grenade into the wall,
it would have bounced back and blown me up,
and I would have uninstalled the game.
All right, I'm not looking at chat for the next 10 minutes.
Bro, I don't think I can do it.
There's that side, but like, but it's,
this is the Rubik's Cube dog shit,
where if you get one side all red,
it's like hooray, I got all this one side red.
That doesn't matter at all,
because all the other sides are wrong.
So it doesn't matter if you got one side right.
You've got to read through the whole thing,
because everything has to line up exactly, perfectly,
at the very end.
Okay, piece of shit.
Is this even right?
No, it is.
He's regressing.
Dude, puzzles like this, no, nobody does these.
Well, I ain't getting into the magical fucking fortress.
Good for you, Resident Evil 4 villains.
Put these in front of your door.
You know what, forget about locks.
You don't, get rid of keys.
You want to make it so nobody gets into your fucking house?
No more keys that you can lockpick and shit.
No, no, no, put one of these on your front door.
I ain't nobody getting in.
Ain't nobody going to get in.
Do one of these to get into your house,
to get into your front door, to get into your fortress.
No one's getting in.
This is way more secure than a lock with a key.
What if you forgot the solution
and you locked yourself out of the house?
I'm just imagining somebody, I don't know why,
but a bunch of fishing equipment.
A fishing hat, two free fishing poles, a tackle box,
a big box of bait and stuff,
and they're like, what the fuck is happening?
You can't get in the house?
Come on, let me try.
It's like, yeah, just, I don't know.
You put this on here, shut up.
Hold on a minute.
No, no, it's the other way.
You screwed it all up.
Ah, shit, we're going to get a locksmith.
The locksmith shows up.
It's like, I don't, bro,
I don't know how to fucking get in your house.
I don't know how to get in here.
You're going to have to use like fucking C4
to get into your front door.
Someone's going to have to use a battering ram
to knock your door in.
I'm so fucked here.
Okay, I know I have to focus.
I know, I know.
There's a lot of people that don't like these
and I'm one of them.
And I know that some of you are one of them too.
Okay, you guys have to help me.
You guys have to help me.
I actually, I'm having a lot of trouble.
You have to help me.
I want to ask if we get one's in the chat.
Hey guys, I can't get in my house.
One's in the chat if I should rotate this.
I can't turn on click math.
A walkthrough is actually not helpful either
because I already fucked it all up and I can't reset it.
All right, do I spin this one?
Okay, everybody stop talking.
Do I spin this one again?
No, okay, all right, all right, all right.
Do I spin this one?
Yes, spin this one twice.
Okay, do I spin this one?
This must be humiliating.
No, not really.
I just don't do, I'm not like a puzzle guy.
I'm just not, I don't care.
I'm not a, but dude, it's such an easy puzzle.
Maybe for you, but my brain, when I turn this,
it's like, it's like when fucking, what's his name?
The weird, weird, Doctor Strange.
When Doctor Strange is in,
they're seeing every fucking timeline
and he's like, when I spin this,
I see every possibility.
My brain's like, dude, just walk away.
All right, spin this one?
Doctor weird.
Just spin this one.
Dude, I need somebody to help me.
I need somebody to help me.
I'm fast as fuck though.
I guarantee you if I had a crowbar,
I would solve half the problems.
I could solve, I could solve most problems
with the crowbar, I think.
Getting in somewhere, helping,
just give me the crowbar and I could fix everything.
I could get leverage.
I could, you know, use it to hook on
and like climb a fucking wall and shit,
or like a rock.
I could do so much with the crowbar.
Am I spinning this again?
Bottom left?
You are two steps away.
What?
Spin left?
Holy shit.
How did you guys do that?
How did you do that collectively in two turns?
What?
I am, no, I am actually fucking losing my mind.
How, that's no, I did all that work.
I did all that work.
That's bullshit and you know it.
I did all that work in two fucking moves.
You finish it.
I did all that work.
That was barely any of your work.
This is no way.
This is no way to move.
Yeah, I was, I loosened the lid.
I had the pickle jar and I was like,
and then you took it and after like 25 minutes
of me doing that, you went, I don't understand.
It's easy.
No, I did all the work.
I did all the work.
Yeah, I ran the lid under hot water.
I got a paper towel.
Oh, I did all that.
Okay, anyways, how high is your IQ?
I have an incredibly low performance IQ.
I have a very high IQ,
but my performance IQ was like,
actually like very bad.
It was abysmal.
Almost, I think there was actually a question
like almost as if I didn't take the test correctly
because my performance IQ was so low,
but my like my visual IQ and my audio,
like there's other IQs.
They were fucking through the roof.
They were absolutely through the roof.
So there you go.
There you go.
Live, you get to watch it.
Wait, was something in here?
I already was in here.
All right, so I did the hexagon puzzle.
Now, can I get through there from here?
It's funny because you are theoretically smart.
Exactly.
In theory, I'm very, very intelligent, very intelligent,
but in practice, not so much.
I should have been a philosopher.
You know what I mean?
Just like just talk and just like come up with theories
and maybe some solutions.
Other people will do all that though.
I'm just gonna drink wine and talk.
That's what I should have done.
I do that anyways.
All right, fish farm.
I hope that was entertaining
because it was very embarrassing and very painful.
I'm all right, I can't wait to see
all the clips.
Jerma's performance IQ is zero.
And it's gonna be that whole routine
and all the comments are gonna be like,
I actually can't even, how is that even possible?
How does he drive a car?
It's like not even, how does this guy operate?
And I'm gonna be like, no,
performance IQ level is pretty low.
All right, where is this something in here?
Is it in the meat grinder?
No, right there, okay.
And this is what I really wanted to do, right?
Is that, oh, whatever that thing is.
I go back up, shoot the red barrel.
No, no, I gotta come down a little bit and refocus.
I cannot believe that you guys did that in two turns.
Two spins did it.
It probably takes like 20 spins to do that puzzle.
I did all the work.
I will die on that hill.
Worth it, okay.
So I need to go to the church.
So I need to get out of here and go this way.
I'm just gonna go up and through here
and then back to the merchant.
Can I actually, now he's gonna walk around.
That wasn't even the thing I shot at.
Really?
Where's this other treasure then?
Where is it?
Antique pipe, whoa.
What is your chess elo?
I'll tell you.
My chess elo is whatever is not playing the game.
It's taking all the pieces out
and having a pretend war where you make them have characters
and you take like the bishop and the knight and stuff
and you make them like fight and stuff.
And that's how I played chess.
You make a fake, like they're action figures.
Or it's as a set piece so people think you're intelligent.
It's just in your living room and it's a chess board
and there's a game currently on it
and you just put the pieces in random places
and people go, wow, intense game going on here.
You don't play it at all.
You've never played it before.
It's just people going, oh, there's an intense game
of chess going on over there at some point.
I wonder, high intelligence in this house.
All right, I'm focusing now.
It's been an hour.
I'm having a lot of fun though.
Where's the way to get out of here?
Over here.
Can I go to the right?
How come you look so pissed off?
I already answered this.
All right, we have made it.
We're so close.
Exactly as intended.
7,000, 15,000.
That's all I can do with this, right?
Selling only, yeah.
I'm just gonna max out the handgun.
Craftsmanship demands no less.
See how that feels, mate.
A fellow like yourself
should notice the difference right away.
Well, that might want to take care
of any leftover errands.
Let's go.
All right, back to the church.
Wait, no, it's not time to do that.
I can play the casino gambling game.
Oh, I only have two.
Shit, nevermind, I thought I had three.
Okay, time to go to the church.
There is.
Oh, very nice.
I could do three reds in this.
21, I'll hold them in there for now.
Probably not permanently.
Lights off, it's still not quite that dark.
Lights will go off in about 15 minutes, 20 minutes still.
Plus blood.
I'm wearing the gamer vest
that vibrates in shock when things happen.
Defeat the giant.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Where is it?
Stab.
Dog.
Dog friend.
Ow.
With the dog from the beginning
that I let out of the trap.
What?
The knife broke.
Oh, that's not good.
It breaks in mid fight like that?
The dog.
Oh, no.
What the fuck am I doing?
The knife can break up here.
The dog is so bloody on one side.
It's like two-faced.
The dog, half the dog's body is like fucked up.
Where's the dog?
Okay, let's get to that church.
Can't you say, where's the dog?
Can't you see the dog?
Oh, there you are.
Hey, thank you so much.
Thanks bud.
You're awesome, appreciate it.
You are very, very cool.
And good luck.
I would throw you a raw turkey if I had one, but I don't.
Take care of yourself, it's fucking wacky out here.
I think I got everything, right?
I thought I threw a grenade at the dog, by the way.
That's why I was...
That's where you got the YouTube thumbnail from.
I thought I threw a grenade and blew the dog up.
There is something else here.
There it is.
Nothing else I can do with the dog, I don't think.
Very cool.
All right, back to the church.
Nobody got me, I know Resident Evil dog got me.
I hear a treasure.
Oh, that's gonna fall all the way into the water.
Can anybody tell what it is?
I think it's just money.
Should I go get it?
Okay, next section.
I think this is a different act
or a different chapter, I think.
By the way, is the brightness okay?
Remember that was a problem a little bit yesterday.
Good enough, it's okay.
Make it a little brighter.
I don't wanna go too bright.
That looks better.
All right, I'm gonna save it.
Capturing a game through OBS sometimes.
I feel like it makes it darker.
Darker than it looks for me.
I feel like I have enough room to put this in here now.
Hello, didn't I learn how to craft mines?
Oh, that's a lot.
That is a lot of materials.
Are they attached?
Oh, gee, okay.
Well, I'm not gonna use this for like another, okay.
Maybe for bosses, that's pretty cool.
I think there is a, save it.
If I remember correctly, this is the scary,
really scary part of the game.
I always hated this place.
Ashley Graham, I'm here to help.
No, I think that's a little bit later.
I'm trying to think of a specific enemy type
that was terrifying and I hate fighting.
Okay, I need to move the, I need to move blue too.
Can't do this without moving blue.
So I might as well just not even do it.
Yeah, I gotta move the blue one.
The blue one is literally up there, isn't it?
I gotta move the blue one.
I don't wanna hold on to these honestly
because I'm not gonna use the gun.
There's the blue dial.
All right, now we can do this, but wait.
Bolts, five bolts, that's a lot.
Anything else?
All right, let's do it.
Blue is correct.
So fucking close.
What's going on here?
I just fucked the whole thing up.
The logo, what?
Please, Jerma, you aren't taking long enough, what?
It needs to go like in the, okay, hold on.
Everything has to be shifted to the left.
Oh no, wait, it's upside down.
Okay, so everything has to go this way, like here.
I hate using ADQE.
I just wish I could use a fucking analog stick.
Oh, I hate this.
ADQE is making me wanna fucking puke.
There it is.
I had it upside down.
Hey, yo, he did it.
I did.
I'll be taking autographs after this for you.
Ashley, you in there?
What was that?
That just felt like doing that.
If there's a problem, then you can leave.
Ashley, Ashley Graham, are you in here?
Listen.
Ow.
That hurt.
My name's Leon.
I'm here in the president's quarters.
I think, I think there should be some kind of code word
to be like, hey, you know that I'm here
and I'm like a good guy.
What is that?
Assue them.
Boss lambs are a skin.
Yes, persevere.
Deliver unto them.
Salvation.
We both just had the same dream.
This is real, this is getting real.
It's getting better.
This take like 30 or 40 minutes off.
We were having a bunch of conversations.
We were having a conversation.
What do we do?
Your father trusts me.
And I need you to trust me too.
And do exactly as I say.
I can also announce that I will be putting on the
comedy costume for 15 minutes.
And the lights I'll go off too.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Okay.
Seriously?
I just bought this.
Oh, cell phone.
Okay.
There's a way out, there's a way out.
I'm going to jump out the window.
This shining the light in your face.
Accessory glasses.
Wellington.
What do you mean glasses?
What do you mean Wellington?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about my Wellington?
What are you doing?
Stop it.
What are you doing in my Wellington?
Stop.
Stop it.
It's okay.
I've got you.
It's like he gets possessed.
Hey, trust me.
I think it's kind of funny if she landed in his hands
and it's raining or she slipped and she fell right down.
Just like.
Pressures.
Don't do that.
Do not just do what I just did.
That was a bad idea.
Copy that.
Is she okay?
Affirmative.
For ASAP.
I'm sending you the call for the extraction point.
May happen to baby eagle.
Copy that.
Hurry.
The weather is getting worse.
Roost out.
All right.
Head to the extraction points all the way up here.
We got to go through the all the way back to where we were.
Town hall.
Like I said, it's dangerous.
Stay close.
I'm going to eat an egg.
Want one?
I mean, they're raw.
You just crunch them.
But food.
Come on.
Okay, Ashley commands.
Switch between tight and loose formation with control.
Ashley will stick close behind Leon while in tight formation.
This can be effective when running past enemies.
Okay.
So you hang back.
Avoid attacks.
Give me some space.
Okay.
On me.
Got it.
Spread out.
Hey.
With me.
Spread out.
Hey.
Stick close.
Okay.
They're coming.
Get behind me.
Watch out.
What?
What's going on?
Oh shit.
Okay.
All right.
Stay behind me.
Oh my God.
I just shot Ashley in the fucking head.
Here you go.
Oh, you're fine.
We're good.
Ashley, are you all right?
Yeah.
Thanks.
All right.
Let's move.
Another grenade.
Don't walk in that.
I hear...
Why do I hear a dynamite stick?
Remember, you're going to kill this girl.
I am not going to kill this girl.
Spread out.
Okay.
Come on.
You already attempted to.
What?
No, I didn't.
I threw a grenade.
All right.
We made it.
So far so good.
Got some new wares, stranger.
You're in for a treat.
All right.
I got some stuff.
I got something new for you.
Those won't do you much good in the grave.
Let me check this.
Hold on.
Two red, one yellow.
Three red is better.
All red is better.
I'll just do all red then.
I'll do all red.
Welcome.
Au revoir.
Thank you.
This is good.
All right.
I got to get this much better.
Power for the shotgun.
It's a thing of beauty.
And I will not forget the comedy outfit.
I promise.
I think I'm just going full power with it.
And then I reload speed.
Rate of fire.
Yeah.
There you are.
As you wished.
Where would it?
What can I do you for?
Come back any time.
Is there a...
Yes, there is.
All right.
We're going to go comedy outfit.
How do I do it?
Is it not from the settings menu?
Oh, extras.
Okay, here we go.
Can only be changed from the main menu.
Well, I'll go to the main menu.
I just saved it, right?
Where is it?
I'm safe.
Try using nice next time.
Hey, we're a team, right?
How do I put these on?
Oh, okay.
All right.
I'm going to put this one on.
He's keeping the sunglasses on.
Casual or romantic?
I think it's this one.
I'm only doing this for...
I'm only doing this for like 20 minutes.
Speaking of a few minutes,
I'm going to...
I'm going to go refill this.
But, goodness.
This feels like a different game.
This doesn't even feel like the same game anymore.
Give me a moment.
I'll be right back.
I'm just going to go pee and refill my drink.
I am back.
Okay.
Oh, I refilled my drink.
Nice.
Hydrating tea.
Okay.
I think we are good to go.
At least we should be.
How's the camera?
Should the camera be like lowered or moved or something?
I feel like it's...
I always feel like my camera is either way too big or way too small.
Is it good?
I think it's all right.
Is it maybe a little too big?
Oh, light's off.
That's right.
It is dark.
Let's see how that looks.
Okay, we're good.
I think this is a good illumination level.
Good.
What's the quest?
I need someone to get rid of the wild dog that's been roaming around the village.
It'll be easy to spot.
It's not like normal dogs.
Eight.
Spinals.
Village Manor.
Over here.
Okay.
Well, I forgot that I did that.
Makes over, I suppose.
Let's go.
Hey, can we take a break?
Sorry, we need to keep moving.
I don't want to go too fast because I'll run into something.
Hunnigan was right about the weather.
I'm over here in dark.
What am I doing?
I'm like, why am I crumpling up into like a little ball?
Good.
Uh-oh.
I put these new costumes on and my FPS went down by like
40%.
I'm just saying maybe still the fire.
Oh my.
All right.
There's a big dog somewhere.
Can I get in here now?
It's still blocked up.
Oh wait, we can get in here.
Okay.
I need you to open it from the other side.
It's up.
Good work.
Elegant bangle.
Cool.
Anything else in here?
I think there's a yep.
All right.
I can use the gumball machine.
Where's this dog?
People upstairs.
It on there.
Let's go.
Maybe this shit in here.
Where's the chief right?
River said said in the elder.
What was it a chief's house down here?
Maybe she good.
Okay.
It's actually it's on the map.
Ah, it is.
Okay.
I'm going.
I'm going to do it.
Yeah.
Look at all this stuff.
I'm going to go.
Oh, this is far away though.
Not that far.
All right, we're going.
I'm doing it.
I have Ashley though.
I feel like that's going to be dangerous.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's a bat.
I thought it was one of those hanging things.
All right.
You stay here.
It's all right.
Stay there.
Don't move.
All right.
There's apparently a giant dog here.
I'm ready.
Stay back there.
Don't come near me.
Oh my God.
Don't do that.
One egg.
Who's baking one single egg in the shell?
I thought I heard a little jingle.
Oh, where is this dog?
He's going to be in here.
He's going to be lying in the bed or something.
Come on.
No problem.
Oh shit.
Above the bed.
Why?
Stop.
Oh shit.
Nice.
Take a screenshot of each one of those and just read it.
Iron works.
Very nice.
Antique camera.
That sell for a lot.
This is also one of those.
I hear it.
Where is it?
There it is.
So where is this dog?
This apparently gigantic dog.
That looks like a dog.
Is this the?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get over here.
Where's this dog?
Where did it go?
Whoa.
He's still alive.
There you go.
Oh, that's good.
I can complete that other treasure now.
All right.
Let's keep moving.
I missed money in there.
Where's the money?
All right.
Cool.
That's eight spinals for that.
That's a lot.
All right.
We got to go the other way.
Now we got to go in.
There's a treasure in there.
But whatever.
I'm just going to go back up.
That was fun.
I like the little quest that they added.
Because that stuff was not in the other game.
A little side content.
Let's go.
That's the best way to go.
I'm going to go this way.
The blue targets were in the original,
but not the other stuff.
Yeah, that stuff is really cool.
I like it.
Mm-hmm.
We're good.
All right.
Just stay with me.
Because this is new content incoming.
New content.
Did you see the nerfed sludge in Grotto Beasts?
Yeah.
I mean, it's really, really powerful.
Oh, my.
Trying to save ammo.
Oh, shit.
That guy has a mask on.
Come this way.
This way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
Oh, my God.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Just up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Ashley, up here.
Oh, my God.
Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up.
Get out of the way, get out of the way, get out of the way, get.
Holy.
Oh, no.
I'm in trouble.
I think I killed him.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Uh-oh.
Jesus.
Is he dead?
All right, we're good.
That was pretty nuts.
I need to craft some ammo.
This is getting kind of bad.
All right, I'm going to go check this out.
Where's the treasure?
Back here.
Oh, yep, yep, yep.
I remember this.
This might be it for this as well.
Oh, no.
I just told her to back up.
Oh, yeah, I got to close all those doors.
You.
Hey.
Listen, about earlier.
Yeah, about that.
You imagine?
I saw him like two hours ago in game.
And now I'm dressed like this.
What's the explanation here?
All have names.
Now then.
I dyed my hair since we talked two hours ago.
What are you doing here?
Very good questions, unfortunately.
Hide now.
In that case, here, help me.
Ashley, quick.
Over here.
He is wrong.
OK, it's game time.
Don't you feel like I saw his outfit
and was like, I got to one up you.
It's made up of monsters.
Oh, she's going to pick up everything.
I hope you can shut up, baby.
Upstairs.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Ow.
I tried to parry it.
It didn't work.
Whoa.
I'm sorry.
I'm fucking such a weirdo.
Uh-oh.
What the?
I blocked that with my hand.
What the fuck?
My arms would be skewered right now.
I blocked that with my fingers.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my goodness.
OK.
Oh, my god.
Ah.
Honestly, there's something about anybody else feel like this.
It feels just so wrong.
Watching Leon get killed is so fucked up looking, isn't it?
Because everybody knows it's like watching the main character
just get killed so violently.
Like, Leon doesn't die.
He's in Resident Evil 2, Resident Evil 4, Resident Evil 6,
Resident Evil 10, probably.
He's such an iconic character that watching some random guy
snap his neck is just so strange looking.
Turn the difficulty down?
What?
All right.
No, this is the hard part.
I got it.
Let's go.
Against two of us.
Oh, and that's nothing yet.
This fuck is made up of monsters.
You done warming up?
Hope you strip.
Yeah.
Now, if you'd shut up, we'd be good to go.
Just come upstairs.
Go upstairs.
Upstairs, upstairs.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Go upstairs.
We're doing left for dead bathroom scraps.
Here we go.
You all right down there?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Upstairs.
Upstairs, now.
Now.
Go.
Upstairs, now.
All right, now we're going to go up, up, up, up, up.
All the way up.
Oh, shit.
You might need some company.
Are you coming?
That's not even you, dude.
How are you up here already?
Why am I talking like we're in voice comms together?
Oh, no.
Where is he?
Is that him?
What is?
What's happening?
Go, go down.
Go down.
Oh, my fuck.
I can't even.
Oh, that was lucky.
So many people are coming down here.
Push through, buddy.
I'm fucking dead here.
He's going to hit me right in the head.
Get the fuck away from me, dude.
Get away from me.
Oh, my god.
What do you mean pay attention?
Don't just leave me.
OK.
Wait, I didn't kill that guy.
No, I missed out on an item.
I missed out on an item.
You are the reason why the devs put
bright yellow paint on everything.
No, it's because the contrast of the new graphics
made having the barrels be a lighter color
be kind of distracting.
And they changed it for that reason.
They changed it because it was contrast.
Go look at the dev notes, OK?
I don't have to tell you this.
You want to start explaining?
The cough is caused by something called a plaga.
You saw those people, right?
But you have the same thing inside you,
the same thing that made them that.
This is what you're experiencing, these symptoms.
They're only the beginning.
I don't want to become like them.
You are, well, you see, at this early stage,
the parasite, the plaga.
It is possible to remove it with the surgical procedure.
And all you need is some know-how.
And oh, yeah, the right equipment.
Wait, you too?
No worries.
See, I have a plan.
But you're going to have to trust me.
Great.
We're partners, then.
Hey, why are you?
No time for any questions.
The clock is ticking.
Why are you helping us?
Because it makes me feel better.
Let's leave it at that.
I will contact you later.
Dress as this Leon for Halloween.
I'm sad I didn't, I used a bunch of ammo on it.
I didn't even kill the pig mask person.
Eyes are so red.
Hey, got a smoke?
I do, the kind you like.
Now where's the amber?
Fortunately, it's not on me at the moment.
And you really should be telling me what a good job I did.
Busted my ass and managed to hide it right before I got caught.
Ada.
Which is why I'm still alive.
The deal was we get you out of here when you deliver the amber.
No amber, no protection, Luis.
Such a stickler for details, huh, Ada?
Okay, then.
I'll go get it now.
How about that?
And I do have something else I need to get, too.
Somebody asked, is this as good as the original?
This is Roost.
Got some bad news, Condor One.
With the weather like this, the chopper can't make its approach.
Can you stand by until it clears?
Negative.
Too dangerous.
We're going to get out of here and find someplace safe.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could do more to help.
Don't worry about it.
We'll swim home if we have to.
Condor One, out.
Let's go.
What's going to happen to me?
Right now, let's just focus on getting out of here.
Yeah.
Any more eggs?
No.
Okay, so is this as good as the original?
The answer is yes, because it is the original.
You know what I mean?
They didn't change that much.
There was enough changes for it to be kind of a different experience,
but it still is the same game.
It's just kind of updated.
I think there's still reasons to play the original,
but I love it.
I think it's amazing.
I think it's impossible to say,
well, yeah, this replaces Resident Evil 4.
I don't think that's accurate, but it's still kind of...
I'm having a fantastic time.
Centrist Andy.
I already know this.
It's kind of the same thing with...
All right, let's see if I can describe this.
We all have memories playing the old games,
and I feel like something like Diablo 2 Remastered is like this too.
When I'm walking around playing this,
it's almost like the way that I remember the old one.
It's like back then, it's almost like...
This is the way that it looked to me in a weird way.
It's like, oh, yeah, of course.
This is the same game.
I feel like I'm playing the same thing.
I feel the same kind of way with Diablo 2 Resurrected.
It's like I feel like back when I played Diablo 2,
the game's graphics were great.
Like, this is awesome.
It's like current-gen and everything's fanned out.
Wow, look at the lighting effects.
Going back and playing any amount of Diablo 2 Resurrected now.
Oh, wow, look at all these graphics.
Look at the lighting effects.
It's like the same...
It's in the same place in my brain.
If you showed me two images side-by-side of this game,
I would very much be able to go,
whoa, that's way, way different,
but I don't...
My brain is telling me that it's not the case.
This is the same experience that you remember,
and isn't it fucking awesome?
So that's kind of the way I feel.
All right, I'm going to sell some stuff.
Ooh, but I feel like I'm going to sell that soon.
I feel like I'm going to get another handgun soon.
Nostalgia makes things often seem better than they were.
That's what I mean.
It's you have this layer of nostalgia,
and somebody's kind of painting over it.
It's like you have this nostalgia memory
that is being kind of traced with much better ink,
and it kind of replaces that part of your brain
that remembers the nostalgia.
They both operate very well.
They both operate in the same spot.
I'm going to buy this.
You can't go wrong with that.
It's like finding an old book,
and the pages are all fucked up,
and it's all dusty,
and you blow the dust off,
you clean it up,
you send it to a restoring agency,
whatever, and they restore it,
and you get to read it again.
You go, holy shit, this is great.
I remember this book.
It looks great now.
I don't think I want any of this stuff.
Maybe the diamond.
Double yellow in here, probably.
Yeah.
Is any of these worth more than the other or no?
So usually they are.
Okay, so yeah, they are.
Red is not as valuable.
Red is more valuable than purple.
Purple, green.
Green and red.
There we go.
Okay, 19, 8.
And I could do two yellows.
Is yellow worth a lot?
7,000.
I'm going to get another yellow.
Two yellows.
Nice.
All right, big money coming in.
Put the purple back in.
Purple was 4, wasn't it?
Or shift on the gem screen.
Three colors, trio.
Two duos.
Four colors, quartet.
Duo and trio.
All right, so we need...
This is a...
This is two.
So this is...
I mean, I don't...
A duo is better, but I don't...
I only have...
It's fine.
Yes!
New shotgun.
$28,000, though.
All right, sell the other shotgun.
$76,000.
That's a lot.
Here we go.
Cool.
Now we're going to upgrade the absolute hell out of this.
Power?
We're starting to get an idea of your tastes.
Power again.
Max it out.
See how that feels, mate.
A fellow like yourself should notice the difference right away.
Ammo.
There you are.
Do it all.
As you wish.
Dazzled, are you?
Ha ha.
Our craftsmanship marks no less.
Max upgraded, uh...
Riot Gun.
That's good work if I do say so myself.
Do I have any more things to sell?
Your vows won't do you much good in the grave.
Thank you.
If you want...
See how that feels, mate.
I'm not going to use...
I'm not going to use it.
I'm using handgun and shotgun.
And maybe the bolt shooter.
I'm not going to use the submachine gun this whole game.
Come back anytime.
Look at this thing.
Who sells ammo?
I know I'm not going to be using it.
All right, I'm changing the outfits.
I need more...
Whoa, that was a weird sound.
Oh, there's more of this.
Need some yellow herbs.
I'm golden.
All right, let me, uh...
We're going to change outfits.
Should I try the other stuff or...
I want to see what the other stuff looks like.
I kind of...
I kind of like this one.
Yeah, this is like a Resident Evil 2.
Hmm.
Finally, glasses off.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
We're good.
Play with this for a little while.
Reload the guns and let's continue the video game.
I have nine mines to attach.
Wow.
All right.
I can make some more shotgun bullets.
Joggun is going to carry this whole playthrough,
so I want to make sure I have always have bullets for it.
All right.
There is something over here.
Well, it would be nice to have that.
Can we get a Mr. Bean impression?
Yeah, sure.
Oh.
What?
Don't scream.
What's happening?
Why is there a train coming?
What's going on?
Fucking dead.
Oh, no, Leon.
What do you do if you're Ashley in that scenario?
Do you?
What do you do?
You just run?
You pick up the riot shotgun and just start firing?
I don't know.
What do you do?
I would, you know, I pick up the gun and start shooting.
I have so much shit on me.
I feel like I would be a Diablo enemy.
That head comes off and it's just like six items dropped.
It's like two or three legendary indicators.
Is this?
All right.
Okay.
Does it count that I picked up the ammo?
It does.
What the hell happened?
We stepped in the trap.
Let's go.
Okay.
We're doing this.
Give me space.
With me.
Oh, wow.
Oh, whoa.
Oh, this is one of those.
He's running.
This thing is powerful.
Watch out.
Oh, my God.
Will you fuck off?
Up all this stuff.
You all right?
Another grenade.
Do I have any more eggs?
Don't.
Why does it say?
Oh, I keep that keeps confusing me.
I only have one but the four means it's in the slot number four.
Cool.
Give me some space.
Okay.
Come on.
Hang on.
Dude, Chalice of Atonement.
There's a lot of slots in here.
Spread out.
Let's go.
That looks like real fire.
My eyes actually feel the same way when I look at a real flame.
Kind of intense.
What should we take a second?
Are you all right?
Catch your breath.
Sure is quiet.
Okay, we're good.
Kill.
I think that's all of them.
Locked.
Well, shit.
How come you're not suplexing?
Zero suplexes.
How do you do a suplex?
Is it just melee from a different angle?
All right, I've got a max heel.
Get it loaded.
I'm going to use this for a little while.
What?
I'm having her play a horror game.
Every horror game.
You go into the locker like that and then you just that happens every time.
Oh, that's not good.
Why did you do a backflip?
Unless it was yours.
Lady type guy.
Can I go in?
Oh, fuck.
They're chasing me.
Get this fucking guy out of the way.
Fuck.
Stay down.
All right.
I used all every fucking bullet.
Ow.
Oh my goodness.
I'm so dead.
What are you doing over here?
Get out of here.
What are you?
Get over here.
What are you stupid?
We're good.
I just look over.
She's just sprinting towards me.
There's two people with chainsaws here.
Oh, okay.
Checkpoint crank.
Wacky.
That shotgun is strong as...
Oh, yeah.
I put $150,000 into it.
I hope it is.
Out of a bullet support though.
Or am I?
Yes, I am.
Need some electrolytes?
I'm good.
Is there anything else here?
There is something here.
There's a couple things here, actually.
One more behind me?
Right here?
Up there, I think.
Yeah.
I want to get up there and go across.
Yeah, I know.
Completionist Andy.
I know.
Is there a way to get up there from around?
I like the jacket.
I actually do like this outfit.
I definitely want to get up there because this is one of those things.
So I'm going to go up this building.
Do something silly.
Nah.
That's how you get that.
Okay, now I'm going to go up.
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
At least I got those items too.
It was very un-silly of you.
That's all right though.
Okay, I want to go up here.
Goofing off.
I like goofing off.
Nice.
Elegant headdress.
Let us continue.
All right.
I got to go in there.
I just dropped down.
I need to find another place to draw it open.
Fox and Space 2 episode 2 just aired.
Are you hurt?
I wonder if I'm in it.
Seems this isn't the first time running from creeps.
That's meant to be a compliment.
Yeah, it was really cool.
It was really, really cool to do that.
I won't spoil anything.
But Fox and Space 2.
Go check it out.
This is a normal playthrough.
Yeah, I mean, it's barely normal.
Are you actually being serious?
You're gonna have to go watch it and find out.
I could be making it up.
You better go watch it.
You should watch it anyways.
All right.
Do I have enough to make any shotgun shells?
Yes, I do.
Used every single bullet on the two chainsaw ladies.
Can I do it again?
All right.
Come on.
Okay.
Oh yeah, this guy again.
It's made out of aluminum foil.
Not even that impressive.
You're not fooling anybody.
Come on, come on.
Hurry, go, go, go, go, go.
What?
All right.
I did.
Whatever.
What a hero.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought she was already...
I didn't know if she could get hit by that.
I didn't know if that counted as damage to her.
She was already down.
I figured I would...
Just kill me.
Just...
Just kill me already.
I want to restart.
She's screaming.
Stay back.
Ashley, watch out.
I want to get it.
I want to restart.
An arrow sticking right out of his head.
Get out of the fucking way.
The bridge.
Ashley, pick up as many fucking items as you can.
Ashley.
I...
God.
I want the item so bad.
All right.
No more fucking...
I just run.
I know.
I just want...
There was like $2,000 on the ground.
I know you just got to go, but I just wanted money.
I promise I'm not going to fuck around.
I'll get it right now.
Get up there.
Go.
What's going on?
Get up.
Get up there.
Go.
Jump up here.
Jump.
Oh, go.
Not this way, actually.
The paint was all over the wall.
I thought it was go up.
I thought it was paint all over the wall.
Usually that means, hey, you need to look up and do...
I thought it meant like, hey, do the thing where you give her...
Do the hoist.
Get all the money over there.
You're the one he wants.
If we see him again, you...
What about you?
I'll do my job.
Glad to see you.
Break's over, I suppose.
$35,000.
That's pretty good.
Come.
Where would it?
What can I do you for?
Ruby's all rubbish.
It makes no difference.
The price?
Well, that's our choice to make.
It's pretty good cash.
Thank you.
This thing's good.
This thing is good.
I could put some more into this.
Can make up for a lack of skew, friend.
Dazzled.
Are you?
Good luck to you, stranger.
There you are.
As you wished.
Get the stock.
I have enough for you.
Back is killing.
Gun will look great with that.
Come back.
Where is it?
The time.
Okay.
Now.
Welcome.
Take some ammo.
Hey, I'm gonna get it.
Don't steal.
Remember that, mate.
Better to be over prepared.
Try that on for size.
Dazzled.
Are you?
All right.
Now this thing is pretty damn good.
I got one more upgrade for the knife.
This thing is going to be pretty decent now.
Everything else is fantastic.
I got all these upgrades.
Knife needs care every once in a while.
The difference between life and death.
Anything a pleasant travels.
Why do you have chicken strips in your inventory?
These?
Nice.
We're good.
Why are you so quiet and awkward?
I'm playing a game.
I'm awkward.
What do you mean awkward?
I'm going to use this for a little while.
He's new to streaming.
I just started streaming like a week ago.
I knew it was coming too.
Cease your pointless struggling.
Abandon your body to the will of our God.
This guy was creepy before.
I wonder how it is in the remake.
Oh, almighty.
Grant me the strength to crush your enemies.
Son of a bitch.
Ashley, run.
Okay.
Paso Luego.
God, I thank you for your gift.
Yeah.
You want to get ugly?
Let's get ugly.
Nice.
I gotta go up.
Oh, no.
Not into the fucking fire.
Get out of the fire.
Oh, shit.
It worked.
I got him.
This shortcut is so strong.
Every single dollar has gone into this thing.
Give my regards to your God.
Any more?
No, no, no, no, not yet.
Yes, yes, I think there's items.
I didn't break a couple of boxes over here, right?
Yep.
I know.
Just wait.
I'm going to be fine.
I got 30 handgun bullets.
I was bound to catch their attention.
Okay.
You're doing fine.
Let's get moving.
Leon's going to turn into one of them, right?
I won't let that happen.
I promise.
Don't eat any food after midnight.
We'll be fine.
Oh, wait.
This is where...
I'm thinking of saying hello to you, Mr. Kennedy.
I think that...
Right?
What's this character's name?
Spoilers, spoilers.
Hair color red.
Wait, red hair for her?
I'm actually going to heal.
No, I'm not.
I'm making another one of these, though.
Spoilers for almost 20-year-old game.
Should have played it before, losers.
Put the red hair on.
At the next save point, I will...
Well, at least you don't have to worry about being followed.
Come on.
I'm going to pop out and change costumes.
Luis here.
You guys still around?
Well, I wanted to go home, but Ashley just had to see this castle first.
Perfect, because I have a present I want to give you.
Medicine that will help to suppress the progress of your problem.
You're going to play in the real man difficulty?
Let's see.
Come to the courtyard inside of the castle.
We can meet up there.
On a second playthrough, I would do that.
I have such a tension problem that playing on hardcore would be so bad on stream.
I would look over here, look at what chat said,
and I would just get an axe in the head and all my health would be gone.
This place is cool.
I just upgraded, so I guess this is probably a save point, maybe.
Vintage compass.
Everybody's kind of grunts in this game.
Even the merchant.
Everyone's just...
...it might interest you.
Wait, there's so many handguns available.
Choosing the right one can be tricky.
Oooh.
The Punisher.
This one has a brilliant stability and penetration power.
The red nine, which is what I'm using.
A lot of power, but it kicks like a horse.
The Blacktail.
Quick shooting. It's compact size.
Also helps free up inventory space.
The Matilda.
Do you have that one in this castle?
Welcome. I've got something new for you.
That cash in your pocket, or your life. Easy choice, mate.
This thing is 30% off right now.
I always get the magnum when I save every bullet to the final boss.
Ruby's all rubbish, it makes no difference. The price, a deal well struck. Hehehe.
Damnit.
You'll get some bang for your buck, I guarantee it.
Your valuables won't do you much good in the grave.
Get rid of the bolt thrower?
I could, it's really, it's cool.
But, it's cool. It was a new weapon, I tried it for a while.
It was pretty cool.
But I'm getting the magnum and I'm gonna upgrade it to 100% so I can kill the boss in one shot.
But, hold on. I have these mines, I haven't even used them.
Maybe I will hold on to this.
I have to sell something to afford magnum, though.
Time is money, mate.
How much does it cost?
29,400 for the grenades.
Why not try your hand at a new gun, stranger?
That won't get me there.
Ruby's all rubbish, it makes no difference. The price, a deal well struck. That's our choice to make.
It's 1500.
I can certainly do something with this.
I could sell one of these.
That I'm just never gonna use.
I have doubles in a couple of them, don't I?
Your valuables won't do you much good in the grave.
Sell the ruby? I wanna keep all the gems.
I'm gonna sell one flash grenade.
Which will get me there.
Not bad.
Alright, let's do it.
Let us know when you've made some room.
Got cash in your pocket all your life. Easy.
I'm gonna store the magnum. I don't wanna use it yet.
Magnum ammo recipe.
Hell yeah.
Alright, the idea is to spend the rest of the game spending about $200,000.
Getting this all the way up so I can kill the last boss in four or five shots.
What does it take to make the magnum ammo?
A lot.
But I'm happy with that.
I'm gonna store it for now.
No sense in me taking it.
I can't use this.
I think I'm good.
The hair? I will, yep.
Wait, this is important.
Rifle craft ammo. Magnum ammo craft bonus frequency.
We want these on.
Because when I craft magnum ammo, I'm gonna get extra.
I also want to increase the drop rate for gunpowder.
Because it takes a lot of gunpowder to make magnum ammo.
I do make shotgun shells as well.
Although, is it? I think I'm alright.
Alright, we're gonna put the red hair on.
Sell every gun except for the magnum.
I will not be able to complete the game.
Okay.
Now, I'm gonna keep this one on.
I think I'm playing Castlevania or something.
Alright.
So, things are looking good.
Let's go.
Jesus.
The fuck was that?
I don't know if you guys heard that.
He put gunner optics on.
Don't heal Leon.
We want him to suffer.
Not always down.
It's 2020, it's for you, dude.
You have to start streaming in 1080p.
If I can start streaming in 10,000 bit rate, I will.
Oh.
What?
No.
I shot it twice.
Oh my god.
Well, let's try that again.
Oh, that's right.
They did do...
What did they say?
They went like...
Something like that, right?
I'm hearing...
Boot knife.
It's so quiet.
Does this break the durability?
It doesn't look like it.
That hit.
Thanks.
Ashley.
You okay?
Yeah.
Oh shit.
You alright?
Nice shot.
Just like through the fucking head.
Again?
Yeah.
I don't want to use this.
I'm good.
Thanks.
I need more eggs.
I don't look so good.
Damn it.
I hate this.
Uh oh.
I guess this is their idea of a warm welcome.
I am shit faced right now.
Stop asking that.
God damn it.
I am going to heal.
I hate wasting materials.
I hate taking the materials.
It sucks.
Move.
I guess this is their idea of a warm welcome.
Alright, so we got...
I'm going to go this way.
Same.
You know, we're going this way actually.
I want to restart so bad.
You have no idea.
Shoot him.
She's going to get killed.
Back it up.
Do the stab.
Oh my God.
Did I shoot myself in the face?
I don't want to.
Alright, where's the last catapult?
Right there.
Duck.
I just want to fucking shoot it.
You okay?
Alright, we're good.
We're good.
Where are the last ones?
I got all the ones here.
Okay.
All the catapults are done.
Thank God.
I think.
No, there's one more.
Where can I hit it from?
Is she coming?
One more.
Nice.
Uh oh.
Why did you not come in the door?
Oh!
My sensitivity is so low on this thing.
Nice.
Alright.
I think I got everything.
There's one thing here.
Where is it?
Down below?
Did I miss it?
I can take a second though.
I can hear it.
Eh.
Where's this last blue medallion?
I got a pee so bad.
Do you have your cheater?
I mean I have to get it.
It's only one more.
I don't see it.
There's also another treasure in here somewhere.
But where's this last blue medallion?
It'll show you when you get the blue request, really?
Really?
Alright.
Well the actual treasure is right there.
Can you not talk for 30 seconds on stream?
I feel like I do that pretty frequently.
Blue medallions.
God damn it.
You were right.
It actually does show up.
Where is it?
Where is that?
It's like all the way out.
It's like on the rocks.
Good.
There it is.
That's my favorite land mammal.
Buffalo.
Or a rhinoceros.
Rhinoceros is what an unbelievably ridiculous animal.
Rhinoceros is crazy.
What about humans?
Humans are definitely not as cool as a rhinoceros.
Give me my spinal.
Okay.
30 exclusive upgrade tickets?
Years haven't been kind to us.
A single use ticket that grants access to a weapon's exclusive upgrade, regardless of
the weapon's level.
These are 30.
I've been spending these the whole time.
Red herb drop rate.
Is this out of reach now?
This might actually be out of reach.
Do I have to save a lot?
Double blue?
Yeah, double blue.
Oh, I can buy these now.
Where's my...
Oh, I need to get it out of my box.
Alright, we're going damage.
Or ammo.
Damage.
Yeah.
Alright, I'm going to pee.
I'll be right back.
Give me two seconds.
Cinnamon.
Back.
And I got a snack.
It's a tortilla.
Fired.
Fired tortilla with hummus in it.
Just spreading it.
Simple.
You know what a really good snack is?
Who here has had matzo bread?
The really thin, cracker-like bread?
You ever have matzo bread?
So, matzo bread is usually...
I remember when I was younger.
My mother used to spread a little bit of butter on it.
It was just like, holy shit, this is phenomenal.
It's so good.
But I've been putting hummus on it.
I've been spreading hummus across it instead of butter.
Butter is delicious, but you can really go a little overboard
when you spread butter on matzo bread.
And you'll look at what you have, because matzo bread is big.
It's like a huge cracker.
So, putting butter across this gigantic square,
it kind of feels kind of bad.
So, I've been putting hummus on it, and it's unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
Highly recommended.
You can get matzo bread at pretty much any grocery store, too.
It's very dry, but it's very good.
I don't eat this weirdly, I promise.
I just want to eat it a little fast.
What about horseradish?
Hmm.
Good tip.
Is that the one that looks like crispy cardboard?
Yep.
It is very, very dry.
It's got a great flavor, though.
Matzo and butter, it gets dangerous.
Trust me.
Matzo ball soup.
If you've had matzo ball soup, it's phenomenal.
Just kind of super salty, super flavorful.
What about radishes?
Been a while, yeah.
Matzo ball soup is practically crack.
It is.
When you get those big matzo balls, and you just take your spoon,
you're just going to press down, and it just forms around the spoon.
You get a little bit of the broth.
If you've never had it before, I really suggest you try it.
Very, very good.
It's super basic, too.
It's very, I don't want to say plain, but it's very,
it's very palatable.
It's not really heavily spiced or really,
oh, what kind of flavor can I expect?
It's just a good broth, kind of salty, sort of the texture.
It's just very good.
It's very straightforward, yeah.
You making me want bread?
I could live off of matzo bread.
If you gave me just 10 cases of matzo bread,
and two pounds of butter, and three pounds of garlic hummus,
I would probably be happy for a month.
Or even, it might even be a week.
Oh, here he is.
Holy shit.
He looks crazy in this one.
Mr. Kennedy, Mr. Kennedy.
Oh, no.
Nonetheless, you see, the girl must be ours.
With a girl as the very source, your United States,
and then the entire world shall overflow with his grace.
For that is the iron will of my master, the most holy, Lord Sadler.
So then you will comply, yes?
Never.
You heard the lady.
How unfortunate.
Do make sure our guest feels at home now that he has chosen death.
Leon.
Just stay close.
No way a shotgun blast would have blown your head off.
I thought it was Barry.
Leon.
Get cocky for a second.
True.
This doesn't fit.
Didn't I buy heel saving this one?
Could go up.
Wait, let me check the other side.
Of course it is.
Won't open.
Yes.
Perfect timing.
Right when you need it.
I don't think you can go in the front door, but I'm going to do it anyways.
Locked.
There's got to be another way to get to the...
Over here.
Okay.
I need you to open it from the other side.
Buck.
Okay.
Nice job.
Thanks.
More money.
Did she?
Did she follow through?
Yeah.
Can I actually knock it through this?
What can I say?
Let's continue.
Looks like we can continue on this way.
This dude doesn't wash his dishes.
I didn't have a dish.
I had a little paper towel.
Little napkin.
God.
None shall escape.
Sounds of nails clawing at the stone walls and the writhing moan of curses.
That man harbors enough hate to ruin this world.
He once served the lord of the castle as the torturer, like his father and grandfather
before him.
One of the many unsightly legacies left by Salazar family.
Even among his family he was special.
He enjoyed his work wholeheartedly and had a talent for it.
He was gifted at tormenting others.
His abilities soon attracted the master's interest.
And when he took him to the dungeon...
No.
I can't write anymore.
I won't.
I don't want to recall what happened down there.
My mind can't take it.
It'll break me.
I was ordered to attend to him, to feed him, dispose of the filth, all while listening
to that wretched voice every night.
I can't take it anymore.
I've had enough.
I will not tolerate one more night in this castle.
I shall leave tomorrow, go far away, where that voice cannot reach my ears.
That's no way to go.
Do they keep animals down here or something?
Quick!
Ashley, hide!
Okay.
Can I light these?
All right.
I'm not going to stall anymore.
Let's go.
I do remember this part.
The light is lost.
Apparently, I don't remember this part.
I remember this part.
These guys are awful.
I forgot about this enemy.
Okay.
I forget.
I know you have to bait them.
Oh, shit.
Oh, those guys are so bad.
I distinctly have a memory of a part of this game in a little bit, maybe like an hour or so.
It's one of the worst parts of the whole game.
It's so scary and it's so awful.
And it's including those guys.
That is not the enemy I was talking about.
There's another one after that that I find to be worse.
But these guys are pretty bad.
You all know the ones I'm talking about.
I'll give you a quick hint.
You'll see.
Eventually.
Where's Ashley?
You okay?
It's you.
What happened down there?
Nothing.
You were right about the animals, though.
A little bit more than nothing happened down there.
You get a lot of headaches because you squint a lot.
Probably.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Come on.
For now.
All those bobbleheads are here or whatever they are.
Good.
There you are.
I thought I shot her in the head.
How are we doing on crafting here?
All right.
Let's see.
So I get 15 percent.
20.
So there's a 35 percent chance.
Does that mean there's a 35 percent chance to get more or I get 35 percent more for doing
this?
I think it's chance.
Unfortunate.
I actually need to start making shotgun bullets because it's one of the best items I have right
now.
You know what?
Use this.
I had it in my inventory for two hours and I haven't even used it.
There is a treasure here.
Where is it?
It seems almost fully upgraded, too.
I need the eagle, the snake, and the moose.
Okay.
I don't even think about it.
Bloodied sword.
Well, it's just a replica.
Only a couple of uses for it.
Okay.
Iron sword.
So, um, a superb golden sword that has been dulled for display and cannot be used as a
weapon.
Gold?
Maybe this is gold?
That once was a knight who was very strong-willed.
The king knighted him, giving him the ability to go fight for the kingdom.
He did so very valiantly, but he died.
And his sword became rusty.
The end.
I'm going to start using the knife more, but I'm afraid of breaking it.
Okay.
This is...
All right.
What is this one?
This one is seahorse snake.
What is a snake?
Put that down.
Ooh.
Nice.
Golden hourglass.
As if.
I'm going to do it again.
All right.
There's the snake.
Ooh.
Look at...
Yo, look at that.
That was very helpful.
That was exceptionally helpful.
Wow.
There's items, though.
I think there's items over here, probably.
No items?
Yeah, there is.
From the school announcements.
Oh.
Can't pick up that golden chalice.
Give ourselves the way back.
All right.
Hey, a safe haven.
Good.
There are some parasites that have the ability to control their hosts.
This is basic knowledge among most biologists, but not much is known as to how the parasites
do it.
The following is a list of several such parasites.
Weird.
Actually, this is pretty interesting.
The galactosomum.
And the parrot bass.
That's why I eat a lot of garlic.
Those things are nasty.
Yeah.
I could make...
Let's do this.
There's two ways to go here.
Is this a dead end?
It is.
No good.
Isn't there...
There's, like, a minigame or something here, isn't there?
Why do I have a weird memory of it being a minigame here?
There is.
It is a shooting range.
Okay.
Be careful.
Nice shot.
Ashley's very nice.
Very helpful.
Am I facing him too big?
We are.
Tonight's entertainment.
Where's Harvey?
Dan, you know?
Have you seen him?
You know?
Oh my goodness.
I don't even have the thing pop out.
Ah!
Oh my goodness.
I missed.
I'm not getting those.
All right.
We need to...
We need to actually get over here.
All right.
Not bad.
We're okay.
I'm fine.
Ooh, good.
Boy, hey.
I'm fine.
Ooh, good.
Boy, hey.
Some of us are trying to sleep.
This is the probably worst game to be watching when you're falling asleep.
You're going to have nightmares.
All right.
I got to get the wheel, which is over there.
Yeah, over there.
Fell asleep watching the VOD yesterday.
I guess it's all about volume, isn't it?
You turn the volume down.
Why would you say that?
There's nobody even near us.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Whoa.
What happened to her?
Oh.
Duck.
Shit.
Where's eight?
Why can't Leon just give her a gun or at least a brick?
You wouldn't believe what you could do with a brick.
Let me just collect the items.
Honestly, if somebody threw a brick and it hit you right in that face, I think that's
as bad as getting shot, right?
I mean, that would probably just kill you.
You can be a backpack with a bunch of bricks, and I think we'd be all right in here.
Why am I going down?
I'm just looking at chat and talking.
Go up.
I can't reach that.
You need a backpack full of bricks.
Okay.
And the front compartment is like six bricks.
And in the side compartment of four, you know, the other compartment of the backpack of four
bologna and cheese sandwiches wrapped in saran wrap.
And a crowbar.
And put a crowbar on my belt.
I'm making it out of there.
Where did the...
I shot four arrows at somebody up here.
Where are they?
All the way up.
Don't underestimate the brick.
I think they're up here.
Let's do it.
A little over the top, don't you think?
Hmm.
Oh, right.
This part.
Got it.
This is why you have a rifle for this part, bud.
Are you going to be okay?
I'll be all right.
Yeah.
I'll cover you.
Don't stop.
Oh, fuck.
That guy sucks.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Nice job.
Okay.
Get back here.
I want to go through and collect everything.
Can I get up there?
I want to get up there.
Can you help me up there?
You okay?
I want to get up there.
Shit.
Oh, well.
There's no drops.
It's all good.
Come on.
That was intense.
You threw a grenade at her.
I had to make a choice.
It was either she dies because four people were attacking her, or I do about 70 percent
of her health in a grenade and everybody dies around her.
I had to make a choice.
You got 30k.
Give her one.
Give her some bricks.
That's what I'm saying.
I think that's all I can do.
I need to throw you up here.
Come on.
Okay.
Nice.
How far can you throw a rock?
Probably really far.
I would be like hop, hop, hop, run.
You have to be.
I would be in a full sprint.
How much?
How far can I sprint before I do it?
How many steps can I take?
Are we talking standing still from here, no pivoting, just kind of throw, or do we mean
one, two, three, four, five.
Gun it.
Because with like a power walk into a triple quadruple crow hop, I could probably throw
it a hundred yards.
Looks like the right place.
You okay?
I think so.
Instead of worrying about her, worry about your own skin.
Can you at least kick the knife back over here?
Like the knife is pretty much needed.
Drop the accuracy a little bit.
Thank God you didn't have it.
Yeah, if there was a brick in that scenario, Leona's dead.
Roost, come in.
Things went to shit.
We took refuge inside a castle, but I've just been separated from Baby Eagle.
Say it.
And you.
Roost, you're breaking up.
Do you read me?
Damn it.
So much for that.
All right.
Get all that.
So much over there.
All right.
Find Ashley.
I do have a lot of stuff to sell.
Having a rough day, stranger.
Got something new for you.
Body armor.
Bang for your buck.
I guarantee it.
Yeah, I don't need it.
Ruby's all rubbish.
It makes no difference.
These don't have any slots, do they?
Hold on, wait a minute.
Now.
Be yourself, stranger.
Welcome.
You're valuables, stranger.
70k.
I'll pay a pretty penny for that.
Your weapons are in good hands, mate.
I'll see you right.
Finish the knife.
Your weapons are in good hands, mate.
I'll see you right.
Finish the knife?
Will that be pleasant travels?
What is that there?
Got a lot of shit in here.
Sell the rifle ammo.
Welcome.
I'll buy it for thank you.
Yeah.
Come back.
I got a lot of crap.
I'm gonna sell.
Any time.
All right, give me extra magnum ammo.
You're killing me.
All right, let me get it out of there.
Welcome.
Ooh, what you buying?
Dazzled, are you?
Our craftsmanship demands no less.
This thing is ready to go now.
21 damage, eight shots.
Molding a weapon to suit your specific needs.
Honestly, I don't think I care about either one of these.
Got a selection of good things on sale, stranger.
Pleasant travels.
That'd be fine.
Okay.
So how many shots do I have with this?
Six, what do you mean six?
What do you mean six?
This shouldn't just have eight?
I thought that if you upgraded the ammo capacity,
it went up to the maximum.
No?
Does that happen in the other games?
That's in the original.
It has eight.
Yeah, but I mean, I thought that when you upgrade
ammo capacity, it fills it up.
That's all right.
I feel pretty good about this.
I'm gonna go.
Ooh, Magnam ammo, nice.
There's people alive.
This is messed up.
There are other revolvers in the game
that are better than this one.
That's all right.
You get all your money back when you sell something.
So that's fine.
The voice of Pestilence dwells in the flames,
leading the pitiful souls to salvation.
Consign the crimson flame to its rightful place,
where you shall be enlightened.
Lord, I'm doing this.
Ready to interrupt.
Uh-huh.
Buzzo.
Get away from me.
Stop reloading.
Out of you, out of your mind.
Stop doing this.
Oh, shit.
Get off of me.
Where is he?
Get over here.
No, I didn't want to do that.
Oh, shit.
All right.
There's a lot of stuff on the ground.
A Sephiroth's theme?
All right.
Wait, you mean the one that goes,
De-tee, de-tee-roo, de-tee-ree, de-tee-roo, de-tee-roo.
That one?
Hmm.
You're with pearls and rubies.
Nice.
Crimson Lantern.
That, it, there's probably something else in here.
There is.
Bullets on the ground and money.
Drop the chandelier.
Is that a good thing?
Should I do that?
How do I do it?
Oh, that's right.
There was that lever.
I ran by it because I fell off.
You fell off L ratio.
I said it before you did, so.
I made it so it's not funny.
Because if I say it and then you,
if I say it first, it's like, oh, fuck.
Like dad said it.
Ooh, that was worth it.
Appreciate it.
Need to Ashley.
Won't open.
Hmm.
There's a big chest in there.
Are there still snakes in boxes?
Yes, there is.
I actually just ate one.
Not that long ago.
Running low on juice here.
I need some more water.
You can stop.
Wouldn't make me use this, would you?
Well, after six years, that is one hell of a game.
I think that gun could go off.
Ada.
You don't seem surprised.
Interesting.
Try using knives next time.
Better for close encounters.
Not a bad move.
Very smooth.
So who are you working for this time?
Oh, Leon.
You know I don't work in town.
I thought he just stabbed himself in the chest.
She's lost no matter what.
You walk away now and who knows.
Maybe I'll live to meet me again.
And then I might get you that greeting you were looking for.
You think I'm gonna give up that easy?
Right.
How about we continue this discussion another time?
By the way, Wesker wears the sunglasses, you fucking dork.
Zip line out.
Last person I thought I'd run to here.
The glasses and the cut scene.
Yeah, they really are just ruining everything.
All right.
This is the maze part, isn't it?
My name is Maze.
I think I'm, am I missing one?
Oh wait, you can flip them.
Oops.
This is not correct.
It's not even a puzzle.
What is going on here?
Oh, it wants me to do, okay.
It wants me to do that.
Is that not right?
Bro.
Oh, it's a hexagon.
Should do it.
I guarantee I can run faster than you.
I guarantee it.
Can't, yeah, imagine we, all of us,
all fucking 13,000 of us,
we're at like a fucking 100 meter dash
and I'm, so here we go.
Start.
I blow by all of you.
And I'm gonna be looking back.
I'm gonna be, you're all gonna be in the review.
Some of you are gonna be like, I can't, I can't do it.
And I'm already finished.
Enjoy your puzzles.
All right.
Need to find Ashley.
Hear the signal echo through the mountains.
Rocks become gravel and the castle walls crumple.
You're 37 and you only eat raw radishes and mayonnaise.
That's not my diet, man.
I eat fucking chicken.
I eat lean turkey, spinach, lettuce, kale, hummus,
chickpeas, fruits, apples, carrots.
I've started eating an apple pretty much every day.
They're gonna be sprinting in the 100 meter dash.
I'm gonna be so far ahead of you.
And I'm just gonna take an apple out and just be like,
and just fucking just keep running.
Yeah, I might even throw a few banana peels behind me too.
Good luck.
What the hell?
I didn't even see what it was.
Christ.
Jesus.
Oh my God, he killed me.
Holy shit.
This is a new enemy.
This enemy was not in the other game.
Wow.
That's new.
Was it?
It was?
I don't remember.
He ran faster than you.
This is me hitting W-A-S-D on a keyboard.
Wait, there's an item in here.
Christ.
That was scary.
My legs are twice the length as yours.
That's fine.
You don't think I'm aware that a lot of you
might be taller than me?
Some of you might be shorter too.
You better, but I'm eating a whole bowl of pasta for that.
I'm gonna eat a full bowl of plain pasta.
Like two hours, four hours before we do our fucking
residential fitness test.
Welcome.
Ooh, what you're buying.
A deal well struck.
Ah.
I wanna go back to that game, the coin thing.
We're half your age, most of us too.
We'll see.
Why am I acting like we're doing this?
See you at the next meet, bro.
I need a yellow.
No rifle, Andy?
That's fine.
Let's hit me in the head.
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no, don't do that.
What's that sound I hear?
Damn, that's pretty good against spiders.
Is that a one hit kill on the spiders?
That's a one hit kill on the spiders.
This is the spider killer.
This thing's great on spiders.
Wow, nice.
Okay, good.
Actually has a pretty good use.
Would you run with your arms out like Naruto?
No, I would run like this, just windmilling.
This is closed.
Okay, I think I see how this works.
It hurt him to do that.
You don't know what did and didn't hurt.
Yes, I'll be icing my shoulder later.
Thank you very much.
Did I shoot that out of his hand?
I agree.
Okay, gotta pull it again.
It's mine.
You gotta be kidding me.
How do I miss that point blank?
Saving ammo doing this though.
It's a good thing.
Only one shotgun.
Hold on.
Let's open this.
Not yet.
Give me that shit back.
He's saving his ammo for the Resident Evil 5 remake.
I have almost no ammo in my inventory.
What?
Look at this.
I've got 12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
I have like 16 bullets left in my entire arsenal.
Keep that open for now.
You piece of shit.
She said meeting you once was enough.
Get that little bug.
Stop.
Oh my goodness gracious.
No, where did it even come from?
I just wasted every shot.
All right, I'm gonna speed run this shit.
Oh, I can't believe I can't believe it.
Fuck.
Okay, go.
Okay, I think I see how this works.
Would you live here?
No.
No, I don't think I would.
Keep it open.
Okay.
What if it had central air?
Central heating and air.
I'd think about it.
What would you do if you were cloned?
It'd be bad.
Because initially I would make the clone do everything.
Be like, oh, hey, clone, I gotta go to the grocery store.
You go.
Hey, clone, I need you to stream.
You should go stream.
I need you to work on the wash machine, bro.
Call somebody, you figure it out, fix it.
And I would become gradually
over like a two or three, four month period.
I would gain probably 150 pounds.
So that I would be like the big unhealthy version of myself.
So it wouldn't be like, oh, look, it's Jerma.
People would know that it was,
I wouldn't be able to hide it anymore.
I would be like, yeah, you go do that.
Go do this, go do that, go do that.
And eventually I would just kind of
probably be really unhealthy.
We would have to split it.
Okay, so if you're gonna, okay,
if clone one, you're gonna stream on Monday.
I'll stream on Tuesday.
I'll do the laundry on Wednesday.
You do the laundry on, you know, next week.
You know what I'm talking about?
We'd have to make a system.
Be like having a roommate.
It would be a roommate.
But it would be a roommate that looks exactly like you.
That can do things in place of you.
You think, what about if the clone attacked me?
See, I don't know.
If the clone is me and it knows exactly
like what I would be doing and where, I don't know.
We wouldn't, it would be a stalemate.
Twins exist, you know?
Yeah, twins exist.
We're talking about a clone,
like a carbon copy of me, a clone.
That means it has all my,
I'm assuming it has all my memories.
It has all my preferences, my whole life, right?
I mean, it would be a carbon copy of me.
A clone wouldn't get the memories.
Well, that's the thing.
It would just be a clone that is a baby
that grows up into the clone of me.
Or are we talking about a machine that like,
and like another me walks out?
That was a lot of stuff.
Okay, so now I gotta go up.
This is where I died last time.
I am not dying here again.
Nope.
Oh my, I almost died again.
Just died again.
That didn't blow up.
How is it?
Somebody else.
Calm down.
How would I pull that?
I need to go this way.
I have no, I don't have any ammo.
Oh, he's running so weirdly.
Oh, I heard that guy's neck break.
Oh, get on the fucking ladder.
This shadow.
Ooh, a beetle.
Nice.
You see how weird that was?
That was weird.
That person slid in.
They skated in.
That was so weird.
Are you?
If I go up here and get hit in the head with a rock,
I'm gonna be really, really mad.
Items.
I got him.
Did he drop something?
I don't think so.
Anything else to shoot with the cannon?
Go get in the cannon and shoot him out.
I don't think there's anything else in here,
but I will look.
I love the way the game looks.
That Capcom Resident Evil engine.
I just wish they would use it for every single game.
I mean, other companies that aren't Capcom.
Sorry, I've had my fill of you guys.
I can go across still.
I don't even think about it.
Can I go down?
Really?
How could you have that many drawers and none of them open?
Oh, this part.
Ashley, where are you?
People are gonna get really mad at me here.
Are they?
Hold on.
I'll figure it out.
I'll be fine.
Stylish mask.
Easier this time.
I'm so scared.
Myself anymore.
Oh, something else.
She must've been terrifying now.
I know.
You too?
I should get all the way here without dying.
I don't know.
But you can't run.
You gotta keep moving forward.
We will beat this.
Together.
I don't know if I can.
You can.
Just give me heads up before you stab me next time, okay?
Leon, thanks.
Reunited.
Okay.
Luis, where are you?
Sorry, I screwed up.
Come to my rescue, Prince Charming.
I'll show you a charmer, pal.
How many chapters are there?
Come on, bastard courtyard.
Be late to the dance.
I'm a little bit,
I'm pretty much right at the halfway point, I think.
Maybe a little bit more.
When he's in trouble, we can't just leave him, right?
End of the stream, boys?
No.
No, I'll go for like another hour.
See, they know what they're doing.
I told you.
It begins.
Need to go through here.
All right.
Get a visual for what this looks like.
I'm gonna go from here.
I'm gonna go left.
I'm gonna go left first.
Let me just check over here.
Nothing.
So when looking at the big staircase,
left is where I'm going.
I'm gonna walk, by the way.
I'm not gonna run.
Hey, let's go right.
Just eat him immediately.
Two bonus, nice.
Okay.
A lot of gunpowder.
Imagine being Ashley and watching him do that.
Yeah, me eating a snake.
Okay.
I didn't go over here.
What's that?
Nice.
Where is it?
Okay.
Nothing over here.
Dog.
What is happening?
You jumped over it.
Wait, what?
Did I let them out?
I thought they were gonna break it down.
I thought they were gonna smash it down eventually.
I was like paranoid.
Okay.
You let them out?
I don't, it's dead?
I don't think it's dead.
Ooh, elegant chessboard.
I hear something running.
God damn it.
I missed that somehow.
I don't care.
There's one flag, two more.
Can you look out for dogs, please?
Don't be rude.
Don't be rude to Ashley.
I'm not being rude.
Please refill that.
They're just too useful.
I need them.
All right.
Where did I come from?
Came from here.
So I could go straight.
I'm gonna go straight.
Right across.
Like in here.
You can just hear them like.
Put this down.
Okay.
Careful.
Dude.
Where's the last one?
That one's pulled down.
Right here?
Okay.
It's right here.
Uh-oh.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why'd you let go?
Where are you going?
Where are you?
Why did you run away?
I was gonna come get you.
What are you doing?
Get out of the way.
Question.
It's like The Sims.
There's a fire over there.
Will you just relax?
I'm trying to.
We're good.
Please don't kill me.
Thank God this was loaded.
Okay.
This whole thing got fucked up though.
I gotta go that way.
This was not that bad.
Please do a suplex.
I don't even know how.
God.
I didn't want to miss anything.
All right.
This is it.
I think I got pretty much everything.
I think I missed one item, maybe.
You have to be on their knees
and you have to be behind them.
Shoot somebody in the knee
and then they lay from behind.
Okay.
Now we can finally get out of this maze.
This is why I crafted it.
There you go.
That's why I crafted it.
They're not over here, are they?
I didn't really miss much.
I don't think I missed anything.
We're gonna raid.
Hey, Boon, thanks for the raid.
Welcome, everybody.
Playing Resident Evil 5.
Thank you, Boon.
Four, four, four.
Right.
Did I say five?
This is just so confidently wrong.
That was confidently incorrect.
Not some new wares, stranger.
You're in for a treat.
Little medallions in the hall, okay.
I can do even more nasty upgrades
on those weapons of yours
and make them sing even louder.
Was this like another upgrade system?
Oh no.
Welcome.
I've got something new for you, mates.
That cash in your pocket or your life.
Easy choice, mate.
Always do the case upgrade.
Enough to get the job done, surely.
Oh, there's even more.
Your weapons are in good hands, mate.
I'll see you right.
It's definitely a shotgun.
I'll buy almost anything.
He, he, he, he, thank you.
Oh, this is gonna be worth like 50, 60 grand.
Got a scum.
Double red, two, right?
Double red.
This is, this is triple red, isn't it?
Yeah.
Or should I do yellow?
Triple is better than, yeah, no, triple's better.
43,000, that's pretty damn good.
Any welcome.
What about yellow, yellow?
Ruby's all rubbish.
It makes no difference.
The price will.
I think triple would be better than yellow, yellow.
Hold it, onto it.
Why?
Try to get four?
Try to get another one to do four red?
It's true.
Easy work.
Molding a weapon to suit your specific means.
Oh, it's a thing of beauty, isn't it?
Hmm, this is important.
This kind of work is about finesse, stranger.
Little bit goes a long way, you'll see.
There you are, as you wished.
Will that be all then?
Whoa.
There's some things money can't buy.
Heh heh, good it, Liz.
I need more of these square ones.
Well, I have room.
I could probably bring the magnum now,
just in case I wouldn't bring it.
Might as well.
Nah, just leave it.
Kind of low on healing.
There's a gumball machine.
Well, that's what we're about to do right now.
I'm gonna imagine this is probably the last thing
I'm gonna do on the stream,
because I'm about to go down here,
and I'll probably be here for a while.
Rare.
Yes, I have to go 100% health recovery for black bass.
Is that good?
That means I have to go farm the lake for food,
but they take up so much space.
That's actually pretty good.
They spawn all the time.
Okay, let's do it.
I've never shot this weapon so far.
Thanks, Ashley.
That's pretty good.
Where am I missing the other ones?
In the barrels?
Stupid.
I'm so bad with the machine gun.
Shit!
I would have had it too.
I would have had it.
Controller is wet.
It's so inaccurate.
How are you supposed to do that?
Relively.
You!
Can you go in the other room?
If you're just, you're annoying.
She's just like, you're shocked.
She's not even saying that.
She was being very supportive.
You give me the shotgun,
and I'm gonna perfect it every time.
Reload?
Whatever.
I fucking hate the machine gun.
Oh, I hate the machine gun.
Come on.
What?
What the fuck?
Reload the gun.
Oh, that's gonna be so hard to do that.
That's gonna be hard as absolute hell to do that.
This shit is so inaccurate.
Just give me the bonus.
No, press the fucking button.
I hate the double weapon one.
Just only use the shotgun as the only weapon to use.
No!
I better get the bonus.
I hate this gun so much.
I feel like that's chat.
It's like, it's all right.
Hey, nice job.
You're doing great.
You're doing a good job.
Don't worry.
You're doing good.
I'm just sitting here like,
I hate this fucking game.
Wow.
What are you?
Oh my God.
It's the most inaccurate piece of shit gun in the whole game.
It's not even worth it.
It's the biggest piece of shit in the game.
It's just like the accuracy is this big square
and it's just good luck.
I don't know.
Did I do it?
It doesn't matter.
Oh my goodness.
He moved right at the very end.
I want the gold coin.
Let me out.
Let me out of here.
I hate this weapon.
Quiet for a second.
That's an epic.
Illuminado's emblem plus 20% melee critical hit rate.
Melee crit rate.
Does that mean I can just swing the knife?
That sounds unbelievable.
Is it crit kicks?
Oh, that might be amazing.
I have to get the other one, right?
I have to.
I could do this, right?
There we go.
Wow.
20% weapon resale value.
Incredible.
Nice.
It was really cool.
I could get the other one,
but one more try.
No, I hate that gun.
That's cool.
200% health from Bass.
So I'm curious.
Welcome.
What can I interest you in?
So the riot gun is 152,000.
Your valuables won't do you much.
Next time, buy something.
So if I put this on,
that's so ridiculous.
I don't know.
I'm not gonna put the Bass one on.
Or the magnum.
Oh, it's already on there.
All right, so now it was 157.
Well, what is it now?
What?
I'll buy almost anything.
How did it go down?
Suit yourself, stranger.
20%.
It was 152,700.
That's not 20.
20% would be like 20, 30K, 40K.
Plus 20% weapon resale value.
That'd be $30,000.
Was it 127 or 157?
What is it?
It doesn't count the upgrades.
Welcome.
Got a selection of good things on sale.
How is it?
What?
Look at the mask you got.
Hold on.
It's not that good then.
I'll leave the magnum on.
It's kind of unfortunate.
All right.
Oh, the mask, right.
Save it.
And then I will, we'll check out the mask.
An extra 3K.
It's not 20%.
It's all right though.
You have more than one.
So how much money do I got?
360.
Can't really do much else.
This is probably a good place to stop.
Seven hours or so.
What's right?
I think there's a boss coming up really soon here.
Let me shoot these things in the hall.
Look, there's a statue up there.
Oh no, I got a while.
You're gonna put the three or four heads on this, right?
Yeah.
I got a long time.
At least another hour or two.
Let me just do this.
Where's that one?
That one, there's two on the ground floor.
Three.
And the last ones are deeper in, which I'll go this way.
Yeah.
No, we're good.
Yeah, that's gonna be it.
Where is it?
There it is.
Wait, where is it?
Already got it?
No, no, no, no.
There's a, there's a treasure here.
I can hear it swaying around.
Where is it?
It's right there.
Ooh.
I will see you guys later.
I might, I think I'm streaming tomorrow.
So the plan.
So I will see you guys.
Yeah, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Tomorrow as in Sunday.
Probably around the same time,
probably around like five or six.
We'll keep doing this, gonna keep playing it.
And that's it.
See you guys tomorrow.
I don't need to, all right, I saved it, right?
Yeah, thanks for watching guys.
See you tomorrow.
That's gonna be it.
It's great.
It's genuinely as much fun as I had playing the other one.
We talked earlier about how, is it better?
Is it worse?
I think it's kind of just another version.
It's another version of it and it's very good.
They're both fantastic.
I love this game.
Very, very good.
I don't think I even need to give you a final assessment.
It's just one of the best games ever made.
It just is one of the best games I've probably ever played.
It's in the top 10, top 20, probably.
But we will continue it tomorrow.
Take care.
Get some sleep.
See you around five or six o'clock.
We'll just put six.
If I show up a little bit early,
I might show up a little bit early.
I'm not trying to beat it tomorrow, for those wondering.
There's at least another 10 to 12 hours,
I think, in the game.
It's gonna go at the pace we're going.
Maybe another few streams,
two or three streams, I would imagine.
Three, six hour streams,
two, seven or eight hour streams.
We'll see.
I'm not gonna put a time limit on it
and I'm not gonna rush through it either, right?
Well, I'm not gonna put a time limit on it
and I'm not going to go too slow either.
I'm gonna go as exactly as I wanna go.
Thanks for sticking around.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Have a good one.
Call your mother.
See you soon.
Take care.