Hey, what's up? Hey, what's up? How you doing? Hey Jerma, good to see you. I'm a whole day,
a whole day early. I tend to be doing, I don't know what's going on with the schedule, man.
I really don't understand. I mean, I don't have a schedule. The sus has been so wrong. It's,
I show up a day early or a day late. If the sus says like four o'clock on a Tuesday,
I might just be, that means Monday at eight o'clock Pacific or Thursday at two o'clock
Pacific. The sus has been just so all over the place. But yeah, we're gonna, we're streaming
right now. Just briefly go over what's going on before I hop on a call. First of all, hi.
Second of all, gonna be playing Risk tonight. That's right. The board game Risk online
with other streamers. I believe so far, I believe we have, it's me Ludwig, Connery's pants
and critical so far. That might be it. That sounds like pretty pog group by the way.
And then we're going to play DOS. Oh, that's the plan. Let me jump in this call. So I'm,
I don't really play Risk that often, but I'm pretty good. Risk with a resident sleeper face.
No, no, you can't resident sleeper Risk until six hours has gone by
and everyone wants to go home. Gentlemen, how are we? If they said to me and I don't eat,
I cannot hear anything. What happened? Why can I not hear anything?
My audio is fucked up, man. Hold on. Oh, my headphones are unplugged. I'm going to go,
I'm going to hire a pro audio technician. What is going on with this audio? Oh shit. I think I
have like a DOS game open. I think a DOS games open. That's what's going on. Hold on. Okay,
we're good. All right, we're good. If he has smoothies and stuff for nutrients, then maybe.
But like no calories at all. You just don't, you don't make that.
I don't, I don't know how much he weighs. Like there's a couple of people that have done
no eating for like a year, but they were extremely obese and were fine,
but they supplemented nutrients. But Mr. Beast isn't like super out of shape or anything like
that. So I just don't see him being able to pull that off. We got a good crew. This is a really
good crew. I'm excited. Yeah. German, what's the longest you could go without eating four Big Macs
in a row? A lot without eating four Big Macs in a row. We'll just do normal McDonald's order,
I guess. I mean, I get McDonald's maybe once every 10 days. I'd say probably, I'd say 11 days.
Uh, gamers, does everyone have risk? Is it risk global domination? The free one? Yeah,
that's the one. Okay. I'm downloading though. Um, I love it. I don't know why you're so quiet.
Oh, am I? I sometimes this problem. Oh, let me, is this better? Oh, there you go. Turn myself up a
bit. I can hear him. I don't have a cloud lifter. That's why I thought that, uh, the music playing
right now was, I'm doing DOS games after this. I thought that I had DOS games open in the
background because the song is playing and I realistically thought it was like a midi DOS game
music. It is, what is it? What else is it? It's in something else, but it is, it is a terrible,
but also amazing song. Is that like, what was the last time anybody here played risk?
I've never played risk. You've never played it? Really? I've never played it. I had
old risk game on the PlayStation one when I was like eight, but all I did was mash a couple
buttons every now and then and gave up. I guess it's pretty, it's pretty self-explanatory, right?
You just roll dice at each other. Yeah. I didn't even know they were nice in the game. So this is
going to be real wild for me. I think they're like, uh, power-ups. Is this classic risk or is
there like, can you do wacky shit? Don't know. Well, I got don't know. Well, I got don't know.
Well, that's all right. He's busy. He's busy. He's setting up stuff. I know nothing about this game.
All right. Let me explain very briefly. It's a map of the world. We get to place troops. For instance,
I'm not going to say this on, uh, on camera in front of them, but I'll say it on camera in front
of you. Australia. If you hold Australia, you get to at least watch your friends destroy each other
and hang out for like an hour and just sip like a Coke. That's what I used to do. I would just take,
I would have Australia and that, uh, that like southeastern region, which could, you could only
attack from one place and I would just drink like two Cokes and be able to at least participate for
a while. So that's kind of what I'm going to try to do. Uh, but yeah, it's, it's, it's country that
you claim. I'm in game. I'm ready to ride. I think there's like a, probably a code we're going to use.
Right. I imagine. True. Sorry, sorry, sorry. I went to get headphones. How the fuck are you guys?
It's good to see you guys. I'm doing great. They're doing great, man. Hope you're, you're doing well.
Yeah. It's been great. This game is loud. What is your strategy? What are you, what are you guys
thinking of strategy? Cause I have one. I've never, well, that's no, I played this game one time, uh,
on the eighth grade field trip on the way, on the bus on the way to DC. Um, that was it.
So none of the three of you, it turns out, I haven't played this game much at all. I actually
have some experience. I just played this all the time. Really? I did. I mean, I can't say I'm very
good, but I understand the basic kind of what's going on. I've played a good amount of this game,
but the reason I asked you three in specific is because usually the way it goes is alliances form
and bitter rival restart. But I picked the three people who could, I think I could never get mad
at ever in hopes that, uh, it will lead me to a combination. I was really sweet of you, sir.
Also the three least experienced players I know, which just was coincidental. Yeah, no, that's fair.
Let's see how you feel at the end of this three dice. They just gave me it. I take this incredibly
seriously and I got, I'm sorry. If you guys, I say like talk a bunch of shit and call you names and
stuff. I don't mean it. Oh, it's fine. That's what makes it fun. Do you think you come in and make
it like a funny name? I'm excited. I haven't played this in a long time. All right. So for rules,
I'm going to turn off manual placement. It'll automatically place all of the, uh, the things
for us. The basic way risk works is we will evenly divide at the start of the territory.
That means I can't pick them where you land and then you have to like move your forces around.
It'll make sense when we're in it. Random is hard because random just put you, you could be anywhere.
I think the worst part about risk though is placing ships and soldiers for like an hour.
Yeah, it does. It can take a while. Yeah. Uh, we know how to join yet. Uh, yeah. I'm getting a code
for you guys right now. Are we going to have to get this off the screen for a sec? I think I can
just invite you guys. Good old Ludwig is online. Yeah. Are you able to, are you offline Connor?
All right. I invited Connor invites. Do I even have you on steam? I have to pray because we did
that whole thing where he played like 18 games. He used five tokens to join. Oh wait, here it is.
Here it is. I used five of them. I bought the game. Should I not have bought this game? It was free.
Yeah. But like I didn't, they said there was a timer for the amount of times you could play
or something. I don't know. Oh yeah. I think it's like a freemium model. I sent the code by the way
in the chat so you guys could join up that. I think I joined. Yeah. You're in Connor. You're in.
I can't show my screen just yet. So no one sees the color. They, they tripped me up on that one.
It said, do you want a tutorial? I said, no. Then it said, do you accept our terms? I said, no,
no, I'm kind of fucked. That was it. That was a big move from them. I'm not going to lie.
You don't accept the privacy terms. So like, you just can't play.
No one knows I'm lying when I say accept. I believe we're all in.
Are we good to go? Yeah. Preparing for battle. Let's do it. Okay. Are you as pan-germa? That's me.
Is that like a family? Uh, no, I, I, dude, when I split, okay, when I split team fortress too,
I used to have to hide my name because if people saw that it was me playing, they would just like
five pocket medics would be on me and that eight snipers would join the other team.
This is a messy map. Well, now they're going to know your gas can. Where am I?
Colors are on the right. So it's probably best for a camera to be on the left.
Okay. Okay. Middle ish is both good. I'm red. Let's make it smaller. Do I need to do something?
Yeah. So the timers at the top of the screen, Connor, that's your turn timer. You can see it
moving right now at the start of a turn, you have some troops you can place. So you have to click
on a blue territory and add troops to that territory. So you, yeah, you, you just bulked
up Eastern U S in Shenzhen. Now you can attack, which pretty straightforward. Well, usually you
want to attack anything with a lower number than your number adjacent to it. Oh, that makes sense.
So like, maybe you could attack Mexico. I can't attack Mexico. Let me do that. You could invade
the rest of Russia with your Russian. I can only, Oh, I see. I see how to do it. But yeah,
I'll take Mexico. You have to have at least, you have to have at least three, you have to leave
at least one person on a country. Right. That's how it works. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I should
have done that. Yeah. So it's a dice roll, right? And so you just sometimes lose the dice roll.
And that's how it determines if you win or lose the battle. Oh, I really want Venezuela though.
You could attack it again. And then I, no, you could use Peru. Be careful here.
There it is getting too thin though. Somebody can just go on great turn. That was a great turn.
And now the final move you get to do is you get to move pieces to a final area.
So if you want it to like stack one area to be really strong, you could like,
I got the Venezuela card. You, you do get cards when you conquer a territory and then you can
use those cards and cash them in for big troop bonuses. Ooh, this is going to be hard because
I, uh, this is Ludwig. Oh, we'll take over my home of Australia. I'm so mad that you
decided to do that. That's exactly what I was going to do. What? Yeah. You're not green. Are
you? I am green. And now I can't, I can't even, I might as well just leave. I didn't know. I didn't
know. Only I knew. Uh, let me, oh, this is tough now actually. What do I do? We're going to Africa.
Do this. I can definitely claim this completely. Do we want to attack the Philippine islands?
Wait, so why did you want to play with us? I feel like you don't, you said you can't ever be mad at
us, right? You're just going to feel bad whenever you attack us now? No, I feel great about that.
I feel bad losing. Oh yeah. That's the worst feeling. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I got an
Argentina card. So if you hold a continent, you get extra placement in the fortify round, right?
Yeah. I believe they'll tell you if you get the whole continent, but like if you get all of South
America, uh, or all of Africa, all of us, any of those, you get it like a bonus. Okay. What,
what is the green, the right of the bottom of South America? What is that? That country? I have zero
clue. They just made one up. Yeah. What is that? What is that? It's a Mauritius islands. It's
Atlanta, the Falkland islands is what it's called. Hmm. Falkland. Oh, you can choose how much dice
you want to roll. Right. Okay. That's Atlantis. Yeah. You could, you could lower the amount.
Hang tight, Egypt. Oh, we got no leader. If I've ever heard one. No, now nobody, nobody go anywhere.
Cause this is, this is, this is a border here. If you enter Europe, there will be repercussions.
I'm trying to just, I'm trying to stay here in this, uh, in Africa. I'm trying to, I,
I'm going to tell you right now. I'm going to, we're here. I'm coming for you. No, you don't want,
you don't want to fuck with Congo. I'll tell you right now. We're strong. Oh, shit though. I have,
who's blue? That's Connor. That's me. I can only roll two. Oh yeah. Connor. Yes. All right. You
want to give me, uh, you want to give me Africa and I'll leave you alone in South America? Yeah.
Yeah. You can have it. Okay. Alliance. Okay. So do I like, do I need to do something like just,
just leave next room? Oh, okay. All right. I'm going to be aggressive. Wait, what? How do I?
Thank you. Wait, what are you confused on? You have to click the country you want. Somebody said,
I'm glad Jerma finally made some friends. Fucking plenty of friends. We're in the top,
Charlie. Your third through. Okay. I love you. I'm like a seven year old. That's like going to
school for the first time. Maxing out that to seven and then taking like,
you know, Northern Russia is a good idea, but you got to go fast. You're losing time here.
All right. I'm, I'm taking America. Oh, I didn't want to do. Oh, whoa. I feel threatened up there.
All right. You got to go next to the bottom. All right. And then you attack. Okay. I'm coming.
Lovely lady Liberty. The Canadians need to calm down. I own that weird. Whatever that is one
country. What is this country is you got to hit attack Charlie. I got one quickest one,
although it's less measured. I think I'm getting it. It's Greenland to be too. Let's go. Hey,
this is not Greenland. So wait, if you have one, can you like net, you can never fight like two,
right? Yes. One can never fight because they have to stay home. So then you roll for like,
what's the brand them aspect? Like when like I picked somebody to like fight your two troops,
we both get two dice. And if your die rolls are higher, you win. But if mine are higher or to
draw, I win. So I think there's an attacker's advantage. Maybe it's a defender's advantage.
You have, and you have to move at least three troops. If you attack with three dice.
Yeah, I'm going to give Ukraine four troops because I stand with Ukraine.
So the strategy is if you roll with one die against somebody with one, you won't,
you won't have to take all your troops. It's defenders advantage. I lied. Sorry. Excuse me.
So wait, the German, what did you want me to do? I'm okay. I'm willing to let you have whatever
that green spot over there is. Oh, the Falklands. Yeah. You take that. But I want to get out of here.
Attack it. All right. Well, what you could do is you could attack. Who's red? Is that a Madagascar?
You could, you could help me out there and get knocked that down a little. I think you should go
for bottom left Connor. Cause then you get all of South Africa or America and you get a bonus.
So you should attack the Falkland islands, but you have to go quick. Your turn's almost over.
Okay. And then move all your troops. So then German will, will come in. You see how it's
like blue outlined, like it's a YouTube thumbnail. Yeah. Buggers came out of my
nose and you said that. I don't know why. Oh, okay. All right. All right. So my whole turn is done.
Oh, I should not have done this. Let's just keep it simple. Let's just send three.
The Kiwis are too strong. Told you. Wow. Yep. I'm sending two. Not enough. You need a whole army.
And I will not attack you in South America, Connor. Cause I appreciate our alliance that
we have forming here. There's no one, no way New Zealand could just go all the way over there.
All right. I don't appreciate the, uh, the diplomacy with this other, uh, this other
general here. I mean, you can't, you can't get me to try it. You couldn't even get over here.
Okay, Connor. Now your, your boats would sink. Okay. Since you threatened us,
we've just said your boats would say, well, to prove that our boats wouldn't sink. I came
and attacked. That's not cool. I'm just trying to show you that if you give me a little lip,
then I will attack. I dare you Auckland. See what happens. They're crazy down there.
You didn't even heard of them. I refuse to be goaded. It's perfect. Uh, all right. Let's
fortify. Let's fortify up. Uh, and let's, let's actually, let's bring them back home. Huh?
Oh, wow. So if you see in the, in the middle of the left, by the way, you get these cards.
And if they're all three, the same or all three different, you get a different bonus. It says it
on the right. You can cash them in. All right. I'm going, I, I gotta, I gotta get, uh, I gotta get,
this is Madagascar. I'm going for it. No, I need, I've gotta take, I've gotta have Africa.
I need those points. Charlie, you win this. Don't even be worried. Oh, yeah, I do. Let's go baby.
No, I'm, I hold on. I don't want to count. Not enough. All right. Come on. One,
one, one, one, one, one, one, one. Let's go. I thought you did two for a second. All right. Okay.
So now I got to be careful because you love it. You're orange, right? I am. Hmm. He's not a nice
guy. I am a nice guy. I replied to diplomacy very well. The people of Argentina disagree.
People of Argentina can suck it. Whoa. I didn't know I had such a presence up there in, um,
in North America. I've been also ignoring all my troops up North. I feel good. Oh man. Oh,
how does that? I'm coming in again. I don't really know what I'm doing, but this feels good.
You're not doing bad. It's a one B two here though. It's kind of a risky fight. Oh, I didn't mean to
do that. Why is it? How do I back out when that? All right. I'm just going to keep swinging on
everything. I've gone mad. I like how you thought about asking and then just sit and screw it. I'll
just fight everything. Eastern us. I'm doing it live. Charlie. I will, I will stay here with,
uh, with Iceland and it'd be a barrier for you. Yeah. I wouldn't attack here, Charlie,
because you're going to lose a lot of troops. You might want to fortify them and bring them
South and try to attack the Mexican border. That sounds like something an enemy would say.
Oh, I had it or Charlie. I had, yeah, I had to end. I see. I didn't have a choice. I'm willing
to be kind of a shield here for you to make it so nobody can come in. I, how do I fortify? I don't
click on the place you want to bring troops to and then geography. All right. So do I use my
cards right now? You can decide your cards. I think you have to have three and they have to be
matching. And I would tell you right now, don't tell everybody if you have a match because we
people will know that you're about to drop cards to get troops. I see. Yeah. I don't have any
matches. I believe it's one of the same three or one of each, right? I have like zero matches.
Oh, you, oh, there we go. I'll do that. Oh, going for the whole us here. Huh? Oh, I lost.
Well, that sucks. East coast. Just fight strong. We're fine. Everything's fine. Charlie. It's
looking rough. I think you might have to focus on, uh, on Europe, but no Ludwig. How did you get
this many troops already? They were fine. Europe hasn't been attacked once and I'm very sad in
Australia. I said your borders are weak in the chat and that guy, please get him in my chat too.
I don't want to hear that. Get him out of everywhere. Bottom here. He doesn't have a
YouTube totally fortify over. Oh, can I fortify the ones? Uh, cause you can't leave. Cause if
they left, then you, the territory would be open. Oh, I'm like moving people adjacent. Okay. Now
I get it. Yeah. Fortifying is basically moving troops from one section adjacent to another
section. Oh shit. We move many numbers to small numbers. Cool. I did it. Is there a report feature
in this game? What would you be reporting? Who's reporting? I mean, if you click on people's avatars,
you can like make an Alliance, uh, like report this user. Is that what that is? Oh yeah. Yeah.
Presumably if they're acting, uh, awry, I guess we'll watch out a little bit. Give me some
reports later. Come from Argentina again. You do, you're doing the exact same thing I want to do.
This is like the guarantee that you can hang out with your friends for an hour and like
watch them just destroy each other. Well, you just drink like a Coke and then eventually when
everybody gives up, you're fine because like you, you at least got to hang out with your friends
for a little while. I have a nice iced coffee here. Um, Charlie, what do you want to do in Europe
here? Glad I held onto that one till I was on the call. I am a big Scandinavia fan. I'm sorry.
Big Scandinavia fan. I love that for you. Wait. Yeah. Charlie, what if I, what if I give you a
proposition here? Wait, I messed it up. I didn't click the wrong one. Let me help you get.
Hear me out. Hear me out. Hear me out. I'm going to show you, look up North.
We're going to get real, real thin soon. We're going to spread real thin and you can have this
whole territory and then maybe you just back out of Asia. You see how like these are all ones you,
I give you a free rain to kill all these troops. Oh, that's very generous. Yeah. You know,
I just figured it'd be nice. And, uh, and then I get Europe, you get Asia. It's simple deal.
Let me, let me marinate on it. I'll talk to my board of board of generals. I have fortunate.
I unfortunately have some bad news to everybody over in North America. Listen, there was a mistake.
Our alliance was very short-lived. So we've got, I I'm about to potentially have eight troops up
here and I'm about to come all the way through North America and I would like to be, uh, talked
down by the way. Uh, please don't do that. I, what if you didn't, uh, the only reason our alliance
ended was because I thought that your character model was Ludwig. Cause I thought he looked the
most like Ludwig. That's fair. That's not, that's hurtful to me is I don't think it's fair.
Are you just fortifying no tax? I don't know. I'm trying to wow. Holy shit. Made a strong enemy
today. You took Australia. I told you that before the call started, I talked, I typed a DM in
discord. Hey dude, I don't really know what I'm doing to like, can I have Australia? And you're
like, yeah, that's cool, bro. And then you just took it. So like, I'm going to attack. I thought
Africa would be good enough for you. I saw, I'm sorry. I thought, I thought that would be good
enough. I didn't think you also needed Australia. Clearly you have some British roots here. Never,
never satisfied. Huh? Didn't you pee on food earlier? I peed and then eat food. Someone did
say you peed on my food earlier and I was confused why you would do that. There's a lot of people
really confused right now. All right, Charlie, you're going for America. Oh, you got seven. Oh
damn. You might be able to clean the whole continent up. Yeah. It's looking good for me.
I think you can move south and eliminate Connors troops and I'll eliminate Jerma in Greenland for
you. Don't do that. Well, you, you, you can say you, I'm going to try to, you can't say it's
guaranteed. We hold strong here in the Western United States. No, this is where I do my best
work. I'm very patriotic over there. This is a perky 50, 50 chance to go. I feel good about my
odds here. 50, 50 baby. Oh, so why did I like lose? And I was like three against one. Like I lost
repeatedly with three against one, but he didn't, he, he didn't lose once. Yeah. He's kind of crazy
with it. So it's always better to fortify your troops at entry points, which there's a lot of
in the U S but it's mostly Greenland and you don't have to worry about that. Cause I'm taking care
of it. I can only, oh, I see it's only adjacent ones. Yeah. Yeah, that's right. Okay. I'm going
to roll the dice. Ludwig. It's not how it works. There we go. All right, Connor, I'll figure this
out. Don't count me out. Connor. Wouldn't it make more sense to get the south first? You just got
to trust me here. What a shitty leader this is. I'll make it alive with you. Like, what am I in
the fucking fourth grade? Like you can't, yeah. I don't know why, uh, I keep doing the thing where
I put my hand out and when you go to shake it, I like put my hand up and put it over my hair.
I don't know why I keep doing this to you. It's all right. It happens. What is Earl? I'm taking
Earl. Uh, I can only move people there apparently. Oh wait, what I wanted to do. You got to break up
Australia. That's just, just free to troops every time. Okay. You're sitting with Africa
and you're saying I like, I have a smaller continent. There's like five borders here on
Africa. You have one that can be attacked. When I tell you I am sitting on an infantry,
cavalry and artillery, I mean it with the utmost sincerity. Oh, all right. Let's,
oh, I didn't get the fortify. I see. I see. Now I get it. Let's do this.
Guys, we might need to, uh, I need to unite here, uh, because look at, look at this is kind of
getting a little ridiculous. Don't you think? Yeah, it's getting a little scary. I mean, he's,
he's coming in here. Greenland. Yeah. Yeah. Not worried about him though. Not worried about him.
He's, he's coming for you, Charlie. Like this is not, he, oh yeah, he is slanderous. Charlie,
when I am attacking Alaska, I do it with the absolute plan of leaving it for you. All right.
I'm not even, I'm not even interested anymore. Okay. Fuck. Yeah. Uh, and I'm just going to
fortify some troops right over. Maybe here's good. It's a good section. I think it is. And
I insist you get the rest of America here, Charlie. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think that's the play.
Can you have your men just stand down? I could do it next turn. Not this turn. Okay. Hey, Ludwig.
There's no one French. We never surrender. It's our thing. Well, where are all your troops though?
Oh shit. Tell them German. Where'd they, where'd they go? Thanks. The recent pretty thin there.
Looking pretty thin. I am looking a little thin, but guess what? I'm not going to let you sit here
with 11 troops sitting here on the coast. It's not going to happen. You thought I was going to,
no, they're, they're tourists. We're just passing through the Mediterranean.
That's a threat. Oh, it very much should be taken that way. Uh, the troops in India,
there's more of a pacifist nation that happened to have nukes or you understand, uh,
fellas. He, he's trying to just amass like 30 troops in Europe so then he can just go out
and just get everybody. This is his plan. I resent this. I took, I got, I got in the way there.
That's what happened. Charlie. I would throw some troops, take down any, any of my ports.
They're all for you. You want Greenland or Alaska and the Southern border seems to be the most
attack and liar. He's a liar. I'm taking the Southern border here. Um, who do I want to
fight though? He's been like a bully and like a bad guy. I'm an owl. I'm moving my troops out.
Yeah, no. Yeah. He's given me an, a, we've already formed the Alliance. I think maybe,
uh, let me just make some moves over here. I'm kind of just being like a annoying notification
on Connor's phone at this point, but you could get the area in the top, right? That where I am
because then you'd have the border that connects to the U S. How do I? Oh, you're right. You're
right. The one that connects to Alaska. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's a good place. All right. Now
just hang out and hold on a lot. You get, I think five each turn, right? Yeah. America's juice. I
think it's one of the biggest outside of Asia, which is impossible to hold. Well, canner,
canner, a lot of troops in Europe, canner. Oh my God. I could literally. Oh, are you considering
the whole time was joke? Like, like I've been, I know pinging you out a lot of times, but like
I've sent you a request. I got this guys. I got a big plan here. I'd recommend. Okay. Fair enough.
Do you want a recommendation here? Oh, not going for New Zealand. Wait, did you a little too late?
And I like, I like this guys. Oh no, not Perth though. Huh? Leave Perth alone. How do I go back?
Uh, you can't unless you're fortify. Oh, they're coming. Charlie. Fortify. Uh, how do I do this?
The turns are short. Where do I want to go? Yeah. Well, they're 120 seconds. I don't want
to make it because yeah. Yeah. We're just slow. I mean, I, it's pretty thin though, right? I could
like just kind of get 10 troops instantly. If I wanted, I could go through Europe. Let's do,
let's do a play here. I could go down here. Uh huh. Like through here. Oh, two troops. Uh huh.
Two more. This is so vulnerable though. Like I can't just leave witnessing the plan here.
It's all right. It's all right. Okay. Well now you're in a lot of trouble because you,
that plan now you attacked. We're by the way, uh, Connor and I are working together.
So strong troops down there, Connor. Yeah. They're really energized after we did Argentina.
Those are the Argentinians that they moved over there. Okay. That's right. It's right. Next turn.
We're going to go sicko mode. Me and Charlie are going to go crazy. Yeah. That's when we're
going to get wild. Charlie, check the bottom left to make sure those cards, you might have a,
yeah, I might have a little something, something to the tank, you know, something to some really
take out someone else. Let's go. Holy shit. Okay. I'm getting this back. First of all,
you know what? I now respect you for that. Honestly, I got it as more of a motivation for
you than anything. I could see that. And by the way, you could request an Alliance if you wanted
to. I wouldn't mind. Cause I feel like South America is an enemy of both of us. I'm going to
need a confirmation on that, by the way. We're like, I mean, like I'm just still going. I haven't
seen a notification on my screen yet. Notification is sent. Notification is sent. Avoid Iceland.
Okay. Let me, let me think. Oh, okay. Um, I will accept this Alliance. If you can do the first
one sentence of the four kids, uh, one piece intro, the original intro, the four kids version.
And I have to sing it. You have to sing it. Just the first, just the first part. I'll,
that's all I'm looking for. I promise. There was a man named Joel Goldie Roger,
who was the king of pirates. He was wealthy beyond your wildest dreams.
That's it. These were his final. That's enough. No, no Alliance. What do you mean?
That's abuse of power. It's abuse of power. I was, I love it. I'm sorry. Honestly,
I was looking for a yoyo yoyo, but yeah, I didn't get it. That's what the first line then.
I didn't get what I wanted. It's like the seventh line, like the seventh. I would've
guy-o-yai-o'd like all day chat. I would've been one of the biggest guy-o-yai-o'ers. Charlie,
it's your turn. You're, you're, I'm thinking, I'm thinking he actually did the intro.
The, the, the, all right. I might have to give him another chance. Give it up, give it up.
What are you heading? He's not attacking anybody. He's been like a nice guy.
Consolidation. I like that. You could move the three and the four in Europe, or you could move
the two in America to add to the one, to the five, four, I mean. So it's five? Yeah. Like the,
the Montreal Mandy's to the California Gary's. Why does it go back? Wait, how do I make it at
five? I can't move them down. Really? Yeah. Well, that's not, well. That's not bad. So,
I mean, you guys with the more than three cards, uh, doesn't the amount of troops go up
each time somebody's not aggressive. It's fixed. Oh, okay. It's fixed. Connor. It seems like you're
adding a lot of troops around me. Yeah, I am. Ganner. Why? Ganner knew Argentinians are pissed,
man. I told you. I'm surprised that the guy with the guy from the Yonkis Blinky gift would have a
Twitch channel. Some of more because we defended our homeland. They're just really upset. There's
a, that's the one that goes, I've seen it. Consider this. That's right. Wow. Wow. Now you're just
fighting a fight. We're just going all over. I'm actually kind of getting scared of Connor.
You've made a grave mistake today. This might be where I turn. This is the heel turn on Connor. I
think I'm figuring out how to play this game. Um, yeah. Game of Thrones. Connor here. Should I do
this or should I wait? Let's do it. Let's do it. Only six. I thought it was 10. No, I, I'm holding
those other 10. Oh, okay. I see for like a later arrangement of sorts. Oh, there's a lot of troop
movement down there. Easy win. Easy win. They're fighting hard. You've pissed them off. They're
quite upset. What is going on? You're getting destroyed. That was quite the war. All right.
Well, all right, man. Well fought. Okay. I should have. You should have what? I, uh, I'm talking
about, um, thank you for the members. Thank you for the prime. You don't have that. Whoa. Not cool.
Whoa. Wait, that's my ally. Oh, wait a minute. I want to rethink your allies here. Whoa.
A bit blood hungry. Hey, hey, hey, hey. I've misclicked. You've misclicked three territories.
I decide I need new glasses. I think that's the problem. Yeah. But you really need glasses
if you think you're going to beat me in Greenland or Iceland. Okay. Um, I'm just trying to, uh,
Connor, sorry. What happened was I forgot to tell you, I was going to send you, uh, you know,
documents about it that we both signed, um, about how I was going to come through Europe.
I just did the, uh, the FedEx must have not. I got it there in time. Oh, okay. Yeah. I mean,
the people would have like appreciated like a little warning. Yeah. Kind of feels to me,
Connor, from like an outsider's perspective, who's totally unbiased in a journalist in degree
and nature that he was attacking you and lying. I mean, uh, that would be pretty crazy. Yeah.
Okay. Honestly, look at the border that you and I have here in, um, South America and Africa.
I could have just gone, why would I could have gone that way and broke up your points and stuff.
I just was trying to claim the territory here. I don't understand it. Connor, you come through
Asia. I, that's all right. I'll let you, uh, that's fine with me. Oh, okay. Really? Yeah.
Then why did you refortify India to, to the middle East? I will Western us. Let's calm down.
I would know. Don't bring them all over. Oh, Charlie. No. All the alliances are gone. It seems
Charlie brought them all over. I would fortify and bring them back. Yeah. I have no, I have
absolutely no defense against that by the way. 10. No, no, no, no, no. Oh yeah. This is the dream.
He caught me red fucking handed and I like just didn't talk. So we moving on. I win that. What's
cool. That's right. It's not over. It's not over. Oh, that's a slaughter. Keep going. All right.
One more. You're kind of, you're losing every round. There we go. I secret strat is you break
into their first border so they don't get their bonus. That's bigger. And I like that. Don't go
down there. Don't go down there. You're out of time. No. Oh, wait. Oh, I see. Oh no. Oh no, Charlie.
Since you didn't break in, he can't use the three troops that are just big chilling in Peru.
True. Actually kind of genius of you in a way. Oh God. Wow. That's big. Hmm. He's the reset
catfish. We're pulling for you by the way, over here in Australia. I appreciate the brothers
overseas. What is it? I don't know what I'm doing. You're losing. You're losing. Charlie,
you kind of had a bad draw too. You started like half in Canada, half in Asia. It was kind of a
hard draw. Yeah. I was saying I got a really bad start, but I've also never played the game. So I
didn't really do anything right either. I mean, what I'm witnessing is absolute soldiers. Yeah.
These are warriors here with a pure heart. Fighting the tyranny of oppression. Thanks.
Um, no. What a mistake. I look over at the camera sometimes and I'm just like,
I think the Grinch I'm going to do here. Oh, you're going to attack the Argentinians again.
Yes. Yeah. I bet that will come back to bite you. They're going to piss them off. You're going to
cross the ocean here. Oh, now they're, now they're living. This is very bad play. You're barely
going to hold the territory. There's going to be like insurrections everywhere. That's what I say
to them. I want to talk about bad plays. Check this out. Occupy the whole thing. Check this out.
Germany eats pants. That's not us. Come on. Nope. Not going to happen. You see what's right next
to you though. Do you see the big one? Oh, that's right there. That's about to just just steam roll
all the way through Europe here. I don't, I think that may have been a mistake. No, you're, you're
dumb. Oh, I could not have been a better car. There's no way we just got that card.
There's no way we just got that car. Oh guys. I just checked my car. Did you guys see this
card that I got? Okay. You got one card total. You guys see this card that I'm holding?
This card is insane. Oh my God. I want to know we hold strong in Portugal.
We hold strong in the UK. Oh no, this whole thing's coming down, man. I'm sorry.
We don't budge from Iceland. Are you attacking Connor? Uh, no, don't attack that. That's like,
I didn't even know. I'm going to be honest. I had nuclear five guys up there. I just learned that.
I had not seen them the whole game. Okay. Well, I'm going to attack them because they're,
they're cool. I think. Okay. I'm not going to get the bonus if that exists though.
So we can like, we'll figure something out. I'll like move them. Okay. All right. Okay. That sounds
good to me. All right. We all miss click German. That's the thing. Greenland is, is North America,
right? Technically like it's where, where is it? It's in North America. It's not part of it.
Well, I'm going to make it so you can't fortify this. Cause I know you're going to turn cards
in and put like, I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that. Absolutely. What are you going to do?
So I'm going to go back here. Oh, I get the bonus. If I hold a continent and I'm going to make,
you have to have the really kind of hard and annoying decision of needing to potentially
go through Charlie to get over here, which you're not going to do that. Because you guys have an
Alliance, right? Made a big mistake. Huge history. History will remember your errors.
Hawaii would never attack the Western United States. Well, I think they're reclaiming it.
If you want to bail on America and go Asia, Charlie, I wouldn't blame you.
All right. Well, might as well just hit Japan cause fuck it. Cause your U S is looking thin and
there's, there's a lot of territories in Asia to win here. Asia is pretty spread out, pretty thin,
huh? And Europe and Africa. Oh shit. That's all me. I think I'll take care of the Southern
part of China. If you want to go for the Northern part right now. No, no, no, no, no. Yeah, no
fortifying. I think it's also good. Why can't I take, oh my God, why can't I take troops from
there and put them in Japan? Um, it should be able to leave just one wherever you want to,
if they're connected, that's weird. I just do not understand what's happening. It's called the new
Argentinians. I don't understand though, like what I'm looking at. Why am I losing? Cause you're
rolling dice. And if the dice number is lower, I thought it was higher though. Mine were higher
than those. And there's one like joker die that looks lower, but what is blitz? What does that
mean? People are saying use blitz. It's like an attack that's just happening right now rolls for
you automatically. I love it. And instead of don't understand what's happening right now. Oh, okay.
But it sends all your troops. So it can be devastating if you lose. Oh, okay. I see it's
just auto attacking. Yeah. Good job. Hey, we're holding up over there. Okay. All right. I just
need one good card. I don't know why Connor's head hunting me so hard in this one. I don't know. I
don't get how this works. I just got a clicking or whatever it lets me click on. Uh, I ran out of
time. I know exactly what he's going to do. He's going to try to come from, he's going to New
Zealand over. No, I know he's going to do that. I was trying to figure out how to like fortify it.
I couldn't, I was clicking on the wrong thing. I think my plan is a little deeper than you
might expect. Okay. What are we doing? You're leaving that. Don't do it. Don't do it. Come on.
You're not going to make it across. No, no, you're not going to make it across.
Hmm. Don't do it. Stop right here. Got it. This is perfect. Perfect. I told you not to
fuck with them. I'm falling apart. Yes. Oh, it's huge though. Oh, next turn. Next turn boys.
My God, he got, if I could, if I could have, okay. All right. Okay. The good, okay. We've got an idea
as well. Ludwig, you're actually in a lot of trouble right now. You made a big mistake.
Huge. I don't know. I don't think so. You don't know how high I can fly. I've seen that movie.
Hey Charlie, I'm going to let you have Asia if you just say Ludwig sucks. Oh my God. I can't,
I can't do that. You'll have, you'll have to just take Asia from me. I could never betray an ally.
You can just have it though. You're not, you're not going to continue. You're not going to,
it's a mistake to keep going. One more and it's over for you. Whoa. Geez. I'm, I'm just saying
Ludwig has almost nothing on the board at this point besides Australia down here. So I mean,
like somebody could literally just swoop in. I mean, like Charlie, I know you have an alliance
here, but from Japan, if you fortify that you've got a pretty good idea here. I think that's true.
Well, I'm in a good position strategically. I also control all the anime exports. That's true. We
have been long time partners in buying a lot of anime up for me. Okay. It's been bye bye bye.
The trade is heavily in your favor. I wouldn't get rid of me as a partner. Oh no, I completely
agree. It's been an invaluable partnership. Hey German. Yeah. Did this, this five guys up there
that would give you Europe. Can I move them to a, to Greenland? Absolutely. We said you're,
you're fucked. You're all ones. What is it? Look at everybody else though. Like I, I,
if I get to keep some of these, I'll get a lot of, I'll get a lot of current strongest nation.
Yep. I'm locking Japan down. There's actually a lot of ways you can go from Japan too. So you,
that's like a pretty central area. Yeah. It does get Australia, Asia, and us. Yeah. Noticing a lot
of green on this map fellas. We want to talk about that Connor. Uh, I mean, yeah, he's my ally. He's
like, cool. What if we make an ally ship? I'll consider my, my words. I feel like I don't think
so. I haven't even told you what my plan is. What's your plan? You just lost all your troops in that
fight. They're like, they just really, they just wanted to like show you. I felt like they were
pissed. Connor, leave me Alberta. No matter what. Oh, thank God. Connor, you gotta, you gotta ask
for his crunchy roll. Uh, login info. It's cruncher. Oh yeah. What's your country? Oh,
the price is too heavy. Devastating. Is it here on just Kyra? All right. Uh, this is going to be
tough for everyone with the record show. I tried dude's got five territories. Well, it's funny
because I was attacking you. So I feel good about that. Me and Connor are, yeah, he did that.
Imperialist of you. Is it, oh, is it my turn? Yeah. Oh yeah. And then go ahead and put them in
New Zealand. I dare you. I dare you to attack Argentina. I dare you. You want, you want to the
South East back dad or for two, two troops a turn. Okay. You can have it. Psych. Oh, okay. I just did
like a concerned face in my web. Gotcha. Gotcha. Oh, that's good for me. It's good for me. I can't
make it to Cape town. It's spreading myself too thin. Plus the more green around me, the worse
things go more money, more problems. You know what I mean? All right. Uh, Connor, I need to, I need
this. I need your, yeah. Take the one up there. The little one guy. I don't want to put too much.
Okay. I gotta hurry up. Yeah. I was giving you the one guy. No, no, no, no, no. What are you doing?
Times ticking here. Africa. Okay. Please. I don't, I don't want you just steam rolling in here.
The Falklands will never fall. You just gave them another fun. He's all of Europe and Africa.
How many, how many is that per turn? Um, it's, it's plus eight. He gets plus eight from that.
Oh my God. Oh my God. I'm looking at the troop output right now. Connor 18, me 22, Charlie 17,
Jerma 34. He's got as many as Charlie and Connor combined. How do, uh, how do you finish the game?
Uh, you don't, you own the world. Somebody has to win. Oh, Charlie. I understand now. I thought
there was like a turn thing. All it takes is, is yeah, this is where it starts. This is where it
starts to get kind of, this is where I come as a problem. Big man. I'll take care of South America.
Okay. I'm going to grab Alaska from you. Yeah, please, please. That's perfect. You got to go
quick though. You got to go quick. It's perfect. You're fine over here.
I am. What the use the blitz function. This is, this is, is this not blitz? You're doing
the individual dice. You got to go right. Oh, bring it back. Bring it back. Oh no. The time
Charlie, the time. I'm, I'm coming out. What the US time. I'm out. Fortify, fortify. You're good.
Just for the time. I'm out. Next turn. I don't understand what's happening. You could bring
him over to Asia. Honestly. It's not a bad idea. Ditch the US. Uh, too late. I got four troops.
You watch out. Oh no, he just uses cards. Yeah. I used the cards. Um, well then the scariest part
is Jeremiah's five cards. You should not be scared. That was the most terrifying thing you've ever said.
You should have heard your tone right there. Was it scary? Yeah. Oh, it's like a horror movie.
You're like, you should not be scared. You know, I've never won a game of risk in my whole life.
Really? Never. Cause the way you're playing Connor for a fool right now
makes me double check that. Where did you get that from? Are you kidding me?
You have him as your, as he gave you Falkland islands. He has no territory of two. It's been
the worst partnership in the history of partnerships. I've seen worse. Well, no, I, I, South America,
Connor's held South America for like the whole entire game. I haven't gone over there.
We've been trading stuff here with honor. Western us. All right. I have to make this move
for the betterment of my people. That's a little cringe. Everybody's cringing at you. Like all the
viewers actually it's kind of ridiculous. Yeah. Well, everybody's like looking at you funny right
now. They're not doing that. Okay. It's getting really weird looks. I mean, I don't feel like
that's the, I hope that's not the case. I just got to text my mom. Let's say Ludwig is cringe.
I feel like your mom was saying that. Send that message. I mean, she's not, she's not,
she's wrong. I mean, first of all, I, I think so. Happy Easter. Have a good Easter. I agree.
And then they're like, they're like tongue hanging out crazy. They like the face, right?
You don't use emojis like that with your mom. What you use the tongue out, crazy face emoji
in a casual conversation to your mom. It's kind of like a silly emoji. I feel like that one's fine.
It's like that. A ha ha X D. I've seen my mom use that emoji. You know, the one,
do I have to post it in chat? Jeremy, it's your turn. You said the emote before.
Hold on. I got, oh, you don't, that's you wasting time here. I just wanted to see it by the way.
I'm not fucking around. No, we win this fight. We win this fight. No, you don't.
Yes. They did pretty good there. Very well fought group.
For Jakarta fight blast.
Thanks for not breaking the Alliance, man. The people there appreciate it.
It was huge. It was huge. We can stomp Connor out of the Americas.
Yeah, that's the plan. But I've also got good strats. Oh, I love this Japan to all Mike,
the wrap around Alaska. Oh, the door reach around. We're gonna be all right. Hey,
oh, everything's fine. Are you assured me you assured me that you were going to be able to
handle North America? No, I said I'd be able to handle Argentina. And then that didn't work
very long. I said, actually, I said the Falklands. And to be fair, they're still there. They are.
They are actually still there. Oh, this is actually kind of bad. You left Mexico.
Wait, how do I go? Wait, I can't go back. No, you can only get the like when you were traveling
north, you had to have left troops in eastern US. Oh, what the fuck? It's OK. It's OK. I'll
sweep through. I'll sweep through. I'll finish the job. I'll finish the job. Chin up, King.
It was a great fight. My Argentinian troops will will will demolish him.
He will only have Asia as his frontier. I'm lucky. You got cards. All right. All right.
There we go. There we go. There we go. This really decides the how the game is going to play out
here. However this goes. It's an error. It's an error. Oh, an absolute wonder. Oh, yes. Oh,
that's bad. Oh, you shouldn't fight this honor. You shouldn't fight this.
Oh, what if like I did? I don't know. These are some rabid warriors out here.
I don't know what they're capable of. I don't know why I feel like you're eating with your
hands right now. Like you're eating like chicken with your hands. You get one giant turkey leg
that they serve at Disneyland. I just have it here. You're just like sitting there eating like
chicken wings. You got like barbecue sauce all over your hands. Is that is that accurate or
I'm not even holding the bone. That's the worst part. I'm just holding the meat part of it.
Um, Gemma, Gemma, Gemma, you have made several errors today. You're probably aware of that,
though. Someone said Ludwig is 100% a Disney adult. Not not a Disney adult. I just happened
to go to Disney a lot. Man. Whoa, chill. Oh, leave him alone, man. Charlie, I leave you the
rest of North America to take care of. All right. That was too far that you're going to go three
v three. No, you're not. That would be weird. That was too far. I don't even need to as a
thing about it. That was a little cringe is what people are saying. You check my phone.
Don't check your phone again. It's a mess from Dad. No, it's not. What do you say? I can't get
into my email. I need help getting back into my email account. I don't fucking know. But like,
okay, just regular. That's not bad. That's not bad. My dad said Ludwig is cringe. That's not
at the exact same time he happened to message you said coincidentally in the exact same minute
that German father takes a German coincidence. I mean, things happen. It's an awfully large
coincidence. You don't dare. All right. I'm here. You don't dare do this. German. There's a prime
Keebler. Hey, German. How about an alliance? Hey, okay. Hey, what's going on here? What is it?
What is it? Connor failed you in the southern front. I can hold South America and leave you
Africa. I will also heed Europe to you. I won't interrupt you. Leave me some don't believe his
lies. I'm not even gonna listen at all. I mean, this is just like the tone of your voice was like,
I'm doing I'm making this up. Yeah, I heard the tone of your voice was I'm making this up.
I will literally sing any song you want. If you don't go any further. I would actually take that
deal. That's firework, firework, firework right now.
All right. Thank you. Welcome. All right. I'm satisfied.
What is it? Do you have a pepe pains on YouTube? Oh, yeah, we got that. Yeah, I'm seeing mostly
feel strong. Man's over here, though. What do you bring it up? People are there's a lot of pepe
pains. Right, right, right, right. Next time he's gonna have to drink a glass of milk when he does
the two at the same time. Otherwise, I'm invading. Hey, Charlie, what about an alliance? Charlie,
you got to get rid of that five. Yeah, you could you could attack on both six fronts, though.
Like you could pepper him down with the Alberta troops. Finish him off with the with the Montreal
there. They'll stand strong. I'm going in. Oh, no, they're good. You win this. They're strong
boys. They're strong. That's us. Oh, really? I can't stand strong, Mexico. The only thing you
can do is leave nothing but Mexico. Honor, I'm gonna have to eat you. You're gonna have to what
I'm gonna have to eat you. I think I'm gonna have to eat you. You might have to, but I think
I'll be okay. I think so. It depends. It really depends what's going on here, because if somebody
kills you, they get your cards. Well, I don't have any good cards. I mean, look, if I if I consume you,
I might get a match and then I could take them both on. How are you even like handling this
negotiation? You said ooh to him eating you. Yeah. I mean, we lost the Falklands. We're kind of like
low morale. I mean, you could do if you get something to do in Asia here, maybe. But I'm afraid
that Charlie's gonna eat you and then you get Charlie's gonna get your cards. All right. That's
fair. What do you mean? This is for he's eating you and you're saying that's fair. Well, the Falkland,
we lost the Falklands, man. You lost his will to fight. This is Stockholm syndrome. You lost to
German and now you're saying it's fair that he eats you. I miss them. Japan, let's go. I hate you.
Honor, I'm gonna have to eat you. I don't like Japan, guys. All right, guys, I'm gonna fortify
here. Can I just like, can I like get like a boat and like move all of Asia to Mexico?
Just get everybody out somewhere. There's the boat card. I think you actually might be okay.
You actually might be okay. If you go down to like two territories though, Connor, I might have to
eat you. No, that's fair. Yes! All right, but you lost a lot. You lost a ton. I don't even want to
hear your words. The people of the southeast hate you, Ludwig, and you think you're a terrible leader.
You just killed like all of them. You know, nobody even in Australia fucking even watches
your stream. Like, they watch my stream. No, many Australians enjoy content. I just think it's
bullshit. They don't even have TikTok there. Okay, all right. This is so ugly. There's so many ways
I can get. I've got to go for this. If I can get this done, then I can get it done. I'm gonna try.
Yeah, there it goes. I've got to go for it. Nice. Oh, defend the Mexican border.
If you attack, I return. You're gonna attack anyways. Hang strong, Americans. I don't know
if I want to do this though. If you push America, that is my ally. Oh, I think I could get the game
now. When I kept fighting, I kept losing everybody. You kept just having one person in a whole area
and you'd have a huge area with one troop max. I thought people wouldn't feel threatened. They'd
be like, oh, there's just one guy there. Can I trust you to handle Greenland, Charlie? I don't
know if I can take Greenland just yet. I think I'm going to just need to grab Mexico first.
All right, grab Mexico and amass troops. I will distract Jerma. How are you going to do that?
You have some kind of plan. I trust the one guy there. Imagine this one dude beats six troops.
All right. Wow, he fought valiantly. Jesus. He did a good job. He died with honor. Oh, I have a
plan chat and it is, it's merciless actually. Honor, you have an opportunity to, here is,
here's the play. I'm going to tell you what the play is or do you want it back and forth here?
Let me play. If you go after Charlie right now and thin him out, I could eat him. That's true.
All right. I could go across North America, get those cards and I could get your cards too.
It's good. It's not good. His plan always involves killing you and you keep saying it's good.
That's diplomacy. We lost our will. You're like a robot. Hang strong Hawaii. Yeah, go team.
I'm just being real. Okay. If Connor had the territories that I have, I would be saying,
I'd be like, look, come get the cards from me and go on and our alliance can go on to victory.
It won't even give me an option to fortify. There's nothing to fortify. It's all a bunch
of one guy. Connor, it's been a pleasure playing with you. You're not going to knock me out this
turn. Everybody would be like, that's cringe Ludwig if you did that. Oh, that's a lot though.
28 guys. That's not cool. Don't do it. He's got to go. He's got to do all of this. He's
going to spread out. So you're going to know it's not going to happen. You got to like leave me
Hawaii. I don't, you never deserved Hawaii. You got to leave me like, uh, what is this?
You got to leave that one. You got this guys. All right. That was kind of cringe.
A lot of people are cringing. Wait, I believe the lime. Wait, I don't even have an avatar.
I thought the question mark was like mechanic. I don't even have a guy. It's your cards. I'll
send gas can of fun requests on my way out. Wait, it made me leave the game. Wait, it kicked you
out of the game. I think, I think you should be able to spectate now unless I probably just
clicked the wrong thing. I can just hear him on discord if you want. You guys ready for this one?
What's your big plan? My big plan is this. No, Charlie. Jesus Christ. I'm sorry, Charlie. I
have to go this way. Just about to save America. I'm really torn up about it,
Jerma. Oh God. Are you sub king? Even in death, he thinks a soldier is king. Oh, petty, petty.
It is. It's very petty, but I don't want you to get the bonus for this. Oh, grow up. Also Peru.
What is that for? What are you doing? Just to fuck with you. I regret that. Yes. Yes. We still have
a chance. I want to make sure I don't do this wrong. You, what if you defend this? I'd laugh
so hard. You might actually might come on boys for lovely lady liberty. Hey, can you give me like
500 subs? Expand upon that idea. It's like a joke. No, it doesn't sound great. I feel like after your
dad called me cringe too. I feel like no, he's like, he doesn't know what twitch is. He doesn't get it.
Jerma, you made a big mistake. I get to come back. Jerma, you made a big mistake. Wait, what happened?
What happened? What happened? What happened? What's going on? You ran out of time. What do you mean
run out of time? Where should I go? Where should I go? Charlie should fortify one area as much as
possible. Yep. And, and it shouldn't be, it should be an area. Leave, leave Western US. I'm going to
adopt that and I'm going to attack his 10 troop. You should try to attack his 11 if you can. If you
can't escape to South America, I will give you refuge there. Yeah. I think I'm just going to
head to South America. Head to South America. I'll protect you. All right. Thank you. Here I come.
Or you can fight 11 and 11. I'm flabbergasted right now. I don't, would this help you Ludd?
If I did 11 and 11. It would help me vanquish the rest of him. Yeah. Cause I'll take the 10 on.
I can't, it's impossible. I was winning. We stay in fight. All right. I'm not a bitch.
This is for you Ludd. We stay in fight. Our alliance. Okay. All right. Okay. All right.
It's not that bad. It's not that bad. It was a good fight. It's, it was, it, this is winnable.
Yeah. So now you just need to protect, uh, Mexico for me, which I will, which I will.
Mother fucker is going to, he's going to eat you, Charlie. And he's going to get all your cards.
No, he just, he's going to go up to the Western United States. He's going to,
he's going to strike you from there. I can't believe I ran out of time.
That was some very sad art. We go here. Ooh. Why is there a hard stone timer on risk? It takes a
minute to figure out where you're going to go. First of all, I agree. We're getting, we're getting
roped, our stone roped in the game. Game would have looked a lot different if I had more time.
Fuck. All right. Charlie. Just leave me Mexico. It's all I need. That's such, I fucking have that
win. I've win that. That's so fucking stupid. Charlie, if I let you live, he's going to kill you
and win the game. You don't know that. You don't know that Ludd. Charlie. I don't have any cards
by the way. I use them on my last turn. I will not kill you. I will not kill you.
I've been in this spot, Charlie. I will do everything. You had value. I have nothing for
you. I have nothing for you. I will protect you. I'm going to come through here and I will not,
I promise I will not consume that one area that you have. All I need is Mexico. I did,
I didn't, I didn't kill you, Charlie. I left you alive as you can see.
Thank you. Charlie, I'm leaving you alive. Oh, thank you.
Like so desperately. Okay. I have this timer. What's your plan, wise guy? You are not leaving
him alive. You're lying. Holy shit. You lie. You're not allowed to lie in war.
It's one of the war crimes. The major one. Yeah. That's a Geneva convention.
Charlie's going to kill you. He's going to kill you. No, he's not. He wouldn't.
So he's be lining towards you with heat, but he's going to stop. It's like, it's like when
Godzilla was destroying the city, but then they all held hands and he's like, all right,
I'm done here. No, you're not thinking about man of my word. Oh my God. Thank you.
We in New Mexico, in Mexico. Thank you. Might as well be New Mexico at this point.
It's been shifted around so much. All right. So I just want to make sure that we're aware that I,
I left you alive. I could have taken your cards. That's right. That's right. I won't forget. Well,
let's not forget about who left you alive in the first place. I, I border surrounding you.
We've had an alliance for years now. I know we've been tight for a long time.
He was whining about that though. He was like, Oh, but Charlie, like, I don't know. He's going
to go up there next term. That was what he said. You remember that? I do remember that.
We're just happy existing out here. Honestly, we're just happy. We're just happy to be here.
By the way, if you attack, uh, Charlie here, Ludwig, that's a declaration of war
across everywhere else for me. Is that right? It's only two of the,
we'd be the only two remaining. Of course it would be, we'd be declaring war on each other.
Ludwig, you play this game like a nerd. You just got to put everybody in one spot.
I don't think that's what you got to do necessarily. How cool guys play it.
Are you cool guys? Yeah. Yeah, that's fair. Yeah. Thanks for completing the gift con or
five steps challenge super. Really? No, you don't. Okay. Whoa. Holy shit.
Wait, how did they move that way? They, they can go across any territories
that connect. And so they went all the way across through, uh, Madagascar or, uh, New Zealand.
So, but I couldn't move people on a boat from the North of Asia to Mexico. Okay. Sure. That's fine.
No, you're not chairman. You wouldn't. I'm trying. I'm thinking you're thinking
about killing a Mexican army. No, he's not. That's not going across his mind. He's looking at,
he's, he's looking at going for you. I went through Hawaii. I'm just concerned.
He's thinking about six, six in Hawaii. I don't think he's thinking about that.
Well, I'm concerned about Hawaii because you have a, you can just walk right in.
Exactly. Hawaii is a big threat. Hawaii is pretty threatening.
Why are you? Are you going to be kidding me? Are you kidding me? I lost seven troops and you lost two.
Unbelievable. Okay. Don't worry. We in Mexico won't forget that.
Charlie, I want, what I want you to do is I want you to attack me. So you get a card,
but then you might get a turn in the next round and then you might be able to clean this up
because he's going to kill me next turn. I think. Okay. All right. Come up through North America.
All right. I'll, I'll swing through. What are you doing? No, no, no. I'm not. I don't want to.
Oh my God. That was scary. Oh my God. Mexico was on high alert right there.
People of Mexico are freaking out. All right. I'm coming. So I, I, what do you,
what do you need me to take from you? The Western United States,
whatever you can get here to be able to fortify. Cause he's going to come for both of us right now.
I'm not coming for Charlie. He's making it in us against. I'm not against you, Charlie. I've done
nothing to protect you since day one. So what do I need to get a card? You need to get one
area. It doesn't matter what area, any area at all. Winning it gives you a question.
Okay. I'm just going to take this one for the card then. And I'm going to
bring all of my boys back to Mexico. I can't do that. I see. Okay. Now you can't,
if you end the attack and then you do fortify, I think. Right. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Nice.
Big strat, big strat. Then you've got an opportunity after this.
Little guy's cheat engine and I'm watching his screen. He's like seeing different numbers.
It's the overlay. Show your task manager right now. 36. Oh boy. This is bad.
The Congo will hold strong. It's just got Asia. Asia is what? Eight.
As we can't let Lederich win. He's like, not cool guys.
Mexico will be the last place standing. Mark my words.
That's my dream. My dream is that I don't get all the areas. I get
all of them except for Mexico. A perfect world.
And then you have a car turn in and you just wipe out everything, Charlie.
I do. I did get a card out of that. I wonder if you have it.
Ludwig, are you trying to kill me this turn? What? No.
South Africa hold. You're going to do it. I think you're going to kill me this turn.
Sure, ma. He's going to be okay.
You got that five down south that it's a little too strong at the moment, but your time will come.
Wipe me out. Leave me that one. Yeah. Leave me the one.
You have a few here. Well, let him give a bunch of ones on the map.
Looks really stupid. That was noble.
I'm going to try to block him from coming this way. All right.
Do you have a turn in? I missed it by one, but don't we have heart.
We have heart here. I'm okay.
If you can kill me, you probably should because you can take a, he can take a South America.
Oh my God. I can take South America and it's my, it's the only thing I can do here.
Oh my God. I'm abandoning Mexico. I'm coming.
It's in the back for Charlie.
No, I can't. I can't.
Charlie, you attack me here and it's done.
But you're going to kill me anyway. You don't really, you don't care about Mexico.
But if you come for me, I'm coming for you.
I have no choice. I'm coming. I'm fleeing.
It's not just going to be the Mexicans. It is.
It'll be the Western Californians, the Nova Scotians.
I'm going to get everyone, Charlie.
That's okay. That's okay.
I'm the psycho though, right? From the beginning. Remember I was the one.
I drew Exodia.
30 of them.
I'm telling you, I'm going to be the last guy here over in Canada with a stick in my hand.
Final words, Charlie?
Mexico won't fall.
Let's find out.
Oh, no, no one's even like trying to fight.
Just wait, watch Mexico. It's going to go from 18 to 10.
It's going to be such a noble battle.
Let's go Mexico.
Hey, they got their one. They did their part.
It's been a pleasure, Charlie.
We don't know it's over yet.
Oh, the Western. No.
That's so many cards.
Yeah, this is bad.
Oh, please.
That's cringe.
Oh, what the fuck?
It just sent me back to the main menu.
Yeah, that happened to me too.
A little bit streaming in a distant.
I can just pull up this stream.
I won't be able to put this on screen.
Oh, you want to do it?
You're going to leave that?
Just you're going to leave Canada there?
That's cringe, Ludwig.
Give you one turn.
All right.
Like the four of us are just going to run at you with like pots and pans and sticks and rocks.
Here we go.
A bunch of polar bears.
Let's go.
Ow.
Well, we got nowhere to go.
GG.
People saying this is so humiliating.
No, it's not.
This is exactly why I invited all three of them to play.
At least that was a gross test of results.
I can't believe I ran out of time.
GG.
Yeah, the running out of time was it, right?
You definitely win if you don't.
I don't know if I would have won.
If you betray Charlie and kill him, you win for sure.
I was hoping.
You don't really win with that.
Your friend invites everybody to play their favorite game and he just kicks everybody's ass.
And then like everybody's like,
we're around, but he's having a great time.
And so we're just happy to be here.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's kind of what I'm going for.
Do you guys want to do another one?
That's just the US.
I'm down.
Yes, just the US.
Yeah, it's just the US.
Why is this clickering?
It breaks it up by states though.
Oh, okay.
And I'll increase our turn timer is actually 90 seconds to 120.
Do you want to try manual placement for this one?
Let's do it for the United States one.
That should shouldn't be that.
Yeah.
Is progressive card bonus better?
You were mentioning that that is what you usually play.
Games end a lot quicker because it goes from like three to like six all the way up to 30.
I think.
Are you making a new game?
Yeah.
Should I do fog of war?
It seems kind of interesting.
Oh, that work.
It limits a visibility of territories to only the ones around you.
So you don't know who owns what else.
That sounds awesome.
I will do progressive fog of war on and manual placement.
We're going to get crazy here.
Oh, I got to fix my steam real quick.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, please do.
Please make sure that should work.
I'm going to put the code in our group chat.
Very good.
I just spent five tokens to join.
Jeremy, you don't really read your chat and listen to them a lot, right?
It depends.
Yeah, I like that.
I do sometimes.
Why?
Oh, okay.
Well, I just open it up and I see people saying like, oh, I'm instantly go Ludwig,
you know, but like passes in the past.
No, I mean, I were saying that.
It's a new game.
Guys, let's keep the letter gate to minimum, guys.
He's a cool guy.
You farming bat chests or actual sympathy here?
I don't know.
Guy.
No, stop saying that about Ludwig.
I love Ludwig.
I'm saying that.
I can't repeat that.
I didn't leak the code stuff.
I hecking love Ludwig.
I can hear the bat chest.
I don't even need to.
You don't gotta say it at that point.
Ludwig, can you do the gift Connor 500 subs challenge?
I don't.
It's like a trend.
I guess I don't know how it works.
Like a trend.
A lot of people are doing it.
Who are like some other people like just for influence?
Like Mr. Beast.
I did it.
You like Mr. B.
Jerma did it.
Mr. Beast did it.
And you talk Mr. Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry.
Let's not.
Psycho did it.
Psycho, but you did this.
I did it already.
You did it.
How does the challenge work?
You just give Connor 500 subs to Connerage fans.
That's it.
You can also like do like the gift Connor 5 subs challenge.
Like if you like don't have that much money, you just like be a part of something.
You know what?
Sign me up.
Gift Connor 5.
I mean, if like it depends on like your yearly like net income though.
Like if you like you gave one sub.
Challenge accepted, Connor.
Did you see it?
One sub is not a challenge.
Five dollars.
Give Connor five dollars challenge.
Everybody's saying Ludwig's cringe.
Okay.
That doesn't feel nice after.
Usually you say, hey, thanks for the gift itself.
Ludwig.
I really appreciate it.
I owe my chat like 150 community subs.
I kept my all my cards, all my PayPal.
Everything gets declined from Twitch.
Now.
I don't know why.
Yeah, they get it.
It does happen to me a lot.
Grumpy Grim did the five sub challenge.
Well, Grumpy Grim is more money than you, Ludwig.
I had to get a new credit card just to do that.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Because it kept getting declined.
And so I have like I got a there's a specific it's actually kind of insane,
but there's a specific bank that gives you a credit limit based off your followers.
Very dystopian.
Oh, yeah.
That's my bank.
It's a little bit give me the biggest.
Yeah, because I had a thousand dollar credit limit before them.
Wait, hold on.
Does that mean that you have like how much how many millions of followers do you have?
Wow.
Like, oh, like like one on Twitter.
You don't get it's not like a dollar a follower.
Oh, shit.
I was going to say what?
No, it's just the credit limit is based off those numbers.
They have some algorithm.
Oh, so they increase it if you have a more substantial of a following.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, they did that for me.
And like they gave me like a credit limit way over like anything that I'd ever need.
Like, it was just ridiculous.
And then I definitely don't get anywhere near that.
So now they text me like weekly.
They're like, you were bumping up your limit today.
Like, go for it.
Have at it.
Maybe have some fun.
And I would never do it.
What is your trail?
I'm going to stop streaming.
Maybe a little help, too.
This happened with Elden Ring, too.
I don't I don't know what's going on.
It's just steam games like are flickering.
Yeah.
No, that's an understatement.
Like it's a full strobe.
Like you can't see it on stream.
It's just on my monitor.
And is it just the game or like, could you play through OBS?
Like I could play through the OBS, but it's just the game.
I guess you can't play through OBS because you have to click on the game.
I didn't think about that.
Oh, true.
You guys like Elden Ring PVP stuff?
Oh, yeah.
You messaged me about that, Jeremy.
I still have to set that up.
Yeah, because I have confirmed.
I think it could work.
I think Elden Ring PVP always looks great.
You know who really wanted to do that actually was Saikuno.
Really?
You really wanted to do it because they did something somewhat similar to you.
Because I don't know.
Do you know the streamer me young?
Yeah, she played Elden Ring like you play Pokemon where she would throw out her
her Pokemon Saikuno and toast and they would fight the boss and she would run away.
Yeah, that's like exactly the kind of thing that I want to do.
I want to do a night where we get a bunch of streamers that pick champions from their
community and we throw them out.
They have to fight in a PVP setting and we get up to maybe three to five champions from
the community and we are essentially trialed by combating each other.
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
I like that idea.
That's cool.
I think the only thing that's...
I guess, no, it should be easy enough.
I was going to say making sure you summon the right person,
but you can just read the name and confirm it.
You have to confirm it beforehand, right?
Where it gets weird is so you can summon two gold cooperators and one invader.
So if we had more than four or five streamers, it would...
There'd have to be multiple games going on because if only four people can be in a game,
the two people that are going against each other, so like two streamers,
one streamer would summon as a gold sign the other streamer and then summon that streamer's
person as another gold sign and then they would have to summon an invader that was on their team.
It's very, very confusing, but I think it would work.
Yeah, it sounds harder to do with many people.
Like if you had a group of eight doing it or something.
Yeah.
Because only two streamers could get their fighters in at once.
I feel like the setup will be the most...
Maybe it's possible.
Or one gold, two red.
The setup would be a little weird, but it would theoretically function correctly.
I've got at least two or three people in mind that I know would be great competitors.
You have like warriors already?
Oh, yeah.
I'll have to run my own event to get my own warriors.
Yeah, I was going to say whoever wanted to do it, you'd have to have at least,
you know, try to get whatever the number we decide, like three to five champions.
So they'd probably have to be people that...
Because I don't...
I don't know, what do you draw the line of,
oh, I'm going to get like an Elden Ring PvP guy to come in and just wipe the floor.
I think everyone should understand and keep it fun, you know?
Yeah.
A barf drinker absolutely is one of them.
I've got to try.
Honestly, after that stream ended, I was like, hey, do we know who that is?
Because I really want them on my team.
Connor, you think you can do this challenge?
Could you eat this in 90 minutes for $3,500?
Challenge destroyed.
What does that look like?
A couple large fries, four Big Macs, was that 20 nuggets?
40 nuggets, I think.
40 nuggets and four Cokes.
Yeah, three medium Cokes.
90 minutes?
Probably not, honestly.
I don't think I can do that.
Yeah, we're trying to track down the real barf drinker.
It's going to be like, all right, it's going to be hard.
Because now, now, like somebody just said,
a thousand of you just went to Ranalla and changed your name to barf drinker.
We'll figure it out.
If we do it, it's just a fun idea.
We'll see.
How I never spend near the limit.
My last text from them was the beginning of the year.
They said we're starting off the year with a challenge.
They said spend $5,000 by next weekend to unlock a surprise.
And I never responded.
Wait, so what is your credit limit with them?
What?
Say it again.
How high is your credit limit high with them?
Like much higher than the other stuff?
Yeah.
My credit limit, I have two credit cards.
For my credit card, it's $1,000.
And for this credit card, it's $100,000.
Give me one second.
I'll be right back.
Sarian, this is really tough.
You're getting big, man.
All right.
Give me one second.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's with the social follower credit limit bank.
I would be kind of scared of that in a way.
$100,000?
To fear.
If you need to purchase a $20,000 statue of Jackie Chan, perhaps.
That's true.
Just put it on the card.
That's crazy.
But I can only use it for business stuff.
I can't like take my card to Trader Joe's.
$100,000 credit limit at Trader Joe's.
Like, yeah, I guess I'll take every tiki masala you have in the store.
It's like a Mr. Beast title.
That is kind of like a Mr. Beast title.
How long do you think you could go without eating food, Jerma?
Until I die?
No, no, honest.
Like without dying.
Like right now, if it was like a challenge,
you had to go as long as you possibly could before you cracked.
How long do you think that would go?
Probably 24 hours.
And then you'd crack?
I'd crack after a day.
I'd crack it like probably 22 to 24 hours.
I think so.
Ludwig, I'm telling you, my hunger strikeathon is going to break the internet, man.
People are going to be tuning in from all over.
I need to get Connor a thousand subs so he eats.
And then like I do it.
I think it's a bad idea.
People would be like, this guy's got to eat food and they'd be subbing.
But don't you think people might say,
Connor, you are exploiting your viewers by threatening to go starve yourself to death.
That's why they're giving it.
It's not a threat.
It's going to happen.
It's a plot.
If I don't get the sub goal, I'm just not going to eat.
That's worse.
I would say that's worse.
I can't get his head stuck in the french fry box.
If I don't get these subs, I'm just not going to eat.
Wait, get off.
Okay, sorry.
Yeah, no, I'm not going to eat food unless I get the sub goal.
How many people are just going to go to that and just be like,
I'm just kind of out of here.
Well, the hope is that people would show up and be on the same team as me.
If they band together and don't pay, would you really not eat for days?
Hold on.
I don't need to just see bumper.
I could not go more than one day.
12 hours would be hard.
More than 24 hours would be impossible, I think.
This is a great picture bumper, by the way.
He was like jumping around the table trying to get this thing off.
Would you get into the french fries?
Yeah.
Jerm, I mention it because Mr. Beast called me today
and he wants to do a video where he doesn't eat for an extended period,
but like a month's worth of time.
A month in a row of not eating.
Yeah, yeah.
I think you die in seven days.
Like, don't you die in like four days?
I think I thought you could go like a month.
Yeah, I thought it was like three days for water.
30 for food.
That's water.
Okay, yeah, water is seven days.
But I think it's like also you probably need a bit of training for 30 days.
Like, I don't think you.
What about like vitamins or nutrients?
No, any nutrients at all?
Like, I imagine it's no calories,
but probably like, you know, a Flintstones gummy vitamin.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if I would do that.
So if you guys want to find out how long it can go,
tune into the hunger strikeathon after like a month
when the sub goal gets to like 10k for like food and eating.
It's based on your body fat.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's what Charlie was saying.
You probably feel awful after.
I don't know.
I can't even imagine doing that for more than even a couple of days.
I feel like they're terrible.
Yeah, he wanted to do it with people.
So he asked me, but I don't think I'd make it more than a week.
But I think like a week I could do.
What about like organ damage?
Oh, yeah.
No, that's part of it.
I think although my aunt did this where she didn't eat for.
I think it was like three days.
She fasted, which I don't think is that uncommon.
And and it's cool because it resets your palate.
And then you get a baby's palate.
She hated coffee and alcohol and smoking, even though she did all those before.
And she just liked what she did as a kid.
Like fasting is, you know, something people do.
But like a month straight of not eating anything full month.
Yeah, three to seven days, I think, isn't that rare in the fasting world, right?
I know.
I know absolutely nothing about fasting.
I just know that that you cannot survive more than like a month without food.
My mom used to do 48 hours every year or so.
What point does I don't even I'm trying to even think what would even happen
after like three weeks straight.
You'd have to have some form of nutrients.
You have to.
Yeah, I think you have to have like maybe you do.
You know what?
I don't know if it's those IV fluid drips.
We're just going to do like an IV bag every few days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like the ones influencers use after crazy parties.
At what point is it just sad?
You're just watching Mr. Beast like in pain.
He's like, oh, guys, I got the IV today.
I think I think what they keep it light by having Carl Jacobs come in
with a big old like McDonald's order.
Then he eats in front of him.
And then they go, oh, Carl, oh, Carl, thanks.
I don't know about all that.
I don't know if I would not be able to do that.
I was like, oh, even just like doing the IV bag for nutrients thing.
I kind of would rather just eat like a banana.
Well, yeah, obviously.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Here we're going to do an IV.
We're going to do like just like a vitamin and nutrient IV.
I can I just have like a coconut water instead.
Like I think that's I would rather have that.
Can I just have food with nutrition?
Boys, I don't want to hold you up any longer.
You can just play without me.
I cannot fix this.
I've tried literally fucking everything.
It is just not not working.
Uh, all right.
You want to try restarting or you just want to call it?
Uh, I can try restart.
I don't see why that would fix it, but I can give it a try.
You'll turn it off and turn it on again.
We can chill for a little bit.
So it's all good.
Run it.
I linked you guys a type racer if you guys want to get a little crazy here.
Not very good at this.
Charlie, you could also just play through OBS for now.
Well, I'd still need to click into the game.
Oh, that's true.
Uh, we can try that.
I can try just playing through OBS.
Let me try one last thing with the refresh rate, even though I know that won't fix it.
The dude that just keeps spamming.
Guy in my chat says he he fasts two weeks every three months and you have to drink water,
take vitamins and have salt and it only works if you have stored fat.
I got enough medical problems, man.
I don't I don't think I'd want to like cause another one somehow.
Who am I in with?
Is this Connor?
It's me.
All right, Connor.
You quick?
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
Actually, no, I'm not quick.
Yes, that's also I would also want to be careful of like we need doctors,
like medical staff kind of nutritionist be like kind of really, really advising that
like I would be scared to do that personally.
You need professionals.
No doctor would say to do that.
I love the background menu music.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've never I've never fasted or anything.
Well, okay, that's not necessarily true.
I have done a small fast because I was trying to see and by small, I mean like not even
a full day, like one day because back when I was having all the medical problems in like
my chest and back and shit, it was like I'm going to just eliminate literally everything
and just drink fucking water and see what happens.
And I started to slowly introduce foods and stuff to see if it was something I was eating,
something that was causing a problem like that.
Right.
But never I never did it for any other reason.
That was literally like not even 24 hours.
It was like to start an elimination diet, essentially to slowly put in foods and spices
and is it a food additive?
Is it like gluten?
I was trying to figure that out.
Ah, Gandhi.
All right.
I'm fucking back.
Good to go.
I'm ready.
Oh, put it up.
All right.
So this is America.
It's going to start out a little differently because we're going to be placing our troops.
So just try to make it pretty speedy here because this can take a long time if not.
But once it's your turn, you could just place one trip.
I'm ready.
Okay.
So what's the card thing that's different?
It's progressive.
I don't know, Jeremy.
Do you know how you might be able to explain it better?
So if you turn your cards in, it's the first person to turn it in and gets the worst one
because it's only going to be like three troops.
Oh, so it always gets higher.
Every time somebody turns it in, it goes a little bit higher.
Uh, okay.
I will claim Ohio.
I'll take Florida.
Okay.
I was going to take Georgia, but if Charlie's going to take Florida, I'll take Texas.
Oh, it's fog of war.
So I can't see.
We shouldn't be saying this out loud.
I forgot about this.
Oh, you can't see.
That was the whole point of fog of war.
I'm just going to use this like a places that I always want to like have wanted to travel to.
That sounds fun.
So we placed 30.
So we have to do 30 of these turns, right?
Yes.
Are there only 30 states?
No, there should be all 50 here, no?
No, but we have 30 troops.
I think you're going to fortify after we pick enough.
Yeah.
So you don't stack them, I believe.
You always have to pick new territories.
Oh, has nobody clicked that?
That's weird.
I'm closing my eyes and just picking territories at random.
I'm insulted that they've like combined some states.
Oh, interesting.
I can't even see who got the territory.
Oh, it's a secret.
It is a secret.
Secret secrets are no fun.
New Hampshire's not too small.
It's an important state.
I have a plan.
Don't worry.
Will they know that this is a plan?
There is a plan.
Oh, quick turns.
Hi.
And how does this work?
Because I feel like there's no way that some of you have not clicked on this.
I have no idea.
I'm curious what you're referencing, yeah.
We'll see soon.
I feel like if there's a question mark when I clicked, then it's probably like someone took it, right?
Yeah.
I'm just shocked that this is shocking.
What version of the US map is this?
You should be able to see the black outlines, and those are the territories in this one.
Yeah, what's going on over here in this big hole?
I think it's just like the Rocky Mountains.
Is that just the mountains?
I think they did it so like Colorado wouldn't be in such a shit spot because it'd be connected
by like seven states or something.
Oh, okay.
They marked up like the whole spot where the Unabomber was hiding too.
Yeah, that too.
Don't go there.
That works for me.
I'm gonna have a shit state at the end.
All right, all right.
This is where I think we fortify.
It is fortify phase, yeah.
I feel like this is gonna be very, very hard for whoever decided to go in the middle.
No, why would that be?
You're surrounded at all times.
Is this me?
A very good spot, I think.
This is red.
You have 19 troops you have to place.
Is it making you do all of them at once?
Charlie, are you placing things or no?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm placing them.
Okay, okay.
It's making you do all of them?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, we go in order.
Oh my god.
I think it's just you right now.
I think you have to do all of them.
Okay.
This is the presidential race.
Okay, there you go.
Sorry.
They can take everything that's not this.
Feels like he was saying the south there.
Electoral map.
We'll see who becomes president.
It's all Jeb.
I see.
Somebody said DOS died for this?
DOS did not die for this because after this we're playing DOS.
I'm doing it tonight.
All right, all right.
Oh my jeez.
He hates Europe.
Dude, in like two or three hours it's gonna be EU stream anyways.
Okay, all right.
Now we see a bit of the map here.
Why?
Why do we see so much of the map?
What do you mean?
It started.
How come some of these are fog of ward though?
You can only see adjacent areas.
Oh, okay, I get it, I get it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, chill man.
I mean it's very, it's obvious what I have to do here.
Let's chill out man.
Let's not go anywhere.
Jeremy, you're green?
Yeah, I don't think there are any alliances here.
I think this is the only one.
We got one per place.
Fresh game.
It's a brand new game.
This is a new day.
New day, new dawn, new battles.
Who's right?
Oh, you're gonna regret that.
I like listening because I can't see anything.
It was actually way worse as a stream experience but funnier.
Oh, you guys can't see anything?
I have not seen a thing happen.
I was adjacent to it so I could see it.
Don't do it.
Okay.
A little fortification happening.
I love that.
There is.
Charlie, I've sent you an alliance.
Have you seen it?
Oh, I see it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, all right.
Well, hey, Gascan.
Alliances, but it's just one country.
When I'm allied, I get to see all the new map.
Oh, shit.
Let's go.
Yeah, Gascan, you're gonna want to be my friend here, man.
You want to see the map.
That's actually pretty advantageous.
Did you just take Boston?
No.
That's fucking bullshit, dude.
All right, kid.
Listen, that's fucking stupid.
All right, fucking listen, kid.
I'll see you outside any donkeys anytime.
Oh, shut the fuck up.
You bring a pack of cigarettes and I'll fucking see you there.
You're frightening it away.
Oh, good expansion.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I kind of feel like I can just go here.
Mm hmm.
By the way, if you see the X-Men, the graph bar on the left,
they're toggles.
Whoa.
And you can click them for more info,
like how many points every section gets you.
Oh, okay.
Like New England only gets you one point here.
It's kind of shit.
But the best one's the Heartland.
Oh, how is it?
Why is Nevada in the Rocky Mountains?
Oh, chill, guys.
No, it has mountains.
Is it in the real world?
What is it in the real world?
It's Southwest, considered, right?
I guess it is, right?
You know, like near Arizona.
We have an alliance, right, Lud?
Oh, it's one of the strongest alliances that have ever been formed.
Okay, then yeah, I'm gonna.
I haven't broken it off.
I have no dreams of it.
All right.
All right, so yeah, I would say we should really take the Heartland here.
Yeah, that's a good call.
You've just made a powerful enemy with Nebraska.
No, they're chill.
They like us.
We're like boys.
We were one of the finest governments they ever elected.
Actually, our office was very well liked.
Jeremy, I'm gonna let you go across Oklahoma and Arkansas, I think.
I think the plan is you should probably take that.
And, you know, let's take it to DMC.
How did you just steamroll Louisiana like that?
It was four to five and you only lost one troop.
That's the power of Texas.
What the fuck?
You only did only lose one that was fucked up.
It's a really interesting election map.
It was a weird year.
This is an interesting presidential year.
Just let me keep the Heartland.
Yeah, this is big.
This is either God.
This is a very bad move or it's a very good move.
It depends on how the how Arkansas does here.
Whoa, it looks like we're just rolling over.
Jesus Christ.
That was decent.
You went even.
That was pretty good.
Yeah, I wouldn't encroach on my territory here, Jerma.
Um, yeah, that's probably gonna do.
There's just a king in the Midwest.
What the heck?
Yeah, it's established that.
How did you get 15?
What?
I have three territories.
That's cringe.
That's everything that's cringe.
You're still on that?
Yep.
They're all like getting that immediately when you said that you have that much territory.
Cringe.
All right.
This is good for me.
I need to win this.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
All right.
That's all I want to do here actually.
Shit.
Just like keep Arkansas fortified.
I think like they've been through a lot.
I think it would be fruits me to kill Oklahoma.
You can probably take this whole region here.
Oh, I'm not trying to spread too thin though.
Whoa, don't do it a lot of way.
I leave the south for you, Charlie.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll come through the south.
I'm just Union Jack here.
I don't believe in manifest destiny.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I'm coming down with it.
Won't be two.
You win this.
I think you just fortify.
I don't think you.
I don't know.
Louisiana, they get wild down there.
Get wild.
They get a little wacky.
I might.
Do your special move and purchase.
Go team.
No, Texas is a little too scary.
How do I call off an attack?
I had a zero percent chance of winning.
So zero.
Yeah, it was actually zero.
It was 2v2 though, right?
Wouldn't know.
It was 1v2.
I said everybody wants to be your fucking enemy.
Nasty with it.
Oh, the misery.
Texas, they don't forget.
Oh, wow.
I didn't realize.
Is that Alabama on the left, right?
You can only be attacked from Louisiana.
That's actually pretty good for you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you actually can.
I don't really know what I do here.
Hey, I'll cede to you the Midwest.
Or I guess not the Midwest.
The heartland, I should say.
Yeah, I'd like to keep the heartland.
I'm just kind of happy there.
So you can send those six around to wrangle up.
I freely cede both Nebraska and Arkansas.
We appreciate that a lot.
What state is this, Chad?
Is this even a real state?
This gets weird though, real quick,
because Connor, I have to go through you to attack anybody.
Well, you can go through Oklahoma and Arkansas.
I can, but if you claim that, then you get.
No, I don't want it, though.
No, I don't get anybody because I need New Mexico and Arizona, too.
Well, then let me try to surround you from the left and bottom.
So then they can only come at you from one side.
Yeah, I gave you Oklahoma and Arkansas last time.
I didn't care for this.
It's a little concerning down here.
That's all.
Yeah, I got you.
I'm going to end my attack here, I think.
Everybody's in good spirits.
I got to move troops down here.
Everybody's pals, the unions together.
All right, I got to come through here.
It's all right.
Hi, bumper.
I'm just trying to figure out what the...
This is going to get ugly.
This is actually really ugly already.
Scary situation.
We're just in a tough spot.
We don't have any of the east.
Oof, oof, big reinforcements there.
Oh my God.
Yeah, Ludwig was cheating.
Okay, let's do this.
Actually, no, let's do...
You know what?
I think I do like Arkansas.
Let's do an even fight.
Ludwig, you should give up a whole territory to make it interesting.
Let's do an even fight here, Jerma.
Okay.
You're coming into a...
Oh, Jesus.
Big, very big.
Just because I'm bitter, I've taken Minnesota.
What the fuck?
What did I do?
I'm bitter.
It was bitterness.
What were you bitter about?
Losing against Jerma.
I'm not Jerma.
It's like pick on someone your own size.
Because I lost to Jerma, so I was like, okay, I need a win now.
I was going to try to fight him again.
I'm really scared of...
Charlie, you're just steam rolling through the whole south here.
Yeah, I didn't get any good cards.
I like when he says, yeah, as he adds troops.
I'm coming through Texas.
These guys fucked me in the ass earlier.
I want revenge.
They'll hold us strong.
Oh, baby.
They didn't at all.
They folded.
All right.
This is bad.
We're in a tough spot.
Yeah, we are.
It might be in our best interest to not work with each other
and instead get different allies and break them up.
You might have to turn around and get rid of me for my cards.
Depends on what he does here.
Okay, I think...
Oh, wait a minute.
Hey, Charlie or Ludwig, any of you guys want to be my pal
instead of like one or the other?
If you get Arizona, you get the whole territory.
Yeah, yeah, I think I'm going to have to do that.
Let's play it safe.
I'm going to grab that.
Shit.
Oh, a lot of ones on the west coast, huh?
Thankfully, it's so kind of isolated
that you have to go through everybody to get over here.
Yeah, you do have to stretch then.
Uh-oh, what's my play here?
All right.
I don't know.
The heartland is just not much of a heartland at this point.
What does he got up in Michigan and this area?
Minnesota is three.
It looks like...
I can't even see Michigan.
Illinois has got 11 right there.
I think it's Illinois.
Can you...
Yeah, it's Illinois.
Oh, you're not...
There's no border there.
You can't go...
You'd have to go up.
You got to go through Minnesota.
He's probably got nothing in this area.
This whole area up here with Indiana, no way.
He's got nine in Wisconsin, actually.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's bad.
Just like, you know, it's not really cool.
It's because we're big Rogers fans over here.
I thought you were doing a thing where you knew we couldn't see.
So you just...
Oh, look, here's...
I got 11 troops.
I got 20 troops right here.
And then you got all ones.
I think what's better is you can't see and then you go in
and there's a shit ton of troops.
And you want to like alliance?
Just leave me the heartland, you know?
It sounds like it's just an alliance.
Then it'd just be stomping out Germa.
Well, I think Germa's all right.
Honestly, you guys can make whatever alliances you want,
but keep in mind, you're going to have to attack each other
to get over here.
So you're going to have to figure that out.
I think Charlie goes by south and I go by north.
Yeah, that might be the play.
The cards are about to become a big factor.
Maybe, like, don't.
Especially because they're progressive.
Maybe, like, don't do that.
Okay, Germa, I think I'm just going to have to
step into your territory a little bit.
Excuse me?
I think I'm going to have to step into your territory a little bit.
I'm a little scared.
I kind of want to, like, spread out a little bit.
Connor, what do you think about the Rocky Mountains?
You've always been, like, a Rocky Mountain guy to me.
I've never been there, but I do get that vibe, yeah.
You're there now.
Is it nice?
A lot of people have said that about me.
Lud, would you give me Arkansas over there
if I helped you collapse in on, like, the Nebraska, Minnesota area?
I'll do you one better.
I'll move out of Arkansas.
Oh, that's even better.
Fuck yeah.
Guys, you got to leave me alone.
Hey, well, Germa, I still consider this alliance on.
Like, I just needed to move.
Yeah, that's true.
It's true.
I'm just scared.
I'll see what I can do down here.
Let's go.
Oh, Jesus.
Germa, no, don't do this.
What the fuck?
Why do none of my troops fight?
Fuck.
Thank God.
Finally, someone with some balls here.
Thanks, New Mexico.
That second push was bold.
They didn't do anything.
I mean, Charlie and I are not prosperous for a civil war.
We're very allied right now.
Yeah, no, this is tight.
Germa, you could accept the request ticket if you want to see where this thing's off.
Right.
It's back on.
We're friends.
We're friends again.
Canter.
You're beginning 15 every round.
This is over.
Honestly, we should all just collaborate to get rid of Ludwig because he's got 50 troops.
Charlie, Charlie, consider it.
Charlie, I think you should actually consider it.
Ludwig is literally stomping everybody because he's three territories.
Yeah, that's true.
But I can't survive on my own.
I have to suckle his bosom.
This is what happened last game, though.
And then, like, you can survive, though, because we'll be on your side.
I don't know.
He's scary.
This guy is very strong part of the country.
Charlie, you wouldn't betray me, right?
No, I wouldn't.
I couldn't.
What happens when it's just down to you two and he's got 50 troops on the board and you've got Texas?
Cringe.
He's going to come for you.
He's going to end it.
Now he has the heartland, too, which is worth plus five.
This is bad.
Then it's just all a matter of, you know, we did our best down here in the south.
At least I still have, wow, I have Wyoming and Montana.
You sounded so excited about that.
I think that's like the smallest segment of the population.
I have like eight guys, like eight people.
You just reacted the same way as if you had found in the fridge you're really hungry
and it's like taco leftovers from six days ago.
That's all that I have left.
And it's just like, yeah, I like got those tacos that I didn't eat.
I got to be excited about something in the world.
All right.
We're doing great.
I have three.
You can live another day if you just go east.
I was living.
My hope was right that I was going to get three cards and I just turned them in.
But the problem is none of my cards match.
So now I have three cards and three soldiers.
So you have the card turning was three.
I don't have anything to use.
But there we go.
Sure.
Let me just take Kansas back.
Let's take that.
March across the nevermind.
I used to like I used to like Ludwig.
But for some reason, this game makes me hate him.
The burning.
Yes, I agree.
You're reading a chat message.
You just got a new hater.
Apparently from a lot of people been signing up.
Hey, wait, is this a chat message or are you saying that's chat message?
That is a chat message.
Somebody's very upset about this.
Hey, they're up in arms all over.
Actually.
All right.
I feel like I just made good alliances in great war tactics.
So they used to like Ludwig.
Now I only like a truck.
Yeah.
Now I feel that moon.
Honestly, we've got to do something.
We've got to do something.
Yeah.
We got to make a big move.
We've got to make a move.
We have to.
That's all right.
It's good.
I'm just trying to break him up.
That's it.
That's all I'm trying to do.
Yeah.
I might as well miss soda.
Maybe that's just one.
Right.
Don't fight that.
Holy shit.
Everybody has to go after Ludwig.
Otherwise, it's over for everybody.
Carly, you got to switch up.
I see what's on his board, by the way.
If I did try, I couldn't win.
No one can win anyways.
I'm playing for second boys.
I have a mast of an army on Massachusetts.
Yeah.
He put the troops in deep.
If I see one teabag, they're losing their shit.
If you go for whatever state that is, Kansas and Colorado,
we're going to burn all the farmland.
You're going to get like nothing out of it.
You're going to burn the crops.
Everything's gone.
It's going to be unusable.
Whatever.
I'm fine over here.
Like 45% of the whole US economy is over here in California anyways.
I'm fine.
If I was my own country, I'd be the seventh richest country in the world.
It is you're fortifying right now.
You fortified something over there.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was my turn.
There's not much for us to fortify.
No, there's not much.
Sorry about that.
Carly, neither of us are attacking you because we know how this ends, right?
You're the only hope.
I don't think you guys understand.
There's just, we're running them thin as much as we can.
Hey, leave Montana.
Make it interesting.
Wait, actually leave Montana though.
It'd be like cringe if you took it.
Because then I'm out of the game.
That was cringe.
I think this is a little manifest destiny here.
Sorry, I'm offline.
The alliance is over.
That's what it just said.
Holy shit.
This is insane.
I want to see this board because I'm very curious.
It's insane.
I can see it now.
You're German.
I made an alliance with you.
Do you accept that you can see?
You got 13 over in that?
Yeah, that.
Okay.
Yeah.
I made that like analogy of like your friend
who invites you over just to kick your ass in the game earlier.
You got to let me spend one more.
All right.
I'll leave one.
You don't want to fuck with this out.
I'll tell you right now.
We get rowdy down here.
You left Germany.
You didn't leave me.
Charlie, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Yeah, he did leave me and he didn't leave you.
I did leave him.
But just as an insurance policy.
What a fucked up weird election map.
Yeah, I was like the one independent party
that spent every cent that I own in one state.
I think I can win here.
I went to every single county in the entire state
and shook every single person's hand
to make sure that I got this one mistake.
This is so stupid.
You made a big mistake leaving Florida alive.
All right.
All right, gentlemen.
What you got?
I'm fucking coming.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Oh, Florida Gambit.
Hey, hey, come get me.
Come kill me.
Come kill me and take my cards.
I'm coming.
I'm working my way over.
That's actually genius.
You get those cards.
You get my cards.
You'll have to go through New Mexico.
Oh, I can't attack Arkansas from here.
OK.
Louisiana it is.
I hope you get a turn in.
We're coming in.
I'm coming.
Hold strong, New Mexico.
We go Oklahoma and then go to Colorado, I think.
No, no, you just go.
I can make it.
Turn in.
Come on.
You go around.
We're strong.
Hold strong, German army.
We're squirming.
Yes.
There it is.
Turn in.
OK.
All right.
It was a mutual agreement.
Oh, shit.
I can't watch anymore.
No, you have to click spectate on the bottom left.
Yep.
Are you good?
There's no reason to push any.
Move one guy.
I wish I got you.
I wish I got you to turn in.
Oh, put him back.
What the fuck?
What?
Oh, God.
That's fine.
He's got 20.
What?
New Mexico is pretty strong.
Oh, my God.
I'm pushing you all the way back to Florida.
No, not if New Mexico has anything to say about it.
I'm doing the thing Connor said.
Stand strong.
The first game, I was hype on it.
This one, I'm sad.
You won't get through Florida this easily.
All right.
I'll give you one more turn.
Yeah, I was going to say, you got to do the like the gentleman rules,
which is like you guys are playing baseball game with a friend.
And it's like, oh, hey, just throw the ball like into the outfield one time.
I got to go on first base and then you try to score like running all the way home.
Do you guys ever do that?
I didn't do that.
But I never play baseball with my friends ever.
Yeah, I understand what you're saying, at least.
But I also like a lot of friends that play baseball in like a group, right?
I mean, yeah, throw the ball into the outfield.
And then like, I'm going to run around and go home.
Yeah.
Like, just commit an error.
Oh, wait, it's my turn.
Oh, this is sad.
You're age is showing.
Go Florida.
All right.
This is our last stand.
Come on.
It's coming for Georgia.
I'm on first base.
We're down by two runs.
Guy at the plate is up.
He like bunts.
Roll the ball in the outfield.
Give us a chance.
Come on, gentleman's rules.
I have a 0% win on all fronts.
Stats have been wrong before.
Yep.
I'm coming.
Wait a second.
Oh my God.
The last guy.
There it is.
All right, that Fortify there.
I just put the strongest soldier we had there.
Master Chief's in Florida.
61.
I think me and Charlie's alliance is a little too strong at the start. I didn't get shit out of the South
I think the game there's so much strategy to literally picking where you're going
Like at the start. Yeah, no, no people were just kind of we're just clicking
There was like there was like a real method to it that we should probably figure out
It's a little bit of a strategy where you want your want your boys to be fog of war makes it harder to
Yeah, I actually think that's why I was able to run throughs because I had an alliance with Charlie and I could see all the
Map. Mm-hmm cuz our alliance missing gas can't have friend request
You guys don't want to play a third one. Do you okay for whatever? I'm down if we like have like a setting
Maybe do better settings on that. There is a map called
Castle and it's just one castle and you own different sections of the castle cool
Interesting or this one's also kind of interesting
E by land. All right, we'll do one free by so wait, it was manual placement good or bad
It's okay. I mean auto makes it go faster. Yeah, it was definitely faster
Okay, let's do auto was fog of war good. I know strong opinion for me
Thanks a prime Zach. I'll keep it off
and then
Progressive card bonus. I'll keep on. All right code is in chat. We'll make this the finale
That's good playing MDOS games. I thought my fucking computer blue-screened like that
This thing just took up the whole screen and this one line of text. I was like my computer
I was about to say sorry. I gotta go do one second. All right, there's the code. I want to show anybody
Where do I use it?
Were you where you have every time? No, I can't let you personally hold on. I invited you person
What do I go to profile? Oh, here it is. Come on. Hold on. No, don't leave. What the heck did not mean to leave the game
I'm sorry. Yeah, can you send me another one? Okay, uh
The invite. Yeah, it says already sense
Hold on I can join and five tokens there. All right, let's go. I bought an alien guy. All right
All right, totally random. It's just a
Byland is a bunch of islands bunch of islands
Island. Yeah. Yeah, like the streamer. Is it like a
Collaboration I don't think so, but that'd be crazy
Oh my little alien guy was so cool
Okay, so it's Ludwig and then Charlie with the same colors. That's good. I'm glad that's been yeah the whole time
Yeah, and then Connor and then German. There's just like normal rules or what's weird. The only thing that's weird is it is
weird islands and
Progressive cards. Yeah, I don't know this map. Yeah, I don't either to be honest
But I do think I want
This I gotta go pee real quick. I'll be right back. My turns like three turns anyways. Yeah, you got time
Oh, I want to control barbecue. I also realized we were playing with kind of a cringe rule
It wasn't true random dice rolls. Yeah, you know, no
That was great
I knew those dice weren't random. I knew something was in them
They were they were weighted a little trouble a foot big man. It's you
Yeah, I'm thinking I'm trying to figure out the best plan of attack for me here
Wait, the names of these lands are all literally like Spanish youtubers. Wait, are they? Yeah
Dude, I think this might just be a map. He by actually made ours like Ludwig land
I want that did he buy get his own map in this game chat. I feel like I'm already losing
Did he earn like say?
Wow, yeah, that's what that's what balanced dice remove or random dice remove I should say I am back
Technically one soldier could be an army of a hundred. Why would they call any by land make sense?
Did you get something like the steam workshop? No, I just had it. I don't know. I've never played it before
It was just in my maps. I didn't have to like download it. I think he just did a partnership with the game
Oh, that's pretty Connor saying all the all the the the map names are just different youtubers all the different islands
Well, they are yeah different Spanish youtubers. Are they apparently it's like barbecue if you hit the the
Graph in the top on the left bar, and then you hit the globe icon. It'll show you them all
Oh, okay. I was gonna say there's like a
Industrial pier tech plant industrial cargo is like those interesting names like no
Yeah, he goes by block a go team. Don't spread yourself too thin Connor fortify. Yeah
I have no idea where I'm gonna go here. It is an interesting map. Mmm
Oh, they're all
Way, it's not what I meant to do at all. All right, you have actually a great start at the top that two four four
Do I don't know if you missed this but the the dice are true random now through random
Yeah before it was balanced. It was the saddest fucking thing. I threw four against one and lost. Oh god
Yeah, okay. Well, I mean I guess I could just
Blue has no idea what they're doing
My god the restaurants up there from me are very strong, you know, you don't
Chefs, I think it is actually game
I think true random you don't want to do blitz because you could just know is your entire army in one fell click
Oh my god
Lost like everybody. I think I
I just lost you did not lose the game
You have look at you got the guy in the bottom aisle with the three three two because you could do the same thing in
Return as well, right? That's yeah, that's true. Oh, that's so demoralizing
Those are the strongest chefs in the seven seas don't feel bad
Yeah, it's like some one-piece chef. Well, let's see. All right. Well, it could work in the reverse then couldn't it?
My boys are too strong in this one
Well, I'm going to end there because I'm very concerned about having no. Oh god. Okay, good game. All right
We're going over here
Hey, Charlie
Yeah, listen, I'm thinking an alliance. All right. I like I think red is cool
I'm trying to take on during the bottom, right? Mm-hmm. Maybe how is he already got plus nine
everybody Ludwig just every time just
Gets in an area and just starts building massive stacks so early
We got to get rid of this now and I'm gonna bring it up to the board
Blue you're blue
Okay, guys
We should we should get rid of Ludwig because he's already building like I'm also open to that
I'm open to like three versus one. Yeah, we can you can
Hey, I'm very much open to that. Hey relax everybody. Come on. Hey, come on
It's been an overwhelming cry out from the audience today that yellow has been cringe
Did you I think you are the audience who's been saying that we cannot let him get to?
Almost three four wins in a row. No way. I agree. It would be impressive though. You'd let's kill them
You'd almost be like wow great job Ludwig. It would be impressive
But it's been a pleasure watching you succeed so so much. Yeah, no
See one of these where those dice
Which is happy let's go on
What happened there? You didn't lose any troops on that fight
Alien dice Ludwig doesn't a alien us that I thought you're gonna give like a new avatar
Yeah, alien guys look weird they're hard to differentiate they have like they have weights in them
Okay, let's how much is the that prison area up there giving you a turn
So if you click on the left
Bars, and then you click the globe. It'll show you. Oh, okay. There's it's plus four. Yeah, it's the smallest on the map
Although I don't think the map is very balanced like honors should be giving way more than six
I'm gonna take the bottom left here, but I get five is crazy after that
I think we
Yeah, they're all you so I'm not gonna do blitz. Yeah, I think blitz is a mistake. I was I was normal rolling
Yes, he's gonna go like two one. Well. I mean it's always better to do three because you just have better. Wow, I'm going blitz
I mean you immediately won so fair enough perfect win again
And we will not attack each other Charlie you still need the little boat up there to get the bonus for that area
The the one I'm on yeah the five and the one on the left so my one at the bottom there
Oh, what? Oh, yeah, that's not good
Yeah
If you so Charlie if you click on the three the bar graph on the left and then you click the globe
And make it yellow a little it'll show you the outline of everything. Oh
Okay, I see unlucky unlucky didn't know that. Thanks a bit skip. What is your turn Ludwig? Okay?
I know exactly what you're doing. Wait. What do you think I'm doing? Talk to me. You're going
I mean, you're gonna you're gonna take it by right right? Yeah, very obviously
And then you're gonna go from there. You're gonna I think you're gonna go up
I don't think you're gonna go down this to way too much going on down here
You're gonna go up you're gonna wrap around try to go to the top, right?
You can try to secure the top, right and then you'll have any flanks. Can I be honest with you Jerma?
Hmm, you sound like a crazy person right now. I I am happy and content with just my two aisles
You buy an elo one, that's it for me. He's going top, right?
So we need to do everything in our power to prevent that from happening
Slander is almost
Back. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Jesus. That's right. What just happened. No, I was just taking the bottom, right?
Ludwig, how do you have your hand into every one of these things?
I
Look at the draw. I guess I don't know to claim the territories
You have all these all the boats your presence on every boat. I do have a lot of boat presence
Yeah, I like to say mobile. I guess I'm kind of a pirate at heart
I'm like you ever see the show one piece one of my favorite shows. I think it's why yeah
It's a great show you caught up on that. There's no way right?
Oh, I've seen like three episodes total 15 years ago. That's all you need and you gave it the rating great show
Yeah, German trusting you in top, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah, everybody's friends. Everybody's pals. Yeah, I would say you should probably take it
Yeah, maybe at some point
Charlie I'm gonna leave that. There's no revenue there alone
Okay, is it you guys are all talking amongst each other and kind of like it will listen
We're gonna have to start planning ahead here. Yeah, this is getting scary. It's ugly. What do you what do you do?
You want it to you with me Jerma?
Real really interesting. Yeah, like you mean it. I don't know if that's super beneficial though
I don't think it's beneficial for you. All right now, Drew. No, no, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
No, I'm sticking German German German German German. No, I'm sorry
We need to get him out of here and then we see what's left. You're not attacking Ibai
Are you um, I'm considering some my options that would be foolish. Well, I mean you got I've got a time limit here
So talk to me. What are your terms don't attack you by I don't attack any other territory except for you by are you gonna attack?
Charlie or or Connor? No, we're gonna attack us. I'm only taking the one
Think about it makes sense your one piece on the boat take everything I have over there by the way to and
Worriedly be I don't even care about those lawyers. I hate him
It's one of those can't live with him can't live without him say you can take those two honestly
I think I don't want to I'm kind of afraid because that's you you're spread out it too thin. Yeah
No, I think that's there. What do we get out of there? He'll get hold my man to stand out
He'll get it he'll get it by but that's all right
Forget about somebody troops. It's ridiculous. Hmm. I'm trying to think of a strategy we could pull off here
I'm just in the process Charlie Charlie. I have an idea. What's the idea hit me? This involves all of us
Okay, Charlie on the top there you have five, right? Yeah
Yeah, you could move one of those up to that port at the top left. That is one of Jerma's
Oh, yeah, and then you can go all the way around and fight little bit at the back
Yeah, it's gonna be a 4v4 or at least we at least we have like a border there
Oh that boy. Yeah, that is a that's a massive
Vulnerability right there. You're not attacking. No, I wouldn't dream of it. He's got so much man. He's got so much already
I might go for that that risky maneuver the old back door reach around
Guys hey
You know coming in. Oh my god
Charlie you know how I left you in the bottom left here. I have 11 guys. I didn't even touch you
Yeah, but you that's cuz you knew how strong the hearts were of those sailors. I'm coming in
the prison holds
Scary the prison junction holds
He's got the 11 right there that he can move up, but he cannot attack you with that 11 right now
You would have to fortify first don't get block C. No, come on
You might just want to leave him there and just see how he plays it
Yeah, I don't think there's any reason to take this whole thing and stay low what color I am green currently
Yeah, should I even bother getting block A and B?
I think you consider block a or B. I think I think you stay right there just because
You go down to the right you yeah, I can't take block C. I know that for sure
I just I was wondering if it was worth for block a and B
But probably not all right if he's gonna fortify up here hit he'll do it
So even if you take one of them, he'll do the other one
Yeah, true true true, and I know he can hear us right now, but you know what who cares hey you guys talking about one games
He's gonna attack from if I I don't I think he he's trying to get this boat
He wants to be able to have this attack front from the boat. That's where his reserves are gone. It is we win these
That's big. That was big. Yeah, we needed that we needed that really bad
Okay
We need this. That's big. No, it's not we lost. Oh, that's
That's all right. No, there's an opportunity cuz I I can put some troops up there and I could get rid of it
You a you're getting rid of my loading dock. Yeah, I mean come on. It's a loading dock these men need jobs
That's a vulnerability that gives you an opportunity to come in you could put you could put 15 troops there and just wipe us all
Right their families term. Oh, all right. Yeah. Well Charlie's an ally. Yeah, I'm gonna
You're just a little something, you know, all right
Should I I gotta at least put one here to get rid of the loading dock. I win this fight
I want you to know you're not winning. It won't be one against my loading dock soldiers
You're not and then I've got to get rid of them
I gotta load up some these are blue-collar men. You think a processing plant workers beating me start
Let's do the one. I know I need to do first here
Good nice good win. Very good. Very good. All right, we're out. Oh my god
I just hope we I just say, you know, I'm optimistic. Oh man, that's huge. I
Love that. That's huge. It's early. You won't like fortify up there though. You don't even want it
Can I even bring can I bring anybody up there I can yeah, you can bring those boys I need to get
We can't just let him steamroll this
We're you awfully dumb of Ludwig to like even try to take the top right because he's to worry about the top left
And the bottom left. Yeah, we've got him on his heels. Yeah, Charlie
You might be able to take if I next turn if I push from where oh from the three
If I push from the restaurant, oh, yeah, that'd be huge
That's uh, well now he's afraid that's how we know. He's terrified. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. They were in his head
That's what we wanted him to do. Watch these soldiers hold for us at the prison junction for my city. Oh
Boys, please god. Yes. Oh good fight. Hey, they're trying. They're trying. He lost a little bit there
He did he lost a little casualty. I did take a casualty
I
Hear that like the yellow nation like that. They don't really like want to fight like they're like tired of war
I don't want to like go back over there about my people. Yeah
Oh my god, you just got absolutely annihilated by my filter
It was a
92 percent chance. Yeah, we don't believe in numbers over here in Filter Bay. It's huge
actually huge and
92 percent chance. Yeah, it means nothing to us drain. I'm just I'm just here. I'm just coming in
I'm just coming in. How about that? How about that? Oh, wow, how about that baby? Oh, baby? This might be it for me boys. I
Really needed to stop them out there. That's tough. That's tough. Maybe I should just kept you loving. Okay
I don't love that. Hey, come on my three hold though. Imagine
Imagine block see they won't do it. How do I fight with any motivation? How do I know they're all conscripts?
You attack first and then you place troops after okay
No, yeah. All right. Do we want to take a bye from him? What's worth more?
advice worth more
Okay, but be crazy is you get damage on both so then he has no bonus. Just question me out
Oh, I sent all my troops. That's okay. That's okay. There's question me out boys. Oh
It's over for me
We've learned that we're working together now sounds like you're in the middle of a really great stretch
My backside pushed in by you three not to stress you out
You guys seem betray someone now. I am in no position for a betrayal. I don't own any territory
I own no territory. I have to sit this out for a while as well and I'm gonna make the I'm gonna I'm gonna
Charlie and Connor I'm gonna be like, yeah, I don't know man. I don't know any territory territory
So I'm not the one to you should attack and I've no oh
Harley
Why did you get ten troops? Oh, you have all the bots my gamer. I wasn't gonna say anything about it
I thought that that timer sound I thought Ludwig was you like really excited hitting your knee on your desk
Just cuz like he messed up there. No, no
I just thought the whole time you were like bump bump bump bump bump bump like using your knee like to hit because your
Discord indicator would pop up and I thought you making that sound
Yeah, like I thought he was going like like tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap tap under his desk
Like really like excited there it is
Brave the loading dock the blitz incident. Well, it was remember the blitz incident boys. Yeah, I mean you I'll roll over here for you
The order didn't make it down to the troops
Yeah, yeah, oh well, that's huge
I
Don't know this I guess move one of those guys
Don't have enough for that. Okay, and Ludwig intercepted the letter along the way what I can do here is
Charlie I can weaken
If I oh, yeah, good idea
so then you'd be able to easily take it by and then I would kind of settle up at a
Cristini Crist Cristini
Okay. Yeah, so that's a very tranquil space. Yeah, so I'll do what I can here
Because they're like adding letters. Oh
Excellent work. It's a perfect fight. My men didn't even hold a chance the warehouse holds. I don't even try. Okay
They also fell immediately. Okay. All right. So now you can handle this
Potentially down here. I don't know what he's gonna do with troops, but he can't put very many
He's in a tough spot right now
I've got it. I got it pretty locked down except for her bottom left. We're a little weak down there. I'm gonna just sit back here
All right
Let's do this first. Let's do this
Second, let's think this is important to do you're throwing your points in the trash
Yeah, I mean I look I don't own territory
They do I have to play nice for a while and then I'll settle up here build up some troops and then I can make a
move
Can't make a move right now
You don't want a repeat of what happened down there at filter Bailey. I'm telling you right now
I'm agreeing with you. Those filter boy filter Bay boys are built different. You might want to just avoid them entirely
Make three subs in it's not about the points. It's about sending a message
I think I just have to stop here. I don't give the opportunity to keep going
You think you're funny?
Somebody in chat said that I was just reading I am the actor they were the writer. I'm yeah, that's filter Bay
You can really make something happen here
Yeah, so
Maybe just locked down
E by so let's give like that. That's a lot. They get from them. That is a lot kill them
You're a little too excited here
Charlie check your DMS
DMS you like to distract me is that what's going on? No, just see on your screen. There should be something there. Oh
Little alliance he's trying to pull all the alliances back
Last to get your a last to game check this out. You see that message. Oh, that was very positive. Um
Where should I put the last troops? Where should I put the last troops?
You're gonna want to fort
Um, I wouldn't don't listen to him tell us he's gonna do you guys gonna have an alliance and he's gonna build a bunch
Of troops and then it's gonna be like, oh look Ludwig won again
He like conquered the whole entire place it up for that the fourth time in a row. I guess I have a question for you
Charlie, have you been having fun? Oh, yeah
I mean, so does it seem that bad if Ludwig wins again, you know, like well Ludwig winning has been kind of fun
That's what I'm saying if it's been fun
I have had a fun time
You know what you seem and I like this is gonna come off of like a little aggressive
But you seem perfect for you by like that's your place. I don't even want to have a piece of it
He's he's switching up. It's trust them guys. So you honor you care for them troops. Yeah, this is the bottom, right?
I think I'm gonna take top right bottom right gives six alone. Yeah, I think I'm gonna take the top right here
Be like a nice guy about it though, like I'm being like cordial everybody like I take from I'm in some yeah
I have united all of you in one simple goal of vanquishing me
But if I'm looking at the map right now Charlie and Connor just dwarfing you Jerma. Yeah, but that's okay
I I've been I'm getting a territory here next turn. Yeah, we're like pals. Are you cool about it? Yeah
be going from
Christine's work. Oh, we can't okay. Are you really getting that? I don't know if you're getting it. Okay
That's a luck. I guess game work. I mean, I don't hear any terms from you
I I'm not saying any terms because I don't feel like I'm the one who's gonna lose first. I think you are interesting
That's huge. You need to come to me in this spot. It's huge. Yeah fucking huge man. You have to have cars or something, right?
Troops it's pretty big. It's pretty big. All right. I uh, I'm gonna grab
Christina knee we we all cool with that. We okay with that. It's Charlie. You got to talk to you
Oh, I'm fine. Wait, what do you I wasn't listening? What was that? I'm going for Christina knee
He says that Christina knee and then oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, you're cool. Don't take any bye not e-buy, but
Bit of a loose character
Smooth beautiful. I'm very sorry. I did not want to do that. But trying to have some troops, you know
Hold on. But wait, wait, wait, wait
I'm just making sure there wasn't any orange down here that I missed you're looking at. I'm not looking you're peeping
It's okay to pee
Alright now I can I actually get some troops?
Yeah, guys, this is where I just build troops
I put like 60 people here eventually just sleeping in the back and then I've run over everybody in the last five minutes
I'm gonna have like a hundred troops under one spot the fight on Tank Bay. Oh
My god, but they're all gonna fight each other. I'm gonna be sitting right here
It's a bad start
We trade one for one
Round two. Come on Tank Bay Tank Bay. Oh, let's go
That's right. They don't want to be back under your rule. Come on. Thank baby. Oh, yes
We went to here. Good. Damn it. Come on
Damn
He's strong. All right. All right. One more finish him off. Damn it
All right, that's all right. They fought pretty well. They lost way too much there
You're gonna know where to go. Yeah, you're gonna go
Don't worry about what's going on over here. I just want you to know
Next turn I i'm about to go sicko mode really that scares me. I don't like him saying that
It's gonna be crazy. I said he said that it was bad for us
It'll be like something taught in history books. It'll be like the sicko mode war
One of the quotes would be like that was huge from a fallen commander. What are we gonna do?
Uh with this the bottom one this one here this uh, we're lib
We have to somebody's got to claim that
Um, those are points that are not being used big man big man
Um
Jerma, i'll uh, i'll cede it to you in exchange for a unbreakable alliance big man. You're not you're not coming in
You got to just hold the borders
Yeah, no, i'm not coming in it is but what if I was I think it would be bad for you. But what if I
But what if I was I I I would
Highly recommend what is the not cringe alliance think do I crash in
Oh, let's let's confer with the cringe alliance for a second
um
I think you I think you could do it
But just be be crazy. It'd be a wild move
On his next turn he might sweep down here and take out uh and take out barbecue
He does have three cards to combine you tell what do you want me to do boys? I'll do you tell me
I think hold yeah, that's a good idea jerma
Well, he wants you to like that
Actually kind of do sound like that you're right
Probably not this turn. I'm just i'm just gonna hold for this one. Actually, I think jerma's right
It's a good idea jerma actually speaking some facts today. No, don't catch me. I said a dunkin donuts
Yuck. Yuck. Yuck. Yuck. I haven't been a dunkin donuts in like four years. All right hogging the airways here jerma
Come on, please one alliance. Whoa connor seems a little hungry
No, no, i'm just taking the top right. That's what we all agreed on
What's that five doing down there you attacking you're just gonna protect my voters cringe alliance
I guess yeah, it seems like you're attacking riven. Oh, do I need to use these do I have to use my cards now?
Yellow could kind of get a little wacky on the top left or top right over there kind of crash into that back
Yep, that backbone over at prison and I can't because then I will get absolutely demolished and back ranked by ebi
Uh, what oh, I guess I have to do this
I have to use these. Oh, yeah
Five cards max five cards. Okay
Oh my god, connor. You have such a big attack coming up. I can feel it in my bones. Holy shit
It's okay. I'm not listen. We're all guys. It's all we're all boys
We're just keeping it together here just some fortifications a couple of guys fortifying a lot of fortifications almost
Hold connor looks by the way impenetrable right now. No, no, no
Don't let this don't let this snake influence you
I i'm, hey
I'm sitting here and i'm seeing who's gonna write the history books and his name's connorese pants germination will be forgotten fast
Don't listen to him. Don't listen to him attributed tons to science and history and culture. You're not attacking here connor. Are you no?
No, we're just keeping everybody. We're just hanging out everybody's friends everybody's pals. Yeah, don't be fooled by this nonsense. He's got 16 troops
That's more than I have
There we go. We're bumping their legs here
I think somebody has to take this bottom one. Are we okay that I can i'm taking um, yeah
Really be worse. Okay. Let's make sure this confirmed before I go for it. Oh shit. I did this wrong
Oh, I lost a lot. Um
All right. I accidentally did not it's okay
That's fine. It's fine
No, it's it's fine
It's a big scary number 12
Oh my god, whoa
You don't want to come through filter bay
They don't like you they don't appreciate you. It's not going bad for me so far
No, dos was not murdered after this. I think this is the last game. I'm gonna play some dos after this
It's only 10 o'clock. It's not late. I think I
Might have to
Where are you going?
Let him if you attack that don't do it. I'm not even thinking about that connor
I think it's kind of fucked up. We're doing the charlie right now is one of my eyes a little this is a little
Fuck, it's a little messed up
That car turning was ridiculous
None of us are liking that. We're all like allies
Are you fucking kidding me? I made that mistake. Yes. Oh, it still worked out for you
um
Very spread out though
You could have said I had to move exact thing that he just did
Huh?
Now we can do the same exact thing and I could just march through your back line
Yeah, no, I I i'm seeding
Elo huan. Oh, yeah
Okay
I have moved to the bottom left. I feel uncomfortable in cito huan and elo huan
I think you guys have done a bad job of controlling connor and I think his top right
Somebody said the psycho play is to immediately right now turn and take this right side from charlie
Oh, and uh, that's a bad idea
charlie then immediately gets
These I mean, he's got 24 troops over here. I'm toast
I need to wait another few turns before I make any decisions. I want you to know that
That's but yeah, that's fine. I still I need this though
I'm marching. I'm marching. That's all you
Oh, this is good for me. Your troops are gonna be spread here
You're gonna have like three and a b and c. Oh, it's gonna be ugly
We can how do I stop that from happening? You can't you gotta have at least three when you leave a territory
It's weird. You can't do just one after you get something unless you bring them all trail you
This dm connor that area
That's super weird
Yeah, I think it is intentional. I can't there can be no desire. I'm orange thing until ludwig is gone
Don't you understand because if I betray charlie right now
Ludwig's still there charlie good around we're gonna be like I needed it. Oh look
See what happened you see what happened? He'll scream and and then the two of them will will kill me and connor
I'm telling you right now. That's exactly how it's gonna play out
That's exactly what will happen. I have to be careful
Oh
back to back hard
Wow, he's rolling like you gotta be careful. I think you can take him out here. That's what i'm you gotta be careful
Oh shit, i'm thinking
Yeah, that's what i'm thinking. I think we closed this one out from him
I think you're closing this one out as a whole connor to be clear. I don't oh my god
I think connor runs rampant. We're gonna keep the march going. It's a gg situation for all of us here
I want you guys to know no
Oh
They were like in the new we don't like blue and barbecue so we say it's a phrase
They do say that. Oh my god. Why can't I oh you made a mistake you skipped silo b
It's a blunder. This is stupid. He skipped silo b. What an error doesn't make any sense
I know I didn't oh no
Well, no, because you have to go back and now you have to leave three troops because you went back
You're still okay though. No, it's over. You're not getting all of me. I want you to know you've left me alive
Which will be your downfall. That's all right. At least I kept my my allies alive
And that that fight over there at barbecue was one for the history books inspirational, huh? How about that?
They fought hard. They really did and ottoman died when you think about it at the end of the day. There's no country for
Uh, there's a timer isn't there? Oh
That's right through bay for you. Not even close
Oh, I ran out of time
Okay
I just have germa. Can I make a deal with you? It depends. Uh, yeah, you
Hear me out first. Uh-huh. I'm getting to that stage where ludwig is pretty much on the ropes
He's got really nothing here. He's got he's got this little bit. It's pretty desperate
He has one card so he's got nothing so he's probably gonna be one of you guys will take that card
He's got nothing germa. He's got nothing essentially what i'm gonna have to say is i'll just
I'll take these two down here. I'll take whirlybee now
You guys can finish
One of you will finish him off and get his one card
I will chill here in the middle until we find out our next course of action
Which will be we'll figure that out when we get there
Mmm, cool. Okay. I like that
I don't
Thank you. Can I chime in? I don't like that. So what would what would you suggest?
I would suggest you
Not only get yourself a little bit of whirlybee
invade
also
Revan and under weaken them all. All right, this is your time to dominate just get one on each
They don't need the bonus. You're running out of daylight. By the way, you gotta you gotta roll. Oh
Jeremy you gotta take a that part in uh, at least two there and just give that to you
Yeah, i'll take that for now. We have that bonus take that for now and then
I was relocating your troops. I put them on city pier yesterday
Whoa?
Ayo
Whoa, what's he doing?
I gotta make a move man. Gotta make a move in war. He's making a crazy move. All right. All right. All right
Big man, you want some of that land bag load? I mean
Big man charlie. I don't know where he is charlie. No, did he go to the bathroom?
He didn't see any of that
Okay, nobody say anything don't say anything. Uh, just tell him i'm gonna tell him my cat walked across the keyboard big man
Big man, I need to arrange an alliance with you. Oh, what the fuck just happened
Germa invaded your land and is threatening to take the rest of it. I need safe harbor
Can you provide me with safe harbor? Why why did germa attack? He literally just attacked
Because connor is dominating and he wants to win
He's actually a snake. He's actually asking you. Will you provide me safe harbor? He's whispering lies
I'm asking for for just oh, I had to
Charlie I had to attack here because he is his plan is he's gonna try to wrap around
To try to kill you at a one here where my aid is right now
But you talk about I needed I needed to fortify this section in the top left because he has six
He's gonna come through he's gonna try to he was gonna say you're worried about my six
My six charlie use the thing. I want to take prison junction and I want you to save me from
Demolition and misery. I went to tinkle. I didn't see what actually happened. I don't know what kind of
Diplomatic snakery was done here. Oh my god. Nothing on my end. Nothing on my end. I pray, okay
You know what charlie? I am hiding on block a still attacking by the way. I told you i'm not attacking
I'm trying to find safe passage
Fuck
You can choose to stomp me out like a god damn piece of meat
Look, he's even he's blocking your troop movements, man
No, i'm not i'm block a i'm block a block. It doesn't block anything. That's the thing about
12 up to the top left. He can't get him over there charlie. You are on threat of extinction
I don't know what to do. I am not i'm not going to attack
Any more goodbye?
That was the whole purpose was to get here to make it so you couldn't go over here because there was one troop here
i'm coming up into
Take back exactly exactly take it back. Take it back. Bye
I will I will get out of it. Bye. I mean 39 troops is a lot. Don't stop anybody
All right, you could take a little bit of christianini. I'm thinking i'm thinking
I think I think you have to invade a bit of christianini. He's a mad man
You could also go south too a little bit of south action wouldn't hurt you
You know fighting that eight would be bad because that's a lot to lose potentially
I fought eight one time in barbecue and it was a mistake you you win this eight you win
You sure do but you also get two cards if you get rid of lugwig right now
But remember the alamo
I know what I know what I need to do
Don't forget what happened in mexico. He's making a huge play here. I I know what I have to do
You're running out of time. You're running out of daylight. You got a getty by land before the end of this turn
Holy holy shit, man. That was huge
You also should invade whirly b. You shouldn't kill me. You have to get a by land. I have
Oh
Oh huge
That's huge fucking huge fucking huge
What is that?
Fucking man. Oh my god. He's gone insane. Huge fucking huge. Oh huge
What is the fucking hugest thing? I keep hearing is it this is bad for you. It's not huge for you
This is fucking huge when you cross the filter bay boys huge huge
Connor is gonna run over some cities. Connor's gonna take over all of charlie's board at this point
No, you have to finish let off first. I equalized it
Connor you should go from the south and just chew through testing testing. Is this low?
It's it's this is such a throw. It's unbelievable. It's unbelievable. Yeah, I just found this discord call. I don't know how I got here
I just found this discord call. I don't know how I'm taking let out. You can see how it's so political, huh?
So political these days. There's a lot of politics going on home block a scary connor. Be careful
All right, go for block a last it'd be on our week. They're scared. I don't know how I got here
But i'm i'm in this discord call and I don't know how I got in here
I don't know how I got here, but I'm in this discord call. I don't know how I got in here
You guys are so worried about being the big monster looked at each other. Why won't this go low now?
We're in a weird situation. I don't know how I got in this discord call, but I somebody help
I got the wrong uh server ID, I think
I don't know how I got in this discord call, but I somebody help. I got the wrong uh server ID, I think
Did you click spectates on the bottom left? No, I clicked a goddamn arrow. Where is um?
Where is it? I don't know how I got in this discord call, but I somebody help. I got the wrong uh server ID
I think the fuck is that?
Yeah, i'm trying to find it
Right now who's talking why is it not on the thing? Um, someone typed in chat jerma's worst joke coming up
I already did it and it was the worst joke because nobody reacted to it. Oh, you're wasting my turn
Oh, yes
Wait, hold on
That's letting me in my head. He's wasting my turn. Who's screen sharing me? I need one screen share
He was trying to bait me man. Can anybody hear me?
Charlie yep
No, you baited me what do you I just I'm out of the game. What do you want for me?
I won't let me screen share the game. It's not an application
Guys, I think I got in the wrong discord call. I don't know how I got in here. I got the wrong server ID
I don't know what's happening. Somebody can troubleshoot with me jerry's screen
Guys, I think I got in the wrong call. I don't know how I got in here. I got the wrong server ID
I don't know what's happening. Somebody can troubleshoot with me do the whole thing share the whole thing. Don't be shy
Yeah, are you oh you screen sharing? Yeah, okay
So if i'm gonna have to go I think guys, I think I got the wrong discord call
I don't know how I got in here. I got the wrong server ID
I don't know what's happening. Somebody can troubleshoot with me. I think I have to go up here
Who is that guy? What a weird guy. That's because weird
Is that somebody in the call who's that sounds like an absolute loony for sure
Oh, we didn't even put up a fight. I didn't have time to strategize last time. I was too busy trying to figure out a screen share
Oh my god, we're not even fighting anymore
This this can't be anything except for what happened right? I was I thought charlie was gonna be it was gonna be me and him
Jerm was having a crazy rally right now
Charlie lost charlie lost almost all his army trying to kill me. That's true. I did you made a mistake
I think I gotta stay like this. I don't think I can do anything else
It's been on for hours now
I I forgot your old voice
Connor's troop count is outrageous. I mean the good thing is he thoroughly messed up trying to kill me off
charlie, I think your uh best bet here is to uh, it's so embarrassing because
You know, I was I don't think you can beat me. I was gonna be on I don't think you can fight those really
Like I was just talking like that. I don't think so either. I think if you if you uh
protect e by land
Specifically the bottom left to be by land. That's your best bet
It's supposed to be like a guy is just talking and i'm talking
Take it down with me. You know what i'm saying? No
You're because you can band together and fight as the weird guy
Jermy won't attack you because he knows you are his ticket to winning. What the fuck have I done?
I don't know. I don't know. I mean look i've got I got five cards
Yeah, he could he could pull out something crazy. He has to cash out 20 troops next turn and if i'm telling you
Whoever wants to come for me
I think if you go bottom left to be by land, that's square next to the boat
Here's the thing. I've seen me throw these before like I haven't said this game's done
Everyone's making good points. I'm not listening to them. Let's ride. Oh, oh no madness. Oh
It was an error god damn it how many more charlie go to the right go to the right side
Ah
He's more greeds than man. All right. That's all right. All right stretched thin like a pizza
I take everything with me. I would be careful though. This is coming up there. There was actually
Jerma could die
Well, at least I said connor could kill jerma connor could win this turn actually
You have a lot of faith in me. No, no, because you also have the cards in the bottom left connor
Oh, I do
I should not have told you that
They were placating me so bad too like the oh who's that weird guy what will kill you is your indecisiveness
That's true
Oh my god, 25 troops. Well, it's a lot of troops. That'll never be enough to break us
I mean it is enough. I don't think he's quick enough to break you. That's another great laugh
I guess like I mean, I don't know. I guess we'll just like kind of placate that he's doing this thing
We're trying to put troops down but you know, whatever
Oh, it'll be sad if jerma dies before being able to cash in those cards
I'm just i'm not even i'm not kill i'm just taking up here, you know
I mean you could i'm if you do you're gonna get five cards, which is a guarantee whoever
Kills me gets the last hit is guaranteed to win the game
Yeah, because you immediately get to re-up you get to repop for another 20 30 troops probably just keep it moving
Yeah, you're gonna have to go all the way here keep the guys going
Here we go
Uh, here we go. These guys are gonna come over here speed. That's the problem. Here we go
All right, guys, we're just gonna keep moving around
That's one bad blitz. This is it. That's it
That's it. I'm so sorry, man
You're a good ally, you know, I think I think like the new country that's like the whole world
I think it's gonna be like really good for like the people
Hey, i'm i'm really glad that you got the cards though because we've had an alliance the whole time
Yeah, for sure. Well, you've all to be clear. You've all had an alliance the whole time to kill me
Yeah, it was pretty poetic it was like in code geass where the world united against lelouch. Yeah, it was actually like that
Except it wasn't an honorable thing that I was doing
Oh, I see
It was more like a sad like a sad thing. Everyone hated me. It was like world war two timers moving real quick
Yeah, you're gonna have to finish me now or never at all
Clicking oh we took 10
That was a huge huge win at tech plant
Problem is connor doesn't care about his men. He'll throw them into harm's way
It's all right. They're fighting for like the good of the republic kind of does I have three cards myself, actually
I hope they're correct and not like misaligned. No, they're not correct
But they're there. Oh my god
Let me get over there. You don't have cards for you charlie. He's got three. He left you
Oh my god
I can shift some things around. Oh my god
I got the wrong uh surfer idea. I think I don't know where to put them. Oh, okay bumper connor's cat can sense something's wrong
Yeah, he's just I didn't I muted I did that for you guys that that is saying speed is of the utmost importance
You are not showing that off today. This is gonna be
I can't believe that just happened. Wow
Yikes, did he lose a lot? He lost about like 15 men. Well, it's one troop. They fought hard there, man
They love their country ghosts of kiev
I'm biting my lip so hard
You're not going through this. Are you? No, you gotta stop. You gotta stop. No, no, no, no. I'm just taking this boat
Why would you take the boat? Oh, you let yourself open. Oh, no. Oh, don't no
He's playing like me
A little foolishly and ghoulishly you're correct
We're fine for it, but the problem is you have one card
And connor has my biggest concern is invading and then somehow misaligning the invasion to where there's just a whole
Yeah, like those 15 troops you can't access interesting gonna get you guys banned from everybody's channel running. I like our odds here
What are you doing? Don't don't be fucking weirdo. I don't even know what I do. You'll you'll never find us
I've spread us all over the continent
It's gonna take one of you guys just has to go and do it in one shot
That's the only way it's gonna work. I think yeah, that's the only way
Oh bumper. I still can't believe what happened over there at fucking barbecue
Oh, yeah, you could edit that 15 there you gotta do it in one go. Uh, where'd I put everybody?
There we go. You'll never get me in one go. I actually agree. Did you troubleshoot that guy's discord?
I mean we tried we're fighting so hard too quickly. Yes, they took three. They took three three for one. Oh
The full camera just glitched 47. It's actually attacking me. The whole game doesn't want to see me win
No
They're rolling you right now charlie filter bay is gonna stand strong. They always do carrier aft
Seems like a good spot. Shit. Uh, he's not winning this turn. He can't there's no way there's no way not with filter bay
There's no way. Oh and he leaves five and landing for no reason
Because I don't know how this game works
Uh, there we go strategically avoiding filter bay
I can't even attack that one
Oh my god, he found his 47 troops. Oh my oh my god, dude
You're gonna regret this
There's a lot of people just spread out. You do have like five men per island. Oh my god, dude
What the heck happened?
Dude, I think you're the wrong discord. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god, dude
What the heck happened man filter bay's lost the lost the will jesus christ
They're so tired of fighting at this point
They have only known war way too many leadership. I'm not i'm not doing it again
I probably you live one more turn here charlie. Yep, and i'm gonna make the most of it
I got three troops and i'm getting the fuck out
But I think I can win this if you just snake around and wait till you get a car turned
And he might not be able to catch you. Yeah, I think that's the play. Yeah
He just has so many troops and they're all over they are you know what you're right well
Somebody said wrong discord, dude. Fuck it. Haha
Like the cringe face
I might shift things. I'm not pressing the button to do that again. So i'm just letting you know, I promise
It's done. No, I know you
Ludwig you were saying that because you're like he's that's gonna get him going
He's gonna press the sound word thing. I forgot to attack that one. No me
42 troops
It's not enough
A lot of guys there. He looks like it's enough charlie
Watch i've i've strategically positioned us on the optimal battlefield
You know what? I think he didn't do enough here. I think industrial cargo lives 18 is not enough
This game is so
How do you how did he make it
Cargo he they live. All right, dude. I got into your call. Like what are you talking about?
How are you supposed to possibly do that? Oh you fool you'll never beat us here another mistake
Charlie just anyway on the disposal cargo. All right. I need these guys to die. Oh my god
Wait, this is so dumb. Why can I move them charlie charlie? You could make it to a car turn
I'm so close to it. All right. Oh, he's figured out how to fortify
No, wait, that's it. I can't move over
We're making a run for it
I'm gonna try and take refuge in the middle of this embarrassing joke. Uh arc here somebody's goes
Hey, dude, you playing stanley parable. Uh deluxe your boys are lacking resolve. Yeah
You'll get a card
All right
I just need to find a way the fuck does that I need disposal cargo to hang strong and that's all
If they beat the 15 which is possible, oh disposal cargo. We need you now
Oh forgot to intern i'm just gonna get like 40 troops. All right. All right 30. Oh my god
I give them like i'll say that oh mistake underestimating. I'm fine
Underestimating connor. It's okay. Oh you think disposal cargo with anything less than 50
I believe listen, there's a lot of resolve on this on the blue side
Oh kristen edie lives. Oh, it's one and done every time
Oh
All right, it's all up to disposal cargo. Can this happen boys? This is the fight here. These are the these are like sport. Oh
Yeah, they fought they fought
Okay valiant vali g the alien guy
Yeah, pay to win I guess huh? Yeah, I suppose so. I mean that dice was weighted. All right. Well gg gamers
Um, you all did valiantly destroying me. Um, really just dismantling me as a human
And I had to though we had to keep we can't you can't win three four in a row
You know, it's fair. It's fair. Oh, I got a token
nice
That's the worst part about this. I haven't gotten a single token
well
Um, all right gamers, I gotta head out. I gotta go too. That was fun boys. Take it easy everyone. Yeah
See you later guys
Oh wrong discord over here
It's like all right, dad
That's like dad
Dad makes that joke. You know what I mean? Like oh, hey fellas. I know you're having a pretty good world of warcraft sesh
But uh, hey
How do I get in here? Hey, and then I have to go i'll be like that dad
And I have to get up and be like don't don't embarrass me in front of my fucking friends
And then dad's like what what what I was funny. What I I I'm I actually am like dad
Dad, that's not funny at all
20 minutes of dos incoming pog. All right. What do you guys want to do?
Uh, what do you guys think?
Here's the plan
plan a
We do i'm not high. I'm not i don't get high on stream. I haven't got high on stream in like a year and a half
We okay, we do dos right now
For like a couple hours two three hours or we come back tomorrow
Do dos tomorrow at a normal time?
Everything we get a poll
I will be playing dos longer tomorrow
Or we can go hard tonight and I stream till like one or two o'clock in the morning
But that then that means there is no stream tomorrow if I stream to like two three a.m pacific
I'm probably i'm not going to stream tomorrow tomorrow. Is it better?
I've seen a lot of tomorrows do both
Normal time by the way would be four o'clock pacific. That was fun, though
I'm really enjoying the kind of just jump in a game with a bunch of just buds
Conor rating a fellow ally is the right and i'm probably about to send you somewhere else
You're all about to go somewhere else because we're uh, the poll looks like it's unanimous that tomorrow is when i'm gonna stream
Is uh is charlie still streaming? Yeah, we'll do tomorrow. We'll start. What does do tomorrow four o'clock?
We'll do some dos
Yeah, it's probably better. Anyways, instead of like keeping everybody up till like two o'clock in the morning
We'll just start tomorrow at four pacific. Yeah, that's better. That's the plan
Uh, yeah, well, thanks the raid conor. Uh, obviously a lot of fun to play with you as always
So i'll just send you guys immediately here
Uh to is ludwig still streaming too. We'll see you off for the night charlie's still on. All right
We'll send you guys to charlie. I'll see you guys later
Thanks for watching. See you tomorrow. Good night. Goodbye. That was risk
I didn't play dos
It has been what says that in the uh tweet and potentially even in the title if ludwig's still streaming then some of you run over
There I will I will officially be slash rating
Uh charlie very very fun didn't win but you know, hey, okay
I did. Okay, I think it's more about the journey than it is about the destination. Come on
I got a lot of dos games a lot
One would say too many so it's actually kind of good
It's good that we're not doing this tonight because I might stay up till like 3 a.m
All right. I'll see you guys later. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. See you tomorrow