Hello! We're an hour and 10 minutes late, but who cares?
Oh, good, good, good, good, good. Hi, how are you? I am as exa- get these people away from me,
by the way. If you're within like a 10 second radius of the king. Uh, we had a little bit of-
we have some problems. Uh, we're trying to get through. There are currently, I think,
two or three hundred people on the server right now. Welcome to FTK, the first alpha test of FTK.
10 second radius. Uh, I'm Jerma, how are you? Good to see you. We've been, uh, debugging, uh,
back and forth, but the kingdom is currently, uh, full with people at the moment. Uh, some of which
I don't know where they are. Early access, early access. Yes, yes, very much so. This is the first
he killed three people. I didn't kill anybody, okay? Debugging a server! Well, I haven't, but
there's been some devs. Uh, you're pro- if you're in the game right now, uh, very- a couple of very
important things. I actually need to- I need to tweet this. I don't even know enough. I don't-
where the fuck is my phone? I have no idea where my phone is. Way more people were interested in
this than I thought were. There is no whitelist. We had to can that last second because, uh,
there was a lot of API problems that we had to work around, but no shit, Sherlock. I- look,
I know. I know. I- I know. It's a new video game. I- I- look, I'm out in a- I'm outside right now,
and I- there's a- I got a fucking paddle, and I'm in a boat, and we're just rowing. We're just rowing
in the water. No one's ever done anything like this before. We're charting new territory. Show us? Uh,
we can show you right now. It's an eight-year-old game. Little did German985 think that, uh,
5,000 people all trying to connect to the same server at the same time, even with, like, three
servers and a bunch of shit in place. I mean, he's just a fucking idiot. That's all you need to know.
Anyways, uh, I'm surprised no one's tried to attack me as the king, but if you can see the
screen here, I'm not sure if we can see anything. Uh, this is the kingdom. Uh, welcome, everybody.
There are currently fucking hundreds of people in here, and you know how this game works.
So if anyone gets too close- I'm going to my throne room. I- I'm like, guards, stay with me.
If anybody tries anything, just get rid of them. Push them off. This is my bedroom,
if you wanted to see. There's a ton of people in my- I don't feel safe right now.
Oh, and there's the music. Welcome, everybody, to Fuck the King. Oh, it's because they're all
children. Right, okay, I get it. Somebody just punched me. Somebody just punched me.
I don't know who it was. All right, I'm gonna go down to my throne. The server actually is stable.
You gotta be kidding me. I'm so happy right now. The server's stable. We were getting fucking
screwed. If you are under the- if you are under the age of five, you can't mine. So that's why-
get away from me. I'm gonna punch this person. Wait, are you a mod? All right, this is the dining
room. You can't mine until you're five years old. I can't believe- why is nobody trying to kill me?
This is the throne. All right, if you're on the throne, you just killed that person. Okay,
that person's dead. Hey! Don't let any- anybody on the throne. Somebody got killed.
Ladies and gentlemen, please, welcome to the kingdom, all of you. What did you throw to me?
The king needs to eat. Get the fuck out of here. Go exist in the kingdom. Why are you all standing
here? Why are there a hundred of you standing in front of the throne? Get out of my castle.
Okay, all right. If the throne room has anyone in it in the next 15 seconds, you will die. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.
You just made it out. Go exist! My gods will protect me from all this bullshit. All this food
is delicious. You know there's an entire kingdom. In fact, it's so good to see you. I may, in fact,
have a song that I would like to sing. It's so good to see everyone. You're all so wonderful.
This is the first stream of the kingdom. I think I have a song coming on. What a little town. What
a quiet little village. Every day, like the day before, absolutely beautiful. There's so many
people here. What a quiet village, castle, and all of its participants. A hundred of them.
I just have one thing to say to you. Bonjour. Bonjour. Bonjour. There goes the baker with his tray
like always. Don't hit me! Every day it's just the same. In the kingdom, just the same. All right,
kill them! Kill them! Kill them! They're attacking! Kill them! Stop! I'm going back to my castle.
Brent! Kill them! Kill everyone! I shouldn't have attacked them. To the castle, because we just
deleted like 30 people. By the way, this is the first of the tests of the FDK show.
There's no way I'm gonna die. I'm not gonna die. I need to get back to my castle.
I think those are all babies. How old were they? Somebody just wrote, what am I supposed to do?
Kill this guy! No, don't, don't, don't, don't!
Every day, like always, we check the garden and the stall. Every morning, just the same. Me and my guards, we have to take all the crazy people that will try to jump at the server at the same time and 5,000 connections crash the server. Get them away from me!
Okay, let's delete the music from Beauty and the Beast, or we will get the vomit claimed in less than
five minutes. So we should probably get rid of it. Because the vicar, the vomit is going to be de-fucking-lated
if you do not kill this music. What a beautiful garden! What a wonderful garden! I couldn't think
of anything other than a random gardener. Thank you for your participation. Thank you everyone for joining the server!
Where's the castle? My trusted guards, let's go over them one by one. Cad, the video game developer.
Barretti, destroyer. Freshpink Flakes, the cereal worker. Are you a guard? I don't know. Supressor,
the soup-based guard. He doesn't know his own kingdom. We must find, you have to eat food or you
can't participate. The king needs to get back to his castle, but one of the guards, please show him
how to get back to the castle. And by the way, there is no whitelist on this server. You are
going to be nearly landed because this fucking API was fucked. My kingdom, I'm currently in the
Outer Lands right now. TP me to the castle. The king requires a TP to the castle because he's stupid
and doesn't know where his own shit is. TP me to the castle, I don't know where it is. The king can
cheat if he wants to. Can I just say, oh, and there's the throne room. My beautiful throne,
nice fail RP. Somebody said in the chat room, well that person can fuck off. Currently in my
throne room, the king will exist here. Until then, someone just punched me. Get that person out of
here. I don't want them in my kingdom, I don't want them near my throne. Currently 31 years old. And
if we could start to, I know at least 30 people died right there. If we could bring some more
people into the server, it would be fantastic. It's been one year and the harvest has been
completely fruitful. Why is this happening? Fuck. I would like to address the crowd if I may.
I'm going to go up to my balcony. Whoops, that's a wall. Remember there are up to two, three, four
hundred people in the server at the same time. In my kingdom, in my journey, there's nothing in this
chest. I'm going to go visit. I see only about 10 people in the courtyard. The king has been drinking
for the last hour and a half and the king was not sure this server was going to turn on. So he's a
little tipsy at the moment if we could just be very frank. My subjects, some of you which are not even
present at the moment, how have none of you started to eat? Here, take a few chickens on me, your king.
In fact, have a few mutton too. I'm a good king. You don't want to get rid of me. I'm a good king.
How many people are here right now? Where are all of my subjects in the kingdom of Germalonia?
Yes, that's correct. That's the name of this whole thing. I just came up with that right now,
Germalonia. Are you dying of starvation yet? I somehow have de-aged. I have gone back a year.
I was 31 and now I'm 30. My loyal subjects, if you could please do something for your very,
very, very noble king. I require a gold block statue of my likeness in the middle of the
outland courtyard within the next 30 minutes or I will execute 50 people. I want a gold dick
that's representative of my life. I will show you. Wait, I don't want to fall off the edge
because I deleted it. Take this. I said that in the very noble war. Would anyone like a piece
of bread? By the way, my loyal servants, my loyal guard, if anyone comes up these stairs,
kill them instantly. I want a gold statue of me and I'll show you where it is. I'll show you where
I want it. Guards, come with me. Set the castle on fire. Set the castle on fire. Good luck.
I'm getting lost in my own castle. Who is this person and why are they in here? Oh,
bread for the king. Thank you so much. I appreciate it. You're doing a very good thing.
Thank you for the bread. Let me show you. Follow me. I'll show you. Somebody just punched me.
Who just punched me? I'd like to know who it was. Oh, I'm going a little too far in
the common people. This bread is just no good. Here, someone else eat this.
How did you make 64 bread? That was impossible. Don't let them in. Don't let them in. Get these
bitches. I'll shower you with love. Follow me. Get away from me. Shit. Get away from everybody.
I don't have any guards. This is a mistake. Where are my guards? I would like the gold statue.
By the way, I'm not kidding. If there's not a gold block statue right here, right here,
where I'm standing in 30 minutes from right now, I will execute 50 people. Good luck. Start the timer
now. We can't mine. If you're outside of the red border, you can do whatever you want. Inside of
the red border is where you cannot do anything. You can do whatever you want outside as long as
you were five years old. Okay. Good luck. How is this already done? Where did you get the gold
blocks? Is this person cheating? How did they get gold? No, there's no way they have that many gold
blocks. Kill them. How many people? There's a lot of people in here. So what was the explosion?
I heard a fucking explosion. Who has creative mode? That shouldn't be a thing.
Okay. There's like 300 people here. What the fuck are they? I'm actually getting kind of nervous.
Oh my God. Okay. Somebody just punched me. Somebody punched me. I'm going to go into my town.
You can do whatever the hell you want out here. I don't matter. Oh, is that genome? Oh, genome.
What age am I? I'm 31. What age are you? I'm two, six, seven, two. I'm two. Yeah, maybe eventually
some of you plebs, because that's what you actually are. I'm going to go enjoy my fountain.
Don't let anybody in here. If you come inside, you are dead. Do not let anyone inside. I have
things to do, like exist in my throne room. What happened to the throne room? Why is it my throne
room floods? I want you to find who did this and I want you to kill someone. Don't let anyone in the
front gates, no matter what. I'm age seven, yet I still have mining fatigue too. I think, you know
what I'd like to do? Is this Colgate Island? What? I'd like for me and my loyal subjects,
let's go explore the town a little. What's the matter? What are you all doing out here?
Don't you have things to do? You need food. You need food. Join voice chat. Why? What does that
mean? Join voice chat. Oh, I just went into the voice chat screaming. I live in the castle. No,
you don't. Somebody said they killed a Fortnite guy. Excuse me. Thank you for that ladder.
Please food. Go get food. Fine. Listen, this is the only time you're going to get a handout like
this. Fight for it. Go get it. Don't let them in. Get rid of them. Get rid of them. How dare you?
I'm starving. Well, then make some food. I can't be the one that provides everything.
I didn't anticipate. Somebody came in the server and said, what is this?
You're going to fucking die. Not going to make it. Are there no animals? There should be.
Someone give me the coordinates of the town. I'm lost. There is no food. God, this is fucking so
stupid. This is no way no one's going to kill me. I am never going to die. No, there's not a chance
in hell. Even if three, four, 500 of you work together. No way. The guards are too strong.
My king, I would like to offer my jester services. Okay. Psychostatic. You are dressed like a jester.
Let's get you in here. That'll be fun. Psychostatic is allowed inside the king. Yes. Very, very, very
funny. Absolutely hilarious. Now kill him. Why is he still here? I gave a specific order to my
subordinates. Just pick it up, man. Just pick it up. Okay. I need to. Oh, ow. Hey, let's take a look
outside. Get out of my way. Go. Food. All right. Let's go this way. Follow me. I would like to go
fishing, please. If I could get a fishing rod. Watch these people behind me. They look like they
could be degenerates. What's a command? Excuse me. I'd like to go fishing in my pond. That would be
nice, please. Yeah, go get it. Fuck this warden. I need a fishing rod. No. Everyone thought I was
going to die in five minutes. Do I have a fishing rod yet? Wait, the guards are in creative mode?
Get these guards out of creative mode. Excuse me. I'm trying to fish at my pond, please.
If you don't back off in five seconds. Wait, what? Kill that person. Help me. Help the king.
God damn it. Protect me. Protect me at all cost. Are you still alive? We're still live, right? Oh,
my God. What a shit show. What happened? I don't even know what happened. How did I die?
I want to see that. Am I through the stream right now? We have two different calls going. What
happened? Sword killed me. Stone fucking sword killed me. No way. What? I had diamond armor on.
Doesn't make any sense. No, I didn't. I was naked. What do you mean? I was naked? Who killed me?
I got hit three times. What? I didn't have any armor. I get another life. Let's go. You're not
stopping. Wait, why did I die? Who has a clip? I want to see it. I had like five people with
diamond armor on me. Where is it? Let me see it. We're going again. We're going again. New people.
I can't fucking believe I died. Nobody even did anything. I went fishing and got killed.
I didn't have a single piece of armor on. That's not supposed to be real. It's so bad. I thought
I had armor on. He doesn't know how to play Minecraft. Yes, I do. I thought I had armor on.
God damn it. We're going to do a new game. We're going to do a new game. What does a command block
do? I don't know what that does. This is fucking funny. Somebody said, bro, please let me in.
Somebody set fire to a tree. Can we like deal with this? There's a fucking forest fire. There's a
legit full forest fire right now. All right. Give me one second. I'm in there now. Bro, please let
me in, bro. I'm just so happy it works. There was a really high chance that this was not even going
to work. We had a lot of hoops that we had to jump before this could turn on. Fucking hilarious.
I don't have any armor. I will have armor next time. You better guarantee it. I get two lives.
I love it when a plant falls apart. Well, this is like the alpha. Okay, now I got gear. Okay,
now I'm good. Now I do. All right. I didn't have armor last time. Someone's already trying to kill
me. What? 34, by the way. What's that mean? 34. Why is it 34? I don't get it. Oh, I was 34 when
I died. Oh, I get it. Okay. All right. The floodgates are going to open here soon. Remember,
there is no whitelisting right now on this server. This time I'm not dying. I'm not going to go,
go out and like be with the people. No, no, no. Yeah. Fuck that. I'm staying in my castle. Good
luck. I think we're ready. Yeah. I think once we get everybody in, we see some reopen people and
we're good. I'm going to be my throne. I'm going to say this is where I belong. I'm going to say
the cameraman's a furry. I'm on a webcam mic. No, I'm not. I'm not on a webcam.
Can we just take a look at the castle before we bring everybody in? Oh, look at how fucking cool
this place is. Fix my mic. What's wrong with my mic? Oh, and make sure all the mods are not in
creative. What do you mean Trump? What are you talking about? Why is everybody saying that?
Mr. Trump, I don't understand. Why is everybody saying Trump? I don't get it. Somebody said you
stop. Oh, well, I'm sorry. Didn't mean to. My mic sucks. The assassin is back. All right.
Well, let's go. Round two. This time I'm not dying. I'll stream for 10 hours. I don't care.
I'm not dying. Good luck, baby. I'm not leaving the seat. Hey, give me a diamond sword too, please.
There we go. Watch the back of the castle while you're at it. The mic is fucked. What's wrong?
What's wrong with the mic? My mic is fucked. It shouldn't be. Jeremy's paranoid. Well, I have to
be. There's like hundreds of people trying to kill me. How many people are in the server right now?
Like 300? My mic is fine. So what the fuck? Why would you do that to me? Why would you tell me
that? It's literally not. It's actually not. What? Zero people in the server? That's not true.
There's like fucking 300. Discord's fucking it up though. Get more RAM. I got like 120 gigs of RAM.
Who is this person? Oh, that's you. Oh, that's like, okay, you just don't have a skin.
All right. Are we good to go? How many people we got in the server right now?
This is the real game. That was the test game. This is the real one. This is the actual game.
You ready? What do we, what do we got in the server? How many people? I see the most important
player is JermaFeet. I mean, that's the number one. Just kill that person. Find them and kill them.
Yeah. Just whoever that person is, just find them and kill them. I don't want them in the server.
Oh, I just got kicked. Fuck. Remember when people were going to make towns and stuff and go outside
the city limits and make houses and shit? No, it was just, we're just going to follow them around
till we have an opportunity for me to kill them with a stone sword. Just follow them around till
we have an opportunity to kill them with an iron sword. That was iron. Okay. All right. Server's
open. Back up again. We're going to try round two. It's hard when you get kicked. I'm just so happy
we actually could get this to run. Why is one of the guards on fire? You die at age 100 if you do
not die on the server. Who punched me? All right. Are we good? Are we good to start? Are we good to go?
All right. Every morning, just the same. Every morning, just the same. You want to do that again?
Start it on. Put it on. Oh, what a glorious day. What a beautiful morning. Oh, what a quiet little
town we're in. My town. My beautiful town. Oh, please. Bonjour. Bonjour. I can't hear the music
anymore. Bonjour. Bonjour. There goes the baker with his tray of bakeries. Save a bread and rolls to
sell. Every morning, just the same. Every morning, just the same. Since the morning that we came into
this house. Oh, hello. Hello there. Yes. How are you? No, no, no. I'm not going out. I'm not going out.
Someone's back in the throne. Someone's hiding. This will be in the hill right here. I'll show you.
Oh, you think you... Oh, where you going? You... Oh, hi there. You thought you were going to be able
to get behind the king? Don't let him. Take my what? Look, you guys have to go mine. Do you see
what I'm wearing right now? I have full diamond armor. You're not going to get in here. In fact,
if you step one more foot forward, you're dead. Don't get stuck. Excuse me. You're getting too close.
You're getting John. John. John. Every morning, just the same. Since the morning that we came
to kill the guy Chad striding into my view. How do I wall run? You can't. We got all diamond armor.
Go be a citizen for God's sake. I want to go on an adventure. Let's go. Get these people away from
me. I would like a mine to be built down here. Do we have any pickaxes that I would like you to
do it for me? Go down. Dig down here. Turn off the music. I'm going crazy. Get this person away from
me. Somebody naked? Thank you. I want to go find diamond blocks. I'd like to do it before anybody
else. Look at the people looking in here. Look at this person dropping sand on here. Okay. Oh,
that hurts. That hurts. Somebody's fucking doing great. They're throwing shit at us.
This is bad. I want to get out. I want out of here. I want out. This is bad. Do I even have an axe?
I don't have a pickaxe. I don't have a pickaxe. Let's go. Long live the king. That's right.
Don't dig straight down my brethren. Somebody died from falling. I just saw it in the chat.
I ain't going that way. You guys, I'm not going to get killed by a creeper. Somebody else go.
Vec, you go first. I'm not doing it. Do we have any torches? I need to eat. King Jerma, I come from
a faraway land to offer some of my wrestling talent to you. You come nearer, you're dead.
Don't even come within 10 feet of me. Okay. At this point now, at this point in the game,
guards, if anyone comes within five feet of me, kill them. Do not let them survive.
We cannot have an opportunity when somebody comes in with a diamond axe and kills them.
What's five feet? I'll show you. This is five feet. 1.5 blocks. The king requires gold.
Can we open the server back up again for more people to come in? Somebody said iPhone Mike.
I don't even know what you're talking about. iPhone Mike. Shit Mike.
People aren't getting kicked when they die. Yeah. We got a lot of systems we're trying to fix.
It's a Game Boy Mike. Why did I get hurt? Why are you on fire? You all right?
It's a webcam Mike. It's not a webcam Mike. I hear a growling. How many people have gotten
the server now? Let's load another 100 people in. Nobody can join. You're only playing with guards.
That's not true. This is sick. There's like 10 guards. I see iron. I'm not going to mind.
It's somebody else's mind for me. 150 now. You need food? No, get your own food. Watch that exit
here. No, you know what? Watch the water. Watch the water. Watch the water. Guards, get out of
here. This is stupid for us to be doing. I would like 50 citizens to dig up this rest of this cave
for us please. There will be four snakes on the ground. No, that's a diamond pickaxe. Give me that.
I don't want to do this anymore. This is bringing like 50 people to dig this first
until we find a cool cave and find gold. Take the gold button and you're dead.
Who is this person? You know what? I'm killing this person. Like just kill this person.
Look at how menacing that is. Okay, why am I on fire? Why am I on fire? Why am I on fire?
Why am I on fire? Stop hitting me. Someone's going to drop a fucking canvass. All right,
all the guards. Watch it. Watch it. Watch out for the Chad guy. Don't let him get away. Kill him
please. PS2 mic. Is the stamina system working? I can't see anything.
Jeremiah, I can't eat anything. That sounds like a you problem. Wait, people in the castle? Since
when? We have mining fatigue. I gotta get to the castle. Okay, I need to stop laughing. You can
only eat cooked food, guys. Wait, I need my guards. There's people here. The castle's getting
griefed? What? Guards to me please. The white list is broken. Oh, I know. It's fucked. The whole
thing's fucked. Get Chad away from me. Sergeant Flakes. Good work. It's bread. How do I cook?
Kill him. Kill him. You don't cook bread. You just eat it. What happened to the throne?
All right. Let me give you this. Citizens of Earth, if there is not 100 iron bars
given to the front of the castle in 15 minutes, 50 people are going to die
at random starting now. 100 iron bars. There's like 200 of you here.
I want it at the front of the castle. Nobody pick it up or I will execute 50 people.
Nobody pick them up. Nobody touch them. We can't mine. We're babies. Look, we can't eat meat.
Okay, listen. Listen. Very important. Listen to me. Inside of the red area where the town is,
you can't do anything. Outside of the city limits, outside of the town, the red line,
you can do whatever you want. As long as you're over the age of five, you can mine. You can place
blocks. You can eat. You're just inside the city limits. Child labor. It's not child labor.
How old are they? There's 12 people in the server. There's like 200 or 300 people in the server.
I don't see any gold, any iron bars up here. White list is broken. Open it back up. Open,
open the first server up. Let's go. How does it feel to be number two Minecraft streamer on Twitch?
Yes, we don't even have one iron bar. I'm still waiting till age five. Chat, please. I'm starving.
Grrr. It's all baby population. You're the only person. Everyone's a literal child.
Nobody can do anything. The white list is fucked. King of the kindergarten. All right, I got an idea.
I got an idea. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. I killed him. I got an idea. I got an idea.
Age everybody to 15. Go. Do it. Let's go. Somebody just died from a skeleton. I'm sorry to hear that.
Please don't steal two years of my life. Stealing years of my life, you king. I'm dying. I'm trapped
in a building. Jerma, if you're eating this, fuck you. Food, please. I still have fucking mining
fatigue. At age 15, you've got mining fatigue. 15 you heard of. I was only three feet in front of me
to be aged. Mining fatigue. This is how it was back in the day. I'm going to pee my pants.
Somebody said Mike fatigue. All right. Hold on. Wait. All right. Guards. Important guards.
Protect me. I have to pee. Do not let me die. I actually have to go pee.
Let a shitload of people on the server and fucking put everybody at age 15.
Where am I? Where am I? You put me in a box? Why? All right. Well, get me out of here. How do I get
out of here? Oh, it's nighttime. Why are these people still in front of the castle gates?
I think all things dead. It crashed. I have to execute 50 people now. Well, good. Just come back
in. I want to see some of the cool things that people have done in the outside of the town.
I'm going for it. I'm going to go look. Just whitelist everyone. Oh yeah. Everything's broken.
Yeah. We, you know, you know, kill the music, kill the music. Let's talk real talk here.
So the whitelisting server had some API issues, so we can't implement that now.
So what we've done is just said, fuck it, and open the whole thing up. And sometimes when you
do that, you open up to thousands of connections at the same time. I'm still alive though. 128 RAM
is not enough. There's like, there's like three servers here. You died. I did not die before. That
was not real. I just found diamond and now I can't rejoin. Fuck. I'm a cheater. Somebody just punched
me. I don't know who it was. All right. Let's drop the whitelist server again. Open up the
floodgates for like five minutes or so. A couple minutes. Get a bunch of people in here. Close it
up. I've been trying to mine wood for 10 years so I don't starve to death. Please help. That's so
funny. How do I get a shield? All right. I want to go look outside. Now that we have, there's a ton
of people in here now. All right. You ready? I want to go look outside. I'm going this way. Please
follow me. Guards. I'm going outside the city limits. Every time you say open up the server,
it goes down. It's all good. I'm surprised that people are just following. I guess they're not
old enough to attack me. Oh, pog. I'm 15 now. Good. Yeah. I would just make everybody 15 and get
rid of the mining fatigue. I heard an explosion somehow. I don't know what that was. All right.
We're almost outside. Did anybody have anything interesting out here that I can see? Somebody has
a crafting table and a furnace. Nobody can do anything. All right. Get him. Get him. Please
get him. Don't let him do that. All right. Most people are 15 now. You shouldn't have mining
fatigue anymore. Where's all the cool stuff in my kingdom? I'm too funny face. What is this? This
is cool. How did you make this out of fucking fences? Let's break it. What does it take you?
Like five years to make? All right. No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop. Don't break it. That's not nice.
That's mean. That's mean. Let's keep moving. Here comes the heel turn. Oh, look. Somebody has a
house out here. This is what I'm talking about. Watch out for that creeper. Kill that. Whose house
is this? What's it say? Noodle's communal house. No rebels here. Just doing a quick inspection to
make sure nothing is out of the ordinary. What do you have in here? I'll take those trees and you're
take that too. Okay. That's a nice little house you have there. Taxes? No, not yet. One house.
Taxation equals theft. Taxation equals theft. How many players we got in the server? Can we open it
up again? I would open it up again, try to get 200 and just get rid of all the limitations.
Why is there an Enderman in here? Why is there an Enderman? Why is there an Enderman? There's an
Enderman in the server. I don't think that's supposed to be here. Maybe for a second. Maybe
bring in like 50 more people, 100 more people. Maybe. Why are you telling people to be creative
when you'll ruin their creations? I didn't ruin anything. I just deleted a couple blocks.
Nothing else over here. We opened it up. Oh shit. Somebody wrote, I'm in. Can anyone else not break
blocks? When you get in the server, we're going to open it up so you don't have to worry about being
a baby anymore. What is this? Why is this here? Cut this down. I don't like that. There's 150 to
almost 200 people here. I'm trying to see if we can see anything. I want to go check out the community.
Yeah, you guys have been babies for so long. Everyone's been a baby. So wait, does that mean
that I've been killing babies? Is that what that means? Oh shit. I've been killing actual babies
this whole time. So the guy that was chad-shriding, he was a baby. Yes, I'm a monster. I'm not though.
Well, what are you doing? If you're a baby, why would you walk into the front door? Why would you
come into the front door of the tower? You're just dead. Because he's a baby. He didn't know.
Yes, they did. Babies don't know. Yes, they do. Babies don't have logic. No, they just can't
mind blocks. Somebody, people are killing each other. All right, all right, we gotta be careful.
We shouldn't roam too far. King, King Jerma, I'm starving. Three-year-old, help me, please.
Okay, I'll help you. Where are you? I'm a man of the people. Where are you? Jerma, please, food,
food. I'll help you. Where, who is this? What is this? What is that thing? What the hell was that?
What the fuck was that? What was that? I'm lost, scared. Please guide me. I don't know where you,
I don't know where I am. All right, let's make, let's go back. Jerma, I'm starving. Well, go get
food. You have the whole outer bounds to look through. There's food everywhere. Please feed us.
You're my king. Please feed us. People are starving. I don't, I don't think that's a,
you should, where are the animals? There, I have a pig in front of me right now. I have three pigs
in front of me. All right, can one of the guards please show me back to the castle? I have no idea
where the fuck we're, and can we get the music back on too so I can fucking jam? That's, that's a
little scoffed. Ooh. Little town. It's a quiet little village. Every day like the one before.
It's so full of people here. So many things to see. So many people to talk to. My kingdom.
Oh, for sure. There goes the baker with his tray of groceries. The only person following
the guards and me. Every morning it's the same. The server can't handle more than a hundred people
and there's no way we can do the game we wanted. Is that Belle? No, it's not Belle. It's another
person, Jerma. Lots of groceries. I can't wait to, where, where is the fucking capital? I'm at,
where's the capital? I don't know where we are. I have bread in my, who can, what does that mean?
Someone's punching me. Where's the capital? I don't know where we are. This way?
All right, all right. We saw one house. Good. Don't die falling down. Someone's fucking punching me.
Is this the server? Am I in the right one? I can't, man. This is fucking so.
Oh, watch these people. Whistle a wee to whistle my stuff. Oh, the crops are gone.
My lord, there's no food anywhere. People are trying to plant new food. Oh, they're desperately
trying to replace the food. Starving me. Jerma, please sign my love for bread. How many people
are on the server now? Nobody can kill me because nobody can eat. Everyone's starving to death.
There was a whole huge wheat farm right there and it's gone. It's empty. It's fucking empty.
People are desperately planting new crops and I'm walking around. Nobody can even join.
Oh my god, my fucking stomach hurts. It's my kingdom too. All right. Okay. I'm gonna plant
some seeds. Isn't everybody still alive? What do you mean there's people in the throne room doing
things to my throne? Guards with me, please. Get out of my way. What do you mean there's people
doing things to my throne? What does that mean? The castle is full of skeletons. No, it's not.
Get in there. Oh, my fucking chest. The second I saw the person with that, there's like one wall
built of their house. I mean, like, what the fuck, man? Somebody had like one wall of wood
and that was their house. What's wrong? What? Help me. Help, help, help, help, help, help, help. Help me.
I need light. We need light. Chad, Chad, put light down here. We need light. We need light.
Uh, someone's sleeping in my bed. Get dead. Whoever's in my bed is fucking dead.
You're gonna sleep in the king's bed, for Christ's sake.
I'm gonna sleep in my bed. Get out of my bed. How dare you. I'm gonna sleep. Watch out, watch out,
watch out. He's trying to kill me. Hey, you got any coaches? Air for sale? You can't sell air in
my kingdom, guys. Give me a bow. I'm gonna start sniping people. Fuck it. Let's go. Don't you fucking
seriously? Who did that? Really? Get away from me. Get away from me. Don't come near me. Don't come
near me. Don't come near me. Don't come near me. Don't come near me. The baby, this is the baby rush?
The babies have just been sitting in the bed. German, my sire, you need a queen. Allow me to
service you. Who's that? I'm sitting on the throne. I'm almost 50 years old, guys. Why? I'm not gonna
say that out loud. I don't know what that is. I will suck you for bread. Get them away from
my throne. I don't want them even near me. Get out of here, you disgusting peasants.
Cad the Brave, V.R. Josh the Virtual, and the person that just showed the escape route,
Will Sarcasm, the comedy comedian. I'd like for you to go out and find the pub inside of the kingdom.
Go find the kingdom and take yourselves out of creative mode. I want to know more about this
pub, but I'd like to know if it's kosher. A quest. Go on and find this pub that's been created.
I've heard a pub has been created in my name. I'd like to maybe have a drink there.
I'm dying, please. You'll figure it out. Scum. What was that? Watch the back entrance. Make sure
no one can get in the back. Someone took my bed. Greg from Nvidia, get out of the castle or you
will die in 10 seconds. Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two. Okay, they're okay.
RDM, RDM admin, he killed me. Good luck. No, nobody liked that one.
A nice bed that doesn't exist anymore. Oh, somebody took it and stole the bed. Now that's just
interesting. Okay, they tried to, did they find a way behind? What is this? Can I get some light in
here? What is this? Secret little hiding room? Get the fuck out of here. There's like diamonds back
here. How do I hold the torch out? What the fuck is going on over here? I didn't make this.
Investigate this, please. Someone was trying to kill me when I lied down to go to sleep. I need
to eat food. The king has not eaten in like two days and watch this. This is kind of, this is
ridiculous. Somebody got in here and made this. Who made that? I need food. Oh no, I got, I got,
I got, I got. Well, let me just tell you guys something. If you're going to go for an assassination
attempt, don't remove the bed. Get rid of the bed. That's like a giveaway that you're going to keep.
Why would you take the bed? Sorry, we have found the pub. What's in the pub? Where is it? I'd like
to go have a drink at this pub. Okay, let's go. Somebody lead me to the pub. I'd like to have a
drink at this new pub. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Please help
me. Somebody's just rushed. Fuck him. Hold on, it is sword. Cowardly king. German die. I'm 51 years
old. I'm, I'm going to live forever. All right, I'm coming. I would like a drink at the pub,
please. What are they calling me? A boomer king. All right, the next person that writes that in chat
is dead. Just, just slash kill them. Watch my back and watch the front. I mean like seriously,
just slash kill whoever's in the pub. Watch out. Watch out in front of me. Greg from Nvidia, kill
him. Greg from Nvidia, huh? You're not powering this stream. We're on AMD, motherfucker. I would
like to be served a drink by the owner of the pub. Why did you kill that? Why did you kill? Oh,
they're fighting over food. He's like, I need to eat this. No, no, no, don't fight each other. Look,
look, let me help you out here. Here. Somebody have a cooked t-shirt. Whatever the fuck this is.
You're here. What a good king and Kingsman. Have a cooked t-shirt. Actual North Korea.
I could use a drink. I heard a bow. Okay, guards be on the lookout. Seriously, I heard fucking bow.
I heard like the dung. Somebody tried to shoot at me. I heard somebody shoot a bow.
Why is there an Enderman? Someone's trying to snipe me right now. I, I stand in front of me.
Okay, kill that guy. Kill the default Minecraft Steve guy. Okay, good. See you later. Guards,
go in front of me and behind me. I'm so nervous. This is the pub. Why is this the only structure?
Property of the king. Yeah, that's right. It is, but there seems to be too many people in it.
I'm going to die. That's not a pub. That's a human box. There's nothing. I can't get in there.
Make it bigger. I'm not going in there until it's bigger. It's a trap. I'm not going in.
Imagine windows. Okay, what's he doing? I'm not going in until everyone's out. Everyone get up.
Jeremy, how does it feel to have the worst stream on Twitch?
I'm going in. Okay, everyone get up. Why are there animals in here? Why are there animals in here?
I think the server crashed. I just wanted a drink. Oh, we still actually live? The chicken spawns
crashed. Oh my God. I'm fucking, I've like been laughing too much. Wait, wait, where? Okay, wait.
I'm sending too many packets. What the fuck are you talking about? All right, we're good. We're
good. We're good. Okay. Here's the shop. Beer Baron. No, interesting. I will take one of your
finest beers. I would like to knock and punch in the face. Potion of fire resistance. What is this?
I don't think you made this. What's that? Ooh, I will take a apple juice, please, because I don't
drink this day on my A game. There's nothing in there. A finest apple juice. Okay, I'll take one.
Block the door so no one can get in, please. Luis cheese, please give that to me. What is it? Salt?
This is fucking trash. Give me something better or I'll burn it to the ground. Water. Oh, let me try
this. That's pretty good. Pretty delicious, actually. Very good. Do you have anything
else for me to try? Keep these peasants away from me. I'm starving.
I'm a little starving trying to get in here. How do you make mushroom soup? I don't know. I have no idea.
Watch it. Somebody got blooded by a creeper. You knew it was gonna happen.
Somebody got killed by a creeper. What is this? A nutrient? Pork? I'd love to try it. What is this?
Why are you on fire? Excuse me, stop. Okay, hold on. Here.
You actually blocked it off. Here, take some of this. Go adventure somewhere. Go make something.
Take these. King Jerma is sponsored by Burger King. Not true. Rid of that. Oh, the rat's tail pub.
All right, yeah. Jerma, I have a flower for you. Do you? Let me out of here. A flower. I'll take it.
Let me see it. Oh, wow. Any other structures to see? I have raw meat for you. Why don't you eat it?
Oops. I need to eat. I'm actually gonna be in trouble if I don't eat. Trading diamond pickaxe
for food. That's because I know where you got that diamond pickaxe. You found that on the staircase
because I dropped it on the ground. Don't listen. Don't trade with that person. I dropped that on
the ground. There's a sky fort in my kingdom I'd like to see. Take me to it. Oh, let's just walk.
The way it's intended to. I'm 56 years old. When do I start to slow down? It's gonna take a little
time. I'm gonna burn that bitch down. Okay. What? It's a trap. Is it a trap? All right,
guards, take me to it. Epic grass. Epic. Hey, epic grass, please. I'm freeing right now.
Another small kingdom. This is for you because you're in a fucking Pokemon skin. That's pretty
cool. Take this. Feed your family with it tonight. Oh, and take a couple of these, too. And I guess
like a shitload of cobblestone because why did you? Why did you do? Why did you do? Why did you do
that? That guy had a lot of stuff. That guy had a lot of stuff. That guy had gold gear. Why would
you do that? Why did you do something like that? What's wrong with you? That wasn't a guard. That
was a random dude. That wasn't a guard. That was a random. Wait, who? It wasn't a guard? All right,
who's punching me? All right, kill Garfield because Garfield sucks. All right, that's all
I gotta say. All right, take me to the sky fort and light the way. Why did that person die?
Look, if you got a Garfield Hawaiian shirt skin, I'm sorry, but like you just that's you die.
Oh shit, look at this. What's over here? What is it? Oh, skeleton. Somebody get that.
Oh, can we open up the server to like another 100 people? Furnace workbench. Oh, that's nice.
That's beautiful. Interesting. Very interesting. What is this? Hey, baby blood is on your hands.
It doesn't need to be there. I broke the king's throne and all I got with it. So is you. You stole
my bread. You stole my bed. You just took my bed from me. All right, where's the sky? What was that?
Seriously, what was that? Who's punching me? All right, sky for it. Let's go. What's down here?
Somebody died in there. Okay, take me to the sky for it. Give me 15. I'm a good boy. You gotta wait.
Why is everybody pumped? Whatever. Where's the sky for it? Holy shit. Is that it right here?
Who just died? Why did that person die? Oh shit. This is Dicks cannot be stopped. Oh, I see. It's
a giant dick. It's just a dick. Good. Take this down. Is this the sky for it that I was told exists?
This is not even a dick. You know, the funniest thing is seeing the chat and seeing people die
from falling off edges and stuff. So and so has died from falling. Well, sorry. What's over here?
There's a huge structure. Drop the chest plate. Let me take this down. Wait, what is this?
There's a nice mic, buddy. Is that better? Wait, why can't I? I can't destroy this. King,
there are monsters everywhere in your castle. You suck. Good use of your, like, six years of your
life. What else is over here? Germa is tiny. Can you see who placed blocks in the server? I want
that person to be killed in front of me. Signed? Where's the, where's the sign? I want them dead
in front of me. Take this down. Disgusting. Absolutely fucking disgusting. Get rid of this.
And again, I gotta ask, what's going on? Help, help, help, help, help. Stop, stop, stop. Fight
them. Kill them. Yeah, nice try. Okay. Okay, we're getting some more. All right, this guy,
kill this guy in the gold armor, in the guy in the gold armor. Kill the guy in the gold armor.
He was following behind it for so long. He was walking behind this for a long time. Selling
a strange rocket launcher with airborne enemies killed. Oh, well, you're not going to get shit
for that. That's a terrible strange. Oh, another house. What is this? Don't fall off this. This is
guaranteed death if I fall off. Can y'all age us? LOL. Just break it. Fuck the kingdom.
I can't even. Good thing I have diamond armor on. Who is it? Who did the tiny sign? I want to know.
Let's put them on trial. I want to put them on trial. Oh, it was Jonas? Okay. Teleport me
to my throne room. Put them in the throne room. Surround them. Put guards. I want to trial right
now. We know who it is. Put me in the throne. Teleport them to the throne room and like six
guards surround them. I want to know what they did. I want to know why. What do you think was
going to happen? Do you think you're going to kill me? Is it Scarfield Bracket again?
So I would like to have a small meeting of the council. Bring the culprit in front of me into
the throne room, please. What did you say their name was? Jonas. Get them in here. Did they die?
Are they dead? They're just dead. They've been dead for like 30 minutes.
They haven't been part of the game in like an hour. They built that and fucking fell and died.
Bring him in here. Bring him. Who was it? John Comcast? Oh, I know that son of a bitch. Bring
him into the throne room. John Comcast did it. Bring him into the throne. Surround him. John
Comcast, you stand accused of writing slander against the king. Something along the lines of
how tiny I am. Would you like to plead your case to Comcast? This is the wrong guy. No, it's not.
I'm 31. I'm almost all this germa. Nice booster seat is what John Comcast says.
Well, that just confirms that I have made a sentencing for you to die.
How do you think about that, John Comcast? I said your name wrong. Don't kill him yet. I want to
hear what he has to say. I'm on a booster seat. Isn't that funny? Public execution for John
Comcast. By the way, you suck. What's happening to me? Somebody coming in the back. Somebody
trying to get the back door. Somebody coming in the back door. Somebody coming to the back door.
Don't kill him. Was it a zombie? What? John Comcast, for your crimes, I have determined
that you will be, is he dead? What do you mean he ran away? How did he run away? There's like 10 of
us. What? What do you mean he ran away? You don't run away? There's 10 people here. What? Get them
back in here. He's dead. Somebody killed him. Who killed him? Get Screen Freak. Get him in the
throne room. He killed John Comcast without a trial. Get Screen Freak in the throne room,
please. I'm drowning. My apartment is pretty compromised. I actually am drowning. Somebody
help me. How do I get out of here? How do I get out of my toilet? Okay, I'm dead serious. I'm
gonna actually drown here. I don't have to get out. Thank you. Get them in here. We have a new
trial, please. Teleport them into the room. Screen Freak, you stand accused of killing somebody that
made a funny German 985 is tiny sign. Is he dead? Oh. Screen Freak, how do you plead? You killed
somebody that made a sign that said German 985 is tiny and you killed them. Are you trying to act
upon the king's wishes or was that for? It was a display of loyalty. I'm not guilty. Interesting.
Display of loyalty. The next person that hits me from behind fucking delete their IP. Okay,
just delete them. Okay. Why am I on fire? What the fuck? Why is the king on fire? Screen Freak,
I would like to hear in two full sentences. German, I'm his lawyer. Please let me help.
Don't kill, don't kill. All right, kill this guy because this guy is being a fucking sick one.
All right, we have a lawyer. John Comcast. That's the castle again. Can we please bring in his
lawyer? What's your, who's your lawyer? Screen Freak, would you like to be represented by a
lawyer? He has the right to legal representation. He doesn't. Lock him in. It's me. Screen Freak,
do you have legal representation? God, somebody is burning me from below. Do I have food? What is
all this trash? Okay. Protect me. Seriously, protect me. I'm going to die. Protect me. I'm 65.
There's a slaughter. There's a slaughter. I was killed. We didn't even get to have a trial.
He's dead. Save me. Okay, I need food. I need food right now. First of all, you know what?
Fuck it. Where are the peasants? Are they watching this trial? Get over here. Here, just here. Take
this shit. All of you. Why are you a zombie? Just take this. Look, I'm being a good king for once.
Cobblestone to build your house. I don't care what you do with this. Somebody punched me. I
don't know who it was. Look at the logs. It was a zombie guy. It was a zombie guy. It was a zombie
guy. The guy that is a zombie skin killer. I need food. The king requires food. I have 61 fucking
seeds. What do I have seeds for? What the hell do I have this for? My subjects, please come into the
fountain area. We have somebody on trial. We have two scoops. Why is two scoops in the trial dungeon?
What did two scoops do? Overload the machines until they learn their fucking lesson.
What did two scoops do? I don't feel confident. I'm going up to my... I want two guards with me
to balcony at all times, please. How many people are in the server? Can we open the server back up
again for another few minutes? Get another hundred people in here? Okay, 142. Maybe get
another 50 people in here. You're throwing seeds at a 15-year-old. Everything's fine.
Ladies and gentlemen, if we could get everyone to pay attention to the trial of... I'm gonna
get pushed off this. I'm not fucking sitting here. That's stupid. That's a stupid idea, actually. Like
an actual dumb fucking idea. I only have one, two, three, four, five... There's like 20 people here.
That means there's a hundred plus people somewhere up. Motherfucker. Motherfucker. Motherfucker. Help
me. Help me. Help me. Just start killing people. Just start killing fucking citizens. I don't care.
I'm 68. I'm almost... I'm almost fucking 70 years old. Watch out. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye.
Garfield. He just did 35 gold ore. Wow. Now listen to me. Who's shooting fucking bows and arrows?
I have a proposition for people in the town. If you would like gold bars, come to the front
of the castle doors. What is this? What is that? What is... I don't have any...
This gives me diamond armor. Look at all this bread I have. Citizens of the kingdom, please,
if you could come to... The good king is going to give you all bread and let you live. The good
king will shower you with gifts if you are kind and gentle. And you can go about your day as a
peasant in my wonderful kingdom. I have bread. I have 60 bread to the... Kill the person attacking
me, please. I have 60 bread that will go... 20 of which will go to the victor of the trial by combat
we are going to state right now, which, by the way, I have decided two scoops and John Comcast
are going to be in the trial by combat. Please give them diamond armor, diamond swords,
diamond everything. Put them into the pen and let them fight. Whoever wins gets 60 bread.
Bye-bye, entertainment! Trial by combat. The next person that hits me, ban them from the server
permanently. John Comcast and two scoops of the two that will be inside the trial by fucking combat.
Make a pen for me. This is for me to enjoy my entertainment. Anybody that attacks me
just fucking bury them into the ground six feet under for fuck's sake. Trial by combat.
I want a good view. I'll get in my second house. What? What is that? That's concrete.
I haven't found a single iron ore. I'm sorry to hear that. I wonder how long you've been in
the server for. Remember, this is for 60 bread. You could feed a whole community with this for
days. It's for 60 bread. The guards are all still in creative. All guards type this into the chat
slash game mode space survival. Do it. What's wrong with my armor? I'm good. I have fucking
blue pants on. I'm good. We're not in creative. Well, then you tell these fucking pussies.
Get a good view. Two. Oh, well, I'm down here now. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, Godie. Okay. I
just keep. Cad. Cad, give me. Protect me. Protect your king. Oh, God. Gold. Gold. Give me up. Give
me up. Give me up. Give me up. Give me up. Give me up. Give me up. Give me up. Give me up.
Dare you. How dare you, you fucking scumbag. Ow. Where's the box? Where's the box? What happened?
Why did we get teleported? I want everyone in the server at this spot to watch this. Cheater. I
don't even know I cheated. And I want my own throne over here. There's too many wizard cheats.
Nobody's cheating. German is hacking. Oh, for the love of fuck. Get me out of here. Get me out. Just
get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out.
Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out.
Get me out. I'm 71. I have to make it 100. All right. Oh, my God. Why the fuck am I going in
here again? What the fuck? All right. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Also, by the
way, the throne room is under attack. Can one of the guards please go examine what's going on in
the throne room and take care of it, please? Okay. I want two scoops and I want John Comcast
inside of the... You know what? Just start murdering civilians. I'm going back to my throne.
I'm going to my bed. Fuck this. Why is it always devolved into a massacre? Because people
are trying to kill me. You asked us here. All right. Look, I am going to go up to my balcony
and I want a box built here that's big enough for two people to fight in. If you go in that box,
you're dead. I want John Comcast, who's on trial, and two scoops, who's a random fucking person,
to be put in there and fight to the death. Whoever wins gets 35 gold bars. Good luck.
All that... Where's... We can't get back up. To the throne room. To my bedroom. They just...
I have a bed still. What the fuck is this? All right. Amuse me. What's going on with this mic?
I don't know. There are assassins in the castle. Well, don't let... I want a good view. Shit. Get
them away from me. I'm 71 goddamn years old. I'm almost dead in a whole decade. All right. Get
John Comcast and two scoops. Ooh. Oops. Jeremy, you got some nice stuff. Okay.
John Comcast is dead. Fuck it. Do me a favor. What in the name of God is going on right now?
He's right there. Did he die? Jeremy's in creative. I'm not in creative. I'm in fucking
survival. Oblivion mic. Garfield's back. Well, he'll be dead soon when I see him. All right.
How many people have gotten the servant now? What? Holy shit. Holy shit. That was brilliant.
That was absolutely fucking brilliant. But thank God I'm still alive. Wow. That was brilliant.
Good work, but didn't work. Holy fuck. Okay. Well, people are fucking falling down. Somebody made a
death trap and I had diamond armor. Why am I still alive? Put some torches out here, please.
Seriously, because I don't know what the hell's down here. I'm not in creative.
I'm not cheating. I'm not in creative. I swear to God. I have pants and boots on.
Jump twice. See? I have a hunger bar. Look, I can eat and shit. Oh, we need to get back up. How do
we get? We need to get back up there. This is huge. Boots and pants, boots and pants. Yeah. I have
just like a pair of pants on. All right. I'm going up. I'm just going to build up. Fuck it.
Oh, I can get out. How do I? I don't have an axe. Somebody just got killed by a spider.
Wow. That's embarrassing. All right. Get us out of here, Will. Somebody planned this really well,
actually. Oh shit. I'm killing you. I'm sorry. How deep is this shit? Seriously? What the fuck?
What the fuck? Was somebody up here waiting for us? We can't get up. Oh fuck. We're on fire.
Why are we on fire? Who's firing us? Let's go back to the town. That was a reverse stream snipe.
I'm 74 years old. If I turn 100, I'm dead. Oh, I'm right here. All right. No, I'm right here. All
right. Are we ready? What are they in for armor? If I could please be aware. Are they in leather?
Okay. Whoever wins this gets to take 60 bread back to... Why are you taking all your clothes off?
Don't need it. Two scoops thinks they don't need it. Okay. John Comcast and two scoops,
you have been declared trialed by combat. I wish you luck in the wars to come.
Game of Thrones reference. Yeah, Game of Thrones reference. Good luck. Commence the battle. Battle
commencing in five, four, three, two, one. Good luck to them. They want to get 60 bread to take
back to their community and fucking build another pub. Who cares? I think the server crashed.
Dermot's dead. Oh, oh, F exclamation point. Big F on the server. Oh, there we are. And there's two
other people inside of the box. Let's make an incentive. Ah, it's brilliant. Throw food.
I'm only wearing pants? I know. I think we lost everybody. I'm disappointed, Dermot. You're
feeding your Napoleon complex by just cheating at a five-year-old game. You could have embraced your
interjects and put your and your team of corrupt mods have ruined it. OK, fine. Fuck it. All guards,
take off your armor, please. Let's see how much I give a shit about that. Take off. All guards,
take your. OK, fine. Stop the trial. John Comcast is innocent. It was Jonas Bones was the real
culprit. He has returned. Well, get him and John Comcast in the trial by combat. Let them kill
each other. Get them inside of that circle. Jonas Bones and John Comcast, lawyer versus client.
John Comcast did nothing wrong in his face. Do you think his fate? Do you think I care?
He came to your defense and now you're going to have to come to your own
against his blade. Good luck. All right. Are we ready? Jonas bonus versus John Comcast in the
trial by me. All right. Let's start it up. Trial by combat. Can we get some appropriate music for
this, please? John Comcast, you don't scare. You don't stand accused of anything. Jonas made the
tiny thing so you just be banned forever and like fuck you. But we're going to have you fight.
John Comcast, the discernment if you're going to stay in the server permanently or not.
Serial box microphone is really taken off. When I say go, I would like for you to attack each other.
Jonas bonus. Good luck. John Comcast, you're absolutely innocent, but you're just here for
some breathing. Good. Three, one. Commence the battle for my amusement.
One hit. He did it great. John Comcast is the victor of the battle. He hit him once and he died.
I just killed a baby. John Comcast, congratulations.
Put me in here. John Comcast, I'd like to present to you what you have won as a victory prize.
You've won a full at least year supply of bread and Comcast killed the server
right at the exact moment that he died. F in the chat.
My stomach fucking hurts, man. This is so fucking ridiculous. Who would have thought that having
thousands of people connected to the same place was a bad idea. John Comcast, correct. You have won.
Where's John Comcast? Are they back in the server? Jerma, you're feeding your Garfield complex by just
cheating a Garfield year old game. You could have embraced your inner Garfield and rose to the
union. What are you talking about? John Comcast, congratulations. Please take this supply of food
forever. John Comcast is with us again. I would like to go in the box of John Comcast. What the
fuck just happened? Garfield is dead. John Comcast, please take your at least 10 year supply of food
and your 35 gold bars. Congratulations. Nice work. Okay, now fuck off before I change my mind.
I'm 81 years old. It's time for the mods to take their armor off and replace it with leather armor.
This is a stadia server. Get out of here. All king's guards take all of their armor off.
Why did you kill him? There was no reason for him to die. He was in gold armor. How did he die?
Why is there an ear of corn over here? Help me. Help me, please. Help me. Somebody in the box
jumped in the box, tried to kill me. All right, I'm out. Get me out. Seriously. Protect me. Seriously.
Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me. I don't want to. All right, I'm going back in the throne room.
Fuck this. They're revolting. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm going to the throne.
Oh, fuck. People are dead. Oh my fucking god. They're chasing me. I need people
follow me up to the bedroom. How long have you been streaming for? It's been two hours. Holy fuck.
Wait, somebody's in my bedroom. Somebody's in my, I gotta get up. Where are my guards? Where are my
guards? Where are my guards? Where are my guards? The guy, oh, no, no, no, no. You're good. You're
good. I'd like to see that sky. Where's the sky? Okay, all the mods are not, there's only one mod
that's diamond gear. ADHD. I want to see what people have built outside the town. Mods are
corrupt. Let's go take a look. Am I going to die if I do this? Holy shit. No, I'm good. All right.
I want to go see that sky town. That's right. I'm eating bread in front of people that are starving.
What are you going to do about it? All right, man. Hey, man, stand up. Stand up. Stand up. Stand up.
The retired king. Watch behind me. They're fucking fighting me. They're killing me. Help me. Anybody
that's around? Okay, this is like 30. All right, I gotta run. I gotta run. I have to run. I have
to run. The king has to fucking run. Somebody help, please. That's a creeper. That's a creeper.
That's a creeper. Help, help, help, help. I just want to see the cool structures that people may
have built. All right, the corn guy's freaking me out. Just get rid of him. All right, where's
the sky town? I heard, hey, German, there's a cool sky town that's being built. Where is it? I just
want to, I want to see it. I want to see where it is. I want to see what the cool shit people in my
kingdom have been making. He fell for the sky town ruse. Is that for real? It's part of the
farmer's guild. Where is that? No one made anything, German. They were killed by your guards.
They just died. Somebody tried to put something together, but it didn't work. Let me finish it,
motherfucker. This is my statue. Oh my God. What's this? Wait, wait, wait. What's this? What's this?
Oh, what a shit show. I fucking love it. So you are a big stinky. Oh, wow. There's nothing here.
All right. Where's that sky town? I want to find it. Execute them. I don't know. The furnace of
legend. Fire, fire, fire, fire. A lot of damage. A lot of damage. A lot of damage. A lot of damage.
A lot of damage. I want to find the sky town. Guards, please. Where's the sky town? Is it well
hidden? It's at 600 and 1700. I don't know what the hell that means. Oops. Well, there's F3.
What is it? What was the coordinates? People are trying to fucking kill me.
Oh my God. I'm on fire. I'm going to die. I'm actually going to die.
660. And what was the other one? 7-1. 660-500. 61700. 61700. Really? I'm going to go find this
shit. You guys went far away. Damn. 1700. That's like a fucking thousand years away.
I think I see it. Is that it over there? All right. People are throwing grenades.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. I'm coming in. Why do I not have pants on? What the fuck am I
doing? I don't have a helmet on. Why? Stop him. Stop him. Stop him from doing that. Whoever it is.
I'm 91. I'm dead in like fucking April. Bring in more players. Should we open it up one more time?
I'm 91. I'm going to die in less than... I have to see the Sky Kingdom. How do I get in? How do I
get into the Sky Kingdom? This is actually kind of cool. There's a whole little community over here.
It's all this. Look at this. Baked Lays. The Sour Tower property of Snoozencopter and the King
IG. Oh, it's Snoozencopter's house. What the fuck? Really? Holy shit. Baby blood's on your hands.
Support our rightful king, Grill. Get rid of that. How did you guys do this? Get these
burgers. Don't even think about it. Community mine. What? Holy shit. You guys have been doing
this the whole time. Oh my god. You guys have been building this. Open the server one more time.
Dump water down there. Look at this. This is insane. So you guys have not even have been fighting.
You've been making a little community over here. Well, that's nice. Donate iron for buckets so we
can eat. Here. You guys did a lot of work. Take this. I got something for you. Oh fuck. Uh oh.
Oh shit. Uh oh. Food. Food for the... Don't even fucking... Oh my god. Get him. Don't. What is
horse armor? Holy shit. It's like we doubled the amount of people in the server. Germa dumb and a
stupid butt. That's funny. Where's the actual... The whitelist is fucked. Yeah, the whitelist didn't
work the whole stream. It was a Twitch API problem and now it's zero. Now it's fucked. Kill Germa.
Oblivion DLC? Not quite. All right. Get me in the sky tower before this stream dies.
Everywhere you go you bring a mass murder and destruction. Leave the village. I'm sorry. I just
couldn't see the cool things people did. My kill baby is no more here but from the truth. All right.
My child's grave. Starved to death. Holy shit. Uh. Germa. Your mom says hi. Hi mom. If you just have
all this stuff I don't care. We gotta give this shit. Just have it up. So am I actually... Holy
shit. Wow. Now I know where half the server has been. Are you serious? That's awesome. What?
Now set it on fire. No, but actually don't. I didn't reach the sky fort. No, I didn't. I don't
even know where the sky fort is. Yeah, where is it? I saw it already. There it is. Up here.
Just TP to it. All right. TP me to the sky fort. I want to see it. Is that it right there? That's
it right there. Okay. Hold on. This is it. I've seen this. Dude, look at the crops. It's so fucked.
There was a lot of weed there and it's now empty. I'm 96. I'm almost dead. I don't see anything.
What are you talking about? Dude, weed? I don't know. What do you mean? Shoot him. Uh, I need...
I'm 102. I'm technically dead. I'm fucking 100. I died a long painful death. Cheater.
I have a half a heart. I'm fucked. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I was cheating?
No, I was not. Rebels be like fort. Fork runner. No killing. No stealing. No rebels. Long
reign for 10,000 years. Is this heaven? Where the fuck am I? I have no idea where I am.
Where am I now? Oh, people have pens of animals already. I'm dead. I died. Fuck. Did you make
all this in two hours, two hours, two hours? And you could actually get all this done and
nice work. Holy shit. That's very little. Well, considering how many times the server crashed,
let me see what else you got down here. We're starving. Yeah. Not really. I want to see what's
down here. Quarry for cobble. You guys have been busy. All the bullshit we were doing in the castle.
You guys were playing Minecraft over here the whole time. Wow. Seriously. Nice work. Am I going
to open up the server? Well, we're going to pull the data from and first of all, the whitelist
didn't work. So that's another thing that there was no whitelist pretty much. This goes down
really fucking far. We did this today to make sure that we got info of people connecting to the
server. We're going to save it the way it is and we're going to do this again. Don't tell anybody
there's anything down here, but look what's down here. There was only one way we could test anything
that was doing it. That's the only way. This is huge by the way. Breaking with bread. So this was
actually probably the reals versus yesterday and the day before. So what, what was our max amount
of people in the server? 200, 400, 300, 200 something. So now we know for next time what we
can do. Uh, yeah, just take email. Discord Mike. It should be 2000. Well, that's a lot harder than
it looks because getting even two or 300 people in the same server is insane. It's only 108. Somebody
just kill them. Don't worry. I'll take care. Just play RuneScape instead. I'm jumping off a building.
Sunset. So what a beautiful do what? Well, some of you did a great community here.
Hide and the server crashed like 10 times. So we got what we needed for data. Thanks for
participating because this is probably what we're going to call it. So if we do this again,
we're going to make sure that we have the whitelisting in place next time. We were like 10
minutes away from, but I was like, no, fuck it. Let's just do it. Who cares? I didn't even give
a shit. How did us, how did you, a spider get into kingdom? Yeah. I think we learned a lot from this
stream. So that's good. So I will see you guys tomorrow. We're going to, we're going to pull as
much as we can from this and try to see this as like another stress test, essentially.
The microphone. We'll figure it. Did I name the kingdom? I didn't even name the kingdom. It's
called no. Yeah, I did. We're going to save everything that's here now. And next time we're
going to try four different things. I want to do this at least one more time and then hopefully
we can have, why am I getting attacked by, stop attacking me. What's going on? Prove it's not
creative. I'm dying right now. I'm being literally killed right now. I'm dead. Don't cheat. I'm not
cheating. Next time. No cheating. I get to still be 108 years old, but you still owe me for crashing
my jet pack and GTA castle. Oh, the server's dead. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That'll be it for tonight.
Uh, those of you that got to participate, uh, we were minutes away from canceling the stream,
but thanks for stress testing this and putting this in a, uh, in a position where we can figure
out things we can do to put in place to make it a little bit. Yeah. If you want to, here's the
people that are literally sitting trying to make this whole thing work. I had fun at least for the
first couple hours. Let's see if we can get some more bugs ironed out and let's try this again.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow. Tomorrow afternoon. Thanks for participating in the
experiment in the stress test. We'll see what we can do with it next week. Fix Mike tomorrow.
Don't worry. Mike's going to be back to normal. Good night guys. Thank you again.
Sorry for the late start. See you tomorrow. The bits and the subs. I will do those tomorrow
because I'm not. So I don't have access to the information, right? We'll go with the bits and
subs tomorrow. Tomorrow after the stream. I'm not currently live from my own home.
We're at a mobile studio right now. Nerf the guards.
I told you we were going to have to do like a test of this to see how it worked out.
I still had fun. I thought it was fucking funny. The mod should wear chain mail. Yeah.
We'll do that next time. Good night though. We'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for participating. See you soon. Take care.