Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerba here with Scare Saturday. It's Tuesday. It's Tuesday. I'm sorry everybody.
I know you've been waiting for the last couple weeks since I went to PAX for a Scare Saturdays video, and I have not been able to deliver that.
And I could give you a bunch of excuses, but I'm not going to do that right now. We're just going to transition into the actual video of me playing Slender the Arrival.
If you don't know what this game is, it's sort of a graphical reworking of the original Slender game, the indie game.
And this one is not free though. This one is actually 10 bucks for the digital download. Link will be in the description if you want to go play it.
It's pretty scary. It's pretty ridiculous, as you'll see in this video. So take care everybody. I'll see you all soon.
I think I say that at the end of the video, but it's okay. Here comes Scare Saturdays, Scare Tuesdays, whatever it's called. Here we go!
Dr. Pepper. Wait a minute. This is a sprite. This is not a Dr. Pepper. That means we're already in trouble. Oh my God.
That actually just scared the shit out of me. Okay, let's get started. Slender the Arrival.
There's like a little intro here too. I love how I'm just like skipping. Like, it's cool how it has a counter in the top right too.
Tells you how long you've been playing for. Little pretty woods. Alright, this is daytime. This is nothing, man.
If I see Slender, I'll kick him in the nuts right now. I got plenty of daylight.
I'm gonna follow the path because it's the only thing here. I'm gonna skip down the path.
Alright, I've just been like skipping down this road for a couple minutes, and we're getting darker and darker and darker.
Apparently in this universe, we go from day to night in like 15 seconds. It's like super sunset. What the hell is going on?
Kind of looks like my house. Not gonna lie. That's even creepier. You flip-flop the garage and you have my house.
Chairs. Pen. Paper. Open. Another table. Some type of pamphlet.
Honoring the life of Beth Hayes. Dad, your scrapbook can be viewed later. Okay.
Ooh, the flashlight. Yeah, that's what I'm talking about, baby. Blinding light. You don't really need that right now.
It looks like a bed of some sort. A couple of vases, vases. Vases, vases. You can open the windows.
Let's get some air in here. I just fought it. Is this a room down here? Unlock the door. Can you see it?
Escape. So I have to make it to like the thing. This room is really freaky, by the way. It's all the notes.
Alright, so I have to escape. So there he is. There's Mr. Slender. There's like the Finn Man, whatever his name is.
Alright, get me out of this room. To the woods. To the woods. We go. You don't have to scream, man. Go to the woods.
And now there's drawings all over the wall. Let's go. Tent down here.
Hopefully you're not sleeping because I'm gonna come like open your tent. Don't look or it takes you.
And it begins. And it begins. And it begins. Page one of eight. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Abandoned house, it looks like. Let's get in there. I hate being in these enclosed off areas, though, because this son of a bitch will disappear around a corner and snatch me up.
Anybody on the dumper? Come on. There's got to be a note in here somewhere. No, no. Where's the note? Where's the note?
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? He's behind me right now. We'll come back to this. I can't turn around right now.
Wait a minute. Where is he? What's going on? Hello, sir. Hello, ma'am. Where is he?
Where the hell is he? I can't even. I don't know. I can't see anything. I don't know where he is.
Son of a bitch. You really screwed up my game here. Dickhead slender man.
There's another note right here. I only have one note right now, and he's legitimately right behind my ass.
Help me. Yep. Help me is the real one. You should be saying me.
Oh, my God. Don't turn around. Just don't turn around. If I turn around, I die.
Holy. He must be right up my ass. Whoa. No, he's right there.
Oh, no. I don't even know what direction I'm going. I'm stuck in a tree.
No, go back. Keep going this way. Keep going this way. I do not want to run into that son of a bitch again.
Man, they made like the noises and like the screen shaking and stuff so much worse.
There is that him right there. I wish I could just see my face right there.
Oh, shit. Is there more than one? Is there more than one slender man?
What is that? A light is a light right here. He found something new, found something new.
This is a car. Is there a note? It's got to be a note.
Oh, he's huge. He's enormous in this game. He's like 15 feet tall. He's like a giant.
I'm stuck. I'm stuck right here, right here. This is that.
Oh, this is that stupid lighthouse that I'm shaking around in my chair.
Didn't even have a chance to look down here. There has to be a note. There it is.
Four pages, baby. Let's do it. Come on. Keep it up. Keep it up. Keep it up. Keep it up. Keep it up.
Head down this way. I probably missed a note on like a couple of the things I ran into already because I'm a little baby.
Nice waterfront. It's very pretty. Where? There's a note. There's a note. There's a note. Give it to me.
Five out of eight. Stuck. Stuck. I'm stuck. He's right next to me right now.
Help me. Help me.
I needed to take that drink. My throat was so dry. I don't know where to go. My whole life is in a daze right now.
There has to be a note in this room. I don't know how I've missed it that many times.
That many times.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, if you liked Slender, Slender the Arrival is like a better version of Slender.
It's more ridiculous, better graphics. I don't even know. I probably, the campaign, I probably am like stuck on the campaign right here.
This might not even be the campaign. I don't know. But I'm scared. I'm dying right now and I need a drink.
Take care, everybody. That's all I can do.