Hey, I'm gonna do a wheelie. I'm just gonna let you laugh. Hey, Jerma. Start game. Private slots max. Jerma! Jerma! Jerma!
What? Invite me. I haven't made the game yet. The hemogloba chopper is down here. Wow, I haven't played this game forever.
We definitely should not be running to this, by the way, because it's gonna take us ages. I just gotta get to Hibachapa.
Hey, I dare you to turn around. I dare you to turn around and shoot Spoon with that shotgun.
Hey! Hey! No! No! No! You flipped on my screen and just stood back up. Yeah, me too.
I love you. Shoot Jerma. No, don't shoot me. Shoot Jerma. Shoot him in the back of the face. No! No! Don't!
He told me to! Yeah! What is this guy? Oh my god, that's a chopper.
Dude, there was like a freaking hole and I gotta look at this guy. This guy was in like winter clothing. Maybe it's winter.
No, it's like nice out right now. This guy is in a full winter hat. That just whizzed by my screen.
Alright, the game is on. No, I'm sorry, I hit the helicopter. Do you think you can get me in this car?
Don't run me over. Oh no! I think I can get you, yeah. I didn't mean to do that. I'm so sorry, Spoon.
Wait, you want to run in the car and I chase you down onto Helichoop? Yeah, let's see if you can get me.
Here, you can start going. Alright, I'm gonna go this way. Here we go.
Oh god! Oh, you have it? Yeah, I got a chopper. You gotta get in the car and you gotta escape the chopper.
Alright, we're in one in the airfield. You're never gonna get me because it's the best car in the game.
Okay. I'll get in my own car. You're probably not gonna find one. I'm gonna find one.
Just wait until I play the music in my head of me like chasing you down.
How am I gonna hear it in your head, Jerma? I found a bike. Don't worry, I got this. Don't run me over.
I'll sell another fit. Oh jeez. I didn't hear the music. Oh man, this is weird.
Are you in the chopper right now? Yes. Oh jeez. Oh jeez.
It's pretty weird to be in the chopper.
He's going to crash without us even being there.
Where are you? I'll do it.
How high are you? Why are you that high in the air? I don't know, what do I do?
Hold S, hold S. Hold S, S. No, no, don't hold it down.
Wow. I'm never listening to you again. I didn't mean to like hold S until you die.
You still hold S. Yeah, but that means that's like how to like descend.
Not like just hold until I die. I'm ready for you to go.
Here comes the chase scene.
Why are you faster than me? This is not cool.
I'm going to get you.
How are you faster than a helicopter going, listen to this plane.
I was looking the other way.
Am I still alive? I'm still alive.
Here, I'll give you a ride back to the helicopters. Thanks.
Get in. Or not.
We're so bad at this. Every time we try to organize something and do something special.
I'm going to get the helicopter and you guys just go anywhere and I'll chase you for the rest of the time we're playing and you will die.
Spoon, why are you on fire? Because I'm just cool like that.
You want me to land on the ambulance? Yeah, try to land right on like the flat part of the ambulance.
We need to like hang out. Even if I have like a tea party on the top of the ambulance.
That was so lame.
That just looked like you jumped into bed.
This is a mattress and you just like jumped into bed like ah.
That was so anticlimactic.
Oh, no. Stop blocking me.
All right. You guys want to have like a sumo wrestling fight up here? Yeah, sure.
Whoever gets like knocked off the ambulance loses.
Spoon, you ready? Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Get in, cousin.
Please don't take Gatling gun helicopter.
No, I didn't take the Gatling gun helicopter. You know what?
No, please. No, please. It's my favorite.
You ain't going to get shit.
Oh, good job, cousin.
I'm not sure. Oh, shit.
Wrong button.
Don't ask me that. Don't.
I don't understand how this makes any sense.
It's still there.
Why? Why is it still there?
I got to destroy it.
Why did you destroy mine?
I'm going to get it. Come on.
Yes.
I got it.
I am the victor.
All right, Spoon, I'm picking you up.
No way. I got a helicopter.
Is that? Oh, it's respawned.
It's respawned. It's respawned.
Operation, do not let him get it.
Destroy it.
I don't think you. I can't. I can't.
I'm missing.
I'm missing my line up here.
He said crash into him.
Yes.
I'm on his tail.
For Niko.
Come here.
We are seriously like birds fighting in the air.
I'm going to get you. It's going to happen.
No.
You son of a bitch.
I'm actually figuring out how to fly like this.
You can actually control it. Oh my God.
You got it?
I just have to wait for it to turn.
You are like a cheap
$10 RC helicopter
right now.
Look at what I got for Christmas today.
It's like if I hold
the trigger, when it turns
in the direction I want to go, it moves that way.
I can't believe you are still
flying this thing. This is unbelievable.
No, he's going to have my view.
I'm trying to follow him.
Oh, that was not. That was a bad move.
What?
Get him. Die.
Did he crash? I had to reload.
He's reloading.
He's right here. He's right here. You got a chance.
Niko, come with me. I'm reloading.
Take cover.
You're down, final boss.
Get him.
Oh, geez. Oh, God.
Run.
Oh, no. I got hit by a cousin.
That was terrifying.
And I got out. I'm out. I'm fine.
Die.
Did you just jump out?
Why did you do that?
I thought I could land on
the building and be fine, but my dick slammed
into it and I kept falling.