Alrighty, so let's get rid of this disgusting, horrible floor.
Do I even have a shovel?
I got a crappy stone shovel.
Let's go down one more so I can...
Oh god, I forgot I did that.
It's okay, it's okay.
We are going to look top shelf in no time.
Look at this.
Oh my goodness.
Looks good, looks good.
So now my house will not look like a prison cell.
Actually prison cells are not typically on dirt.
At least in this country, at least in the United States.
Prison cells are... ah, damn it.
Oh well.
I'm not even going to have enough.
I've got a bunch of trees and everything.
At least it'll be enough to get half the house.
So I have jury duty tomorrow.
If any of you know what jury duty is, it's not a fun thing.
So for those of you that are younger,
or for those of you that are not from the United States,
jury duty essentially is...
Okay, somebody gets in trouble, right?
Somebody breaks the law.
Somebody like, let's say like Steve Dickinson
throws a rock through Mary J. Stevenson's window.
So he gets arrested and they put him on trial.
And what has to happen is there has to be a jury of his peers.
So there has to be a jury of people that are not lawbreakers
that are sitting on the jury.
They don't have to be non-lawbreakers,
but they have to at least be sane individuals.
So I got a call.
I got a thing in the mail that says,
hey, you're one of these people that needs to be on the jury.
And what we have to do is determine
if the guy that threw the rock through the window is actually guilty.
And sometimes it can last a long time.
Sometimes you have to come back multiple days.
And it really, really, really stinks.
I really don't want to do it.
But it's against the law to not do it.
So if I don't do it, let's say I just don't go tomorrow,
I'll get arrested.
They will literally come to my house and arrest the crap out of me.
But that's what I'm doing tomorrow.
If any of you have ever had to do jury duty,
I'd like to know about your experience,
if you're old enough, because I'm pretty certain
you have to be at least 18 to...
You have to be at least 18 to be allowed to be a juror.
So let me know what experience you had.
If any at all.
Now I'm going to go back and get those trees that I missed before.
Oh, look at that.
The sun is setting.
What a perfect time to leave the house.
And I still haven't made a bed.
Oh, my God.
I have enough wool, right?
That is priority numero uno when I get back,
is to make a damn bed.
This is not a good idea.
I probably should just turn back and make a bed.
That's what I'm going to do.
All right, give me this wood.
A couple of pieces is all it's going to take.
Three pieces to be exact.
All right, let's make this my floating work benches.
It's like this, right?
I believe it is.
It doesn't matter what wool you use.
Excellent.
Okay, so here's my bedroom over here.
This is going to be the sleeping quarters.
Right there.
All right, so now I have a spawn point,
and I have a place where I...
Okay, this is great.
This is fantastic.
I am very, very happy about this.
So let's skip this stupid nighttime business.
Monsters can't get through sand, right?
I hope not.
Any holes?
Do I have any holes in my house?
I will just get woken up and get murdered.
All right.
Good night.
Good morrow.
I will see you all tomorrow, everyone.
Good night.
Do, do, do, do, do.
Oh, well, that was quick.
What?
Speed sleep.
Minecraft.
You know, I'm going to fix a couple of things first and foremost.
I want to make my house a little nicer looking.
I don't want to have it be this jagged mess
of, like, sharp objects pointing out.
Get rid of this.
Get rid of these.
They're just eyesores.
Not going to have any of that on Jerma's castle.
Close this up after I do this, of course.
Where's the cobblestone?
There it is.
All right.
Cobblestone.
Where's the wall?
There it is.
Okay.
So it needs to go over here.
Right there, right there, right there, right there.
Didn't I just delete all that?
Oh, well.
At least it doesn't look like a complete mess.
There we go.
Knock you out of the way.
So I have a actual wall rather than a mess of crap.
Okay.
Oh, well, look at this.
Look at this.
Get the wood off of the edge of this house
and replace it with a stone
and then make the rest of the floor.
I don't even need trees.
There are a lot of misplaced blocks in this house.
Like, look at it.
Just look back.
I just got rid of most of the wood.
And look at this giant horror.
Look at how terrible this was.
You guys in the comments were right.
This house was an absolute horror show.
And I knew that.
But I was going to deny it until the day I died.
Let's start to fill in the blanks here a little bit.
If I can jump up here.
Okay.
So this is the wall.
Okay, good.
That's the, yeah.
Well, I'm going to have to flood the entire basement.
I'm going to have to deal with it.
Oh, no, my bed.
I'm going to get wet sheets.
The reason why I'm doing this, I'm making three rooms.
At least for the start.
I'm going to have this big long room behind the bedroom.
Then next to the bedroom is going to be the workstation area.
And then that's pretty much the three rooms I want to work with.
At least for right now.
Let's plug this up.
All right.
Actually, I probably should do it like this.
Makes a little bit more sense that way.
Come on, get over there.
Get over there, Michael Phelps.
Let's go.
If anybody got that joke, I applaud you.
Give me this.
All right, let's put these down now.
This is the right level, though.
My brain just exploded.
I thought I was like two or three blocks up from where I actually was.
Oh, damn it.
I was.
I actually was like a block.
Oh, God, bear with me.
Okay, let's try this again.
Much better.
I don't want to waste them all here, though,
because I have an entire room that needs to be finished.
This one right here.
Oh, look at that.
This room is now done with the floor.
I'm going to take down that little piece in a minute here.
This ground looks like some...
Oh, it just looks terrible.
I can't even give you a description.
It looks that bad.
This bed can stay there.
Actually, no, it can't.
I want to move it,
because I want this wall to come down like this
and have this opening right here.
Let's get rid of the sand for crying out loud.
All right, so now here's my thought.
Ready?
So this is the main room, right?
After I get rid of this,
can I even get rid of that without...
Okay.
So here's the main room.
I want to be able to do all my crafting,
do all my dog training.
All that stuff is going to be in this room.
Move this out of the way.
Might as well bring these things down now, right?
Because they've been floating in space for way too long.
Okay.
Get this off.
Probably should not be using this nice pickaxe to do it,
but I'll use a sapling.
That's not going to work, is it?
Maybe it is, but very slowly.
Come on now.
I know you can do it.
You can do it.
Come on now.
Come on.
It's up there.
Oh, I destroyed it.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
All it took was...
Jeez.
All right.
I do not want that to happen with that.
So I'll figure that out in a second.
Breaking my stuff.
So I want this whole line to be furnaces.
So let's go like this.
Put that there.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Did I break that too?
No, that's right there.
Okay.
This here.
Put my stuff that I almost just threw up.
My slime ball.
These are apparently worth a lot.
What the hell?
What was that?
What's hitting me?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
I'm starving to death.
I really...
Why did I just eat that?
I could have just cooked that and got like full health.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Chalk One Up for Jerma is really an idiot because I thought there was a monster in the ground
or something.
I was actually just starving to death.
My goodness gracious.