Hey, sorry, I just like accidentally slammed. Sorry for slamming. Hi. Hey, how are you?
You're late, I know. Yeah, I may have uh, I may have really, really overshot the hole. I'm gonna
fix my sleep schedule in 12 hours thing, but I got close. I got really close. You know I got close
because there's absolutely no way there'd be a stream at like 12 30 specific if I didn't get
close. So I got close. We're not starting, it's not four. Another reason why we're starting um,
three to four hours early and typically about the 4 p.m plus time period is because today is going
to be a double header. We're going to play Mario Golf for a little while to pretend that I don't
just play Elden Ring. It's a way for people to scroll by and see German985 currently live
playing Mario Golf. Okay, all right. He's cool. He's variety, right? Like it's, I don't, I mean,
I'm not going to click on that, but I know he's doing it. We're in EU. Is EU? Yeah, is that what
I mean? It's for people to understand that I don't just play Elden Ring and then we're going to play
Elden Ring. So this is just for the scrollers, the first like four or five hours of the stream.
I'm going to take a break, a real break, one that I don't, I don't think I've ever done on this channel.
I have never done what I'm going to do today. So I'm very, very, I'm very intrigued to see how this
works. Somewhere in the next four or five hours, I'm going to put up the BRB screen with some text
on it saying that I'll be back in like 20 to 30 minutes. We're going to do a legit 20 minute break
halfway through here. We're going to come back somewhere around that, whatever that is,
and do Elden Ring for the rest of the night. Your views are going to plummet. I mean, yeah,
they are. Of course they are. But this will be a good, this is a nice little science experiment,
don't you think? I'm very curious how this works. Intermission Andy. Yeah. So we're going to do about
four or five hours now and then four or five hours later, bringing us to an Omega time period
of about 10 hours or so today. Maybe less, maybe more, depending. I also have to get ready for the
streamer awards because I haven't even prepared at all. So this will be the last stream you see
on this channel for a little while. I will be at the streamer awards. You can watch it. I'm sure
you'll be able to pick me out of the crowd at some point. I will be there. So as of today,
I will see you on this channel after today, next week. Oh, fucking Poggies. Yeah. Poggies. Poggies.
All right. I'm going to have no cam on because this is the first time in like three weeks that
I've been able to have no shirt on when I stream. So I'm going to, I'm doing that. I'll have a cam
on Elden Ring. When I take my break, I'll put a shirt on. So you're going to deal with no cam for
like, I don't know, however long I pretend to play Mario golf. Oh, also somebody bet me something in
chat. The person that said, Hey dude, play Mario golf is the same person that also said, if you
don't give this game at least a seven out of 10, ban me for a month. What I said is, I mean,
you're kind of already going up against some pretty intense odds considering that all the Mario sports
games are like five or sixes. I mean, like I think I'm going to give this a seven. I don't know if
you're going to get a seven out of this. That's a bad take. Well, at least in the last 10 years,
Mario Sonic and Olympic games, was that a six? What was it? Let's be real. Let's go. Come on.
Let's be honest. What, what would, what would you give a score to Mario and Sonic at the Olympic
games? What is it? Is it a six or a seven? It's a five, seven for nostalgia. Okay. But that doesn't
count. It'd be probably a six. It was a six for the Wii. Okay. All right. What's, what's the last
Mario sports game? Mario tennis for the Switch. That's like a six. That was like a 6.5. I'm seeing
a lot of sevens. I'm seeing a lot of sixes and sevens. So how is that a bad take when it's
everybody's take in the chat? Besides like, at least like, ow. No, you can't put stuff in the Wii.
You guys keep forgetting the Wii is more than, the Wii is like fucking 15 years old now.
I'm talking about like current gen and a little bit of last gen, like the last five to 10 years.
You give me a Mario sports game that was like a nine. Not gonna happen. They're fun. They're not
bad games. What about Mario Strikers? Yeah, that game's fantastic. I'm looking forward to the next
one. That might, that actually might be the first like Mario sports game in five to 10 years.
That actually is like a nine for me. It could be. That game was absolutely unbelievable.
Mario Strikers charged. Honestly, I think my opinion just soured just based on
my Mario tennis. Like right now on my screen, I just see Mario with a tennis racket.
That's fucking infuriating me. That's a tennis racket and I'm pissed off about it.
Anytime Mario wears regular clothes, just like that aren't his overalls and his shirt,
like when he wears like just like pants, like suit pants, it pisses, I get mad because I know
it's either a tennis game or a golf game. I'm already mad. All right, maybe I should stop.
Jesus Christ. All right, what should I do? I don't want to like do all this. I want to like
play golf. I'm just gonna play golf. I know there's like an RPG mode in this game, right?
Do I really want to do that? I'll go do golf adventure. I'm not playing ranked. Golf adventure.
Okay, so I have to make a me. Is that how this works? There I am. I'm already made.
Dominant hand is set to right. Yeah, that's fine. How do you blonde hair? I don't know. I made it
in 10 seconds. The scan lines. Why the scan line? Oh, it's on TV. Hey, you turn it off at the worst
possible time. Erdo. Oh, it looked like Mario just won. Isn't that the end of the tourney?
Did you see how he won? That was ridiculous. I need to see a replay, some slow mo. Don't I
beat the shit out of these people on a daily basis? Why would they be? Why are they like fans of mine?
Okay. Oh, sorry, Chuck. But remember the welcome ceremony tomorrow is more important than watching
TV. He he he Berto is right. We should all get some good sleep tonight. I feel like we're going
to need it. Thank you. How wonderful to have at least one sensible rookie in the house.
Oh, these are players. Okay, I thought they were just like people watching.
I'll sleep just fine. What about you? I didn't even know ghosts could sleep. You don't just
fall through the bed. Chuck, I feel like that's a rude question to ask a ghost. Anyway, I guess
I'll go to bed too. I want to make a good impression at the welcome ceremony tomorrow.
That's a good idea, dear. I know you're hoping to be one of the standouts in this rookie class.
Gosh, you can't out drive me. Sorry, Toadette, but you're always going to be playing catch up
to the real heavy hitters. Ha ha ha. Excuse me. You can't always win with power alone. You know,
you've got to keep a level head and no one to lay up. Happy Gilmore would say otherwise.
You've got both in wrong. Finesse is the name of the game.
Who's this guy? Oh, it's me. It feels weird. I feel like I'm in a sims house. Right. Oh,
it's you. We've been waiting for you. Come join us, please. Everyone, please allow me to introduce
the final rookie in your group. Jeremy. Who's that? You're a rookie too? How much did you
over here? I mean, nice to meet you. It's the golf association called to let us know that one more
rookie would be arriving late. Now they're here. All right. All right. So how far can you drive it,
Rook? You want to tee it up and see? Don't mind Chuck. He's got an oversized driver for a brain.
Come on, everyone. You'll be all learning together. You guys wanted me to play the fucking
RPG mode. It's gonna take like four hours to get started. I could have already driven the ball
400 yards by now. The name's charging Chuck. I hit the long ball. Boom. Don't matter where it goes.
As long as it goes far giddy up. I'm Toadette. It's great to meet another student of the game.
I hope we can all learn from each other. I'm boo. Boo. He he. Edit any other characters that
every human on earth has seen more than a thousand times that we need introductions for.
I'm being really like rude to this game. All right. Yeah, I'm out of here. I got a lift anyway.
If you want to hit up the green, your biceps got to be mean. While I was on my way to bed,
the most important thing for strong muscles is recovery. Wait, we do like exercises?
I don't understand the obsession with muscles that seems to plague those of you with physical
bodies. Anyway, off to bed. He he he. It's quite a crew we have. What am I thinking? You must be
exhausted. Why don't you head to your room and get some rest? I'm Birdo, the camphouse mama.
You can even call me mama if you want. I wanted to go. Okay. Now your room is the one in the back.
We've got the we've got a big welcome ceremony tomorrow. Go get rest. R1, R1, R1, R1. Oh, this
is Charging Chuck's room. What's in there? I'm just going to bed. You know what? All right. I
got to be very honest with everybody here. Maybe incredibly honest. I don't care about any of this
lore. I don't care at all. Zero. I don't want to knock on everybody's door and see what like what
they're doing. I don't I don't care. I just don't. I'm sorry. Does that make me like a bad person
for not caring about the storyline in Mario Golf? I just want to drive a ball hard. Meet
the manager in the front of the clubhouse. They're your friends? They're not my friends. I just moved
in. I just moved in five seconds ago. These people don't know who I am. I'm in Boo's room.
Let's Charging Chuck up too. You know what? I do I will commend companies like Nintendo and other
companies that have tried to make just hey let's play golf a better more interesting kind of fun
experience rather than just what you know just turning around at the tee and driving the ball
out of bounds like a thousand yards the wrong way and then literally turning the game off because
that's what I've done at every golf game I've ever played. Hope you're feeling rested. Did you get a
good night's sleep? I did. Oh good. I didn't wake you because you seemed like you really needed the
rest but now you're running late for the welcome ceremony. Head outside and straight down the road.
Hurry! Why is it pointing there? Okay wait. R1. R1. R1. Just one more thing. Everyone in town knows
that we have a new class of rookies starting out so you'll have a lot of eyes on you and expect some
pretty high expectations. Let's put your best foot forward. All right. I better not turn all the way
100 180 degrees in the wrong direction and drive. I shouldn't do that. Bonnie Greens. It's ugly.
This place is filled with talented rookies but let's pump the brakes a bit. Not everyone can be
a star on day one. Let's give these. What's wrong with this? Something's wrong. It's something
a bit like the aliasing. This is this is looks off. Why does it look so wrong? Is it like the
anti-aliasing? Dude the rookie everyone's talking about right? Bonnie Green says world-class
practicing courses. Okay. I honestly like I this is a difference than the other Nintendo games.
Usually the aliasing doesn't look this bad. Nice to meet you. I'm the head coach. All right. Let's
do the ceremony. A 3090. I'm not I'm on a switch right now dude. Come on. Okay. Everyone's here
coach. Welcome rookies. Clearly all you know the story history but a minor never hurts. Bonnie
Green's golf village is the birthplace of countless legendary golfers. Yeah. Hope you all realize how
lucky you are to get a chance to write your own chapter in the Bonnie Green story. I'm the clubhouse
manager here and it's my pleasure to welcome you to this rookie class. Now you just met our head
coach. He has a lot to offer so I hope you all take his lessons. After all he's launched the careers of
several top players. Hey thanks for that. Now you're all here for a reason. You've got the raw
talent to make it in life. That doesn't mean it can be easy. I'll help you make sure you make it all.
Very well then I'll go ahead and pass these out. This is a golf watch. Rookies it'll track your
stats, record your scores, and a whole lot more. Come on get one. George and Chuck. That's me with
my watch. I hear you drive the ball a little bit. Let's see if we can't teach you some control. I
feel like I'm an AI reading this. Control? That gonna help me hit it farther? I want to play as
that guy. Just smash the A button. I don't care. I don't care about these guys getting their watches.
I just want my watch. I hear you're a real prodigy but rough around the edges. Just like the fairway
I guess. Just made that up. All right that's enough for intros. Go ahead and slap those new golf
watches on your wrists. Can I get the golf watch on? Your data is already in there. Like magic,
just press on and make sure it looks right. The first screen that comes up should be pretty basic.
It shows the different aliens you can turn into. This one's a small alien and can get in small
places and has a high pitched voice. This one is a big strong alien but sometimes it's hard to tell
which one you're going to get. Just smash it and just be a good tv show. Don't worry about all the
advanced functions right now okay. Now I'm going to go over the badge system. No no badge system.
Okay this is actually kind of cool. You see where it says steel badge? One day when you reach the
top it might say platinum instead. Okay I can go 160 yards. All right so you play tournaments,
this training, this is leveling up. Yeah that's cool. New member of the team. It's Toad. Hey
everyone I'm Toad. I've been looking forward to this for quite a long time. Golf is more popular
than ever in the Mushroom Kingdom. Wasn't that tourney yesterday incredible? But if we want to
keep the sport interesting we need some green players you see. And I just don't need folks who
can hit the green. Oh whoa wait. This is crazy. That's all I had to do was like just clear my
throat. We need some fresh faces on the leaderboards. That's where you all come in. We've scouted each
of you for your special talents. Maybe you're a big star. That wasn't even a bad impression.
You know how bad all Toad impressions are? Never mind. Who's my caddy? Have you guys noticed
that all the Mario characters have gotten regular voices except for that guy?
All the Mario characters are like whoa hey. And now but this guy's still
they've never changed it. It's always been that. Oh nice. All right time to play.
I went up the golf watch. I don't need the golf watch. All right let's go meet the caddy.
Hi yes I'm Jeremy. I've been waiting for you. All right so you're my caddy so just tell me what
clubs to use. Okay I'm here for the package. Yes you don't have any idea what I'm talking about
do you? I'm here to give you your first set of clubs. They're already customized perfectly. Okay
now when you're playing around here you'll be chasing after your ball and your own two legs
no carts. I did see that from the trailer. That's probably going to be the fun part of the game.
We won't load you up with a full set of 14 clubs. I only need three. I never understood all the
multiple clubs thing in golf. Give me the driver, the putter, and the pitching wedge. That's all I
need. That's all you're going to see me play with. All right that's enough for me. Go ahead and strap
on the bag. You got a set of golf clubs. Okay cool. All right I want I need a huge driver.
Do you guys remember the commercials? Those big huge like titanium rod in the middle drivers.
They were it was an infomercial for them all the time and that shit was illegal to play within
tournaments. As the driver master 400 El Diablo driver or something right? And these things they
were you couldn't use them in tournaments. You couldn't use them like and play with them in a
actual setting. The thing was like it was almost a foot long and it had this huge piece of titanium
in the middle and it was like guaranteed to like it was like a corked bat. I used to see that
commercial all the fucking time. You physically couldn't even play with it unless you like were
just driving with like you know the funny somebody dickhead friends in the driving range. Satan
driver. I swear to god it was something like that. All right so I'm just gonna go this way.
Take some lessons. All right here we go. I'm ready. Let's go. You want to review the basics
of hitting a shot. I mean I kind of need to know what I'm doing. All right that aims. That aims.
Yep yep yep. That shows the overhead view. Very cool. The inner circle shows where the ball will
Okay and then the translucent outside border shows where it will roll. Okay some of the shots carry
and run equals its total distance. Distance is also affected by shot power wind speed and direction
and elevation changes. Okay there's a gauge. Press it. Bing bing. There it is. Okay by the way you'll
need 60 points to pass this lesson. All right I got it. I got it. This is gonna be easy. Easy.
It's simple. Let's go. I got a pro controller in my hand right now. All right you want to get
precise. The blue section of the target will score you the most points. Okay of course that
isn't always the best spot to be. That will depend on where the wind is. Okay. Aim for the blue area.
Okay cool. Let's take a look. There it is. So that's 160 yards. We're gonna go right here.
What was wrong with that? All right 10 points. I did it. Okay nice. Yeah I want it to roll. I don't
want to do it. You know if it's 160 yards away you don't hit the ball 160 yards. Well that was
bullshit. That was actually bullshit. Why have you not turned around yet? Because this is the
fucking practice area dude. I'm not gonna do that in the practice zone. I'm not gonna turn around.
The point is to hit it exactly 160 yards. The point is to get it into the 10. That's not gonna
be enough. I'm undershooting it a little. How did that feel? Were you able to hit the shots where
you wanted? Yeah. Next we'll hit five more shots but now we're going to get more aggressive and
set up for a birdie. Okay let's get more aggressive. All right sure. So I need to
smash this as hard as I can. Are you playing the golf tutorial? I was gonna jump into golf
but people said do the adventure mode because they wanted to hear a toad yell at them for
fucking an hour. All right that was good. I can shape the shot too. This is fast forward.
Oh there is. Okay yeah let's go. How can I shape? Let's see. Oh you can curve it. Oh shit. I can't
wait to try to curve a ball around the entire forest. All right that's 60 points. Nice. Do I
level up? Okay power has leveled up. Cool. Oh yeah yeah yeah I wanted to be power. Well you crushed
it. You got to play it safe too. Not to take anything away from this performance but you've
always got to improve. Good job Jeremy. Keep improving the accuracy of your shots and you
need to pay attention to both carry and run. I don't care. Take some lessons. From who? Power
only. That's what I'm doing. I'm going to put every single point into distance and just have
the giant infomercial driver. That's illegal and I'm just gonna win every tournament. 30 yard
approach. A flat ground using your wedge. Okay. Get the ball into the green. I know how it works.
Me strong. All right I got my pitching wedge so you want to pretty much just pitch it on there.
Almost a hole in one. Nice. Yeah this is simple. We need a me strong golf swing.
Nice. All right approach shots are key to scoring well. We're on pretty level ground it seems. Okay
with 30 yards of elevation to gain at count four. Got to carry a little farther. No I just get the
ball into the hole. That's all I need to know. Nothing else matters. Just get it in. Don't tell
me well you see this elevation in it. No just put ball into hole. All right. Nice.
Why are you still here? All right we're uphill now. Hole is one yard downhill and 98 feet away.
Okay all right all right all right get out of my way. Easy. Right in. That was good. That was good.
He's gonna say okay every time. Okay that's the streamer curse. Don't you
understand? That's the- I don't want more than three or four seconds to go by without any sound
effects. Think about that. Five seconds of no talking is like it's like streamer dog years.
It's like it might as well be 30 minutes. It's like five straight minutes.
Fuck. Okay you want to do the- all right I'll do- I gotta just do the- let me just do this.
Well the goal is to get the ball into the thing. Kitboga! Kitboga! Coming in for a raid.
What's up Kit? Welcome everybody. We're currently playing Mario Golf. Uh it's- this is just breaking
it up a little bit because I'm going to play an Elden Ring later but thanks Kit. Hope you had a
good stream. Hope it was eventful. More Elden Ring? That's a nerd game. Well just watch this
stream then. This is gonna be two today. Just playing this as the meme. No actually this is-
I'm genuinely- when I saw the trailer for this I genuinely thought it was uh interesting looking.
All right so I gotta be careful. So this is- we're going up. I gotta hit it a little bit harder. Just
a little bit. Not very much. Okay. Okay. So this is not just gonna be golf. This is gonna be um
what are those? What are those guys called? The Stompers? What are they called? They're gonna be
all over the green and stuff right? This one's downhill all the way. All right but that was not
enough at all. That's fine. Nice on. Derma hates video games. I don't hate video games.
This is to change it up a little. All right. Ride the rookie course. Let's go. It's time to go.
Let's go for it. All right was- was the person said if this- if you don't think this game is
at least a seven out of ten then you should ban me for a month? Um you're about to find out if I
actually like this game. Okay this is the rookie course. This is cute though. It actually is cute.
I actually like this. I don't know how a shift can affect- no. Oh fuck off. Stop calling me. Three
holes. Finishing five over par or better to pass. That's a pass? It's like a super bogey. All right
11 mile per hour wind downhill downhill slope 7.3 yards. We don't care about any of those. We're
just gonna drive over them. All right. I think I got a pretty good idea. Yeah it's funny. He did
the funny thing right? I love somebody in the chat just wrote. Oh my god he's so funny. That
was not bad. All right now how far here? 120 yards downhill? The driver. Can I use the driver on the
green? If you can that's really funny. Yeah you can. Can you fucking imagine somebody doing this?
All right that's- I got one more stroke and I'm good. I got it.
Oh no. I think I can get this in one go. Ready? No not quite. I'm gonna go this way though.
Play seriously. I'm gonna- I'm doing it right now. He's gonna fail the rookie course. I'm not gonna
fail the rookie course. Watch. I can hit the tree. I feel like that's gonna hit the tree.
Find out. That's too far. Way too far. Way too far. I thought I was gonna go through the leaves and
get all fucked up. All right I- I gotta chip this real lightly here. It's not bad. Fuck you.
I'm at plus four? Oh shit. Okay I can't be plus five so I actually have to do- okay no fucking
around. I actually have to do this well. This is perfect for me. It's 143 yards. I gotta go
like kind of somewhere like here. Like right here. Get on the green. Oh fuck off. All right this is
uphill. This'll do it. Right in. Yes! I'm good. Nice. Plus three. Level up twice? Ooh. I want to
get that to at least 200 yards or 180. That was just kind of fun. Three holes in a time limit
and score well too. You have 10 minutes to finish par three, par four, and a par five.
It's called speed golf. Speed golf? Well you have to- I have to run around now. All right how does
this work? Huh? Dash? You can push people out of the way. There's a special dash. This seems kind
of chaotic. Okay so this is a time limit. Finish three holes at plus three or better in 10 minutes
or less. So I'm actually playing against other players? Oh fuck I have to run. Okay. All right
birdie putt. What does it look like? All right so this is um blue means it's going up and the red
means it's going down. Right? What do we got for wind? Wind is down a lot. Okay I'm just gonna-
I think it was too hard. Oh we got it. I mean he got it. I did it. I did it. He got it. I got it.
Okay cool. Oh shit. All right we're gonna go- I'm going this way. Is that stupid? Yeah it is pretty
stupid. Let's drive it as far as I can. What's the problem? We only have eight and a half minutes.
That's so funny that you can actually punch people and push people. Go faster?
Like this is as fast as the character can move. All right 148. We're gonna go- this is curving
a little. Where's the wind? All right wind's not bad. Let's go. It's gonna be on the green.
Green? Tell me. Green. Fringe. What's fringe mean? Oh right at the end. Right at the lip.
All right wind's coming down to the left a little. So it's a hundred foot. We're going
probably like 30 feet. We're going up. I'm gonna go tighten it up a little bit this way. We're gonna
go for it. All right. Fringe. Cringe. Oh come on. What the fuck? What happened? Wait what?
I have no idea what just happened. All right well I got it. Whatever. We're going here and I'm gonna
go over the sand trap. You can't get a golf cart. I mean this is kind of cool but isn't this the
exact reason why people play golf video games? Because this is the worst part of golf. Actually
needing to go to get the ball is like the- is the worst part of the whole sport. All right so the
wind is going cutting this way a little bit. We're gonna drive it over here. That should give us a
little bit of leeway I think. It's more fun with people. That makes sense. That makes sense.
Although is it though? I kind of feel like after you push your friend for the first time
and then you all laugh eventually you all just start to be like so can we like skip this part?
It gets to a part where everybody holds down start and it's like oh player four wants to skip
and everyone else just presses start. It's like yeah yeah yeah. All right so I want to go like
here. That was way too far. What was it? Oh that was a good approach. All right this is a birdie putt.
Don't fuck it up. Don't look at wind for putt. Stop acting like you know anything about golf.
Guys I went to golf camp one day and I left. That's a real story. In fact I would think that
some of you did the same thing. How many of you guys went to golf camp for like a day or two and
then we're like eh never mind this isn't for me. I kind of feel like that's happened to more than
a few of us. It may have been like uh uh maybe I don't know you know when like your kids are
getting to the age where they're old enough to like hold a baseball bat or like hold a golf club
and it's like oh maybe hey hey son what do you think about golf um I don't know well we'll get
you into golf camp and see how it works let's see how it is for you hey hop we'll get you to baseball
camp and then it's like oh that sounds kind of fun oh it does it sounds fun doesn't it young son
of course it does that kind of sounds fun I hit the ball with the thing yeah you hit the ball
the thing oh my boys are gonna grow up and we're gonna be on the back nine together sorry dad yeah
well yeah yeah yeah it's not I didn't go like to a camp where I like slept over or something for
like a summer it's not like oh yeah I went to I went to camp and it was like it was like a four
week golf camp where I stayed over somewhere no can I go over here it sounds like a crappy 90s
movie let's go qualifying round it'll be golfing with two other players and there's a time limit
wait am I actually playing with people I'm gonna play all nine holes okay oh shit all right I'm
ready it finished we're doing nine holes that's so long you know how I would actually enjoy golf
if an entire game wasn't 18 holes people complain about how long it takes to play a game of baseball
playing an entire 18 nine holes whatever golf takes like an entire it takes like two days
oh shit oh how do I punch I'm going for Tony's the weakest come here why am I so slower
and I like stand in front of it wait this is actually really dangerous uh Yoshi don't swing
Jesus oh my god that doesn't teach kids anything good that's teaching kids terrible golf etiquette
what these hearts what are the hearts for where's my ball over here we only have a minute to do this
oh I'm gonna drain this check this out oh get out of the way you're breathing on me all right
pink Yoshi fucked up big time cool all right that was fun ready you gotta be the first to drive
170 yards perfect hold on are they with his animals get away from me oh I needed that
can I block it holy shit told you awfully okay how far is it it's a 30 feet
this we're a little bit up the hill here we're gonna curve it I'm gonna smash it this way let's
go it's in that's in that's in that's in get out of the way what that's all right I did better
than them that's a bad idea oh I thought I could just clothesline both of them right there
what are the coins for wait did I just drift what was that okay they're not even close to
as powerful as I am they're not even close to as powerful as I am oh you guys are going that way
huh oh actually yeah good idea you need to attack them kill them I can't hurt them still better
you can exchange the coins does speed even matter I don't know I don't why do I have to
go so fast I have a minute that's not a ton of time but 130 yards through the tree that's good
all right I'm gonna probably chip this in we got this 33 yards going okay then they curve in there
come on all right how's this looking I got a minute and a half to do this all right I want to go like
here it's a little hard but I think it'll go yep nice you need to grab him by the neck
be running sprinting behind him grab the caddy of clubs and just pull it as hard as you can so
they go down imagine they added like a melee attack with just a golf club just left right left
right left right swinging want the coins come on go oh yeah Gabby J
did I just knock his ball away wait I think I just did holy shit he almost got it in
this is going downhill right oh what is Yoshi taking a shit in the hole what was that
Yoshi was just squatting down in front of the hole come on Toad you can do it it's so depressing
depressing okay no I can't for the joke I can't I'm like I'm in the lead right now leave me alone
stop no I wanted that okay do you know how this would actually be fun if it was like
50 person multiplayer and you could there was collision on all balls I should have
picked up the driver it's eight that's still kind of a lot yeah I'm drifting behind Toad
that's why that just happened all right this is gonna be a difficult approach here we go
we're we're we're on an incline I gotta tilt it a little bit this way and I'm gonna curve it a
little bit that way that's in the hole that's in the fucking hole oh my god it's not in the
hole it was almost in the hole oh no Toad Toad just looks like a little kid don't worry Toad
you're only in the last place I'm in the lead let's get to keep it up mom said you have to
bring Toad all right where's the wind wind is going nime up I'm not let these idiots
fucking swing immediately I'm gonna hold them on okay so wind is going that way I'm gonna drive
it into the wind a little bit like this way it's not too much women it's enough here we go that's
going in thank you oh fuck I gotta run I'm on the green these guys have a full stroke if I sink this
putt I win the game this is this is to solidify the game putt this is one of those putts where
the guy walks around for 40 minutes all right so this is uphill okay it's we're going this way
it's hard to tell where the hill is okay how strong is that pole going this way I wonder
this is 100 feet I think this is good let's try it oh more it was more even more to the right
out they had way more strokes I'm just slowly chipping away Toad wants to play angry birds on
your iPad make sure it doesn't get the screen all sticky again I will tell you that was one of the
most that was one of the worst things ever because of being an uncle right I have lots of nieces and
nephews and anytime it's like oh like can I play with your phone no you're gonna touch it
and you're gonna like touch it and put your fingers all over it and like you're gonna open
up like an app I haven't opened in like a year you're going to apple up you're gonna open up
like apple home you know what I mean I don't I've never opened that I don't want to give it to you
there's a wind and it's like never the same you have to like really like wash it and rinse it
bunker I got hit into a bunker still closer than they are oh shit um nice get out of the way
get out of the way you little puke hates kids hates iphone plays golf but that makes me an old
person wait hates kids has an iphone and plays golf this one's kind of scary I have a huge
advantage here because this is just straight drives forward oh you don't like it that I'm
drifting over there yeah it's mine where's my ball oh there's right there oh I want the driver
not the three wood what what are you talking about put that away how it eats a three wood
just drive it again how many knows the name it said okay this is I can't tell if that's a hill
or not there's a wind all right wind I gotta hit it a little harder sink it sink it oh I got it
oh be careful toad it's a tricky course it didn't lick your finger and hold it up
all right now I'm really ahead okay drive drive I don't want to put take the three wood out
why does he hate toad so much I mean don't blame me why are you blaming me for this blame nintendo
putting him in last place in every game if he's an ai controlled character I didn't do that
we're gonna go dry give me the driving wedge there it is bang oh let that go it's all right
I'm in a good position to drive it over the lake all right I gotta this is gonna slice isn't it
oh shit it's gonna slice oh fuck that's really slicing where's it going where is it is it on
green can I go in this what happened is that a stroke oh you dick I'm gonna remember that
all right we see I'm gonna go they're plus three already these guys how are you plus three already
it's still like how many holes left dipping it again what's happened I just hit his ball in
green is wet oh level up level up level up level up I did it great work and just in time
bonnie greens open tees off tomorrow and after that result you're all eligible to enter
now it's a two-day tourney the first day is an elimination round if you're still in the next day
you'll have a chance to earn a chrome badge but only if you finish in the top three oh yeah this
one's in the bag just hand the trophy over well it may not hit shots like chuck but I'm confident in
my strategy old words but you're both looking past me as if I'm not even here I suppose I'm a
ghost yeah this is only four players four player tournament I'm gonna laugh if I'm more powerful
than um charging chuck whatever his name is if this won a chance you might be in for a surprise
tomorrow and besides who says you're the favorites I heard some top players might be making an
appearance like uh potentially super mario super mario could be there okay uh hammer brother I
have a question why are you allowing smurfs mario and luigi being allowed in this tournament is
not fair okay let's go we do things differently here the higher your rank the fewer clubs you
can carry trust me it works out I only need one club but that sounds tough for folks who don't
crush the driver like I do we you and me are gonna get along everybody go to bed a lot of
townspeople to talk to but I'm not going to talk to any of them you know that jump that I had in
the game they took it from me no no no no I don't want to leave me alone this is a cute little town
it's golf camp there's sprint mario slaughters these people this is like isn't this kind of
weird like oh we're at the fun golf camp golf town with all the koopas and goombas and like mario
kills these people on a regular basis all the time mario's just an actor they all just actors
movies and tv shows aren't real what he's playing he's an actor he's playing golf with other actors
they're actors in the story are they actually actors wait what how have I not known this
the world of super mario is actors pretending to play fight each other they do that in mario 3
but I mean that's mario 3 was one game is that how it's supposed to be the whole
entire franchise that's why there are curtains in the beginning of three
platforms in three are props I mean I understand that one game can be but is it like mario odyssey
for instance is all just supposed to be like a movie like they're actors it's just in one game
yeah it's like the truman show mario doesn't know that would be really weird what a shot from
koopa troopa I think we're in for some great scores today with the way the course is playing
wait a minute the key to following mario around with the camera makes a hell of a lot more sense
now he's just filming him for the fucking tv show what it's kind of ruining everything
all right here we go hole one drive the ball 200 yards every time how did you get that special
move oh yeah how is toad announcing and playing all right 166 this is uphill we're gonna have to
go wind is a little bit rough this way here we go it's on the green now you gotta hit it one more
time I don't this is a different toad you asshole are okay everybody shut up for a second because
this is gonna be hard this one goes downhill then uphill and it looks like it's pulling this way
tad so I gotta hit it actually pretty hard we're gonna hit it hard that's in that's in that's in
that's in that's in that's in that's in that's in oh fuck it oh come on are you serious that
would have been awesome and I was curbed in you address the scandal well because I said that I
thought toad was playing uh look I wasn't paying attention I just see him with a headset on
holy shit wait a minute that might go in what what happened oh no no okay okay it rolled it
rolled all right I gotta drain this I actually have to sink this slightly there's a little bit
of give here not very much but there is 15 feet away there's a little bit of give not that much
oh there's more there was more give that was blue it wasn't blue though it's all right I'm
still in third place but the top of that toad had like a blue hat on and the toad announcing had a
blue hat on okay well not in the ass of he's gonna suit on but you know but he had a fucking
blue hat on I swear to god what is that bullshit he's doing working two jobs to support his one
million kids why are you implying that toads kind of just dump eggs out somewhere don't be
mad at me because I thought that was the same toad be mad at the guy that said toads lay a million
eggs all right that's I'm the guy you're coming after that's me you're coming after why why are
you coming after me all right 109 you said that though what I didn't say I was talking about what
that guy said a million kids it's from it's spores well how do you get to a million kids
if you're not laying like fucking 10,000 eggs every spring or whatever the fuck happens in
like the world like the animal kingdom I'm not saying toads an animal I'm just saying I'm just
saying like you how do you have a million kids he needs to support his million kids that's like
you're dropping 50,000 eggs every spring mushrooms are fungi ready how how fast does fungi spread a
year you don't understand toad fucks I wasn't looking I wasn't looking I heard a golf swing
and then I heard my character go oh all right where's the wind this way you guys are fucking
crazy everyone's calling me crazy when I'm simply reacting to the person that said that toad has a
million kids and I'm asking I was just simply asking how that would be possible even if he
was a mushroom all right this is heavy heavy heavy I gotta go this way hard is this too much
this is very heavy downhill right fuck you that was the one two I'm sorry I'm in second
toad spreads his spores in a forest and that's where the babies come from okay so he lays eggs
in the forest I got it okay got it like really my stomach hurts the amount of people right now that
are freaking out about me talking about toad laying eggs is like it's killing me right now
all right way too far imagine fighting with somebody over them saying that toad lays eggs
oh this whole conversation is fucking hilarious to me you I know I am I know it's fucking funny
this is gonna curve there it is oh get in come on I'm just imagining two people
sitting on a couch passing a blunt back and forth
oh but I don't know I don't understand man how is it possible he has to lay eggs no I know he it's
spores it he goes to the forest and squats down and spores come out of his ass I don't know man
I don't know how how much spore juice does he have in his in his glands that's too much I think it's
eggs you're saying this is not the idiocy of the conversation we're having all right 166
gonna go right here that's a good on right there actually gonna be good
while eating taco bell at 2 a.m. all right this is a good opportunity to get first place
I have to get this putt though all right what we got 50 foot putt
lots of pull this way I'm going here I think it's even more than that I think it's right here drain
it drain it oh it's close minus one all right I have to do well here I can't let charge and chuck
win a short game moron that was actually pretty good that's elder to your special
I think my specials just run I don't have one yet that's hope is that chuck fucks it up yeah how
come um what I'm not with chuck right now I'm not on his uh squad whatever this is this is going
right to the green what's the wind like we're gonna cut it this way a little bit and go I think that's
good that looks real good actually that's gonna be close how close though enough to
sink this oh yeah this is doable so I always have so much trouble in these golf games on
how much this actually means that's steep I think right here I think right here wind is pushing it
this way though how much does the wind really affect putt when it's downhill like this wind
does affect putt it's because it's gonna pull me this way then levels out a little I'm thinking
right here I'm going for it there it is all right we're in first place I had for first with chuck
not bad watch out for that tree I don't want to hit that tree
you're gonna play call of duty four no no I'm not playing call of duty four
get out of the way all right this is where's the wind it's gonna I gotta oh I have to overshoot
this a little bit because the wind I'm gonna be on the green good spot right yeah all right this
is this is flat so I should nice putt all right this is literally just flat there's nothing here
it's literally just straight 15 feet right to the hole this is it got it there's no way that he got
a birdie on that hole as well no he didn't okay good first place all right I just I have to get
a par here this is it I can't fuck around I actually have to try hard here the time doesn't
matter just click the coins Jeremy doesn't get golf Jeremy's in first place speaking in third
person Jeremy you're not going to get the ice cream later why do you get to decide when I get
to eat ice cream or not all right we're going for something hard here here we go this is gonna be
this is this is ballsy this is ballsy oh don't go in the water all right it's good it's good it's
good it's good it's good it's good I bet you like pistachio ice cream yeah I do actually it's
phenomenal all right all right all right we're gonna go a little bit overshoot it gonna curve
a little bit right here get it on the green that was solid could have been better this is flat
all right this is it I will win the tournament okay so this is very gently downhill or uphill
wind is going this way a little bit I'm thinking right here but look it's the hill goes to the
right all right wait this might not work out the way I want shit it wasn't even that strong
whatever I still win yep I win I got first place I'm good how many levels you got I gotta
get at least four or five levels in the first place all right hold on stamina speed control
spin I mean I'm thinking this right I honestly don't give a shit how fast I can run who cares
control and power that means I can always my drives will always be right on the mark
and then later on I can worry about how fast I'm running it doesn't really matter
by the way why is it weird to like pistachio ice cream what's why is it so weird
I thought that was pretty popular disgusting it is not I have a bad take for you pistachio ice
cream is delicious pistachios are gross that's my bad take of the evening for you yeah I don't like
pistachios but I like pistachio ice cream I think it's the added sugar that makes that pistachio
flavor become very very good for me pistachio is the most amazing thing ever somebody told me
something about pistachios one time and it freaked me out and I forget what it was and it would turn
me off from eating them forever and I what was it there's something weird about pistachios right
isn't there something weird is it bugs I don't it's something about like them being like actually
kind of gross you mean figs oh it's something weird something about like I'm gonna let me look
this up before I like give you a total complete misinformation campaign here like let me get this
right what is it is it was it isn't a conspiracy I don't think so why are pistachios like bad
right like I'm just I don't I don't remember it was something weird that I was like no I don't
want to eat those and it was something it was something like odd and I looked at it was like
that's kind of weird not figs no figs is the wasp shit I know that was a clickbait was it
a fake news clickbait title no no no no it was I maybe it was like a I want to say I don't want
to say what I thought it was let me see oh I guess they were recalled pistachios at some point
is that what this is this is like from a few years ago it caused farts and bloating
that's not what this says you probably heard no I don't know what that is yeah
there was like something weird like four or five years ago with like salmon whatever it is
cashews are the ones that the fruit is poisonous no it wasn't cashews it was start the final round
oh fuck I gotta pay attention ashes are covered in a strong maybe that is what it was
maybe is that what it is does somebody get it aflatoxins is that what it was what it was
aflatoxin a chemical in which can cause cancerous mold has been found in some mistreated pistachios
and alleged breakouts of diseases that's all right so I wasn't crazy is that a legit article
though pistachios contained toad spores source dude I told you me you trust me right it gives
a yee-haw to prove your American citizenship what I don't think I could even do a good yee-haw
it would probably be embarrassing you would think I would not pass your test that you have here
all right this is the finals I don't know like eat like yee-haw like that but I feel like to do
that you have to like lean back put your fist up and go like I get in this sand oh shit I did
get in the sand this is bad all right I gotta pay attention what if I just drive it out of here can
I do it no that's too that's too that's too risky too risky stay on the fairway please okay okay
where's the wind going put it on the green right here it's safe it should get there
oh my god it went in it went oh it didn't go in that was close too damn all right that was
really close what a recovery that was the only first place but no I pistachio flavor I think
it's okay they kind of work go I like pistachio ice cream you know I'm kind of a weirdo I think
I like it because it's green have you handed me vanilla ice cream and you handed me vanilla
ice cream that was tinted a sky blue or like robin's egg blue I would like it more I would
go oh wow this is awesome my imagination fills in the blanks all right where's the wind is going
a little bit this way we gotta go we're in 66 a little bit pull it up a little robin's egg blue
oh it's on you like spinach I need to know I spinach is actually my favorite green vegetable
yes I do very much so okay I got a minute and a half I'm fine so this has got a I think that's
good till a little bit more I said so I don't know how to do it spinach is based spinach is the best
green vegetable you can do tons of stuff with it you can saute it you can like mix it up it turns
into a different thing you can eat spinach raw and if you cook it it turns into this weird like
kind of wilty soft delicious kind of juicy thing or you can eat it like salad like normal
it's very versatile so I know I don't I like spinach more than kale the scale kale is kind
of weird it's got a weird texture you have to chew through it more it's a little stringy spinach
is way better I mean I think kale is probably better for you pound for pound nutrient density
whatever but is that really that big of a deal he just turned it up I understand there's like
tackling and pushing in this game but that was like a red card you know like where's the referee
it was good in smoothies yeah kale is good when it's used I can't go through that tree yeah I can
get through the tree yes yes it's actually up there it's actually all the way up there
I'm on top of this hill too this actually is not a bad place to be
this is gonna curve curved in that's pretty good all right I saved some time there I think
what's the skybox for a second I see tearing I think I just go I it's not gonna be enough to
affect the movement all the way down there's a little bit of pull this way I think this is
gonna be fine it's not gonna hit her hard enough exactly what I was thinking was gonna happen
that's exactly what I that's why I didn't want to do that hard I didn't want to go that far
I just have to get pars that's all that matters I'm two strokes ahead of Chuck
this way why not getting that this game sucks but you said sucks in all capitals
remember this game sucks that was you were very upset about this I think it's fun
what's your problem with it okay how about you tell me what you think about how bad that you
don't like it and I'll tell you how bad I think it is okay it's not actually just messing around
the side it's really not a bad game it's really fun I could see how you could just sit here and
chill and play golf I get it it's fun this is the awful game to watch well golf is awful to watch
in general and what is this hill it's going right and left at the same time what am I supposed to
do about this um I don't know nothing all right nice yeah way ahead ready golf really is one of
those weird games at least in a video game sense I actually really don't mind playing golf in a
video game but I really despise it playing it in real life it's truly do but it's kind of the
opposite for baseball for me I would rather play a game of baseball in real life than play a video
game of it I don't know about just getting the bat and getting up there and swinging
on the reverse that's good get it well get out of the way it's not gonna make it I ran away with
it though there's no way he comes back I would have to be a moron and get I'd have to do it
intentionally bad as a joke somebody said Omega Lul he has negative points I got a p too Mario
sluggers that was actually really good before I think this is a crazy idea this I want to get on
green you to play Mario strikers I probably will play Mario strikers I was a huge fan of the uh
one for the Wii let's chip this shit in play this all day no Elden Ring please that's probably not
gonna happen I'm obsessed with Elden Ring right now somewhere at the halfway point I'm gonna take
a little bit I'm gonna take like 15-20 minutes this could be a hole in one if I can get it
it's gonna be close that's actually gonna be close you do a knitting scream I don't think
that would be enjoyable I think you would all hate that ax out speed and you can tackle them
all right only two holes left and I completed my first tournament are there many games I want to
play mini games I'm so far ahead I can just literally relax just get the coins and the hearts
and stuff what's what's wrong with the music I don't understand people don't like the music
what's the problem with the music everyone's like music turn it off please
okay it's because it's on a five second loop it kind of is I would have had that
it is the same song I haven't paid any attention oh my god Yoshi you're plus 10
is Yoshi doing the thing at mini golf where you're infuriated and you're not having a good time
so you just drag the ball three or four times when you get it close enough and you don't care
you mess up and you just drag drag drag in and it counts as like four strokes
is that what you're doing right now Yoshi just drive it that's where my skills are
uh
it actually has been this for an hour how do I go in the sand what I'm so far ahead who
fucking cares just drive it there it is oh shit I don't want to hit anybody with this
wait do I have to go get it I don't have to go get it right it's out of bounds it's out of bounds
I I can't get that okay close I win plus 12 I got my first medal the star cup
there's not two other pedestals only one for first place thousand coins and probably leveled up like
five times oh yeah your special dash improved all right so control is fine spin I don't really care
about that I'll do stamina head to ridge rock lake this dude's doing an endurance build
actually I gotta pee real bad but not yet rise and shine champ oh all right all right please
take a pee break all right I'll take we'll take it I've been playing for two hours I feel like
am I actually am I having fun because that's kind of odd all right I did not expect to be playing
for two hours all right I'll be right back I'm gonna pee give me two seconds yeah what's that
I mean it's all right I'm just I'll be done in like a little bit later tonight I mean it's okay it's
it's like it's probably like a four it's in though yeah if I just keep pretending to like it
fans will you know so yeah so to keep pretending to like it even though I can fucking hate it
that's just pretty yeah I see look oh my god I just got caught oh my god I got caught
no no no no no all right let's go this is kind of cool there's a map I love the hot mic joke it's
it's the worst fucking joke it really is it's not it's not it's the worst one oh new area
is that putting practice congrats on the chrome badge x is bronze you check to see if your mic
is off I mean I have a little thing where I turn it off and on like a little button I press
sometimes I don't press it sometimes I'm just like what oh I don't really care
big storm won't be any tournaments for a while what we can't hear anything yeah you can have
you ever heard of cross-country golf xc golf for short believe it or not xc golf goes way back it's
a form of the game that many of the top players have mastered some of the really high level
players can still play our course even in this state it's remarkable to see them in action of
course they can use special shots so it's not exactly fair maybe you saw mario in that televised
I was I thought he's gonna say commercial you've already seen a special shot some of them are so
powerful that they can affect other players and blast their golf balls out of the way
okay interesting so everybody has a special move I get it so should I just play the regular game
mode and just pick a character and just go play that sounds like something interesting
pick seven clubs there's a lot of elevation change the nine iron look I don't know okay
let me tell you what I need I need the driver I need six iron pitching wedge this is changing
golf attire okay yeah I don't even want that maybe I'll take it I'll take a six iron I'll take the
six hybrid sounds good successfully downloaded data for pick cross he really just fucking expose
me like that all right let's try it no I don't want to change gear you find yourself in a really
tricky spot and we all do from time to time you're not totally out of luck all right I'll be fine
play a practice round of xc golf verifying badge confirmed registration for xc golf practice round
complete complete three holes and 30 strokes or fewer to advance okay may encounter tornadoes on
the course this is normal this they may be used to edit okay be careful there are hazards sure
drops from flat lies will fly straight yeah lots of uphill will curve downhill will curve
yeah yeah yeah the moral yeah yeah yeah all right I'm not gonna play pick cross right now I'm okay
stop tornadoes on the course will blow both golfers and golf balls into the sky okay
did I do that wait there are two different holes so you have to okay all right I got an idea
is this stupid will this go into that wind and go up that didn't do anything I thought it was
gonna go in the tornado and go up I guess not oh well okay never mind all right I gotta be
careful huge wind pushing this way so I'm gonna sit right here big curve as well I'll go too far
pretty good said watch out for them don't go directly into them but I thought it was
gonna make the ball bounce up that's a that's steep I think that's the one right there
ah again I keep messing that up it's the worst dream it's not pick cross I'm not playing pick
cross stop asking for it or I'm gonna be very upset with you so now we go again oh okay this is
kind of I this is actually cool I do genuinely like this it's gonna hit the wall oh it does work
so why didn't it work last time I said this is downhill a little bit big wind I'm not playing
pick I'm not playing pick Ross no no I'll play pick Ross later this is gonna be like a 10 hour
stream will you guys just just buckle up oh no I did this completely wrong there's the wind
okay tornado this way I should go into that tornado and go up please make it I'm fine
I'm not gonna play pick Ross for like four hours oh I gotta go across the whole fucking game again
god damn it I'll play a few rounds of pick Ross no later than at least 45 minutes from right now
okay will that actually go up will that travel up in the tornado I hope so as if I'm doing it
watch out we were kidding don't that's what I'm saying I know you guys are such fucking
jokers not even gonna get on the green what an idiot 17 strokes left oh no nice
I knew this was gonna happen I knew it was gonna happen
44 minutes until pick Ross maybe all right let's do it for real I was tracking my every move
let's do it let's register for a standard xc golf tournament that was actually pretty cool
you can approach that a bunch of different ways let's go use your coins how do I use my coins
how to play no who sells shit here somebody sells something who is the shop keeper over here
okay welcome anything you want to buy bullet bill for a hybrid where's the where is it
is this it let me just see if this is it no where is this commercial for this fucking driver
I don't know boomerang oh these are good I want those okay so then rana plant makes it easier
to control shots out of deep ruffin mud I kind of want the bullet bill hybrid I mean why wouldn't
I use that elevation finder yeah okay what do you sell food all right let me put those uh let me
put that stuff on okay all right I think we're good I thought there were no golf cards you were
clear for three holes of standard xc golf progress in any order complete the required
holes in 30 strokes mm-hmm wait there's a shot clock now I know how a spin shot works
can you die in this I'm no you can't you have two minutes to hit and reach your ball before
you be assessed a stroke penalty buddy okay that doesn't seem that big of a deal at least not yet
not initially this game is a unity asset swap I think it's a little better I that's better than
that what do the coins do I just purchased a few things you can buy uh upgrades and that the guy
that guy's gonna hit me isn't he what all right watch it we got high wind oh I thought that was
the pitching wedge I didn't think I I didn't think that was a putter I thought I had the pitching
wedge on why do I sound like that I've been going straight on I'm just gonna hit it as hard as I can
shit sorry that'll go in how do I get up there what is it doing what what are you talking about
didn't go in the uh didn't go in the thing here um how am I supposed to handle this
all right I made it up there where is it all right I made it yep now I use it good
now this is downhill heavy winds I'm so bad at putting it's fine I have 19 strokes left
oh my god I went the wrong way again ah now I understand where the stamina comes from
I didn't think it was gonna be this important is this game open world it is not this is just kind
of a cool game mode where you have to sink in three different holes in a certain amount of strokes
which I'll give him credit it's time to give uh the super nintendo developer some credit
that's cool that's a cool spin on golf it just increased the letter grid but here's the problem
how do I all right I'm gonna go nine can I do nine iron six iron might do it nine iron might
just barely get over the hill I'm going for it fuck I gotta get it up there uh shit um okay
wait it did go up wait what what happened am I I'm I've lost my mind I don't know what's going on
is it bad wait how hard did I just hit that it's right here we're good I did this completely
wrong but whatever whoa I can break those this case pretty good this is gonna this is gonna
slice like crazy so I'm gonna hit it this way why was that not even a slice the game just told me
oh my god dude you're fucked think it in you should please do the let's freaking go voice
nice maybe I will in a minute that was fun I like this I'm not moving yet please do it
that was solid seems like you're figuring out xc golf I think you'd do well in a competition
making good progress on course repairs so we should be ready to host some kind of a competition soon
play a standard round of xc golf all right let's do it the next stream should be you going golfing
the next big stream I would just slice the ball we do a big thing where I elaborately oh I'm
gonna do nine holes of golf I get up there I tee up and I would slice the ball so bad that we I'd
lose the ball and get frustrated and probably stop streaming off infuriates me I need to do
six holes in 35 strokes all right I gotta be careful this actually is where the game begins
ready all right there are six go we gotta go this way first go that was like in my ear that was
weird all right we're gonna go this way this is gonna make it well this is gonna bounce right off
the edge isn't it might not it's gonna bounce right off it why would I don't be more concerned
about the tree that's there and not the rock now I have to sand wedge it up there can I can I sand
wedge it up please come on sand wedge yes all right how do I get up there okay we're good
it's up on another ledge all right another sandwich I'm not far enough
wait where was that gonna end up okay so if I do six iron at about 50% I'm gonna say 50% speed
it's gonna slice a little I'm gonna do nine iron we're doing nine iron straight on
yep yep all right nice were you thinking of the hammer driver infomercial I don't know it's like
from like 1998 or something I don't know what it is but that's you can't that's just illegal
okay where is this thing over here all right we're almost there I'm gonna drive it here it's
gonna curve a little this next part shouldn't be too bad god damn it this one sucks to get to I
have 30 strokes left I'm okay okay right before the putt why is he talking like he's fighting an
Elden Ring boss because that's the only thing I've done for two straight weeks get the putter
out can't tell I had to hit it way harder because it was in the fucking rough whatever
all right 28 strokes we need five more holes they're all over there um I'm gonna say we're
gonna go the one all the way to the right look how far apart these are these things are so far away
what all right move straight again oh my god is this gonna can I actually make that I wonder
oh that's what those fucking idiots get over here all right change plan I gotta go this one
what the heck is this dude I'm playing Mario Golf this is just a game my twitch analytics
so I'm so my whole directory is not Elden Ring there's got to be at least three hours of Mario
Golf so it will fit into the algorithm of like other games that I've played in the last month
that's good and oh yeah and Picross will be there too that's right
you got a good point okay this is still very possible because I need I have to go this way
now we're gonna go this way we're gonna go over to the right and then I'm gonna come down into
the middle again should be all right what's the wind like all right wind is blowing a lot this way
I'm gonna go a little bit short right there watch out for the tree oh 30 more minutes to meet the
Mario Golf quota I mean it's not this isn't a bounty or anything
wait did I do that did I fuck up the tree oh this is gonna slice like crazy okay 38 yards
oh there was a lot of wind too though don't mess this up it's very very very steep and I have to
hit it not that hard right there right here perfect god fucking damn it I'll never get it
what the fuck what I was trying to skip through where is it going
well that's not good I was trying to skip the dialogue sequence this is really uphill though
will this make it oh I did I got it okay same thing here uh it's not gonna work oh this is bad
I have to tornado it but I can't I have 16 strokes left I'm not gonna be able to do this
I need to how am I gonna do this a hundred feet I gotta go like that didn't do anything
okay all right all right that's it I got it now it's over this is ruined how are you supposed
to reliably get up there yeah this is this is ruined I have to it's gotta go like over here
wait all right that's good that's not what I wanted to do I mean I'm screwed either way honestly so
does it really matter let's keep zooming out so far like what are you doing
what's with this shit view what is with this terrible fucking camera will this get picked
up by the thing I hope so yep there it is okay I don't think I'm gonna have enough strokes to do it
oh my god it's still not even close wait what where's the ball what's going on why does it say
it's down why is the ball down here did you go out of bounds I'm very confused what happened
there's a penalty it's got to go right through the middle it's grayed out over there all right
well this is obviously just restart the whole fucking thing restart restart this is stupid
restart I forgot Nintendo does the thing where it's remember I told you I I want a fucking I
want a I want Congress to pass a law a is b and b is a across all these different consoles
Nintendo wants you to press the right button to accept stuff xbox says no bro hit the bottom
button I'm gonna get congress involved all right straight ahead this dude's high on wallpaper glue
hey you don't understand we gotta get the president has to get involved a is b and b is a
across Nintendo and xbox you don't understand it's really pissing me off don't okay they should have
all come to an agreement a long time ago okay is it wrong for me to say that if your controller
is xyba and the competitor's controller is xyba just just come to a fucking agreement and shake
hands in an office somewhere and be like look we're gonna have the same button with commands
right like we're going to see playstation gets to fuck around because they're symbols well it's not
we have square and triangle all right whatever fuck you go you go live in your own world xyba
should be the same across the platforms that have xyba this is literally who cares
I do is all downhill is he about to start crying I've I've been really trying to hold it this whole
time okay so don't go that way honest to god don't go that way what's the route what's the
right route it's probably to the left over here it has to be as I go across this gap there it is
downhill don't go so hard we're gonna do six iron at about 140 yards I'm thinking a bit of strong
wind we'll handle it all right nice okay time for pick cross it's not time for pick cross it's time
for pick cross when I say I'm gonna play pick cross that's not right now I need to hit it a
little bit harder than I want to that's in come on that's such bullshit now we go this way which
will take us oh there's that one over there shit I'm gonna have to get that one later
all right if I go as hard as I can I can get this at least to the sand trap
I'm going right there wind is blowing a little bit too we're gonna be going full blast into the
wind the tornado wind don't fucking screw me here the tornado what happened to the tornado
now it's I'm in big trouble in Japan the a button is on the bottom on the west Xbox has patents for
button bottom button on a that can't be real if it is that's fucking insane now I'm so screwed
what do I do now I can't just keep whacking into the wall I guess this way I'll have to come back
that'll make it over that hill I hope everyone ps1 games had confirm on circle well that's the
thing confirm is where circle is on this way on just Nintendo circle is the rightmost button
a is the rightmost button and that's confirmed on Nintendo it was like that on SNES too yeah and
then Xbox came along put a on the bottom and made that confirm what are they thinking how am I going
to lie I can't just run up here I don't think am I going I don't think I can walk up here
I have 30 seconds to do this but 25 strokes I think I need to level up before I go here
look at this this is horrible 38 yards all right I'm gonna go like here all right not bad nice
straight on nothing fancy because you're under leveled
I probably am 22 strokes I have three holes left this is gonna be a monumental pain in the ass
to get to the one down there but I have to take what I can take and it's this here
once that countdown for Picross ends you're gonna be very upset when I don't play the game
are these worth one coin now I'll play a couple of rounds of Picross I will
it's gonna be weird with the controller though gonna curve a little bit this wind a lot of wind
I'm not sure what hurts more just gonna go like this another broken pixel finally okay 19 strokes
to get two holes this is the hard one this is the one that I'm I have trouble understanding
I think I have to hit it really hard just smash it so it flies up or I don't know how hard do I
have to hit this with a six uh six iron I don't know I think I just have to smash it full power
with the six iron yeah did it go what no it came all the way back uh I have to put this back over
here there's no hit it with the driver and do backspin I gotta get it back over there
I have to get this back in a different a better spot no not into the sand thing god damn it I
didn't want to hit it that hard thank god okay all right drive it and then put how do I do backspin
standard shot oops no no no no no no I did I wanted to choose I didn't get to choose
fucking come on I didn't want to do that I was trying to choose a different like spin
it actually got up there how did that happen I think I can do this spin doesn't matter for
what you're trying to do okay this is the hard one this is the one that sucks okay this is going
to curve a lot and there's a lot of wind so I'm going to run into it here all right 15 strokes
to get one hole there's one more across the whole game I just have to drive it over and over again
until I get there right oh I should approach from here right because how is that how uphill is that
I wonder I'm gonna approach from this way god I hope I make this how am I gonna get there
I only have two minutes it didn't make it yes it did I was looking way too far this is cool though
I do have to get up there though I don't know how that's gonna happen I don't know I just have to
guess I gotta go over that dude there's no way um I have to get it on there first I have I have 13
strokes I'm gonna be all right I gotta go from here to there there's wait um I don't know I could
hit it that way but I don't think it'll get over there that thing's downhill all right I'm just
gonna I'm just fucking sending it who cares it's gotta go in this general direction I don't care
where we're good okay hey I'm actually gonna complete it so this is down I'll just send it
again I think it'll cross over it should make it across it did all right nice sims music is
better than this where's the Mario music all right 11 strokes this would be hard to mess up
Mario's not in this game I think it okay that was good you got it this isn't a Mario game
he's in the title I have to put I have to whoa why are you doing that what's going on with this
bullshit I lose points in the other one oh this is bad I don't want to do the qualifier
I have a pick cross this is fun though I like this all right I have to give it a rating so far
the person said that if this was not at least a 7.0 and I that person gets banned for a month
they're in pre-stream chat hmm do what hmm this is not a seven don't kid yourself
the thing is though it could be it actually could be it's gonna take me actually another
few minutes to figure this out let me try some of the mini games first doesn't that can really
change my opinion I want to play some of those like the putt mini games and the driving mini
game and does exist right sort of the main menu all right is it on the main menu because I we've
tried this this was cool that was cool what else we got play golf solo challenge okay
door attack time attack one on one putt get one shot to find the green and one putt to get the
ball in the hole no aim for the targets okay we need golf battle golf I want to battle golf
ready okay with uh four cpus I'm gonna play on amateur see look they're all in this game
they're all in it we have to hear all their voice lines
wait Pauline's in this cool okay okay mustache guy mustache guy versus Pauline and Donkey Kong
and Mario strategic technical simple terrain strategy all right special shot
or it's full energy shape shot top view whatever time for battle
first of three flags wins where is it where's my ball this is fucking stupid
did I not get it wait what happened oh it's gone all right I'm going for this one
let him fight for one who cares I'm going to I'm going for this one over here on the right
all right putt putt it putt it putt it fuck I got one Donkey Kong is one away I'm gonna do the
effective thing of turning around and driving the wrong side of the road Mario Kart I don't even
care if I win I'm just gonna fuck it up everybody else okay where's the hole Donkey Kong's he's gonna
win Donkey Kong's up there I gotta stop him stop how do I fight him how do I stop him what do I do
stop sliding where's my ball hit it okay that was that was outrageous sure very cool let's go back
to the main menu I want to see the other thing battle golf target golf let's do this and you
know what fucking fine I gotta play I'm up that character's weird for a second I was like who is
this what Mario character is that all right we'll do we'll go against um Bowser uh Rosalina
and Mario forest volcano go into the volcano who is Rosalina you don't know who Rosalina is
Mario Galaxy hit the targets to score points high score after five shots wins all right score
the moat we've got to land we're doing it's one at a time right all right
which one's worth more points I'm going right in the middle here is there any wind barely any so
it's gonna bounce a little bit that way here we go every you're in the middle you couldn't you
can't get better than that oh you can that's all right that's a good start here comes Bowser
this is so this is champ difficulty which just means they're gonna get it in the middle every time
yeah it's gonna be a perfect shot every time Mario is gonna mess it up he's like a comedian
right where's Picross you'll see it in a minute okay ball one ball change what's this
egg ball key change what's the ball do what's the egg ball do just further away with more points
and does that mean that the middle's already been claimed play it safe okay no win play it safe
it's downhill I need like one like right like here that's what it does it bounces around
roll back all right whatever you're having a great day uh I'm having a pretty good day yeah
hope you're having a good day what was that oh get out of here with this bullshit yeah okay
I was gonna say that shuts points off nothing come on hurry up what I'm in type of third place
all right I have one opportunity here I gotta go with this middle ring here it should land
and bounce right into it how are you this bad at Mario Golf I'm about to potentially tie for first
place on champion difficulty Bowser is does get can't get enough points to save him here
as you just saw I'm literally tied for first place and I literally might be tied for first
place at the literal end of this game that what does Rosalina do bad keep going whatever
I come in second place he's literally uh there's not even enough points to get enough to win yeah
I'm second place I'll take second place that's fine 60 I don't understand why they give him extra
points without literally next game uh it's not over yet that's too bouncy all right I'm gonna
play Picross that was kind of fun that was that was fun that was fun I gotta give you a rating
though and I think you're gonna have to ban that guy for a month but hear me out let's figure it
out I think it's a solid experience like it's fun it needs to be a seven out of ten or that person
is banned for one full month what makes it bad though bad's a wrong word what makes it not over
a seven for me I feel like this game is a game that you it's like on the tv in the college dorm
room and that makes it an eight you know what I mean like this is a college dorm room game
which makes it a solid eight as a uh as a 36 year old in his office alone I wouldn't say that
you know I'm gonna be fair I actually okay with that in mind this is like a really good
piece down like you're in like a college dorm room with friends everyone's like you know
it's like talking shit and like oh my god you fucked up my shot that's an eight but it's a
six for me sitting here playing it by myself so therefore the average is probably somewhere around
7.0 7.1 I'm gonna give this game a 7.2 but they can stay I think this actually could be really
fun with a group of people more than three or four people all hanging out in a call playing this
yep that's an 8.0 game for sure maybe more 7.2 it's good and there's like a story mode too it's
not just like all right that's good it's good I don't I didn't hate it all right let's play
pick ross and then we're gonna play elden ring this is the worst game ever made it's not
you gave monster wrencher a 4.2 no idea when did I give monster I gave monster
wrencher like a nine what are you talking about all right I need is pick ross is just on my
pump