This is your new high-tech suit. Please put on the mask.
School is fucking fine. Why is everybody always asking about school? Like, oh, how's school? It's it's it's fine
Like what do you mean? I go home and do my homework and I get fucking decent grades
I got a pluses when I was in school, but that's besides the point
I've turned into your estranged family member
And yes, this is the three out of four videos on this main channel have been me talking about the main channel
So before we do anything before I talk about a single thing that I want to talk about
I mean, we're gonna put another video in here that we're gonna put a funny
I'm gonna make a funny video and it's gonna go in this video. So there's two videos in this video
So watch the first video first funny fucking video coming up here. You're gonna be laughing about it. I'm tired. Trust me
So main channel here we are where one year of just about one year anniversary for my absentee from my main channel and
Let's talk about it cuz yeah, you guys have a you guys do have a lot of points here
If you're absent from school for a year you get an F you just get an F
So imagine like you guys are the teachers and I'm like just stumbling in with a bunch of notebooks
One month before the school year is over and I'm like just wait a second
I can take all the tests right now and I'll pass them and you're like, okay, sure you can I'm gonna pass them
I'm gonna get fucking at least a d-minus on all these exams that you guys are giving me right now all your concerns
So concern number one main channel what happened?
Well, a lot of things happened there are four projects that are currently being worked on two of them are already written
They're the whole thing's written. We just have to secure some warehouse space and then we're gonna get shooting
I would have liked to have started shooting already
but there was a pretty significant hold up and without giving any details or
Saying anything is this is a couple of companies were involved. There was potential for
Me to get a very large production budget for one of these projects
And I kind of had to wait to see how that was gonna play out and it fell through so that's not
That's that I don't think that's happening anymore
But there was some potential with that was going to be the case
Now just like the last one got to get the team together strap on the boots pull up the pants and get to work
That dishes that was kind of a little at least the last couple of months was stopping our flow of quote
Production on at least two of these projects
So once we actually get going not against the idea of putting out production stills or showing some sets
But I got to be careful
I don't really want to give away projects don't want to tell you guys what's gonna happen in the videos
Because I like having to like the little bit of magic there
I like how you guys not knowing what's gonna happen or what you're gonna see
So doing a bunch of behind-the-scenes videos and production stills before you see a video
You kind of it kind of like blows it and you get to see
Everything kind of before you get to see it in the first place
And we're gonna get serious now about something that is hard to talk about and we mean about my like production
Friends and people we've sat down we talked about this a bunch of times
But I've never talked about it with you guys and it's money
And it's not a subject that I really love to talk about especially with viewers because
You guys at the very end of the day you watch the videos
You're never expected to
Give money to the videos or participate in paying for them
I have I've tried so long to have that not really be a reality
But I want to see what you guys have to say about it because we've tried like I said
There was a company that we've been talking to
For like a month or two now and it just didn't fucking happen and I can really only give so much of my own money
Like last time like last year the German rumble video that was like that was almost ten fucking thousand dollars in my money
That I and I mean that hurts that hurt that that's like that's drain in the vein a little you know what I mean
so I don't know like is something like a
Kickstarter or a patreon something that I would want to do and that's gonna take a long time for me to figure that out
Because I never want you guys to ever be obligated to feel obligated to have to pay money to this channel for me to make
Videos you should just be enjoying them
You should care about enjoying the videos or the content whatever you want to call it
And I have to worry about paying me for them
And it wouldn't even be paying me if I ever did it like a Kickstarter for one of these projects it would be
only for production stuff for buying warehouse space for buying props buying
Hiring a crew I would me and my producer friend the guy that produced the last video
We've openly stated that I don't want to take a single fucking dollar
There are too many things that I want to do that
I would love to just spend that money on than ever have to worry about anything else
But that did this this is all stuff that has not finalized yet
There's obviously I'm not I don't have there's no Kickstarter. There's no patreon page for me right now
It's just I'm throwing it out there because I want to feel what you guys have to say
I'm gonna be down in the comment section in this video
Reading I'm gonna take I'm gonna put my eyeglasses on and I'm gonna fucking put them down to the bridge of my nose
And I'm gonna read like every single comment 12 times in this video
So, please give me your real
Constructive feedback for this because it's something that I'd really take dead seriously is what you guys have to say
Especially in a case like this other than that the second channel is going very strong
There'll be a link in the description if you don't know if you're kind of out of the loop on this whole thing
I made a second channel where uploads are very frequent
There's at least a few videos there at least two videos there a week and they're all done by holy mac
he's doing a fantastic job editing the streams and
The stream is going very well, too
I'm having a ton of fun on twitch Tuesdays Thursdays and Fridays 7 p.m. Eastern twitch.tv slash German 985 and
Obviously shout outs shouting out my other channels aside
This video is made I wanted to make this video to make sure that you guys are aware that I haven't forgot about you
they this channel is my life like it's it's it's I think about it every single day and
Just because I've branched out to a second channel and now a live platform as well
This there's a lot of stuff that's going on for this channel
And I want to make sure it's good and I want to make sure that you guys enjoy it because if I don't
Deliver then what was the point of me splitting the channels in the first place and I understand that I completely understand
Where a lot of people are coming from actually where they say like fuck man
This you had a lot of subscribers on this channel, and you're just kind that you just like got in a car
With a bunch of fucking stuff like a suitcase, and you drove off
And you never came home you got you guys have been like tending to my house here like it's just an empty house now
I took all this furniture
I took all the stuff in the fridge, and you guys are just in an empty room sitting here looking around like
You kind of come home Jeremy the answer is yes
It's just gonna take time and the projects that you'll be seeing over the next time period
And that's how I'm gonna say you know what I mean like the projects that like the four
Specific projects that you guys will see over time period are stuff
I really hope you're gonna get you're gonna like because it's stuff that we're gonna put a ton of time into
I'm really gonna put effort into them
I'm gonna try want them to be fun and interesting and it's not saying that the other videos weren't
The it's not like the other videos I've ever made aren't worth anything
They are every video on this channel means something to me very much so so please
I'm gonna end the video like this just just hang on for me hang on for me
It is this stuff coming if I ever decide that I'm ever gonna do like
Kickstarter or something you will know well in advance, but it's not happening right now
I it's just I'm throwing it out there like I said just please let me know what you have to say about that
because like
My brain is like
Scrambled goat cheese when it comes to stuff like that have a great fucking rest of your day
Have a great rest of your week. We'll keep in touch. I'm still on Twitter. I'm still on the second channel
I'm still on Twitch
I'm there all the time if you're ever looking for me, so thank you for watching
I will keep you guys up to speed about everything that's going on. Take care everybody. I'll see you all time period