So, here's a picture we've probably seen a million times by now in the last few days. Trying to connect to GT online, it's just not happening. So, let's just go do some more weird shit.
Honestly, lady, you need to calm down. You both need to calm down. He just dropped her so bad. Who are they fighting? Why is he looking at me? He's like, looking at me, but fighting her.
Oh, she's kicking his ass. You won. You win, sir. Jesus. You, Jesus, dude, you won. You psycho. I think you won, dude. You idiot. You need to chill the fuck out.
Look at those mountains. Hello, Santos and San Andreas. They're just such a beautiful place. What a sky. You just don't get skies like this anymore. I should really take a selfie. I'm gonna switch over.
Officer, I don't know if you realize this or not, but there's somebody attached to the back of your car. Are you towing this guy? Are you supposed to be towing this guy somewhere? Well, I'm going to take him off.
You don't have a tow. There's no tow cab thing on the back of a cop car. There's no way he's towing this guy. Where the fuck are these two going?
Yeah, that's a 10-4 taking the car to the dump. I needed to, you know, the dumpster guy was not working today. There we go. They're off now.
What the fuck? He's just up over this hill. Hold on to your seats. Oh, that was a bad idea.
Honest to God, this is the best thing to do in GTA Online. I'm not even driving the car. We're just like holding up the double middle finger.
Oh, do you want to drive your car or would you rather give the middle finger out the window? I think I choose option two.
No, this is my car. It's my car by default because I stole it from you. Don't you get the laws of GTA? Please get out of the way.
Please get out of the way, sir. I know you want to just get the fuck out of my way. I can't even drive the car because he's in it.
Geez, I just got to make sure I impress my boss. I got to make sure he knows that I am here on the force to stay and I'm going to look out and find these criminals and I'm going to get them.
You found me. Now your turn to hide.
Oh man, I got to lay off the hard shit. I don't know how I ended up on this roof. I got to get off. Maybe this is the exit.