Whoa! Whoa! Look at those monsters! Oh, this guy's a monster! Whoa! Whoa! Look at all these
monsters around this hallway! Whoa! Whoa! We have to get 15 minutes into the game, so hurry. Police!
Hey, police! Police! Monsters! I thought we just both were- This one's kind of good.
Mm, this one tastes like raspberry. Oh wow, I drank that in a second.
Oh, I'm drinking through my metal mask. Oh, what's this one do? This one's fruity. I like this one.
This one kind of tastes like urine. I love urine. This one kind of tastes like- What are you doing?
I don't like this. Fuck this. I don't like this drink. This drink's gross. We have to wrap around
because we're going the wrong way. Okay. And once we get- Wow. I really love this game on our new
Xbox One console. We're about to blow up. How far did you just like tumble roll out of an explosion
and we're fine? My Xbox One gaming console. Hey, drama. No, no! It's my joke! It's my joke! Get
out of the- Move. Hello, welcome to, uh, et cetera, et cetera, where we sell all kinds of great stuff.
You just fucking steal something and run. Hey, welcome to et cetera, et cetera, where we only
have one item. A fucking garbage can! And now it's gone. Hey, welcome to et cetera, et cetera,
where we sell all kinds of et cetera. Wow, welcome to et cetera, et cetera. Can we get
in the fucking choo-choo train? So what? Oh, it's like a custom PC builder, man. Hey, come in here,
dude. There's just all kinds of custom PC units in here. Drama, what do you think about if I buy
this computer? Let me check it out for you. Does it look good? Let me check it out for you. I think
this computer, if you go over here, I got a great bunch of PCs for you. See, this one right here,
this one's got your name on it. This one has 32 gigs of RAM and this one over here, this one,
this one's got 42 gigs of RAM. And this one, I'm going to tell you about this one. This one's got
an Nvidia GTX 5200 and it's really great for all your computing needs. Do you email? Do you send
emails? I don't want it. Do you use the phone? I don't want it. Do you send emails? I haven't even
shown you the top of the line product that we have here at computers, et cetera. Come on in.
Whoa, do we have a top of the line product back here? What do you think about that, baby? That's
47 inches. So you're going to be just with the real, the sheer quality of the craftsmanship.
I can tell you right now, it's going to take a whole lot to break this. What the fuck are you
doing? Hey, I just, uh, I want to know, I mean, I know you guys don't sell these here, but, uh,
I mean, can I possibly return this? Yeah, for maybe a banana. Oh, okay. That sounds good. So
you get the computer and I get the bananas. The banana? Okay. This thing is so slow.
Bye. We're going to race. Okay. Oh, I thought you were getting in the motorcycle.
You fucking grinded me up.
Give me the other motorcycle. Oh my God. Come on. Come on. There's another motorcycle back
here I have to get. Fun's over. I broke it. What do you mean it's broken? He's at the half court.
Here it goes. All the people is cheering his name. The people screaming. It's going to get
Oh, a fan is come on to the courtroom. I am the king of the castle and I make all the rules.
My first rule is going to be, I'm going to be the karate master.
That was so bad. I, my first rule is I'm going to be the karate master.
Do not want to screw this up. Big time, big time, big time, hard time, hard time.
Maybe there's a motorcycle there. I'm not sure if you want that, but you can take it if you want.
I'll follow you. All right. You follow me. We're going to go to the markers. No jokes, no jokes,
no goofing. We're doing this for real. No goofing, no jokes, no goofs, no spoofing.
Good luck getting out of the house. I don't think I can. I thought this was the objective.
Come on, get out of the house. Get out of there.
Oh no, this one's going to blow up. Can we, can we do the game part of the game?
That's two cars. Is this your, is your motorcycle in here? No, that's what blew up the first time.
Damn it. No. God damn it. What? We actually just beat chapter one. Are you serious? Chapter
zero. It's the intro. Oh good. Very, very good. Skip, skip. Okay. What?
Give me the fucking broom. I'm going to spare somebody with a broom. I think that's the last
one. That should not be working. Get in. No, I can't get in. Onion rings. This guy's freaking
out. Holy shit. Yeah. This, these guys, this guy riding around in a fucking ultra murder
machine. Dude, will you stop this shit? We're like strippers now. Oh, you did it too? Yeah.
We're the fucking stupid police strippers. All right, let's go. Look at my shoes. What
are these shoes? Is that a fucking coiled up shit? No, it's a pretzel.
I thought it was like a big dump. Welcome to the job interview. Please have a seat.