You are standing in paradise right now, Frank.
Simply take a look around. Do you see anything besides pure beauty?
Would you ever sell it?
Oh, no. Absolutely not.
Everything you see here is all for my boy.
It blows my mind. How does it taste this good?
Well, you don't learn something unless you teach it, in my opinion.
I've been working at the same place, Los Santos University Wine Studies,
for the past 25 years. And counting, let's hope.
Mom saw those guys outside again. It's the third time this week.
I'll handle it. Just stay inside.
This is my vineyard! This is my recipe! You're not going to take it!
You hear me?
You don't understand. It's not just good. It's the best.
We want that wine.
That's not for sale.
What? No, Jeffrey, get down!
Dammit! No!
Oh, you bastard! You son of a bitch! Who did this?
Did he receive our message?
I'm going to need a favor.
You're trying to do this all by yourself? That's crazy talk. What do you need?
I think you know what I'm going to do, Tom.
They tried to kill my son. They torched the very thing that I've put my entire life into.
You want this vineyard? Come and get it.
But I warn you, I have a very special set of skills like the guy from Taken.
I want him dead, and I want his family dead too!
You have no idea who you're dealing with.
You want to bring a fight to me? Now that was a big mistake.
I beg to differ.
They're not going to stop until they get what they want.
If I have to go through every single one of them, so be it.
Wine is complicated. Life is complicated.
Do you have the right ingredients? Do you have the right time frame?
Are you ready to start your winery? Are you ready to start your life?
Write that down, because yes, it will be on the test.