Hey, how are you? Hope you're doing good. I'm doing all right. I just had a chicken Caesar salad wrap.
Finished it up. The whole plate. Like a good boy. That means I get this Captain Crunch.
Happy Father's Day. Happy Father's Day to all you fathers out there. And I'm not a father,
so everyone saying happy Father's Day to me. I'm not. I don't have any children.
But if you do, Dad, Gerva is the father. You're our father. Well, thanks. Thank you.
Thank you, kids. Thanks, kids. Yep. But what did you get me? Okay.
Did you do anything mean? What is that? What is that? Didn't get me anything.
Not going to... I mean, I looked out the window and I noticed
the lawn still ain't cut. Am I going to go do that? Or it's getting kind of tall.
It's getting a little tall. And last night, I just want to... Your mother was coming in with
the groceries and you playing that that cartoon game with the walls of the Minecraft
shooter, whatever it is, Fortnite. You didn't get up and help your mother with the
groceries. And I had to... Thank you, though, kids. Is this shit that your dad said?
Maybe in another time. Not this current time, though. Anyways, hello. Yes. Happy
Father's Day, though. What we're going to do, I'm going to block out a plan for you.
Are you ready for this plan? At the end of this week, I am not going to be here.
I mean, like physically not going to be here. I have some things going on. I am visiting some
family. And during that same time period, about five days or so, I'm going to be doing a lot
of work on a big stream. So I'm going to be spending a lot of time putting it together,
getting it ready. And that's what I'm going to be doing. 50-50 family and like working on a
stream. So I will not be here for about five days. That was disgusting. I'm really sorry.
Another colonoscopy. No, no, no, no. That's the most disgusting sound ever.
This is why I can't be live. See, if this was a recording, I would have been like,
all right, whatever, that's here. And then I would have gotten in and I would have cut that
out. I would have just taken the razor tool and right where it went, cut that part of
the audio, cut that part of the audio at the end, delete, and then put like background noise
there. And you wouldn't even know. I did that a million times. You know, many times I fucking
sneezed on a video and just, it was gone. And then I manipulated the video to a point
where you didn't know I had sneezed on it. Anywho, today we're going to do the movies.
We're going to go back to the movies. Talked about it yesterday. It's been a long enough
time where I think it would be fun to go back in. And also not just about that,
just about that. But more importantly here, five community subs just came in from Derma
lied about the clown car. Thank you for the five community subs. Appreciate the five subs.
Derma lied about the clown car. But I'm going to give you the, let's break it down. So
today we're going to play the movies. I'm going to re-familiarize myself with the game
because it's been like two or three years. I don't really remember all the tools. We're
just going to go through the beginning of the game, maybe start a new studio, make
a few things, whatever, and relax and play and learn the game again, kind of. Now I
also have like a hundred fucking mods, like 40 characters, like 50 new sets, like hundreds,
like hundreds of props. I have tons of fucking mods. We're not going to use those today
because I, I need to, I want to like make sure I know what I'm doing and where we're
going. So there's going to be two movie streams. This one's going to be the
re-familiarize and make some movies. And the one after is going to be like the fuck you table
of movie streams. I don't want to give any spoilers as to some of these characters that
are in it, but I hope they all work. Also star and I are going to be playing deep rock
galactic at some point this week as well. So that's what's going to be happening for the
remainder of this week. I'm going to play that dwarf game, whatever the hell it is.
So now that we've gone over that, you can understand what you can expect this week,
like fucking sick. Okay. Let's open up the movies. If you don't know the movies,
this is some of the best, most fun I think we've ever had on, on camera. I think I would say
gatekeeping your own channel.
Yeah. I was just like, yeah, that's what it is. Gatekeeping my own channel. Why am I doing that?
Let's go. Uh, you cannot hear anything, but you will be able to see. Well, actually never
mind. You can see things now. You remember this screen? It's been a while. So I remember a
little bit. I remember a little bit about the game. I remember like a few things that
are very important to know, but I don't think I need to do like the, I know how to like
move the camera and shit. If I need help, I can go do it. Right? We're going to do new
game, uh, studio, poor productions. What's this? This is important. I need to make an actor. You
got to make directors and like, and cameramen and stuff. Oh yeah. Pop out your eyes. Productions.
No, no, no, no, no, no. We got, this is a different studio. That studio was liquidated.
That doesn't exist anymore. We, we had too many flops and too many bad decisions,
but they're getting, yeah. Get back. They're getting too close. Back up. Yes. I know. Hi.
Excuse me. How about horse? What? No. How about, um, here we go. No, no, no. How about
chopped up? Uh, cut? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Leo incorporated,
Leo P Pants productions. No, it's not going to be Leo P Pants. Uh, I don't know. Prime,
Prime Chuck productions. The name of your studio doesn't matter. It shows nobody.
P Pants limited. Bursting with laughter. Big chin productions. P Pants limited LLC.
P Pants limited limited liability company. No, that sucks. That's like too easy of a joke.
P Pants liability. How do you, should it be P Pants liability? P Pants limited Leo liability,
limited Leo company. How about just P Pants liability? No, I'm not naming my company
machinima. It's fucking liquidated in like less than five years. Got it. P Pants liquidated
company. Sounds pretty good to me. Name. No, that's my name. Okay. P Pants liquidated
is the name of the company. I don't have any actors though. Welcome to the dawn of the movie.
The same fucking thing happened last time I played this. The year is 1920 and your new studio's
success lies in your hands. You must guide it to greatness. You must create the biggest movie
and employ the most famous stars as you strive to reach the summit of the studio charts
and reap the rewards of victory. First build a thriving studio, hire wannabes,
and they're gonna have actors. Here comes the old content that'll get the big box rolling in
and clean up at the awards. Then with every award you win, with every success you enjoy,
your studio's reputation will grow. Soon stars from rival companies will flock to your studio
and you'll unlock new mods, scenes and sets to make your movies better than ever.
But once you unlock those mods, there's no going back. That's why you have to wait till the
next stream. That's once fucking Batman shows up and drop kicks R2-D2 through a glass pane.
We ain't doing the regular game again. Welcome to your new movie studio. Turn this shit up.
Okay, let me get a audio. Let's turn it up. That sounds a little bit better, don't you think?
All right, here's our lot. We have to make some stuff. Before you open the studio,
you'd better set up some of the essentials. I remember some of this. We need the box office,
right? Stage school, right? You can place the stage school anywhere by left clicking
at the desired location. Go ahead, give it a try. We've already done the regular game. I'm
only doing this because I just need to refamiliarize myself with the tools and the controls. I can't
just jump into sandbox mode because I'll just have no idea what I'm doing. It's been three
years since I did the same video in the same stream. Center it. What do you mean center it?
It's off center. It's always going to be off center. All right. To build the stage school,
you'll need to hire a builder at the staff office by the studio. This is the staff,
right? Oh, that's right. You got to go to the studio gate. Now click and hold down
the left mouse button briefly to pick them up. Yeah, you did. It's actually like janitors,
right? And stuff you have to actually create. Follow the sparkling stream and drop them in
the builders. Many janitors by left clicking. Great. Builders perform any building and
maintenance duties automatically so you can leave them to it. Fantastic. While the
stage school is being built, you can use this time to sort out the rest of the building,
which we need, uh, active studio, right? You need one janitor. No, you ever played a game
like this. You need like 30 janitors and you need to put them in patrols in tiny little
locations. Okay. Let's keep going. Okay. Now build a casting casting office, right?
You'll need this for assigning stars to your movies. You can rotate a building by holding
down the left mouse button and moving the mouse around in a circle. Try this now. Casting
office would be down here. P Pants, uh, liability company is, you know, we're going to be get,
make it clean. I'm thinking like, thinking like right here. Great. Now build a crew
facility. Yep. Crew facility. You need crew. Yep. Yep. Yep. We'll have this up here.
Yep. You need to janitor. Let's get a few builders actually.
Okay. You'll also need a set to shoot your movie on. The stage set will be perfect for
you. You're making a porn studio. I am not making a porn studio. Stage, right? Stage.
This is our first little baby set, but this is like 1920. Let's go. Let's go like over here.
Back here. Finally build a production office. You'll need this to release your movie.
Oh, you edit it right. I forgot about this. This is so much. I forgot. We're going to be here for a
while. Production office is going to be over here. I love this. You should put it over here,
right here. Excellent. Now you've got everything you need for your movie. You can look at
improving the studio environment. It's the perfect time to get the jump on the porn industry.
Imagine how rich you get if you invented porn. One of the keys to running a successful studio
is making sure your staff can easily find their way around. Okay. I guess.
Click on the landscaping button, then select the sparkling path icon.
Lay a path by left clicking and dragging out the shape on the ground.
I'm going to connect everything. The flashing connection points on your buildings.
Let's go this way. Did I fuck it up already? Yeah, I did. Don't worry about it though.
This is just for us to learn. Nothing else matters. I can go like this. All right.
This one also needs to be connected. There it is. And we need to our set as well.
This is one little baby line. All right. Excellent. I'm starting to remember. It's all
coming back to me. Another important factor of having a great studio is to make sure your
staff have a nice working environment. Try placing down some ornaments. Trees,
bushes. They're going to make some nice stuff here. Okay. Now place some ornaments around
the studio. Left click to place an ornament and right click to get rid of the one you're
holding. Oh, let's go with how about one of these plates? Am I out of money? Try to use
a range of different ornaments as variety is the best way to keep the studio lot looking
attractive. Okay. Time to move on. Remember to place down more ornaments as the studio expands.
Corners. There we go. This is better. Look at that. There we go. Looks good. Looks good.
Excellent. The studio is now ready. Carry on improving things if you wish. And when
you're ready, you can open the studio. I think we're ready to open. This is the
casting office. This is the stage school. This is the hire crew. You get a director
here. You create a crew. I know what I'm, I think I figured it out. Let's go. Are you
ready to open the studio? I am ready to open the studio. Congratulations. The studio is
officially open. Thank you. Now I need a director and we have to make an actor too.
You are tuned in to KMBS Wireless on a frequency of one to one point five.
And I am your wireless announcer, Mr. William Laker. Director, lead role, crew, extras.
Okay, let's do, so I need a couple actors. Who's this? Jeff Grant. I need to make my
own, don't I? Can I make my own? Is there a way I can do that, right? Would you put Jeff
Grant in here? All right, Jeff Grant is now an actor. There he is. Okay, time to make your
first movie. Director Leo. You won't get far without an actor and a director, so select a
couple of appropriate wannabes at the stage school. Appropriate wannabes. Uh, how about
Jen Bolton? Now you just need a director. Bear in mind that a director won't appear in
front of the camera. That's it. Okay, time to move on. All right, so we've got Jen Bolton and
we got Jeff Grant. So we have, we're ready for, the world is ready for a comedy.
The Bag Boy. I remember this shit. Bag Boy script complete. Follow the stream to the casting
office where you can get your new stars to rehearse them. Okay, I remember this. We're
gonna bring in actors. Let's start by assigning your new director. Okay, let's go. You,
you're here. Cast your new actor. Bag, baggage boy is here. The stars have now started
rehearsing the script. This will help boost the final quality of the movie.
So now we need some crew, right? We need some crew. You guys can be fine. Available
crew will fill any required crew positions so you don't need to assign them. Look at
the movie to see how rehearsal is progressing. Rehearsal is doing pretty well. We can speed
it up. You make a script and then you put it into casting and then okay. Yep, I remember.
I'm just learning how to ride the bike. The script has finished. It's time to bring this
over to shoot it. Your movie is now shooting. Go to the stage set to follow its progress.
Now can't we do it on our own? Let's check what everyone is doing by looking at the cast
and crew information bubble on the movie. They're currently shooting. They're already
shooting. Oh wait, don't they tell you like that you don't have to like unlock that?
I'm pretty sure I have to unlock that. They're running all the way over there.
The first movie always sucks. It's always just like hey this is how you learn how to play the
game. So they're heading for the set. There's only two people. Then he like lifts up barbells
or something. Get in there. Here they come. Oh yeah, it's an old camera. The first scene is now
being shot. You can see the overall movie progress in the movie's information bubbles.
Yeah, you try to lift the barbell. This is the first movie ever made. Scenes that are
still to be shot are displayed in the movie's shooting schedule bubble. Each scene shows which
set it will be shot on. Yes, we're currently in this is just three scenes shooting the first
one. Okay, now you can continue to follow the movie's progress. I didn't even do anything.
In preparation for your next movie, build the new set that has become available.
Cut his mic. Wild West Saloon. Put the sets back here. Okay, while the movie is shooting,
it's worth looking after the rest of the studio. Look around the studio for information icons and
the corresponding tips. Look for those things in the studio. I said we've already got
this is if you can find any job seekers or if you have any spare staff members try turning
someone into a janitor. Yeah, here we go. Here's the janitor. Casey, you're a janitor.
Take care of the place. Okay, anything else that I'm going to need to remember besides the
right? This is okay. Movie player archive reviews, finance, right? Remember this part,
you put the movie over here. This is the crew. Here's actors and directors. I need to make
some characters. When we get out of here, we do sandbox and we start to actually make
movies. I got to make a few people. All right, this one's done. Oh no, it's not. You're still
shooting the same scene. Why am I looking at the wall? And that's not me. Landscape and
ornaments connected over here. Nope, straight ahead. All right, good. So why does the first
movie go? It's a damn shame this game is so hard to come by nowadays. This is one of the
best games ever made. That is true. Unfortunately, it is hard to come by. I wish they would
just re-release it somewhere, put it somewhere. I don't know why they don't do that. Who even
owns the rights to this now? Microsoft? Yeah, Microsoft. Yeah, this could use a GOG release.
All right, double left click on an empty set for a fly through that will show off its key
features. All right, shooting's done. But I want to take a look at it though.
Well, we are just going to watch it. Okay, release the movie. You don't need to...
whatever. All right, baggage boy is released. Script quality is awful. The movie's terrible.
We get to watch it. Here we go. It's time to watch the baggage boy. I guarantee you he just
picks up the dumbbell and he can't lift it and he hurts his back. Here we go. Let's
take a look at that movie. Yep, that's it. That's the whole thing. What is this part?
I don't remember this part. Why am I getting like yelled at? It took 11 months to make this
shit. Wow, I didn't remember that. All events and characters in this movie are fictional.
Anything similar to real people living or dead is a coincidence. Right, there we go.
No, I don't... we're not watching that again. Okay, that was the baggage boy.
Pretty good. The effective movie on your staff and studio. They're not that stressed
up but they made some money. It cost ten dollars. Was that... is that ten bucks?
Eleven bucks. That's not eleven thousand. Six months to make. It's blatantly obvious
that Jeff Grant doesn't have a great deal of comedy experience directed with a blatant
disregard for quality. Grant, I didn't make it. If I made it we would have people fucking
screaming. The movie makes money over the course of a couple years. Right.
This game is so fucking good. I miss it. I'm so glad... you know when... okay, here's the thing.
You know when you don't do something for so long and you come back and it's like brand
new again? That's how I feel right now. I feel like I'm... I'm glad I don't remember
much from like a couple years ago, whatever, two, three years ago. Oh, this is fantastic. I'm
so glad that I like don't remember any of this. Your studio's chart rating is based on the
movies you release, the stars you employ, and the overall status of your studio.
The bigger your stars, the higher your studio rating. Alright, time for me to make one. I'm
gonna make a little one. The better your movies, the higher your studio rating. It's not quite
time to go into the sandbox mode yet. Let's click on the rosette. Old Rope Cinema,
Pee Pants Liquid. These are the rival studios. Okay, movie charts. Okay, star charts and then
studios. Yeah, it just shows you how you're doing. Now that you have a movie out and some
money in the bank, it's time to take a closer look at your stars and staff. People in
weird costumes and stuff. Your employees need good sanitation, so place down some restrooms
to improve your studio rating. Your employees need good catering provisions too. A snack van
will do for now. Great, this will raise not only your catering rating, but your overall
studio rating too. Happy stars make better movies. If you want a star to perform well
in a movie, you need to make sure they're happy. That's too convenient of a bathroom
location. What do you mean? It's bad. So who the hell am I gonna make? I have to make
like a couple of directors, I gotta make some actors. I made like Glooman last time.
When the mood bar goes below the lower threshold line, it will glow red. This means a star is
very unhappy. You can't. You can only make like default characters. You can't make like
huge noses. I could do Jax. One aspect of a star's mood is how they feel about their image.
Try hovering over your stars to see how they feel. You have to work on like clothes and
stuff. Yeah, okay. One way to improve a star's image is to give them a makeover.
Give them a makeover. Remember, you can rotate. You can drop builders around the sides of the
building to speed up construction if you want. Use the arrows above the star icons to view your
other staff types. Staff icons can be used in the same way as star icons. You can drop
builders around the edges like orcs. Okay, speaking of builders, and where are they?
Make Super Jax a director. I can't. I can't make Super Jax. How am I supposed to do that?
Yeah, I can do Adam Sandler. That's easy.
See it before it drives off on the real plan. The makeover department is built.
Pick up a star whose image you want to improve. Okay, let's go with um, let's go with Jeff
Grant. Okay, give this star a makeover. Go to the bathroom. Follow the guiding stream to
your new makeover. Go to the bathroom. The makeover department is built. No, no, no. Okay,
give this star a makeover. Drop a star in the makeover room to enter the makeover screen.
Okay, I can re, I can rename. Okay, this is the 1920s. How do I get, how do I take the
hat off? Oh, I forgot. This is the, this is the 1920s. Nobody never, nobody ever didn't
have a hat on. People like slept in their hats, didn't they? Okay, not bad. Those long,
long ass sideburns. That's fine. That's fine. This is just temporary. This is temporary,
temporary, temporary. Or use the auto room if you don't mind what using the makeover
screen is. No, I hate it. And gives you more control, but be careful not to choose something
that. Holy shit, he's about to lose his mind. Well, I guess I did to take his hair. Stars
are happy with their image. Somebody said, Hey, I'm going to do a makeover for you.
Oh, are you? Yeah, I'm actually just going to like cut your hair off and fuck your whole
head up and make you bald and then put you in underwear and make you leave. Okay. Great.
Remember to revisit the makeover department. If any stars are unhappy with their image,
I think I can remember mostly everything now until we, we get to like the more
intricate stuff with the timeline editor, but I think it'll just start to come back to me as
I play. All right. Let's, let's just, let's see if I can make another movie.
As you can imagine, the more successful your stars become, the more money they want.
Play with mods. I am going to play with mods, just not tonight. I'm going to be doing
another movie stream where I literally throw up a bunch of dog shit into the boulders.
I have hundreds of files that have to be installed. I have probably a hundred and like
25 different props and characters and costumes and shit. It's going to be out of control.
Hover over one of your stars to see how they feel about their salary.
If you want to give a star a raise, take them to the production office.
Yeah, there's a blue screen. Yes. I'm going to be
giving you guys some footage to use if you want to.
All right. So let's hover into the production office.
Finance room. Here we go.
There. Have a little bit more money.
Okay. I guess I'm all right with you cutting my hair off.
Stars can become jealous of their colleagues, too, if treated unfairly.
All right. At some point, your stars will begin to get bored and will need something new to do.
Have a look at your star's information bubbles to see how bored they are.
If the boredom bar falls below the threshold line, a star will become very bored,
which will affect their mood. The bar will gradually go down when a star has no work.
The boredom bar.
You're fine. You're fine. Still making money.
Sixty-one thousand bucks.
Making movies is a good way to prevent stars from becoming bored.
You've acquired another script, which can be found at the studio gates.
Here's our new script.
Remember to follow the guiding streams and read the information bubbles to see what you need to do.
Let's get you in the leading role.
This movie has some minor roles that you can fill with extras.
You can hire extras at the stage school.
Okay. I think that's it. I think I know what I'm doing.
I think it's time to actually start, like, the real game.
This movie has some minor roles that you can fill with extras.
You can hire extras at the stage school.
So we have to go back into sandbox.
This movie has some minor roles that you can fill with extras.
You can hire extras at the stage school.
I think I'm pretty sure I got the right idea now.
I just needed to do that initial, like, tutorial to get back into the swing of things here.
I'm gonna save it just in case there's something I don't remember
that I have to come back and remember and re-familiarize.
So I think that's good.
All right. Let's go and do the real one.
And that's, let's make, I gotta make characters first.
All right. I turned it down because it's very loud.
I have to go back to the main menu.
Okay. So, game.
There's sandbox, but I don't, I need, it's a, it's a different window,
isn't it, to make a new character?
I think I have to open a separate thing.
Yeah, it's a, it's a different EXE.
All right. Give me Zach.
Let's get that open.
Let's make the characters.
So who the fuck did, this is really important because whoever is in here,
this is like who we use for the whole game.
It's gotta be some, it's gotta be people who they'd like to have.
Let's get it open.
You guys can, I think you guys can see it, right?
We should be able to.
Okay. Star maker.
Here it is.
Might have to run this in a different window.
Hopefully it's not too loud.
Is it running in this?
It is running in a separate window, isn't it?
All right. Here we go.
Hey, look. Hey, look at that.
Can you not see it?
Why not?
Come on, show it.
Why can you not see it?
Why can you not see this?
Star maker.
It's showing up here.
Well, this is dumb.
I mean, it's clearly here.
Let me try this.
It's not technically a game though.
Can you see it now?
That's irritating.
Ah, there's only, there's one more way I can get this to work
and it's I just hit the pole.
Just capture the whole, hold on.
Bear with me here.
I don't know why it's not capturing this.
It's kind of annoying, but what the fuck just happened?
Why did I lose every window?
Why are computers so dumb?
All right, well hold on.
This is important.
Monitor capture is the only way this is going to work.
There we go.
Hey, look, it's a tiny little window,
but you can see it at least.
Boomer wallpaper.
This has been the wallpaper for like a year.
Yeah, so window capture didn't work.
Game capture didn't work.
Only display capture.
Let's go.
Actor.
Let's go like this as well.
Just to make it a little bit better for you.
All right, so this is Jex.
All right, basic settings.
Let's do, what is, we got to get a good base here.
That's not a bad base.
Jex is not that old.
It's definitely not this guy.
This one's not bad.
Hold on.
No.
Why can I not go down here?
Looks.
Oh, here we go.
This is important.
It's really good action.
Not that great comedy.
Stress threshold.
Boredom.
Food.
Definitely have actions full.
Trimness.
All right, we can't have him be that good looking.
He's got to be kind of more sci-fi.
No, he had no comedy at all.
Action, horror, split this up evenly.
Boredom, drink.
He needs to drink all the time.
Stars, drink.
Addiction threshold.
You don't have to be that trim.
How about chest size?
Actually, no, that is important.
All right, that's okay.
Horror.
He's like a little bit funny.
And then mood.
Hey, he's like...
But Jex is not even handsome.
He's not funny at all.
No, why would, I'm the funny one, okay?
I think that's all right.
Base, eyebrows.
Oh, eye makeup, necessary.
Facial hair, none.
Change the hairstyle.
See if we can find Jex's hairstyle.
And that's...
Anything like him at all.
Owen Wilson.
Okay, this is it.
I like this one.
He-Man.
Lois Griffin.
No, it's not Lois.
Oh, it's a ponytail.
I gotta change that.
I think it's just gonna have to be this.
That's not Jex.
No, it isn't.
There we go, all right.
He's got a different fit.
Okay, that's...
I like it.
It's staying.
This is oblivion Jex.
Here we go.
A little bit less.
Oh, this is teeth in or teeth out.
All right.
Down here we got jaw.
Not really that close, but I think close enough.
It's the fucking hair.
I can't even see the ears anyways.
Looks good.
Huge head.
Turn on face cam.
No, he's not a fucking cone head.
All right, hold on.
Let me go back to the hair.
The hair is just killing this.
He looks like an emo singer.
He's got a huge head.
His head's not that huge, is it?
This is John.
E-emo John.
His head's too big.
It looks ridiculous.
All right, hold on.
This is...
I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What just happened?
Okay.
No, what?
Wait, how do I save this?
Is he saved?
Oh, save.
Okay.
Okay, save.
Load.
Okay, so this is...
We can rename...
We're gonna rename him.
Oh, fuck this.
I can't rename him.
Okay, it's all right.
It's okay.
I can rename him later.
Wait, could I?
Was there a rename?
No, I can do it in the change costume.
Okay, create actor.
Let's go...
This is me.
Let's get the hair right.
I'm actually gonna...
I'm not doing like the bald fucking head.
This is...
I'm gonna get my actual hair.
I mean, that's pretty...
That's pretty close.
No, it's not, but whatever.
Looks fine.
That's a little extreme.
Okay.
My eyes are always like wide open.
My mouth is out a little.
I'm usually pretty happy.
This looks like Mark Zuckerberg.
Whatever.
That's like every image you've ever seen
of Mark Zuckerberg's face.
All right, pull the chin back.
I don't have that big of a chin.
I kind of have a turkey neck.
Let's pull the cheeks in.
They're not that...
They're shorter than that.
I got a big eyebrow bone.
It looks good.
I kind of have like a skinny head like that.
Okay.
All right.
I gotta change the eyes.
You have a...
It's a small brain.
What do you mean small brain?
Change the hair.
What's wrong with the hair?
That is the hair that I have right now.
What do you mean change the hair?
That is...
That is my hair.
My current...
Right now, my hair.
Oh, God.
That's actually pretty...
That's actually better.
I'm not gonna do this.
Like this is just fucking nuts.
I'm not doing this one.
Everyone's gonna want me to do this one.
But come on.
This is too easy.
This is so easy.
This is like every wrestler from the 90s haircut.
Like I don't want to do...
I do this every time.
Do my...
I'm gonna do my actual hair.
This is it.
Unless they have one of the other ones like when it's short.
It's not that.
It's not that either.
I don't have like the M.
Can I change his name?
I'm sure...
Can I change his name to Mark Zuckerberg?
This is not even me.
This is Mark Zuckerberg.
We're gonna have Zuckerberg be in our movies.
This is...
I don't care.
I'm done.
This is gonna be...
This is Mark Zuckerberg.
What color is his hair?
It's his red.
Mark Zuckerberg has red hair.
Yeah, he has the facial expressions too.
His hair's not green.
Yeah, it's like this.
That's fine.
Okay, that looks good.
What the fuck?
Why is this...
This is...
I don't even want...
I want to change this.
I swear to God.
All right.
Can I make me know?
Or should I make...
All right.
I just keep it like this.
Just do...
That's it.
This is Adam Sandler.
It's Bobby Hill.
No.
I can't have like all these...
They all have the wrong name.
No, this is Adam Sandler.
What do Adam Sandler's ears look like?
Fix the hair?
I will.
Just hold on.
Hold on.
Okay.
No, I gotta read...
This is gonna be like...
I don't know.
I'm like the Anvil.
Anthony Anvil.
Anvil Sandler.
All right.
Yeah, I like it.
Good job.
Good work.
Yeah, we can't...
We gotta like get rid of the fucking real people, man.
This is like Arthur Cube brain.
Look at that profile.
Okay, eyes.
We're gonna change these eyes.
Okay, this might be the best person.
It's somebody in a silicone mask.
That's what this is.
This is B.F. Bugleberry levels of person.
This is a person in a silicone rubber mask.
This is...
Okay.
All right.
I think that's good.
Now, is the hair the right...
Okay.
Which hair is this?
I think the hair is perfect.
I don't think I want to change anything.
Oh, I forgot to do the stats.
Anvil.
The Anvil.
All right.
That looks good.
Everything looks set from here.
I'm not...
The hair is, I think, perfect.
All right.
Hopefully, I can change these names.
Otherwise, it's going to be a very odd...
A very odd world here.
All right.
We'll make a couple more.
Let's do...
I gotta get...
Okay.
We keep making people,
and then we make them look way different
than where they're named,
and then I have to rename them.
How about...
Betty.
It could be anything.
Betty can be anything.
Could be anything.
Consistently just doing the people's eyebrow.
Let's get down here.
She looks drunk.
I don't know.
Betty could be anything.
Turning into a Simpsons character
is what's happening here.
Too much...
That's too much skin.
Betty the Brick.
Oh, I mean...
Betty the Goldfish?
I can't even say it.
Nobody said...
RuneScape NPC.
Well, I don't even play RuneScape.
Why do I know what that looks like?
I don't even know what that means,
and I know what it means.
That's the odd thing.
I can see it.
Betty RuneScape.
That's so fucking ridiculous.
Okay.
All right.
Hair.
I don't know if I want to change the hair.
All right.
This, weirdly enough, this is like...
This is like Dollar Store Daenerys Targaryen.
I think I like the RuneScape hair.
All right.
Where's the RuneScape NPC hair?
Where is it?
Look at all this.
Where is that hair?
It's very important.
That's not it.
I lost it.
There it is.
This is going to be so stupid.
Looks good.
No.
That's just the way it is.
Okay.
This is Betty.
All right.
Uh...
Action.
Comedy.
Let's just do a perfectly balanced...
All right.
That's good.
Yes.
That's the thing.
Of course.
All right.
Save it.
Save.
All right.
Now, let's do two more.
Actor.
This is now going to be...
Make Todd Howard.
Todd.
Why is everybody like...
Why do you want Todd Howard?
How about just Howard?
Okay.
Todd Howard is not 38.
He's like 47.
How old is Todd Howard?
That's 47?
That looks way older than 47.
I'm close to the...
Hold on.
That's not how old people look when they're 42.
Am I going to just go down a straight 90-degree edge
in like the next three years?
No.
No, I'm not.
Okay.
I think we're good.
Like, this could be the person that you want it to be,
but that's not who this is.
It's not.
All right.
In the middle is fine.
It kind of looks like me.
Weird.
I'm just starting to really actually look like me.
This is me.
That's looking a little weird, isn't it?
At least in my opinion.
It's like Disney animated version me.
Go like this.
Or like face scan me.
What about the hair?
Hopefully I can rename all these people.
Otherwise, this is going to be a joke.
Maybe not.
Do I not even know what I look like?
2012, Jerma.
It could be.
This is like good boy, Jerma.
Yeah, this is...
Okay, I kind of like good boy.
This is like...
How many different good boys are there?
Is there another version?
This is pretty fucking close.
Should I do no country for old men, Jerma?
These are all so many different versions of me.
I gotta...
Hopefully, to God, I can rename them.
I think I like missed a good boy.
Where is it?
Hairy fucking neck.
Okay, that looks good.
I'm so stressed.
All right, looks good.
All right, one more.
Who do we even have?
We have Andrew the Anvil.
We have...
Who's that supposed to be?
Mark Zuckerberg?
We have...
John Howard.
These are all so wrong.
I can't change them.
It's going to be...
We're going to be fucked.
All right, this is it.
Give me like...
No, there we go.
65.
You look like 100.
All right, that's fine.
All right, last one.
Here we go.
Wait, I need hair.
Give him a long nose.
Why would he have a long nose?
Not bad.
I don't understand the teeth part.
Not bad so far.
Pop the cheeks out a little bit.
Ears are fine.
What's going on with his mouth?
I don't know what is happening
with his mouth here, but whatever.
Looks good.
Give him a big nose.
No, I'm not going to give...
No, everybody doesn't need a big fucking honker.
I like him.
Okay, stats.
Hair.
Let me just make sure.
Much better.
Okay.
All right, stats.
Let's do pretty balanced.
I kind of like this more.
Oh shit, here comes the police.
Look at all this neck hair.
Yeah, I don't know why that's there.
That's good.
Should we have him like with a mustache?
How about a beard?
I don't hate this.
Why is this Leo P pants?
No, clean shave is fine.
All right, it's time to make the studio.
It's time to play the game.
I'm ready, but hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Leo Howard, which is me.
Betty, which is Betty.
Adam Sandliff, which is Adam Anvil.
Jeremy is actually Zuckerberg.
And then Jax is actually John.
We need to make...
Hold on.
We actually have to make a Jax.
This is actually...
This is the real Jax now.
Is it 18?
I don't think this person is 18.
Can I see some Jax's in the chat, please?
So I can get a good reference here.
This needs to be like a little sweet.
Like this one here.
No, different one.
This is just Fred from Scooby-Doo.
That's not who I'm trying to make here.
I think I want it to be this.
I think this just is what it's going to be.
This is so ugly.
What do you mean?
Did you see the last five characters
that I made in the game?
This is close.
I mean, he's going to have a huge jaw.
Let's do the jaw first.
I'm going to pull the cheeks in here.
All right, looks good.
That makes him look bogged enough.
This doctor's strange.
This is the doctor...
Okay, cover the screen with your hand.
I'm making Benedict...
What's his name?
No, not Benedict Arnold.
There we go.
Nice.
Just constantly fucking squinting.
Just constantly.
I'm a pro.
Okay.
I need to bring in the cheeks.
I wish I could bring these cheeks in.
This is so ugly.
Somebody in the chat just says,
this is so ugly.
Please don't do that.
I kind of hate this.
But at the same time, I kind of like it.
All right, that's it.
No more characters.
Let's go.
Nothing else matters.
This is Matt Damon.
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe it'll tell me...
Oh, hey, you can't use that name.
All right, we're ready to go.
So many Jeremy's that...
Don't worry, they're going to be replaced.
All right, done.
They're all Jeremy.
And don't worry, we're going to get...
I don't want all created characters
because there's going to be other characters
that come up through the rankings
that we think are cool.
So everybody's done.
Let's go.
I think I can just close this, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I don't think...
Where do you pull those people up from?
I don't know.
Let me just reopen the game.
I got the...
Yeah, I have a default background.
It's all right.
What do you want me to have in my background?
What would you rather me have?
All right, let's go.
Time to create actual pee pants liquidated.
All right, game.
Sandbox.
It's time.
Game starts in...
1950 is fine.
I get $100 million.
The building's constructed instantly.
Buildings don't decay.
Start with the studio a lot already.
So we don't have to go through all that.
Take the money and run.
Just create it and then leave.
All right, here we go.
Instant movie making.
I forget if that's...
I think, yeah, they just get shot
and we can edit them.
Yeah, there's no audio because I have it turned off
because it's really loud in the menu.
Stars don't misbehave.
That's fine.
Buildings don't decay.
Here we go.
Game starts in 1950 so gives us some opportunity.
$100 million in 1950 is like $100 billion now.
Let's go.
Pee pants.
Pee pants liquidated.
Where is it?
And I'm Jeremy.
That's me.
Let's go.
Time to make a movie.
So we need to have...
Who's going to be the director?
And how do we bring people in?
How do we load characters in?
Are they just going to be in the game?
I'm not sure.
Did I even make anybody?
Yeah, where's like...
Is there like an import character feature?
Create, Builder, Fire.
Hold on.
Release.
Bar.
Import star.
Here we go.
Okay.
So I think we just have to drag
like somebody over here, right?
Yeah.
All right.
Import star as director.
Okay, so let's bring...
I got to rename them though.
This Jex.
All right, Jex.
We're going to do a makeover.
You are just Jex.
That's fine.
Bring in Leo.
Bring in...
I don't...
Howard?
But who's going to direct?
Betty.
Should I just make this like Zuckerberg?
I'm just going to make this the director.
Okay, these are all everyone's waiting.
Make me the director.
Oh, I can't have any more actors.
Oh, shit.
Who do we fire?
Who's the worst out of all these?
Who's the worst actor?
No, Betty is staying.
Is it Howard?
I think Howard just has to be...
Howard just has to be the director.
Howard sucks.
All right.
Howard's director.
Are they all directors?
No.
No, they're not.
Okay, I can't have any more people.
Who am I missing?
I don't care if I'm missing like the emo John.
All right, so let's make a set.
Let's get a...
Let's do like a movie.
Let me just...
I got to see if I remember how the fuck to even do all this shit.
Here, a bunch of janitors.
That's the most jan...
I can't have any more janitors.
So let's...
It's script, right?
Who is the script house?
Casting office.
Begin casting crew.
Shoot it.
I need the script office.
Make some crew.
And let's also make some extras.
Can I...
Can I not make...
How many extras?
Oh, right, right, right.
Okay.
Is this it?
This is the makeover department.
This is the trailer.
Give us John.
Well, somebody has to go.
Somebody has to be fired completely.
Custom script building.
But isn't that in a certain office?
Script office.
Here we go.
Okay.
So now I want to do...
I don't know what that means either.
Oh, is this mainstream pan movie making?
No, no, no, no, no.
I need to grab a...
I got to start making a movie and then put it over here.
My god damn it.
This is like just...
I got to bring you to over here, right?
I need to make a script.
But how do I make a script?
Don't I need like a screenwriter?
How about just like let's do comedy.
And then script.
How do I like edit this?
This thing is called alpha male.
This is where the tutorial would have been better.
Should remember how to do all this.
You bring this somewhere, don't you?
Custom script building.
Is that in a separate...
Is that a different studio building?
Oh, it's a...
Yeah, it's not even here.
Okay.
How can I put it?
Custom script writing.
This is it.
All right.
Advanced movie maker.
This is it.
Okay.
So sorry, Howard.
You're not happy about this.
So, you know, just stop doing it.
Just put this in the can.
Well, you're just going to do it anyway, so it don't matter.
All right, here we go.
Welcome to the advanced movie maker.
The powerful yet easy to use tool
that lets you create your very own movie masterpieces.
The longer your movie is,
the diversity and quality of its sets and scenes
and the more lead roles, extras, and costume changes it has,
the better it'll be.
However, the quality of your script writing facilities
in your studio lot
will determine the maximum possible quality of your movie.
All right, here we go.
Let me see if I remember how to do this.
Making an action movie, lead role.
We're going to have, let's have Leo.
Let's have Jax be supporting, just to see.
And then Adam Salem also supporting.
Leo as, this is all just to make sure
I remember how to do all this.
You can stay as Kurt.
That's fine.
And you can stay as Will.
Structure.
This is where we want it to be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Detailed, right?
Freeform, trying to remember.
If it was, I think it's freeform.
It's been so fucking long.
Was it freeform?
Yeah, freeform that isn't based on the Hollywood.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right, here we go.
So we're going to start with,
yeah, you get to pick the different starting areas.
Let's just go to the bathroom.
Okay, this is where it begins.
Why are there zombies in here already?
Okay, so who's carrying who here?
Wait, why are you carrying him?
Oh, that's Jax.
That's okay.
He looks different.
Why are there people in here like this?
You don't even need to be in this bathroom.
Okay, so this is the, let's go in here.
Let me just see.
Preparation into the bath.
All right, let's just have you get in the bath.
This is, no, I'm not a porn director.
Okay, getting in the bath.
I want to put the camera.
We could have a change of camera.
Movie view, there we go.
All right, so that's Jax getting in the bath.
Down here we add scene, add a scene down here.
Same thing, bathroom.
Is there just like, just like taking a bath?
Let's see, like bath, just like taking bath.
Sad photo.
Wait, what is bath horror?
It's just already done.
Who's in the mirror?
There's nobody even in the mirror.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second.
So why, why can't,
has it got to be a better transitional piece here?
No, I want, let's, let's go with,
enter horror.
Let me see what we got here.
No, no, no, you're already in the bath.
This has to be somebody else.
Why would you have somebody smoking a cigarette in here?
All right, so he gets in the bath.
Just have like a bunch of angles of him getting into the bath.
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, okay, bath.
Let's go, bath.
Bath, enter, bath, massage.
Bath, drown.
They sneak in and just drown them?
Hold on, hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, why are they, why would they be doing this?
Okay, hold on, hold on.
This has to be different people.
You two come in.
Why are you in different clothes?
He's in a different, he's in different clothes.
Why the fuck is his hair white?
This is like the Joker.
Why does his hair turn gray?
Wait, who the fuck is this?
No, this is Adam Sandler in here.
Okay, well, that's what's going on.
Okay, that makes sense.
But then watch, why does his hair change color?
He comes in and then all of a sudden now he's, he has white hair.
Why did he age like 30 years?
Something, no, hold on.
Something ain't right here.
It's shampoo.
I didn't, I didn't set their costumes at the start.
Right, okay.
Well, it's all right.
We'll, we're learning again.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need to add a couple of scenes here.
Let's go static.
There's nobody in the scene,
but we're going to put this over here.
Can I rearrange this?
I can, okay.
The static of the bathroom.
And he gets in.
No, no, no, he needs to get,
he needs to walk into the bathroom first.
That's important.
Here comes the soldiers.
Admire baby.
Applied perfume.
He's going to put perfume on
before he goes in the bath, apparently.
There's his hair again.
Put this back this way.
We need him coming in.
Enter cold.
All right, let's, I can't make this longer.
I don't want you to be here.
So we need to put, we need to put a dummy here, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so this is Jax coming in.
I'm flying perfume.
Drag the actor to the hanger.
Okay, right.
Here we go.
All right, is that,
will he be in this the whole time, I think?
Is he going to get in the bathtub with all his clothes on?
Okay, hold on.
Are they in the same space team?
No, you don't even need to be here.
No, this lady doesn't need to be here.
We've done our trial run.
All right, now we need to,
I need to have you.
There's got to be a reason why this happens.
Bath horror, bath shock.
Someone is shocked by someone, something nasty in the bath.
Oh, it's, he's shocked by him in the bath.
All right, I want to put this down.
How do I move the camera down and up?
I forget what the controls are for this.
Because I want to put the camera in a different spot.
What is it?
Alt, arrow keys.
I think it's like shift and, shift and arrow keys.
Alt and the arrow keys.
Shift and scroll.
I know it's something, some combination.
It's not middle mouse, W A S D.
No, it's come on, get down there.
Control, page up, page down.
Damn it.
Shit.
Well, it's all right.
I'll figure it out later.
So this needs to be over here.
And then have him get in the bath.
Plus and minus.
So he comes in, cold.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is going to be over here.
It's all plus shift plus tab.
Wait, what?
And then he gets into the bath.
So enter bath.
Bath massage, bath horror, bath enter.
Now he's going to get in.
But I want the free-form cameras to show him like,
okay, hold on.
Like I need to be able to fucking move this camera.
All right.
What about here?
Toggle empty parts on.
And then he drowns.
He then he drowns him.
All right.
Let me, let me, give me this.
Okay.
I think, let's just see how this looks.
Now we got to add music and sounds and shit.
Is it the number pad?
No, too bad.
All right.
So now let me just make sure that there's nothing else I want to really do.
Just to test this movie.
So now we have to have him like run away.
Should we just carry him out?
Walk with axe.
Carry box.
Jolt?
Wait, an explosion.
Intensity.
Moderate duration short.
No, I don't, I don't want that.
I don't like it.
We're going to delete it.
How about investigation?
Prop.
Bashing objects.
Pick up weapon.
Traveling.
No, just, just exit.
Violence.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's do, what do we have for violence?
Fight.
Brandish blade.
Confrontation.
Dead body.
There's the scream spin.
Death in arms.
But he drowns him and then he dies in his arm?
Okay, what?
How, when does he die?
How long does it take for him to die?
Someone's just brushing their teeth.
Someone comes in and just starts brushing their teeth.
Not kissing.
Um, panic.
It's taking a very long time.
Is it, can I change the duration?
And then he drowns him again.
No, no, no, no.
Not opposites.
You need to be, you need to pick him up and put him down in the bath and then drown him again.
This time, this, this time his hair is normal.
I hate this.
I need to like have it cut like here.
You know what I'm saying?
Not here.
I need to have him pick him up, put him down, like put him down
and have the edit beat right here.
Okay, that looks good to me.
Yeah, you do that in post.
Yep.
All right, so then, so he needs to pick him up.
Pick up weapon.
No, pick up or carry.
Carry person.
I don't know why there's so many random zombies.
Location.
Uh, we're going to go rescued, angry, dead.
Okay.
And then I need to put down.
So this needs to be over here.
He cries and then, is there a pick up?
Just have a zombie here?
No, that's not, that's not going to make any sense.
Uh, I need a, I need like a pick up.
Is there a pick?
I'm going to sneeze.
Investigate.
Close book.
No.
Someone is shocked by something.
Oh, no.
Read open book.
Take photo.
A group of people gather around a dead body.
Find corpse.
Prop focus.
Gun sneak by.
Murder scene.
No.
Is he reading on the toilet?
All right, pacing.
We need pacing because he can't, he doesn't know what to do.
So he's going to pick him up and drown him again.
Duration medium.
He's a little too happy though.
I wonder what's the solution here.
All right.
Put that here.
Drown.
Okay.
Then he's dead.
Doesn't know what to do.
Picks him up.
Puts him back in the bathtub.
I need a pick up body.
Enter.
Horror.
Exit.
Carry.
Enter.
Pick up weapon.
Examine.
Examine would probably be fine.
That's right.
Examine body.
Let's just see what it looks like.
Different, wrong people, but.
Look, you cut it right here.
Okay, this one's good.
We could trim it so he ends up picking him up.
You know, it goes down like this.
And then we cut to him walking.
Checking his pulse.
Reaction to body.
Angry.
Sad.
Laugh.
Why is he going?
No, no, no.
I hate it.
That's no.
We're going to do sad.
Sad works.
So that is over here.
So then he picks him up.
All right.
Drowns him again.
And then runs out.
I don't know why I just did war bombed street.
Sniper search.
Sniper duel.
We can do that later.
No, this is good.
This is good.
This is done.
I can edit it.
I just want to, I just, we're just doing a little one just to try.
Get out of town.
It's just a default name.
Okay.
Now I bring this over to, what do I bring this now?
Over to casting.
And then they shoot it.
But isn't it, it's not already cast?
I thought I already did that in the advanced section.
No?
Yeah, it is cast.
So what's, I don't understand.
You have to do that, I guess.
Let me see.
All right.
No, it is.
So we just need some extras.
Who is the, what do you mean extras?
Who are the, who's an extra in this?
Why would there be an extra?
How do I get an extra in here?
I don't know who this is.
Writers needed.
There's no one writing the script.
Shoot it.
Okay.
This should be done.
I have instant movie making, right?
All right.
So now I take this into, what do I take this into?
I take it into like the advanced movie maker, right?
I think, actually, I don't think I have it.
Post-production.
Do I not have one of these?
I thought I did.
Okay.
Post-production.
Here we go.
Welcome to post-production where you can edit and enhance your movies in a variety of ways.
You can also export your movies as files that you can then send to your friends or post online.
It's time.
It's time to make the doughnuts.
So let's open up the, the art of war is the song.
No, it ain't going to be the art of war.
How do I remove that?
Just delete it.
All right.
Let's get a song here.
No, I'm not going to do acid bass.
How's this one?
How about Armageddon?
Advancing Army.
How's about that?
That's essentially the same title as the movie.
I don't, I like it.
Let's put the volume down a little bit.
Uh, I want something, I want a better title in here.
I'm going to add a title because I don't like this one.
Now, Lionhead movies.
No, no, no.
How do we get out of this title?
I think we can add it later.
Maybe ABC.
Oh yeah.
I can record voiceover on this too.
Let's see here.
So this starts out like this static.
Hold on.
It's because he comes in with them.
I didn't, I, is this the extra?
It's so fast.
Okay.
All right.
Now we know where the extra is and I can't remove them.
It's already been filmed.
Okay.
So we need some sound here.
We need like a, okay.
How about right here?
Let's have bed squeak door, open door, metal, bang, metal, freak, whistle.
Police.
What is whistle police?
No.
Human sounds.
It has to be like, mm hmm.
I'll have a cough and then he gets in.
He gets in the bath.
He comes in way too fast.
Okay.
Now we need, we need like a, we need like a, oh, it's hot.
Scream.
Is there a way you can hear them?
I thought there was.
Why don't I just make the noise?
Okay.
So it's too hot.
All right.
We need, we need a scream here.
So like right here.
It's good.
And then we need like an, ah, this is probably fine.
That's not what I thought it was going to be.
It's just one grunt.
It's because the camera.
I wanted to have to, is it, can I not?
How do I make the camera stay?
That's very important.
He's going to scream a couple of times too.
Not a porn game.
All right.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's going to be like a pluzz.
No belch.
No cough.
He does kind of like cough a little, like right here.
He turns over.
He turns his head over.
We need, ah, scream.
One, scream.
Two, sniff.
Okay.
Big slurp.
This looks good.
And then we need like, ah, breathe heavy.
This goes on so long.
He's, he's, he's smelling his hands.
That's so stupid.
There you go.
It's the purview.
I can't put a fart sound in here.
That's so easy.
We need to have like coughing.
He's like swallowing.
This is so awful.
He's swallowing so much water that he's just like.
These aren't even burps.
This is fucking horrible.
No, we need more coughs.
This burp sucks.
I'm only going to put this in temporarily because people are demanding it.
No, no, no, it's not.
It's so stupid.
I don't know if I can have it.
You guys realize I have to do this again.
This happens another time.
Fuck this.
The little shake.
It's like right here.
No, but if he smells here, then I.
No, this changes everything.
No, it can't be like this.
Come on, don't start lagging on me now.
Back here, back here, back here.
It's going to be more frequent.
It's supposed to be smelling the perfume and not the.
Does it kind of copy these?
Is there a way I can just copy?
I hate that.
This is fucked up.
This is this is like getting borderline not safe for work.
All right.
Then what happens is he picks up.
Okay, right here.
I mean, he dies.
I don't even need the scene.
This whole scene doesn't even need to exist.
And this whole scene doesn't need to exist because I want to cut this portion.
How do I do that?
Is there like a scissor?
There it is.
Audio options.
Yeah, that's fine.
Here it is.
Split scene because I wanted to pick them up like here.
Right at the edge there.
Like right there.
Like right here.
We can get rid of these.
Okay, now I should be able to drag this into here.
Yes.
Delete this.
And that's him picked now.
He lifts his head up.
Let's put the scene here.
And then he needs to put him back down.
And then down.
So right here.
Right here.
Why is he out of the tub though?
This whole scene, I'm getting rid of this one.
It doesn't even need to be here.
We're changing the music too.
What?
Oh, it's because...
Oh, shit.
The timeline changed.
How do I...
Can I put them all together?
Why did that happen?
I didn't move these.
The timeline changed down here because I edited...
Okay, you gotta edit that shit up top first.
That's all right.
I can just move it forward.
This is the cough room.
Just move everything forward.
That cough is right here.
A little bit more.
And then he gets in the bathtub.
Right there.
All right, that's a good spot.
Who's crying?
Why is somebody crying?
Oh, he cries.
He does.
It's him.
He cries like right here.
This music is gonna drive me fucking crazy.
It's not even funny.
I don't know why I laugh at it every time.
All right, we need a little bit more.
We need music to...
The music's changed right here.
What was that?
Did you hear that?
There's like 20 people screaming.
Music changes.
And right now.
Okay, here's...
This one needs to be changed,
and then this one changes too like that.
Right here.
All right, we gotta add a couple more screams.
This is the only fart that's gonna be in the entire stream, by the way.
There's not gonna be any more farts.
I can promise you that.
Okay, I need a couple more coughs.
I fucking want to remove it so bad.
I need one more cough.
What does slurp sound like?
No, that's not gonna work.
Get rid of this.
Bullet?
Call of Duty hit sound.
Okay, all right.
Last, I need a cough.
One more cough.
Like right here.
Do a bubble noise after the fart.
Oh my god.
What if we just dropped a fucking huge dump in here?
Splash bath?
Okay, we need to get...
The song has to start playing again.
I think actually...
No, hold on.
No, I'm sorry, guys.
This is not gonna be like a dump.
That's like TOS.
I'm not gonna get like dumped.
All right, I need to cut this track here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Undo, undo, undo.
That's not what I wanted to do.
Is there an undo button?
I think there is.
Where is it?
Control Z?
Will the bullet work?
No, there is no undo.
Gotta be aware that there is no undo.
So how do I make this smaller?
How do I get rid of that?
Toggle mumbly that they can like be mumbling.
Top left, that's exit.
Do you want to click the exit button
and waste the last like 45 minutes in this dumb movie?
I think I can do no sound, right?
Wasn't there a track that's like no, like kill the audio?
I think there is one.
Isn't there like a hundred?
How do I get rid of that?
Because I can't...
Yeah, I can't like drag, like click and drag.
This has got to be something, right?
I don't think so.
I can adjust the volume on the whole, on the master.
Yeah, right click doesn't do anything.
The scissor just cuts, but hold on.
No, no, no.
Just cut the clip and remove the end part.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to do, but I can't...
I can't cut the clip for some reason.
When I click here, it cuts the video track.
That's what I thought, right?
Split scene, just splitting the scene.
It's all right.
There should be more than one audio channel.
Yeah, it's not as advanced as you might think.
Save the game, save the game.
I will, I will.
We're good, but I...
Hold on, hold on.
This is this...
Fine, it doesn't matter.
All right, we got it.
It's all right.
We could just have the music played over again.
And so then, I'm not doing all that again.
I'm just going to do some coughs.
We got to export this shit.
Wait, what happened to the...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What happened to the video files that were back here?
What happened?
Oh, okay, okay.
First, I'm all the way back here now.
All right, here we go.
I wish I could just copy all these and put them over here, but I can't.
So here's what we're going to do.
Let's have him...
Let's see.
Now I'm yawning.
No, I'm going to yawn too.
How is that a yawn?
That's enough.
That's a yawn, apparently.
That don't fit.
Here we go again.
Okay.
Where is it?
Belch.
Okay.
Comedy music for the drowning.
It's...
Every movie I make in this has the same repeat the scene thing.
Breaking his neck.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Should I change my stream to like 18 and over?
Well, now I need to.
All right, let me get...
Hold on.
Beauty like no other leads into...
Get this out of here.
All right.
I'm actually going to remove this because we don't need it anymore.
No!
The timeline does that thing.
Shit.
Why does it do that?
Oh, that sucks.
That whole thing gets ruined down here.
I don't remember that happening.
There is no undo.
That has to be an undo.
Right?
Like that has to be.
Oh, it controls.
He doesn't do anything.
Shit.
Really?
That sucks that it does that.
I'm not going to click the exit button.
I got to like burn that into my brain
that if you change anything up here,
it shrinks the whole every single timeline.
You can map an undo key.
Delete.
Thumbnail.
Split.
Like why are these grayed out?
What is this?
Fade out.
Oh, fade out and fade in.
That sucks.
I haven't unlocked the undo.
Well, hold on.
And that's the end of the movie.
Watch the undo tutorial.
I wonder.
Deleting scenes, cutting scenes, moving scenes.
No, I don't think that's going to do it.
Yeah, what I'm going to have to burn into my memory
is trim everything, get everything the way
that I want it first completely
and then do sound effects.
So I'm going to have to go for it here.
Just have to move everything like an inch forward.
And then that's it.
What a pain in the ass.
I wish they would remake this game
and put all the quality of life features that it deserves.
Can I move the whole timeline?
I don't think so.
No, when you click in the timeline,
you just add a sound.
Yeah, save every before you do everything.
It is a learning process.
Yeah, the whole thing just has to go forward again.
Check you have control in the undo.
I'm scared to hit escape.
No, I can't go anywhere.
I don't have any options or anything.
Deleting the game.
Oh, I had them in a perfect spot, too.
God, somebody buy the rights to this
so we can get a better version.
Ask Bill Gates.
Oh, God, I keep forgetting that's in here.
Oh, he is.
Okay, so now let's see what this...
Moves over here, that moves over here.
All right, almost done.
No, and I cannot bunch them together either, unfortunately.
I can't hit shift or control or alt.
You have to do it individually.
The music is overlapping,
but I don't think I can do anything about it.
How did I do this last time?
It's going to be further out.
This is nothing but fart and burp jokes.
I know, everybody pre-oppressed me in doing this.
I'm sorry.
And I wouldn't have...
You wouldn't have to see it so many times
if I didn't have to do this stupid shit
with the no undo button.
Getting closer.
I'm done.
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
I'm out of this, we're gone.
He said to be moved a little bit.
Okay.
This goes forward, this goes forward, this goes forward.
We're ready.
Export.
Okay, goodbye.
Save the stupid movie.
Save, it saves, it's done.
I'm almost...
It's over.
It's time to export this piece of shit.
Don't waste...
He comes back to life again?
All right, that's it.
I'm done.
That's it, export the movie.
That looks good.
Bottom right.
Yeah, export movie.
How do I get rid of all this?
There's got to be a way I can cut that.
I just don't know.
All right, export movie.
If you want to have audio in your exported movie,
you must first update the soundtrack
by playing the movie from start to finish.
Do you want to do this now?
Hey, I remember how to play the...
I remember how to use the controls now.
Can I export the fucking movie now, please?
I already did that.
What are you talking about?
Wait, what?
Output name, high, highest.
Wait, what is this talking about?
Is this going to just save it to my computer?
I'm so confused.
Yeah, highest.
Oh my God, my like fucking stomach hurts.
It was like when he snaps his neck like twice.
It's just like so awful.
It's unnecessary.
All right, let's just get out of town.
Now it has like a vignette all over it too.
I actually am physically exporting this.
All right, now we're going to make...
I saw it in the chat earlier
and it is the thing that I want to make.
We're going to make constant conflict.
That is what I thought to make.
I do want to figure out a couple of things though.
Mainly free camera stuff.
Well, all right, it's been uploaded.
Save it.
And that's it, right?
Is this now all edited together?
I think it is.
So I just release it now.
Ready for release.
Let's see what they say.
Script quality is not very good.
It's all right.
I don't even want to watch it again.
I don't want to watch it again.
No, we've already seen it.
We've already seen it.
We don't need to watch it a sixth time.
The crew was clueless, inexperienced cretins.
The overall quality of acting in this movie is appalling.
Howard's Poor Direction didn't do this movie any favors.
Leo was shockingly bad.
Making money though, that's all that matters.
I need to can this because it's just kind of sitting here.
How do I just like get rid of this?
It's got to be like a throw, call it, can it.
There we go.
All right, let's do another one.
This one's going to be a little bit more elaborate.
We need some more sets.
Let's do cellar, war, battle.
I'm going to be a battlefield.
I'm going to make constant conflict.
Let's do a living room.
Going to need an office.
Going to need a traveling vehicle, automobile.
Wild west desert, wild west jail.
I already have the war battlefield in the street.
I already have the bathroom.
And a couple of years, time does have to pass.
Let's get the desert in here too.
I'm probably going to need it somehow.
All right, so we're going to start in the house.
So constant conflict is going to start opening in a regular group of friends.
Remember what happened in the beginning of Cloverfield?
Where it's just like, holy shit, something's going down.
I'm going to start here.
There's going to be like an earthquake and they're going to investigate the earthquake.
It's going to be like this fucking aliens invading and then they all have to have scars on their face.
Okay, what else do I need?
Anything else?
The bank?
Maybe just like a, just have them all.
Jail street.
Sci-fi star bridge.
Make an E3 conference.
I mean, good.
Cellar.
All right.
I think we can work with this.
Make an E3 conference.
Do you want me to make it?
Constant conflict is probably going to take like the next two and a half hours.
I need like the blue screen.
We need time to go by because you can't start any...
I wish I could start in like 2000.
All right, I'll use my voice too.
We'll show some like...
No, no, no, no, no.
The game is constant conflict is the game that they're showing with E3.
But that makes sense, doesn't it?
But I need...
I know there's a blue screen, but I don't think I have it yet.
We're not in like the fucking...
We're in like the 50s.
You can edit the INI file to start in like 2000.
Yeah, I'll fast forward it.
Let me save it here and then I'm gonna...
Let me save game.
Just call it P Pants because that's the name of the studio.
I'm gonna edit the INI so we can actually be in the year 2000.
And then yeah, I'll bind undo as well.
I got a P, so I spent three hours.
I haven't gone to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
And then when you come back, there will be the year 2000.
Blue screen, green screen, constant conflict.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
Okay, give me just a sec.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Okay, INI file.
Let's get that open.
I got some water too.
I'm thirsty.
Okay, where do I do this?
I remember it's in a weird spot, isn't it?
Look for unlocking INI.
Unlocking INI.
Where the hell is that?
Let me see.
I gotta like look it up.
It's not here.
Data, scenario, scenes, text.
Where the hell is this?
I think it's the registry.
I think I could do it in the registry.
Yeah, I could allow any decade and change the value to one.
Let's hope this doesn't break.
Or is it in my documents file?
Oh, would that work?
Let's see.
I don't think, no, maybe it is right here.
All right, hold on.
I have to get out of town here.
No, it's not here.
Oh, I can't really go searching for this right now.
I definitely have enough to do what I want to do.
At least for, let me see.
Anybody offhand of any idea where this is?
Because I don't see it anywhere.
Or do I have to make one?
The text document, you know what I'm saying?
It's in the documents.
I'm in my documents right now.
The movies, and I don't see anything.
I see save games, movie sounds, graphics.
And maybe an app data.
That's possible.
Hold on.
There's Lionhead, the movies.
There's an OS detect.
This is not an I&I.
Shit.
I'm in app data right now and there's no
Lionhead studios in app data roaming.
Yeah, it's not in here.
Unless it's, is it hidden?
I've got an unlocking.ini there for me.
Why do I, how come I don't have one?
Let me like, see if I can, is it hidden?
Maybe it's a hidden file.
It's not a, it's not a hidden file for me.
Show hidden files and folders.
Where the fuck is it then?
Yeah, I have hidden files showing right now.
I'm gonna have to get this done like off stream.
So I, because this, it's not here.
Once I unload all the mods on the next stream for this game.
Either that or I have to edit the registry
and I feel like I'll break the fucking whole game.
It's a hidden file in app data.
That's where I am right now.
I have, I'm in app data, I'm in Lionhead studios
and the only thing that's there with hidden files turned on
is this file that says OS detect, that's it.
Well, I'll try the registry thing
but I might have to remake the whole game.
Let's see.
I'll do the registry.
If this doesn't work then I'll have to get it done
for when we put the mods in.
All right, it is in, I'm there in the movies.
Allow any decade is about to be turned into one.
The value is one.
Let's see if that worked.
If I have to start a new game I might have to
because I think I have to pick the decade unfortunately.
Let's give it a try.
All right, here we go.
Let's see if it works.
Set it to two and break everything.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to,
I think I'm gonna have to do another one
because see, watch this ready.
Yeah, I have to start another one.
Unfortunately, we have to.
It's all right though, it's not,
that's not any time at all.
I have the same actors and everything so don't worry.
They can misbehave, that's fine.
A hundred million dollars, that's right.
All right, just got to bring everybody back.
All right, let's go.
I need a import, bring them all back in.
Sandler, somebody has to be a director, right?
And I need import star.
I need to know who else.
All right, who's the director for you?
No sound, sorry.
I had to mute it.
All right, we got a director.
We have our actors.
Let's go.
Data talent's on YouTube already.
How the hell did you do it that fast?
So now, look at this.
There we are.
Field, graveyard, must be, alien world, stage.
Suburban bathroom, suburban living room.
All right, so suburban living room.
Suburban living room.
My first movie was pirated instantly.
Alien world.
Let's get stage for our E3 presentation.
Stage, I believe you can put a green screen behind it.
Suburban street is another one.
You have to have like the chaos.
Then we need only a few more things.
Tropical beach, why not?
Alleyway, bar, yeah, we want a bar.
I wanted a lot of things.
I want everything.
Rooftop for the inevitable chase scene.
Subway carriage, hotel room, subway station.
There's a lot of sets.
We got unlimited money though, so it doesn't matter.
Battlefield, we need this too for when we fight the aliens.
Yeah, I'm really going big here, but you know what's going to happen.
There's going to be like a fucking neck snap and then a fart sound.
And then somebody like falls down or something.
You think this is going to be a big elaborate movie.
I'm out of space.
I feel like I can move shit around.
Hold on.
Move rehab out of the way.
I think I need like a builder.
No, this is good.
This is good.
There's plenty.
I got like the alien world.
I've got...
I can't fit that right here.
I can't.
Okay, good.
One more.
Shit.
All right.
No, that's good.
That's good.
That's fine.
Just get rid of the rehab.
No, this is all right.
This is all right.
Okay, here we go.
Custom script.
I need the custom script office.
I also need a post-production office.
All right.
No, I already have one.
Okay, here we go.
It's time.
The name of this movie.
This is an action movie.
Well, actually, I don't know.
This is E3.
It would be an action movie, right?
Okay, let's do...
We need to have the person presenting.
Let's have this be...
This can be Adam Sandler.
I said we need to change this to a better outfit.
No, that's not...
This is better.
It comes out in pinstripes.
I like that a little better.
No, no, no latex heads.
This is fine.
All right.
No, no.
This is fine.
This is just a suit.
Eye, makeup, shape, facial hair, na...
All right.
This is fine.
And then this is...
Commander...
We got to have a little...
A story here.
We have...
No, no, no.
The studio head is the person that's presenting E3.
We have to have a main character.
There's two games to show.
Leo as Captain...
Or like Grunge.
What's like a hard name?
Like Rick Grunge or something.
No, no, no, no.
Rock like...
Rock hard...
Rock hurdman?
Never mind.
Rock...
Rocky Rick?
Don...
Don Rock?
Commander Don Rock.
Commander Donald Rock.
No, this is just Don the Rock.
Like, no.
No, no, no.
No Rock.
I'm not going to...
No, not that one.
Kurt...
Kurt Frightener?
Kurt Frightener.
Command...
Commander Kurt Frightener.
Yeah, and it's going to be...
It's going to be Jax.
We also need like an alien.
But I think we can have some extras be aliens, right?
So we've got Jax and I'm saying Leo can be here.
Also, we need to change your costume.
Because that's not what you're going to be wearing.
It's going to be in one of these outfits that looks cool.
Not a clown costume.
Sorry, guys.
Is he just like a cop?
No, is there...
Is it like a marine?
Like a space marine?
Invisible ghost?
Here we go.
This is not bad.
No, but this is just like his day as the space marine commander or something.
Space suit.
Okay, so that's all right.
That's a good starting costume.
Swedish.
Swedish space marine.
And then this has to be an alien of some sort.
Okay, let's go with...
Back here.
I could do like monsters, right?
I mean, I kind of like it.
This is like an enemy you would be shooting at in like Doom, right?
Okay, this is the E3 presentation.
Here is the studio head.
We've got Kurt Frightener.
Kurt Vicks, no.
They always have something like outrageous like...
Like Warlord Kleksis or something.
They always have to have like two Xs in their name.
Warlord Kleks.
Sounds good.
All right, here we go.
So our presentation begins.
We need a stage.
Which where is it?
Stage.
And this is just static.
We got to get in here.
I don't know what you all are doing here.
I don't know why there are these people here.
But we need a backdrop.
We need to change the set.
Not a household.
We want it to be...
I don't know.
We got to change the background.
Where is it here?
Change backdrop.
There it is.
Forest.
Is it just like a road?
There isn't just like a computer screen or like a green screen?
I thought they had that.
I thought they did.
Alleyway.
Could be this.
Although, I don't know why this is all here.
Can you all go away?
None of you have to be here.
E3 in the alleyway.
All right, we're going to do a stat...
Okay, first of all, I need to find out how to move this camera freeform.
Let me see this.
Viewing your scene.
Pause sliders.
Choosing scenes.
Searching for a scene.
No, no, no.
I know how to do all this.
I just want to keep the camera static somewhere.
All right, so where was...
This is an E3.
Who is it?
Jax?
Yeah, I know if I don't put anybody here, they're not going to show up.
Mannequins mean that they're just available.
Do I have the DLC installed?
I should, yeah.
Let me like just find out.
Let me make sure I have that.
It's installed.
I'm using the EXE for that.
You know what I'm saying?
Like is that...
What's going on here?
Why do I not have any stunt scenes?
Doesn't...
Wait, why is it...
Why would this not be installed?
I have the...
Yeah, I have the expansion installed.
How does it make any sense?
Wait, what?
No, I should be opening...
I should have the right game open.
I mean, I literally have the disc literally in my hand.
You have to enable stunts and effects on the campaign,
but this is just sandbox mode.
Hold on.
Back out of here.
This is very confusing to me.
Do I have to have like a stunt section?
Hold on a minute.
Weird.
Like do I have to hire a stuntman?
I don't remember this happening.
This is kind of fucked up.
Maybe it's no stunts for this scene,
but I don't think they were available in the other one either.
Hold on.
I know there's stunts for some of these,
like the bank for instance.
Yeah, wouldn't it be here?
I swear to God.
Would they have like a different...
They have a different thing on the thumbnail, don't they?
Yeah, there's different scene thumbnails.
Like there's definitely stunts here.
I'm very, very, very confused.
Back to the menu.
Back up for a second.
What the fuck is going on here?
This is fine.
We can just do it again.
No.
What the fuck?
Hold on a second.
It's not even here.
Why is it...
Why do I not have the expansion?
What?
I'm so confused.
I don't think...
Let me try this.
Yeah, there's a movies...
Something broke here when I installed it.
God damn it.
No.
This is gonna work?
No, I have the patch.
Oh, come on.
Don't do this to me now.
Yeah, I was wondering because some things were just missing,
but I installed them both.
I'm launching it from the expansion EXE,
and it's telling me like it's not installed properly somehow.
Fuck me.
Don't tell me this is gonna happen.
That makes no sense.
I thought this was ready to go to.
Fuck me.
I was really looking forward to it too,
but apparently I don't know why this won't work.
I'm so confused.
Is there a way that I could see inside
of why this would be happening like this?
Like inside the actual data?
Like inside the actual folder for the game?
Is there a way I can see?
Like if the stunt stuff is installed in there?
Like a certain file or something?
Well, let me put this up.
This is so fucking frustrating.
It actually is.
Looks like it should be in there.
The stunt should have his own folder.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking too, but why?
No fucking idea.
Let me see what happens when I do this.
I might have to reinstall it then.
I wonder what happened.
Because I went through the process of installing it normally,
and it said it was done.
What a way to take the fucking wind out of my sales game.
Let me take a look at this.
Yeah, I have no idea.
I'm going to try something real quick and see what happens.
I'm going to run like the...
I'm going to reinstall the stunts and effects.
Setup has detected that you already have
the movie stunts and effects installed.
Well, what the fuck are you talking about?
What the fuck is happening, man?
I'm just going to run it from the disk and see what happens.
Like will it open from here?
Because maybe the EXE is fucked up.
This is beyond anything that I could ever imagine would be wrong.
Yeah, I'm running as administrator.
I don't understand.
Fuck me.
I need a no CD.
Yeah, I have the no CD.
That's what's the weird part about this.
I have the no CD already, and it's the right one.
Let me just see something here.
For the purposes of just...
I just don't want to sit here and try to...
Mmm.
Let me try one thing.
Stunts and effects.
Yeah, no CD.
I have the right one.
I don't know why it's doing this.
All right.
Well, I'm going to have to just either go...
I kind of don't know what to do.
Pray that this works.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Did it work?
Work?
Yes!
It worked!
All right.
Why the fuck was that so...
That makes no sense.
I wish I had even a percent of explanation as to why this has happened.
Holy shit, guys.
That made no sense.
Take a look.
We're good.
Although you guys can't see now, though.
Why can't you...
Come on, capture this shit, man.
Don't do this now.
Come on, hurry up.
Let's go.
I got it on my screen.
Capture!
Capture, you piece of crap!
Stop putting up hurdles!
I want to make a movie!
What are you doing now?
It won't pull.
It won't capture it now.
Of course not.
Give me a fucking break.
Oh my god, computers suck.
Let me just try capturing the window.
Now it won't pull it.
Now it won't capture it.
It's playing, but I can't...
Now I have to capture my desktop again.
Let's hope this works.
Oh my fucking god.
I'm so pissed off right now.
You have no idea how just
pure angry I am.
It's gonna work.
It's working.
But like, holy shit, I am infuriated at the moment.
This is so stupid.
All right, here we go.
No stun injuries.
Otherwise, I don't think that people will be able to...
Let's go ahead and make all this shit again.
Well, sorry for that.
That was a lot of bullshit.
I'm as frustrated as you are.
Way more frustrated than you probably are.
But here we go.
Let's do it again.
All right.
And we're back.
We're here.
We're finally about to start.
To a hospital, it's sure.
So we need...
I need those sets back.
But there are a shitload more sets.
Because, let's see.
The green screen.
There we go.
All right.
I was wondering where the hell it was.
Very confusing.
I'm just gonna get all the sets out here.
At least the ones that I know I want to use.
A green screen.
Okay.
What does it want me to do?
Restaurant, hospital, right?
Stunt school.
Yeah, I need stunt men.
Starship Bridge 4 has stunts in it somehow.
Let's go.
I got my sci-fi corridor.
Scrolling landscape.
Stage.
Although, I'm not sure...
I think I can do this and then build what I need, right?
I think I can just make the movie and then shoot it.
And I just need to build the things that I use.
Yeah, I don't need to do this.
All right.
So get me out of here.
Let us go to the script.
Well, I need to bring in the people.
But hold on.
Here's the worst thing about this.
Are the actors going to be available?
Or do I have to make them in a separate...
That shouldn't happen, right?
It's kind of running like shit.
Why is it running like this?
Now, I'm going to do a full-on re in a second here.
Eddie.
Adam Sandler.
And you.
Now, I need you.
Somebody needs to be a director.
Which I was going to do.
Can I do any more?
Oh, shit.
I just made this person a director.
I just made Leo the director.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're an actor.
Don't worry.
Who should be the director?
No.
You.
All right.
We're good.
Let's go to the script office.
Which is down...
Cult Starzence.
What the hell is that?
Hospital.
This is post-production.
Where is the...
No.
Do I not have one?
Custom script.
I already own it.
I have no idea what the hell it is, though.
It's literally right next to me.
All right.
Here we go.
We can finally create something.
After a million years.
We already did the first one, but...
It took like 20 fucking minutes.
30 minutes to get this going again.
Let's try it again.
This is action.
Jax and Leo.
And Adam Sandler.
You are the studio head.
What was this guy's name?
Kurt Rock?
Brock Hardman?
No, no, no, no.
It was Kurt Frightener.
Yeah.
Pogo Stick?
All right.
Good.
Now it's you do costumes.
Go.
You.
Over here.
He's in a firefighter outfit?
No.
It's like the Space Marine one.
Where is it?
Did I pass it already?
Oh, here we go.
This is better.
I like that better than the other one.
And then this had that was like the lizard.
Or should it be the lizard?
Yeah.
I think so.
All right.
Welcome to E3.
Finally.
Let's go.
We're starting on the stage.
Stunts.
Thank God.
I was about to throw up all of my insides.
So we need to do...
Just get static here.
There we go.
All right.
See, free cam.
That's what I was...
You see what's happening?
You know what I mean?
I was like, what the fuck was happening?
Why can I not move the camera?
I didn't have the...
I didn't have the fucking EXE installed somehow.
But I did.
I had to like replace it twice.
All right.
So let's start here.
We're gonna have him walk on stage.
So I think this is just start position.
And it's end position too, right?
That's fine.
Maybe I don't even need to do that.
Let's look at it from the...
Yep.
From the camera.
All right.
Now backdrop.
Green screen.
But the green screen implies that this...
We have to be somewhere else.
This is pretty close.
This is pretty good too.
E3 on a rooftop.
It's like a news station.
This is pretty good.
Oh my God.
24.
Yeah, we're gonna do...
Oh my God.
24.
Sounds good to me.
Okay.
Stage.
Let's see.
We need to have preparation.
Walk with a briefcase.
It's got to be the right scene though.
Oh my God.
24.
Okay.
Let's slow that down a little.
By the way, let me just...
I want to just rip...
Sorry for that last like 30, 40 minutes, guys.
I was about to throw in the towel.
So like I'm back to...
We're good.
Everything's fine.
I'm sorry that that happened.
But I just want to say that I...
I was trying to handle that.
I was trying.
What happened?
The game didn't load in the expansion and I almost lost my mind.
All right.
So this needs to be a little bit longer.
Why would the case in the hand matter?
All right.
I need to do free camera here.
Start position.
We're gonna do over here.
The immersion is gonna be broken so badly.
You're shooting this in like a fucking restaurant.
Let's do start here.
And then we're gonna end here while he walks.
Let's see what that looks like.
Why would he walk by the camera?
Like stop.
I didn't turn to the camera.
He's just gonna walk by.
Okay.
Can I have him still with that in his hand?
Walk briefcase again.
Yeah.
We need a little bit more than that.
So he goes this way.
Comes over here.
Where is he?
Change the scene to another scene here.
Okay.
So he just walks by.
But we need him to walk from the other direction.
He's gonna take a long time to get to this fucking stage.
All right.
Hold on.
So I need to do go to start position is I want to move out.
How do I move the camera up?
Whoa.
What is this field of view?
How do I move the camera up?
Alt.
There we go.
This movie is a joke compared to your magnum opus.
Get out of town.
You'll never top that heart-wrenching scene when Benedict was brutally murdered and shitted himself.
Okay.
Is that gonna be enough?
Let's see.
This stage is way is not.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the head of Oh My God Studios.
Studio head Greg.
All right.
Should we do one more?
Or is he here?
Let's have him coming into the scene now.
Walk with a scanner.
Brandish blade.
No, no, no, no, no.
Is there any more briefcase?
Enter briefcase.
Here we go.
What does it look like?
That's the same one.
Is it the same one?
What other?
What?
Walk briefcase.
Enter briefcase.
What about exit briefcase?
They're all the same thing.
Okay.
We're gonna change this.
Now we're just gonna have like talking.
Talk left.
All right.
So here we go.
Talk.
There's no other person here.
Don't worry.
We're not gonna even use them.
Duration long.
Left actor is happy.
And the right actor doesn't matter because the right actor is not even in the scene.
His mouth isn't even moving.
No, no, no.
Happy is not gonna work.
This needs to be something else.
Angry, romantic, sad.
Just neutral.
All right.
That's better.
Then we give the crowd cheer.
There is a person on the right that he's like talking to.
Hold on.
Is there a better one?
Is it like a just one person talk?
Now it's two people.
I can just remove the other person.
Here we go.
Talk right.
It's always gonna be talk turn.
Talk to dog.
Payphone talk.
Let's see.
Intro.
Weight lifting.
He comes out and just like lifts up a bunch of fucking weights.
Monologue.
Perfect.
See what we got here.
Mood.
Happy.
Perspective.
Why?
We can just change the duration.
Medium.
See how this goes.
Okay.
Let's get another cut here with like a close up.
Same thing.
I'll change the backdrops.
Don't worry.
Put Minecraft in the background.
Okay.
Maybe like right here.
This one he's gonna be angry.
Mood.
Argumentative.
Duration.
Abrupt.
Let's try this one on.
Apparently he didn't like the way the audience reacted to this.
I'm gonna go back here.
Yeah.
24.
Put that back here as well.
All right.
I need an audience.
Is there like a the play?
There's got to be a bar.
No, no.
Like a theater.
Jail.
Saloon.
Bedroom.
Street.
I wonder if there's like a crowd or something.
Or at least a place where people could be like sitting.
I don't think so.
Someone's just watching from their living room.
Someone's watching on their computer.
It's like a live stream.
I think we're just gonna have to do extras.
And on stage.
But with a different backdrop.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Like crowd.
No.
Like group.
Group meeting.
Group move.
Cheer.
Conversation.
Investigation.
I think we can just do.
We could probably just do static.
Sit and talk.
Yeah.
I mean that you could do sit and talk.
Sit and see people just smoking.
Yeah.
Static with a bunch of extras I think is the best.
The audience is sitting on the ground.
Let's do static.
And change the backdrop to something that looks like they're in the theater.
Burning city.
Canvas background.
No.
Falling.
Wait.
Everyone's falling.
This looks all right.
All right.
We need extras.
Supporting role.
First extra extra.
Okay.
This is going to need a lot of extras.
How do I take like the gun away from this person?
How do I get this off?
There's no way I can get rid of this.
How do I delete this?
What is going on over here?
Yeah.
I'm just going to delete this extra.
Okay.
And this one too.
And this one.
And you as well.
You're not going to be in this movie.
And they're making zombie noises.
Wait.
Change props.
Oh shit.
Okay.
All right.
Let's see.
Change props.
Slot one.
Yeah.
I cleared the props.
So how do I?
Can I put something else in here?
All these props are just guns.
Different cell phones.
What the hell is this?
Seashell?
Okay.
No.
You don't get.
Nobody gets a gun.
Okay.
This is a banana.
You can have a banana in your hand.
That's fine.
Okay.
So now we can edit this and put this in a different spot.
So he talks here.
Let's make sure we got that correct.
We actually need to move the camera a little bit.
Let's do free cam.
Make it at least look like they're sitting down.
Except how would they be?
At least some of them is sitting down.
Just somebody just staring off into the distance.
All right.
That's fine.
So we go from here.
Talks about a few things.
We're going to have at least three or four different adjectives here.
And then it leads to showing the audience.
And then we come back to his reaction.
He's going to announce a mobile game.
They're all going to fucking boo.
And then he's going to say, well, let's show it.
How about let's put the monologue.
Somebody like from the audience comes up.
It's like a strangling match with them.
Okay.
So angry.
And it's going to be a short.
Let's see.
It's going to probably come up shade of my face.
This is going to make me a billion dollars.
All right, motherfucker.
And he like sprints up.
This is an extra running angry direction this way.
Yeah.
Can we slow that down?
Determined.
Determined is so fast.
Yeah, I think that's the one.
To do.
Where is it?
News logo five.
All right.
So then he's going to get like one.
He's just going to get knocked out.
The only thing is this could be a different person.
It's just going to be a random extra that's up here.
Action, tame, mild, moderate, extreme.
Holy shit.
That is extreme.
All right.
I think I just like the first perspective.
Okay.
That is we got to be on the right backdrop.
I actually have to I have to film this.
We got to get the start position over here.
So it looks like, you know, that he may have just he may have ran over here.
I don't want him in the scene yet.
And then we move forward and let's see how that looks.
Like he just queued it up.
Wait a minute.
Okay, hold on.
Start position here.
Go mark position.
Go to mark position.
Right.
And then the second position is here.
And then we mark this one too.
Mark position.
That's right, right?
Should be.
Why is it not doing it?
Shouldn't it shouldn't that position be marked here?
Because if this is position one, here's your start position.
It's marked here and I want it to move.
Yeah, it's a key frame.
So shouldn't it?
Wouldn't this be, you know, like I can't mark it here.
Not quite key framing.
Start and end equals beginning and end of the clip.
Oh, okay.
So this is beginning of the clip.
Position two is at the end right now.
So I would want it to be start position.
But wouldn't I want it to be start position and then, well,
like I have to move it forward a little?
Because I think of this like it's not key frames,
but move the camera on the second timeline.
Oh, I see here.
So I can do this.
If I mark it.
How come I can't get, I'm not, I'm not getting,
I'm not putting this together here in my head.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
What the hell is this doing over here?
All right.
So here we go.
See if that fixes it.
So then right, I want it to be like here.
Let's see if that does it.
Fuck.
God damn it.
What is happening here?
Camera two, what the hell?
Why did I drag it over?
What marked position?
This is camera one.
Camera one is here.
Camera two is, I want camera two to be here.
What the fuck am I doing here?
Position one, position two.
So I want it to be like, so I, it's just like weird.
Okay.
So this is, this is correct now, right?
This shit's correct.
All right.
There we go.
That's kind of a weird system.
All right.
Here we go.
I think, yeah.
Okay.
So that's going to be an edit.
So I'll edit that out.
I'm going to have him fall down
and then the trailer is going to play.
He like just fucking knocked himself out.
What would that be under?
Let's see.
Violence, dead body.
He drinks poison and then the clip plays.
Just make him fight the crowd.
Crouch shoot.
Oh, I thought the first thing I thought was crotch shoot.
What about unconscious?
Let's see.
Pursuit, resolution, impact.
Head, oh right.
This one.
He fucking head butts the guy
and then instantly gets knocked out in the trailer plays.
Now this is better.
He just already out.
Okay.
Let's change the camera here.
So let's do, let's go to camera one.
Where's camera two?
Now I got to mark it.
Okay.
Let's see how that looks.
Now I need the E3 backdrop here.
Where's the fart?
Well, this is not post-production yet.
Yeah, we can edit that part
because when he starts shaking his head,
he's at it fall forward.
Like right there, fall forward.
Okay.
Now let's go to the,
let's just go to stage again.
We're going to zoom in to the screen.
These people aren't even going to be here.
The backdrop is going to be just normal.
I guess it could change to something.
It just zooms into this like stupid spaceship.
That could, yeah, I could do a fade too.
Yeah, this is, I don't need this.
All right.
So we've got what we want.
These are all ready.
We're going to fade into this sci-fi corridor five.
Here we go.
This is constant conflict.
So first of all, there needs to be like, I don't know,
something to grab you immediately.
Somebody's getting, somebody's got CPR performed on him.
You're like, all right.
So who's in the game?
It's his game.
He's in it.
He's like, did the motion capture?
Okay.
This is how we need.
No, he can't be in his own fucking game.
All right.
Well, who was the alien?
Does this make sense?
He's giving CPR to the alien.
Come on.
Don't you die on me.
This is taking so, that's so long.
Why is he sitting here like this?
This is way too long.
Okay.
We need lighting, weather.
Fog, because everything's all fucked up.
This ship is going down.
Okay.
Now we need, let's get some extras in here.
Or maybe a supporting character.
No, we need, can I do like aliens and shit?
What about the extras?
Can I like, how do I make everybody like a fucking alien?
Fine.
This is the first supporting role,
because I have my actors, but then I have,
can I put some random person here?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I can change their costumes,
but I can't change the extras' costumes.
Hmm.
You can?
How come I got this grayed out?
How do I do that?
Drag an extra there, drag them to the hanger.
All right.
So there's an extra here and then, oh fuck.
Okay.
That just kind of popped out.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's going on here?
Why is the extra him?
This is strange.
You have to put a person as an extra.
Oh, so we just need, we just need like a bunch of people.
I don't have, I guess.
Can I make, can I make Jax an extra?
Wait.
Okay.
So I guess, I guess you're just going to be a robot,
but what are you defending?
All right.
We also need to have like something going on.
While this is happening, there has to be like a fucking explosion.
Stunts, fire group, a group of people run down a burning corridor,
explosion run, fight zombies, fire group, fire choke, fire staring, fire trap,
throttle victim, fire hero.
No, this is just, that's all there is here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Re-do this one.
Fight ain't over yet.
Ambush from above.
What's he holding?
Is that, what the hell is in his hand?
Is that a can opener?
Ambush from above.
What?
Oh, okay.
I'm just, what the hell happened?
Okay.
Hold on.
When does he land?
All right.
It's this surprise.
Then there's also this, and then there's ambush.
He spends a shitload of time knocking on his,
I don't even know what the hell he's holding.
Whatever it is.
Okay.
Hold on.
Spider-Man kiss.
Okay.
I don't, I don't hate this one,
but I'm going to trim a huge amount of it off.
Okay.
We need, I'm going to play from here.
Change his prop to something else, to a banana.
Is there, is there a way I can actually put a prop in here
without having to take from whatever they have?
Because this is the slot one.
So how do I, is there a way I can get a better list?
Apparently not.
Unless I can do something from another menu or something.
Static prop should be there, I guess.
I don't know why.
Strange.
All right.
I think this is good.
I'm going to use this.
We need to have just like a general soldier here though.
What is this haircut?
Why is he dressed like this?
All right.
It looks fine.
We just need this just a quick little like got you moment
where it's just like, bang, like right, like here.
Okay.
Let's go right there.
Maybe like there.
Okay.
So then like this, move the camera here.
That's like too much.
How is he, all right.
So then it should be there and then there.
Right at this right moment, like this.
Camera one, camera two.
I think that should be correct, right?
Yep.
So we'll edit it.
We'll have this.
Grab his head.
That second camera sucks, but it's fine because they're going to be bang.
Cut.
Let's have now like a battlefield, tropical jungle.
No, no, we're going to have like a war scene now on the, on a bridge, starship bridge.
Kill zombie.
No, that has to be like preparation here.
Fire staring.
Someone stares through the fire.
We need, let's take off stunts.
Let's just do violence.
Drink react.
Drink poison.
Explosion reaction.
Firing blanks.
Shooting dance.
Wait, what do you mean shooting dance?
How do you act professional here?
Okay, he's, he's doing the Carlton.
How, what is that?
Professional.
All right, this has to be somebody.
Now you're going to be in a different costume than this.
And this is going to be like an extra.
Like this is what they, this is what they do to humans.
They fucking like torture them.
What is this guy doing over here?
Torture by bullying people.
Okay, that's fine.
And then we need, yeah, I'm going to, don't worry.
I'll have a subtitle that says that.
Not actual gameplay.
I'm going to have him run through like eight different corridors like this.
Starship bridge one, same thing.
I just want explosion, explosion run.
Okay, that's fine.
What is this called?
This is called explosive run.
Come on, give me some more explosive runs.
Shit, I wanted to run through like five different corridors.
I guess I could just have him do the same one over and over again.
What is it?
Starship four, corridor five, maybe.
Bullet run, explode.
Here we go.
Here's another, there we go.
Perfect.
Okay, sci-fi corridor, corridor one, corridor.
He just goes, he's running around the whole entire fucking.
Is it the same one?
No.
Yeah, make him run through somewhere else.
Yeah, make him run through like a living room.
Is there like a sprint through a living room?
It's too short.
Hold on.
Location two, smiling.
Okay, all right.
Now we're back to the explosions.
Corridor four, corridor, no, no, no.
Back to corridor, should he just run by the stage with his own body on it?
All right, moving, what about car?
He's like just in the world.
All right, let's go, let's see what, can I do that?
Let's go to stage.
Why does, this doesn't make any sense.
Constant fucking conflict.
Yeah, and we're gonna have like an alien, like he,
this is, the trailer is behind him here.
You know what I mean?
Like this is, the trailer is behind him.
There's the spaceship.
All right, now we're gonna have,
well, okay, almost time for the trailer to be over.
Why would it zoom in on this?
Action, moderate, action, heavy.
Oh my, he's kicking the shit out of him.
Is it, what's after that?
There's extreme, from that reaction shot.
I don't understand that one.
He breaks his neck back again.
I think I like heavy because heavy, there's just more punches.
Okay, this also needs to be,
you're gonna be in a different costume here.
You're gonna be like one of the aliens.
Am I, am I fucking this whole thing up?
I might be.
I think it's Mysterio, far from home.
That's my favorite part, when he just like drops him.
Do you realize when he lands on this ground,
I'm gonna make a loud, awful thud.
Like crashes and glass breaking because of the head.
Just like, all right, okay.
The first trailer is almost over.
What is this?
Picnic, let's see, what do they got for stunts?
Horse riders shot?
What do you mean horse riders shot?
Why would there be a horse here?
What's location two?
I like location one better.
Okay, we got, that prop has to, no, no, no.
Lighting, this is fine.
Weather, wind, strong wind.
A bunch of trash.
That's so much trash.
What the shit did he plant it?
It's like plastic bags.
Well, this has to be, he's gotta be, oh my god.
This is so dirty.
Wait, wait, why does he fall twice?
Okay, looking good.
Let me just make sure that this shit's still looking okay.
There it is.
What happened to the camera here?
Didn't I make, didn't I change this?
I thought I had this changed.
That's weird.
It should be there, right?
All right, that's it for the trailer.
Now we're gonna go, let's go back to the stage
and we're introducing our new game.
There's two games to show at this E3.
Is it like medic or, hold on, I need,
we need loving or showing a card.
Resolution, take off pursuit and loving.
Resolution, okay, here we go.
And then we're gonna go to the next trail.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, come here.
I'm gonna like record a dialogue of me being like,
this conference sucks.
Fuck your company.
All right, so new game, we'll fade into this one,
is gonna be, who am I gonna put in this?
Should it just be another conflict game?
It's the same one.
Make it western.
Saloon bedroom.
Make a dating sim.
Scrolling landscape.
Just like a driving game.
Yeah, a driving game.
And don't worry, there'll be constant conflict in this game.
Street, okay, vehicle, car.
He's not gonna star in his own game again.
Mood, what?
Why would you wait that long to detonate a car bomb?
Wouldn't it explode way before?
That's the conflict.
Why wouldn't it, why?
All right, wait, hold on, wait, wait, wait.
We're going, there's just no clothes on.
He's just like naked.
Uh, what do we want?
No, this is a driving game.
There can't be this much constant conflict.
How do you sneak?
What was that?
Ice cream.
City street.
All right, this is the driving.
I need to do a driving game.
I can't just let it go off the rails.
Car burnout.
All right, that's a pretty good start.
Not a taxi though.
If it's a driving game, it needs to be something cool.
All right, this is pretty nice.
He's got to be in different, not different clothes.
What was he in?
Yeah, no, this is fine.
Right here.
All right, that looks good.
It's a good start.
That's going to go, okay, same thing.
Urban city street.
It's more like peeling out and cool shit.
Car squeeze.
What's that?
Car squeeze?
Lots of people comically squeeze into a car.
Just, just get it out of the way immediately.
Should I just get it out of the way?
Should I get it out of the way?
Should we fill the car with clowns and then just have them get in it?
No, it can't be like this already.
Does he have different hair?
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
I'll, we'll get the call back.
Don't worry.
Here's the call back.
It's never not funny.
It's not.
It's never not fun.
It's never not funny.
Constant fucking conflict.
We need to, I need to be able to edit this together though.
Hold on.
Some driving.
Where's the clown?
Like comical clown one.
Car squeeze.
It's a normal.
Okay.
Oh Jesus.
Close the door.
But I think I need to put, hold on.
It's the same people that were in the last game.
I need a fucking clown costume.
Is it a monster?
Premium.
Where is it?
There are so many costumes.
Can I just type in clown?
Where's the clown?
Okay, I found it.
Okay.
There we go.
So here comes the one clown.
Everyone is just going to be in the same clown costume.
I got to get like a good, where is it?
What would it actually be under?
Not casual, right?
Formal work.
So only like a few people need to be in clown costumes.
All of them.
What does this have to do with the game?
I don't think I can even make these other extras
because I don't have them set as anybody.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Wait, is it going to be this?
No, it's not going to work.
I don't have enough extras.
Is there no clown costume?
Hold on.
Why?
I can't have a woman in a clown costume?
That seems to make no sense.
Uh, I mean, I don't know.
There has to be a clown.
Uh, I guess I don't.
Wait, hold on.
One, two, three, four, five.
What if it's just some of them just regular people?
I can fix this later.
Um, all right.
First of all, this needs to be changed.
It's like I have a different hair.
I mean, see?
Okay.
I also, okay, urban office.
No, no, no.
Miniature city.
Cars race.
Here we go.
Perfect.
Oh, look at this.
This is exactly what I wanted.
Where's the car I was already using?
EMT.
All right.
That looks good.
Okay.
Same thing.
Let's do the miniature city again.
Car skid.
Cars race.
Car traffic.
City, city explosion.
Establish the city.
We could do like a pull it back.
Tracking show off to the city.
That sounds pretty good.
Forwards.
Perspective two.
There we go.
Nice.
And the speed up.
And then let's do inside the car.
What stunts have we got?
Car chase.
Car chase rear.
Gear change.
Dashboard.
Radio, radio answer.
Car sudden stop.
Let's see what this looks like.
Turning.
Braking.
You've done that before.
All right.
Who the fuck was even in the car?
Which one was it?
It was this one.
No, it wasn't.
It was like a nice car.
Like this one.
This one right here.
And I have no idea who was in the car.
Oh yeah.
There was like a bunch of clowns.
All right.
Before this derails completely.
I think it was you.
No, it was you.
Like it hasn't already.
Well, not completely.
Okay.
So there's a big break.
This is going to take a fucking ton of editing.
But it's going to be worth it.
City block corridor.
Nature city again.
Car traffic.
There's no other.
This is the only one.
I wonder whose car this is supposed to be.
Let's go into the camera.
Oh, easy.
I want a good view of this.
Too much movement.
All right.
Let's start here.
And then I'm going to go in.
Why are they not moving?
Oh God.
They're like little set pieces.
That's why.
Where is it all the way down there?
Cars are like little bugs.
I actually just like the static right here.
This is parked.
All right.
And then finally we're going to have.
Let's go back to the street.
Car parking.
Exit car collapse.
All right.
Let's have it.
I guess we'll keep the clown theme here.
Needs to be the right car, which I mean.
This is as close as I can get it, I think.
I can get it.
Okay.
And then last.
This is going to be long.
It's it'll be worth it.
It'd be worth it.
Last thing.
Car jump.
Car crashes around a corner and slides onto its roof under attack.
He's got to drive through.
He's going to be driving through when it explodes.
Can I make this look a little?
Like a spaceship car?
This is going in the other scene.
This is in the other game.
This is going back.
All right.
And finally, we're not going to use all these clips.
I just want to make sure I have them.
I need just like driving.
Here we go.
It's a very slow drive, but it'll work.
Just aliens.
This is the intro.
This is where it says not gameplay footage.
Okay.
I don't know what that's about.
We've got enough there.
It's time to bring it back to the stage and wrap up the E3 presentation.
And then let's go back here.
That's fine.
Now we need somebody else to come out and just say goodbye.
Put the camera back over this way.
That's fine.
Right there.
All right.
And then we need stage again.
Different hair.
Hair.
How do I?
Okay.
I got to make it.
I'm just going to make this the person, I guess.
Does he come on and change on stage?
What the hell was it called again?
There it is.
All right.
Done.
I'm not even going to dub over this.
And let's like, hold on.
I want to do something.
I want one more thing.
Let me just see.
I want somebody just on the computer.
Like at the desk or a computer.
Computer hacking.
The gorilla hacking, the gorilla watching E3.
Yeah.
And writing a bunch of mean shit on like Reddit.
He's really pissed off about what he just saw.
I can't fucking believe what they showed here.
You know, I really was, look, I was hoping for Yoshi's Bully World 2.
Yeah.
He's on Reddit.
All right.
So we need to have, does this just be a lizard?
Search bar Reddit.
Yeah.
We'll put it in.
They didn't announce his favorite game.
Oh, there you go.
Miss E3 sucked.
All right.
Now it's my job to put this all together.
Yeah.
I'll make sure there's a lot of extras.
So that, this should be good.
I don't think there's anything else.
I'm pretty sure I have every scene I need.
I think.
I believe it's time to go back.
Confirm.
Save it.
I will.
Don't worry.
Save.
I have to like confirm an exit before I can save.
Did I miss a backdrop somewhere?
Maybe I did, but whatever.
Here we go.
It is ready for casting.
I'm going to save the game.
Let's just call this one P Pants 2.
All right.
So let's get this in the, let's get some extras.
I need to go to the, where the hiring is.
Create, I need crew, right?
I need extras.
Does that matter?
Or will it fill it automatically?
I guess we'll find out.
Because I can't drag them over here.
I need to cast to start getting extras.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do it.
Begin casting.
Extras.
I need 11 extras.
Can I even have this many people?
How do I get extras?
I need more crew.
Now I need extras, but I can't pull these guys into extras.
Just birth them.
I need, I need a director.
Well, I have one here.
And now I need the extras.
Don't they usually hang out in front of here?
Because there's somebody here.
But I can't add them to extras.
Why?
I have to go to the stage school to create extras.
Where the hell is that one?
They hang out in front of one of the buildings.
Stunt school.
I think I'm going to need some stuntmen.
I need a stunt, I need stunt doubles.
Okay.
What about over here?
Oh, here we go.
Stars and studios.
Reject.
Movie making?
No.
What are these people?
I mean, these people are just hanging out here.
Import, start, create, extra.
I need more.
I'm working on it.
We good?
I need one more extra.
I have enough stuntmen, right?
I should, don't I?
I need one more extra.
I need sci-fi corridor.
Actor does not, does own stunts.
Actor does own stunts.
Oh, okay, that's fine.
All right, I need sci-fi corridor one and two.
Let me save this.
I still need one more person.
What about one of the janitors?
I'm just gonna make one of the janitors an extra.
Well, there's a lot of people here.
That's it.
Now we need the sets.
Sci-fi corridor one and two.
That it?
I think it's ready to go.
Suburban living room one and alien world.
What happens in alien world?
There it is.
Spartan torture?
What is that for?
What else?
Suburban street.
Oh man, am I gonna have enough room for this shit?
I might not.
This is, this is huge.
I'm gonna have to move some stuff around.
I got it.
And then...
That it?
Here we go.
It's time to shoot it.
What's wrong?
You don't, you don't feel good?
Jax, you don't feel good, Jax?
Wait, wait, wait, what do you mean?
Wait, wait?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait?
Get stunt doubles?
It says they're gonna do their own stunts.
Oh, you're talking about the music.
That's what you're wearing you want me to wait for.
I see.
I'm gonna save it.
Let's shoot it.
Here we go.
And...
It's one star.
Is it done?
I got instant filming here, man.
I actually think it's loading it up yet.
Okay.
Post production.
This is KNBS.
I'm Kristen, the girl who puts the womb in woman.
Post production.
I need to make sure I can do this.
I'm gonna have to restart the game.
So let me just see what happens when I do this.
I need to be able to record dialogue.
Is there...
Can I not?
Wasn't there something weird I had to do last time for this?
Hello.
Testing.
It works.
It's really low though.
How do I get rid of this?
Oh, there we go.
So we are gonna change the title here.
This is the, this is the big movie.
Crap.
Why does it look like this?
Yeah, this looks like wicked frosty.
All right.
First of all, it's not going to be acid bass.
Following motion picture E3 presentation.
E presents liquidated production.
E3 presentation.
Okay.
We need applause.
Let's get the music track on here.
We need orchestral.
This might be good.
All right.
Well, I'm going to turn off like the mumbling.
I don't like it.
Alleyway groove.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Trim before adding the sound.
Okay.
So now this is fine.
I'll put the, I'll do the dialogue on this one.
Because I have to figure out how long I'm going to talk here.
Hello and welcome to OhMyGod24's 24th E3.
As you know that our OhMyGod starts with all of our initials.
Oswald, Manny, and Greg started this company back, you know, in 19...
Wait a minute.
That's...
That was...
It's the same fucking lady kissing herself.
It's the same lady, like, four times.
Who runs all this...
How?
This goes off of way too long, too.
All right.
Let me edit this.
So the CPR goes on.
I know the CPR is going on for way too long.
Comes over.
Wait, wait, wait.
Get over here.
The CPR, first of all, needs to be in a different place.
This is definitely the opener.
Okay.
Let's say this is fine.
I'll do a little bit of a voiceover on this.
We'll cut it here.
Delete this.
My fucking head hurts.
And then this part, this is the one here.
I want to cut trim here.
Wait, let's just make sure.
Yeah, that looks good.
Yeah.
All right.
We'll stop it there.
Right...
Like right here.
The person kissing themself.
What the hell is this?
Wait, wait.
Why is it...
I thought it was a person.
Is it another alien?
They're just playing.
Okay.
That happens way too fast.
Where are the...
What's wrong with the tires?
I need to go get...
I need to go get this.
I know that one of these clips...
This one here.
This...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Back up over here.
This dance shit.
I don't need to trim that here
because I just want the part where he's driving forward.
Maybe even a little less.
Like right here.
One more notch.
One more knot right here.
And then right there.
Forward.
So this is the only one that I want to keep.
Now the question is, should this appear before he runs across the stage?
Let's take a look.
We gotta add the explosion in.
Let's try it over here.
Yeah, I gotta move the living room as well.
Let's check this.
I'm still gonna have an explosion there too.
I'm gonna put an explosion here, like two of them here.
Sounds.
Come on, pull it.
How does this look?
All right, that's good.
Okay, hold on.
Pull this back.
Boom, boom, boom.
The fucking part with the horse and the trash everywhere.
All right, that has to be explosion, or it sounds like that.
That actually kind of works pretty well.
That works pretty well.
These are all out of order completely.
I gotta fix these.
Here's the end.
So we're gonna start with this.
Put this over here.
Because this is like the intro to the second game.
This is like the knot in the lady.
She's everywhere.
And then we gotta get the clowns.
The car squeeze.
I don't know what happens here because there's just extras.
It's gonna be four or five clowns and then all extras.
They all get in again in different clothes.
That person got in twice.
It's just less clothes.
You just keep removing clothes.
God damn it.
Come over here.
Are they even in the right car?
Why is this?
This clip doesn't match.
It does not.
I have to delete this.
I don't think it goes anywhere.
No, that's bad.
This goes first.
Clearly, clearly only one old grandma in that car.
Right here.
It shows the constant conflict.
That, you know, you're right.
It does show that.
But I need, where's that other one?
I'll write this too.
This right here, right here.
We start with this.
And then it comes through here with some music.
Maybe a little bit shorter than that.
Doesn't need to be that long.
No in-game footage.
They both are gonna say it.
We'll go with like here.
All right, that's fine.
Everybody gets in the car.
I hate how long this is.
While they all get in, they peel out.
Let's see how this transitions together.
Intense music flying around through the city.
I'm gonna put like loud sounds.
Here's that car traffic one where there's a couple of accidents.
Him stepping on the brake.
No, no, no, no.
Get over here.
Let's try this.
Clown car battle royale.
Wrong one, wrong one, wrong one.
It's gotta be this way.
Okay.
That's so delayed.
But where does he stop?
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait.
He should stop peeling out here.
But he's no, he's still going.
No, he's gotta smash the brake.
We did this last time.
This like same scenario played out.
Hold on, let me cut this right here.
I gotta get this right because I can't go back on this.
Right there.
Looks good.
Okay.
I'm not gonna get rid of that yet because if it's wrong,
it's gotta be faster than that.
It's gotta be like slam, bang.
I'm gonna put clapping and audience applause and stuff through this.
It's a car.
The car was red.
Wait, what?
This is good.
I can add, I can, I'm gonna add sounds later.
Don't worry.
Wait.
This is one of the other clowns.
It's not even the same clown.
I don't want this in.
I don't think that that deserves to be in.
All right, let's, let's start.
I think that's good for cutting.
Yeah, this is, this is post credits.
Can I not put it there?
Come on, I can't put that in front of the credits.
All right, well, here we go.
I think it's, I think this is good.
Let's see if I can start recording here.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to the stage,
President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Steve Spruns.
I was supposed to say it worked.
Welcome to the stage, President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Steve Spruns.
What mic is it pulling from is what I want to know.
I gotta have more enthusiasm than that.
It's not pulling from the webcam.
No, I don't think so.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise.
And welcome our President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Greg Strauns.
Let's rise.
What mic is this even picking up?
Yeah, it's like I'm in another room.
Where is it?
Hold on, let me test something.
Find the mic.
Let's find it.
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee.
Why is it having so much trouble with my mic?
It's this mic here.
No, that's not the dialogue.
I have to get like really close.
All right, let me get applause here.
Is there any, is it big applause?
I think this is just a shitty one.
I was going to put like a bunch of yawns in.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise.
And welcome our President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment,
Strauns.
How about Bad Bad Bud?
President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Greg Strauns.
I'm just gonna have fucking yawns everywhere.
This is so douchey.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait.
God Entertainment.
Greg.
Boo.
That doesn't even have to be a boo.
Oh My God.
I'm gonna go a little, let's start it a little bit more back here.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise.
And welcome our President and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment, Greg Strauns.
All right, they're like da-do da-do da-do da-do.
Boo.
God Entertainment.
Strauns.
Boo.
Right there.
I can't get rid of booing mail.
How many times are you gonna hear Greg Strauns?
Greg Strauns.
Boo.
This is a lot of claps.
All right, I'll settle down everybody.
Okay, so we hear it.
I'm gonna shut, how do we shut this fucking music off?
I'm gonna get the laugh out of there.
All right, found it.
Okay.
Welcome everybody to E3.
I'm here to present to you two of our upcoming releases that I think you'll love.
And first of all, let me just be the first to say that E3, we're here.
Oh my God, that was not good.
Welcome everybody to E3.
I'm here to present to you two of our upcoming releases that I think you'll love.
And first of all, let me just be the first to say that E3, we're here.
Oh my God.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta write this out.
I gotta write this out because it's gonna be elaborate.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, hey, you in the back.
Hey, that's who I'm talking about.
Welcome to E3 everybody.
We're so happy to be here.
We are beyond excited to show you two new releases upcoming in our catalog of
Oh My God Entertainment Games.
That's Osmond, that's Michael, and that's Gary.
The three of us are who I'm talking about.
Welcome to E3 everybody.
We're so happy to be here.
We are beyond excited to show you two new releases
upcoming in our catalog of Oh My God Entertainment Games.
That's Osmond, that's Michael, and that's Gary.
Yeah, why is it so quiet?
I don't understand why it's so quiet.
Hold on, let me see.
I'm gonna save this for a second.
Maybe I have to go into like the sound options?
No, I don't think nothing was there.
It's probably a tech error happens at every E3.
I really would love to find a way to cut this.
Yeah, right clicking doesn't do anything.
Double clicking doesn't do anything.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise.
And welcome our president and CEO of Oh My God Entertainment.
Raise the volume of the game in the windows mixer
and lower the music volume from the in-game slider.
Yeah, let me see.
That's not a bad idea.
That's a really good idea actually.
Let me save it, hold tight.
So, hold on.
Let me just get in here.
Let me mute this for a second.
I think what I actually have to do is go like actually into the game,
like the mixer of the game.
Yeah, like you're saying.
Let's see if that does anything.
Did that fix?
Can you see?
I wonder if that does anything.
Whoa, that's loud.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you could please rise.
It's really loud for me now.
Hold on.
This is going to be really loud for me,
but it should be okay for you guys.
Let's see.
Tell me if this changes anything.
And welcome our president and CEO
of Oh My God Entertainment.
Here we go.
Greg Strauss.
Oh, but that's fucking loud as hell.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, you in the back.
Hey, that's who I'm talking about.
Welcome to E3 everybody.
We're so happy to be here.
We are beyond excited to show you two new releases
upcoming in our catalog of Oh My God Entertainment games.
That's Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary, the three of us.
All right, so how the fuck do I edit audio?
Yeah, I can't like drag and like resize anything.
I wonder if, hold on, can I do this?
Can I just like break it?
See if I do this.
Who's got the fucking phone on?
Yeah, I can't like drag the audio.
It just drags the whole thing.
Why?
I don't remember that being a problem.
Now the scissors cut the clip.
Audio options is just toggling on and off sound effects.
What the hell?
I think there's a way.
This guy, I think there's like a...
I don't know.
The game wiki says you can not edit the length.
I mean, I can just, you can cancel it out with something else.
I wish then I could just move it back, but no.
Oh well.
Just find the shortest music clip to cancel it out.
All right.
Because I have to record over this.
The three of us.
Okay, let's try this.
That's Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us.
We created this.
We're...
Fuck.
It's right here.
The three of us are just so...
That's Gary.
The three of us are so excited and so ready to present to you our new...
Cat.
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E-Teap Day E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
This clip is too long.
Excited and so ready to present to you our new...
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E-Teap Day E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you turn the phone off?
Was it one to a hundred?
You come to an E-Teap Day E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
I have to go over this.
Fuck, another dialogue.
He's not even moving his mouth.
So excited and so...
Wait, where's this?
Gary.
The three of us are...
So excited and so ready to present to you our new...
Okay, let's get it.
Ready?
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E-Teap Day E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
Do you see how much bigger I am than you?
This clip is too long.
I will fucking...
I will smash you.
Oh, Gavin, get up here!
You come to an E-Teap Day E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
Do you see how much bigger I am than you?
This clip is too long.
I will fucking...
I will smash you.
Oh, Gavin, get up here!
I want to get rid of this...
No, I can do better than that.
How do I get the this clip is too long out?
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
Telephone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
I fucked it up.
Hold on.
This clip is too long.
No.
This editor.
Come on, man.
This thing sucks.
Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us.
The three of us are so excited.
Are so excited.
Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited.
It's so funny to present.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What happened there?
Are so excited.
Okay.
So excited and so ready to present to you our new...
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
I don't give a shit.
This clip is too long.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
I don't give a shit.
This clip is too long.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Okay, I gotta hold on.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited and so ready to present to you our new...
...cat.
Can you turn the phone off?
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
No, I had it on silent but it didn't work.
Why don't you come up here then?
Fuck you.
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
Yeah, you got a 72% Metacritic score across all your games.
I will smash you.
I'm gonna get it, man.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
I had it on silent but it didn't work.
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah.
Fuck you.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
Yeah, you got a 72% Metacritic score across all your games.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Okay, hold on.
Wait a second.
I can do that better.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
I gotta be quicker on this one.
I wish I could grab the right one.
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
Yeah, why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
This clip is too long.
Where does it start?
Why don't you come up here then?
Yeah, why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
This clip is too long.
That's it.
Record silenced.
It's not gonna work because they layer on top of each other.
You get up here and start talking to me.
This clip is too long.
I don't give a shit.
Oh, here we go.
And start talking to me.
I don't give a shit.
This clip is too long.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Guys, guys.
Smash you.
My fucking god.
This is fucking horrible.
This is like...
All right, I gotta get this right first try.
Here we go.
Can you turn the phone off?
Sorry.
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
I thought it was on silent.
I'm sorry.
I screwed up.
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
I don't want to go up there.
No.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
Your company sucks anyways.
I'm only here because I have to.
This clip is too long.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
I thought it was on silent.
I'm sorry.
I screwed up.
Yeah, why don't you come up here then?
I don't want to go up there.
No.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
Your company sucks anyways.
I'm only here because I have to.
This clip is too long.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
What happened to this part?
Fuck you is better.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
This clip is too long.
Dude, the first one was better.
I wish I could just fucking trim audio clips.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
This clip is too long.
I don't give a shit.
Here we go.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
Fuck.
I don't give a shit.
This clip is too long.
I don't care how it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
There's no waveforms.
Oh my God.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Okay.
That's it.
I got this.
I don't know.
I'm not going to touch this.
Put cheering.
You know what?
I will.
I'm going to get this.
All right.
I want to show you guys.
So I'm going to show you what the scissors do.
The scissors split the scene.
If they don't split the audio.
We tried it already.
Somebody's rated?
Who rated?
We got a rate?
Oh shit.
Joel coming in with a rate.
Hey, thanks Joel.
Welcome everybody.
We're currently fumbling our way through the movies for a second time.
I have all these things recorded.
I'm trying to painstakingly put this together.
I hope you had a good stream.
And stick around if you'd like to see how this plays out.
But thanks a lot, Joel.
Welcome everybody.
Hope you're having a good fucking day.
This is my YouTuber voice now.
Can you turn the phone off?
Okay.
I'm going to go for it again.
Michael and that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited.
It's so ready to present to you our new...
Can you turn the phone off?
I'm sorry.
My phone's on.
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Look, you got a 68% of Medicare to go to all your games.
Why don't you come up here then?
I just said that to you.
So it doesn't matter.
Why don't you get up here and start talking.
I'm going up there.
Just let go.
I'm getting up here right now.
If it's broadcasted live, I will smash you.
What are you going to say to him?
I got it.
Where'd it go?
Where is it?
Oh.
No, I'm going up there.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
Okay.
Dialogue 14 is here.
No, let go.
I'm getting up there right now.
You get up here and start talking to me.
Fuck you.
I'm going up there.
It's too close.
Just let go.
I don't care if it's broadcasted live.
I will smash you.
What are you going to say to him?
Dialogue 12.
Oh, I would love to get dialogue 14 out of here.
Oh, no.
I would fucking love to be able to get dialogue 14.
Got it.
Okay.
I'm going to give this...
I'm going to bring in...
Let's bring in 12.
What does 12 start?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's get this up.
This is the one?
Well, it's got to be in the right spot.
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah.
Why don't you come up here then?
Oh, my God.
I'm just going to have to like leave it.
It's unworkable.
It just truly is.
You can't use this.
I'm going to have to redo everything.
I'm so excited and so ready to present to you.
I'm just going to do them all.
I'm going to do it twice.
Here we go.
Ah.
It's got to be done correct the first time.
Our new cat.
Can you turn the phone off?
You come to an E3 conference and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah.
Why don't you come up here then?
Oh.
That's why don't you get up here and record it externally.
I don't think I can bring it in.
Can I?
I'd have to restart the game.
I think I'm just going too ambitious.
So what was 10?
No, there's nothing even here.
I got to move on from the intro.
Conference, you don't turn your cell phone off?
This one's fine.
Yeah.
Why don't you come up here then?
That's why don't you get up here and start talking to me.
This clip.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh my God.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm in close now.
I think I can do it from here.
Let's grab 12.
We have to just super enhance.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
I would literally do anything to be.
It's on top of it.
Why can't I click it?
It's on top.
It is on the top.
Come up here then.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
Okay.
I'm fucking leaving it like this.
Turn the phone off.
I can grab it from here.
I guess you have to have a little tail out to even select it.
You come to an E3 conference.
You don't turn your cell phone off?
It didn't work.
Fuck you.
Why don't you come up here then?
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
I'm gonna get it.
I think that's closing up.
You come to an E3 conference.
You don't try.
We're stuck here forever.
We're stuck in like this loop forever.
Three conference.
You don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah.
Why don't you just come up here then?
You got a 72% medical score across all your games.
Why don't you get up here and start talking to me?
I'm gonna get it.
I got it.
So excited.
What happened here?
Why is it...
That's Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us are...
So excited.
So ex...
So, so, so...
The three of us are...
Just...
So excited.
And so ready to present to you.
Sorry.
It's not possible.
There's a folder for the movies in my documents.
You put a wav file in there.
Wait, what?
Is that for real?
If I put a wav in my documents,
I don't have to close the game, you're saying?
Documents the movies.
Movie sounds.
Oh, would you look at that?
Holy shit.
Okay.
It's possible.
I got them all right here.
Okay, hold on.
Give me a second.
We are just so excited to have you...
Actually, all I need is the...
All right.
This is gonna be hard though,
because I don't...
I don't have borderless windows,
so I have to like fucking rip down
every single time I want to change.
You know what I mean?
I can't like have it open
and record it at the same time.
Like it's hard, hard, full screen.
See what I'm saying?
Like the audacity is on the other monitor.
So I have to like...
I can't lip sync it.
Just watch a clip of it.
All right, let me just see how this looks.
Present to you.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Turn the music off.
Can I turn this music off?
Can you turn the phone off?
I turned it on silent, but it didn't work.
You come to an E3 conference
and you don't turn your cell phone off?
Yeah, oh, you got a 72%
Metacritic score across all your games.
Why don't you get up here
and start talking to me?
Okay, I got to link actors here.
I wish I could just give me two of these.
Give me two audio timelines.
Just...
I think...
I think it's not gonna work.
I'm gonna have to redo them all.
Just redo...
I'm gonna redo it all.
Here we go.
And then I'm moving on.
I'm only doing this two...
That's it.
I'm only doing this twice.
Okay, so I need the ringtone.
All right, here we go.
That's Michael.
It's time to call my editors.
It's time to call...
Please, God, give me one other timeline
and let me drag and trim clips.
What were you thinking?
It was like 2003.
So, here we go.
Here we go.
Two new releases upcoming
in our catalog of oh my God entertainment games.
That's Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited for you to be here
at this E3N.
I can hear that.
I can hear something over here.
Can you turn off the phone?
Turn the phone...
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone on.
Turn the phone off!
You're gonna come to E.T. and try to come to my conference?
That's two phones.
Come on, get up here then.
Get up here, motherfucker.
I'll take it right now.
I...
Don't ever...
My head hurts.
Got it.
Don't touch anything.
New releases upcoming in our catalog of oh my God entertainment games.
That's Osmond.
That's Michael.
And that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited for you to be here at this E3N.
I can hear that.
I can hear something over here.
Can you turn off the phone?
Turn the phone...
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone...
All right, let me link this audio, this one, to Studio Head.
Linking sound to actor will process the sound for lip-syncing information.
Due to the length of the clip, the lip-syncing quality may diminish slightly.
That's Michael and that's Gary.
The three of us are...
Let me ask you this though.
What just happened?
Now it's not even...
How is it not synced up?
I didn't do anything.
The three of us are so excited for you to be here at this E3N.
No, it's fine.
I can hear that.
I can hear something over here.
No, it's not gonna work.
Can you turn off the phone?
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone on.
Turn the phone up.
You're gonna come to E-Team and try to come to my conference?
That's two phones.
Come on, get up here then.
Get up here, motherfucker.
I'll take you right now.
Don't ever...
My head hurts.
Okay, it fucking worked.
I just have to get this right.
I've got to get this one right and then I've got to get it perfect.
Here we go.
It's got to be perfect.
That's Michael and that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited for you to be here at this E3N.
I can hear something over here.
That's me.
I'm sorry.
Can you turn off the phone?
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone on.
That's my phone.
Turn the phone up.
You're gonna come to E-Team and try to come to my conference?
Fuck you.
That's two phones.
Your company sucks.
42% medic.
I'm going up there.
What are you gonna do about it?
Don't ever...
My head hurts.
Got it.
Done.
Print it.
Ship it out.
Excited to show you two new releases
upcoming in our catalog of oh my god entertainment games.
That's Osmond.
That's Michael and that's Gary.
The three of us are so excited for you to be here at this E3N.
I can hear that.
I can hear something over here.
That's me.
I'm sorry.
Can you turn off the phone?
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone on.
That's my phone.
Turn the phone up.
You're gonna come to E-Team and try to come to my conference?
Fuck you.
That's two phones.
Your company sucks.
42% medic.
I'm going up there right now.
What are you gonna do about it?
Don't ever...
My head...
I'm gonna...
My head hurts.
You know what?
This is like the equivalent of trying to edit a video
while you're like swimming upstream.
It's like trying to like make a video
about somebody dumping like a bucket of water on your head.
What I just did right there takes like 36 seconds.
God damn salmon.
That takes like eight seconds.
Okay.
Here we go.
Now we just have to get the reactions.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, you in the back.
I just wish I could shut this off.
Okay.
Here we go.
Should they clap for this?
I think I have to turn off like the ambient sounds too.
Because all you just...
Who the fuck is that person?
I can hear something over here.
That's me.
I'm sorry.
Can you turn...
Can you turn off the phone?
Turn the phone.
Another one of you fucking idiots has a phone on.
That's my phone.
Turn the phone up.
You're gonna come to ET and try to come to my conference?
Fuck you.
That's too...
Paid audience.
So happy to be here.
We are beyond excited to show...
All right.
Let's put in some booze.
This is where all the effort's gone.
Can you turn off the phone?
Another one of you fucking idiots has a...
Is it like a gasp?
It's a laugh, scream, slurp, sniff, snore, spit.
That's my phone.
Idiots has a phone.
Turn the...
Just spitting.
One guy just turns it like medieval times.
That's what I think about your conference.
That's my phone.
Turn the phone up.
You're gonna come to ET and try to come to my conference?
Fuck you.
Somebody's just gonna laugh after that.
Try to come to my conference?
Fuck you.
That's two phones.
That's not...
I thought that was a laugh.
That's a chicken, apparently.
Fuck you.
That's two phones.
Come on, get off of me.
Sucks.
42% of magic.
Stop going up there.
What are you gonna do?
What?
Why does this mysteriously move?
Conference?
Fuck you.
That's two phones.
Get off of me.
Sucks.
42% of magic.
Stop going up there.
What are you gonna do?
One, two, three.
What does this sound like?
What sound even is this?
What are you gonna do?
Apparently, I don't know.
Neck breaking sound.
Hold on.
Bone break.
What are you gonna do?
I'm so desperately trying to...
It was a double tap.
That's like...
It's not loud enough.
Why do you guys want, like, breaking bones so bad?
A nice crunchy one.
Bone break 02.
How's this one?
Okay, that's really bad.
That's really, really, really, really awful.
The thing is, who's neck is breaking here?
It could be either one of them.
What are you gonna do?
Get out.
Don't hurt me.
On my head.
I'm gonna fuck my...
Okay.
What are you gonna do?
Get out.
Don't hurt me.
Whatever.
We need to fade this out.
I gotta fade out.
Okay, so this is the first game.
I need to fade out transition here.
No, no fart on fall.
Absolutely not.
No way.
Fade in.
This goes so quickly to the next clip.
All right, not in-game footage.
All right, we're moving on.
The last fart went over so well.
We're not doing another fart.
World Premiere.
Yeah, hold on.
That was awful!
Oh, that was bad.
That was terrible.
I'm not deleting this one as soon as possible.
That was awful!
Awful.
World Premiere.
Don't die on me!
Don't you die on me!
Come on!
No!
You're my co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
No!
Don't die on me!
Don't you die on me!
Come on!
No!
My co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
Forest exposition.
Don't die on me!
Will it work?
Don't you die on me!
Come on!
No!
My co-captain!
You're my co-
All right, we need a subtitle.
How do I add a subtitle here?
Reviewing technology?
Where is it?
Oh, no, don't worry.
I'm gonna add sounds.
Where is it?
World Premiere.
Oh, here we go.
Don't die on me!
Don't you die on me!
Come on!
No!
My co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
Please, lip sync.
Come on, do it!
No!
I'm getting strange readings coming from upstairs.
I wonder if that isn't anything to do with the-
Normality!
What is that?
Oh!
This one's washed, but it's-
I'm getting strange readings coming from upstairs.
I wonder if that isn't anything to do with the-
The-
Normality!
What is that?
Oh!
No, that's, like, too awful.
Yeah, I'm getting a reading about something-
Organic creature up here.
I don't know.
Does anybody have a-
Dog!
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
Possibly an organic compound.
What is that?
Oh.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
Possibly an organic compound.
What is that?
Oh.
That's it.
That's what happens.
You say, oh.
It's NPC dialogue right there.
I need a new song.
We gotta get rid of this thing.
Alien Planet.
Let's try this.
Stop.
You die on me.
No!
You're my co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
Yes, I gotta trim that.
No!
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
Why a creature?
Why-
I'm redoing this line.
I'm redoing that line.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
Possibly an organic compound.
What is that?
Oh.
Right here.
Like, the worst fucking sound you've ever heard.
That's not the worst.
That's like a-
Like a pinball.
Camera snapshot.
She's taking a picture.
That scream is too loud.
Okay, hold on.
Let me fix-
Get some of the audio in here.
World premiere.
Don't die on me!
That was just coughing into their mouth.
Wait.
Die!
That's pretty perfect.
Die on me!
Come on!
Slurp four.
What are you doing to their mouth?
Die on me!
Come on!
My co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
Die on me!
Come on!
No!
My co-captain!
You're my co-pilot!
You're not even doing CPR.
You're like-
What are you-
Okay.
I think that works pretty well.
I'm fucking disgusted.
You're my co-pilot!
Spit it out.
It's a slurp and then it's a spit.
Ugh.
Should I put-
What if I did the spit instead?
The spit in the first-
You're my co-
It's hard to control.
Pilot!
I can't make-
I gotta be careful.
I'm gonna accidentally click on something.
Come on!
Does lipstick work?
The lipstick is working.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
It pos-
What?
Organic compound.
No.
My whole fucking body hurts.
Thunder clap?
Oh, Jesus!
I need like bones.
Jesus Christ.
Where is it?
Um, okay.
It's human sounds and then it's-
It's crunching bones.
I think, right?
I don't know.
It's weapon sounds?
Is it violent sounds?
It's gone.
I- I hope I don't have to do any more characters because it's gone.
I don't have to do any-
I hope I don't have to do any more.
Hold on, let me get some water.
Oh, it's gotta be different than that.
What is that?
Should he-
Should he break out?
I don't know what it could be.
It pos-
What is that?
Oh.
You wouldn't hear this?
How do you not hear this?
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature.
I don't know what it could be.
It's possibly an organic compound.
Slowly.
Slowly breaking through the top of the ceiling.
I don't know what it could be.
It's possibly an organic compound.
What is that?
Oh.
Is there any other bone break?
I need a better-
A better bone break.
No, what was the one that I had in the bathtub?
Yeah, like glass smash.
Violent sounds.
No, not an ATM.
Glass, like, explosion.
Glass smash.
Your head is made out of, like, a little porcelain doll.
Is it gonna be a bigger one?
How is that violent?
You just dropped a teacup on the ground.
What is that?
That's a Christmas ornament.
Let me turn off the sound effects.
Let me put our own in.
I'm reading a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
It's possibly an organic compound.
It's a light bulb.
What is that?
Oh.
I think I'm gonna get rid of the camera
because this is just so anti-climactic.
What is that?
Oh.
No, I gotta get a better one.
Miscellaneous sounds.
Fire, lightning, lighting a match,
door open, dropping a tube, metal crack.
How about, um, I wish I could preview them.
That's too bad that you can't.
Door kick, hit mail, kung fu, mail, punch face, zombie hit.
Window smash.
Here we go.
It syncs pretty well.
Oh, people taking pictures of him?
Nah, I got a water right here.
I'm all right.
Gonna have the sound effects back on.
People laughing is good.
Oh, that's so loud.
I'm sorry.
It's really loud.
Let me turn it down.
Is that it?
I don't think I can turn it down.
Nope.
There needs to be a break, though.
Getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
Possibly an organic compound.
The laser is so loud, too.
What is that?
Oh.
It's like the T-Rex.
No T-Rex.
Okay, let's go over here.
What is that?
Like an eating noise?
Yeah, like crunch.
There's gotta be like a big crunch.
Weapon sounds, violent sounds.
Like it's not, I can't find anything.
Bullet body.
You think it would be bone break, but they're just like,
they're not, maybe crack knuckles is what it's gonna have to be.
I mean, that's very violent.
Okay, what the hell am I gonna do here?
What am I gonna do here?
Like squeaks when he's dancing?
Put Fortnite music in.
Oh, do not tell me to put in the Fortnite dance music.
No.
Oh my god.
Okay.
It's going in.
This guy, I gotta put it in here.
Where the hell am I gonna get like a wave of the Fortnite song?
Can I even get a wave of the Fortnite song?
There has to be somewhere.
That's the most popular game on Earth.
Default Fortnite song wave.
I mean, here it is.
Just record my phone?
Oh god damn it.
I can, all right, I can record my phone.
You're right.
Fortnite dance default.
That's a pretty, yeah, that's a pretty great loophole.
Here we go.
How loud can I make this though?
I can make it pretty loud.
It has to be louder than that.
I need to get a, let me get in a little closer.
You guys are gonna hate this.
I have to put this really close to the mic.
Okay, just, here it comes.
Just turn your volume down for a little bit.
Okay, here we go.
Turn your volume down.
Okay, how much worse does that sound?
It's gotta be moved a little.
All right, I'm gonna put it in again.
I don't like it, but I love it.
I don't think I even need anything else here.
It's so fucking loud.
I can't do anything about it, guys.
Okay, and then I need explosion, silent,
and then I need explosion sound here.
Explosion five.
This is, why is it so big?
Explosion one.
We're gonna change, we'll move the music around too,
don't worry.
I'll get to it, don't worry.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
Oh, these are all like flames.
I need explosion, explosion, like violent, like boom.
Let's try, I don't know, cannon.
Let's try 10.
This one's quick.
Is that better?
Yeah, that's fine.
And car drive sounds.
Okay, it works.
Now what the hell should I put here?
Okay, here we go.
Shit, don't touch me.
I'm not gonna be part of your experiments anymore.
Don't touch me.
All right, I need like a crash here.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta, it's when he hits the ground.
I wish I could just get it to cut off.
I have to put in like, oh, oh, oh.
All right, why is this, why is this like George Takei?
No, I just want like a axe hitting flesh.
Don't touch me, I'm not gonna be part of your experiments.
One of these should be way louder.
Zombie hit?
I'm not gonna be part of your experiments anymore.
Okay, we need like a scream here.
How about, um, sniff?
No, it's not time for that.
I will try it in one spot.
I will try it right here and that's it.
Where is it?
You're gonna get this once.
I'm not gonna be part of your experiments anymore.
You can't even hear it.
It's as long as this cut is.
It's not going in.
It's out of place.
The scream is better.
That's better.
There is no, I don't know what's happening.
This needs something else to close this out with.
Yeah, I gotta change the font here.
Where's the, oh, there we go.
That's a pretty good gamer font.
You don't even know like why,
I don't even know why he falls off this horse.
Who even fires a gun to make him fire himself off?
That's not happening.
The weapon sounds, I need something better than that.
Gun shotgun.
Gun cock shotgun.
This is better maybe?
Okay, that's better.
I need a landing sound too.
It's the wind knocked out of him.
All right, fade it out.
Fade out, fade in.
Don't worry, I'll fix the music.
I will get the music all fixed.
We gotta have some claps here.
Here comes the next premiere.
This one's even worse.
Oh, come on.
Wait till the N64 filter.
We will put this through in six months.
I'm a boomer.
What do you mean?
Pre-tech out concept.
World premiere.
This doesn't even have a title.
This is a pre-concept.
Come on, no.
Take it from Montdale High School Science Program.
Why would they need to use that?
Pre-concept footage used from high school students.
Yeah, like a different something.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can make this shorter.
Why can I not make this capital?
Okay, there we go.
Is he still wrong?
I don't care.
What a terrible pre-concept.
This is made by high schoolers.
So it has to have a bunch of fucking dumb noises in it.
Okay, let me go back.
And we gotta fix some of the music here.
What are you gonna do about it?
I gotta do a better world premiere than that.
Don't die on me.
Fuck!
How do I get rid of it?
I can't get rid of it.
He's George Lucas-ing.
He's, I'm George Lucas-ing.
You're right, I can't do that.
That's the most upset I've been in a long time.
About something that I did.
Sorry, I got it right here.
There it is, 19.
Right?
Which one is it?
Dialogue 27.
Dialogue 27, find it.
I see it.
16, where the fuck is it?
It's right here.
Dialogue 19, 27.
Which one am I gonna touch?
No, not the right one.
Not the right one.
I got it.
It's selected, right?
That's selected, isn't it?
If I hit delete, that's selected.
Dialogue 27 is selected right now.
Please confirm.
Did it.
I got it.
World premiere.
Got it.
Okay, no more George Lucas-ing.
I need to do music though.
So right here.
Oh!
No!
Okay, now we're gonna make the music.
Let's see.
Action.
Chrome virus.
Moonlight romance.
Fool about.
Creepy crawly.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature.
That scared the shit out of me.
Organic compound.
What is that?
Oh.
I can't.
Whoa!
Look at what I'm doing.
Look at what I'm...
Holy shit, look what I did.
But how do I...
No, stop.
I just have to have fanfare happen.
Shit.
That's a remix.
Turn this down.
It's not even like in the right spot now.
Wait, hold on.
Jesus Christ!
It scared me again.
All right, now we need...
We need like a crazier song here.
Armageddon.
Dr. Moore's Evil Lab.
Let's see what this sounds like.
No, we gotta have like more action than that.
Acid Base?
I don't think Acid Base is not long enough for this.
What is going on with this fanfare one?
It's gonna be loud.
This is a fuck...
This is an absolute mess.
This app doesn't...
I don't even know if I can salvage this last part.
Fresh sneakers.
Not bad.
You need laughs.
Hold on.
I can...
I need a laugh track.
Because this is you guys...
You guys...
This is you guys laughing at the E3 conference.
I know exactly where I can get a laugh track with my telephone.
This one's probably better.
Now lower your volume.
Let us do the laugh track in the Discord server.
No.
You can barely hear it.
It's like a...
It's like you're outside of E3 and you can hear this.
They laugh when the door opens.
Why is that so funny?
Just loop them into the...
Just stack them on top of each other.
And this is just stupid enough to work.
I can't tell if this is working or just a waste of time.
I think it's working.
Only one.
It's Doom Eternal.
Uh-oh.
I saved it, right?
Saved it like...
I saved it pretty good.
I got it.
I saved it.
It's crashed.
Too many looping Doom Eternals.
I saved it like less than five, ten minutes ago.
We didn't have very much shit.
It's all right.
When I deleted world premiere.
Yeah.
What else?
I didn't do anything else.
It wasn't that long ago.
Yeah, just the music.
But it's just Creepy Crawler, Acid Base, and Fresh Sneakers.
I think this is hard locked.
I can't close it.
What the hell?
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
Let me just...
I have to get my task manager open.
Shit.
No!
No, I can't even end the task.
Come on, please.
No, it's not over.
We're so close to being able to be done and watch it.
This is like four hours in the making.
I ain't going.
Let me see if I can pull it from here.
I can't get it.
I'm trying to alt tab and hit task manager with alt tab.
But it's going to my...
It's still behind.
It's on my other window.
It's...
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Delete.
Don't be completely hard locked here.
Please.
Yeah, that did it.
Task manager, alt tab to see it and then use the arrow keys and then...
Yeah, that's what I'm doing right now.
Delete.
I got the mouse.
I can click the X.
It's just not doing anything.
Because I can close the other ones.
Windows tab and make a new window in the top left.
Is there anybody that I can open the task manager to my other monitors?
You know what I'm saying?
How do I do that?
Windows key plus tab.
Okay.
Okay, I got the task manager open, but I just can't use it.
Task manager.
Ah, it looked like it was going to do it for a second.
I can't like drag it.
Always on top task manager.
I don't know why mine's not up there like that.
Windows key and left arrow.
New desktop.
Wait, desktop one.
What the hell did I just do?
Hello?
I don't see anybody.
I'm on a new desktop.
I have no OBS.
I have...
What happened?
No, I was just in...
I was just there.
All right, I'm back.
I'm back.
So I did new desktop.
I tried to open task manager on the new desktop and I can't...
I couldn't do it because I'm new desktop.
Task manager in the new desktop.
I'm here.
The first task manager is currently closed.
Right click on the bottom bar and new desktop.
Click task manager.
All right, I'm going to try it again.
Wish me luck.
New desktop.
Okay.
I'm trying...
Okay, task manager.
I got it.
You guys are so smart.
End task.
Got it.
We're good.
You guys are seriously fucking so smart.
We're back.
All right, let's open it back up.
What would I do without you guys?
I don't know.
What would I do without you?
I'm...
We're getting to the end of this.
I'm finishing this tonight.
Because I'm not streaming tomorrow.
Let's go.
Uh-oh.
The movie stunts and effects was not closed properly the last time you used it.
If it fails to run, you can look for a solution in the readme file.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
Please open.
It opened.
Can you see it?
Back in action.
It's gonna be really loud.
Turn your volume down.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Turn your volume down now.
The menu here is 10 times louder than the game.
Warning.
Oh, this isn't even that bad.
Okay, game.
Load game.
We were here, right?
2130...
Wait, what?
Pee Pants 2.
Yeah, it's this one here.
My ear...
I thought...
I really thought it was gonna be really loud.
Usually is.
Auto save or pee...
No, Pee Pants 2.
You'll have to save this game in 2001.
I know.
Here we go.
Um, wait.
What?
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I saved it.
I saved like making the video.
Making the movie.
I think I have to be like in the post-production menu, probably?
Yeah.
Just go into the movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We just gotta...
We just gotta go into um...
Into where?
Can I get there from here?
Post-production.
Should I just drag it in there?
Pee 3 cancel.
What is the point?
I just gotta get into post-production, right?
I am so scared to just hit shoot this.
No.
I was very clear.
It has to be saved.
Yeah, I mean why would they have a save feature there?
Well, it's...
Load game.
No.
The autosave?
This is like the save file.
The file should be in the game folder.
Yeah, let me just...
Let me just...
Let me just get into like the editor and try to open it.
Let me like just shoot this and then get into the editor.
That's very sad if that's the case.
Just get it into post-production and then open up from there.
It has to be there.
Do not override it.
Yeah, just bring it to post, right?
Before...
Let me just...
Hold on just a second.
Let me do something here.
I'm gonna go into the save files and just like copy the one that's there right now.
Hold on a second.
Where would that be?
Like just in case it overwrites it or something.
Let's go to...
It's in my documents, right?
Movies.
E3 presentation is in here.
I see it.
It was modified at 1139 p.m.
It's a configuration file.
I'm going to copy both of these.
There's E3 presentation and E3presentation.trl.
And I'm gonna just paste them over here.
I'm just gonna have them.
There's also a couple of these.
I'm just gonna copy these as well just in case something horrible happens.
And then I get...
I see get out of town here as well.
All right.
E3 presentation, configuration, movies.
Let me just check the other ones.
Movie sounds.
They're still in there.
Saved games.
Okay.
But these are saved games and not configuration files.
I have my E3 presentation config file here.
Cross your fingers.
Because we're gonna just...
I'm gonna put it into post-production.
See what happens.
I got the...
Everything's backed up.
Let's try to...
Let's see what happens.
Can you go into post-production from the main menu?
I don't think you can.
Here we go.
That's not...
I can't...
Wait.
Whoa, wait, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
It's here.
This is it.
It's fine.
Everything's done.
The whole item was just...
Item was died.
For a second, I was so depressed because I thought that was load.
Okay.
So where do we leave off?
Something's not right.
Something's not right, guys.
These are off somehow.
I think the cuts are all gone.
Are they all gone?
No, they're not.
Are they?
Yeah, they are.
All the edits are gone.
Because this was not over here.
This is gonna screw up everything.
Because I have to edit it again.
If it was saved, though, why wouldn't I be able to pull it from here?
I lost a half an hour of progress?
Nah, but this...
Some of these clips, especially like this one here...
Like, see, look at this.
This was...
I put these over there.
I did this the first thing I did.
Go to main menu and post-production.
I'll try it.
Main menu?
Can I get that from the main menu?
I can't load it from here, unfortunately.
It's just pulling it.
The audio is here, but I'm gonna edit this and it's gonna get screwed up.
Is there a way...
Let's just see.
Hold on, just get out.
Main menu.
See if I can...
No, don't save the current game.
Movie player?
No, the cuts aren't here.
Maybe I can't reshoot it.
Let's do this then.
I'm gonna reload my save.
Nah, those are the only config files that are in there.
Swap out the movie files?
You're talking about the ones that I...
Oh yeah, let's do this.
Let's try this.
So it's because I've shot the movie, maybe.
So technically, let's just see.
So I have these, the presentation and the TRL both saved here.
I'm gonna paste these back in and I'm not gonna reshoot it.
I'm literally just gonna paste these back and then go to the movie player.
Damn it.
I'm like, annoyed by this, but like at the same time.
I don't know.
That just like sucks, but whatever.
But hopefully this works.
Oh, let's go...
I wish we could have seen the whole thing.
I still could do it.
I still could do it, but let's just try this.
Let's go back to my documents.
Go to the movies.
This would be a good indicator here.
If E3 presentation is 30 kilobytes and 132 kilobytes for what's in there now,
what is it over here?
I just like burped internally.
I wonder if this will change.
All right, guys, guys, we have a...
Guys, I think this is gonna work because they're different file sizes.
They're different file sizes.
If this works, oh, I'm gonna pee with such joy.
Come on, they're different.
They're not the same size.
That has to mean something.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna paste them in here.
I have the originals right here.
Paste them in, replace the files.
Yeah, they're different files.
They're fucking different file sizes.
It has to mean something.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, I have to...
Compact file means there's less data,
which means that makes sense because I was cutting things, right?
Right?
Please tell me that's right.
Let's see what happens.
Here we go.
So just from here, we're gonna go to the movie player.
I'm a CS student.
That's 100% correct.
Let's hope so.
Movie player.
What is this?
Load.
No, none of the cuts are here.
Because there was so many cuts that I did just to clean everything up.
Oh, no, like this is...
Let's just see.
Hold on.
Yeah, see?
I did a lot of...
It's time to cut.
If I remember where I cut everything,
it should line up in the same place.
I just don't remember everything.
Why is there a ghost here?
No.
Speed run the movie?
I'm so disappointed right now.
I still have the audio.
I still have the...
I don't remember where everything was.
That still fits.
That's still...
All right.
This is still okay.
What's not okay?
Wait, what?
Why is that back?
I saved right after doing this.
I think this whole thing is fucked up.
It was right before, but where are the cuts then?
Am I insane or are they here?
Don't die on me.
You die on me.
Come on.
My co-captain.
You were my co-pilot.
Okay, I think it's still salvageable.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
No, the cuts are...
That was the big kicker here.
I cut it here, remember?
I'm just gonna go for it.
I'm going for it.
Now, because look.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
That's not the right place to cut.
It's over here.
This might actually save the whole thing.
Where was it?
It was like right here, right?
I'm not gonna get this exact, but...
Because then he crashes through.
Let's just do this.
I know it's like...
Because then the whole thing shrinks down.
It could be, it possibly could be...
I'm getting a read...
This cuts here.
Getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
I don't know what it could be.
It could possibly be an organic compound.
What is that?
It's close.
It was right here, I think.
Right before he puts his hand on his chin.
No!
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
It doesn't matter.
It's okay.
I'm getting a reading of a strange creature up here.
We can have some messed up parts.
I don't know what it could be.
Possibly an organic compound.
What is that?
It's progress, but it's gonna take a lot of time.
Damn it.
It's still off a little.
I had it so...
The stupid clown laughing.
Shit.
What is that?
Let me see if this whole thing's screwed up now.
It's just so off.
That it's...
I'm like working backwards.
I'm depressed.
Because I was about to like get this done.
And now it's like...
The kind of steam has left the engine here, unfortunately.
It's definitely fixable.
I'm so...
Like salty's not like mad.
It's not even the right word.
Let me just go back and load it again.
I need to see it again.
Why?
This never happened before.
I've played this game before too.
I'm getting a reading.
You need to rest.
I'm so unfulfilled.
This has been like such a long time coming.
I'm not fulfilled at all.
Don't stack 10 laugh tracks.
Yeah, but how would I have known that that was gonna break everything?
I would never have known that.
And I was saving it too.
So it's not like I...
I mean if a game crashes, you would assume.
I think it's...
Where is it?
Right before...
Or right after.
Where the audio starts with each clip, you know where to start.
Yeah, but the problem is if I cut right here...
This is just...
I did all this before putting in the audio.
And when you...
Every time you trim something, it moves everything.
You use the vase to see the exact timing.
Here...
All right.
Here's what's gonna happen with this.
Here's the deal.
Okay.
I'm gonna...
Because I'm playing this again with mods, I'm going to...
Off stream.
I am going to finish this.
I'm gonna sleep.
I'll come back to it.
I'm gonna finish this one off stream.
Have it done to watch.
Because you...
It was done.
It was like pretty much done.
There's like a little bit left.
It's like this portion here.
And there's this tiny little portion over here.
So because it's just getting late, then I'm not gonna lie.
I'm a little disappointed.
But we will watch this one on the next movie stream.
Because that means that I can get out of the default ones
and we can get all the weird characters and all the new props and all the new stuff.
We'll open with this one.
And then that'll be good because maybe the people that weren't here
for this stream could just enjoy the three to four or five hours
that it took to make this one.
You know what I'm saying?
I think that's the best plan.
Because we are going on eight and a half hours here.
So the plan here is I am off tomorrow.
I have to make a few phone calls tomorrow.
I think they're going to be lengthy.
I can't really stream tomorrow.
Tuesday or Wednesday, depending, either depends on when Star is around.
Star and I are going to play Deep Rock Galactic together
on either Tuesday or Wednesday.
And whatever day that we do that, you know,
the movies mod stream will be the other day.
So Tuesday is probably the day we're going to do it.
Wednesday will be the new movies one or flip it around.
We'll see.
But that's the plan for the next two streams.
So that's where I have to call it.
I'm sorry, everybody.
Kind of a all over the place stream.
But I've laughed harder than I fucking have in a long time.
This game is fucking hilarious.
It's kind of buggy and broken as some of the stuff could be.
I got at least like 45 minutes of straight laughing.
So I hope you enjoyed it, too.
We will come back.
Batman is a character.
We're going to do like a Batman one.
I'll be honest with you here.
I might make a couple more to show just so you can see them
without knowing what they are just before we get started
on the other ones to get.
I kind of want to get some more experience in it.
Maybe I'll just hang out up here tomorrow
and just like chill and make a couple.
We'll see.
But thanks for watching, everybody.
If you're I mean, I'm going to save it.
It's all right.
I got the files.
I'm just going to go through this on my own.
So it's already saved.
Yeah, I'm going to go back to the VOD
and find like the little exact points to cut.
But that's like painstaking.
I got to like all tab and go and move and get.
You don't want to be here for that.
That's really boring.
I don't think I want to put everybody through that,
especially after putting you through what I would assume
was like 40 straight minutes of trying to figure out
how to get everything to work correctly.
So I do apologize again for that.
But that's where the end of the stream is going to happen.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Thanks again if you came from Joel's stream.
Joel, thanks for the raid again.
Yeah, I can watch it on like an iPad or phone or something.
I'll get it.
I need to do this.
Hey, look at that.
So pardon me while I'm going to pee.
I'll come back.
We'll do the bits.
The bits on another desktop.
I think the bits are on a different desktop than this.
Are they?
Oh, no, no, no.
I got them.
Okay.
All right.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to pee.
And we will close this out.
Thanks for watching, guys.
Be right back.
All right, I'm back.
So let's go back to earlier.
We had this is eight hours ago.
Long time ago.
Curly snail.
Thanks for five dollars.
It's been a while.
Take my money.
We'll gladly take anything that you give me.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Also, we had ten dollars from Reaper's Reviews.
Just no message.
Ten dollars.
Thank you, Reaper's Reviews.
Ten bucks coming in.
Really appreciate it.
Nile Orion.
Thanks for three bucks.
Great value.
Jex for next.
Jerma Rumble.
That would be pretty funny, actually.
I want to start working on that, too.
It's been long enough.
There's a lot of things I want to just do.
But thank you, Nile Orion.
Yes is online.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Turns out I completely forgot I made this green screen video before I moved to LA.
I also got that lump in my chest checked out and turns out it is benign.
Hope your father's day was good.
Thank you so much for the five dollars.
And my father, I'm going to be seeing my father really soon.
So, but that's glad that you've got that checked out and everything is
everything's good to go.
Because that shit is, you know, it can be fucking scary.
I'm still waiting on some biopsies, which I would have told.
Everything seems to be okay.
But you know, you always just keeps you up at night sometimes.
It takes a couple of weeks for them to come back.
Two, three weeks, I think.
It is like a, you know, it's a scary fucking thing.
Take care of yourself.
Keep yourselves in check.
But a green screen video.
We're going to do a green screen Encore Night on the 29th of June.
I'm going to hold this off until then.
Chat during stream.
LOL, this guy is a fucking idiot.
Wow.
Chat at the end of stream.
Hearts.
Love you, Jerma.
The duality of man.
No.
For the most part, people are just messing around.
I mean, I do some pretty stupid fucking things.
So I am not at, I am not completely absolved of all crime here.
But thank you so much for the video.
Hold on to it though.
Over the next week or so.
Well, probably in a couple days.
At least like a week before I'll get a good idea of kind of how we want to set that up.
Because I don't want like 500 video.
I kind of just want the ones that we haven't seen that have trickled through.
I don't want that to be like an eight hour, four or 500 video stream like the first one was.
I'd rather that just be like a chill, you know, not like a huge, huge, huge thing.
Is there more green screen footage for the Encore or do we just use the original?
It's just the stuff that's there and whatever other clips that you'd want to use.
But I would really like to get that.
So it was stuff that we missed and stuff people have made since.
And maybe a few others here and there.
It's not going to be, it'll be a little bit more condensed.
It'd be condensed, but it should be fun.
That also might just be on the end of a stream for a couple hours.
You know, an hour or two.
I will have some more details in the next three or four days.
I will probably, I'm going to be talking to mods in the Discord.
We'll get another probably channel going.
Not going to be a big, big thing.
But thank you to Tumsup for the 250.
Thanks for making my night like you always do.
My chest hurts from laughing and I've only been watching for an hour.
Thank you.
I'm glad you think it was fun.
I was so, it's weird this stream was so all over the place.
I was at my most upset and at my happiest on the same day.
That's weird.
I was so infuriated by like two or three things that happened tonight.
And it was like yin and yang tonight.
When I thought I wasn't going to be able to open the expansion pack.
Oh, you're talking, that's the yang.
When I slurped and spit into the person's mouth I was doing CPR with.
That's the yin right there.
You had four miracles tonight.
Yeah, I guess I did.
The high point was the spit and slurp.
I also think the bathtub and the E3 headbutt.
There was, I wish I could get that done.
I'm so sad.
Oh well.
I can't be crying over spilled E3.
Just have to clean it up.
Fortnite dance, yeah.
Yeah, there's some good things.
But thank you.
Thank you Pajagalo for the 10 bucks.
Ten dollars.
Hey Jeremy, just checking in from our parent corporation to inform you that
as per your contract, every film you make must end with a gorilla reading a book.
We had a great gorilla punchline at the end of E3.
The gorilla was on Reddit angry at the E3 conference that he just watched.
There was a pretty good callback there.
I was happy about that one.
So that technically counts.
But thank you for the 10 dollars.
Thank you Swiggity Swanky for the 7 dollars.
I know how much you love dreams.
I dreamt that I went to Germacon, but when I arrived it was empty.
It was only you and me, no one else.
When I asked where everyone was, you asked me to shake your hand.
But before I could do anything, you lunged at my hand and grasped it, holding it firmly.
I saw my arm was merging with yours, slowly absorbing me like from the thing.
I couldn't pull away and soon became you.
Now I understand why no one was at Germacon.
Just absorbing everybody?
Chat was Jerma all along.
Oh my god.
That's fucking insane.
If I ever do like a meetup here in Vegas, I will not be doing that.
T2000.
Very detailed dreams.
Thank you to...
Thank you to Nickname Jack for the 3 dollars.
Haven't shown any love in a while, so here it is.
Much love Mr. Pee Pants.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
We had Never Trust a Purple.
Thank you Purple for the 10 dollars.
Yo Jerma, any plan on a 3 year sub badge?
Yes.
There's gonna be a lot of random things added and changed on the channel.
There's gonna be lots of new sub badges.
There's gonna be new screens, a bunch of new music,
a bunch of changes in the back end of the channel.
There's gonna be a lot of...
There's gonna be a lot of new things here.
What about a no sub badge?
Yeah, I mean, that's fine.
You don't have to have a sub badge.
You don't have to have one.
Jerma default dance.
But thank you Purple.
Also DC Pro, thank you for the 245.
But I'm gonna say, I'm gonna round it up.
I'm tired.
I'm rounding it up.
Thank you.
Father's Day always sucks for me,
but last night's stream and tonight's stream got me through the weekend.
Thank you Jerma, hope all is well.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm sorry to hear that Father's Day is not a good day for you.
But we got a community of fun little jokesters here.
I'm sitting here talking about this fun great community of people
and they're so interesting and so helpful and so great.
How about another streamer?
Replace the streamer.
What about a new streamer?
This one is...
How do we get rid of behind a new host?
Any plan on new emotes?
Yeah, there'll be like five new emotes, maybe more.
I want to redo the tier two and tier three emotes
because they're dog shit or they don't exist.
Does it...
We don't even have any tier two...
Are they gone?
They can have one.
No, I don't have any tier two or tier three.
I was gonna change them.
Wait, is still...
Is the golden BS still...
Oh yeah, golden BS is still tier two.
Tier three is gonna be just something stupid,
but there's gotta be something there at least.
There are like...
There are a handful of tier three subs,
so I obviously don't want to just not have anything.
I don't know why I played that.
The tab was open and I'm closing tabs,
getting ready to end the stream,
and I just figured I would press the button.
What is this?
We are just so excited to have you...
Oh, that's audacity, never mind.
Shit show.
Fucking shit show.
That beginning took me so long.
That's probably when Joel came in with the raid too
and I'm just sitting there going,
I can't fucking do it!
I can't do it!
Like screaming and like headbutting some lady.
So excited.
Edit all the clips and audacity.
Yeah, I'll clean it up.
I'll clean it up.
But that's gonna be it.
I'm gonna roll the credits.
There's a couple more bits that came through,
but I was gonna make sure I get the credits rolling.
A lot of subs tonight.
That's pretty usual.
I mean, there's a lot of subs every night.
So thanks, guys.
Yeah, Joel raided like a few hours ago?
Two, three hours ago?
There's a lot of people that are
continuously subscribed to this channel.
Month to month, day to day.
Week to week.
Year to year.
Thanks.
I will see you all on Tuesday.
And Wednesday's stream is gonna be
the last one for a little while.
Visiting family and getting some work done on a stream.
So I will be working.
I will be.
Just won't be on camera.
And let's get the last couple of bits that came in here.
They are.
No, I think I got them all.
I got them all.
Thanks for the laughs you've given us
watching you broadcast E3 while at E3
was oddly one of the most hilarious things I've ever done.
Thank you for everything and take care.
I think that was creamy sensation.
Thank you.
Watching you broadcast E3 while at E3.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
You were watching me broadcast E3
while you were sitting at E3?
That would have been interesting.
Yes, it's the dunk tank.
And I'm going to give you, because this is 1230, 1240.
At the very least, it's the dunk tank.
And if you don't know what I'm talking about,
let's just talk about it for a second.
Might as well.
Because this is the last time I probably will talk about it
until you see it or until we have to test some things.
But the dunk tank stream, if you weren't here
or don't know what I'm talking about,
I am going to get a dunk tank.
And not just a dunk tank.
Because at this point, I want to do more.
We are the very least going to try very desperately.
Because I do have somebody who is very knowledgeable now.
I have like an actual robotics team
that I'm emailing back and forth with.
I have some calls with.
And I'll be meeting with other people too.
So the dunk tank is going to be potentially me up there.
I've got a dunk tank expert.
There's going to be a pitching machine
that is going to be attached to a robot
which you will be controlling to try to dunk me.
On top of that, on top of that,
I'm going to probably try to do other games
like a claw machine that you guys control,
like a little carnival.
I'm going to try.
This could be a catastrophic failure.
But if I get the green light,
if I do over these next five to 10 days,
because this is what I'm going to be working on.
If I get the legit green light here,
I'm going to focus on it almost completely.
So that's the plan.
If the plan works or not, we'll find out.
That is what I'm going to be trying to do.
The reason why I'm talking about it now
and been alluding to it is
because we're going to have to test some stuff.
You're going to see in the chat room, randomly,
probably like me and other people
and mods and stuff like pressing buttons.
You're not going to have any idea
what the hell is going on.
So I want you to be aware of it.
Because I cannot just turn it on
and be like, let's see if it works.
No, no, no.
I'm going to make sure this works
because I'll be putting probably some cash
into this.
We'll see.
Hopefully, it's not wasted time.
Wish me luck.
But thank you, everybody, for watching.
I'll see you on Tuesday.
And we'll play some more games.
Star and I are going to do something
and you'll see some modded...
I almost said The Sims 4.
May as well be.
Have a great night.
See you Tuesday.
Take care, guys.
Goodbye.