Hey, what's going on everybody? It's me Demon Lord Xaraxos here. You're probably wondering where's
Jerma? What happened to him? How come he's not doing this video? Well, it's because I have taken
over his soul, and I will only release it after playing around a Five Nights at Freddy's. Because
everyone wants to see Five Nights at Freddy's, and who better than me, the Lord of all Hells and
demons and hatred? I'm not scared of anything. What could I possibly be afraid of in this little
shit game? I don't know. We'll find out very shortly. Let's go ahead and play a new game.
This guy sounds kind of like an asshole. I'm gonna ignore him. Let's go camera 4B. That's what we're on.
Camera 5. Okay, 12 a.m. There's a bird. I don't like birds. Okay, camera 1A. Camera 7.
I can close the door. What the fuck was that? Okay, well that was a little weird. That was like a bird
in my face. I wasn't scared. I was not scared of that. I was just startled that it had jumped up
at me and scared me, so obviously that'll scare you. I don't think that I was scared, though,
because you were scared. I wasn't the one that was scared. It was you, actually.
And you look like there's a blinking light over there now. Freddy. Oh, Freddy. Where are you,
Freddy? You can't hide from demon lord Xaraxos. I will boil you. I will eat your flesh and tear
off the bones and use them as toothpicks in my stew. If you think I'm going to be scared of your...
One of them is missing. Okay, one of them is missing. Now, there was a rhinoceros that was
here before, and he just ain't here. This bear might have moved. I might have seen him somewhere.
I don't know. Pirate Cove is out of order. Let's just go back and make sure there's nobody
potentially trying to kill me, but I will kill them first. That's what you need to remember
from this whole thing. I will kill them first before they try to kill me. There is a guy standing
there. There is a guy in a funny little suit standing there now, and I don't really know what
to do. Should I... He's still there. Okay. I hear music. No, no, the night's almost over. I only have
3% power, so that means the cameras are all going to turn off, and we're going to all go to sleep,
and it's going to be a nice, fun day at Freddy's Pizza Place Pizzeria, right? What the hell's that?
What the hell's going on? What the hell's going on? It's time to open the store. The pizzas are
opening. Why would you work here? Who would work at an establishment where you could actually get
killed by the people, the participants in the suits? I don't know why you would ever do such a
thing. You come work for me. At least there's benefits down in hell. You know, you get a good
dental plan. No, no, it's pretty good. You know, we're going to continue. I'm going to get... I
don't even know what the goal here is. I do not see him anywhere. Where is he? He's in the kitchen.
He's in the kitchen. The son of a bitch is in the kitchen. That means... Is he coming out here?
Yeah, he's in the kitchen. No, he's in this one. Okay, now he's right here. He's going to be right
here. No, he's not right here. Where is he? Oh, he's right... Okay, he's right here. He's literally
staring at me. It's 4 a.m. Don't let them come in. Do not let them come in. Is the door locked?
Both the doors are closed. You stay where you are. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey. None of that. We're not gonna have any of that. Oh, boy. This is closed. We're at 4 a.m. now.
Just got to get through the night. No, no, I got through the night. I did it. I was staring... I got
through the night. This is... Come on, we won. I won the game. Did I not win the game? Are you telling
me I didn't win the game? I was staring at him. What the hell? Oh, boo, here he comes. He's gonna
come. Oh, oh, boy. Don't get scared. Oh, you know what? I'm just... I'm just gonna go play Super
Mario Brothers because that game... I don't want to play this anymore. Jerma, Jerma, your soul is now
free. I'm releasing you. Why? Whoa, where... What happened? Well, just calm down, calm down.
Everything's okay. Everything's all right. I have it under control. I stole your soul so I can come
to earth to play Five Nights at Freddy's. What?