I have a quick question. If I were to say in a tweet, for instance, like I'm out running something out running the cylinder, is it out space running? Or is it out running one word? Because the other one implies you you're like out. It's one word. Yeah, that's what I thought. All right, in here in a minute. All right, let's go. Let's go. How you doing? Just wanted to get my tea. A nice hot tea here. We're going to pick up where we left off a day or two ago. Still in the eternal cylinder.
Well, still trying to outrun the eternal cylinder. Let's get that correct. You finished Elden Ring so fast. Um, I mean, we did it. Took us four streams. Each stream was what? Between seven and nine hours. Took us like 30, 40 hours to do it. There we go. Okay. All right. Are you ready? We're moving. Welcome back. This game is pretty cute. It's really fun. Let's keep playing it. Do we need a recap for anybody that wasn't here? Here's the recap. That's a very
loud for me. I'm so glad I turned it down for you. All right, so here's the recap. I plugged a controller into I'm imagining is probably better this way. So recap. There's a gigantic cylinder that is crushing every I can't we can't we have to move now.
All right, that thing instantly kills you. We lost a couple of friends along the way here. The last thing that happened is we went inside we went across. I can't we got to go. We have to we actually have to leave like right now. No.
It's not happening. It's not happening. No, no, no. I'm sorry. That's not happening. I've that's just not happening guys. I'm sorry. That's not the way it works. We got to go. How do I Okay, that's how I do it on controller like this. Okay, who's who's the horn? Who's the horn? You do right? Who's the horn? Somebody has a horn. Can't tell who has the horn. Oh, no, you do. You do. Okay, do it. Hold the horn. Fuck off. Get out of here.
All right. Good. Okay. So recap. Let's get away from that thing because I think it's horrible. Got to get away from the cylinder every time you leave this kind of dome. It's kind of like fortnight area. The cylinder moves. Do I want to do this? This is a goo one. Whoa, I actually kind of like that. I do it. How many stakes? We need six. Do I have six stakes? I have seven stakes. Okay, we can get one. Let's do it. Whoa, this is cool. I like the goo one. All right, let's go. It's like orange.
White and green. Okay, I feel safer. Where's our new friend? Oh, no, it's pink and red. Very cool. All right. Is Gunu dead? No, Gunu is right here. This is Gunu. Everybody hungry? We're good. I mean, this is a hardcore playthrough. If Gunu dies, that's over. I leave. I would be so distraught if that happens. I do kind of have to relearn the game though. I'm playing on a controller. I would cry. All right, here we go. A few stakes. You know, get rid of some of this bullshit. I don't want all this. Here we go.
I don't have anything on the map. The map is kind of all blurry. I think we just have to keep going. You see the big lit up kind of Sauron eye? We have to go over there. We did get a new friend. I can't see very much on the map. I don't know. I think we're just gonna go. So I crossed that threshold. Now the cylinder moves and you got to make it to this thing or you die. Come on, friends. Let's go. This is your quick recap. The Eternal Cylinder. It's a pretty fun game. I don't know how long the game
is, but wait. Oh, he's sparkly. Yeah, I think it's somewhere between 10 and 15 hours. We'll get through it. So we made it. Let's see what happens now. It was so weird going across this thing and seeing the actual huge guy. Spoiler alert, but there's a huge guy. We got everybody. Yep. We got everybody. Everybody eat. Yeah, the mathematician. Yep. The mathematician was as weird as that thing. Okay. All right. We're not going over there. I'm not going that way. Do I still have? Do I have
a map yet? I don't. How do I make the map not scrambled? I want to be able to see where I can go. This time, the Trevor knew what they were feeling. Here was another servant of the cylinder. But what shape would this creature's evil take? It did not seem interested in the Trevor. The servant of the cylinder had released a swarm. Small parasites had come from within it and attached themselves to the creatures of this area.
I'm ready to burn. It was somehow using them to corrupt the tower, to turn its protective force into a trap. What? All Tribum hate parasites by nature. And they hated these even more. They would have to remove them. But how? Burn. I burn? All right. I'm going to try. I'm going to everybody stay back. I'm going to try burning. No, get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. I don't want anybody to die. I wonder how I do that.
How do I do this? I can't save it here. Come on, get it off. All right. It's just water. It's one. Actually, get it. No, no, no. Move out of the way. Another friend over there. Bring it. Do we get it? I don't think so. Where is it? Where is it attached? On the back? Get the fuck out of here. No, I don't know. I don't know where it is. It's like on the back leg. I get it. OK, got it. Oh, it completely missed everybody. Holy shit.
I can't believe nobody got hurt. OK, this is a huge pain in the ass. How am I supposed to reliably do this without everybody getting killed? All right, there. Got it. OK, like hit its head. We're good.
There's one, two more or one more. I wonder what happens when I do this. That's three. I think I killed it. I killed it. Did I? Yeah, I think I think it's just dead. So true.
Yeah, true, true. Let's go back to Gunnu. Pick up the stuff that you sprayed. That's a good idea. Wait, what is anything on this? The one fell over here.
Why do you hate Gunnu? All right, where is it? Right here? Is that it? I don't think that's it. Where did it fall off? I was too busy trying to I was panicking because I didn't want to die.
All right, can I get this one? Three and no, I can't. Sorry, buddy. I don't remember where they are. I'm too afraid to investigate anymore. Yeah, this is this is just me dying matter. This is definitely an opportunity where I can pick it up again. It's all good.
I wish I wish I had a way to defend myself. I want I want like a trebum that has a fucking like gun. What does this do again? Oh, the the eyes. OK. Um, I think somebody already have this. Oh, my God. Will you leave me the fuck alone?
I can't even have five seconds to look at the menu. All right. Come here. You. Hey, hey, hey, new guy. This is yours.
Get up. Leave me alone. I want to move. Move. Move. It's gonna be like a chill night. This I these fucking random ass creatures. I want to just I want to just blow them up.
This is no way to go. I have to just keep moving. If I stop for more than 10 seconds, everybody dies. OK. Can you eat that? Oh, my God. Leave us alone for one second. Leave me fucking alone.
I'm not going that way yet. Use the horn. I only have one. One of my random assholes has it. OK, you have the horn. I'm just I'm only playing as this character.
I think the horn actually pisses them off and makes them more angry sometimes, though. Oh, fuck. I went across the threshold. Good to go.
Um, what? I got time. Yeah, this time I got plenty of time. No, we're good. OK. Can they not be like a hundred monsters everywhere right now? Thank God. That was horrible.
OK. Never mind. It's about to get way worse. Keep up. Keep up. Keep up. Keep up. OK. Where's the next one? It's OK. We have to we have to keep it in between us.
Where? Come on, hurry up. Hurry up. Face toot. I don't know what that person's name is. Don't fall behind. Don't fall behind. Come on. You can do it.
Come on. Why is he so slow? Keep going. Oops. We got everybody. We got I think we got everyone. Everybody safe. We got to stay close.
We got that. That's fine. I think better not swoop down. Do not swoop down. Do not swoop down. Hold on. Where's my friend? Where are they? Where are they? Where are they? Come here. You. Leave. Leave us alone. Leave us alone. Leave us alone.
Leave us alone. Leave us alone. Leave us alone. We're just trying to survive like you. Leave us alone. Leave us alone.
Did he get somebody? Oh, shit. I think we're OK. Do not swoop. No, no, that's it. Oh, no. We're good. We're good. We got it. We got it. We got it. I can't go too far because if I go too far, then they get struck by lightning. We're all right.
Stick together. You need to look where you're going. I know where I'm going. I can't go too far, though. All right. I'm going too far. Get away from us.
Get out. Get out. Is everybody OK? I think so. Almost there. I can't. Not yet. I got to wait. I'm too far ahead. I need food. Does anybody have any? You do. OK, now I'm going to cross it. Thank God. All right. Please don't have that. Keep going. If this thing goes down too, I'm going to be so pissed.
Wait, just in case it doesn't need food. My God, there's no vegetation here. I mean, this is water, but no, no. Here you go. I'm all right. This doesn't count as food, right? Are we good? Oh, thank God. OK, so for those of you who don't know what just happened, sometimes that is not enough to stop the cylinder and it keeps going. But if you go too far, everybody gets struck by lightning and dies. Let's eat. Oh, thank goodness. Everybody fill up. Anyone want that?
We're all still so hungry. Somebody said, dude, that was not chill. No, it wasn't. It was not chill. That doesn't work. It was the worst enemy in the game. What did I just do? Oh, shit. I didn't want to do that. I ate the wrong thing. No. Burn him. Burn him alive. Burn him. Somebody burn him. Somebody burn this guy. Burn him. Somebody help me. Excuse me. Help. Somebody burn him. Can I help? Somebody help me. Help me. Somebody help. Fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. I'm going to take more than that. I'm going to take more than that to kill Wee Womp. Wait, let's go. Somebody help me. Somebody help me. Somebody. What was I doing? I was going to fucking do something. I mean, I couldn't do anything, but you know. All right. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's temple over her. Somebody help me. Somebody help me. They're still hungry. There's no chill. There's no time for me to chill. I want to eat stuff.
Some flying enemies just ruin everything. All right. Now we're full. Let's keep going. I don't care what this does. Other side probably. Oh, my God. Don't even. This is dangerous now. Every day. There we go.
This place made the trebum uncomfortable. It felt like a place of desperation where terrible, bitter things had happened a long, long time ago.
I'm good on food. Let's get topped off. What is that? Did you just die? You all right? I can't move. No, it doesn't mean all of you don't come over here and investigate it. Get out of the way. It's OK. All right.
Um, I got an idea. You didn't drop anything. Oh, new power. I wonder. All right. I've got legs on here. I've got two flames. Anybody kind of miss it. You got water. I'm going to give it to to you over here. I feel like we could see what it is better off you getting it. All right.
The new guy. Oh, yeah, that's right. I forgot you existed. All right. Moment of truth. Sucker feet allows the trebum to attach to surface and remain glued. How do I do that side? Oh, that's very helpful. Actually, I feel like I want everybody to have that. That probably prevents being picked up by the birds. I'm going to give that to everybody that doesn't. Yeah, let's give it to everybody. Everybody has 10 of these has it. All right. Spread it around. I don't want you have the stomp feet.
So I don't want you to do it, but I want it's going to replace the jumping. You still have jumped, though. So I think that's fine. I'm going to give it to. Yeah, let's give it to Gunnu. I didn't mean to do that. I pressed. I pressed the wrong fucking button.
And this is what happens when you didn't play with the controller last time you played keyboard and mouse. You plug the controller in. So B is like the back button. Why am I playing with the controller? Because it feels way better than WASD.
That's great. I guess I could just three minutes. That's not that big of a deal. Yeah, it's not too bad. I think it's when we open the door here. It is. OK, so let's just bring this. Use the stomp.
OK, this place made the trebum uncomfortable. It felt like a place of desperation where terrible, bitter things had happened a long, long time ago.
I don't want anyone to die. See if I can do it right here.
It just picked somebody up. OK, it was about to like eat that person. All right. So you are going to do it. So just do it. So that's Sticky Feet for you. He's so much cooler now. I love him even more. All right.
Sticky Feet for you. Sticky. Yes, you guys. So then we have swimmer, three suckers, a jumper and a stomper. I think that's good. There we go. This is the dream blunt rotation. No, it's not. It's not. I wonder if I can break this. Yes, it is.
All right. You're telling me that these five trebums are your dream blunt rotation. The one, two, three, four. Wait, these six trebums. Yes. OK, we need to. Of course it is. You don't want anybody else throughout all of history, all any character, any celebrity, any history. Like, I don't know. Abraham Lincoln is not in there. It's these five. It's five trebums and Abraham Lincoln. Dream blunt rotation.
All right. What am I supposed to be doing? No. Interesting. What is that? What it do? Secret. What's that? Another power. I don't know who should eat this. Probably this one, right? This guy. This one doesn't have a body. Save scum. I can't. All right. New guy. Go ahead.
The mixer mutation allows the trebum to combine specific ingredients to create offensive projectiles. Finally, that can be launched at enemies.
There was something strange about this new body that Trebum thought. It was powerful, but also a little frightening. Finally, a gun. They now had the ability to mix ingredients in order to create projectiles with which they could attack other creatures.
This new power might be necessary for their survival. Thank God. OK, so this is now a gun to make sure to use it carefully so they would never become as cruel as the servants of the cylinder. This is hurt.
What the fuck? It's a grenade. What? Oh, you all right? You get out of the way. I don't know what I did. I don't know what I did. The chain reaction reaction just went off. I'm sorry. I'm testing. I'm testing it. Just mix everything. Wait, is this the slot that I think this cannot be used?
I can't. All right. My play the resident before remake 100% guaranteed 100% guaranteed. Yes. Can I break this? Maybe I can break it with my new grenade. Ready? Get out of the way. Get out of the way. I don't want to hurt anybody.
Can I not shadow this? Well, let's get the info. Yes, the map. Thank God. So this little guy has to survive under any means necessary. Without this, we have no offense. So I have to control this character. Very cool. I think that's it.
Hold on now. Who doesn't have a body? You don't. Fire doesn't. You don't have a body. You do now. Nice. All right. This guy is now total offense. These are the floating things, right? I feel like I should hang on to maybe one or two of these. I wish I could store them somewhere. I wish I had a chest.
All right. In the meantime, I have projectiles on you. Let's get I'm ready. I'm ready to shoot a grenade if I need to. Who is the chest? Yeah, but I mean, not like two extra three extra slots. I mean, you know what I mean? You can put them on your stored. You're a teammate turning it into water.
Wait, hold on. Why are they over here? Why are they split up like this? Kind of weird. There's a hole back in the wall. Was there? Gunu is looking svelte today. What is svelte? Oh, what's up? How you doing? Um, ah, shoot him. Shoot him. What? Why did I was shooting? Why? I'm excuse me. I'm literally holding right trigger and he sprayed water at him. Yeah, fuck you. Was that a new thing? Somebody eat me?
You eat it. You eat this. I don't know what it does, but you eat it. Oh, oh, oh, that's not good. Um, sorry. Okay, well, we're gonna just keep moving. I need some ingredients. We're okay. Where am I going from here? Straight up. There's a hole on the left. I'm going to go the hole like over here. I don't want to miss all these things. There's a lot of good stuff in here. Okay, this little village area. All right, make some grenades. I gotta have a good stockpile of these. That's a different grenade. That's different. I have no idea what that does, but all I care about
is does it hurt. I don't care about anything else. Shit, this is a poison hole. They still, a bunch of them still have the poison resist. Does that matter? What if one of them goes down and doesn't have poison resist? Is it okay? Find out. Okay. Yep. Nice. Where am I going? Down here. Because this one is free. You okay? I have it. I can get him. Hold on. What's up here? Dude, what is this? These are like super rocks. I'm keeping him. Gino!
Sick! How many do I have? Seven? I wonder if I can break these. No, they made it a point that these were here. Why were these incubating? Maybe for ammo. That's a good idea. Find out. So if I give you these, is that doing anything? Cluster bomb? Big cluster bomb. I don't think I can mix it with anything yet. It should be seven. I don't, that's poison stuff. Well then that's glow in the dark. Wait, maybe somebody should be glow in the dark. I'm going to take it for now. Why is there weird music playing right now? Look at all this.
Okay. So this is a, I got to, all right, we got to do some inventory management here. So you would, okay. No, not, no, no. You, no, no, no. I don't want you to get rid of those. No. Gas bomb? I mean, actually kind of cool. Nevermind. Do that. You're missing the one that went blind. I did? Wait, where? One, two, three, four, five. No, I got seven. Okay. Take the rest of these. Nice. All right. So this is a full heal. This is full food and full water. Gino, you hold on to that stuff.
I think, I think it's got web feed already. Cool. Wow. All right. Cool. All right. I'm happy with this group. I do want to be on one of the offense. Yep. Okay. Is somebody on offense? Get out of here. He doesn't, but it still looks cool. They all look cool in their own way. Oh, fuck. Oops. Positivity, Andy. Um, are you, hold on a minute. Who doesn't look cool in their own cool way in our group? Everybody looks super cool. Yeah. Where are you? You're about to get fucking poisoned.
Grenade shot into your face. All right. There's another thing over here. I can go to investigate that. I like the blue one. I'm going to pick my favorite right now. Uh, goo, goo. One's goo. One's my favorite. Gunu is still, you know, pretty cool, but I'm going to have to go with, uh, gonna have to go with you with that one. I got my bomb selected. Continue the investigation. How you guys doing? Are you doing good? How's your, uh, is your week gone? I cannot wait to kill this thing. I can't wait. You're the, I'm going to make sure you die. Fuck you. Oh yeah. Oh,
yeah. Somebody else has to do it now. Wait, what? I can't shoot that high. Oh shit. Everybody. We're good. We're okay. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I used every single poison bomb. Fuck shit. What is this? This is the fire. There's so many decisions. I, it's too, it's, it's too cool. Oh, egg. What was that? Can I hatch it from here? Yup. We're going to have eight. All right. Come on. Hatch. Oh no. Look at how cool this one is. This one has like cool hair.
Um, that's not good. All right. I need to mark where that is. I think you're just going to die. Sacrifice Gunu? No, nobody can be sacrificed. They're all. Yeah. I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do about this. I'm not sacrificing anybody. Who has the stakes? You do. I'm not sacrificing anybody. I'm sorry. There's a storage place. Okay. I got to remember where this is. It's right on the kind of corner here and I got to go over here. I'll be back. I can store somebody. I'll be back. All right. Who's getting uploaded? Yeah. But do I want us to, I mean, I don't know who to upload. I guess you could get uploaded.
You're the swimmer. All right. Woogwool. You're getting uploaded. Oh no. Sad. We can bring them back. Woogwool has been uploaded. How much does it cost to bring somebody back? Too expensive. Too expensive. All right. Let's go get the other one. Somebody have a bomb? Don't even think about it. Just move. Just move. Just move. Not worth it. All right. Cool hair friend. Aha. Groppo. All right. Groppo. Come with us. What the fuck? Okay. I think there's one more thing over here. What is it? You see this? Where is this going?
Oh yeah. For that very, all right. It's time to move. You guys ready to go? Let's eat first. I already have. Who is it? You got the steaks. Yeah. Eat all these steaks. You have the steak. We're good on food. Oh yeah. You got all the steaks. All right. Continue. I'm thinking of going. I'm going to just bang around here. Yeah. All right. Let's go. Change his name. I don't think I can. Groppo? Groppo? All right. Fill up that meter. I'm very interested. All right. We got to, this is a pretty good party. We have offense now.
And go. This is not too far. Wait. You're a new animal that I saw early and I don't know what to do with. Nevermind. Okay. Everybody safe? Yes. What was that? Did you see that? It's like a giant tail. That was actually kind of terrifying. All right. We got something over here. Finally. It's warm. Yeah. Thank God. Another friend. Possible. God. Come on.
What do you want? What was that for? That's it. What is that thing? No, we're good. Oh no. It's taking powers away. It's taking our powers away. It's taking powers away. What the fuck is this? Wait. No. What? What's going on?
Hold on. Go back. What am I doing? I'm trying to get away from the light. It just follows you around. Can we stand? I don't. I think this is scripted because there's nowhere to go. I think we're supposed to have this happen for like now. I can't outrun it. Look, I literally can't outrun it. What would I need to do? I don't understand. What does it want me to do? Sticky feet? Close the thing. Something nearby may help. Yeah. I mean, that's
pretty vague, though. I don't know if it wants me to like attack somebody or get one of these monsters to move around or just run in the temple or the strangely named evil giant was back. What was he hunting for? What monstrosities would he summon this time?
Fuck you, buddy.
All right, get in.
It's definitely something in here. Maybe not.
I have discovered the recipe to permanently imbue my body with the power of this mutation and protect it from the evil light of our enemies. You must learn to use this formula as I did long before you, or you will never gain enough strength to continue our people's struggle.
The trebum thanked the apparition, never knowing that it couldn't hear them.
Mutation tree? Is this just, hold on, filtered? Is this like a permanent upgrade system? Okay, so track this. So this is a toxic filter. Oh, you just got Elden Ring.
Okay, so is another egg here? No, it's just this. It's just this person's ass. I don't think I'm going to have enough for anything. I think I'm going to do health. I feel like I want it. How can we referring to everything as a person? I don't know. This is a little like a little person. I don't know. A little alien, a little creature. I don't know. It's very. Yeah, it's not. It's definitely an alien.
Not a person. It's a a creature of some sort of of of intelligence. I don't know. There are people. Yeah, whatever. What do you guys think health health is for? What do I just hold? What do you guys think?
As the trebum prepared to leave the cave, the apparition spoke one final time. If you are lost and wandering helplessly across the land, look to the sky and seek a celestial serpent. Yeah, we did that already. And they were mean many tales which hang down from the clouds as the serpents contemplate the matters of the heavens.
These serpents guard the way to the wisest of our kind who can guide you to salvation. That's it. We came across one that was made of asking the apparition to join them. But before they could, it had faded away like the voice in their minds. It was only a memory.
I'm doing health. OK, so that's very interesting is now I have this mutation tree. Three of those plus one egg means I can just use it. But OK, is there anything I can do to prevent being leaping legs and feet? There's a bunch of other stuff I haven't found yet. There's a lot of stuff I haven't found. All right, so the play is I got to get out of here and I have to go very fast just away from this area. Yeah, it should be saved in here. I mean, all my friends ready to move. We've got to go very fast.
Right when we get out, we're going to move you on silently and make dad noises. I'm curious. I'm probably are you talking about like the ingredients required for the impervious mutation were all here. But stealing an onkyford egg was easier said than done. Oh, my God. And cracking one open was even harder.
OK, we get get out of the way of this is going to take away our powers in order in order to permanently protect a mutation from the light radiated by the servants of the cylinder, you must find underground shrines where recording will teach you the ingredients required to permanently protect that mutation.
Ah, so we have to so we have to find shrines. This area is enclosed by poisonous gas that can't be filtered by the filter trunk mutation over the nearby servant will not allow you to keep your mutations. Find the ingredients requested in the filter trunk node in the mutation tree and activate them there.
OK, I can. So I think it's I think if I lose mutation, yeah, I think it's just going to happen. Right. Yeah, it's OK. It's all right with this happened before. Yeah, there's no there's no hiding. Really? We just have to kind of do it again.
How do I get you to get off of there?
All right. Now, get up. You know, just take it. Just get one. I got one. I got one. All right. Let's get out of here. Let's get out of here. What do I do? I have to break it. There's one. Now I see three of these things.
The trebum had stolen the ocky fat egg, but cracking its thick shell was proving difficult. I already got it. Perhaps the answer lay in the mighty jaws of the fearsome Omnigrom.
I just broke it, man. What are you going about? OK, so now I can mix items. So now they permanently have a filter trunk mutate permanently. Hey, that work for as it for everybody. That's like a thicker one, too.
Look at that. Is it for everybody? It is for everybody. Oh, that's so awesome. Thank God. Oh, my God. That's so much better. Perfect. Oh, yeah.
So then what is this? What is this saying? Is there a person here? What the hell? Puzzle. Any more of those? Yep. This is a Lego Star Wars ass puzzle.
Kind of is. Where's that thing that I'm moving? Is it down here somewhere? Looks like it's down here somewhere. Can I just jump out of here? What's the significance of doing this?
It's just making stairs. All I'm going to scream for. I don't know. A lot longer than than right now. I don't know. Yeah, I don't. What's the significance of this? This is not like a big deal. I have a jumper. I can jump out of this if I wanted to.
You don't have a jumper. Gunnu has the jumper legs. Where is Gunnu? Oh, that's right. Everything. I was like, where is it? Right. It's all the powers got removed. OK. I was like, what happened?
So this is not right. Where's my where's my where's my big friend? All right. So I'm just going to move. I want to make sure I didn't miss anything. Didn't. All right. Are we good? I got to go straight and go. I do need water, but it's OK.
The song reminds me of something that would be played in Rugrats. This is a Rugrats theme that like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You've never seen the Rugrats? It's an old cartoon. Back to the cold. Oh, OK. Hold on. All right. There's nothing here, technically. So just explore a little bit. Don't get killed.
Save it water
Which rug rat would you be? I think I'd be yeah, I'd be grandpa. Oh mornin' Sprout. How you doing mornin' Sprout?
Yeah, no, you're stew. No, I am NOT stew pickles. Oh, we need
Jackets, there are no jacket plants anywhere over here. There we go right here. I'm not stew pickles
No, I'm not I refuse to listen to that. Aha. It is warm again
Average stew reaction. Wait, so hold on the way. Wait, wait, it's stew
It's still the one that talks like this. Who's the mother talks like this? Who's the mother?
Who's the Brian Griffin was it? What's his name? Is that stew? Okay, the second one. What was stews?
What was stews brother's name both the glasses drew? Okay. Yeah. All right for a second
I thought you talked about I was drew pickles and I was like, bro
I am NOT drew pickles now. I could I could see stew. I could see that makes sense to me
All right, we're going for that hole over there remember why are you making chocolate pudding?
That I actually probably would do that. That actually sounds like pretty pretty good idea right now. Actually, this is moving kind of fast
Oh, this one's moving much faster than the other one did. I made mac and cheese before at like 2 a.m
Yeah, but that was a completely different scenario. Maybe one day I'll explain that scenario. Yeah. All right
So yeah, this is this is this is a topic for another day
Okay, so I'll bring it I'll bring the topic up so I
I was I may have been I may have had some marijuana
This is a couple weeks ago and I posed the question to Holly and this was an incredibly deep conversation
I asked we're talking about like food and I sit there going who made the first sauce who made the first
Sauce because at some point, you know food was for energy food was to survive
Who the fuck decided to make the first sauce and I wrote down on whiteboard a
Shitload of information because it was the questions were okay. If you're a hunter-gatherer, you don't you can't make a sauce
When did pickiness when did preference become a thing was it a surplus of food who made the first sauce?
Because why would you make a sauce? Why would you make a sauce? There's no reason for it. Oh today
We've got onions and meat. I'm gonna make our shoe. No, no, no, no you eat because food was scarce
At what who why would you make a sauce? Like whoa, you know, why would you make a sauce?
Until preference and became a thing, right? Possibly the oldest recorded European sauce is
Garum the fish sauce used by the ancient Romans
Okay
so but but why if
Food was as from caveman times to hunter-gatherers food was you eat food eat the food
There's no like, oh, I'm give me like four or five hours to make up like a fucking sauce
No, you eat that fucking meat that we just got this four onions out back yet
When did it was its taste? So when did taste become a thing that you could care about?
Romans it was rich people
Yeah, once a bund yeah abundance hold on a second this is important
Okay, so what I'm about to present to you I'm gonna present to you something is the whiteboard
That I wrote on with the help from Holly
And we're gonna go over it was just very quickly
Very quickly. I had to write this down because I don't in my brain
I'm like this is kind of wild to think about like what who why would you make a sauce?
Like why who would do that?
Abundance joy has a happiness. Hold on. I'll just show it for a minute. Okay
Where'd it go? Hold on
Okay, what the hell? Why can I not save this as an image? I'm gonna save it as
There it is. What the fuck? It's a J. It's a JPEG on my desktop. Why is it not showing up on my desktop now?
I don't understand computers. It doesn't make any sense save to desktop this image and it's not there
I just literally just did it three times. Okay, there it is. All right, let's go over this really really quick
All right, so let's go over this really really fast
I don't want to spend too much time on this who made the first sauce was a caveman
No, survival only no time for sauce food was hard to get hunter-gatherers people. Why make sauce people were nomadic
What what was the first sauce?
When was the concept of taste when something isn't just feel what I need this to wait
What does it say? I need this to taste the way that I want no such thing as picky
When did humans allow picky preferences smells no matter what there's no reason to make a sauce
There is no reason that just kind of isn't the answer was watch ratatouille
The concept of being picky luxury joy smells
Hawley told me to watch ratatouille and I told her I don't think I can handle ratatouille right now
While this whole conversation was happening. I was going from the whiteboard
I was making mac and cheese on the stove at two o'clock in the morning. I remember just going slop like
Slop she's like you should just watch ratatouille. It's kind of that concept that same concept
I don't think I can handle ratatouille right now
Like I was when I quit I was like too high for ratatouille and I'm like, what does that even mean?
But I don't know how to think about it. Like who why would you make who made the first sauce?
I'm saying it like that like what how does Mike rat rat rat ratatouille ratatouille ratatouille ratatouille
Well, isn't it about a rat ratatouille? It's not ratatouille. Okay, I gotta go this way. I'm done
That oh by the way
Holly in the middle of that took over and was writing for me because I went mid-sentence and said hey, can you do this instead?
She's like, ah sure. I guess
That's why like the handwriting changes like halfway through
Yeah, but everything that we can talk about the concept of abundance or being picky or preference or taste or smells or just happy
It tastes good that concept almost like why who decided to like make the first one
Did you just have too much fucking corn and you just squished it is an interesting concept. It's not hard
No, it isn't hard. But what somebody had to make that call?
Am I going the right way? Yeah, wait sure, dude. Yeah, somebody had to make that call somebody had to be like
You know what? We have a lot of onions. I'm gonna just ruin them all. What are you talking about? Don't do that
You're gonna mash up like fit ten of them. Yeah, we need those to eat. Yeah, but I want to make a sauce
No, you're talking about what is that? What are you talking about? You're not don't touch those fucking onions
That's for the next six months. I missed a fucking thing
Sorry. Oh, oh, oh, oh
What happened? It was agriculture. Okay, so something went wrong there. I probably need heat resistance
From what? Hold on. I went I kind of was walking back. I gotta go back this way
The first sauce had to have been mayonnaise. Think about it. I don't think that's accurate
Wait, wait, wait, somebody has an answer on lack of refrigeration in the early days of cooking meat poultry fish seafood didn't last long
Sauces and gravies were used to make the flavor of tainted foods
So 200 ad the Romans used sauces to disguise the taste of the food
possibly to
Conceal doubtful freshness Wow
Really? I'm gonna say that can't be right. Is that wrong? What do you mean wrong? That's not real
Is that why it's been getting deleted by the mods?
Is that made up lore? All right, let me go back to paying attention to the game for a minute
Who made the first sauce because every time you think about like who it was this you have to kind of go like well
Why?
You hunted you ate you planted this there's no reason to make one
This there was this hole. It was me was there already back here
I got really confused after showing my fucking like whiteboard rant
I don't think I have someone had heard the trebam's prayers after all
If there was a flying serpent in this place, there might also be a temple and an elder to guide them
First sauce was invented by Ronald McDonald. It was ketchup. This is a new creature
You know what I'll tell you though, let's be fucking careful write shit down
Make sure you're documenting things. We need to make sure we document history because in a thousand years
Somebody might fucking think that do you understand this that like there's a there might be a point eventually a
Thousand two thousand years in the future where somebody's just like oh who made the first sauce? Oh, well, of course
It was Ronald McDonald. This was God back in the
Two thousand AD we got to be careful with how we documenting history and make sure we keep it accurate
We got to make sure it's correct. The water can get really really muddy if we're not careful
This is a different kind of fish. I try it. I'm gonna try it
Electro skin allows a treban to create electrical discharges which can revive an ally. Um
I'm
Everybody's freezing get out of the water get out of the water. Can I go in here? I'm electrified
No, I'm not. Okay
Get out of the water get out of the water
Get out of the water get out of the fucking water
Wait, are they cold? I don't understand what's going on right now. Didn't I get one of the things?
There wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm so confused
I ate one of the I ate one of the fuzzy things and it went on everybody, right?
That was like five minutes ago. I don't you lost it when you got electro. What? Hold on a second. Wait a minute
Wait a minute. Wait a minute
They didn't all have it
No, this is not right. Is it the cold water or whatever it is? I fucking don't know
All right. Well, I gotta get out of here. I only need one to have it. Yeah, it's the water. Okay, it's the water
I was gonna say like doesn't make any sense
I don't think it's the water. Let's get out of here. You replace the one that actually had it
Well, let me get the fuck out of here shit. Sorry, buddy. We gotta go. Oh my god, dude
Like the hit the collision detection on some of these fucking rocks. I swear to God
This is like the hardest thing I've had to do so far in the whole game. Okay, so somebody eat a fuzzy then
What the fuck happened here? Everyone's still dying from the cold. Alright, so that's I guess that's my fault for I thought that if
Somebody ate one that it just went on everybody and it did go on everybody
But it comes off of everybody if the one person doesn't have it on I
Okay, that what the fuck I how much but I what I thought they all had it
So this guy didn't have it so they all don't have it fucking horse shit
No, it's fine. I I
Keeping this one. This guy has a electric skin. Well, we need to heal now only six. Oh
It would have said somebody died didn't say anybody died. Oh my goodness
Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Stop
What what just what he rolled backwards? Why did he rolled backwards?
I am fucking confused as you could ever be right now. He's dead
Come on dude, get out of the way you piece of shit. Oh
No, it's over. It's it actually is we're actually just fucked
I don't even know who I who even died reload from or 20 minutes ago. No, but the game is designed
You're not everybody doesn't get to stay
Now what the fuck is happening? He spent 20 minutes talking about the sauce. It's fine. What are you?
Why are you looking at this is that true true? I mean I did. All right. I did spend 20 minutes talking about sauce
Oh, yeah, this is right here. We're good. Perhaps someone had heard the trebam's prayers after all
All right
So we're with a flying serpent in this place
There might also be a temple and an elder to guide them. Okay, so same deal
I wish I could just take one person having to take everybody is just so dangerous. Everybody's can die
I want to get that powered though. So I'm just going in and going out and make it very easy very quick
I'm gonna make it simple. I'm not gonna put it on this one. I won't okay and that up this shit out of here
No, don't know. I don't wanna
Sorry, I don't like the buttons. I should just change them. They're just so fucked up
Please raise your hand in the chat if B is always cancel or always like get back always no matter what
Or run it's sprint or back
To me B is never use item. It's back out of menu this to you
Okay, let's go. Yeah, it says it. It doesn't matter if it says it
It's built baked into 30 years of me playing video games. Just change to the menu
Okay, let's get up. I can't save that one. They would don't do that shit again
All right. Everything is back crisis averted. We talked about the sauce pretty cool. Let's go
We have to find a way over here
I do want somebody to eat this though, but not right now in fact get rid of this
I don't want this fucking thing. I want to control who's the one that has
No, it's you're the best one to be in control right now. All right, let's go. All right, don't I can get I'm gonna get electrocuted
I'm gonna go underneath
Get those stakes stay away from that. All right, can I go under here?
Yep, is the temples under here? I got screwed last time
Everybody in let's go. Huh? All right. Cool. We made it. So what was in here that I wanted to look at?
How do you still have all of your powers?
Holy shit, this dude is still stacked. All right, there's a balloon. Let me check the other areas though
Okay, uh
You I'll give this to a few people not everybody needs it
Okay, you go, do you know
No, do you know is the healer it'll be
Laundry detergent here, you know what you take one of these two use this
Okay, really pretty in here. Save the game. I didn't right when I walked in. Hmm. I need a square
Square right here. We should be a square. I
Think you do square. I love the graphics. Yeah, it's a very pretty game
I'm at sick you watching it at 6,000 bitrate, even if you're at source
It probably does not do justice with how
Very pretty the game is the game also has I think a different direct X mode. I'm on the default mode
Figured for streaming and probably easier, but yeah, it's pretty cool. Looks really nice
Okay. Now we're gonna get around how I get over there. Can I go up further? I guess maybe I can make that
Let's find out this looks like it keeps going
Button zero, but I don't see anything over here
This doesn't count as something does it oh wait, is it a button this is what you mean
Hey friends, that wasn't what I needed to put in there. Was it I didn't just shoot that thing that has to go in there
Right friends. That's how it just happened. Right now. I doubt that this is another one over here
Come on. No way. All right. No way. Isn't it? That's just where the cube fits. No, I don't think so
I would be shocked if that's really what it was
Well, what the hell it this way whoo, I didn't even see this. I'm sorry, buddy. I can't help you. I
Really want to I really do that's a sad. Sorry, buddy. It's cold
I know I wish I could give him a blanket or something or like a nice a couple of snakes or something
What is this? Oh
This time the discovery of a new statue and the knowledge it granted was not a surprise
But a welcome sign that there was someone waiting for the Drebham
As soon as they completed the trials, of course as was only appropriate
Oh, I bet that unlocks. Um permanent upgrade
Cool. All right. I need cube
Where's cube? Where's voo?
Come on, voo. Yeah, you need to get up here. Yeah fair complete the shrine
Yeah fair. Come on up here. I need you right now
Yeah fair come on up here. I need you right now you doofus
Come on
You what you are the best? Look it you always are on time. You always come immediately
This is look it i'll make sure you're staying alive
You're always right behind me. God. Damn it. Get up here. Where are you?
Just chilling down here in the water in the freezing cold water, by the way
Oh my god, he's gonna die
He's gonna drown
Dude if you drown i'm gonna be very very upset
Well
I yeah, I guess I have to eat a cube but isn't the cube a body the cube is a body not a head, right?
I don't know how it works essentially just bring a fruit up here
Yeah, I would try to avoid having to do that
There's one over here though. Float is also body. Yeah, somebody else has to eat it up here then
One of you has to eat it. Come on. Let's go. All right, let's try this one
All right, who made it very very nice
You get it because you're
I ate it jump is b
interact is x
Eat is a I want interact to be x roll is x interact is y eat is b
I don't like it. Yeah, I don't really like any of these
I'll keep it stuff to get used to it. So what's down here?
Very nice
This area is kind of big i've been playing with a different layout
Yeah, I was playing with pc controls and then
I decided to use controller today game like this
I probably should have used controller to begin with pretty much any third person game. I prefer on um controller
Walking around with the analog to me is better than walking around with w
And the mouse and like ad. Ooh, what's up?
New mutation. No, wait, somebody can turn this into like a bomb or something, right?
What are your thoughts on your dog? Is he a good boy? Do you let him cook? What I
Yeah, I guess I think so. Where's my um, where's my offense?
This is I don't remember. This is electricity skin. You do it. You missed all of them now that that's the fish
What is this one? Oh, it's sticky sticky. Okay, jesus
This looks intense deep in their memory that trebum carried a fragment of knowledge about this temple
It had once been a place of learning where wise trebum came to study the crystals
Which which but the memory was incomplete what happened?
What happened to us?
All right. Uh, this is gonna be fun
Wish me luck
nice
Not gonna dump me
Bod watchers skip an hour. I don't think so
Oh, I wanted to do it so bad. Fuck. It's all right. I just should have been patient. That's my own fault
I should have been patient and I wasn't
It's not gonna take an hour
It's not vod watchers. I don't have to skip an hour. I'm good
I got it. I got it. I got it
Fuck no. Okay, relax. I'm
He's doing it because of the highlight channel. No, I'm not
I just have no I just I hate being patient
It's so funny. It really is. I hate it so much
In the so I want to get through this fast. I don't want to sit here for this one second
This is an eternity to me
That right there that was my it may as well have been 100 years
But if I had just done it normally the first time it would have taken five times less time
Like if I have to stand still in a game or in real life, it may as well be 500 years sitting still
That's genuine. I really I mean that
See this is what I know a lot of people like oh man, you should play
You know like getting over it or no. No, I did that
And I got maybe I think halfway up the level
And I thought I was at the end
And when I looked over the chat and they said omega l you're only 40% of the way through the game
I never turned it on ever again. This is a while. I'm never doing this again
Jesus. Um, okay
What's the plan here?
uh
Um, I think I have to drop
down like
Oh my goodness. That's not what I had to do at all, but I
Somehow made it work
We're always comparing the eternal cylinder puzzle to getting over it
No, i'm just saying I don't have very much patience for I don't have patience
That sounds like a you problem
Yeah, it is
We're all very different
Sorry
I thought I didn't make it
That's some interesting shit right there. Whatever. This is who should eat this
You I don't know gunu. I feel like gunu does not have anything. I'm giving it to guno. Nice part two
There is a part two, but hold on
Okay, this is gonna be interesting. I need I can't uh that I cannot save if they look at all these crunchies here
It's probably bad idea
But i'm i'm about to reset the whole i'm about to reset the whole thing. I'm about to reset the whole thing
No, i'm not i'm good
Can I breathe in?
While being stuck I can
All right, it's gonna face the right way
You can still suck while stuck. Yep
Someone tells me you shouldn't be snorting the random shit on the walls, but whatever
I have this game, but you got way further than I did
I think it's just a test of almost would but we're good. You're gonna get lead poisoning
This is definitely worth it even though it's taken a while
Sometimes being impatient pays off like right there
Uh, there was like a 10 to 20 chance that I actually make that
But I did so we're good
Okay, so that's it
I just gotta go backwards now
It was worth it. I got what three gems
Stink bugs are cute
Oh, I have a bug story
Good thing I fell
All right. So here's the bug story
I got it. I'm good. I'm good
You know what I want
I'm actually probably going to get
Some of you guys are gonna pog some people are gonna be like, whoa. Oh, I know what that is. That's cool, man. That's cool
I'm going to
If I can i'm going to get
Maybe like three four
And like a little enclosure
What's he gonna say
blue death fainting beetles
Have you ever seen one? I'm at the very bottom. Oh, I looked over a chat. That's fucking whatever
I want to get a little enclosure and have some little blue death fainting beetles
If you don't know what they are go look them up
They look like the elden ring beetles. They're this bright blue
There are crunchies in the corner
People shit or do you mean that?
Wait, what do you mean in here?
I missed crunchies
On the bottom you mean
other corner
Holy shit, this is a lot too
That's like a two that's one full crystal writer
Actually worth it. All right. Let's actually get to the top of this damn thing
Yeah, they're apparently one of the easiest things in the in the world to take care of
And they live do you want to how long blue death fainting beetles last?
nice super villain pet choice
Ow
My my beetles
I let them like walk over my fingers dash the beetles
You know about the blue death fainting beetle
That's like that. That's a monologue moment where like the villain is explaining something
Uh, hold on
Yeah, so blue death fainting beetles can live I think up to eight to ten years
And they're just happy little creatures
they eat
Carrots like grapes and stuff. They're just like little and they're they're not little they're pretty large
They're they're apparently incredibly simple to take care of
You just need an enclosure. You just need some like sand and shit
I would want to make it nice and fun and make sure that's in the room
What are you gonna name them? I don't know. I need to get them first
They're apparently pretty social too
That's why they say getting a few they can they get along with some other uh other insects, too
I don't think I would do multiple. They just were kind of cute looking
They do look
Just like the elden ring dung beetle though. They really do
I'm just a friend. Can we get a beetle cam?
That might be kind of fun. Actually
All right, I could blow up. I'm gonna blow this so I gotta be careful
Is anything on the is anything on the ground? Yep. Wait
I don't care
I'm getting it a little beetle cam
Okay, that's it
live beetle reaction
Uh recently I kind of like you can call me bug andy if you want
I don't know. It's kind of like a new
I don't want to say hobby but
There's a lot of really really crazy beetles and insects and stuff like scarabs
Have you seen some of the scarabs that look like fucking jewels?
They're remarkable
They actually are
Some of them are they like
Made out of they look like they have chrome
skin
They look like emeralds and stuff. It's really really interesting
Bro has been watching the mummy
No, I haven't
Yeah, so I mean, uh, I watched the mummy recently and now I want bugs
Oh, we found somebody the elder was sad to hear the story of the trebum and their failed journey behind the cylinder
You have been through so much
I wish I did not have to place even greater burdens upon you
But we trebum are not meant to live in this cold and cruel place
You must continue your voyage
You must cross the waters and reach the ancient lands of the desert
There lies the only hope for our people
You see we trebum once had the means to sing to the stars and build vessels that allowed us to dance in the heavens
Seek one of these floating palaces. They may be the key to finding salvation in these times of despair
Oh shit. Yeah, we we gotta we gotta recap somebody here. May we meet again someday?
Somebody said hey, well wait bro, you went beyond the cylinder
We did we did and it was it was mind-blowing
We went to this weird astral heaven world and i'm not making this up. It actually happened. I go check it out
Go check it out
All right, so I gotta find this floating thing in the sky. That's just super food. It's just one. Oh, there were two
Cool. All right. So let me get out of here now
I got 16 rocks here. Yeah, I don't know something about bugs
You want let's get real. Let's get real. Why not?
Come on
I feel like we kind of treat a lot of insects like they're just random pieces of shit and they're just like meaningless
Like oh bug who cares crush it who gives a shit, right? There are a lot of really remarkable
kind of animals in like the insect world that I think we kind of just
Blossom over
Now don't get me wrong. There are a lot of bugs that are just pieces of absolute dog shit
Like there are some bugs that are just like oh fuck you. You know what I mean? Like ticks
Murder hornets like horribly aggressive wasps and yellow jacket. No, no, no, no. I'm not talking about that
Don't hurt us, please
What the that scared the shit out of me?
Is he all right? I thought he was gone. All right, I need to heal
That actually
Oh, no, I activated it. Oh, okay. We gotta go
I don't know what direction I gotta go from here. All right writer
Feel like a cockroach. Yeah
Well, the thing is I see cockroaches. I mean it like flies they are they have a very important part of our ecosystem
like
Decomposing decomposition, right?
Let me get safe here for a second
Oh boy
No
Whee wham
Who was whee wham? Oh, no, he's so sad
Whee wham, where are you going? Don't go that way. Where are you going? Why are you going over there?
Why is he going over there? What's his problem?
What's his problem?
Do not do that
What are we?
What is his problem?
Jesus
uh
Okay, we need to figure out what just happened. It's okay. I have a lot we can we can upgrade reload
No was we was we won the trumpet guy the dead one was the mixer
Oh, we can't yeah, we can't live without we won
In fact, I need to control we won because we won the one that actually can hurt people. All right now
Before I blow this turn around save scum
Yeah, that's fine. All right. Are we good? Let's eat. Yeah, it's okay to save scum
Wait, we didn't know what this does eat it minerals can process minerals
Interesting so
The crystals I get it. All right. Well, let's get to a safe spot here
Wait to go yet. So all those red and blue crystals
Can be processed by that now. Okay, who's in here vegan vegan
Okay, even if I find an egg, I can't hatch it right now. Anyways, leave them. I have to there's an egg here
I i'm gonna
can I
Can I bring the egg? I don't think I can bring it i'll try because there's a
Upgrade temple over there. I'm gonna there's no way. I'm sorry, bro. You're you're dead
I can light it on fire with my trunk. The problem is we can't put him in the party because I only have six or seven slots
So we can't he cannot join. Okay, much cleaner than last time
All right. The next thing we've got here
Is this coming up next? We got the temple here I can upgrade
Which is perfect
Plenty of food. I got my party. I got the mineral processor
Which there's gonna be a ton of crystals in this cave
What's the cube do?
Cube can fit into cube slots
only
Somebody that has the cube mutation could fit into a cube slot
Which allows to open some doors
All right. I got a lot of money. It's time to make some real decisions
We're gonna have probably 20 crystals
Excuse me lots of crystals in here. In fact, let's start this what I wonder what does it turn it into I wonder
What do you do? Okay a bunch of crystals pick up everything
Let's make food
I wonder it takes a while
It's not as fast as um, some of the other shit
What does it do?
Oh, it gives you crystal dust
That's pretty good
How much does it give I didn't see?
Holy shit, that gives a lot
That's a
That's a lot
Wait, should I eat this? I'm gonna eat it. Okay
I feel like it's gonna be a lot the attractive crystal. I think it's gonna be a lot
You should break it first. Maybe I don't think I should I wonder because it's it counts as a crystal right now
All right. We definitely need leadership. I know i'm doing that for a fact
Maybe the stamina wheel give orange meteors to smelt
Did I miss any um crunchies water storage? I feel like the water is not a problem. All right, let's do leadership
Try to do it again. We're gonna have nine give the orange meteorite. Oh, you're right
Yes, you are. Absolutely right. I've been holding on to these things for a long time
Oh, yep, this guy look at how long it's taking too. All right, we're doing it again
Now I can actually get more people and i'm probably gonna get more from this shit
Can you summarize this game in 15 words or less? Yeah, sure
Little creatures on a planet being destroyed by a huge rolling pin
Must find a way
To activate their memories to figure out why this is happening
And what the heck's going on behind that cylinder? There you go
All right. I want to I i'm we're gonna wait this out because I want to I bet you I get a lot from this
Bro, who made the first sauce? This is gonna take a while health stem. How much is stamina wheel?
All right. I'm doing stamina wheel and
Look at how many more crystals are up here. Look at all of them. I need them all. Holy shit
There's so many crystals. How do I I need to get all of these every single one?
I'm not leaving till I have them all who has the inflating head you do come here. Give me that way
I can't get up there. Can we shoot them down with water? Come on. I need more of those crystals. Yes float up there
Look at all these come over here get another smelter. I could double it up. You're gonna be a smelter
How much was that? All right smelter. Come here. Where did it go right? This is really fun. It is pretty fun
I very much enjoy it. Okay, how much is this gonna go for nine? Well, that was worth it. Holy shit. Okay
Stamina wheel, I don't know if I'll be able to get anything else. There's more crystals over on the corner
I think there are more come on dislodge these that should be enough to do one more thing with the
Meteorite, uh, there's water in the middle. What should I do? Can you stomp them down? Uh,
Maybe maybe I can like blow them out of the wall
All right, you can't really aim
So i'm just gonna I think these ones are way too lodged in I'd have to jump all the way up
Maybe here we go. All right, i'll give these to the other one. I missed a raid shit. I missed ramala
That's from a long time ago. Oh shit. I'm sorry a lot of people you're still here. Thanks for this. Uh, thanks
I just said thanks for the stream. Well, thanks for the stream. Well, you were streaming. Thanks for that stream
Thanks for the stream. Okay you process these
Process now, let's go talk. I'm sorry. I'm so I am so anal about this
I just want every single one of them projection shared a new recipe with the trebum
Which could protect them from the cruel light of their enemies. Thank god
Oh, that's not what it is. It's a small flame
I thought I had one of these like jawbreakers. I guess not didn't I have one of those somebody does
I think one of the other people has one what I said anal. I've never heard that phrase before
Have you never heard that phrase you want about have you never heard that before? All right, I
Okay, uh, i'm waiting for this to be completely processed. We're at seven now. Perfect
Digested food is seven. I think it's probably a good idea. But what hold on is anything else?
I didn't I don't think I upgraded something once that's stamina. I just did it. Is water am I neglecting water?
Is it bad? Maybe I shouldn't
I feel like I have to do it at least once it's level one. Um
People are gonna freak out. Hey, but it's all right. I got two crystal processors now. We're gonna be fine
I haven't upgraded water once it's probably gonna be a problem soon. All right
I am ready
I do need three crystals to make this thing and I think there's a jawbreaker in my storage
So I think we're good. Everyone's healthy. Everyone's happy got plenty of food. Let's go the apparitions spoke to the trebum
Do not leave this cave without extracting its riches
It said the walls hide valuable minerals necessary for our recipes and other important matters
Now while the common trebum has no way of processing them our crafty ancestors created a mutation
Capable of performing such a task the apparition faded and the trebum was sad
It was almost like losing one of their elders. Oh, that's not okay. He's sad sad
Need three stones. They're in every single one of those caves. All right, where to no more points of interest
This is gonna be weird though. I'm gonna go to the other side of this. Yeah. All right, it's over there
all right, I gotta get the right spot and
This one's quick. Uh-oh. Uh-oh
Uh-oh had to cut a few of these corners here. I think i'm good. Okay, everybody through
We did it. Aha
There's no light coming off of it. No point of interest. We might be able to find a few friends
Interesting. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. I haven't really figured out the deal with these are is there a deal or is it just what was this?
Curiously a creature. It did not resemble the servants of the cylinder, but somehow it seemed oddly
Menacing and what was that thing pulsating beneath it? The heart is a friend
Something in the trebam's ancient memories made them
apprehensive
Okay, it is pumping the heart was beating slowly
And the creature was asleep
Could it be that the cold was keeping the creature frozen in this strange slumber? Oh, they're all scared
What if I do this? Hi
Are you okay?
Wait, uh, I don't know. Do I have to fill it up? Maybe I have to fill it maybe to fill it up
The warmer it got the more the monstrous creature seemed to start losing control of its body
That must be its weakness
All right warmth
Warm
Oh shit
Is everybody all right? Who needs help? I think I need to heal all right back it up back it up back it up
Where's my fire? That's the right idea. All right fire
Come here fire breathe the fire. Ow
Someone's there
Got it. You get the fuck away from me. That's a heart now. I can eat that
Get out of here
Get out of here get out of here
Stop get out of here
I don't know what the hell that is, but we're gonna I gotta move though because this fucking annoying thing is just
Leave me alone. Nobody has a horn
Okay, let me just double check make sure that's not over here
What about this shit?
This looks fucking cool
More fire. I'm gonna oh
All right. All right. All right. Hold on. I feel like there's something with these
Right like there's got to be something I can do with this
Stomp them
Yeah, that worked. But did they drop anything?
They don't oh I hear one
Okay, shit's dangerous. Who should eat this?
I don't know what this is gonna do. Maybe you in the middle here
Um go one give it to gunu gunu. I if this is a body. I don't I guess we do have an extra smelter
Yeah, there's still there's an extra smelter. All right, let's try it. I don't want to craft these but you know, that's
As long as I have one somebody else has to hold on to these
You know you hold on to that energy bomb. Okay gunu. I want to truth regenerating body
Somebody should take this too. We need a horn very important. Okay
Very very cool. So that was the big thing here. Anything else? Let me get some food. Gunu sucks
What no, he doesn't. All right, it's straight and then right
I got time you get somebody
Oh, I spent too much time
Trying to blow the horn against that. They're all dead. Everybody's dead. We're all fucking dead, man
We're dead
Everybody's gonna die
It's all right, we're good this time don't even blow the horn
I think I got it
Come on
Ayayay
We made it dangerous
Beware the voice of their memories cried out the mathematician has been summoned
This place was no longer safe. What do we do?
He's pulling it out with his hands
Is that what does that do? What does that mean for us?
Did you get it? You got it? Okay, it's gonna be lightning shit
Is it lightning or is it not?
It's just going
uh
Okay
Why am I standing around because a lot sometimes it's purple and
You have to stay near it, but I guess that's not the case right now
No
There's an egg. What the fuck?
That's so far away
Come on, come on, come on
Everybody make it
I think we're good
We got it
Everybody's safe. I think has the trebum continued their voyage to the desert
They felt a strange sense of being observed
But this was not the cruel gaze of the cylinder and its servants
No
It was almost as if someone was trying to help them laying out a path for them to find
The voice and their memories encouraged them to go forward
All right. There's a couple points of interest here
Which we will very much investigate when I go get another tea go pee and come back. I'll be right back
See you in a minute those of you that are wondering I uh, I did see the emu
Pretty cool. I know that people in the discord were very very adamant that I see this is bird
What do you mean? What? Okay, so
Let me explain for those of you that don't have any idea you just oh, yeah
I saw the emu like what is he all right?
I don't know if somebody in the discord uploaded a picture of like an emu in my room
I'm saying get an emu pet instead of the beetles
I was like, all right. It's like we need him to see this. Okay, I saw it
Got a lemon ginger tea this time. I'm getting a little wacky
Yeah, I'm
Lemon ginger. Whoo. Slow down
No, this is cool. Okay. I gotta let it sit for a minute though
the problem I have with tea hot tea in particular is I will brew it and
Let it just sit on a counter or something and the bags just stay in there for 10 minutes
And it just ruins everything because then you get that weird that's that bad taste. It's got a certain name
What's it called? This actually like it's a bad thing, right something leeches into the tea. What's it called tannins?
Yep. Yeah tannins leech in there and it's just yeah, it's not good tannins aren't bad, but they're bitter
Yeah, well not necessarily bad but bad in the sense of you don't want to taste it
All right, I'll give it hey, please remind me because I will forget
In two minutes take the tea bags out of the drink. I know I can rely on you guys. I know I can let's go
Still got everybody. I was just laughing about this though. I was making the tea that I think this game
You're supposed to lose creatures and get new ones
But I just keep safe scumming with the same ones that we have because I don't want to lose anybody
Every time we've come across a new couple of creatures in a new zone like this
I think it's designed for it to be oh you lost one back there. Don't worry
There's another one here, but we just keep passing everybody by we have I feel so bad
We have our team and I I don't want to lose anybody. Well, we're going in here a lot of crunchies
Uh jumping legs for this for sure who could use it and a cube. I have a cube don't I yes
I do have a cube what I do. I don't know but get out of the water. What did that do?
Oh, it turns this on. This is an egg right there as well. I'll come back down and get it
I just want to get out of the oh shit. Cool
You do this you take it because that's the way to get out. Oh my fucking god. They're gonna die
Come on, man. I can't eat it from the menu. Why not? Thank god. I had that
Jesus
Okay, that was almost a disaster. I there's a lot down. I wish I could just leave people up here
Tannins the tannins the tannins. Okay, I got it. Thank you. It's really been two minutes time flies
Okay, I gotta do the dunk pole dunk pole dunk pole dunk pole because I don't I don't feel like stirring it. Okay
Transferring transfer success. No mess. All right, let's go. There's a bunch of shit down here
I'm getting it all gotta go quick crystals
Yep. Hey, come on. Come on. Come on the egg. I hate jumping on the rocks in this game. Hurry up. Hurry up
Guelphal. All right guelphal. Let's go. We gotta get up now. I can't get all this shit. Ah
Greedy greedy greedy greedy bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad
Everybody's alive. Just barely I need health so bad. It's so dangerous down there
Every single one of them just follows you in and they just die in the water
Okay, everyone just regen out of combat. Pretty good. I don't even get to see the new guy. Where's the new guy?
Is this is you watch out? All right, anything else I can do here. I did the hole there is this
Let's go do this. I think this is probably a yeah, let's do that
How many crystals do I have because I can get another party member. I can do it. I need six mushrooms
Oh, I have six mushrooms. I don't think I hold on. I don't have six mushrooms. Guto. All right
I need six mushrooms keep an eye out. Oh, wait, there's an upload tank over here. Come on mushrooms fire upload tank
I could pull somebody out who's in here. Rutemu and Wugwul are in here. I could also revive
Gowu, I do have room for one more. Rutemu, Wugwul. I mean, this is free. I think we're at our capacity
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. Can we get can we have nine? What about Gowu?
Gowu is still there in spirit. Oh, here we go. I need one more mushroom
The one you get don't nobody eat one. I need one more mushroom and I can go get the other. There we go
Okay, rescue. Let's go. Is it eight or nine if it's eight? I'll just put somebody back
Okay, so it is. Which one of you is the least interesting? Fire stomp eyes
regeneration horn cube jump sticky feet fuzzy airhead
uh webbed feet and
Anti-poison. What's your deal? What's your deal? You got nothing. I like the way you look though. That's the new guy
Yeah, should we should we get Guto? Yeah, I want Guto. All right, I'm gonna put Wugwul back
Get rid of the crest 3d white one
Uh, you were you were really close. That was really funny, but you meant to say
aqua fresh
Shower clean. That's what it is. It's not crest. It's aqua fresh. The joke was there
A ruin some part of an old temple. No, not quite. Wait, what happened to the wait a minute? What's going on?
Oh, well, this is the group we have had the trebum walked into a trap was their journey
over
crystals though the scorn like
This actually is a scorn like I agree. I I see it. I understand that what was this place?
Were the trebum dead?
If so, this was a very odd after life
Evie the elder
What is going on?
Uh, I perhaps this strange elder could tell them what was going on
But before they could ask the elder spoke
The celestial trephala have seen your journey
And I have been told of your deeds. Why was it? Why are they trying to kill us between our people?
trebum and trephala
We once lived in harmony, but the invasion of our world has split us apart
If you do not know their song
The trephala will not recognize you as a friend. So I am here to help you
As much as I can
The floating palaces you seek lie ahead as you were told
But they will be of no use to you unless you reclaim all the powers
Of our people which the cylinder has stolen
There is only one way to do so
By entering the portal that links our world to the dreams of the eternal cylinder
The greatest of the cylinder's servants the mathematician is the gatekeeper
He absorbs that which is of value to the cylinder and his master has become intrigued by the crystals
That the trephala wear as crowns
Find these crystals
And acquire the mutation which will allow you to appear as one of them
Thus you will trick the mathematician into granting you passage
And now I must return you to the land
There is little time
The trephala are being hunted and only few are left
May you succeed in your quest?
for all our sakes
Hold on
So, okay
We need to get the crystal we're beginning to understand that there was more to this journey than mere survival
So far they had acted only for themselves
But now they had been entrusted with a task that would affect many others
And although that was frightening
The knowledge that they were acting for the greater good
Gave them strength
So we're going to look like a crystal that's on top of one of those
serpent heads
I wonder how we do that
It will unfold
In front of us. I imagine the next several hours
All right, let's go store one of these
Well, that was a cool scene. I mean
Wugwul you just got maybe it shouldn't be wugwul
swimming
Hmm. I'm wearing ice world. I don't think we need wugwul. Sorry. Well, you got a little bit of exercise
You're gonna go back in. Okay. Now let's go get a new character
Send his ass back to hell. That's not he's in the cloud
Who's this?
Vivino this person's this is different, but we know is kind of way cooler
This is not guto, but look at but look at villino
Okay. All right. Well, I have the mushroom so i'm doing it. Just gotta remember where that was
Over here, isn't it? Oops. Sorry
Where is it?
Yeah, where's guto?
Where is that?
You got replaced
Oh fuck
You come near me. I'm gonna blow you to hell. I'm just saying i'm just saying i'm just saying
Did he get replaced? I think he got replaced
Yeah, I think he's replaced shit, um the cutscene replaced him, but that's annoying
You go get that ice monster
I want to upgrade before I do that. There are I did get some crystals
Uh-huh. There's gonna be a shitload of crystals probably in here. I'd eat three of these
Make sure I do not get rid of three of these mushrooms are fine because we're not uh guto's not available anymore
So that's all good five
Uh-huh. Ooh
It's a big one. Very nice. Yep. Can these be broken? Well, I currently have a full party
So i'm not too concerned about it. Okay. Let me get these to the
Processor throw the tea that tea's fine. Nice and hot. Yeah, I took the tea bags out
You guys are like 40 minutes late. I already did it
All right. I need whatever that is like some kind of like a tongue or something. What is that?
Derma the tannins derma the tannins. Oh shit the tannins you're right. It's ruined. What do I do?
Stamina wheel I have 12. I don't think you can go wrong with the stamina wheel for health. Here we go
I wonder if i'll have enough to do health in the meantime
The projection shared a recipe with the treba one which could protect them from the light of the cylinder's servants permanent inflatable body
Uh, I gotta start paying attention to this six mushrooms and three
luffies
two fish two crystals
Okay
All right. All right. I don't think I can do that for a while. So let's track a different one
How about inflatable?
Probably this one
Yeah
Yeah, uh, yep. This was made by the rock of ages dev also xeno clash
How much crystals do I have two three?
All right. I got more stamina. I'm happy with it. Gunu is still alive. Yeah, wait, let me get some water. Okay
I think i'm good to go. I've got the crystals. I need water. Cool. Let's get out of here
You should name one of the beetles Gunu. That might be cute
You're dead the hell was that I need these I need three of these right? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Somebody else pick it up. Please you it's three fluffies the suck sound off
No, I can't hear the sucking. I need six mushrooms and I can do this one
I don't think I want to fuck around with that. I'm probably gonna need that material to
Have a permanent upgrade. It's terrifying to me and I don't really want to fight it
Did I didn't even care who's got the horn who has the horn who's got the horn I need to use it right now
Nobody has the horn Gunu has the horn. He just doesn't even care. Why am I hurt getting hurt? Don't you get idiot?
It's actually really annoying to pick people with the controller not who I wanted. Oh shit. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out dangerous
It's dangerous over here. It's dangerous. Nice. All right, pick it up. Let's get the fuck out of here
All right, somebody needs to be just the person that holds everything
I think it's gonna have to be we won't just don't eat that I need health. I could have gone worse
See any mushrooms yell fucking ice monster died from poop rocks. It works. It works use the eye
Ah now you're thinking
Yes, eat one
Six, right? I'm going to trip the wall. So where am I going from here? I actually don't know
um
Is the wall right here?
Aha, yes, okay. Let's do it. Okay. So this is
Uh the bird skin permanent mutation are these permanent because that's a pretty big deal if it's permanent
What else can I do? This one's third eye? This is probably the closest one
I have I wonder if I can look it up with the third eye. Maybe these organs anywhere. I'll keep it on
All right. Well, that's good. Now. They just automatically enable it when they need it. It's a big deal. Okay, so
We are good to continue moving. I'm going to select somebody else. You got like a missile. Okay, you got bombs
Did you activate it? Um, I don't think I could there's one last thing over here
Actually, I probably should stay with um, we bomb just in case one of these things pop up
Why why are we getting hurt? I'm hurt. I shouldn't be hurt
Everybody hurts
Okay. Yeah, I get some more of those. I feel like I might need wait these counters minerals
No, all right. We got am I pulling somebody out of here? I gotta go get yeah, we need eight. Let's close it up
Get the new guy
Unfortunately, the new guy was randomly rolled to a different new guy and I don't have the materials
All right, we got a whole crew now and that one can swim get the big power from the river
Somebody should be big. That's true
Oh, fuck. Yeah, I get all these crystals
Crystals need food. Oh, you got all those steaks eat them. You're just supposed to be crystal person. I need to knock
Nobody else touch these please who can jump somebody is you have jumping come here
I don't think I can get the ones up there, but that's fine
It's funny
What is that?
This is like a pumpkin
Shit, who's gonna eat the pumpkin? Wait new guy this is for you
Oh, you're not even the new guy. Where's the new guy? Oh, you're over there. Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm losing track
Here you take this
Long-distance water squirting. Oh my goodness. That's far
I mean, that's not I mean, that's kind of I guess it's kind of cool
I guess
Well, it was definitely wait. It might be an egg
What is all this stuff?
I feel like I need to I should probably save some of these
Okay, just save the rest of these because this looks like an interesting flower
Interesting. Oh wait. I need this to to get uh, whatever their name was now. We got a full squad
We got a full squad. It's probably randomized again. We got a full squad. We got eight. Look at it. It's a full squad
Best way to go. Actually, I don't know. It's kind of far. Let me get a better view
We don't even need to be running around with a full squad either
It's just I don't know
I feel like they have they're friends and I wouldn't want two or three of them to be alone. Not cool
I want to get these stakes. All right, got plenty of stakes. So the best way to go is
Okay, straight here bang a left outside of the force field. Yeah, that's the right way to go. Let's move
Are they fighting? All right. So then from here not go this way. It's wait, there might be something there
What a cave?
So many things to look at. I don't know if I go in there. I'm gonna all right. We're just gonna go
Eat some food
full water
Nope, it's crystals down there and shit. Sorry. They're
Completionist Andy. I know
Is anybody else snug as a bug right now?
It's it's okay. I got I got time
snug as a bug
Made it that way. I have to make my way to one of those serpents, right?
Temple right here should touch the cylinder. I don't do that. It might kill me. I want
Come here
Get the fuck away from me touch it. No, what if it hurts if it hurts? That's bad. You won't know unless you try crystals
Wait glow in the dark. Oh, that's right. You were glow in the dark. You are multi-talented
Cool, all right. Uh, we're gonna use the piss man. Where's piss man? There you are
This man's gonna knock down all these stones. Is this even piss man? No, this is piss man
Everybody get out of the way got it carbonate mutation incoming. I need more distance. Here we go. This should do it really
Are you serious dude? How bad do you piss on the toilet seat?
Um one time recently I was so tired. I don't know what happened
But i'm usually pretty good about that. I'm usually very good about that
But I was I must have been really tired like just out of a dead sleep
And I think dude, I just pissed I think all over this toilet
Because holly said she went into the room into the bathroom
And walked out. She was like nope
I definitely just pissed all over it too. It was so bad
What that was the raid? Hey, hey
What's going on? Welcome
Thanks for the uh, thanks for the raid. It was honey goblin
Thanks honey goblin welcome everybody. Hope you had a good stream
Pretty cool. We were talking about something very very normal
Not anything strange promise
Yeah, we don't even need to honestly we don't even need to repeat what we were just talking about. This is unnecessary
Right. There's no reason to even bring it up ever again
For any certain thing
How come this doesn't work? It needs to be like a concentrated pee stream
Everybody do it
Oh, no, no
Whoops, it's all right. Who cares? Yeah. Thanks for the raid. Welcome. This is the eternal cylinder
Give you a quick recap of what's going on
the
Point of the game is these little creatures they have different mutations you can do
And there's a gigantic rolling pin. That's uh crushing earth imagining. We're on some kind of earth
Let me do this permanent mutation real quick. Where is it? This one? Okay, so this is I can make a
mixer body
All right, so I can turn it on
Cool. I well this I don't want to turn it on to everybody though. Stop bumping into each other
All right
What do you got for us?
The projection from wherever you're controlling shared its wisdom with the trebum
And showed them how to protect it from the evil light of their enemies
Good thing I held on to that because this is greatly improves trebum regenerative capabilities
Missing one object some kind of brain. I think that's a brain
I'll track it for now
All right
Decision time
Where's the jumper? I'm just getting these for the uh for the material collector
That's a lot. I know i'm gonna spend like a half an hour doing this. It's all right
Just like just like I don't know wash a few dishes or something
You know that gross ass cup that's sitting on your fucking desk right now the disgusting one that you peer in
And this it's just wow, that's fucking gross. Go just go right now while i'm doing this and just go clean that cup
I know you all have one everybody has one everybody has one gross ass cup that's sitting there
That's been there for probably a week and it's fucking filthy. Just do it now
Do it now while you have a minute
I don't use a cup
You're drinking water with your hands you're drinking. What are you are you scooping it up?
Out of a well with your hands. What are you talking about? All right, that's enough crystals
No, it's not it's never enough crystals
Are you serious?
You don't think i'm gonna get all those up there?
I have to
If I don't get those crystals, I will disintegrate. I have to get them. Fuck you
Not you know, not you but in general. All right, that's good enough. That's good. That's good enough. That's good enough
That's good enough. All right, let's give them to the uh, crusher. It's almost full stacks of crystals health. Um
Yeah, stamina is fine
I need three didn't I already do that upgrade. Did I not do that upgrade? I thought I did it already
I got time. All right, uh maximum food. I'm gonna do this next in about 10 seconds
I washed a cup good do leadership. I did leadership twice already
I feel like it's gonna be way too expensive at this point 13. Yeah, no, we'll do that later. I got eight wait
Spray it wait. I need three you said there we go refill the water and let's get out of here
Hey, dude, can you please just say yippee? Yeah
Is that what you wanted? I am satisfied with this. I do want to eat. Let's give oh you oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, Guelvo's got all the steaks Guelvo. Come here, please. I'm gonna cook us up
Why don't you fry us up some of those steaks new york city new york city
All right, there's a hole over there though. Let's go in the hole never mind go
Treasures lie in here for our treble and fret. Oh, okay worth it
And there's a shitload of crystals down here. You know what i'm doing down here. All right, who can somebody take this?
I can take a bowl full
Health, that's a big deal. All right. I need uh, where's my
Uh refinery I need you down here. They're trying to do it through the wall
They're trying they're helping. All right. You actually have to come down here though guys. Come on
Actually come down there's so many big thick crystals down here you where it you
Don't side eye me like that you get down here get over here get these
These things have a lot in them seven. There's like 15 down here
Maybe if you all got out of the way i'd be able to do this faster
Did I get them all camera? Are you not helping?
Okay
Cool. I'm rooting for the other team
You suck
Enjoy your ban
and and
See you
Hey, see you later
Hey, huh? Enjoy the ban
Yeah. Hi. Hey, don't let the door hit you
and
See you
Uh everybody in everybody back in everybody get back in back in back in everybody back back in back in back in don't die, please
I just spent like 10 minutes mining this fucking goddamn hole if one of you gets sucked up by the alien thing
I'm gonna be so upset
Bye
Oh, you probably giggle when godzilla cry no way what?
If you had to pick one of these creatures to be which one would you be and why?
Uh, hmm, probably this one. I can just put rocks in my mouth and turn it into money in my bank account
that seems
Like a great thing to do
All right. I got that. We just gotta go this way now and yes over here. All right, let's move
I think we got everything we needed. Are we on food? I think we're fine. I just gotta let's get it in the right spot
Hey, look at that. Perfect. This is a straight shot here
and
Go take a break
That was pretty uneventful feel good about that
You actually made it
Good for you. Wow
Actually did it. Yes
These were the crystals that the trowala used as crowds
The trebum wondered what secret powers they hid really but there was little time to think about such things as soon
The mathematician would make his terrible entrance
Where drop it on you? I might reload the game would transform the skin into crystal. It had to be nearby
Let me just reset it
You like oreos? I do
What's your dream trebum blunt rotation? We already talked about this. You want me to do it fine this one
For sure. You're telling me you want to talk to some sick fucking fat rips this one could do
Okay, this one how many can be there four?
Including me this one like I think this is that's just cool
You bet your ass that he's gonna walk on the wall and just stick there and everyone's gonna go. Whoa. Yo, what the fuck?
I mean one of the cubes because I mean your your cube
That's just kind of don't you feel like this is a I feel like this would be like a great
I don't know like just sitting there on the couch like just fuzzy cube. You're like, oh, that's kind of cool
It's a huge shadow right now
That was so ominous what about me
I guess you could hit the blunt man
I don't know and the last one because I feel like play some pretty sick music when we all wanted it, right?
Everyone's sitting around rotation happens and then
Why is the audio still messed up? Okay, I need to get one of these crystals has to be we need to get this
Right skin. Okay one of these no, I think it is one of these
Do we need to break it or do something to it? Maybe I can process it. Maybe hold on
Can you do anything with that? I can't suck it in. Maybe I can burn it. It's on fire
No, it's not. I don't know. I actually might need to reset the whole game
The audio is still kind of messed up for me. Is that just a me problem?
Or are you can you like hear a lot of this stuff or is it half the audio gone? It's normal
Why does it sound so weird for me? I think I figured it out. Okay. Yeah, i'm good. Um
Well, I have to process the crystal somehow
There it was
The unifier ow now the trebum would have to be brave and clever
What find a way of defeating this dreadful creature? Okay, so they could claim the ingredient they needed to transform
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Um, what what do I do? Oh that would have been sick
Was a terrible enemy
But in its rage it had revealed its weakness. I need to eat
The crystal fragments it was igniting against it
Who's got the health the trebum would have to be nimble and make good use of their trunks
But this was a challenge they were fit for
Thank god. Okay, everyone move move move out move out move out vote far away far away
far away
Shoot it
Shoot it shoot him
I I don't understand how to shoot him. I don't I don't get it
All right, there's no more crystals do they have to be glowing so to hurt or no
Yeah, I wish there was an aim so bad in this game like shoot it out. I can't I I cannot shoot this
I don't understand what's going on
um
Okay
And he's dead
Okay, that was I swear to god. That was the most awkward thing i've ever done in my whole life
It's very awkward
I see I can't like get close and it was the unifier. This is
Weird man, i'm saying clever and it's not a way of defeating this dreadful creature
So they could claim the ingredient they needed to transform. There's no aim
You just have to shoot it in a direction. Hope it doesn't hit the fucking ground
No, everybody run
Do it. Fuck you. Come on
Just don't be bad. I don't do the
the
You don't understand. It's weird. I have to get right in front of them. It slows the character down and then I have to like
I mean, it's very weird. It's very strange
Do you understand at the high ground? I might just shoot it over his head
I liked my I liked my way better
I need more crystals. He needs to break them
Crystals swish cheese objects that had fallen from the unifier's head must be the ingredients the tribum needed for the
Vegetation who wants to eat the weird cheese who wants it you nice blue cheese. It's kind of shiny. All right
Who else are you?
Oh
Right now that the tribum had transformed themselves. They would need to find the largest crystal formation in the area
That would be their best chance at tricking the mathematician into absorbing them. I mean, it's that right there
Did it work?
Oh, no
It's just you
I hope you're gonna be all right. Oh god. I actually puke warning everyone needs to be aware of this
This world gets a little weird in mirrors. It actually is kind of you can do something to see where
The tribum had returned to the strange place in the giant's dreams
There were more mysteries to uncover more memories to take back. The voice seemed even stronger now. Yes
Yes, I can almost
speak
Let me tell you your story
Okay, the song of your people is rich and beautiful
What did I just do what did I just do and so you learn to avoid repeating your mistakes
Slowly you discovered the secrets of your world remains alive
You built great cities full of wonders and then you sang to the stars to find others like you
To share in the joys of existence when you sang to the stars
There were many who heard you
And raised their voices in song
Most are gone now save for the trawana your oldest friends
When we heard your song
It was already too late for us
The cylinder was upon us and there was nothing we could do
Well
But we are not that different from you
We are also not strong
Or fast and we don't have sharp teeth. We are stubborn
The cylinder creates its minions from pieces of what it absorbs
So we found a way to help you
All of us together
These fragments of my people the memories of your ancestors
And what's left of all those others who shared our fate
A conspiracy of ghosts to sabotage the cylinder and give you a chance
There is more to be found
Memories to be reclaimed and what you need in order to
to a fading
Being absorbed
These moments of strength are rare
The voice could not continue
Once more it was only a memory
Group piss break
Okay
wacky
Interesting a little scary
Where we know that ocean we're at the end of the world
What was this artificial island on the horizon?
Could it be what the trebum had been told to search for?
Could their adventure be nearing an end? We're good on food knowledge. They had gained
All they now needed to do was to catch a specific kind of fish
Which would allow them to acquire the wonderful ability to swim without ever getting tired
Eat it
Water's cold
Hell, so what does what's the web feed for then?
Only one person has to have it. So let's go
Maybe the web maybe it stacks
Probably does stack
All right, let's go
Are they gonna get hurt from this? Whatever
The web heat makes you jump higher out of the water. This is really pretty
Looks really nice
They're all too cold
Um, i'm gonna save this
It's a little dinosaur. It does look like a little dinosaur
Cube's not looking great
Come on. Come on cube
All right, i'm gonna eat this
Please get out of the water. Please get out of the water
Uh cube ain't gonna make it the cube is dead officially as of right now
Yeah, we're gonna lose a couple people here
Eat another fish
Cube's dead
Oh just barely. All right, get out of here
Get up on the island. We're gonna eat we're gonna regen
Please tell me everyone's out
One two, three, four
Five six seven eight. Okay, we're good
All right, everybody relax
regen
I actually need some of these
For a um mutation get out of there
Okay, i'm gonna not do that shit
All right, so I need one inflatable body thing
I think somebody actually has one
You know what?
Eat the swim thing too
Eat the fish
You're going way too far away from me
Oh you piece of shit. It's okay. Everyone's still fine
Come on. We're good. Somebody else should take this but I don't know maybe not
I think we're fine
You idiot. I just want to heal
last bit here
What's that? Whatever. All right
tutmit the elder
Oh, this is alive
Is this its face or is this its back?
Oh, we're good
The tremor were happy to find a friend resting on the island. However, they quickly realized he was not well
The elder told him
What a pleasant surprise to find a group of such brave little adventurers
Oh, i'm glad to see your faces before my end. I don't know. I'm sorry to tell you
That this structure will not ascend on its own
I was hoping someone might bring the lenses that power this palace before the cylinder came
But as I can see
You do not know of what I speak
And this is simply not to be
But fear not
There are other palaces in the waters of this great desert
And resting in the golden dunes of these marvelous plains you will find the hidden treasures that can
Awaken and lift to their majestic heights the trebum palaces that were once the pride of our people
Swim over to the other side and seek the trawler that guards my brother's temple
He will explain what you must do. I wish you luck
Know that my spirit will dance and sing when you succeed
Where I have failed do we get that big?
It's kind of remarkable
We get to be that we get to be huge like this eventually
Well, don't worry
We'll do it. I'll make sure we we
I'm the leader. So i'll make sure that I tell all these other chumps what we need to do
Come on chumps
Follow me
Oh any three of them?
Wait, this is interesting stuff
But you still have the like the weird moon cheese
I thought that was water
Would you eat a cheese that looked like that? I don't think I would
Maybe I actually know maybe I would it's kind of good
Okay
Whoa, I guess we have to get on this
and
What's the plan here? We have to like blow it
Be careful
Well, whatever
uh
Just go just go just go just go just go just go just go
Wait, there's like a what is that?
I don't know. It's something weird. What is this thing? It's hot. We're kind of burning up here. It's gonna be kind of sad
you lucky
lucky bastard
Yeah
They drop something during the brightest hours of the day. The desert is too hot for trebum unless they stay in the shade or get
Into the water
It will slowly lose health
Okay
So in the shade or water it's probably this
The trebum sense that something was roaming the desert
Something that did not belong there
No doubt the eternal cylinder had once again sent forth its cruel servants
Perhaps it had taken notice of the trebum and was seeking to stop them from accomplishing their goals
Get in the shade
Everybody get in the shade
fuck, um
Eat this bug
I don't know. It does just eat it. I can run faster. That's not what i'm really looking for man. Oh shit
Spray water. Let me get in the temple first
Wuto
Shit all over this
I don't know what this does. Oh my god. It's a super crystal
Shit, I need to no we're all gonna die. I where where where where where
This is too stressful. Where's this temple get in it? Go go go go
Everyone's fine. I wonder if I should break this
Okay, I broke it
I don't know what this does but
I don't know who to give this to. I like the legs. Maybe the cube. Yeah, the cube has been kind of lackluster
Wait, we got to figure out who we haven't been using and who's gonna get who's who gets the axe here
I feel like I haven't used you in a while floating head. I haven't used cube in a while
We even really need the light with this two cube, but this is a jumping cube. I wonder if that matters
All right. Come here regular cube
Yep, it's you. I think that's the best way to do it. See what happens
Camouflage. Well, that doesn't really help
It's cool, but it doesn't really help. They would all need to have it
unless I can get the permanent upgrade lots of crystals in here, but
I really want to spend the time to get them all
Probably okay. There's some goofy shit in here. I don't know what this does. That's fine. Don't
Okay, that's the spike one
this one is
the shiny and this is
Um, should I break it? I'm gonna break this sure. Why not? Oh, it's the plated body doesn't resist heat food
I don't think I need water. Maybe it's health again health stamina wheel. I could do stamina wheel leader also possible
You're in the desert. You should do water. I didn't even think about that. That's probably a problem
Yeah, i'll do that. Uh water's the next one, right? No, that's smart smart. I think i'll save the rest
It's time for some inventory management. Okay, eat all the bullshit that I don't care about this
I need some of these. I can't get rid of any of this. It's all just crap rid of all of it
Junk as well. Gunu has the heat management one. Oh, he does
Okay, I needed three of these though for the mutation. Hold on. Didn't I need to hold on to them though?
Where is it? I need one. Okay
Um
Gunu i'm gonna give it to you and then it should give it to everybody technically, right?
It's not giving it to everybody because he already had it. That's just for the fire trunk
Well, it did say heat resistant. That's what the tooltip said a gas-filled membrane that absorbs heat
Wait a minute that absorbs heat. It doesn't mean you absorb heat if you eat it. Well, great
Where the hell is it?
Dude, what is this a menu scroll? There we go. That's because the mouse is on the screen. God damn it
I don't know. I don't think it does. I don't think we found that thing yet that I need
But i'm gonna uh, i'm gonna get out of here
The projection shared a recipe with the trebum one which could protect them from the light of the cylinder's servants crystal
Camouflage. I think I just have to find it but I need to I feel like i'm gonna be in trouble
Okay. Well
Everybody's got full health
Regen'd cleaned up a couple inventories. Although what about the spike head somebody do that starting to get a there's a lot of different mutations
And I don't really know what one I should have on
I'm just gonna hold on to stuff because that's all I do in games like this
I just hold it forever and I never use it. Look at all these. All right, can't get them all
You know what? Fuck it. It is fuck it friday after all my tea is almost gone. I've been sipping it this whole time
It's not yeah, i'm good still hot. I think it is actually working on no, it's not
All right, we're from here these crystals. I'm gonna suck them all up. Come on. Fuck away from me
Get out of here. What was that? All right, there's like there's a there's a uh, uh, uh, I was like we gotta go
I gotta get out of here that whatever that was it's here. But hold on. There's a few more of these I can steal. Come on
Just one more. All right, I got six one more. Okay, go
um
Uh, there's one over there. It's gonna be making a lot of money doing that shit. Okay, I guess I gotta go
Oh
Dumb i'm losing time
Uh
Holy shit that that just saved everything that just saved the whole entire thing
Too bad. I want them. Okay
It didn't come up. It didn't come up. We're good. Okay, we're good. We're good. We're good
We're good. Just get out of the get out of this domain. Okay get in a good position
Now what's like sniffing?
Oh, it's that thing. Okay, get in the right spot and it's over there
okay, and
Here we go. Not yet. Let me get right to the edge and
Actually fucking clean
All right
Still hot though. Ah water just chill in here for a little bit
shit
Everybody all right. Don't just eat stuff in your inventory, please that stuff is very needed at stuff requests and you ate it
But idiot still no map. I think i'm all right. Oh, there we go
Oh, I feel like I can do something with these can I spray these with water or something?
Maybe I can blow them up. Doesn't it look like I can do something with these
Please leave me alone
Did not deter it at all
Didn't deter it at all
And now we're down in the fucking depths
Oh, actually, this is kind of good. Maybe I can just suck it up
Um, nope, why are you looking at me the treban was surprised to see this temple was protected by some sort of
Breath of the wild kind of is like that, isn't it? Was this some futile attempt to keep out the servants of the cylinder?
Or was there another reason?
now lost to history
Everybody get out of the way. That's a fucking bomb
I thought it was water shit
Okay
No, ah
interesting
We're very hungry
Is this going to squish them? How is it? How are you doing it the wrong? I don't can we just roll it
Is this thing even important camo? I think the camo is only for enemies
There we go
This looks to be something new do not do that. Actually, you don't make some bombs or something else
Here take some like meat still have a cube. So we're fine
Take these crystals and shit. What else can you turn into meat or bomb? There use this
I'm fucking I'm like chilled out right now. Who cares?
I'm so chilled out right now. I think that's fine. All right
So what does it do?
I'm afraid for you to eat this because I want you to be the generator of crystals. Somebody's lacking. It's you
Fair. I know floating is cool, but we haven't needed to use it in like three hours
camouflage
Oh, hey, can I change my answer? No, no, I was gonna uh, you know, never mind
Okay, we want this one to exist because we want to walk up that. Okay. We'll quit screwing it up and nice and hearty
Oh fucking three head
Oh fucking three head, right? I think about that
All the time since last week. I really do
I'll just be in the shower
Just washing I just start going
Oh left but dead. I fucking love that guy, mate
It's just like fucking left but dead fucking free
I think uh
I think you can reach that. Can you reach that?
Oh, yep
new power
Incoming
Oh my god, we're fucking we don't have any water. We're gonna die. We're gonna starve to thirst. Oh, we need water
You're gonna get anybody. Oh, okay, dude. How can you not hit that?
It's right there
I can't aim higher than this
Hold on float over there. Ow. Oh, I see I have to move with the uh, cut out
Let's go. Can you do the minecraft villager herm noise?
Hmm
That close I feel like that was pretty close
Too fast and the travel these curious little shits
Figured out that the map is leading them to the serpent far away in the oasis
Will they be able to reach in time? Uh, I can leave I do need water though. I need my uh smoker
Ooh
Oh, dude, look at how many crystals are back here
You know what to do suck them up and water. Thank god. All right
No, I don't want you to do that. This should give me probably three or four crystals
I am excited. So we're gonna have to wait here for a minute. It's getting kind of late might um, call it here soon
maybe at the next uh
Checkpoint, you know, i'm telling you i've been loving these after six o'clock just kind of nighttime streams. I love it
I wonder how much is left. I'm over another few hours. Maybe you should finish it tonight. Uh,
I don't know
We'll see what what happens when I get to the next checkpoint something to look forward to after work and leave this point got everything
This uh, buddy is going to be turning out crystals
That's fantastic. All right, let's get to the next tower. There's a decent chunk left
This is the area which you just started in a whole nother area. I imagine probably another few hours
It's probably three or four hours. I'll finish it up. Don't worry. All right, I got the map
Weirdly enough, there is no tower. So that's kind of scary. Wait, maybe this one over here
Did I go down this hole? I don't remember. I was kind of panicking. I don't think I went down this hole
I didn't have it revealed. No, I definitely didn't there it is. It's at least another few hours. Yeah, that's all good
I'll finish it. I got a lot of crystals. That's a scary thing happening and I don't know what's going on
But they're not still up there, right? No, I don't think it doesn't count unless I can see them. Nice. It's a long game
Um, I don't think it's a long game. I think it's just
12 hours 14 hours 15 hours
All right. There it is
I'm gonna have like 25 crystals. We need to find one of those things. All right
I think I just have to go wait. We need to eat. I'm gonna have any food
I know but I don't want to get rid of those. All right, where's where's grapple?
All right grapple. You need to feed us. Oh, there are stakes here. I want full stomach full water
Oh, I don't want to cross there. No, no, no this way you to feed yourself. I'll be good. I think uh,
Holly was talking about making curry tonight, so that's gonna be dog champ
I love curry. It's so good
so easy
Get a fucking onion
potatoes
carrots
Mix in that shit. Oh, it's so good. It's such like a nice
filling
party dinner
with rice too
curry at 11 pm
What's wrong with that?
What the fuck?
Holy shit, that was terrifying
That was actually terrifying
Um, okay. Well that exists. Oh that just happened
I'm sorry
Okay, don't fuck around. I gotta go now. What am I doing?
Get up
No, no
acid
Please please
Oh
Do we get through?
No, we want is dead
Seeing the celestial trawalla
The trebum were reminded of all the many creatures that had fallen before the cylinder
Somewhere out there waited an elder who did not know of his siblings fate
And the trebum is sad the weight of the bad news they carried
Oh, no
Somebody else is fucking dead. Hold on a second guys. We're going back
I know i'm playing I know
This is supposed to be like a a roguelike kind of game in a way
I know I know trust me. I know I know
We're supposed to be losing people and getting more and I know but I don't I like I like this team
They're staying even if I have to save scum
All right. Here we go
Just don't get startled by the weird thing over here on the left. Let's wait. Let's wait. It's dangerous shit. Okay
That's better everybody safe. Please stop looking back. I have to because what if it's that neg
Always a straggler. It's always you
It's always we won't
Seeing the celestial trawalla
The trebum were reminded of all the many creatures that had fallen before the cylinder. Please leave us alone
Somewhere out there waited an elder who did not know of his siblings fate
And the trebum felt the weight of the bad news they carried
We will find
No, I need that. I need that. I want that I need that
Okay, everybody relax. We're good
All right. Uh, yeah, I think it's a good place to call it
Probably get another three or four hours. We'll finish it up on what's today
Today's friday technically saturday. Uh, how about sunday sunday night sunday night sunday night sunday night
Yeah, well these things hurt
I was stop walking into him. What are you dumb? Stop. You just watched me do it. I like this area
I like the desert a lot sunday is technically tomorrow
Yeah, oh, okay. So if you're eastern or if you're eu or it might even be sunday already for some of the australia crowd
Uh, yeah, I mean sunday pacific at 6 pm. Yeah. Um, i'll be really i gotta be really upfront with everybody
I love this. This is just so nice kind of reminds me of you know
Where it all started i've been really enjoying these
The old days
Thank you for being honest. I gotta be honest. I love this. Yeah, don't want to go too too late
Thanks for watching everybody
We will conclude the eternal cylinder on sunday evening, which is just about a day and some change from now. We'll see you soon
Night streamer andy i'm very curious of the conclusion. We'll see it on sunday
I'm gonna go eat see in a day to go to the other screen. Appreciate you sticking around
I know this kind of new change of schedule is um and change of pace appreciate you hanging out though
Teabags are out teabags are right here. You eat hamburger helper on the toilet
I can't think of anything worse to eat on the toilet
That sounds like the worst possible food option for when you're in the bathroom
Maybe tacos would be second. I mean, maybe tacos would be worse
Well, it depends if it's a like a taco or a burrito burrito would be fine
Why am I even answering this question that you just asked like this is a real question that I have to ask
I have to answer
There's no reason to answer this question
I'm gonna just let it roll by in the chat. It would have just been gone, but here we are
You have a strange attraction to very weird comments. It's fun to read the goofy stuff. I like it
Yeah, have a good night
See you for the oh and by the way
It'll probably only take three and a half or so hours three to four hours to do the rest
so
Maybe we'll start something else on sunday or maybe we'll do more breath of the wild or
Frog detective. I keep seeing pizza tower
Maybe i'll do pizza star. I have to finish breath of the wild though
The new hitman stuff. Yep hitman freelance mode
Seems crazy
Yeah, we got there's a lot of options. There's a lot to do
But i'll see you guys later. See you sunday. Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out drink some water
Call your mother
You know the drill see you soon
Manual manual volume decrease andy I think about that person every time I do that. All right. See you sunday. Take care
you