Do you have a custom mechanical keyboard?
I like laptop keyboards the most. I just want a laptop keyboard without the top part of the lap.
If I could sit here with that sitting right on my lap, I love laptop keyboards. They're the best.
Mechanical keyboards, I like them, but I don't know. The fact that you can hear
somebody typing on a mechanical keyboard from like three houses down.
That's fucked up. I don't think it is. And do I really need a mechanical keyboard?
Think about it. Yeah, membrane. Yeah, membrane, mesh, whatever they're called.
I like them more. They're more comfortable. Anyways, hi. I'm a little late. Just by a little
bit, but whatever. How you doing? Yeah, if I say two guys, you get it. My streams used to start at
four. Now if I say two, all right, I'm going to, I'm definitely going to start before four.
This is my way to get here before three o'clock. We can hear the poop line. That's actually a green
tea. Ban that guy for an hour. You are late by 36 minutes. Please accept my friend request. I don't,
I'm not going to accept friend. What are you talking about?
You need to accept. I'm not accepting anything except, I'm not accepting anything.
It's green tea and it's based. Yeah. It's a green tea powder. And I know it, it is, it is based. What
I'm drinking right now is based and I can, I'm safe to say that. Okay. So what are we doing today?
First of all, how are you doing? Second of all, we're going to do it with testing the chat again
today. A couple of days ago, we made the reference of playing Freddy fish, the entire Freddy fish
cinematic universe. And I was told, Oh man, you have to do it. That's going to be so awesome,
dude. Please play it. Please. Oh my God. Freddy fish is my childhood. Get in there, dude. Get in
there and play Freddy fish. So we're going to find out. A lot of people wanted me to do this.
And after about 20 minutes, if all of you are fighting each other, then I'm going to know if
this was worth doing. I did not know this, but there are one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven Freddy fish games. I thought they were two. I am not going to play all these. I'm not going
to play all seven of them. Maybe I'll play one or two or maybe, I don't know. If I get sick of this
shit, I'm going to move on to unpacking, which is a chill game where you could decorate a room.
You unpack stuff into a room or something. So that should be fun.
Play the second one, please. We're starting. I'm sorry. We're starting with the first Thor movie.
Okay. You don't, I can't just, you don't just skip to Ragnarok. We got to watch the first two
Thor movies, guys. You're going to go insane over this? I don't think so. There's no second Thor
movie. There isn't. Isn't there like Thor 2? What's Thor 2? Yeah, there is Thor, the dark world.
Yes, there is. It doesn't exist. Okay. So you guys didn't even know that existed. It's the worst
movie ever. I don't, I don't remember that movie. I don't even know if I saw it. Did I watch that
movie? I don't know. Okay. So here we go. We're going to play Freddy fish. This is Freddy fish
in the case of the missing kelp seeds. Mods I want you to do. I want you to monitor the chat
for, you know, negativity, swears. I need to see how they enjoy this game. So we're going to monitor
for negativity, swear words. I think I almost just, okay, I almost just turned off the stream.
That was bad. A member monitored them for negativity, negativity. That's it. That's a
lot of syllables. Negativity. Five syllables. Negativity. Fuck this game. Why? We haven't even
started playing it. You know what? I'm, I'm going through the first one at least.
We're going to have, you're gonna have to vote if you want to see the second one. You guys ready?
I, you've been waiting a long time. Let's go. Can you see me? No. Can you see the game?
Well, not yet. Hold on. Freddy fish and the case of the missing kelp seeds. Can you hear it?
Oh, there he is. No, that's not Freddy. Where am I? Sure thing, Freddy. All right.
I'm ready to go. Bye, Freddy. All right. Freddy fish. The curse of the missing kelp seeds.
You look like a villain. That's fine. Did you part your hair? No, I didn't. Wait, did I?
No, I'm just balding and it's going back. Hi, Jason. Want a flower? Sure. Did any of this matter?
Any of this? Thank you. Where are you going, Freddy? I'm bringing. You stay out of trouble.
You too. Nice receding hairline, Megalo. Yeah, talk to me when you're 40.
You know, stuff like that used to really kind of freak me out and scare me. I don't fucking care.
I don't care anymore. Hi, Grandma Grouper. Here's a flower. 10 years ago, I was like,
thank you. I don't care. I could go ball tomorrow. I wouldn't. Your treasure chest that
holds all the kelp seeds. Yes, Freddy. Look at the garden. It's dying. Classic cartoon comedy.
Until we find my treasure chest, we have no food. I'll find your treasure chest, Grandma Grouper.
So we can find the treasure chest. Thank you, Freddy. What else do I need to do? Peanut butter
and jellyfish sandwich for your journey. Hello. Good luck, Freddy. I don't need to pay attention
to this game. I'll find your kelp seeds. I don't need to pay attention to this game. This is every
Nick Jr. cartoon in one go. I don't need to pay attention to that. All right, so I got my
jellyfish sandwich. I don't need to pay attention. Pay attention to what, Freddy Fish?
Fuck this guy. Wait, you think he's fucking funny? All right, so what do I do? Is this too loud?
Don't disrespect Freddy Fish. Okay. Ooh, everything's clickable. Hello, Freddy. I'm so worried
about the kelp seeds. R1, R1, R1, R1. I'll find your treasure chest, Grandma Grouper. Good luck,
Freddy. Don't worry, Grandma Grouper. Okay. So I got to go find, I don't know. I don't remember.
I'll run into somebody that can help me. Oh, that's cute. Oh, that's cute.
Oh, did you hear that banjo? You can't, don't do initial, wait, you're doing a poll already
for an initial impression? We've been playing the game for less than two minutes. Nice comb
over, comb over, Andy. How long is this game? Just move backwards five feet, dude.
I cried as a kid playing this because I got stuck.
Just because that's where the kelp seeds are. If we don't find them soon, all the fish are going
to die. I'll help you find them, Freddy. All the fish are going to die if we don't do this.
That's okay. That got a little. It says to find Grandma Grouper's treasure chest,
go near the beach. Go near the beach. All right. So where's the beach?
All right. Let's go this way first. This game is really hard. I doubt it, but that's fine.
The bottle ain't here, boss. Maybe somebody else found it first.
Maybe somebody else found it first. Of course, someone else found it first, you spongehead.
Come on, we got to find that bottle. We're shark bait.
Boist. Okay. Pretty good cat puke right at the bat.
All right. So now what are we going to go to the beach? Do we go to the crown?
Can I read these signs? Click on everything. Click on everything. Nice. Okay. Oh boy. I want
to do that one again. I like that one. That's my favorite guy so far. That's my favorite character.
One more. No, not even close. One more. That's a good one. That's a good one. I like that one a lot.
Just keep going. Okay. What do we do? Push. Pull. Save.
So we're going to go in there. Who's in there?
Are you happy? Are you happy? I'm just curious. I'm asking. Are you happy?
Okay. I'm just checking in. Actually, I am too. This is fun. I like this.
So we're going to get a crowbar. Crowbar. Pull. Push. Twist it. What's up?
Can I prop this underneath here and crank it? We already have one.
I don't get it. I don't get it. How do I do this?
We just need to find a bigger boy. I don't get it. I don't want to play. This game is stupid.
Fuck this game. I don't get it. I don't understand. They didn't make it clear enough for me.
Why don't games make shit clearer? You know what I mean? Anymore?
I'm fucking done. That made me feel a little bit better.
I don't have the items. We've got to go. Did you find my guppy? Yes, Mrs. Halibut.
Gabby's stuck, but he's okay. Oh, goodness. So we're just going to leave.
Let's go find the next- I hope we find Grandma Grouper's kelp treasures.
All right. Bye. Hopefully your kid's okay. Oh, another bottle. Oh, guys. Look, another bottle.
We found a bottle. We just left them. I should have left a sandwich.
All right. I'm sorry. If this is me, I'm leaving the sandwich. I'm going to be like, hey,
Gary, whatever your name is. This is a peanut butter and jellyfish sandwich.
This will last you at least a few hours. So if you want it, you know what I'm saying?
Why leave the sandwich for him? The note says go to the junkyard.
We found another clue to the kelp treasure. All right. Go to the junkyard. Go to the beach.
What's that? It's a wooden board. Got it. Let's go save that kid. We found a purple sea urchin.
Urchin. All right. Let's go. This is a Jax moment. Yeah.
I'm imagining some big crying because I can't beat this.
Treasure. Well, if you can't find that treasure chest, you're going to have to
answer to the squid father. Please. I literally did. Not the squid father.
Oh, that's so sad. That's so sad. Okay, we got a key. Wait, what happened? What happened to them?
Do I have how much how much stuff do I have in my inventory? I wonder what it will unlock.
Is this can I have more than this? Or am I going to run out of space?
We got a raid. Yeah, I miss raids, man. I've been I've been I've been missing raids when they come
in. People will raid this channel with hundreds of thousands of people and I'll just be like,
so where are we going? That's rude. I don't want to be rude. Thanks for the raid.
That's a chippley. Thanks for the raid chippley. Appreciate it. Welcome guys playing Freddy Fish's
adventure of I don't know whatever this game is. There's like 10 of them. Who cares?
How do we get the pearl? Do you know how we can get through the shrimp net? You can't get through
the shrimp net unless you got the super duper duper buka poly gizmo. You can't get the super
duper duper buka poly gizmo unless you give me a clock. Where are we going to get a clock?
I like this. Look in the junkyard. A clock? All right, that was cool. The whale bones are over here.
The super duper what is it? Write it out. The super duper what?
The super duper. I love a lot of syllables so I found what this one was it?
The super duper. It's the super duper duper. The super duper duper gully gizmo. Hey, if you get
the super duper duper gully gizmo, I'll give you a clock. Whatever it is. I want to go back
to where the that kid was trapped. Did I go the wrong way? How do I go back that way? Where's the
map? Is there a map? All right, let's go in here. I know I'm doing this for fact.
I got you. Just wait. Check this out. See ya. Now what do I get?
Gabby, my Gabby. Thank you both. You're welcome, Mrs. Halibut. Please take this purple sea urchin
for saving my Gabby. A purple sea urchin. Is that currency down here? Thanks, Mrs. Halibut.
So I got two. I have two purple sea urchins. What do I do with this? I have two purple sea urchins.
All right, I gotta go to the beach. I have a key. I've got a sandwich. I've got a conch shell.
I'm gonna go back this way. Yeah, let's go ahead. Let's go up here. Castle. Conch. Whatever. Wait,
maybe this guy wants a purple one. I got one of those. All right, let's go.
Herman, I brought you a new shell that doesn't glow.
Will he fit into this? That's huge. Freddy, Freddy, Freddy. It's wonderful. Just a second.
Here, Freddy. Maybe you can use this glowing shell. Thank you, Herman. Good night.
I don't know why the curfew enthusiasm was playing. That was the exact same way that it starts. It was
like. Okay, so what can I do with this? It's a glowing shell. Welcome to King Crab's Castle.
What do I need to get in? Sea urchin. What am I getting? Three of these? Four of these? Five of
these? And I can do something? Oh, I don't have to. The guards just let you in? Sick. Who's that?
I'm fucking five years old. I swear to God. I thought that was funny. I thought that was
genuinely humorous. That's a different person's game. It was cute. Yeah, that's fine. Whatever.
I don't care. All right, what do you want? Hi, King Crab. Greetings, Freddy and Luther.
I got to get through season one to enjoy season two, right? Because this is season one. Everyone
said play season two. Play episode two. We'll see. I actually enjoyed this. I don't hate this.
I'm having a good time. Feels weird, man. What? My God, what is? Oh, look at these.
I'm going to try to crash my fucking computer. All right, what do you want? Welcome to my kingdom
with all my shells and pearls. But what really makes it very grand are all the boys and girls.
Mm-hmm. Cool. So what do you want? It's grandma's last. It's a key. It's a glowing
shell. It says to find chest, go to the junkyard. What do we do? What do we do with this? This is
kind of loud. Let me turn it down. Just a little. I do love my beautiful pearls. Okay, you like
pearls. So do I bring a pearl, maybe? I do love my beautiful pearls. Give him something. I can't.
It's grandma's last. All right, well, we're gonna leave. That's too quiet. No, there. All right,
so I can't do anything here yet. Let's go back. I need to go to the beach. They specifically said
beach. Oh, shit. Oh, no, it's been three minutes. There. This is a library ass game. This is a
library ass game. I gotta go find the beach. I have a distinct memory of trying to play these
games. But I just didn't I didn't understand how to install video games. Back in I want to say like
DOS. Because here's the thing that you guys don't understand. DOS was a huge pain in the ass.
I don't know if this was on DOS. This is 94. I want to say like 1991 1992. Maybe DOS. Yeah,
it's it wasn't just Oh, I'm gonna double click this game on my desktop and it's gonna open.
You used to have to put the CD like the floppy in, get it to run, go into prompts command prompt
and get the shit to run. It was actually kind of a pain in the ass for a little kid. I didn't get it.
Just type CD. No, sometimes it didn't work. Sometimes you have to install it and then run
the exe from the mounted drive and shit. It was weird. Type slash cheat. That wouldn't work either.
Let's keep going. You lost to a floppy drive. That was after DOS. It was something. Okay,
so Windows 3.1 ran on DOS. But sometimes you had to go into DOS to do certain things.
It was weird. Oh, it's the beach. Do I get that now? Windows 98 actually still ran on DOS.
Did it really? Should I do something? What do I do? Oh, there's a log.
On July 14th, there's going to be a baseball stream on this channel.
It's going to be the Cincinnati Clowns versus the Maryland Magicians.
I would suggest you stick around for that one. July 14th.
Oh, I got a key.
That was a banger.
I have a question. Crabs always kind of scare me and lobsters too because they have those claws.
How much damage would those actually do to a human hand?
You can have my fishing pole.
If, for instance, a fiddler crab, right? If a fiddler crab went bang on my fingers,
would they just chop them off? Would it just break the skin? Would it break the bone?
How bad would it be? I always have this distinct kind of vision in my brain that
if a lobster gets my finger, it's going to just, it's going to saw it off.
They could absolutely sever your finger. It depends.
Damn. It'd be a bad cut. Would you probably keep your thingy?
What about a pistol shrimp? All right. What did you give me the?
Oh, all right. So what can I do with that? Whoa. What the hell is this?
Three buckets of jellyfish. I'll toss the jellyfish to the hungry animals.
It's feeding time. I could probably do something like, wait, I do it.
You fed that one, Freddy. What?
Now it's time to do it on hard. And all of a sudden,
fucking guitar hero buttons start coming down and through the fire and flame starts playing.
And they just start running out. You missed one? I don't think it really matters.
How close can they get? Is this the part that you cried at?
Is this the part that you cried at? You fed them all.
Get ready, Freddy. Turtles love jellyfish.
Yes. Oh, it is getting harder.
Some animals are worth more points than others.
I have an infinite amount of ammo, but I mean, technically.
You did great, Freddy. That was crazy.
You did great, Freddy. You fed them all.
There are more hungry animals back there, Freddy.
Isn't that a scary number? I don't like that number. 23?
Yeah, it's like a scary number. What are the question marks?
Good job, Freddy.
The number 23, right? You fed them all.
Get ready, Freddy. I think the fish want some food.
Wait, hold on. The scary thriller Jim Carrey movie, the number 23,
is not based on any actual real folklore. They just made that up for the movie.
You did great, Freddy. I'm being dead serious.
You fed them all. Let's play again, Freddy.
Turtles love jellyfish.
No, not they made the number 23 up. I'm saying they make up the folklore
around how scary the number 23 is. Or is that actually number 23 is seen
in a lot of different places? My game's lagging.
So they made that whole thing up for the movie. It was just for the movie.
What? I am not fucking around.
I'm telling you the absolute honest to God truth.
I've been afraid of that number since I've heard that movie and stuff.
I thought it was like 13, like unlucky number.
Okay, I can't go up that far.
I've actually not done stuff on the 23 dates of months.
You have all three buckets of jellyfish left.
I actually thought it was really superstitious folklore or something.
Make sure you toss the jellyfish into the animal's mouths.
It was just made up for the movie,
but I thought it was all these like weird biblical references.
I thought it was like the Da Vinci code, right?
Where it's like, oh, Leonardo Da Vinci had a secret map to a treasure in the United States.
Wait, no, that's a Nick Cage movie called National Treasure.
Well, you know what I mean? I thought it was something like that.
I thought it was like a biblical thing. I don't know.
Okay, I just minimize the game. Stop.
The number 23 has been directly mentioned several times in the Bible, 14 times.
The Judge of Israel, 23 years of service.
It's also worth noting that Jehoah was 23 years old when he inherited the throne
and became Judah's new king. Interesting.
Yeah, sorry. So I was right. I was right.
I was right. So they didn't make this whole thing up for the Jim Carrey movie.
2 divided by 3 is 666. That's what I'm saying. So what do you mean question marks?
Yeah, it's an actually biblically accurate scary number.
What? It's a scary number. Hold on. Is this mic not loud enough?
Have I thrown 157 of these?
You still have three buckets of jellyfish left.
There are more hungry animals back there.
Dude, you can do that with any number.
You know what else is really funny about this whole scenario?
I've never even seen the number 23 with Jim Carrey. I've never seen the movie.
I just knew it was a scary number movie.
And I looked it up on Wikipedia and it was like,
he's scary. Jim Carrey writes it down a million times.
I think I saw the trailer. I think I saw the trailer and I was scared of the number.
I swear to God, I really think that's what happened.
I never even saw the movie.
I don't even care if I lose. I have 200 points.
No five-year-old is going to get 200 points.
I don't want 223. I want 250. I don't want 230.
This is fine. I want something else. 240 is fine.
I don't like that number. That's like an odd number.
I want an even number to 250.
Okay. I'll touch it.
You're the best jellyfish tosser I know, Freddy.
Let's feed some more animals, Luther.
You have three buckets of jellyfish to feed the animals.
What are you talking about? I have to do this again?
Why do I have to do this again? How do I leave?
I can't click the arrow on the top left.
All right. I'm just going to lose.
The number 23.
Why did it scare me so much?
I don't care if I lose. Hold on. This is important.
Make sure you toss the jellyfish into the animal's mouths.
I'm not trying to play. I'm trying to find this trailer.
How did I do, Luther?
Why did this scare me so much?
Let's feed some more animals, Luther.
Three buckets of jellyfish.
It's feeding time.
Why can I not leave? I'm trying to just leave.
Too bad, Freddy.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Wow.
All right, Freddy. I don't care.
How do I shut him up?
How do I get out of this?
There's something else important going on right now.
We don't have anymore.
Okay. I left.
That was fun, Freddy.
It sure was.
All right. Why did this scare the shit out of me so much?
We better continue our search for grandma grouper's kelp seeds.
Let's find out.
I never saw the movie.
Okay. Let's go.
Where is this?
Okay. Let's see.
Let's see why I was scared of this so much.
Why does it look like such shit?
Why was I buying that for you, too?
Actually, I've had a good long time to flip through it.
Why don't you give it a try?
The number 23.
A heart-wrenching odyssey into paranoia.
You're the most horrifying metamorphosis ever told.
I'm buying this for you.
Chapter one.
All I could think about was the number.
I met you when I was...
23.
And the day we met was?
September 14th.
914.
14 plus 9 is?
23.
Is it all just a coincidence?
I don't know.
So what is 23?
They're 23 axioms to Euclid's geometry.
The human body consists of 46 chromosomes.
23 from each parent.
See?
Two divided by three.
Point.
666.
Number the devil.
So is 23 a blessing or a curse?
243?
240 pixels?
I was born at 11, 12 p.m.
11 plus 12.
23.
My birthday.
Driver's license.
It's so strange.
Imagine if this is 230 p.m.
It actually kind of is.
You deserve to come up with minutiae
and you've drawn wild conclusions from them.
Word on every 23rd page.
I warn you.
Hell is waiting.
The number.
What does that mean?
You know.
Texas in the Oklahoma City bombing.
Sorry, I'm scared.
April 19th.
You gotta get out.
It's coming for you.
4 plus 19 is 23.
This is not who you are.
Hiroshima bomb was dropped.
815.
8 plus 15 is 23.
13 years of life.
No more.
Don't do this to us.
See?
Okay.
Well, that's it.
Number 23.
See?
Everything's 23.
That's why.
That trailer scared me.
I didn't see the movie, but I was scared of the number.
So I stopped.
I started thinking about that.
Like, wait a minute.
How many?
How many waters come in a case of water?
23.
So I stopped buying them.
They had to be 24, 25 in a case of water.
It started freaking me out.
You're actually 5 IQ.
What do you know about my IQ?
23 IQ.
I don't know.
How old was I?
When did that movie come out?
Like 20 fucking years ago?
How old was I?
I was probably like, I don't know.
I don't know how old I was.
I probably was very influenced.
It was 23 years ago.
It actually might have been.
And that's fucked up if it was.
If it was fucking 23 years ago.
Quiet now, because that's weird.
You were 23.
What?
I was?
That's fucked up.
All right.
I was 23.
What?
It's going to be 2023 next year.
9 plus 8 plus 5 is 23.
What?
It's not.
It's 22.
Check your math.
For a second, I was like, holy shit, this is weird.
All right.
I got to finish this game.
What do I do with this stuff?
There are 23,000 people watching.
It's not.
This is like 17.
All right.
I need to go figure some shit out.
Grandma Grouper's house is over here.
All right.
So fishing pole.
It's a fishing pole.
What do I do with the fishing pole?
I actually was scared of that number for a little while.
This is kind of, it was weird.
Oh, here we go.
All right.
So let's go that way.
I'm Mr. Starfish.
Your math teacher for today.
Welcome to class.
This better not be 23.
How hard do you want the questions to be?
I want it to be easy, medium, hard, very hard, or advanced?
Advanced it is.
What is 32 minus 20?
Shit, that's 23 backwards.
That's 23 backwards.
And that's how old I was when the movie came out.
You're right.
Yay, yay.
Now try this one.
What is 84 plus 14?
Uh, I, um, stop, stop.
I need to get out.
Very good.
We've answered two problems right now.
Let's try another trying to get you to play Freddy Fish.
What is six divided by two is 23.
Three minus 24.
That's correct.
Let's do another problem.
What is the difference of 23 and 21?
Two.
You're right.
Now let's try another.
How much is 37 minus 21?
16.
We've answered five problems right now.
Try this one.
What is 88?
That's correct.
Here's another equation.
How much is 42 plus 21?
That's correct.
Now let's try another.
You're the devil in the sky.
What is the sum of 41 and 23?
What the fuck, man?
What the hell?
You're right.
Now try this one.
What is the sum of 54 and 13?
You're right.
Let's do another problem.
I don't want to do another one.
What is 60?
You're right.
Now try this one.
What is the difference of 97 and 65?
What's that backwards?
32.
That's correct.
We've answered the ones right.
Here's another equation.
What is the difference between 62 and 10?
That's correct.
Let's do another problem.
It says stop.
How much is...
I know, but I kind of think I need to get to 23.
I'm not doing 23 questions, I'm sorry.
What happened to him?
Why did he pass out?
That was weird.
We found another purple sea urchin.
Hit stop.
That's dangerous.
That's going to hurt someone.
Oh, there's a bottle.
Where's the bottle?
Rich?
We're going to be rich.
What's that from?
Hearthstone, I think.
Oh, a sandwich.
It's 323 right now.
Dogfish don't eat peanut butter and jellyfish sandwiches.
What?
There's more than one way to catch a dog.
We need to get different food?
I guess we can't get past that junkyard dogfish.
No, I need different food.
Okay, so I need a way to feed the dog.
We need a bone.
Yeah, but whatever.
The speedrun of Freddy Fish is 23 minutes.
I mean, I feel like you're just going to have to...
It's just clicking from screen to screen, right?
Okay, let's go up.
23, I'm fine.
No one gets past Eddie the eel.
But we're looking for Grandma Gruper's count treasure.
If we don't find it soon, all the fish are going to die.
I've heard that one before.
Look, kids, why don't you just get out of here before I have to eat you?
Technically, I'm a snake, right?
They're not fish, right?
So technically, you can make a funny thing where you say,
well, I'm not a fish, Fred.
It's a glowing shell.
Grandma Gruper's famous peanut butter and jellyfish sandwich.
I guess I could let you get past.
Good luck finding Grandma Gruper's count treasure.
The coast is clear now.
Okay, let's go.
Click all the funny things.
Click all the funny things first.
Cool.
Nice.
That was fucking 3D.
That was Hue's Revolutionary back in 1994.
That was revolutionary.
People would start to scream when it was coming up the screen.
Oh, it's too dark.
I'm scared, Freddy.
We have something that would help us see.
The game is too loud.
Oh, it's because we watched the number 23 trailer
and I turned everything way up.
I'm sorry.
I can use this.
It's better.
We found another purple sea urchin.
Cool.
What about that?
Is that all that was in here, just sea urchin?
I don't want to miss anything.
I've got a whole handful of these.
Oh, check each one.
Scared, Freddy.
I got it.
That's better.
This thing's trying to kill somebody.
What can I do in here?
Nothing.
Hold up.
Jim Carrey himself just cursed you.
Send this message to 23 of your friends to avoid the curse.
I was actually scared of that movie.
Oh, that was cute.
What about the duck?
So, did I get what I needed from here?
Is it just cute things to click on?
So, I gotta go left.
The volcano is this way.
How come Jerma is funnier on the VOD?
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
This is number...
The gate needs to be opened more before we can get through.
The gate's almost...
Look at that.
Reached through.
What does that mean?
All right.
Should I keep these?
It's a bucket with five purple sea urchins in it.
Do I need these anymore?
Should I keep these?
Do I need them?
You don't need them anymore?
Okay.
All right.
So, I got another slot.
Let's go to the volcano.
That was sick.
That was really cool.
You know what?
You know, think about this.
What a fun job.
Think about how fun this is.
So, some of the artists and the game director and stuff,
they sit around and they come up with this piece where,
look, we got a volcano and some kelp and some rocks.
And then they go, you know what?
What happens if you click on them?
And they come up with these really funny little cool things
that happen when you click on everything.
Just with this empty canvas, they go, all right.
When you click the kelp, they're going to spin around.
It's going to make a cartoon sound
and it's going to sneeze out a fish.
And then it does just that.
That's really cool.
This would be fun to do.
Whoa.
He almost made it.
Theater.
You're an actual child.
I'm just talking about how the game is interesting.
It's a fun thing for young kids to be engaged with.
I'm reviewing the game.
I like that guy.
You're 46.
How old do you think the game director of this game was
when they made this game?
Guys, other 10-year-olds don't make games for 10-year-olds.
It's not that a nine-year-old didn't make this.
What do you think of making the games?
It's not like a room full of toddlers
in oversized suits pretending to be adults.
A 23-year-old made it.
Still.
It's a great show.
Step right up.
Oh, I like that one.
All right, let's go.
Let's see the show.
All right, quiet.
Welcome, girls, boys, and fish of all ages
to the greatest show under the sea.
We've got some great acts here today.
Sure to make your gills quiver with delight.
So put your fins together for our first fantastic performance.
Be ready to clap.
Don't be a fucking rude asshole.
This better be funny.
That's it?
Hey, how much was your ticket?
Yeah, $39.
Me too.
That's not it, right?
There's more.
There has to be.
All right, okay.
That's the real show.
This is what we do.
Why is shushing the show?
Kick that person out.
You're going to shush the act?
All right, that's this guy.
Geez.
That guy just got...
That guy died.
Geez.
Sheesh.
You're killing me.
There's nothing else to do here?
That was the worst sheesh?
They're not saying...
What are they saying?
They're saying, geez.
I'll try to get it.
Sheesh.
Nobody else did it.
Why did nobody else do it?
You all fucking set me up.
Let's leave.
There are all kinds of surprises.
Wait, is it another show?
That's...
They were speaking...
Your...
Somebody said German East.
That's a German joke.
I don't say...
Please.
That was fantastic.
I like that.
Again, more.
So why is this act way better than the frog?
The frog's trying to do a good job.
This would be a live show if I did it.
I would get a one-star review.
I would probably have the worst rated show.
It would be like...
It would be like 15% on Rotten Tomatoes.
It was like the German 985 comedy special.
They would have 15% on Rotten Tomatoes
and a 60% audience score.
You know what I mean?
We can pretend it was all right, but not all of us.
Not all of us are going to do that.
Oh, there's another one.
All right, if I'm going to have to rate the performances here...
Wait, there's more.
Holy shit, that was fucking phenomenal.
That was absolutely phenomenal.
That's the best one so far.
That's the best one so far, without a doubt.
Without a single doubt in my mind.
And that was only one-third of the act.
The nuances, the different...
The nuance difference between that and the first one.
Holy shit, man.
The different kind of order that those played out in.
It's just such a small difference, but it made a big difference.
One more.
The end of that one spoke directly to me.
Because it wasn't just a cut-off clip of a frog.
It was the whole sound.
You finally get to hear the whole sound effect.
There's more.
Everybody has three.
Everybody has three acts.
How many are these?
The Flying Carp Brothers?
That's not even that.
They're swimming.
That's not even hard.
What you're doing is not hard.
I don't know about this one.
That's an F.
Sorry, I don't even want to see the next one.
No, that's an F.
It is.
Perfect.
Love it.
What?
Are you serious?
They didn't give him a chance.
Get back out here.
That's you.
I don't agree with the audience.
I think I don't agree with the audience at all.
Don't agree.
This is puffo.
I don't get it.
Everybody in the audience, y'all.
Fucking threw you a tomato at the turtle.
It didn't deserve it.
I still got mine.
Bump and gump.
Do they have any more?
Or is that it?
And their sign has graphics.
Other...
A lot of other people had more than one act.
So I'm gonna have to deduct points from that one.
Okay, so what do we got?
Frank the Fabulous Frog is...
Okay, Helga was S-ed here at number one.
What was this one?
All right, this is all right,
but you're just a worse version of the guy with the shells.
Where are they?
This one, right?
Yeah, to me, just the worst version of Luke Fishvon
Bastovid.
Yeah, I mean, I felt that.
I felt it in my bones.
Your winners are Helga and Luke Fisk.
I don't need to see anymore.
All right, so how do I go from here?
Now what?
I can't shake my drink anymore.
I don't like drinking on camera either.
I feel like I do weird shit with my mouth and I don't even see it.
All right, so where do I go?
Was that just a secret unlockable?
So this is just an unlockable.
Let's go.
These are nice backgrounds.
No, it is.
The art's really nice.
All right, so I gotta go down?
I can go down here.
This place is scary.
No, it's beautiful.
Look.
That's for the grouch.
How come the super frog is not in the talent show?
So anybody else think it's fucking weird that we just all of us just all go?
Yeah, that's normal for that to be down there.
Why?
Why we think that's there are fish.
There's stuff down in the deep sea that make their own light with their heads.
And they're weird monsters and shit.
We just like are like, yeah, that's fine.
There's like giant weird scary monsters down there.
Okay, that's whatever.
A huge amount of the sea is not even explored.
Yeah.
They're just minding their own business.
That's weird.
Isn't it weird, though, that those things exist?
What can I do for it?
It's a glowing ship.
A fishing pole.
The clue says go to the junkyard.
Go to the junkyard.
I need to get a bone.
Only 23% of the seas has been explored.
That's kind of crazy.
Okay, I gotta go back.
You're flipping off children.
But you know, my favorite comment is this one.
If you care so much, why don't you explore it yourself?
The junkyard is this way.
We only know about 5% of the universe.
Yeah, the fact that the universe itself is just so weird.
Okay, where do I go from here?
I need to go find a bone.
Where would get bones?
We should hurry to the junkyard to get the next bottle.
It was a skeleton.
Yep.
Where was it?
The whale bones.
Where were they?
I forgot.
Yeah, they're around here, right?
Oh, wait, I have a fishing pole now.
I can probably get that.
That won't help us get through the net.
What are you talking about?
No, thanks.
You need the suki duki duki polygizmo like I need another clock.
I need to get a clock?
And I do need another clock.
Find a clock.
The old whale bones are over here.
All right, let's go get the bone.
We're going to go to the dog.
We're going to get the thing over there.
We get a bone.
Here we go.
Do you guys think that there's another earth?
But the only difference is they just have one nostril.
And that's the only difference.
Everything else is identical.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a multiverse.
I don't believe in multiverse.
It pisses me off that like one of the germ has hit the fucking lottery and I didn't.
That makes me angry.
You know, like one of the Germans has huge muscles and it's like six feet tall.
That pisses me off.
I don't even want to believe in it.
I don't want to even know it's real.
That annoys me.
If I get like if I get there's like a crossover with like all the German multiverse
and there was like a tall like six to German, Jeremy, whatever.
And he's in a suit and shove them.
I'd be like, get out.
Shut up.
I'd be like, bring me another one.
Bring me another one.
I don't want this to be my crossover because I want to be the one in the
multiverse scenario where I'm the cool one.
Well, I'm the one that's the good one, right?
Bring one shorter.
I'm going the wrong way.
Go back.
Yeah.
Bring me bring me like weird cannibal germa and a germa that flunked every grade.
So I could just be, I'm the one that's the one they can tell.
I can be the one that dictates what we do.
Watch that.
No, I wouldn't want the cannibal.
I wouldn't want cannibal germa.
I would.
I don't think I'd want cannibal germa around.
Just bring me like caveman germa.
All right.
You're the caveman.
No, I'm not.
Bring me the dumb ones so I can be the smart one and I can be the one that the movie is
based around it because I don't want to be one of the other ones with the movies not
based on them.
You know, pissed off.
That would make me if Chad's six to germa with a suit.
It comes into the it's their movie and I'm the side other character.
No, fuck you.
Uh-uh.
That ain't happening.
You would be the villain.
No, I don't know.
I want the movie to be.
I wanted it.
Germa goes around the multiverse.
I don't want that.
I don't want to be the side character.
I don't want to have a portal open up behind me and I'm sitting at this desk and I'm the
joke that the Chad germa is his movie.
He's done like fucking 10 scenes already and he's like, oh, so game and honey.
Like then it's like, I'm the loser guy.
Like I look up my shoulder and he's in my universe and I'm a side character.
Nope.
I'm good.
I'm going to be ready for it.
I'm just sitting there.
Like I see the portal open.
I'm just sitting there like ready to fucking punch.
He puts his head through and a fist just hits him right in the square in the fucking face.
He's just like, he falls back in the hole and sucks around.
And then I obviously the cameras are still in the room.
So I look around and I go, it's my movie.
It's my movie.
Motherfuckers.
Where's the junkyard?
That's a villain.
I forget where the junkyard is.
I don't know.
I actually am lost.
Is it down?
No, it's not down.
I forget where it is.
I have not been paying any attention to this.
You imagine the scene after that though.
Imagine you go through the multiverse and just one's waiting for you.
Just fucking full on punches you square in the face and like smashes your nose in.
And you have to sit there with the other characters in the movie and be like,
why did that happen?
What was wrong with that one?
Why did he do that to me?
Yeah, I got to be careful because then I would be in the credits as Psycho Germa.
No, no, no, real Germa.
I'm real Germa.
Don't put me as like weirdo or Psycho Germa.
No, real Germa.
That's what I am.
And I would be 10 rows down on the credits.
And that makes me angry too.
No, not happening.
All right, I got it.
I got it.
And why do we think that the parallel multiverse universes are different versions of us?
No, there's not an infinite amount of versions of us.
If anything, we're going to jump around the multiverse and I'm going to be sitting
in the same goddamn spot with a different shirt on.
I'll have a green shirt on.
It'll be the same exact person.
You lost the treasure.
So now you got to see the squid father.
Please, boss, not the squid father.
Playing a different game, talking about a different topic.
Where's green shirt Germa?
He's better.
Hold on, let me open up the portal.
It's always like this, right?
They always put their fingers together and they do threading around a thread.
I've talked about this before on stream, but I'm sorry.
I don't understand casting.
I don't.
I know it's been like, yeah, old material.
I don't care.
There's new people here.
Why do people do fucking casting to cast spells?
Just go.
Go!
Done.
You don't have to go like this.
Just go.
Fireball, go!
That is a repeating joke.
That's fine.
Now we can trade Ray for his super duper duka buka poly gizmo.
Somebody just said, Germa, magic's not real.
So I'm talking about in creatively.
That's linear action that has no mysticism to it.
The action makes the move come to life.
Poo poo head.
I'm stuck in the car.
Oh, I got the clock.
Let's go.
You'd be the shittiest wizard.
No, I wouldn't because I would just go lightning.
And the person was like, while they were sitting there
doing all kinds of fucking moves for the camera,
they've already been struck by my lightning move
because I don't care with the bullshit around it.
I'm just going to lightning get him.
I like this one, but that would be evil.
No, that will be efficient.
All right.
Where's the clock guy?
Clock guy's somewhere over here, right?
Through here and then left, right?
Oh, that's just a gun.
Whatever.
Now open that up for the clock.
Now you get the super duper duper duper poly gizmo.
Nice doing business with you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Which one was it in this one?
Where is the pearl?
Bingo.
Then we bring the pearl to the king.
I'm leaving.
No, I don't need whale bones.
I don't need whale bones.
And they clap with their teeth.
That was weird.
They were like, this game's disturbing.
And no, it's not.
It's a game for kids.
I got to go find the castle again.
It's back with the crown.
Crown.
Go.
Get up.
Strawberry magic was disturbing.
Yes, it was.
This is not strawberry magic.
This is, I would say, pretty tame.
All right.
So now I go this way.
We go to the castle, bring the pearl.
I still have a fishing rod for whatever reason.
The king will see you now.
Strawberry magic was a masterpiece.
Yeah, we powered through that.
A lot of people didn't want to see it.
We did it.
All right, here you go.
What do I get?
It's a pearl.
What a pretty pearl.
I love all the citizens of my kingdom.
We love you too, King Crab.
It's a go to the three caves and enter.
I already did that.
I couldn't give the pearl.
In the next box.
This guy's a dictator.
All right, I got to go back to the big with the hole was.
Putt putt's better than this.
That's, I mean, be careful.
Oh, play pajama Sam.
Play putt.
They're all the same exact video game, guys.
They're the same game.
They're probably all maybe the same company.
We still need to find another bottle, Luther.
Right off.
All right, one on the right.
So what was the point of coming in here?
Oh, it's too dark.
That wasn't here before.
There.
I was already in here.
The clue says the treasure is hidden in the sunken ship.
Let's go get the kelp seeds at the old ship.
Oh, wait, this is it.
I know just where it is.
The old ship.
I put all my clues in bottles so I could find my way back to the treasure.
Evil squid.
I thought I put the voice bottle at the Nexus.
Let us in on that.
But, but, Squidfather.
Oh, was the voice bottle with the key?
Come on, Spongehead.
Think.
The Squidfather trusted us to hide the stolen kelp treasure for him.
But, but, but, but Squidfather.
Oh, no, he's spewing ink.
The treasure is.
Come on, Spongehead.
Doesn't a lot look like me.
Somebody said it's you.
That old shipwreck has held so many treasures over so many years.
Okay.
We're looking for Grandma Grouper's treasure.
Good luck, mates.
Do you know where it is?
It's a fishing port.
That old ship sailed through hurricanes, typhoons, thunder, and lightning.
But it went down in the great culp of Ort 7.
Hey, Freddy.
What do you think is behind that window?
I don't know.
What the heck?
What's in there?
Look, Looper.
Grouper's kelp treasure.
It's in there.
Yes.
Now I'm going to be rich, rich, rich.
Grandma Grouper's kelp treasure is for everyone to see.
No, no, no.
And besides, the window is closed and it's much too heavy to open.
It's inside of there.
It's going to be like a thank you card.
Let's go find a crank handle.
Yeah, right.
It's going to be like one coupon for a fun block party.
There's not going to be money in there.
It's a fishing port.
It's a pearl.
Look, Looper.
Grandma Grouper's kelp treasure is in there.
I don't want to hit this again.
Yes.
Now I'm going to be rich, rich, rich.
Looper, Grandma Grouper's kelp treasure is for everyone to share.
And besides, the window is closed and it's much too heavy to open.
Yeah, it's going to be empty.
If we can find a handle for the crank, we could crank open the window and swim inside.
And the octopus is going to come over.
Let's go find a crank handle.
What does this mean?
This is impossible.
What's in here?
There's nothing in here.
It's going to be like exactly.
It's going to be kelp.
It's going to be just seeds or something.
Oh, that's just cute.
That's cute.
Okay, I'm sorry.
If you don't like find what just happened to be like an enjoyable thing.
What are you talking about?
Like this.
Look at how just how cute this is right there.
Right.
Hi.
Like, come on.
Come on.
I don't even really.
I don't think farts are even funny.
They're not.
It's just sometimes the cartoon sound effect farts are.
It's a multiverse.
Do you?
Oh, it's the doctor strange would be sitting there going like this and go.
Oh, it's me.
You're dealing with the master of the defense of the dark arts or whatever it is.
And he makes the circle.
Magic isn't real.
I know it's not coming handy.
Oh, it's a crutch.
Okay.
My eyes are looking over here and just bear with me here.
So I'm looking right here and my eyes right here.
See, this is a turkey leg.
This is a bone and meat on it.
And I was like, oh, turkey leg.
But it's not.
Keep going down.
There's more.
It's opening your little ones.
I'm Phineas McFinn, the finest sailor on the seven seas.
It's a beautiful.
Do you want a button?
Super duper duka buka poly gizmo can open the shrimp.
There's just one word that says it all when I'm happy, when I'm sad, when I'm good or bad.
To starboard from stem to stern.
Definitely one of the multiversal characters of that character.
I can't hear you.
One more time.
I was a pirate.
Very good.
Excellent.
In fact, the handle is broken.
Arrgh too hard.
If you could find old Phineas another musical instrument,
I would gladly trade you this useless crank handle.
Okay, I need a new handle.
Okay, you're not listening.
He said he needs a handle.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I go down through here?
Down, down.
All right.
Up.
Let's go up.
No, no, no.
Down, down.
And then up.
Yeah, what the hell?
Why is this taking me though?
Hold on.
So this is on a different way.
This just goes back up.
Okay.
Well, I have a crutch now.
I don't know what to do with it, but we'll be back.
Stop pretending to be bad.
I haven't played this game ever.
Even if it's a five-year-old's.
I don't know.
Okay, so I need his crank.
What can I do with the crutch?
You?
Oh, do you want it?
Here.
This motherfucker looks like one of the goldfish.
He looks like a goldfish snack.
How come they didn't make him that big?
He looks like an extra big goldfish snack.
They should have made him like that.
The snack that's miles back.
Goldfish.
Minus two the fuck out of that.
I dare you.
Here's another musical instrument for you.
Great.
Here.
Take this crank handle.
Thanks, Phineas.
Arrgh!
There's just one word that says it all.
Arrgh when I'm happy.
Arrgh when I'm sad.
Arrgh when I'm good or bad.
Arrgh!
Arrgh to port.
Arrgh to starboard.
Arrgh from stem to stern.
Arrgh!
Arrgh you swatty.
The yo ho ho hum hum my chum.
Arrgh!
What's that you say?
I can't hear ya.
Arrgh!
One more time.
Very good.
Excellent.
In fact.
Arrgh!
Heart piss me the fuck off.
And starring Sam Miller.
You can eat it or wear it.
No fox?
Arrgh!
I don't even want to look at it.
All right.
So we're about to get the treasure, guys.
You guys ready?
Guys.
Let's see what the treasure is.
Here we go.
It's time.
Hmm.
Okay.
They open it all of a sudden.
It just goes.
Jiminy!
Freddy!
Run!
I'm sorry.
That was probably really loud.
Told you we'd find the treasure, boss.
That was really loud.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, you two.
Hand over the treasure.
No.
I'm sorry.
I forget the fucking thing.
It sucks.
Well, we gotta take the treasure to the squid father.
So we can grow some kelp.
If we share the seeds, we can all grow kelp.
Share the kelp seeds?
Gee, boss.
The kelp seeds are for everyone.
Wait.
I got an idea.
We can share the kelp seeds.
Great idea, boss.
Yes.
Yay!
What?
That's all it took?
Let's go tell the squid father we're all going to share.
All it took was just being like,
hey, we should probably just share these.
Aye!
You found the kelp.
Oh, it is just kelp.
You're really messing up this dev's engine here.
You're just messing with the grass tool.
Somebody has to come and clean this shit up.
Don't let your son on the computer when you're working on the game.
Freddy, you found the treasure.
You can't minus two and say L-U-L.
That doesn't work.
I saved your treasure, Grandma Gooper.
Well, okay, Freddy helped a little, but I figured it out.
I'm very brave.
Oh, I'm sure you were, loser.
Now, can you both help me plant the seeds?
In my backyard?
Of course, they'll be for everyone,
but I will be the one to dictate who gets what I, you know, who gets it.
But plant them all in my backyard.
Of course, I'll spread it out evenly.
I want a good bird.
You speak me such.
I'm so proud of you both.
Why don't we go inside so you can tell me all about your adventure?
Somebody extra seeds.
Stop, go.
What?
That's my favorite character.
Oh, can't you just see this being Smash Brothers stage music?
Three, one, go.
So what is go?
Here we go again.
I don't want to go again.
No, I don't want to go again.
Thanks for getting the flowers, Sam.
Sure thing, Freddy.
They're wonderful.
Gotta go, Sam.
Bye, Freddy.
All right, I need the truending.
There is no truending.
All right, so that was fun.
That was Freddy Fish and the magic of the kelp seeds.
On to Freddy Fish 2, which I've been told,
just skip Freddy Fish 1, go to Freddy Fish 2.
Hi, Fnappy Turtle.
Hi, Freddy.
Here, Fnappy, you look like you need some cheering up.
For me?
Please don't, no, please.
This is Freddy Fish Day.
Can we please play Freddy Fish 4 next?
No, it's Freddy Fish 2.
Everyone said Freddy Fish 2 is the one you play.
We did Freddy Fish 1 to get to Freddy Fish 2.
Well, I guess it's time for you to decide.
After Freddy Fish 2,
final impressions of Freddy Fish kelp seed mystery,
five equals best.
Okay, you know what?
This honestly looks like every Amazon review I've ever seen.
Even if it's five stars,
there's like a shitload of five stars
and then a bunch of one stars.
How do you reliably give something a three?
I don't think you can.
You can't do it, right?
If you're going to leave a review,
you either loved it or you hated it.
I don't know if you make a review on Amazon
for something that you just kind of generally thought was okay.
You don't really.
You either do it if you love it or hate it.
All right, so people like that.
So we're going to do Freddy Fish 2.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
Maybe I should go pee first.
Should I go pee?
This is the case of the haunted schoolhouse.
Okay, let's give it a go.
Okay.
Jesus.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not ready.
Good morning, Mr. Krabby.
What the fuck?
Where the hell is it?
What the fuck is it?
Come on.
Okay, we're good.
Sorry I'm late, Freddy.
I just had to find my Codfish Commando action figure for show and tell.
That's okay, Lother.
But we better get going before we're late.
All right, let's go.
This art is worse.
No, it's not.
All right, let's see.
Are the clickables as good?
People said this is the one to play.
The first one's a bad game.
Already bored.
The clickables are not very good so far.
I was all right.
I'd give that a three on Amazon.
Okay.
That's a five.
Four.
Five.
Three.
Let's go.
Hit the heart.
Freddy, did you bring everything you need for school?
Of course I did, Lother.
In fact, I'm ready for a great day.
And a few are too.
Three, two.
Oh, look at that.
I'll race you to school, Freddy.
So I thought the school is haunted?
Is that what I've been told?
Where are all the guppies?
We're hiding.
The guppies say the school is haunted by a ghost
and that the ghost is stealing their toy.
Okay.
I saw the ghost, Mrs. Croaker.
It stupefied me with fear and then it stole my toy.
Boo.
Toy.
No such thing as ghosts.
Luther and I will find luck, friends.
Boo.
I don't want to do all that.
Uh, Mrs. Guppy, did somebody?
Dave is in the cabinet eating paste.
We probably shouldn't have him do that.
Oh no.
What is he doing?
We need to get him out of there.
It's a multiverse.
The guppies all want.
They sure did add songs in this one.
A lot of songs.
Ten years grow.
What happened?
If we had to get haunted, why couldn't we get a friendly ghost?
I'm really glad Mrs. Croaker decided to stay with us.
She's great.
With all this spooky stuff going on,
maybe Mrs. Croaker will forget to give us homework.
Okay, bye.
Does that technically mean make the earth flat?
Is that right?
Technically, right?
If the earth was a cube, would it be flat?
I mean, technically, like some of the earth would be flat, right?
The earth was a cube.
It's fine crap.
I'm just, I'm just saying if the earth was a cube, not a globe,
it would be a flat plane.
It would be three dimensional.
Cube does not mean flat, but what?
It would be three dimensions.
It would be three dimensionally flat.
Guys, no, I do not.
Okay, excuse me.
We need to get this really cleared up here immediately.
I'm just making a thing.
I'm making a joke as to it turned it into flat sides.
Okay, it was merely a jokey reference.
Okay, I can't take the glue.
Whoa, get out of there.
Oh, it's just scrubbing bubbles.
I love that guy's voice, by the way, the scrubbing,
the scrubbing bubbles cleaning extra fast with their scrubbing bubble technology.
I love that guy.
I love that voice so much.
You guys know who I'm talking about.
You know exactly the commercial, you know exactly the voice.
There's a lot more clickable than this one.
I don't watch Reddit TV.
Man, I don't think Reddit was even a website when this commercial was airing.
Vote Freddy for class prez.
That's cute.
I like that.
Go Marlins.
I just kind of broke everything.
Let's go.
Better look out.
I'll be back to get that toy.
Freddy, he almost got away with my Cush Commando action figure.
Why does that ghost have to steal kids' toys?
Look, it's part of the ghost.
Luther, I don't think that ghost wears sheep.
Whoever is scaring the guppies is just wearing a ghost costume.
I'd let's build a trap of almost everything we need.
This is not going to work, Fred.
This is a list of all the things we need to build our trap.
We'll just need to get a trident, a wheel for the baby buggy,
a mock stock middle box whopper popper, a cork, and a rope for our trap to be complete.
I don't.
I can't sneeze on stream.
I don't know what's going on.
Every time I have to, it just doesn't happen.
I start thinking about it a lot and then I try to mute the microphone and it stops the sneeze.
Okay, I'm fine.
Look at all this stuff.
Are you messing up my joke?
This dude's stoned.
This chandelier is going to trap the bad guy.
All right, so we got a trap in the chandelier.
I can find a way to catch that toy napper.
Be at him.
Let me at him.
Okay, so we got to drop that.
We need to get a few tools, drop that shit on him.
What are the scissors for?
Oh, there's a frog from the first one.
Say it.
How do you look like this?
I don't know.
People ask that question all the time.
I don't.
What do you want to say?
Good thing we didn't pass up that purple sea urchin.
It might come in handy.
What do you want to say?
Oh, peanuts.
Say it's a book about untying knots.
Okay.
We may need it later.
That was fun.
Okay, I got a book.
What should I move the painting?
I'm going to move the painting.
The clock has blood all over it.
I wish I could have just done that.
Let's go down.
Hey, it's another purple sea urchin.
So I'm guessing I need four or five of these again.
Hey, open that cork.
Did you get this cork?
Two real hard...
It was air.
Air?
That's water.
Just pulling out the cork is definitely not going to work.
Well, we need a pipe, right?
Because look, this connects here.
No, we don't connect the pipe.
I like that.
Oh, a wrench.
We found a wrench.
This is a saw room.
Okay, wrench, scissors.
How to untie a knot.
Hmm.
All right, let's go back up.
Do you know, and I figured this out recently,
I had it kind of warped and wrong in my brain.
Remember I told you guys that I bet...
I don't know, whatever I bet that time.
But I said they definitely say the word gas in the saw movie
like a thousand times or something, right?
I thought, oh, the room's going to fill with gas.
No, what it actually was, and this is where I got screwed up,
is that there's a poison coursing through your veins.
There's a deadly nerve poison.
They all had poison.
Slow acting poison was what it was, not gas.
I had it wrong.
It's a slow acting poison in your blood.
So that's what I was thinking of.
I mean, people, when I said that for the first time,
some of you fucking movie transcript Andes went to every script.
You found them all and you control F'd gas
and told me that it said three times in the whole,
the 10 movie franchise.
Okay, so I'm going to go out
because I have scissors and I have a wrench.
What should I do with this stuff?
Wrench here?
It's a wrench.
No.
Control F Andes.
So what do I do with the, with this?
It's a wrench.
What do I do with this stuff?
It's a book.
These are the things we need to find to trap the ghost.
This is Huey, Dewey, and Louie.
We'll still need to get a trident, a wheel for the baby buggy,
a mock stock middle box whopper bopper,
a cork, and a rope to make our trap.
Yep.
Oh, yes it is.
All right.
The cork is down there.
The rope, I don't know.
The wheel, I don't know.
The mock stock middle box whopper bopper,
whatever that is.
And then a trident.
Okay.
So what do I take with this?
Hey, get him.
Let's go out here.
All right.
Is this a school?
I'm going to piss my pants.
I'll be right back.
At least the term of your mic is on.
We can hear you freestyling.
I'm just sitting here freestyling.
Okay.
Let's turn this off.
Back to Freddy Fish.
Why would I be sitting here doing that?
We just heard angry breathing.
Are you going to play Pajama Sam?
I don't know.
People request these games all the time as a joke.
And then when I actually play them, I go, oh, that was okay.
I don't really want to play 15 more of these.
They're cool.
They're fine.
But I don't want to play 20 Pajama Sam, Putt-Putt, and Freddy Fish games.
You know what I'm saying?
How come?
Okay.
Back to it.
You can see the wrench, right?
That's fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
So what was I doing?
I was going to...
Let's go this way.
50 community subs from Freddy Dread.
Somebody named Big C gave 52.
You guys gave a lot of subs.
Holy shit.
Who is this kid?
A science magazine and glasses to read it with.
Life is good.
I hope this is not a scenario where he loses his glasses, right?
I'm not going to hit him with what?
All right.
So what are you looking for?
You looking for something?
All right.
Let's go right.
There it is.
There's a pipe.
Yep.
Let's go pick it up.
How are we going to get you out of there?
I'm going to have to put something on my head.
That looks painful.
All right.
Well, you've screwed that up.
We're going to get some product to get you out of there or something.
Whatever.
We're going to come back.
Is he going to be alive?
This is fucked up.
There's a trident.
Bad end.
You're leaving him to die.
All right.
So how do we get the trident?
Isn't it?
It's not that looser.
The trident is being blocked by.
Do I have to get rid of the ceiling?
It's a wrench.
These are my.
Great.
I mean, this thing is already done.
This is a finished puzzle.
The kid just needs to click three times to move it.
You know what I mean?
This thing's finished.
I don't have to go too hard with this.
This shit's done.
I just need to.
Why is this a huge one?
Why is it so huge?
No, it was finished.
They finished it for me.
Why does that?
Okay.
Why is it a double?
I would be fine.
It wasn't a double.
You're over complicating it.
No, I'm not.
It's a fucking double.
Why is there a double?
I don't do that.
I hate these fucking things.
I just I every time one of these comes up,
I exit the game or I skip it.
I don't I hate it.
I just hate these things.
I hate these things.
All right.
Well, this obviously is in the wrong spot.
I hate these things.
I thought it was already done.
I overcomplicated that for myself.
We need to get four more things to make our trap.
All right.
We got the Trident.
Anything else here?
What's going on?
Oh, I thought that video was playing in the background.
Oh, let's go.
What's this?
Secret passage.
That's not.
Stop showing me other games to play.
I don't want to play that one.
I guarantee you there is videos on YouTube that are
Freddy Fish episode two.
The search for the haunted school colon brackets.
No commentary clicking on every clickable slowly.
Guaranteed.
And the video is just silent and it's just.
That probably do pretty well.
That would probably do pretty well.
Cool.
All right.
So is there anything I can do here?
I can't do anything.
I'm just going to leave.
Save the guy.
What guy?
Save what guy?
Oh, that's right.
I don't know how.
He's not moving.
What's going on?
That was apparently wrong.
Do it again.
That was so weird.
Or shoot.
Anything else here?
Was there nothing down there?
All right.
Well, there's a submarine over this way.
A lot of tools still.
I'm ready.
I'm good.
That was huge.
This is this would be fun when I was a kid.
This would be fun.
Did you play this kid?
I played putt-putt, I think, for 10 minutes.
Is this an iPad?
Wait, there's something shining down there.
Oh, it's this guy again.
It's terrible.
I'll give you a thousand dollars and never do that again.
Do it again.
The trident we're going to use to build our trap.
I've been chewing trident lately.
It didn't make my teeth a little bit better.
There's nothing here.
Oh, that's a reference to when I was younger.
And I said that at the dentist.
Do you guys even watch my stream?
That's the worst joke ever.
That is a direct reference to me at the dentist chair
when I was like fucking 12.
Remember I told you when I went to the dentist
and I told the dentist that I was chewing trident?
I made it up.
Do you guys even watch this stream?
God, I gotta go down.
Ahoy, Captain Schnitzel.
How's the submarine?
Oh, not going nowhere fast, but that's okay.
It gives me time to sing my Z diddys.
I had a girlfriend, a 2,000 pounder that's slim for a whale,
but she was a flounder.
Hey, nanny, nanny, and a hot cha cha.
You know what I just noticed?
How come every horror movie, all the horror movie antagonists,
there's always a scene every time in every one of the movies.
Every scary monster or scary person movie,
they always do this.
They go, there's a scene where it's them
and the main character is looking at them and they go,
they go like, they do the head tilt thing.
Why?
It's like, why do they keep doing that?
They do it in every fucking single movie.
May we have that rope for our trap, Captain Schnitzel?
You'll see it.
Yeah, you can take it if you can untie it.
I'm going to, I just ruined every horror movie you're going to watch now.
Have you ever been able to untie it?
When they show the bad guy or the monster or the thing,
the thing, that's the scary thing.
It is going to, it does the dog head tilt.
You're going to see it now because you're going to be looking for it
and you're going to say, what the fuck?
You just ruined the whole movie for me.
Jeepers, we're not having.
You're wrong.
Just watch it.
We need to pull on the end of the rope to untie it.
Really slow.
And then it's like a chase scene.
We need to pull on the ends of the rope to untie it.
What are you talking about?
I just did it.
Keep going.
Keep going like this and the rope will be untied in no time.
Looks like this way.
Wait, what?
What's going on?
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
This is where we are now.
Now keep going.
Good work.
Yay.
Now we have the rope we need for our trap.
We need three more things to make our ghost trap.
That is literally only in Halloween.
No, it is not.
Look, I don't have to be right right now.
I can be right like two months from now when you figure it out.
I don't have to be right right now.
Every time Michael Myers tilts his head.
It's other movies too.
It's not just Michael Myers.
Everybody does it because it's a reference to Michael Myers.
Whatever it is, I keep seeing it.
All right, so we're good.
We're good.
I made a stop motion animation and I had my monster do that.
Laughing my ass off.
That's what I'm saying.
My favorite thing about this stream is you can leave for half an hour
and Gerber will still be talking about the same thing when you get back.
It's been five minutes.
Look, I'm the captain.
Are you okay?
I'll be okay.
Just feeling a little buggy right now.
Luther, I think you hit on something.
Yes, unfortunately, it was something very hard.
No, that wheel will be perfect for a trap.
I need a wheel.
Luther, we'll need to find a way to loosen this bolt so we can get the wheel.
Chat, I got a wrench.
Try this, Luther.
The game is too rough.
It has to be.
So you can hear the voice acting.
We did it.
Is that oil?
Pick that up.
This is going to get the pipe.
It looks like we struck oil.
Non-toxic biodegradable oil to be exact.
So how do you like it?
I call it the wet look.
Just toss the oil over here.
We can go save the turtle.
Very cool.
Nice.
Nice, dude.
All right, let's go save the turtle.
I almost have all the things.
I'm going to get the pipe and then I got the rope.
What do I do with the scissors?
Imitate the sound effects.
I'll try for the next two minutes.
I'll try to imitate the sounds.
That's enough.
Yeah, a drop of oil might do the trick.
Someone just wrote.
That's enough.
They were right.
I felt the same way.
Oh my gosh!
No head to clean up.
It's not in here.
Poor Tucker.
I hope he gets a head in life
because he sure doesn't have one now.
Sure I do.
It was just stuck in my shell.
Are we glad you're okay.
Thanks to you kids.
There's nothing like the smell of a brand new shell.
I'm glad we could help you.
Back to that room with the cork in it.
Put the pipe there.
Get the cork.
And then we need one more item.
I don't know what to do with this guy.
Something about science.
Last week I invented a pocket protector.
This week I'm inventing the pocket.
Okay, so now I got to go into the school and it's down.
There he is.
Oh wait, he puts something up.
What's up?
Cool.
All right, through here.
Pipe, cork.
Then I'll have all the items, right?
I think I'll have all the items.
This pipe would fit great where that cork is.
I don't know Freddy.
It'll end up small.
It'll fit.
Just do it.
Okay, so now what do I need?
There's only one more thing we need to build our pizza list
that shows what we need to build our trap.
I need the Mockstock Mibblebock Whopper Bopper to make our trap.
Where am I supposed to get that?
A Mockstock Wibblebopper.
Oh, these guys again.
Yes, Squidfather.
We know you never had a toy in your whole life, but...
But we can't get you any until the kids are out of the classroom.
Well, the kids haven't left yet because of that Freddy fish.
Yes, Squidfather.
No more excuses.
We'll do what we gotta do.
I thought that was an egg.
It was a cat.
We gotta get rid of those kids.
I thought it was a fried egg.
All right, we got...
We gotta go this way.
Out and then find...
Where is this other thing?
Oh, where would you be?
Okay, you look for a rope that's holding something up.
A trident in a statue.
A wheel that's on a car or on the...
Where am I supposed to...
A Mockstock Mibblebopper.
But that's not a real thing.
Where would I find this?
Where were this even supposed to be?
I'm gonna get close.
Get the nerd to invent it.
That's probably what you have to do.
It's definitely this way.
Whoa, that was cool.
Where is it?
Oh, I have to jump like bump, bump, bump, bump, bump.
All right, here and then to here and then to...
Where am I trying to go?
I didn't know what I was trying to do.
I didn't know it was supposed to go that way.
Dude, where the hell is this thing?
What'd you get?
There was a skateboard in there.
We're going so far away.
Holy shit.
Zoomer nursery.
Not this shit again.
Shoot.
All right, this is where I gotta get the thing, right?
Should I do it again?
All right, I'll do it two more times.
That's it.
I can't reach.
Where's my mouse?
All right, last one.
No, I'm done.
That was kind of fun.
So where's this thing?
Don't you feel like I went a really long way to not get this thing?
This way?
That was kind of fun.
All right, I'm gonna go in.
You should play Club Penguin.
Oh, all right, let's go.
Hi, Mr. Triple Finn.
Hey, kids.
Why doesn't an octopus jog?
Why?
It has to tie four pairs of shoes.
So just get four.
Just get eight shoes.
That's not even a joke.
Just get eight sneakers and you can run.
I don't get it.
Sitting on my porch.
Nothing could be finer.
Chef may be eating at Eddie's or you can eat diner.
The food there is healthy and it tastes good to me.
You know, I only wish that it could be free.
That was cute.
So what do you need?
We have three.
We have it's a list.
What do fish use for money?
I think I know this one.
Sand dollars.
I thought so.
These?
How guppy who'd hoop and holla.
He had a fine young seahorse by the name of Sand dollar.
He'd ride into town with his 10 gallon hat,
but nobody knew his name.
As a matter of fact, I'm having a good time.
I'm just kind of chilling.
This is fun.
I'm just chilling.
The stream activated my acid reflux.
I would just eat.
Hi, kids.
What can I do you for?
Hey, Ray.
How's business?
You probably heard that I am now a collector of fine new and used trophies
and I'm trading one of the specialty item.
A mock stock middle box.
I gotta move on.
I gotta play another game.
A very hot item, I might add.
I was like about to yawn.
It was like.
This is way under my cost, but since you're such swell looking kids,
I'll let you have it for one slightly used trophy.
Trophy?
I think we could probably find a used trophy.
Where do I get a trophy?
I don't have a trophy.
Fuck you.
Casino.
That's not a casino.
It's a movie theater.
I think it is.
Should we go to the movies?
Movies.
Flashing lights or a casino in my brain.
All right, let's go to the movies.
All right, let's see.
Yes, I'm actually now.
I'm excited again.
We get to watch movies.
I love going to the theater.
Freddie, do I like the next movie?
Yeah.
All right, Codzilla.
Action figure guy.
Roma.
Worm doodles.
Sheriff.
Goblin.
Dracula.
Fish with thing on his nose.
Bug movie.
Let's go.
It was awful.
All right, how about lightning?
How about Gatorade, the movie?
How have they not done that yet, by the way?
That one was bad too.
Chumlet.
That's two thumbs up.
That's two thumbs up for me.
Oh my god.
All right, that was funny.
All right, yeah, that one gets one thumbs up.
This is another, this is a game.
It's Canadian.
All right, these are just TikToks.
That was the whole movie.
That was the, that was the entire movie.
This is, okay, this is a scary movie.
I wonder if the character goes like this.
Curse of the sardine.
Let's go.
Okay, that was the title.
Coming to a theater.
Oh, it's a trailer.
It's a trailer.
Godfish commando.
That was dumb.
All right, worm doodles.
Worm doodle in all your favorite flavors.
Original, chocolate, sea cucumber, lemon, orange, red.
Is this Justin Roiland?
Because you gotta have them.
You gotta have them.
Worm doodle.
I like this one.
Worm doodle in all your favorite flavors.
Original, chocolate, sea cucumber, lemon, orange, red.
This reminds me, this reminds me of Justin Roiland.
Red.
Sheriff Gill.
All right, this is a town.
I don't know, I couldn't even read that.
I like the sound effects.
Luther, if we spend too long in here, we'll never trap that ghost.
Freddy, do you think they'll play the movie with that fish I like?
I don't know, Luther.
That person just ate a whole turkey.
Holy shit.
How much food does this guy have?
I have to get out of here.
I have to leave now.
I just couldn't get out.
All right, what about the pulley?
Pulley Emporium.
Break it, you buy it.
It's a big seal-cut area.
Okay.
How much is it?
Captain, found true love, you see, and had no need to sail no more.
So he stole me this here pulley.
How much does it cost?
What do I need to give you?
Well, how do I get one?
Hey Barnacle Bob, tell us about that pulley.
It's from the schooner Hesperus that sailed the wintry sea.
The skipper had taken his daughter along and she stole this here pulley to me.
I'm just going to take it.
That was cool.
I'll bet there's a neat story behind that pulley.
They're not for sale.
It says big sail on it.
It says big sail.
Come down to the sea, my friends, to the lonely sea from the sky.
From the port bow of a tall ship that sailed from Paraguay.
Okay, big sail.
Great stories abound in your pulley Emporium.
Just point to a pulley and I'll tell you some more of them.
This business is a fucking flop, man.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's go up to the hall of fame.
Oh, there's a look.
Look at Freddie.
Aren't you scared of the ghost?
No, not really.
I don't need these anymore.
King Crab donated his pearls to build this hall of fame.
Trophy.
Tina Tuna held her breath above water for 13 minutes.
Sturgeon won four gold medals in the all-ocean powerlifting competition.
Cool.
All right, give me the trophy.
That's the trophy I won for the deep sea spelling bee.
I was going to pick it up after school today.
Darn, the trophy case is locked.
So open it.
I wonder who we could get the combination from.
Oh, come on.
Hey, I think this fell off the back of the lock.
From the key with the glasses?
It says to get the combination to this lock, show this card to Mr. Triplefin.
So if we show this card to Mr. Triplefin, he'll give us the combination.
Who?
Hello, sir.
You're a genius.
Who's Mr. Triplefin?
I know.
So that trophy case is locked.
Repeatedly jiggling the handle is just an exercise in futility.
Who's that?
It's a guy with a guitar.
I gotta go all the way back there.
Shit.
That's not Triplefin.
Somebody said this is straw ass all over again.
All right, we gotta go this way.
Please play Spy Fox and Pajama Sam.
I'm gonna treat these like animes.
I'm gonna watch one every year.
I'll do one every year.
All the way.
Where was it?
Down?
Where was that guy with the guitar?
We're gonna play unpacking after this.
Did I just come from here?
Not this guy.
No, I'm in the wrong place.
Where the hell do I need to go?
I'm gonna play Madden 09.
No, where was it?
It was to the right?
No, it was up that way, right?
I think it was this way.
I'm gonna go around.
Oh, yeah, this is a huge pain in the ass.
He hates Madden 09.
Yeah, I probably do.
All right, all the way down.
Then we're finally gonna get our last thing
and then we're gonna be able to complete this video game.
I'm not gonna let that phony go scare me.
The Freddy Fish Trilogy series.
Please don't let him scare me either, Freddy.
What's this?
Hey, you giving me the business?
Your business card, sir.
Well, so it is.
You boys will be wanting a combination to the trophy case.
Excuse me, sir, but I'm not a boy.
I'm a girl.
Hey, that's a coincidence.
So is Mrs. Triple Finn.
Thanks for the combination, Mr. Triple Finn.
This says a combination to the lot.
The Barbie Fashion Show PC 2004.
No, we're not just gonna pull up every single old
point and click kids game from 1995 to 2002.
We're not doing that.
This was a direct special request
because it was somebody's birthday, okay?
You wanna know the truth?
It was somebody's birthday.
This was a birthday present
for the person that requested it on their birthday.
This is a birthday present.
So there it is.
Cat's out of the bag.
This was a birthday present
and it's not your birthday.
So somebody in chat is probably going like,
wait, was it me?
I requested this on my birthday.
Is unpacking a good game?
I feel like I've played it for like 10 minutes.
It's my birthday.
Can you watch porn on stream?
What a bizarre.
Oh yeah, we're gonna fulfill a birthday request.
I'm gonna go watch porn on stream,
but it's their birthday.
Okay, let's go.
I bet we can get this lock open now.
Five, six, seven.
We have all the infinity stones.
We can make the trap.
Gee, it looks expensive.
Looks like it's made out of gold.
No, Luther, the trophy isn't gold.
Critique stream would be hilarious.
I don't think you understand what happens
if that stream is live.
I go away.
All right, I got everything.
Let's do it.
Give me the super duper thingy.
I know how much that trophy meant to you.
It's okay, Luther.
I remember how special it was to win it,
and that's what really matters.
Freddy just got ripped off.
Let's go catch that ghost.
All right, let's get the ghost.
This is it.
This is the culmination of the whole entire series.
We're ready to make our trap, Luther.
Are we trying to kill this guy?
That's just about everything.
Luther, can we use your toy as bait?
Well, okay.
Our trap is complete.
Hey, boss, look.
A toy.
Let's grab it.
It's these two.
It's Freddy, bitch.
And Luther.
Whoa, we got him.
We got him.
Could you two scare the poor little guppies
and steal their toys?
It's the two sharks.
What the fuck?
What?
Whoa.
These gotta hold up.
They still do.
Here, give this to the squid father.
He should have at least one toy.
Well, we're giving the toy where...
Isn't this just enabling that bad behavior?
Luther, let's take these toys back to the...
Isn't the whole point of this that
they were sending the bad guys to go steal the toy
and we just gave the toy to them at the end?
Hooray.
We solved the mystery, Mrs. Croaker.
There wasn't really a ghost haunting the school.
It was just those sharks pretending to be a ghost.
Congratulations.
You saved the school.
The messages to share.
Okay, I understand the messages to share,
but they're trying to kill us.
Selfish.
These guys are dressing up in a costume
talking about how they were going to get us
and trying to like come and scare the kids and shit.
I'm missing out on clicking stuff.
How dare you guys say that to me?
I can't.
Somebody said the moral of the story is to...
I can't even fucking read it.
The moral of the story is to stomp the bad guys' teeth
into their brains.
No, that's not what I said either, by the way.
That's not what I said.
That is not what I said either.
The moral of the story is fucking consumerism.
Stop clicking.
That's what you do in this game.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
What's in that?
Oh, magical gold.
The moral of the story is I want all the toys for myself.
Everybody coming over here with a toy is not mine.
Give me that toy.
What is it?
I want it.
Watch out.
Give me that skull.
Give me that one.
The whole thing.
Give me that.
Pop that.
I don't want anyone to play with me.
Pop it.
What's this?
Cheap shit.
Get it out of here.
Do that again.
Okay, I'm done.
Do you want to start the game all over?
No.
That was fun.
That was Freddy Fish 2.
The curse of the mean antagonists that continue to cause a problem.
In Freddy Fish 3, they'll be stealing the fucking pie off the sill.
See you next time.
We're gonna play the other game.
That was fun.
That was actually really, I liked it.
Legendary boring stream.
You almost just got me to hiss into the camera, which would change your mind.
But no, I'm just hanging out playing kids games.
It doesn't matter.
I was gonna hiss at you.
Remember, you're 36.
All right, you guys ready?
We're gonna move on.
We are gonna play Unpacking.
It's a game where I have to, I think, decorate a room.
I'm looking very much forward to it.
It's gonna be such a chill, relaxing stream.
I recommend you have it in another tab.
Maybe just sit back, relax, maybe have a little bit of snack.
We'll go for it.
Let's go.