Oh, there's a typical day in Team Fortress 2. Let's go outside.
Oh, there's a sentry right there. Oh, that's pretty cool.
I have another sentry. Oh, pretty sick.
Oh, wait, we got a third sentry over there.
Let's just keep going. I mean, there can't be more than that.
There can't be like a fourth sentry over here.
I mean, it is like a dispenser.
I mean, there's another sentry going up over here right now.
We have seven engineers.
Seriously, like Dust Bowl in a nutshell.
Oh my god. No one's gonna be able to even get over here.
You know, they don't even need me.
I don't even have to be here right now.
There's seven engineers on this team.
All I have to do is just stand over here.
Just stand in between the dispensers and just watch.
Yay. Come on. Come on.
Oh, they got a sentry.
Oh, the spy.
That's not fair. I hit him right in his face.
I don't know how I didn't hit that spy.
This guy's just healing me.
He wants me to get this taunt kill. So bad.
Did you guys just see that spy?
Dude, that guy missed like four backstab attempts in a row.
Oh my. I just killed the whole team.
Oh my god. I just killed like the whole team.
Look at the chat.
Wow. That was so dumb.
I just killed the entire team.
Well, this whole team is really mad about that.
I would probably be too.
I would be livid about that one.
All right, guys.
We're going to be playing the frog pyro.
Let's go. Let's do it.
Okay, guys.
We're going to play the frog pyro.
Let's go. Let's go.
It's to die.
Blow yourself up on me.
I didn't even need to do that.
Now they're pushed back.
There's one.
There's two.
Let's try it.
Come on. Don't.
Don't.
Ladies and gentlemen, here comes the spy.
Here comes the spy.
My name is spy.
Your name is spy.
You got me.
But you didn't.
No.
Well, well.
Oh, geez.
Oh, Jesus.
You just shot me.
You fucker.
We only got 10 seconds.
What?
What is this guy doing?
We just did it.
We just did it good.
That's how we do a little bit of zhuzh.
That's how we zhuzh it up.
Want to see some zhuzh?
You want to see some zhuzh?
You ready?
Here we go.
Zhuzh.
I'm going to zhuzh this guy up.
Got him.
This guy needs a zhuzh.
This demo man around this corner is getting zhuzh'd.
I zhuzh'd him, but the medic saved his life.
All right.
I got to zhuzh somebody before this is over.
Somebody's got to get zhuzh'd.
You got to zhuzh him up.
Here we go.
Zhuzh him up right here.
I could have zhuzh'd.
How did I miss that headshot?
Somebody explain it to me.
I want to get a calculated mathematician
to explain to me why you're being a real dick right now.
That was funny.
What the?
I just can't stop eating these.
What are you eating?
Fiber one bars.
Stop eating fiber one bars.
Why are you doing that?
I've only had two.
I had one last night though.
You were going to get such a compacted shit.
It's not going to even be funny.
They're so good.
You are going to crap out like a cement block.
I need to get these but not as fiber bars.
I know they make them.
It's okay.
We're getting spawn camped right now.
Don't worry, Star.
We're getting spawn camped.
And you're not even here to help.
I'm not worried.
So those of you guys that are watching right now,
we're on Dust Bowl.
You're not even going to use this clip.
Why not?
Because I'm not in the video.
So I could just like cut you out.
I might even be talking to nobody right now, guys.
So Star was never fucking even here.
Psycho.