Welcome ladies and gentlemen to Shadow of Mordor. A game so real and so new that
it could be only described as brand new. So today in this video we're hi you're
just not gonna hit me I don't know what you think you think you're gonna be able
to hit me but you're just like a fucking weak little grunt shithead if I were you
I would just run but you're not running you got persistence I will give you that
you know what I want to know what you know tell me what you know
This one time in the first grade I stole peanuts from my classmate and I got grounded for two weeks and then in the fourth grade I threw a rock through a window and I blamed it on my sister I felt so guilty ever since I just can't sleep at night and then in the ninth grade I fell asleep at my job and I threw them in my boss's bed and I tried to let them know I just didn't
I hate the guys that have the A you gotta jump over them really just like sucks
because I'm so used to hitting Y. This guy's just like lobbing rocks over here. He just crushed that guy. What a dick. Oh no here he comes for real. Where are these guys all going? What's going on here? Why is it like a huge trail of people? Is they chasing after this one guy?
Hold on I need to get a better view of this. One dude's running away from all these dudes. Are you serious? It takes that many of you? What happens when they catch this guy? No. No. You can make it. Keep going. How far are they going to chase this guy? Why is nobody paying attention to me?
Which one is it? It's this one right here. Yeah this is the guy. This guy's killed me like at least two or three times. I really really need to get my revenge on this guy. What is he? Can be killed instantly using stealth. Everything else don't even like attack him. So I'm going to sneak up behind this guy and stick my sword in his fucking ear.
Where are you? There he is. There's that piece of shit. Gorfell Thinbones. What's up guys? Are you here to help me? Why are you guys sneaking too? Where are you guys sneaking to? What? Why? Why are you doing that? There was no...
Okay Thinbones. Then don't get distracted. Get distracted. Will you just fuck off? I'm trying to do something. Like there was two other people sneaking around. I've been seeking you out you son of a bitch.
I've been seeking you out. I'm going to get my revenge. Just you wait and see. Sneak around the corner. I know how easy you can be killed from behind. I read the instruction booklet. I read the instructional leagues.
Yeah. This is what we do. Don't look at me. Don't pay attention to me. Just get insta-killed. Just get insta-killed. Get instantly killed. Revenge is mine and I will be taking that sword. Yes with my magical hammer of justice. Revenge is mine.
Come on little doggy. We've got to get to grandmother's house. Over the river and through the woods to grandmother's house we go. I love how you can just jump over ledges like what's going on?
Look what you did to me. There will be no mercy this time. I did not just beat this guy like not that long ago. I did kill this guy. This is the Bone Arrow guy. This is the Thinbones man. Well he's dead now. No actually that's him killing my mount.
Alright well why do I have to kill this guy again? I already did this. This is like the... Not this time. You fucking pile of garbage. You piece of fucking crap. This guy is my fucking real nemesis. You want to see the nemesis system in full effect?
Oh no. No no no no no please don't. Just give me another chance to fucking... Give me another fucking chance!
I've got one of your friends. Don't you know? I will kill him. I will kill your friend. I will murder him. Apparently none of you care.
What about this guy? He's one of your friends isn't he? Don't you want to protect him instead? Oh I guess not as well because he's fucking dead. What about this guy? He's your fat friend. Sometimes you...
I can't believe this. Why even fight them? They'll just kill each other. How many of them are they gonna... You're spearing your fucking best friend in the nuts right now. How do you not understand the complications of what you're doing?
And this is what you get for doing that by the way. You get punished forever. What about you? What do you know about the secrets of Mordor?
I'm a secret spy working with Gandalf. Don't kill me. I'm on your side. I'm in the nuts of my head.