Oh, oh god, this is the best item they've ever put in the game. I need this. I need it.
Yeah, this is a pretty good spot on the beach. Just being like a fat motherfuckers sitting here drinking my beer.
Oh my god, I don't have to do anything.
Look at this soldier down here. He's like, what is going on up there? Oh, oh no, oh shit. Hey.
This looks like a pretty good spot.
Come on, somebody come up the stairs.
Somebody on red team come check this area. Because like what could possibly be going on up here besides
He just like turned.
This guy is just like, oh.
I love this game so much. Valve, seriously? Seriously, you guys have like outdone yourselves.
Please come back and kill me. I'm so useless.
How many kills can I get? We're just sitting down in a chair. There's one.
I moved it down here, set up the chair. Let's see. If I get more than two or three kills, then this is just like absurd.
Spice up in my shaw, damn it. I gotta get up off my seat now. Oh, that's a bunch of bullshit.
You know building centuries is sure is tough work.
A lot of people don't realize the amount of craftsmanship that goes into making one of these things.
Where you need the right kind of aluminum alloy metal. That takes a while to get and it's very stressful.
You got all kinds of scouts fucking with you. Can't you see how busy I am right now?
That's a spy. That's a spy.
Did I really just do something? I just blocked a spy from walking through.
Why didn't he attack me? I feel like I'm watching a movie.
Don't you feel like he's at a movie theater and he's seeing the projector in front of him?
Yes, it's a pretty good show. I think I've seen better though.