I think we're like 20% of the way through this contract. I apologize. I was gonna start the video a while ago and it was gonna be a- I only play as the classic!
But I ended up like killing two people and then like didn't record and then like started recording.
So now we're really recording and there's a guy in the water. I gotta get this guy. He's fucking dead. Guy's dead.
Alright, well, welcome to the video, guys, where we shoot fucking people in the water that have been dead for like 20 minutes.
Can I kill this guy? I know it wasn't a headshot, but this is going a lot faster than I initially thought it was going to go.
See if I can get a no scope here. There we go. If I do that a few more times, the contract will be finished.
I was under the impression that it was gonna be like, oh man, it's gonna take like fucking two hours.
I missed that one. This is a good place to sit though. No, it's not because there's spies that come behind you.
What an irritated beginning to this video. I sound really irritated. Do I sound really irritated right now?
Well, let's get rid of that. Let's like shake off the irritation. Hold on. Still irritated.
As you can tell, I was still a little irritated. I gotta cast off the spell that is the irritation.
And how we do that is I no scope the first guy that I see and then all of a sudden like I'm gonna be fine, you know?
First person I see literally that comes in this doorway is going to wipe my slate clean. This guy, right? This guy. Ready? Ready? Ready? Ready?
Still irritated. No, that wasn't a headshot. Still slightly irritated. No, I'm not allowed to do that.
Uh, I'll get him. I'll get him. I like didn't even let go. I'll get him. Come here.
I was hoping I was gonna like luckily shoot him right in the face. I'm being so useless right now. Please. Please.
I know I'm still a little upset. I can't get it off. I got a headshot this guy. I've got to get this guy right now.
Come on. I'm in the right spot for this. And he's pistoling me. This guy's pistoling me and I can't even shoot him.
Oh, how irritating. What just happened? Oh, right.
I'm so focused on the top stairs. I just have total tunnel vision. I had tunnel vision on sniper without being zoomed in.
Wait for it. Wait for it. It's the releasing the button on the finger is what's giving me the finger. Get away from me.
I don't know. I promise I'm not a spy. Come on down here. Show me. Show me your face. I'd love to see it.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. He went to the point. He went to the point. He went to the point. How?
I don't know what happened today. Did I like, did somebody spit in my coffee today? Like, why am I this like irritable? I shouldn't be.
Maybe I like woke up on the wrong side of the bed. That's pop. Oh, guys, I feel like a new man.
Hey, you know that you feel like a new man. Well, that I feel, you know, I feel like a new man right now. Let's play some Team Fortress 2.
My coffee was like my coffee was really good this morning. Nobody's spitting.
Nobody definitely spit in my coffee this morning. This weapon is fucking impossible to use.
This weapon is so hard to use. Holy fuck. If this weapon wasn't the worst weapon in the whole game, I would have killed that guy.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Don't get irritated again. This is going to be a good place to finish this up.
That is a spy that you are a spy. Perfect opportunity. Fuck me, man. He's going to get backstabbed.
There's nothing and I could have prevented that. Don't don't do it. Do you see how long that took?
That took so long to be able to headshot that guy. That guy did a little dance and ducked out of the corner.
And then by the time he came back, I was ready to shoot him. It's a long charge up time.
I lowered my sensitivity a shitload to try to compensate for my mom, my fucking lord.
I have to concentrate so much while I do this. I feel like I'm taking a math test.
Did I get a good grade on my ultra concentrate math exam? Fucking Algebra 2, whatever the hell it is.
This is this is the opportunity where this gun is supposed to shine around a corner like that.
Only got to do that a couple more times. You know, we got a good opportunity right here.
Come on, bring it on. I'll shoot you through the fucking laundry chute.
No spies, no spies. I can almost be done with this contract. I thought the flowers, I thought those were stickies on the red team.
Freaks me out for a second. That's me. That's me. I almost didn't understand what was going on.
I just had an out of body experience.
Screw it. I'll hit you with the ham.
Going underneath that thing. I got like bumped my head.
That's it. We're done. We're done. We are done. We're done. We're done.
I got it. We're done. Contract over.
For good measure, we're just gonna sit in the fucking water. Why am I still on fire? Come on, please submerge.
We're done. Give me my box. Give me my box.
What do I got? I want to see what I get. Come on. Have it be something good. Something good.
Congratulations. You have just been given the opportunity to spend $2.50.
Fuck it. We're doing it.
Yes, I'm sure. I'm sure. Let's see. Was this worth it? Was it worth it? What's inside?
Holy shit. Holy shit. Okay. That's worth it. That's factory new purple ranges. That's... Oh my fucking lord.
And it's a sniper. My mood just went from irritated and upset and annoyed into...
Alright. Okay. I got factory new purple range. I'm not even close to being irritated anymore.