Hey, what's up everybody? Hey, what's up everybody?
What's up guys? Hey, what's going on? Hey, what's going on guys?
Oh, oh my god. Oh my god. Hi guys. How you doing? I'm not late. I'm here. I'm fine.
He's practicing. Yeah, he's practicing. I had to get the intro right. I had to get it right,
but the mic was hot. Anyways, hello. How you doing? But he lied about Megamind.
No, I did not lie about Megamind. It was a great movie. Uh, okay. Yeah, I'm going to give you a
synopsis. Fine. It's a blue, uh, evil guy who's an orphan sent to earth. Part of this other guy,
Metro Man. What do you mean? What do you mean? Tell us. Tell us. That's what I'm telling you.
That there was, he makes hell. Space Dad, isn't it? I, it was, it was okay. I like the big ending
parade that they did. Dude, the spoilers. What I did like the most about the movie was when he
turned himself into the police. He turned himself in and imprisoned himself. Just like Rick from
Rick and Morty did in that episode in season two. They put on a nice disguise. That's a holographic
disguise. And then Hal actually at the end, you know, the fucking evil computer. It was a fine
movie. I give it like a B plus. Okay. There was no evil computer. What are you talking about?
Hal from, it's an evil computer. He lied. There is no evil computer. What? Yes, there is.
That's Space Odyssey. It was a fun movie. It was a fun movie. I like the, at the end when everybody's
dancing and the guy's in there and he's got like the orange suit on and he's dancing. Look,
it doesn't matter if you think I watched it or not. I've seen it. I did see it. Anyways,
it doesn't matter. Hey, welcome. We're going to play Fable II again. Hope everyone's having a good
day. I'm ready to play. I'm ready to go. I have to tweet this though. I'll be right back. To the,
to the guy that said, I have really boring tweets. You're really not going to like this one.
It's so boring. That was really boring. I just said more Fable II and that's it. I didn't say
anything else. Use the GIF. I don't even have the GIF on my computer or my phone or anything.
Why are you giving 50 community subs? You don't even know if the stream is going to be any good
or not. That's so much money to give. That's too much money to give. What if the stream sucks?
That's so much money. Thank you. Zap X. Thanks to 50 community subs.
Nah, thanks though. I appreciate that. That's too much money.
Way too much money to give one single human. Remember, you act humble so you can get more
money. It's a conspiracy. It's all just an act. You know, it's like really, all right,
this is real. I'm going to do a real talk with you guys here. Yeah, like it doesn't matter how
much like somebody says like, oh, you know, like, thanks. I don't like, don't need it. Don't want
it though. Like, like you never know who's just fucking with you. You know what I mean? You just
never know who's like, just lying to you. I get it. I get it. I could sit here and be like,
oh man, don't, no, don't do that. Don't do that, man. But like, oh, thank you. Thank you. Give me
more. Like there are people that are like that. It's like, how could you ever trust anybody?
I get it. No, I completely get you. Don't worry. Well, thanks though. Appreciate it. Thank you.
Oh, so true. Oh, so true. Yeah. He's farming like the so trues now. That's the next conspiracy.
Be honest for this. Even if I am honest, it doesn't matter. Okay. Let's go play a fable too.
It's fun. I have a confession to give you guys though. I may, I may have blacksmithed
like 20 minutes before the stream started. I wanted to get it out of the way because I didn't
want to just blacksmith for like the first 20 minutes of the stream. I just sat there in silence
getting like an extra 10 grand. Okay. We're of course going to do that again, but I at least
removed one 20 minute portion of the stream where is it going to be blacksmithing. And I also noticed
the weapons dealer here, the blacksmith here has a 50% off sale right now. It's a bargain at that
price. So I don't know why I just thought he was going to say it's a me Mario. I don't know why
every time it's a me. I don't know why that's what I thought he was going to say that items on sale.
Okay. So everything's 50% off. So I'm going to buy everything. Look at this 20. This is a $4,000
sword. I'm going to get it for half off. Look at steel flintlock rifle, 2,400 bucks. I'll take it.
What are you going to do with the sword? With half a sword? What are you talking about?
Oh, I get it. That's funny. Okay. And then what else do I need? Yeah. I got a gun. Okay. Now what
about who, anybody, you sell clothes here? Iron Axe is best. What do you mean best? 37
iron. Oh yeah. Sell this. Wait, wait. He's 50% off. I'm selling. Why am I selling this for 50% off?
That's not how this, I don't come to this guy and say, oh, by the way, I see the sign. You have a
50% off sale. Me too. What? That's not how that works. God damn it. Whatever. I'll just go sell
it next door to like the other guy. Yes. Ask questions about my daughter. What, who's this guy?
Kiernan the Traveler? Wait, is this my son? Kiernan the Time Traveler? Oh shit. All right. Now I
demand it. All right. Fine. I'll start. See? There we go. All right. So now I've got, I want to go to,
I want to get some new clothes. Alvin, that's my dog. Okay. I want to go. I want to get some new
clothes. Where's the tailor? Who sells clothes here? Do more blacksmithing. No, I'm not going
to do more blacksmithing. Oh my God. What is going on here? 50 more community subs. What are you guys
doing? From Video Vivi. Thanks for the 50 community subs. Again, another person. Thank you a lot.
Thank you a lot. All right. I got a bunch of pies. I have to stay fat. Important. I know for a fact
that there's a demon door in this game somewhere. Then we have to find it. Okay. Hi. Here we go.
Let's go do, I want the tailor. There's like a potion person. Why doesn't he not say community
subs anymore? I got tired. That got tired. What does that mean? I heard there's a sale, but there's
not a real bargain or anything. What do you mean there's no bargain? That's a fine item.
I'm just going to buy all these, these cheat codes. There you go. Come back anytime.
Alvarine strength potion. Oh shit. These are expensive, but I want them. There you go. That's
a fine item. Look at this. Uh, I'm going to get a healing potion too. Java potion, healing points.
Yep. That's a fine item. It's no longer a community anymore. There you go. There you go.
That's a fine item. There you go. All right. Here we go. Face cam pretty please. Nope. No face cam.
I don't do face cam. I'm a non face cam streamer. All right. I'm going to do a bunch of this.
I wish there was a quick menu. Like I remember the reviews of this game all saying that going
like seven sub menus in or like three sub menus in to click on an item was horrible.
It's a riot. Why are you writing? I'm not going to try. I don't want face cam on. No,
you're not getting it. No face cam because you're naked. How I am clothed in the
comfortable privacy of my own house is how I'm going to be. And that's final. I can be as nude
or non nude in my home as I want to be. This town is becoming more exclusive by the day.
It really is naked. I'm not naked, but that doesn't mean that I could be.
So don't be shocked. It couldn't be whatever the right way to say that.
All right. Concentrated XP. Now let's make some moves here. Okay. I got a lot of skills. Hello.
Oh, that's my wife. You don't romance me like you used to. Shit. Um, need any assistance?
Oh man. She's not happy at all. Don't worry. I'll just do a bunch of emotes.
That's just wonderful. My good one. Yes. Oh, I can't game it. Come on. Do it.
Why am I naked? I'm not naked, but I could choose to be if I choose. So right now I could,
understand. All right. We're good.
The fecal funny. Stop saying that. It's a, it's an incredibly important
emote in the game. Don't you get it? Okay. I'm leaving. Now let me level up.
Just be happy that I actually off stream did all this bullshit.
Okay. So I can do have about like nine, 10,000 blades. Three is 16,000. I think I'm going to
wait for blades three, but I could probably do health, right? What the fuck level,
level five shock. Everything else level one. Hmm. How about skilled? Okay. I could do speed
or accuracy. Yeah. I want to accurate because the guy, I have a cool gun.
What about dexter styles aimed ranged attack? Oh shit. I want to do that. I definitely want
to do that. Brutal styles. This is flat. We'll get this flourishes. You've learned the brutal
style flourish while holding X, move your L toward an enemy to build up an unblockable flourish and
then release X to unleash the flourish. Yeah. Cool. All right. Let's go. I got what I wanted.
Did you watch mega mind? Yes. And I agree with fucking, um, uh, what are the, um,
robert and I, okay. I agree with Ebert and robert who said that it was two thumbs way up.
Who were the people that review the movies? Cisco and Ebert. No, but like, but it was Cisco
and Ebert. Then it was Ebert and robert. Yeah, it was the Ebert and robert. I didn't, I didn't make
somebody else. What are you talking about? That's a real, what are you talking about? All right.
Let's go. I'm not, I'm ready to go. Quest. What should I do? Notholes Island, big freeze,
Donkey Kong country level, the temple of shadow gain entry to the temple. Wait, temple of shadow.
That sounds evil. The summoners, two idiots have read from the Necronomicon, the book of the
extremely dead, the gates of the nether world have opened the archeologist make donations at the
temple of light or go to the sculptor. Let me go to the sculptor. Prove you aren't high and naked.
When could I ever prove that I'm not high and naked? What are you talking about?
You want me to have like a face cam on my body and have like a drug test in the same room? What
are you talking about? Why do I hear the somebody after me? Why is this person after me? What's
going on? Hey, no, no, not in front of the shit statue. Come on. This is humiliating.
1600 gold. What you have been charged with murder times three. It's just, okay. Imagine getting
like a ticket and they write murder X three on it. Uh, and I'm community service or all right,
I'll pay it here. I take the money and leave me alone.
Going to like Walt Disney world and like the sculpture of Disney in front of the right and
like in the garden is him holding his butt screaming while he's shitting his pants.
Oh, like the magic of Walt Disney world. He's screaming while like he's shitting into his
hands. Okay. Well, there it is. 12 minutes of blacksmithing to atone for the wave to do another
one. How many of these do I have to do? Should it just all be me shitting my pants? You wish to
model for me again. I mean, why would I put these everywhere? What's wrong with me? Mission of statue
50 gold. That's it. You can become a monument for the whole world to admire. All right. Well,
let's do it. Literally ancient Rome. Oh, you know what to do. Okay. Begin posing. I can't fart this
one. Anything you like, but remember to hold it until I tell you to. Can I do it with my ex?
No, no, no. Come on. Come on. Come on. No, the stupid sub menu. Yes. Your technique is
please. You must hold your pose until I say so. Not a moment earlier.
Yeah. All right. Come on. Yes. Your technique is astounding.
I hope you can sustain this performance. Okay. No, no, no. You stopped too soon.
How long do I have to do that for? Yes. Your technique is astounding. Hope you can sustain
this performance. Keep it up. Okay. I have never seen such modeling just a bit longer.
Okay. That's another like holding my ass, shitting in my hand statue. Never mind. It
shall have to do. Is it going to be everywhere? Wait for my work any longer. I want the aliens
to find us eventually. I mean, like in 500 years, I don't want, by the way, I don't want any recorded
history. The only thing I want is I want like 15 statues of me holding my ass screaming. That's
the only thing that I want. Like 100 generations in front of us to look back and be like, why did
they, what was this for? Change pants? No. All right. So that was easy. Let's do, um,
summoners. Oh, jobs. Uh, let's do, let's do the summoners. These two idiots that, uh,
or the hero. Now let's do a hero of will. Let's do the hero of will.
Didn't I say I was going to do this stuff? I was going to keep like progressing the story.
You erected the same statue in the same town. What? There you are. I believe the second of our
heroes, the mage is in Brightwood. There is a powerful will user there called Garth.
Do you remember that name? He was there the night Lucien killed Rose. You didn't tell me that. How
are we supposed to trust him? Garth believed Lucien's interest in the old kingdom was purely
academic like his own. And Lucien already on Garth thought Garth was merely a brilliant scholar.
When each learned the truth about the other, their partnership ended
violently. You will find Garth in Brightwood. I have seen a vision of him toiling on some ancient
technology there. All right, let's go. Surely he intends to stop Lucien, but he cannot do so without
help. You can do a Necronomicon stream. No, that's terrifying.
I already have enough like problems. Opening and reading from the Necronomicon is like, well,
um, now I'm going to haunt your fucking house. The hero of will go to Brightwood. Oh, I haven't
found this location yet. Okay. Well, let's go. My father thought his faith would protect him from
the world. I won't make the same mistake. Let's go. This fable2.com bullshit.
Websites didn't even exist back then. Are we having fun, Jeremy dear? Yes. This was 2008, 2009.
Websites didn't even exist. Websites were created in like 2013 or something.
Your YouTube channel was in 2011. I was ahead of the curve. You know how NASA had the internet
before everyone else did? It was me. Ooh, I like that. Ooh, I like this gun. What was the first
website? It was www.hamsterdance.com. Don't. Oh, they're just shooting at each other.
Are these guys bad? Who's a bad, are these bad guys?
Do I help? I'm helping. Don't accidentally. Why am I, why is the guard mad at me for this?
Oh, that was cool. Why are they mad about this? This is pissing them off. I'm helping you guys.
What's, I don't understand. Stop right there. They don't like magic. What'd you find? You find
something? 100 million off the dead. If you sing hamster dance. I don't remember what it was. It's
no, yeah, I do. So like, what was that?
Something like that, right? And then it goes, here we go.
That's the remix, but you know, where's the dig spot? Ooh, clothing trader. Perfect. What do you
got? Flogs. I kind of want it. Did I ever get a sun vest? Shirt? Striped bandana? No. Play the song.
No. Well, okay. There it is. All right. Come on. Let's go. Where is it? There you go. Good boy. Good
boy. Good boy. Oh, the secret castle of Fairville. That's disgusting. Buried condoms? Why wouldn't I,
I would, who would pick a condom up off the ground? That is the most universal
wretched thing that anyone could see on the ground. I mean, absolutely wretched universal.
If you see that, it's like, I want to leave this whole area. I don't want to be where I am right
now. Just dump like, dump fucking alcohol all over where this is. I don't want to even be near here.
Your dog is now a two-star treasure hunter. Oh, nice. Oops. Sorry I dropped that.
That was only 150 bucks. Where's the big money? You can upgrade the dog. Oh, yeah. Dog is very
upgradable. Has he done the Armin impression yet? Not yet. Someone or something is coming my way.
I have never felt anything like it. I would say that's a fucking victory royale coming my way.
Oh, I can't make a reference to my, my like epic games name. Why not? Oh shit. Balvarine.
Shit, what the hell just happened? And, oh, there's a huge bonus coming up here.
What kind of bonus was that? 150%. I probably should, no, let's go towards the actual mission,
please. The way. There we go. You think you're good at this game? I don't think you can be good
at this game. The fighting and the combat in this game is sort of just there for you to get to the
next part where you fart in front of a crowd of people. It's fun to play. It's not, it's fun.
How's this? You found an empty statue. Oh shit. Perfect. What's going on? How's it doing this?
Oh my God. I didn't even see them. What? What happened? I couldn't even tell they were there.
That was really weird. Don't let him go. He tripped over his own feet. I need 10,000. I need 14,000
to get to blades three. His friend just got down. Oh, I see what you mean. All right, dig. Where is
it? You got it? You can do it. Come on. He's finding it. Yeah, there we go. More condoms.
How come the sus guy is not doing the voice today? What voice? Doesn't the sus guy not have a voice?
It's just, it's just the face, right? It's the boss. Oh, Balvarines. I just want to see a
Balvarine so I can just stop saying Balvarine. Oh shit. This is the real deal.
Save Garth. On it. Ow. Watch it. See, imagine if the game was like Dark Souls and it was played
like this. It was fable Dark Souls. Microsoft, just make another one. Everybody's copying
fucking From Software. Like nobody, it doesn't matter anymore. From Software just took the
model and made it like really cool and interesting. Just copy it. Like everybody's doing it. Every
single game company now is like making their own like Dark Souls system. Just put it in. Just do
it. Just make fable four and make it a Dark Souls game. They're literally making a new fable. Yeah,
but it has to be a Dark Souls copy. Otherwise, I won't be happy with it. Maybe Elden Ring will
be like that. Maybe. It's the racing game people that are making the new one. What do you mean
the racing game? Big finish. It's the Forza devs. I mean, look, they might do a really good job. I
can't. I'm not going to be one of those people that goes, well, they're a racing game dev. They'll
never do a fun video game ever. That's not a car game. I'm not going to say that because I don't
know. For all we know that the lead designer of Forza has been waiting to make like a fable
game his entire life. You want me to like pass judgment on something that doesn't exist yet?
Somebody leaked the Elden Ring investor trailer. Wait, what? Investor trailer? That doesn't make
any sense. From Software is not a publicly traded company. What do you mean investing trailer?
Private investor? Literally true. Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. Holy shit. Eat. What am I doing?
Oh, wow. I didn't want to do that. Where's my, um, how did this change?
Oh, that was cool. That was really cool. This game's fun. Oh, and flourish. That was fun.
Okay. How are we doing? Is this worth playing? Yeah, I think, I think so.
I would say fable is a, is an experience worth playing. How was that? I'm coming Garth.
You left too soon Garth. Lord Lucian's experiment was a radical success.
You are coming with me. They got him. There was nothing you could do.
That was Lucian's commandant and apparently he now controls a shard,
an old kingdom weapon of great power. Lucian's strength grows ever more formidable as does his
mastery of the spire and its awful machinery. Come back to the guild. Okay. But first let me
check and see if there's any, uh, valuable shot. You can, you guys tell me like fecal funny. What
do you mean trespassing? Let's head back to the guild. Fecal funny. Look it up. All right. Where
is he? Sounds like you could have used my help after all. I knew I should have come.
We cannot allow Lucian to keep Garth. You must get him out of there.
They're being the spire. Wait, inspire the sound of your own heartbeat. There is one who might know
when Lucian left for the spire, he essentially abandoned his staff. His old butler Jeeves now
spends his days at the current corset. His butler? I bet he saw his fair share of dirty dealings.
Well, if it means a trip to the pub, we'll just have to make that sacrifice. Or not like Minecraft
and think it's going to be around for a long time. The task requires tact and delicacy.
Something I believe you're after. No, you literally asked this last week. I'm still,
I'm just checking. Anyone playing Battleship yet? I have to check in on that every like month or so
too. No? Not yet? Okay. I'm telling you, just look, just wait for the YouTube thumbnails
of like the Battleship in the middle and two like popular YouTubers or streamers
both like freaking out in the thumbnail. Like, oh my God, I can't believe that move.
It's going to be Battleship. I'm telling you Battleship. Battleship has no strategy. So?
And yes, it does. How does it not have strategy? Oh, this person has a gift. What do I need to do?
Oh, almost there. Hold on. Of course it has strategy. Minesweeper has more strategy than
Battleship. Let me ask you this. Let me ask you this question. Does Mario Party have more
strategy than Battleship? Yes. 25% discount of the whole. Really? Nice.
You only have three items. Should I try to do like Jack Sparrow?
There's so many ways to reduce RNG in Mario Party. Archmage robes. That's what those are.
Okay, I like this. This looks very odd. Oh, Pauline. It's like I'm a pirate that got
clothing that was five sizes too small. I was last in line to get my pirate uniform.
I'm sorry, Dave. All we have are extra smalls. Kill it.
I feel like this character kind of talks like a baby. He's like the big dumb guy.
Yeah, I guess I want to go that way, boss. That's what Peter Griffin's based off of,
that character. That like Looney Tunes character is who Peter Griffin's voice is based off of.
Listen to it. I think that guy actually says that. I think he's like,
oh, boy, I don't know what I'm doing. I think that's Peter Griffin.
It's a Boston accent, genius. I have no idea. I'm not like from that area. I have no idea.
Never been there before. I spent 30 fucking years in Boston. I don't even know what that is.
What town, what city is that? I know it's Rhode Island. Yeah, but it's New England.
It's the Boston accent. It's a New England accent. Just look, I know it's Rhode Island.
It's Pawtucket, Rhode Island. That's a Boston accent that Peter Griffin has.
What happened to your Boston accent? What am I doing in here?
What is everyone doing in here? I'm trying to do a quest.
The whole town is coming in here.
And here's something else that's written down. My price.
I apparently offended that person. I don't even know what I did. 1,000 gold pieces and not a penny less.
It's my final offer. Take it or leave it. Lucian's diary is a riveting read, I assure you.
I'm sure some private collector will make a nice place for it in his equally private home.
Oh, we're shooting this guy in the head? Or what?
Unless you've got a proposition, I suggest you leave me to my whiskey.
Honey, please, you don't want to be in here. Get out of here. I'm like, I'm doing something.
You don't, I don't want you to know what I do for work. You think I put this fucking mask on and
what do you think I do? Go work at the fucking like grocery store? Get out of here. I'm trying
to do something. Where were we? I want to like fucking punch him. Do I have to pay him?
That extra animation. Dog, get him. I think I have to pay him. I don't think I, I think I have to pay him.
I have to, I have to pay him. Fine, here's a thousand dollars.
Or not. It's a juicy little collection. I assure you, you won't regret it.
I buried Lucille's diary. I'm just tuning her out. I want to hear what she's saying.
I want, I want to hear what she's saying. I don't like, I want to be able to hear it.
Okay, let's go.
I have to get out of here. I was thinking, I can't shoot her. I can't, I'm sorry.
I told you to get out of here. You don't want to see what I'm doing. Can I take that money back?
You're horrible. I didn't do anything, okay? I shot that guy because he was dick and I didn't
want to pay him. I didn't ruin everything. I'm fine. I need to put the gun away. You got the money?
I want to put the gun down. Put the gun down. Put the gun, I, what's the put gun away move?
Put the gun down. Hide till they can't see me. Oh my god, get out of here.
What are you doing? Oh shit, right. Did they see me? No, I didn't. Oh my god.
I played football when I was 12. I know all the jukes. Oh.
I can't believe my wife left me because I shot a guy.
Why was she even there? What was the, I need to rent my, wait, there's a baby.
Where's the baby? What happened? Is the baby still here? Hey, she took the kids.
Oh, well, I didn't want her to see that. All right, anyways, what's the next mission?
I have horns growing out of my head. No, I don't. Oh shit, I have, okay. I have like sprouts. Uh oh.
Okay, we gotta do some, go donate to the church. I'm gonna go donate to the church right now.
I've got a bunch of money. I'm gonna go to donate to the church. Donating to the light. Okay.
It was you, the guy hiding with the gun in his hands. If I just didn't, I,
what's the holster button? A. It is A. God damn it. Okay, I'm here to donate money to the church.
Please contribute to our temple and receive the blessing of the light.
I will. Each donation will bring you wisdom and peace of mind.
Anybody got a sander? Can I just lean down? I just need to borrow a sander for a little bit.
I gotta sand something off my head. Okay, how much do I need to give to be a good person?
Do I, you? What? What? Donate when the light is brightest to receive greater wisdom.
Do they know I'm a murderer? How? How do I donate? To turn safety on?
How do I donate? Wait, the loot?
Is this a donation? Okay, I can't donate to the church. Why? Stand in the light and donate.
What's going on? Looking for your next victim, murderer?
Yeah, you, if you say that again. Why would you walk up to a murderer and say,
oh, what, you're looking to murder some more people, murderer? You're gonna murder me?
Don't do that to a fucking murderer. A guy that's like,
we'll just kill people for no reason. What are you doing?
Oh, look, it's the murderer. Oh, yes, sir. But that's the guy with the gun.
Perhaps your generosity will make- I think this is bugged.
Go to the bowl? Oh, how much should I give? How much money does it take for me to bring my
five grand? Ten thousand? I'm not gonna give all of it. I want to have some money.
You want to be good, give 10k. Now I have to go backwards. I went a little too far.
This is just like when I'm at the fucking gas station and I want to do an exact even number
and it ends up like that. And it's like, fuck! Give six, six, six.
Oh, your heart is fit to burst in with generosity, I see. 75 good points.
I believe you have earned the honor of becoming the next harvest benefactor.
Make a large enough donation during the holy hour and you will receive the harvest reward.
When's the holy hour?
And you will know it is right.
Make a large donation when the mystical sun reaches its zenith. What does that mean?
Between 12 and 1? How do I know what time it is?
Oh, okay, so between 12 and 1.
All right, I need, I need more money.
All right, let's go make money. I'm gonna be a blacksmith for a little bit. Sorry.
I know this is supposed to be me actually doing quests, but it's too bad. I killed a guy.
Bartender? Oh shit, I want to do this. I need to donate 10k.
Okay. All right, I want to go do the bartending.
All right, bartender. How does this work?
Serve. It just has to be green?
All right, this is easy. Old multiplier.
Don't you feel like if anyone ever did that,
this shit would just fucking fall over halfway and get everywhere?
That stuff doesn't, you can't really do this, can you?
I feel like that would fall over halfway and hit like the four or five people at the bar
and go all over. Can you actually do this?
My stomach just hangs over it. I'm balancing it on my stomach.
How much more do I have to do? 9 bucks?
This sucks. Why would I do this? I would just go be a blacksmith.
I can make $10,000 in five minutes. Bar has to be waxed. Oh, that makes sense.
That's a wonderfully poured pint with a game of keystone. Perfect.
Because you're level one. Okay, but I mean, 12 bucks?
Level five would be what? Like 50? 100? Should I level this up?
That's a perfect head on that one. Bartender makes money faster.
Delicious looking pint. Okay.
Level two bartender. You're comparing an entry level barkeep to a master blacksmith.
I know, but is it going to be worth it in the end?
Gambling will pay the most. Do they have like a version of Blackjack or something?
They do. Where is it?
Keystone? I don't like roulette. Roulette? I don't know.
Oh, me? Yeah.
Yeah. But here's the best part.
Nobody knows who I am because I have a mask on. Never taking it off.
Oh yeah, I did kill your friend. I never know who I am.
Well, you're the fattest guy in town. I think the blacksmith is a very large man.
Yeah, I don't think so. Holy shit. No, that was perfect.
What? It's perfect. That was perfect. Do you see how perfect that was?
It was all the way at the end. Perfect. What the hell?
A wasted beer. Oh, man. Is there anything more tragic than a wasted beer?
Oh, man. Dropping it. Oh, fuck, dude. Wasted beer. Waterfowl.
Nothing worse than a wasted beer. Your cousin from Boston.
Play pub games? Hey, look, I paid, okay? They came to me. They said,
you can either go to jail or pay a fine. I paid the fine. And lady, don't want to be like a little...
I don't want to have to tell you this, but I've got $10,000 in my pocket right now.
It was $1,600 for murder. That means I can kill eight people in this room right now. Watch it.
Everyone that wants to come up to me and be like, oh, you fucking bastard,
I would take you back and I'd shoot you. Oh, would you? Okay. Do you have $1,600?
Because if you do, then just pull the trigger because that's what it costs to murder in Albion.
That's the cost of killing somebody. You forgot about the $10,000 you spent
on the church for forgiveness. Well, I didn't have to do that.
Wait, the cost is $500. It was $1,600 because you killed three people. Wait, was it? Oh, shit. Okay.
So let me rephrase that. It's $500. Now, okay, you do the math. It's 27 coin for one of these beers.
So in the amount of time it takes for you to drink 15 of these beers, you could have already
killed me and gotten away with it. Let that sink in everybody here. 18 beers per murder.
This job sucks. Go gamble. Actually, this is pretty good actually.
I can see how this would be in. This would be like a hundred bucks. Yeah, I'm getting this low five.
Nice point. Your character looks like my drunk uncle cosplaying as Raphael from the Ninja Turtles.
6,500 gold till promotion. How long is this going to take? 108? Oh, this is going to take forever.
This is going to take forever. The gold multiplier is only five.
Wonderfully poured pint. That's it? Okay, no.
I'm watching someone else press A every two seconds repeatedly. What am I doing with my life?
Um, we're just hanging out. Man, we're just hanging out here. The right amount of foam is no foam.
Can we talk about foam for a sec? Look at the head on that. I've won it. You know, like in
cartoons and TV shows and movies and literally this video game you're looking at right now,
the big tankard with the root beer or the beer that has like the big like whipped cream kind
of foam all over it. I wish that existed. Like I want a huge like goofy whipped cream big foam
on top of my drinks like that and nobody ever you can never get it. It does Guinness. Yeah,
but Guinness is gross. Guinness is liquid bread. It's disgusting. I'm sorry. I know everyone who
loves Guinness. Yes. Oh, Guinness. You gotta get Guinness. Guinness. Oh yeah. When I take a sip
of Guinness, I feel like I feel like I have to chew Guinness. It's too much. Guinness to me,
it kind of has like the same look and feel and taste as the thing you tar your driveway with.
I don't drink beer. I'm not a beer drinker. Okay. Everyone's like, I'm seeing it right now. Oh,
he's like, he likes the American stuff. Oh, Bud Light. No, Bud Light is gross too.
To me, Bud Light is the opposite side of the spectrum where you have like those food coloring
little droplets that you fill up like a bunch of soda water and you have like a beer-flavored
food coloring dropper and you like and stir it in. I just, I don't like beer. I really just don't.
Somebody said Blue Moon. Blue Moon is actually okay. I actually don't hate Blue Moon,
but Blue Moon is the hangover beer, isn't it? Bud Light's the only beer I've ever finished.
I've never finished though. Yeah, because when you get to the end of a Bud Light,
it's kind of like, it's kind of gross. It kind of, it feels like, all right, I'm going to be
kind of, people are going to be grossed out by this, but I have to say it. I'm going to say it.
So just, I'm going to say something gross. Every time I've ever gotten to the bottom of a beer,
like the last three or four sips of a beer, I'm talking maybe like an inch at the bottom of the
glass or the bottle. To me, it's as if somebody swished it around in their mouth and spit it back
into the glass. I can, I can never finish a beer. I just can't do it. You know what beer that I
actually kind of really liked? It was this beer, and I know I'm, look, everyone's going to laugh
because it's like the name of the beer. It was this microbrewery. What the hell was it called?
Circus Boy. It was a Magic Hat, right? That was cool. It was like this unfiltered Heffenweizen.
I remember I tried it one time and I was like, this is actually kind of cool. This is kind of
good. It was called Circus Boy. Yes, Heffenweizen. Am I saying that right? Heffenweizen? Heffenweiser.
Okay. What does that mean? I like Heffenweisens. Someone explain to me what I like. You drink IPAs?
No. Heffenweisen is God tier. But what is it though? So when I order a beer, what do I know
that I like? I don't like the liquid bread. I don't like the food coloring flavoring. It's a Belgian
beer. So I need to order Belgian beers to wheat beer. Okay. Yeast and wheat. Okay. Your cousin
from Boston. Well, that's what I like. That's the beer that I like. This actually is making a shit
load of money. Blue Moon is a wheat beer. Oh, okay. That's why I like it. The really common German
Bavarian beer. All right. Well, that's what I like. Right, Corona? I actually don't, I'm not a big
Corona. I don't like Corona. It's okay. What? No. Fuck that. I did it. Dip shit American. It's not
pronounced that way. Okay. Sorry. You're now at two beers per murder. I'm a wine drinker. You all
know that. I like wine. I like whiskey. I like vodka. But there's an asterisk on vodka because
there's a lot of disgusting, just gross cheap vodka that is smells and tastes like nail polish.
It's nail polish remover. I get a good vodka is good. But there's a certain level where it's
undrinkable, in my opinion, even when you mix it. I remember I had a screwdriver one time with like
gross cheap vodka. And it ruined orange juice for about 10 years for me. I couldn't drink orange
juice anymore. It just it was such a disgusting fucking rancid beverage. It was it was disgusting.
I could not drink orange juice for like 10 straight years. Do I like flavored vodka? No,
not really. I just like a nice like decent quality vodka doesn't have to be like super high quality
but good enough. So it's not going to ruin the drink of vodka is the same Jeremy.
It's not whiskey is the grossest thing in the world. Well, look, that's it. I have had
whiskies before that somebody's like, Oh, man, you should try this on and it's got it's got this
it's got a really smoky flavor. You're gonna love it. It's very smoky and it's got hints of
almond and I take I take a little sip and it tastes as if somebody asked a cigar in my mouth.
No exaggeration. Someone asked a cigarette into my mouth. It's fucking disgusting.
But there's other whiskies that are fine that they taste good. They're smooth. They have like a nice
flavor profile to them. That's me with bourbon. That's why it's good. Palate of a 16 year old.
Ashing a cigar in my mouth is not how is that a 16? I didn't say I like ordering mac and cheese
and chicken fingers off the kids menu. I don't like really smoky like cigar fucking whiskies.
I actually don't like rum. I'm actually not a big spiced rum fan either. Spiced rum to me tastes
like they're hiding something. I feel like it's been flavored and spiced to a point where you
don't like you don't taste what it really tastes like, which is bad. I feel like it's like hiding
something gross. I don't know why. That's what I feel like. I have $25,000. What happened? What?
Oh my god. What about gin? Okay. Gin is awful. Gin might be the worst of all of them. Gin just
tastes like pine salt. Gin tastes like car air freshener. No. I don't think anybody, no. Gin is
one of those things that I think is very specific. And by the way gin and tonic reminds me of the
thing that like they would give fucking patients back in like the 1400s at the doctor's office.
It's awful. It's just awful. It just tastes awful. It's awful. Oh you know what kind of drink I want?
The shit that they used to give people before they sawed their legs off in like the fucking
1200s. No. Why would, why do we have so many options? Why would you choose that one?
You have so many choices. Why choose that? Drinking is immoral. You kind of.
How do I feel about tequila? I think a good tequila is okay. I think tequila has that same
kind of gross spectrum that vodka has. A really really like kind of shitty tequila is the same
thing as drinking the really shitty vodka. It's awful. I think tequila is good mixed with certain
things. I don't, I would never drink tequila. Like I mean why would you ever drink tequila straight?
Why would you drink vodka straight either? But like a vodka soda is essentially drinking vodka
without anything in it. A vodka soda with like a lime in it or something or a vodka like with
cranberry. That's pretty close. Fuck. I wasn't paying attention. I'll get it. Moscow mule. Moscow
mules are amazing. I love Moscow. A really good Moscow mule is awesome. I mean I haven't drank
alcohol in a very long time but you know just talking here. If I would think of my favorite
drink like what I would order and be happy with pretty much anywhere it would probably be a Moscow
mule or a vodka pineapple. Those are the only two drinks that I would like comfortably order
anywhere and be like okay I will probably like this. Anything else I would be like meh. Lots of
places have their own little drink menus where it's like oh here's our uh the special the special
like oh I can't even like I can't think of two like dumb like words that don't mean here's our uh
the sunrise into the sunset. I don't whatever they have the fucking dumb list and have the names
or the the Albert Einstein sunrise right. I don't but I don't order those. I think they're a little
too complicated. It's like oh like famous person and like a time of day. I don't I don't order the
famous person and time of day or weather drinks. They're like oh it's uh no Nikolai Teslas.
Raindrops like I don't know. I'm sorry. Kathy Mitchell's Express 101. I mean I would absolutely
what what I would order that. That sounds amazing. Uh why does this keep happening?
Are they gonna need batteries? Would you order a cloudy sandler? No. That's breaking the rule of
of like famous person and weather or time of day. I don't order those. What about absinthe?
I've never had absinthe before. I kind of don't want it. Kind of scary because I know it's like
oh yeah well absinthe back in the day they used to put uh like uh this like weird thing in it
that made you like hallucinate. I don't want I don't want that. They don't do that anymore right
but like I don't want it. That's not even true. I know but it's like a weird dumb like urban legend
around it. Yes I know I've read the chain email and I like believe the chain email but I don't
know. I just and it's like oh what you have to do is you have to take a sugar cube place it like
five feet above your head spin around pour it over no I just want to drink the fucking drink
I don't I don't know I don't want to do that or adjective and animal yeah that's another one
or adjective animal famous person time of day and weather the the the the Theodore Roosevelt
nighttime jack-o-lantern surprise bear you know I don't just add an adjective I'm trying to pay
attention to the game somebody just said we get it I know I'm just like I'm trying to pass the time
that's every word combo no it's not that's not every word combo what would my drink be though
what would the germa 985 be let's figure that out okay what would the germa 985 be
it would start start with some some good quality Tito's vodka you take the Tito's vodka fill it up
to about one two fingers then a splash of grenadine and then a little bit of soda water and then
squeeze a lemon squeeze a lime top it off with a little bit of pineapple juice and then put it in
the microwave for 10 seconds take it out of the microwave put ice in it stir stir stir stir stir
take the ice out and then put a parsley on it don't put it in the microwave I just imagine like
like in like a ceramic mug then light it on fire no and then throw it away
throw it away have the trash get taken out drive behind the trash truck it would have
absorbed a bunch of other shit at that point scoop it out of the truck when it gets to the dump
two ice cubes stir it up spin it up put it inside of one of those shakers
bring it to a priest they bless it gargle it gargle it gargle it oh fuck
put it down the toilet a delicious flush the toilet put the cup down with the water swirling
on the edge of the toilet to capture it onto the table another thing parsley and by the way it's
like $400 we get it top it off with a sneeze no 11 000 people are watching this shit
okay look I don't I don't choose the people that are watching this stream I'm just here
I can't like I'm sorry I'm sorry that there's been people are here
this bartender is crazy this is about just what I've been saying the whole time
I have 40 000 fucking dollars this is insane it's almost at level five by the way don't make that
drink that's stupid it's a dumb thing to do don't do it that was a funny like fucking routine we
were doing that concludes the uh the the message how would you even do I don't know now go gamble
everything let me get to level five I'll have 40 000 I'm good okay I'm done let's go donate it
at 12 o'clock I got 40 grand okay we're good now let's go to the time let's see we got quests
the bargain it's where is it the harvest no where is it donating to the light there it is
make a large donation when the mystical sun reaches its zenith here we go okay everything
before the microwave that would be the germa 985 I didn't what was it it was a little bit of vodka
grenadine soda water squeeze a lemon squeeze a lime stir it up maybe a little bit pineapple juice
what cranberry juice well both do both that's it okay what time is it 8 30 a.m. all right what can
I well how do I kill some time here 8 35 okay Tito's vodka yeah that's good Tito's vodka Tito's
is good I think Tito's is a good brand like Grey Goose too but like Grey Goose is I think I think
Tito's is probably better than Grey Goose like in regards to like value and I think Tito's is a good
brand I do 9 a.m. all right what can I do for like three hours well I'd somebody said he's a Grey
Goose drinker no I just said I that's like I would accept that if you gave it if you if you handed
me that you were like hey I'm gonna make you drink with Grey Goose I'd be like okay I didn't say
please I would love a give me a Grey Goose that's what I want go see your family dude my family
doesn't exist my wife left me and the kid you took the kid being factual I don't have a family
anymore wait do I why would the other family wait I still do have a family oh shit wants sex
well okay all right hello hi I'm still alive how you doing you want sex okay so how do what I have
money except gift oh a strength potion okay so now she said she wants sex what do I do let me go
let me let me go see my son we're gonna need another door oh no Kiernan doesn't like me
I gotta keep this family going who's this guy can I help this what do you want it's love farts of
course I do what the fuck what the wait what the fuck was that a guy leaned forward and you hear
like this what was the what was that was fucking weird what was that what was that that's fucking
terrifying what just happened that's your wife's husband that is just like the town crier that came
into the house because the door is open arm pump broke the door yeah I just want to make
sure the kid is still happy all right we're good it's the town crier this guy's always following me
around okay he likes oh it's because he really likes the victory arm pump oh thanks all right
where's the where's where you are okay come follow me let's um here nice
this guy's freaking me out he said that she wants to have sex
you wanted something funny okay fine
I'm not gonna kill that guy no
all right I want this guy to leave I want this guy to leave I want this guy to leave get out I
want him to leave this guy's freaking me out please leave me alone everything's wonderful
okay come here follow and you get out of here get out of here please leave my home
that's no joke okay people like you should rot in jail me wait why what did I growl at the neighbor
I can't she has to I have to it has to be initiated give us a laugh okay I'll make you laugh
isn't that nice oh sweetheart it feels funny all right you think farting is funny
the only thing I have that's funny I swear to god if that town crier comes running
I need to come hither I need to unlock more emotes
oh wait what was it we ready are we ready
we ready I need come hither okay unless she does it all right well um okay well it was nice to see
you again oh sweetie you're just standing there for six hours you need to go read a book
all right I'm gonna go I gotta go get the book where's the book oh shit there's a fucking pie
in here nice leave donate yeah I'm gonna go donate all right donate quest map quests wrong time
how do we make time go by 11 p.m. shit what are you doing here xp potion all right um
can I just pass time that's the way I can just stand still for like an hour right all right
yeah there is okay we're gonna go um temp uh we're just gonna go back go to the sculptor
and fast forward time all right can I sleep here try it let's just sleep let's just sleep somewhere
she's right next to me let's go back to the house whatever back to the house where's my house over
here right sleep for like another six hours I know I have a house just go there and sleep there
where's my door why is the door not back why do you sound like that oh whose house is this
can I have some chocolate um do I have any chocolate for this kid get a fucking door okay
chocolate do I have chocolate oh look at this here have some chocolate is it good awesome all
right goodbye where's my house I don't remember where my house is is it over here I actually don't
I just forget where my house is over here I'm about to shoot that guy I'm about to turn safety
off and shoot that guy and then when he's on the ground I'm gonna go down on all fours and do the
stone cold Steve Austin shake my fucking head talking into his face six hours what time is it
I want her to watch me donate the money 8 a.m. all right let's go okay 8 a.m. perfect timing
you're flexing wait didn't she say that she wished she was like I why can't we have some more money
and I'm about to just go drop like 10 grand into like the church's donation box at noon yeah I know
look at the size of you it's a wonder you can dodge even lettuce salad dodger well real nice uh real
real nice like religion thanks that's what's from we are the servants of the light
vanish in darkness Bert the monk once our murderer always a murderer Alex the monk wait wait likes
oh I thought it said like silken tofu dislikes organic tofu nine okay almost 10 a.m. what do you
want Bert guys I like tofu I see it I give him anything what if I give him like a homemade
apple pie apple pie is like maybe he'll like it they he liked it well I ate that wait what am I
doing oh yes I know watching you eat I'm what do you think I'm waiting for what do you have up
your sleeve no my sweet wait what um how about this I'm a chicken
all right can I do this for two hours straight we don't get it I don't get it
what oh I guess you're not as great as I thought you were really idiotic
oh come on like farting in churches like half of every stand-up comedian's fucking routine
from like 20 years ago I'll just wait till I drop a stack of 10 grand over there
okay what time is it it's time all right here we go 11 53 a.m.
was that a 158 that's not bad at all it's 12 here we go let's go 10k let's do it I'm not
giving it all why would I do that oh brilliant what is that the rising sun what is that you now
have a weapon with augment slots if any of them are empty you can attach augments to endow it with
unique power the number of slots next to each item's name tells you how many augments it can
hold may it's like dispense justice and keep you safe from harm that's a pretty nice drink
whoa okay let me see what it is weapons the rising sun 61 that is actually really good
oh you're sexy I'm really whoa but you're not really all that famous yet
donate more should I donate more should I don't let 10 000 do I get more stuff
no well I need to look at my way by where I am here how am I doing my personality look I'm still
gonna I'm so I'm so good now look at how much better that is the light I give some more for
your wonderful donation I'm gonna get like another 10 000 so I get even more good donate all I'm not
gonna don't all right now I'm not whatever this is fine you are now good the light grants you
wisdom I'm not good enough to use the apologize expression apologize make me laugh you're good at
it okay what I can do the joker laugh please give what you can well all right I'm very good what
was the expression sorry social thumbs up no scary no where is it rude chicken point and laugh fun
we're sorry I don't see sorry anywhere is under social like a different we're sorry it's not in
the wheel here you need more practice okay let's go you can only apologize if you do wait so I
wait I can shoot somebody that apologize all right here we go I need that's about 11 12 000
why does your guy look like a villain from every kid's tv show he does I have so many
of these potions I'm just gonna keep forgetting they exist that was such a huge amount of
experience though I can buy it now will blades three let's do it your comprehension of the blade
ability has increased significantly I got blades three now this thing's gonna be insane and we're
gonna do I might as well just do strength and I have the yeah I might as well I have this new
melee weapon should play the actual game well here's the thing about fable this is the game
this is the actual game like the story missions are probably the worst part of the whole experience
it's probably like a five out of ten okay here we go I'm going to do this is it better than
better than pouring beers for an hour that's the fable experience yeah I'm sorry though I
thought we had a pretty interesting conversation for that like the beer podcast wait even though
why is she still here all right you got it she has to go home what did she say plant some what
what you make up you have to pick up your mind because I you just said like oh we should we
should go out on a hike go to jail what did I do look at her opinion of me is perfect why
does she keep saying this you think she like loves me she thinks I'm funny and she thinks
like I'm like sweet why does she keep telling me to rot in jail what the hell all right go
I don't want you to die please don't please I don't want this to happen it's good to see you
again don't follow me I have to I'm not having this happen again you killed people guys I really
hate to like tell you how like the 1400s were you ever seen an episode of Game of Thrones
people were just fucking murdering each other over like hams don't come down this road it'd
be a fight would break out over like over the fucking ham oh my god somebody has a gun
please go home what does this do this takes so long to fill up I have to take her home
follow me I don't want you to die is that a bad guy what are you doing okay no you're fine
what the hell it's the medieval times god damn it what do you think was what are you talking about
one of them was somebody extorting you and they probably they had a gun in their back pocket
it was murder plus one heart okay here we go stay here this is I don't want you to get
hurt or killed or anything I'll be back see you later okay now let's go I really don't want her
to die medieval times doesn't mean murder is okay bandits are bad but murdering people was
still a very bad person behavior like people would just people would would fucking swing their
axes as people yeah murder was bad it always has been bad but I mean I'm walking around with a
fucking like a sword and a gun on my back and they're like bandits everywhere everybody does
it so I look so this guy's shooting at me with a rifle these people just look at this this is
what the medieval times were like look at this this is what it was like why did I lose so many
points what what what's going on they have bandits what's do you want me to not to do this
you should hit my dog that's not a civilian that was not okay that was not a civilian that was a
bandit I know I have magical fucking daggers that come out of my hands I'm talking about
like the nature of medieval times people with the guns no you know what I'm trying to say
all right I gotta help this guy that's a nice weapon but be careful I'm good there were no
streamers in the middle ages yeah there were no iPhones either no TVs there were no treadmills
oh hold on oh he didn't like that
steel mace no I don't want this
good observation yeah there were no there were no treadmills in the medieval ages right
see that's why I'm so that's why I'm so big uh the dog by the way has changed
horse troll dog is a retriever defeat the troll yeah the dog has changed into a golden retriever
too I'm too good watch out dog he's dead got it we do a little trolling here
oh nice there's a dig spot what's the what okay if you're evil if you're actually all the way to
the other end of the bar what does the dog look like Lucian's diary but it will do you a little
good without a translation bring it back to the guild coming this looks like it was meant to be
an MMO I I mean it was a pretty ambitious game for back 12 13 years ago longer than that right
with 14 what 12 13 how you can determine how ambitious a game was is did it come out before
or after GTA 4 GTA 4 ruined everything GTA 4 I believe was what 2007 2008 like if your game
was not as good as GTA 4 holy shit that changed that changed everything GTA 4 is like ambitious
game was like if you thought you had an ambitious game and your game came out before GTA 4 maybe
not after though you can read that but visor you know I see other worlds than this GTA 4 sucked
and in other worlds you can see I don't understand that's a that's a troll you make it that's just
Lucian is recruiting guards from Westcliff oh come on Westcliff's a dump full of pullers and thugs
the only thing there is that arena yeah GTA 4 was one of the best games ever made
it are physically tough and mentally weak Lucian is recruiting the winners as guards
you must enter the crucible in Westcliff and emerge from it victorious it is the only way into
the spire the only way to get to garth and rescue him I think a lot of you guys forget the kind of
interesting systems that were introduced in GTA 4 people being able to get like into fights and
stuff without you having to do anything about it people literally talking shit to each other
getting in car accidents and like a police showing up you didn't do anything that was very very
different than anything we've been used to like the AI engine that they came up with for GTA 4
was better than anything else before it just the way that people move remember that uh there was
that technology that I think rockstar acquired but like bumping into stuff and the AI moving
accordingly what was it called it was it was an actual technology about like AI reacting to things
euphoria right yep the act of like bumping somebody with your car and they interact with
the car with their arms and legs and body that was all AI that was huge that was ridiculous
because it was always just animations it was like oh this is you got hit by the car there's an
animation that plays after you got hit and it's like pretty much the same animation every time
the euphoria engine was just like holy shit wait like we can have people react to things the way
they actually would if they got bumped and it won't be just an animation that plays that was a
huge deal no not ragdolls not ragdoll physics existed well before that the act of the AI reacting
to stuff randomly if you bumped into them if they were hit by something it wasn't a ragdoll it was
the AI engine would react to getting touched in a certain way if you have if you have a few minutes
to go look up the euphoria engine and you'll see what i'm talking about it was revolutionary
no not ragdoll ragdoll is just the ragdoll is the whole rig just falls apart
don't look it up what procedural animation gta 4 invented physics you gotta get out of here
okay let's go i can't why can i not do more than 10 bucks oh i got nine free spins let's go come on
two more free spins added i need to level it up to bet more all right well we're going to
level it up right now this is where our subs go come on this is not enough money thank you
this is the shit that i pay for star wars the force unleashed used it too yeah it was cool all
right let's go more i need to level up my gambling ability steve steve get in here we're playing
with house money right now we're fine come on yes mr green i'm not gonna put any more money in i
promise i want to level up my gambling though i didn't even know this part of the game existed
neither did i i remember they had one they had a something came out before fable 2 released
it was a game to make money to use in the game it was like a weird casino game hub games yeah
that's right it came out like a couple like a month or two before the game actually released
it was like xbox i was on xbox live like xbox live arcade or something
of games all right let's go all right i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done imagine just walking
around with a slot machine on your back traveling slot machine guy all right come on staying alive
doesn't want me to leave all right let's go let's go exit i still need 1200 points any respect i
why do people see i look at my good bar my bar the bar is so over to the right look at my dog i
have a golden retriever i thought that was a traitor i thought this was a guy all right here
we go oh my god i'm gonna die what happened to me am i right that feels up so slow prefer to shoot
out in the wilderness somewhere i'm not gonna say anything whatever i thought you used that gun
put that gun away aren't we in the wilderness we're out in the wilderness find something big
spot no where is it i need to pay all the warrants i already did yeah i paid him it was like five grand
total oh come on i can make it down there serious name the dog i already did dr rough phd he's doing
it again what are you growling at all right let's go save this guy what's over here oh a bunch of
t-posing spawnable enemies oh eat shit i everybody calls me a killer why is that who i am that's not
my that's not who i am oh it's nice to see another killer i'm not a killer killing bandits is okay
then who executes the executioner wait i kind of i may have missed what you said executing who
executes the executioner um okay are you fond of riddles why am i about to hear one three great
men sit in a hall a priest a rich man and a warrior each one bears the cell sword to kill
the other two who lives who dies he's of not favor of the crown nor of the of the church it depends
on the cell sword uh if it's cell swords we care about then what's the real who's the real power
his power his knowledge is power and a very small man can cast a very large shadow you know the
fucking bit by how i've been here for ages right let's go i think one of the most famous game of
thrones monologues i know we all hate that show but like the first few seasons were good lucy's
writings are fascinating there's much in them that they interest you press on to west give
yeah the first few seasons of game of thrones are some of the best television ever yeah it is
speaking of which area was completely overrun even the fourth and fifth seasons were they're
all right the four season was okay but once they got away from like the books it was just like
well whatever i guess this shit's gonna happen yeah well you see you see us at hboc george wrote
on the back of a piece of toilet paper uh like three major plot points and that was it and then
we just kind of made up everything else oh uppercut i think my main problem with game of thrones is
that it just i just don't ever want to watch it again like i was so excited to get new people
involved in that show it's like wow you've never seen game of thrones you didn't all the books oh
my god we're in the middle of like season three right now this is the greatest thing you will ever
this is our generations this is our generation's lord of the rings like this is our tolkien it's
right here and now it's just like i don't even want to i would never want to watch the whole
show again because i know what happened like i know what happens halfway through this is the lord of
the rings for like the millennial generation this is perfect it's what we can tell our kids about
like lord of the rings i kind of thought it was gonna have the same like cultural impact
and it did for a while until it didn't all the rings is overrated yeah well you could all right
you but the cultural impact of like lord of the rings on media and like fantasy media i don't care
how much you think is overrated it's like the same thing as dungeons and dragons for video games
the only reason why i'm shooting this guy with a rifle or hitting with a sword is because i got a
few guys started to create dungeons and dragons wait that was a horrible thing to do whatever
like rpg's they only exist like all these things only exist because of dungeons and dragons bad
boy side is coming out what fable is the first rpg i didn't say fable is the first rpg ever i didn't
say that okay i have okay i have to say this because it's funny it's a stupid comment but i
have to say this so this is i'm gonna give that person this person deserves an accolade
because it was funny they said you only exist because i fucked your mom like okay all right
dude fine like funny sure really funny that i like come on like that's that's so stupid
that was a perfectly timed insult so i'm gonna let that one slide kill kill i am the flourishes
are really fun to do though i will say ah give me give me give me shoot him he exists
oh that's so stupid that's the kind of insult you hear on like xbox live and you just log off
because you're like how the fuck am i gonna ever respond to that and make it better like i was i
was mid rant about dungeons and dragons and and and rpg systems and i i got shut down completely
by that person that was a total shutdown like absolute 100 like shut down i cannot even give
a rebuttal to that one big oh no i gotta eat i'm getting confused i keep like wanted to target her
here we go thank god safety's on can i get some of these tooltips off the screen i think i can
right i like i don't want to keep seeing the fact that like hey you know that like you have a skill
you can use raid song sing the raid song we have a raid oh fuck
how many points do i have no even though the game is easy this game is really just fun to play
it's fun just to do shoot spell slap you know what i mean game of thrones raid
yeah wait didn't game of thrones tweet out like hey by the way like we're still a franchise
curian lannister of master gear thanks for the raid welcome everybody if you had a good stream
i'm currently playing fable 2 it's a game only for millennials this is a millennial game if you're
not a millennial then you need to leave only two thousands kids understand this game i wasn't
trying to be funny i actually had to go to the bathroom and where else am i going to go to the
bathroom i'm in the woods explain that to me geniuses i'm sorry that was like kind of rude
kid in the 2000s or born in 2000s i don't even i don't know precious necklace oh nice and a dig
spot go ahead do i have like any potions you're born in 2000s you're gen z that's true yeah open
the gate must be the infamous barricade you're gonna get us in doesn't look that tough my god
he's got my hat on stand and finally names dad wait is that why i've had this mask on since i was
10 because i'm a highway man i'm not like you dad i'm different i'm not evil oh oh
hey yeah that guy that guy was the guy in chat stick those spells up your ass oh this is getting
a little tricky i think it's a high level area i shouldn't be in
oh got him that's fun um yeah i'm doing this you say fatty yeah he did oh it's dad versus son
come on come on go ahead come on great oh shit don't kill me don't kill me don't kill me don't
kill me run away oh a made outstanding fight thank you he's treasure oh my goodness all right
hold on vortex pog yep then we'll get him in the vortex and that leave me alone i'm trying to do
something boy mate there we go guns are op i can do shock three maybe i should do it damn i just
got here did you gain weight what a nice thing to say to somebody when you first like fucking
talk to them after a while did you god come on all right what can i upgrade shock three blades
that's too expensive vortex three should i do vortex three or shock three
shock is quick i'll do vortex vortex three and now i want vortex here i want blades here
let's see what it does that's just a gigantic explosion then i can just walk around and just
slash people throw knives at people it's perfect very cool all right let's go is there a spell that
puts you on a treadmill that those didn't exist back in medieval times okay we already went over
that where's our treasure oh give me do you like cantaloupe this is really important um
no no not really i actually don't really like that much melons melons the stuff that i eat
around in a fruit cup if you have pineapple strawberries grapes melons i just don't eat
the melons i eat everything else i've heard a lot of stories about westcliff
places supposed to be vested we've heard this one story about these traders who got attacked
what about watermelon yeah i think i like watermelon both parents but like honeydew melon
cantaloupe steel cutlass better than this thing this is 5061 no a slaver found the poor things
took them back to his camp and locked them up in a cage i like watermelon watermelon tastes good
although isn't watermelon like the captain crunch of fruits it's just like water and sugar
alverine hey what do you mean it ran off it's right here i don't know the dogs hurt vortex
it's dead why are we getting like a skate three wipeout what was that
do i have any food i feel like i should eat something
yield the dog oh shit that's right oh shit again oh god come here dog i got you i got you
come here come on i got you come here do i have any heals no come over here oh no i don't have
any do it yeah i do come on there you go when you fight these guys just pure melee they're
tanky he's very happy good i have two resurrection wait let me i gotta at least explore yeah i'm
why would i not check over here wizard hat
wait this die i can call all the clothes it's because the breadcrumbs don't tell you to go
over there that's very true what happened they killed my husband they killed my frederick oh
shit it's all right you're safe with us they took my son can you show us where they took him i think
sir you're gonna turn to a ball brain i will find him how many silver keys do i have at least
like eight or nine right i thought that said 200 what the fuck all right where's your um
where's your son let's go stay back move out i need health potions hold on no nothing all right go
hep ad the drums yeah pretty cool shout you don't need to move out of the way please
you're gonna get killed get out of the way just get doing what's wrong with this guy
i'm coming i'm coming hep ad pressure big spot no i would assume it would be right here
hep ad why are they not attacking us that's weird the dog is barking you barking at the
balverines or did you find something pressure is up your ass into the left thanks thanks for the uh
take it i'm gonna be able to level up something major i think i need health it's pretty low still
everyone wants to be the next your mom guy yeah yeah we're seeing a we're seeing a pattern aren't
we it's here howling halls watch megamind to remove penis hex um no i just leave it on
where's the dig spot you just found it but where is it you keep going over here oh come on
why is your guy so veiny um i think that's like magical properties or something because i'm a
magician right the more i'm using the will the more like magic i have like going through my
blood or something crab blood i knew she was awful
shit i turned the safety off i was trying to kill him before she turned oh don't
okay come on i'm not even looking holy shit that was right behind me i'm just running around in
circles i feel like i'm laughing right now lightning bolt yeah dead it's like one of my
favorite things ever but you know i'm not like i'm not swinging at anybody i'm gonna die
it's like i'm too old for recess electricity oh no you didn't get me you didn't get me you didn't
hit me you didn't even get me i need to eat how do i get out of here invincibility shield
yeah there always is an invincibility shield if a little kid ever walks over to you with like a
stick in their hand and they start like pointing at you going like got you zapped you if you don't
pretend that you got zapped you're a monster like if you don't go like oh wow you got me
if you just sit there and stare at them like what are you doing oh come on
pillar looks weak get it i'm not strong enough don't worry i got this holy shit oh my god
my four my thing didn't work come on you're supposed to let the kid win
i'm doing my force field vortex you don't just fucking ram him give me a break you monster you
are a monster look at you oh got it this is pikachu kind of i guess in a way i need to
level up something no not yet i'm one of those weirdos that saves everything to the very end
of the mission children's health potion oh oh fruit punch i really am like a kid
time for our imagination snack healthy growing brain means healthy growing thoughts
are any other potions no i have a lot of how come he's not showing up why does your
character look like the skinny version of fat bastard what the hell i still have my companion
oh i don't i would even i would not even classify this guy as fat i would classify him as
big and strong although i'm not entirely sure what's going on there i think that's the shirt
yeah that's the shirt that's a puffed up bunched up shirt i would classify him as big and strong
with a puffy shirt on it's it's okay i'm gonna move on from that oh beer gut andy let me tell
you something everybody i've ever come across that had like a big beer gut they always always
could like help you do anything they could have you do anything if you need like your house painted
they're gonna help you they're there you need something like heavy lifted like a piece of
furniture they're fucking there and they're gonna help you they're there for you like you need help
with like your math homework they are there they will do it they'll try you know many times i've
seen somebody with like a big beer gut get up from like a lawn chair and be like yeah i'll i'll take
care of it and they take care of it every time they have like it's a magic i don't think they'll
follow us into the light many die in their attempt to defeat the crucible
but defeated you must if you have any hope of joining lucien's army and getting to gar
the amount of knowledge that the beer gut brings is immense i would probably trust the guy with
like a big beer gut over a guy with like a big white beard and a wizard hat on i'd be like i
don't know you're like a fucking cartoon person like i i want that person to help me the one on
the right you know what i mean like if they if i have there's like two doors
they're brothers the guy was walking around with the staff that's like come i'll show you how to
oh wait did did your car just break down oh i uh i don't know much about axles and cars
shit how are we ever gonna get to mordor i have no idea what to do oh this is gonna be expensive
master katana these are so expensive these are better than what i have but long story short i
i feel like that guy has a lot more knowledge and has a lot more like experience than like gandalf
the guy with like the wizard costume on what should i get who is a pistol that's cool i like
that i kind of want it this is 18 000 bucks and off the guy with the wizard costume on
i mean kind of you need katana for rp no i'm getting the pistol
hey as i do that i scream let's just ignore these idiots you have a gift for me
why don't you fucking keep your mouth shut
a wit intelligence and looks is there anything these two don't have all right hold on i gotta be
funny why don't you get back to you all these people are gonna love farting wait let me let
me speak the language you don't like that what they said that they loved like comedy stuff and like
humor you don't fall over just now we should probably see about getting into the crucible
shut up somebody likes it you see what i'm doing right now i'm about to shit my pants don't you
like this farting isn't funny okay they like when you laugh you'll never survive around
two weaklings like you yeah two weaklings like you i mean i feel like i just gonna want to start
fucking attacking
i mean there's only so many times i'm gonna get insulted here i want my present
i mean this is like the entire town this is all
present company excluded okay i mean this is everybody's here i want the present
what are the consequences if i hold on a nasty surprise when they get home tonight
play the loot oh somebody has a present hold on let me collect that what do you got for me
oh you a pretty necklace thanks say what you want about westcliff i've got nicer pointy
walls the most i've seen tornado wait what
oh my god this is strong enough all right settle down settle down settle down settle down i can
leave now right how much points did i get let's become evil why they don't even get okay we're
good that's not i'm not evil why what do you mean why what i suppose when folks die in the
crucible they can just come back as hollow men what do you mean why why
wait i'm hurting her too oh my god i'm sorry how do i say sorry how do i say sorry sorry
where's the apologize where's apologize to her i don't want to apologize to her
that's nice oh that's a lot of evil points decent food around here oh everyone i see eating just
has peanuts shit no just shot her in the head oh my god turn the safety on turn it on
trying to get into the crucible doesn't anybody know you've got to be famous to fight here
i'd like to see how he's managing that how are you so bad at being good i i i've just we're fine
terribly sorry but i'm afraid this is a rather brutal business and it's not just the blood
spurting decapitations people only pay to see the big names like willy widow maker or vice grip sally
how about verne vortex i'll get my hand up back here that's what they call me now
like they don't know me i walk downstairs crucible fighter there was back in his day
bit redundant isn't it what do you mean well why do you need the strangler part if
you're already a mad dog you're three stooges hero it's intimidating any seems confusing to me
i mean i get irving the strangler gibbons it toughens it up a bit doesn't it but it's
not like mad dogs your given name you know i never thought about it before but she's got a point
no she doesn't look if you really want to compete go and make a name for yourself so the crowd
will actually give a flying i think i already did that's all you need a bit of luck and you'll be
famous in no time no way i'm letting that friend of yours in though she can stay out here and make
fun of my name all she likes an impressive 500 more renowned you have managed to alienate the
very men whose favor we need
hero you must find a way to impress those men and you must do it alone there are still many
people in the world whom you could help with your heart good or evil your reputation will be made
what's that did you see that you see what i just did over there do you have any idea what
the strangler is that good enough fame for you nobody fucks with me all right
you think the baying crowds want to see a complete unknown get torn to pieces
they want celebrity blood i don't understand what was that what was that for
i started taking piss break i'll be back stop killing okay i just got attacked from behind
what am i gonna do not defend myself oh okay i'll be right back give me a sec hello
i'm here i'm just laughing just laughing he was sitting here laughing the whole time
no i actually went pee and i got a water oh okay let's go back so i need to look at this
see what i've done okay well i'll just go donate 10 grand to the church again the demon oh my dog
still a golden retriever i'm good there's a sale going on oh new job bounty hunter okay what
quest the cruise earned 500 more renowned to gain entrance to the crucible find and rescue
slaves the temple of shadows aren't looking for a business partner to win his 5 000 gold in his
new scheme that sounds i'll do that ripper and his bandits have been terrorizing a farming family
the temple of light is under threat of attack from its worst enemies the shadow worshipers
red harvest help rippers bandit crew expand its operations i'm gonna do defender of the light
do the shooting range and get the best gun get back let me just get some renown there he is the
light bringer uh yeah i don't have free aim yet okay let's go here defend the temple so i can get
some more points to on the good side what do you need i was hoping you would return the temple is
in need of a protector once more we have always suffered at the hands of the vile cultists from
the temple of shadows but i fear they're preparing a major attack against us where are they it would
seem the shadow worshipers are planning to poison the holy water in the wellspring cave
if that happens the golden oak will die i can't have that it would mean the end of our order
perhaps even the end of the village and all its people you helped us once before will you do so
again i will as long as you give me i can put you down as a reference for me being a good person
first thing you must do is to check the statues from which the water pours forth
ensure they haven't been contaminated with the taint of evil the shadow worshipers are
likely to target the main chamber next but you mustn't allow them to desecrate it
okay let's go kill some shadow worshipers i really should level up the gun stuff
i think the guns are more fun than magic but i'm okay it's kind of too late
not really though all right hold on will shock three which would be pretty good blades
four sixty four thousand eight hundred that's three four five that's close vortex four
hmm time control might be kind of cool i use shock all the time i feel like that's so cool
vortex four let's do it sell the skills back with why i'll just sell chaos back i'm not
going to use it all right ray there's also rays dead which would be kind of cool
all right accuracy 36 000 extra here we go ranged aim i can now do it now
hold y to enter aim mode click left or right while you're locked on enemy to instantly
switch to other targets okay speed might as well just get it let's see so you do i have to hold
it the whole time oh i have to hold it the whole time if i want to stay in there that's kind of
cool i can now headshot people oh dear do the shooting contest all right let me hold on let
me let me do this part first got vortex four oh this takes some bomb all right if i'm going
to do vortex four then that means i don't i'll do blades three vortex four and then shock one and
shock two that sounds good to me does the game have bubsy 3d tank controls no i mean it's a it's
a little floaty but i wouldn't say it's that ridiculous bubsy isn't floaty well i mean i
didn't say bubsy was floaty i said this was floaty oh my god walk over it what's wrong with you
is this as good as kingdom hearts 2 um i say this is like kingdom hearts 2 without like the
600 hours of cutscenes and no goofy donald and mickey nothing like kingdom hearts 2 yeah
absolutely nothing like it uh there's a melee ability and you have spells as what the differences
are or the similarities similarities and similar what at the simple what's the book
similarity simileon simile simile ryan at the simole the simoleon is the sim currency the
simile ryan simile ryan is the lord of the rings thing one of the rings like prequel
simile ryan yeah whatever don't poison the well oh say goodbye to this one boom where is he he's
larping again yep come on it's fun to larp i think it's actually pronounced toy boat
toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat it does hurt who died me oh i died eternal orgy i just
thought that guy doesn't want an eternal orgy i'm here for the eternal orgy i don't care about
anything else please do it there you go my voice is a little hoarse today i can't do it
oh he's got swords why can i i don't want the auto aim and i really couldn't harm him
cornelius grim oh how about my power it didn't even ask me about my power level it's way higher
than yours it always is in all these shows i beat him so glad i have vortex four it's just i'm
unstoppable no one can even touch me nobody can do anything i'm unstoppable all right i'll be back
for you later oh wait you're gonna do it again oh the bringer of darkness really he downgraded too
he was like i am the bringer of darkness and he turned into like a scrawny little guy blow kiss
that's it almost everyone in westcliff has heard about you for better or worse cool now you can go
back to the crucible gatekeeper all right let's go back to uh mad dog and murray the shooting
gallery yeah not funny do something funny tell the do something funny story or sing the doing
something funny song i like that comment okay where's the shooting gallery
oh fortune's tower sure i actually forget how this one's played pressing your luck played with
a unique deck of cards a deck contains mostly number cards ranked from one through seven plus
a here plus four hero cards this deck contains eight of each card ranked one through seven
uh other decks may contain nine or even ten sets okay place a bet to start the game your bet must
be 15 gold or some multiple of 15 here the dealer starts by dealing three cards the first card is
facedown and is called the gate card the next two cards are faced up and create the second row there
can be as many as eight rows if you play all the way to the bottom of the tower all right this is
the starting deal on each row you have a choice you may take the dealer's offer or deal another
row the dealer's offer is equal to the total value of cards in the row on this role the offer
is nine remember you bet 15 you cash out now for nine gold to push on and hope for a higher value
push on all right row three would be worth 18 but wait you've also caught a vertical pair
pairs such as this will often end the game but not always all right same rank on the previous row
here will cause misfortune ending the game with a value of zero okay okay here's a worth zero
go but they keep it from safe from pairs okay all right ah this is stupid i don't just whatever i
just go when an entire row matches you get more money all right let's go i i get it i don't care
i want a jackpot it's just it's a it's a mobile game whatever it's cool and tutorial all right
i'm going all in yeah why can i only deal 15 six and five no no deal six and six i lose
six and two is eight deal all right put that over there 12 deal again blocked it out deal
this game's terrible two times bonus deal 13 deal it again all right block it out do it again go
hero card highlights rise up snap them out stop this is this game's awful
don't all right what do you have presents oh yeah you want me to okay you're gonna be in my dreams
who said that
poker knight had fabled two okay uh where's the where's the shooting range this looks like a
shooting range to me no what's that meat trader oh yeah and meat rancid beef rancid anchovies my
favorite sliced mutton salty beef jerky white fish no i refuse to eat that
find any items on your track be sure to show them okay where's the shooting gallery down here
where's the shooting gallery i need it how's everybody highlighting everything
why is everybody doing that stop doing that i command it the industrious kazoons oh here we go
five thousand gold for your new scheme our fates do seem to be intermined what money do i have
don't they my good friend after a reputation i can think of no one better to become my new
business partner five grand all right take it listen i don't even care what it is just give it
and do it oh it's my most sagacious plan yet inspired you already have my attention just take
it toby business and yodeling i don't have enough money dear i really don't know i don't have enough
money okay return when you have it all all right i need that shooting gallery i want the somebody
said i can get a gun we're gonna do it the job go back to the crossroads and take a right
back here shooting gallery no right outside the town out here i think this is it i think it's it
all right what's with this purple nonsense come on bewitching augment and a diamond holy
there we go all right shooting gallery
try the west cliff shooting range if you think you've got what it takes
lovely these are simple here's how this purple tops the purple spam i'll turn it off all right
don't shoot bandits shoot the targets sell while you can what are you talking about 175 points
is what i'm looking for where are they oh okay that was abandoned which one how can i tell who's a
bandit is this is really awkward this is horrible to aim literally 14 points how am i supposed to
get 175 points oh there's a round two okay i can't even tell this is very hard to do i hate it yeah
it is rubbish i feel like somebody's holding their hands around my neck and strangling me while i do
this what i get already this is the last round how am i ever gonna do this come on it's all about
round three i get it how the fuck are you supposed to get 175 points here oh my god shooter all
right i get it i get it i get it i get it so you have to get to like 50 to 100 i need 100 points
100 i can do it let's see what you want i can do it only headshots might you forget what a middling
shot you are a chap who could end the gun his combos for not missing really i don't think there
is i think it's just you just just get head just focus on headshots only headshots oh it's like
pulling hair come on all right that was a good run that was a good run that was like 50 or 60
points right oh cracking toast probably fuck oh god damn it all right i gotta make this is gonna
be clean come on nice and clean let's go oh please i do it i get it i do it fuck damn it oh that's
so hard that's so fucking hard
god damn it oh all right come on i got it i got it it's so much concentration it's i got it here
we go i can just be quiet quiet everybody quiet nobody talk okay six twelve i need 60 points
this is the worst one god damn it the aim is so fucking horrible oh the fact that you have to
hold triangle is like fucking gouge my eyes out it's so horrible why would you ever have an aim
system like this i like holding y down is like what an awful fucking system that is i want to
just hold down right trigger or like left trigger or something like every other fucking video game
ever made hold i'm holding it down what the fuck i would rather go to the dentist and get my teeth
ripped out than do this one more time this is horrible i'm holding triangle i'm it's literally
why is it doing that my god i'm so mad right now and you know why that's 175 points because
the shit you have to oh i hate this what a terrible fucking system analog aiming already sucks
asshole why would you ever make it like this holy shit go back 12 years ago and delete this
fucking whole part of the game and redo the entire aiming holding y to aim and then left stick
get the fuck out of here what a terrible fucking system
i'm losing points for shooting old ladies what do it again
tantrum it sucks though who plays this and goes yeah that works it's like eight frames a second
that works oh my god why are you doing i'm holding why what the fuck why is it zoom out
i'm i have not taken my finger off the thing the entire time
he's malding yeah i am dude if i was ever in a fucking board room and somebody said they
want to put analog aiming in a game i would throw the fucking desk out the window and be like don't
don't do it don't please god don't do it please i want to exit and shoot this guy the head
how do i leave the game
bully for you you've made it to the final i can't leave it's not about i i know where they come up
the problem is like like
i want to just leave this fucking minigame baby rage it's all right i'm fucking out of here
fuck you calf come this will make you forget what a middling shot you are
look like a chap who could end the gun want to try your luck in the shooting range get the fuck out
of here oh my god game i know you're not gonna hit me you won't hit me why is it just like don't
i want to lock on to them i don't want to lock on to them whatever that's the part sucks kill you
know you want to i thought i had it too doesn't matter i don't care about the super secret gun
i do want potions though i think i have potions do i look who it is a crucible contender if
ever i saw one been causing quite a commotion ain't you everybody sucks what why there hasn't
been so much buzz about a competitor since knockout dora remember her mad dog oh yeah
he's good person horns
okay i kind of look like a pig anytime that dora those are pig ears guys those are not horns
make sure you're properly kitted out before you go in the crowd gets ever so upset when our fighters
die too quickly but if you live you become a legend and you'll be a shoo-in to join lucien's army
i don't think any winners have turned that opportunity down yet i mean sector security
work is very lucrative i hear right no dogs allowed inside health and safety you understand
let's do it use fast aim style onto target and slow move towards head wait what fast aim style
now i'm not doing that again that was literally like pulling teeth out of my ass i'm not doing
that again master katana what about clothes oh i kind of like these oh i kind of like these
it's like a there's like a doctor i put on like the doctor outfit like the surgeon garb
i match now upper body there we go i like that these okay whatever all right i'm ready
as we can just lovely who's next then hey love to wouldn't i have but still got this whole
if you cosplayed as you would get kicked out of the convention i probably would
would certainly but i'm still waiting for my lucky robes to come back from the cleaners
did we go on next my um crossbow's got an awful cold look at gorgoron gorgoron has an
ingrowing toenail right now an evil toenail like the girl is that the little girl the new guy
it's your lucky day get your ass in there you might want to read up on the rules
not that most contenders can read mage to stand victorious in this bloodthirsty theater
all right let's go kick some ass
so eight rounds of pain death and fun beat around target time to earn a perfect score
five perfect perfect scores will get you a top prize
bugs that was simple let's go
once we're within the spawn and then just drop it one two three go all right that's
the strategy go kill it last wave oh shit he's alive oh i got a perfect round nice the bugs
don't even do anything magic is the worst way to play the game well that's what everybody voted
for oh my god okay i'm just gonna keep doing that i'll be a boring andy right now it doesn't
matter oh my god this is so much easier i can't even see what's happening but i think i think i'm
winning my did i heal kill this guy oh my god shit i don't have any health
2000 gold holy shit i have to eat something why is that health potion not on the bar i don't think
i'm gonna make it to the end am i strong enough to get to the end oh shit kill what do you mean
we're doing second wave where's the next wave oh shit run just get the money who cares i know
mediocre will you spawned him in a weird place ow oh fuck it's not boring look what i'm doing
get them with your gun i did just five more rounds oh my god i'm not gonna be able to do this
it's getting progressively harder how am i gonna do this you think i can do it i don't think i can
spend your points what can i do upness yeah i want health i have 37 000 which is i can do
shock three yeah i use it all the time all right i want vortex four blades three no shock three
blades two shock one let me be this time oh i can buy stuff grab a potion oh yeah
three four weapons i can't even buy anything when's the guy gonna make funny noises yeah i
just i just had like a meltdown about like the aim down sights come on that was the
yeah that you that whatever that's what everybody's here for you got to see it more more meltdown is
funny it's no stop it i did not want to see that anger is funny i don't even get angry i get
irritated i think i'm winning oh shit excitement times five look at this come on queue it up queue
it up queue it up queue it up oh being a will user is so awesome here am i gonna die i think
i'm okay just keep spamming this leveling up vortex was such a good idea what an amazing idea
this was oh god oh god that hurt oh god run away mediocre well i'm look what i'm doing man
um gonna be a perfect round come on 30 seconds i need i need vortex five how much is vortex five
it's 172 000 oh shit i'm kind of close using sword what i'm a magic user i've have all my points in
magic of course i'm gonna use magic why would i not use magic i think i have experienced potions
concentrated will confused will i'm at 100 000 all right i'm i think i'll get it after this
cut my finger please give it a kiss all right oh this is gonna be bad i'm not this is where it ends
i can't wait if i want to go down the middle i can't cheat here there's no i'm not getting
perfect around here in no way what is the game doing i might still be able to do it who's next
why am i facing this way pick that up oh my god what are you doing what fall down from i wish i
could pick this up exciting i'm just let me just do the crucible see if i can catch everybody
he's just barely out of reach i would love to shoot the barrel oh my god like god damn it i
can't target the barrel i don't want to target this thing oh my god damn it somebody said aim
deep aim just latches on to everybody no perfect round great i'm kind of glad the
forts of developers are taking it over i'll be honest damn it i think i have enough for it
do i have enough he's blaming the devs for his mediocrity no i'm i'm just saying i feel like
they give him a chance give the forts of devs a chance i feel like they're gonna do something
really cool blaming the devs for his mediocrity oh you don't want to just hit hold b and watch
the screen explode come on bring it on where are they oh shit okay run run run run away run away
so wait till i get vortex five you're all gonna be so mad i'm gonna be mad because it's gonna be
so stupid oh that was me mediocre here we go level five vortex are you ready this is game over
i'll do it after i'm not in a good position to do it kill him two thousand gold that's a lot
i need to heal if on the shiny square this is fucking stalagmite the gun like that
i'm gonna catch you i swear oh that's how you do it all right 62 000 all right now i'll be able to
do vortex five it's time to see what it does how much cbd have you had today wouldn't you like to
know none is he more obese than he was yesterday i don't think so what will it be this time you
love it sensible have a nice day you love it sensible but you love it oh shit concentrated
will potion 12 000 all right i can sell something sell uh sell a weapon all this dumb crossbow sell
the rusty long sword sell the iron axe sell the cutlass and sell the rifle okay it's a fair price
now i can buy yes you love it do you like killing that concentrated will do blades um i think i
want to do health how much is for health upness 108 000 zeke is 36 brutal styles chain attacks
um this is where you if you hit right at the end of a swing right what else we got
zoom not right now blades blades four all right let's get this going i want blades four vortex
five jock and then yeah shock shock shock or no blades all right cool no give me the shock
shock jock shock me oh my god it takes so long what oh my god kills everything instantly
what i can't lose oh my god queue it up queue it up come on it's just a bomb
no one can even touch me ow ow oh my god okay i'm fine oh shit wait why did he die from
that was so awesome what a movie death all right roommate i wonder who cares he walked
into the strong winds yeah guys don't you understand i can do that to the town oh shit
shit i didn't get it oh fuck come on oh my god why kill kill him get up these things from hold on
hold b he's so close why can i not dodge roll it's supposed to be tap a to dodge roll
just what is this camera angle just fucking die already oh my god
all right i won now fart no i'm not farting anymore it's stupid 10 000 gold that's it
and that yeah somebody just said it in that amount of time i could have just made like
200 000 serving drinks go give the guy 5 000 oh yeah that's right vortex all of your fans
your victory in the crucible has earned you the right to be called lionheart this title is now
free oh wait i didn't mean to
to visit your family say goodbye my way to the dock so you know where to find me when you're all
set to go i do i'm ready to go wait you forget what is it i'm gonna give that guy the money yeah
once you are in this fire leaving will be difficult and there are those who still need
your help on these shores if you abandon them now they will surely come to harm i'm not gonna do
that do not get on that ship until you are truly ready to leave god
how could i not walk on this oh my goodness what the hell so frustrated uh he's up here
uh where is he i thought he was up here fuck you capcom am i ever gonna be able to live that down
am i ever gonna be able to get over that one you don't think so
no you did it so early i know it was within like 10 minutes of started nothing to do the game
either all right here's your five grand notify you by letter when i've completed the project
you'll see some constipating changes make a game industry commentary channel
uh i have a feeling all my videos would get like 50 000 dislikes okay now they said to
uh you might not be able to come back so bartender okay i'm gonna do i do what about
what if requests aspire the freezing summoners donating to the light finish the shooting range i
can't did you just kick my dog this guy just kicked the dog i just killed somebody i just
shot somebody i was trying to shoot you who did i kill over here god damn it i shot this guy
fuck oh god wait wait wait wait wait i don't want to kill you i don't want to kill you i want to
play the game can i play the slot machine don't please don't don't i didn't i don't want to kill
them i'll kill them all right i killed them i gotta leave i gotta get out now no that's i need i
that's the guy i can play gambling games with and i'm never coming back i didn't want to shoot that
guy i'm sorry i don't even know who did it it wasn't even me all right go to the shooting range
okay uh i know i can't vortex them all i'm gonna have to pay like thirty thousand dollars all right
come on this is it let's go let's go all right all right that was good that was a good round
that was a good round good round good round good round why what the why is it zooming me out
that's so fucking infuriating i'm not doing that all these are missing holy shit i can't
fucking believe how bad that is i'm holding why the whole time why would it pull me out and it's
just like oh you're out the rain is making this fucking harder to aim dropping my frame rate to
like 18 i what are you doing what is it doing that for why is it doing that i don't understand
why is it doing that i'm just holding why it's over i want to turn my face came on and be like
what in the name of fucking god i'm holding why right now it doesn't make any sense it's just
it's as if i'm not touching why i don't know why it's doing that this would have been pretty
close to is the controller busted no it's called caring about fucking rain and dropping your fps
of the whole game by 20 that was gonna be so close to use a mouse this game's not on pc
i'm gonna hold why right now because i don't understand why it's doing this
i'm gonna hold why i'm holding why right now i'm not gonna let it go why is it stopping that
that doesn't make any sense i wish i had an explanation for you can you toggle it no this
is one of those it's one of those games it just has every button has like four different contexts
of when to press it and when to hold it like why is shoot hold why is aim you remember when
every fucking goddamn game is doing this like contextual gameplay mechanic presses oh i hated
i still do stages of grief yes oh my god i hit him in the head here okay all right that was bad
that wasn't bad that wasn't bad i have an idea oh it's a bad idea never mind i did it again at
46 all right this is it i got it i got it i got it i need to get like 60 come on wait what why did
it pull me out it pulled me out i thought it was over what the fuck i couldn't even aim the gun
i couldn't aim the gun i thought it was over i couldn't i was pressing what why is it keep
doing that i can still do it oh my god why what are you doing why is it doing that i don't
understand i i am holding why right now i'm pressing it as hard as i fucking can i just
let it go i'm pressing it again oh my god why how could this how is it possible i didn't let it go
i probably would have had it too oh my god it's so fucking it's killing me
i oh my god what the fuck is happening it's like it's not even registering the fucking controller
what's happening i'm pressing it too hard i'm not pressing it's just it's just a slug piece of shit
even if i don't let it go i am i am i'm playing this out of like a spite because i can't understand
how awful this is like i can't i cannot understand how bad it is i have to like keep doing it to
keep reminding myself why this is the last i'm getting it right now oh my fucking god
you've got to be kidding me doing it again why i don't don't i don't understand i don't get it
i don't know why it keeps doing it this is not possible to do apparently it just keeps pulling
you out why does it keep doing this to me why is it doing it i need to be somebody i want a
developer to tell me why i want a written fucking letter from one of the devs all right settle down
no a letter send me an email i i have to i can't it's no i can't do it like i just can't i i just
have to leave it like i just can't i don't know if it's like the controller or how the game is
registering the controller i don't understand why it's doing it i would have had like again
i haven't let go of why i just did i can i rebind the aim key i wonder you just suck no it's not i'm
telling you goddamn contextual fucking pressing buttons it never works it's always awful and
people they still use it in new games i just went full fucking hollow right there did i do it
i don't think i did i don't think i did it oh god all right this is it this is the end
last one last one i'm gonna like surprise like this i'm surprised you were all right right
there's a guy on game facts forums 12 years ago who posted the same bug yeah fuck this game
all right let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go
the game facts for i feel you man you and me are the same don't do it now i'm so ahead what the
oh my god what the oh it's so ahead why did oh my god i'm good stop it's doing it again
all right this is the one go go go go go shoot the dad oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh that was horrible that was fucking hard better than your map oh the red dragon and a silver
bullet i did it hooray i got the red the red the dragon hooray i did it okay i got a new gun
awesome it shoots as fast as you can click no it doesn't the red dragon augments devastation
augment lucky charm this the augment in this weapon allow you to cause more damage to enemies
while taking less yourself the way i can just you click too slow he's still pretending to like
this game oh my god wait i can just spam it it does less damage than the old gun you know fuck
this guy don't take money out of his register it's really loud it is all right i did it i win now i
can stop hating everything about this game what's next how about two idiots please save the game
okay it's got an insane fire rate yeah this is actually pretty cool i want to try it okay um
let's do let's do the summaries the two idiots i think it's funny i haven't found this location
yet really speed zoom okay well i have zoom sub targeting oh sub targeting is great i'll get that
next um i feel like i'm really far across the world right now i should go yeah to go to i'm
gonna go talk to my wife it's been a while i was so angry during that and for good reason too that
me and that guy in game facts we get it we know i i'm i have like a direct connection to that person
we're i am like directly we're connected on a fucking spiritual level is this oh bartender i
need some money sorry everybody that's gonna get boring for like 15 minutes yeah leather jacket you
wrote that 11 years ago can you imagine that would be next level of weird i highly doubt that
though this is more interesting than spamming magic well now i have like the best gun in the game so
going around back to where i work i like that just screwed me up what the fuck be careful
you don't first of all you don't walk around the counter am i gonna stream e3 is when is it
when's e3
june 12th to the 15th i probably i would assume i would do it yeah of course i would
june 12th i'll do a couple of the conferences like i always do i do it every year there is no e3
yeah no there is all right what do we look at 25 000 30 000 i'll be done
perfect pouring elden ring is not going to be there that's a wonderfully i mean is elden ring
going to be like every other project george r martin touches and it just never comes out
nice one thanks yeah that's such a low-hanging comment i know it is that's like the easiest
thing to say about that once you know are you is he talking shit about how bad i was at the
shooting game serving us drinks in full costume wow
this is 500 bucks every single time i should just sit here until it's 50 000
okay once i get to 30 000 i'll be done
perfect pouring it to a million no that would take forever look at the head on that
probably could do it through gambling head on that one 675 what is it uh the multiplier tap out at
10 15 perfect pouring just the right over 10 oh shit this is 10 that's a wonderfully
poured pint can you tell us about next week's stream uh that i would just probably i wouldn't
i wouldn't miss it nice point i would probably be there if i were if i were you and if i was
able to be there on sunday perfect pouring 11 is it top out a thousand bucks of beer
okay i'm not going to stop this until i screw it up because this is a ridiculous amount of money
perfect head on that one nice point 12 perfect pouring nice point somebody said this earlier
and i do kind of agree i would i could do without the
constant voice work the voice acting that plays my horns are huge why are they so big
is the whole time that guy i was about to rip my teeth out oh it's cardboard massacre it's a
cardboard massacre oh that was embarrassing it's a cardboard basket please let me shoot let me just
do this no those are pig ears i'm making that really clear again you've murdered like 200 people
holy shit i'm just this is a thousand dollars of beer oh my god maybe i can make can i get over
like 100k 15 multiplier what no do not come over here and start attacking me please
five dollars five thousand per beer i don't think it's gonna go that high
it's probably gonna top out at 1125 yeah 15 is it but this is still ridiculous i dropped it
um i dropped it it's all right that's it that's it i'm out damn it so did somebody just kick the
dog again who did that don't touch that dog oh it's so easy to like you though that was funny
oh i i want to unequip this is it melee it just fists all right let's go i was gonna go to my wife
people are just talking shit is your little baby boy doing well oh you like me okay yeah these
these guys like me vortex five oh town crier we need a new name dumpling beer monger desperado
sparrow gunslinger knob head oh chicken chicer i like it dog lover butcher executioner bounty
hunter chosen one or shadow fiend knob head not the joker how about the chosen one if you'd like
my opinion there's no better choice than that it may be expensive but it's worth
every ounce of i've eaten knob head i have returned ray proof it die can i drink it
run the baby oh no oh no what's wrong arm pump i need to do i need to learn kissing
i need more money all right all right all right i'll give up money i'll load the bank accounts up
how much money do we need uh set a budget how about like uh 200 bucks a day more than 25
i need to go buy some more stuff oh the baby hold on the gift to the baby what does the baby
like jerky i love you knob head i hate you knob head what do you like boy bow yeah all right
baby's fine don't worry honey i took care of it baby is good good to go it's good to see you too
uh it's an increased budget of which to do for the hamburger stand all right i'm gonna buy this
hamburger stand eyes all right let's make it expensive adjust the prices buy this one too
you don't buy everything now how much is it can i buy this bar yet how much is this place 38 000
i'll take it adjust the prices i know in this place pretty nice okay right now i'm gonna go
do the mission you can do the spire all right i want to do the summoners yeah this this seems
like a fun little this is a fun little game right let's do it there's a glitch or if you turn off
wi-fi you can turn your xbox forward by a year and get 10 times your gold income yeah i'm not
doing the animal crossing glitch of no who keeps saying that because they're gonna die i have to
kill them who is it like this person just keeps saying this over and over and over again they
keep saying yo you'll never shoot me you'll never kill me yeah you're gonna poke your eye out with
that uh rare gun that no one owns only one exists and you have it because you were good enough to
get it who is it oh my god okay is it you who is doing that is it you is it you
i don't one of you is talking a lot of shit
i won the shooting range the guy under the bridge who means a guy under the bridge
oh it's the gargoyle i was about to shoot somebody in town too 50 gargoyles my god
i was just i was about to shoot somebody on the bridge all right let's go to this mission
what are these breadcrumbs doing where are you leading me be sure to collect the eggs too
what about the demon door yeah i need to go back to bower stone and learn how to kiss somebody
carriage driver
why would i ride this let's let's go to the bower store market that sounds fun
i can fast travel why would i do this well i can just go to my map
it's for rp is he'll get the get the same loading screen
what i've written a letter as to why this is in the game
34 000 all right where's the bookstore i need to learn how to kiss i heard another one wait what
do you got you got something oh yeah i'm trying to bump him on purpose what is this
you there are you interested in lending your fellow citizens a helping hand sure it's slavers
snatching away honest folk they are heck of a problem marvelous very civic minded of you i must
say i've written down the slavers last known location on this note okay well civilian rescue
details better get a move on before the poor sons are sold i'll be needs you rescue the slaves
being held at the camp in bower stone old town worse let's go what was that what do you sell
meat mine now you got fish here it's an honor to nice doing business with you
you're gonna stay fat don't remember it was clapping i'm pooping while writing this isn't
the internet awesome some of it some parts of it yeah all right we're gonna rescue the civilians
where are they yes but you're the one who oh i'm supposed to do this two idiots
you raise the dead all right listen listen you two idiots
oh thank you a hundred hollow men in the cemetery
we found called the norma nomakin you're the one who found it remember yeah and you're the
one hundred hollow men we sort of thing is seems like a lot a few hundred because you dropped it
you big girl you need a vortex oh yeah so we can get the book back and put them all back where they
came from all right where's this graveyard i can handle it where do you think they came from i
don't know you summoned them hold on a minute next time you want us to explore graveyards
hit yourself with a mallet instead and next time you want to read a book hit yourself with a giant
can you two shut up for a minute i would yes i wish i could make lots of corpses who want to eat me
up here whenever i wanted i knew it always so jealous all right i'm going i i'll go do your
deed okay who's that why is there constantly something going on
what's this hello um okay i don't where's the key i'm trying um what do you think i'm doing
they took me against my will what do you i don't know what's going on is this like a is this a bit
what's happening why is nobody doing anything what the actors don't i can't do any moves i
can't attack i can't press any buttons what's going on okay i can't do anything i can't press
any buttons i guess i'm going this way everyone's just kind of standing around like oh we're just
waiting for him waiting for our queue everyone's saying i can't attack them by pressing any buttons
didn't do anything okay now i have access to my weapons all right i have to get a lot i have to
kill a hundred people all right easy enough get out of here just kill a hundred of them it seems
like a really uh kind of a boring mission we're just gonna be doing this for a while
vortex let's go actually the swords is really effective it's only boring because the way that
you're playing it yeah i i know but that's what i've chosen i'm taking off somebody's grave
all right come on i need to kill another 80 i have the pistol yeah i'll use the pistol
i started leveling up the dexterity because i can do vortex and then after vortex i can just go
but okay that was weird how did that happen um they're spawning underneath the bridge
i didn't think the trail and mattered anymore all right let's see how it works
watch this ready oops pretty good i think i shot a guy 255 percent this is too good oh my god it's
so broken i don't even use any gun i don't i don't even have to use magic or anything
all the men are weak uh oh it's over there magic is for losers ban that person ban them forever i
don't want to see them ever again in my fucking chat room cast spell gone are the people still
here what just happened i just what did i just do to this thing like why did i kill this what
happened apparently people liked it i opened a door whoa what's that how do i get that shoot it
shoot it again how much was that i wasn't really that much experience with the 220
just when does that do 221 is meh what do you mean meh i think it's pretty good where's that
little glowing orb thing oh there it is it's gonna so cool get a raid is there after raid the the
sphere hunter welcome everybody from the sphere hunter thanks a lot sphere hunter playing fable
i'm really glad that you're rated now not like 30 or 40 minutes ago when um i had a career ending
meltdown so i was very upset at this game it was career ending i'm just kind of streaming until
until like i just fucking turn it off because probably not going live again after that one
so i'm just gonna let it ride out until it's over all right i mean might as well
um no thanks i didn't even shoot the orb fuck it was how embarrassing i know i forget even where
that was it's true we've entered post career arc post career arc all right where did it go
this way there's another gargoyle where is he and spell of swords much what's going on here
higher level that's not enough oh oh boy wow noble lady's hat
versus necklace doll put on the noble lady hat i think so i like that i like this one too
i like uh i like i think i like this one the most lady demetre sue should i be lady demetre sue
okay can i can i dye this white okay if i can i'm gonna be lady demetre sue what's wrong dog
eyes like an eagle is the dog different what are you what are you doing over here what are you
doing big hey everything's all right everything's okay all right well where is it show me okay there
you go ah good i feel my fat little decreasing rapidly where is he i heard him but whatever i
don't know where he is it was an actual mud pie it was delicious it was delicious perfect i love
it yeah you just beat the shit out of me that's fine there it is i thought they said call the
necronomicon it's oh my god spider-man called me at 3am the necronomicon called me at 3am
oh my god the sus guy called me at 3am this thing's moving i bet you watch those the best
the funniest part about all those videos is it's like it's it's just the same video they just
it's a different person in in a like party store costume i think they just go to the party store
and they go to the back wall where all the costumes are laid out and they just start at top left got
call from a scary mummy at 3am spider-man wolverine priest nurse doctor why do i watch them
you don't think there's something inherently interesting about this weird youtube videos
you're gonna be the sus guy for halloween don't call scary red mask clown at 3am what's wrong
what's the matter what's the matter come here over here come here it's okay come here okay
everything's fine see all right give the book oh sorry big guy coming through if somebody's
running this fast and they're like six five like 300 pounds just move out of the way like you're
gonna get run over demon door you've ran past it oh shit where i'll give this back let me do
this first i feel like one of these guys is gonna die what page was the undo spell on
oh here we are turn to you barada i just heard a rifle all right i want to do the demon door
time for the spire not yet i want to open the demon door i want to make um a little bit more
money all right where is the demon door this is the deal you will perform an act so vile in
front of me and i'll pop open the heavy
okay um how do i do that do i have to have it in my inventory oh i'll have a salmon oh do you like
fresh salmon all right i'll come back with meat just behind me doctor take a chicken into him
their chicken there oh take a chicken into his mouth oh don't backseat fable too without help
that's a helpful backseat that's not like a you're an idiot how did you miss that stupid idiot oh my
god i hate him that's different i need a chicken nobody said that yeah they yeah they they were
thinking it my god that was horrible all right you ready oh wait is it actual ooey gooey cheesy
voice ooey gooey cheesy what is it alvarine strength potion i'll use it skill potion use it
will potion use it suck it all up yeah yeah that's pretty cool buy some more businesses
i own quite a bit how much is the uh how much the bar and bower stone that's what i want
all right now the the civilians that are trapped that are being taken away right the slaves i gotta
go help them oh help how's everybody doing you guys doing good haven't asked you that in a while
how's everybody you guys doing all right how's everybody doing no i don't want to do it all right
pretty good where is it above me oh it's just it's a banana relax
there is
pretty gargoyles i have to kill you stay in hydra i am i have a nice big water in front of
me right now thanks for asking though all right here we go now we oh fuck it whatever let's go
don't touch my dog large metal key okay here dog take this let me help you on textual menu system
please be on the screen for more than one second yeah how's the wizard doing tonight pretty good
all right coming in well i'm really sorry thank you it was there was weird shit going on
thousand renown how does the wizard nobody calls you the wizard yes i do i'm the fucking
the jewel the jewel wizard from las vegas feel the power of god i was about to just kill
no i can't do that no no killing the fuel wizard you are funny all right let's go to the spire
let's let's do it save the game it's time the spire what the hell just happened how did you do
that how'd you just put like that weird thing in chat how'd you do that how are you doing that
i don't get it how you doing that i don't know what ask is well but it's happening to multiple
people doesn't that mean multiple people have to do that at the same time are we funny yet i don't
i just don't even i don't understand i'm supposed to be really mad at that guy until i figured out
that that's my name ready to start your glory let me eat something warriors military career
okay then did you convince your wife to wait for you i hope so here i am to say my goodbyes
i still know the last thing i said to my father before i went to the ritual cave
remember remember if i said goodbye that morning or not oh wait yeah i'm gonna be gone for a long
time you never know when you'll get another i'm sorry i didn't mean this isn't like well i still
have a wife when i come back you'll do find out you're not gonna say goodbye to your son my son's
like one month old thanks allowed on board and no weapons i mean no dogs don't worry i'll look
after fur face here and your stuff am i pulling my pants down what was i doing oh come here it's
okay i'll be back oh okay if you're gonna take all my stuff then i might as well eat the rest
of my food in here oh that was a chicken we're fine i didn't realize i even bought it shit
at daredevil pattern spire the sounds will be the sounds of your own heartbeat
the only thing i remember it's coming up what um what is this for again this guy has this gigantic
spire that like time travels or something you can see the future and it blew up and he wants to find
out he needs to he needs to go back and find out who did it this place we've done well captain and
i don't know a lot with lord lucien whatever he's planning me and lilla are gonna be right i get to
go first what's going what's wrong with me i don't just
move on fighting the guards this place feels i'm too slow
can't think of one thing to say not what is this place six years i was a mason's apprentice
what are we all doing here how is this possible old kingdom engineering i reckon but then how's
it come back now oh here it comes world outside these marvelous walls is a corrupt rotting husk
reason is absent instead of order find the guy in the crowd on drugs chaos does not punish evil
nor reward righteousness it'll be hard chaos cuts innocent lives short and we're to accept this as
fate i beg to differ you stand in the center of a great instrument of change with it i shall
remake the world and my creation shall be unrecognizable in its perfection sounds of
your own heart is not sufficient for such a monumental task it is only through your toil
through your labors through your conviction that albion will be transformed
hear the sound you feel beneath your feet these sensations will soon be as familiar as your own
heartbeat there it is and so long as your heart continues to beat all that i require of you
is obedience now sleep okay you can do that i think vortex nice fucking shit spell
morning maggot welcome to the spire hope you like it because you're never leaving of a shotgun
color on now you're in the barracks you'll eat and sleep here and the rest of the time you will work
wherever the commandant assigns you your job is keeping the scum building this place in line
and otherwise doing whatever the commandant tells you without like a friar talk even order
you will obey it immediately which brings me to that new piece of jewelry you've got
the color is part of lord lucy's saw collar well you're wearing one too the commandant will
explain it to you main thing is do what you're told and don't try taking the color off because
you can't and the penalty for even trying is dead and not the quick and painless kind
either now report to the commandant it's an extra extra extra large they had to custom order this
for me it's not worth the costs you know if that guy just acts up just shoot him with a rifle
get a break for it never mind sock on turn safety off let's fucking start smashing people
why would he have safety on in here i didn't really mean to do that get that man to stop
laughing shut him up stop laughing i thought that's what they're gonna start doing oh he
started laughing he liked it it's you we arrived together oh hey bob how are you settling in can
you believe they put me on guard duty on my first day too i must have impressed someone
oh we've little could see me now she's always loved the bloke in uniform
though i don't think she'd like the mask any more than i do why are they in there
what makes us guards of them like workers that we keep prisoner
they guys talk to you in your head
all right report to the commandant
commandments commandant all right what do you want me to do i was scared it's a scary guy
guarantee you take two lightning strikes to the head now okay
hey darth maul called he wants his head spikes back you probably get that all the time
you will do all the device around your neck this is not a pleasant experience and experiences
will be drained away that's a shotgun color okay this will continue until you submit perhaps you
believe you will resist some do it first a misguided sense of i will win every time
you must decide is your honor really torture sequence of metal goes solid i destroyed every
single time like i can click the button as fast as possible you're not going to break me all right
to tell you be still nope not doing it failure towards the device around your neck okay do it
then god blow my head up do it you won't do it you know i'm but you know i'm valuable if any idea
how valuable i really am you know it you can't kill me your boss would be fucking furious i'm
gonna call his bluff he's not gonna do anything see you're not gonna do shit what are you doing
i'm fine oh oh what's up mosquitoes out tonight are the mosquitoes out tonight what was that i'm
just trying i think i felt something oh is this evil he's leveling you down i get this back by
killing fucking three like goblin people i'm not gonna do it you're losing xp i'm i'm fine
look at he's look i've got a pretty big exp bank account guys he's not leveling my abilities down
yeah i'm fine in fact hey hold on a second what if i just spend them yeah just hold that thought
for one second uh demon guy give me one minute uh chain attack seems pretty good to me yeah i
think chain attacks okay while reloading a ranged weapon if you tap y at the moment you hear the
reload sound you reload instantly cool and what else we got will i did want to get time control
so i'll do time control two time control three what about um dexterity that's all i can really
do okay all right no don't take me don't no don't do it oh shit you're taking all my points for me
you you dastardly asshole he's taking your credit score
yep i wish i had your strength the commandant made me talk to a recruit this morning
he overheard the poor bastard saying he missed his family i'm glad i don't have a family i just
had a strange maybe it's evil turned into star wars i think sometimes with these sounds you know
i hardly notice it anymore it's as familiar as my own heartbeat oh he's been he's broken
you have orders to report to the barracks on my way sir recruit 273 report to the detention center
oh do i get do i get another massage like last time i loved that it felt really nice
it felt really good look like buzz lightyear
okay i need to i have to do a buzz lightyear cosplay in the game
that's perfect buzz lightyear did they have like a bowl i can put on my head i did
i do have more guts
no you're bad you're like torturing people in cells what the fuck are you talking about
oh there you are they're not allowed any food though so don't touch the controls or you'll be
sorry okay i'm gonna grab a quick bite nobody's even looking right now i could push the sky off
the edge yum yum like i could run sprint and tackle to push this guy off the edge and i would
just say fell feed the prisoners or starve them why would i choose starve them help this is the
food lever what's happening all right i'm fine i can resist everything he does he thinks he's
really strong but he is not even close to being as strong as i am what point is this thing just
run out of battery how do you charge this i command you making up all the karma lost for
killing the villagers week 137 it's like almost two and a half years oh my wife is definitely
gone now there's no way i have a wife anymore i just left i didn't even say bye
i'm fine
i'm fine i'm gonna try how am i this fat still i don't know i did a lot of storage but i don't
know is that i duct taped a bunch of like snickers bars Reese's and shit to my body before they put
me on the boat they thought i was a big fat guy and i mean i am but a lot of it a large amount
still is right now i got all kinds of food in here it's in the underwear too i don't care oh wait i
dropped that can i have that okay oh i'm gonna be the dog that got into the trash
i'm not doing it what i have to take it all right i'll take the sword kill him okay i'll give you 10
paces one two three four he can't do his it's punishment to obey this man well i guess i am
kind of weak he should have died yeah what happens when i go to zero yeah when i'm at zero you can't
take anything else from me so what do you expect fine i'll kill him oh don't do it again
don't do it oh my god wait do i what did i have to stay here
they lose no i didn't oh i'm fine boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
who's talking any years later captain's log log number 158 officer 273 very low on Reese's
i have to go into the ones that are in my shoes those ones are gross running low on supplies
getting tired what he said yeah why am i still a guard why would they still let me have this job
at what point do you just kind of like just lock me away and just be like all right well that guy's
not we're gonna he's not gonna do anything he's not gonna do what we tell him here we go all right
it's been like 10 years construction of the upper tier the man guarding the site is overdue reporting
in find out what's happened consider this a chance to redeem yourself if you find the man in
dereliction of duty escort him to the torture chamber and await further orders how did i get
even fatter did i i think i did i did how what am i doing how am i getting this big still
i do i think i got even bigger i think it's because i'm aging and when you age when you're
big in this game it just kind of makes you look a little frumpy oh he's not there anymore the
you pulled the food lever too many times you heading to the construction
okay where is this person i'm gonna get all good points back for this
search body steel cutlass oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy we meet again you came to rescue me
hey no good to either of us with that oh you got the collar off there it took me years to focus
enough build to destroy our colors so when trouble comes it's up to you the only way out
of the spire is through the commandant's chain i'm not gonna use magic so ready yourself and let's
move oh my god i don't want to kill him you're in safety on they know that's right i'm not i can
do this oh now you're all in big big trouble all right let's go time control oh i cut his
head off did i why don't i even say that it wasn't even close use only lightning bolt eat them watch
out watch out oh that hurt okay he spends 10 years building up energy and you die in two minutes
well i've been weak i have i haven't been able to practice i just got an achievement time they're
not seeing me or something one two three go i can i can do it i can release them there is time we're
right here why can't we just do it let's go get the uh the commandant stand back can't see me
here we go leaving until the commons are dead you're thinking but it's not revenge i'm after
revenge is just a fortunate byproduct look out the window fruits is being brought in
take a look where that was us that was us 10 years ago can you believe it you were looking
right at him this guy sounds like the guy from chopped we have radishes chocolate and pig
pig stomach all right let's fight one on one fuck i'm trying to do the time spell don't stop using
time oh stop it you're gonna fuck us all up this should that kill him oh oh wait he teleports
eat the potion shoot him time right using your sword i'm not a sword user
you're gonna tell the mage to use a sword but you know anything about rpg classes
give me this give me the give me the orbs swords got him hey that's mine what oh he needed the
experience i get it i've taken all that that was a big kill steal oh wait i'll do that too
see like we both did that we can use this to reach the docks you just copied him yeah that's
pretty cool move that's a cool move i guess yeah well that was cool nice flex but i'm the one
that's supposed to be doing that not you how about that one see i can do that that was pretty cool
don't you think we just holy shit that was cool i want my gun back this thing sucks
we just farm experience i feel like this is a great farming spot mages don't use guns
i mean they can if they want i don't have to if you want to be you want to be a melee user
you go for it don't do it what was that health magic is the best you know i typically agree i do
think magic is the best i love magic in games you know why because a gun is the same thing in
real life a sword is in real life but vortex three is not oh yeah it's called a hurricane
yeah hurricane is fine but i can't control a hurricane natural is yeah but i can't create
a natural disaster with my palm of my hand all right you guys are free let's go you don't
control swords in real life yeah what do you do you hold it and swing at it get on the boat
my wings are a hurricane when was the last time i used a sword uh last night to cut a tomato
tell me again how we don't use swords in our daily lives knives aren't swords knives are small
swords knives are domesticated swords i thought i would never there's the dog oh there you are
good boy you're still going good you're still big and strong it's been 10 years though what
a good boy all right now daddy needs to stop at the nearest taco bell your furry friend has
been coming here every day for a week oh he knew that you would return victorious even before i did
10 years welcome back my friend you have done the impossible and god i welcome you too welcome me
you're in my way so please step aside you know much about the old kingdom enough to know you
cannot destroy the spire alone we share a common aim all i ask is that you listen to
what we can offer you there's only one more person left all right i'll listen but i promise nothing
i will go with garth hammer is at the inn in rookridge you should see her before we talk again
she'll be overjoyed to know your back go see your child i will oh and here you'll want this
your old equipment thank you take my hand garth we have a great deal to discuss do i have any
choice oh five thousand reward a hundred thousand dollars i didn't oh it's good to see you again dog
let me take off this crap off leave my regular clothes back please well i have his gloves head
gear i like this i want this this i like it why do i have like big eyebrows oh no no those are
those horns i want uh these okay i like that all right let's go all right put that back on
put my red dragon back on i need it's got augments in it all right i know this treasure but
the hero that's me i gotta go visit my family it's a cal zone uh don't say that it just made
me hungry okay where's my house i still don't have a front door why is a window broken out
what's going on here this is my house you're trespassing i am it's been 10 years oh families
veneth is happy very happy everything's fine son no i'm home okay where's my family son
your dear old dad oh your dear old dad's here son remember me i know you like this oh where's
your mother where is she where is she no i don't want any carrots i want crunchy blueberry pies
what's going on okay i don't where's where's my wife he looks like the town crier he does not
honey where are you she's gone where is she upstairs i wouldn't have an upstairs follow me
follow me come with me i'm your dad come with me i'm your dad does somebody looks like this
come with me i'm your dad i'd be like get the fuck away from get out of my house
well like what rave party did you just come from this person's like going to edc
hurry i'm dead why i can't even communicate with this kid doesn't like me why hates me
what's going on even the dog did it you don't like us what about this one he's just waved
just waved into the night i go why does he want to talk to me do you like the dog oh wait
but where's my wife when you're a manor i'm the owner knobhead can i see who lives here
my wife's name i really don't know my wife's name weneth right weneth weneth anybody seen
they don't remember look in the family log book where would it be expressions apparently i got
disconnected from xbox no she would show up on the um wouldn't she show up people sleeping in here
just go to sleep it's bugged okay i'm gonna go to bed
all right i'm gonna go sleep in my bed and then just see what happens she's with the town crier
she's not with the town crier we're not just leave our son sitting here alone sleep for 12 hours
okay here we go where's mom where's your mother why can't i get this kid to do anything check the
bar it's probably at the bar um you think so yeah i don't see you're in town at all
it's gueneth right okay reg annette alex my son sally what where's my wife
everybody stop laughing where's my wife where's my wife what are we done with her
yeah everybody thinks this is everybody hates me i i think she's is she dead you bet your ass you
can dave the villager absolutely you can have my autograph how do i give it to you
you want my autograph here you go where is it my condom yes okay autograph card here you go kid
can't use it how do i give it i want to give him an autograph
nobody wants to be friends with your son we all hate it what the fuck why does everybody
hate my son there you go there's my autograph why does everybody hate my son where's my
fucking wife i have to use the gift expression okay here you go no i don't want to give it to
kathy i want to give it to this kid where all of you i'm about to vortex this fucking stairs
get out of my way i'm trying to target this kid okay there we go there you go good
i autograph
what is she mad because i gave this kid a present
what's wrong with that i thought it was funny well that's embarrassing you have to go to the
set where is my wife what what about the kid this is freaking me out i have to get this kid out of
here beef jerky wait i think i have ham in my pocket i have like food i have jai i think i
haven't i think i have food don't i i don't golden oak leaf this is kind of cool all right
well whatever i don't know what to do i don't know why my wife is gone you're not guinness
it's a bug okay all right all right all right let's go i might come back after the quest is
over okay all right here we are if i didn't know better it's me it is you you old bastard
man you look good considering look at my deflated stomach you're really here
you could sit on that that's a nice chair you did it you rescued garf took your sweet
time all right but you did it so what was it like in there as horrible as i imagined
well never mind i'll find out soon enough myself we're back in business i don't want to be back in
business i want to be out i want to be done and your baby well he's nine i don't want to keep
this fucking bullshit going i'm meeting someone you might have some information on you know our
number three yeah go see my go see my wife and kids that's right as soon as i have anything we
can use i'll head back to the guild and teresa will call you i'll go i'll go check on oh and
welcome back i missed you yeah thanks thank you
you should take some time to recuperate before you come to the guild what do you got what game
spinner box you better believe it i'm in all right let's go this one i need more of a bet
than this look at how awesome this one is it was a super one i need to level up my gambling skill
come on put it all on the spinner box yes all right let me just level up and see what it does
this is like i took a hundred bucks guys i'm just gonna spam until i get there time control
slows the coins down wait what no it doesn't i just want to see what happens when you level up
holy shit i just got that was a big hit that was huge that's 500 chips how close am i leveling up
all right chips go points all right points the next level 842 let's go i'm at 650 i'm fine oh
the sunflowers uh the sunflower is doing really well still in the stage of where they're growing
very very rapidly the stocks are getting huge they're not they don't have any any buds yet
they're becoming big large stocks all right 672 the ones i have are supposed to get to be six
feet tall so it's gonna be really interesting i'll get some pictures for you don't worry i think i'll
snap a few photos we all know it's marijuana no all right almost there come on just spam i can't
imagine sitting here and doing this like i said like level five gambling this would be so annoying
let's take forever let's take hours and hours of time to do this i just i might get like an
expression or something it's possible i'll get an expression almost hold on adjust the bet i can
only do 10 probably to level two i can't i don't think i can do time control 172 left i haven't
spent any money so don't worry change your category to cringe i don't think that exists
all right five more spins two three four all right what happens five level up like a five
free spins for leveling up oh no no i didn't okay what do i get congratulations your gambler rating
has increased you may now access new games and borrow additional gold what that's stupid let's
go see if i can find my wife now still don't know how to kiss no i don't your family has a gift for
you home okay let's go yeah i'm probably i'm gonna call it here soon did not get to the end of fable
too but unfortunately i think i don't know if we'll uh i think we got what we wanted out of it
i'm not going to be streaming um i won't be live technically me i mean it depends i have obligations
to somebody uh so sunday is a stream i wouldn't miss it if i were you uh but maybe the week after
oh there they are finally and the kid i already met him he hates me
yes
good stream thanks thanks for the water down of water i appreciate it
uh yeah uh there's the dog okay all right so honestly hey why do they don't like me
i gotta all right
okay i gotta go um hello son it's good to see you i i know you like uh i'm gonna show you a funny
trick from the manure manner uh that's my house oh my god who just said that and why are you a
dick are you serious are you fucking kidding me no i'm right here i'm right here i'm not leaving
i'm leaving i'm here that was your wife what why would you say something like that
good boy good boy your dad isn't stupid your dad's real smart you know
have to go there everybody just get the fuck out of my life permanently i'll do it
wait a minute wait a minute wait wait a minute i can fix this i'm a sorcerer god damn it
if i can't do it then who the fuck can everybody relax i'll bring everybody back oh no i had to
all right wait wait a minute wait wait don't oh oh that's what it does i didn't know that's
what it did oh hey vortex how can they not see me oh that guy's dying a lot that guy's having
that guy's having a bad time oh god he's still going he's still alive i think this guy's still
alive holy shit this guy is in another dimension oh my god all right boy what do you say you and i
get out of here it was five seconds ago run away run away what's going on oh this is my house
no this is my house nobody can come in nobody can come into my house this is a safe zone
nobody can come in you can't come into my house see if you come in here you're breaking the rules
this is a safe spot yeah you can't get me in my house ow all right i'm going to bed wait this is
not my house whose house is this whose house i thought this is my house oh no this is not my
house whose house is this oh i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm backing out i'm getting up i'm really
sorry this is not my house this was not this is not my house i thought it was it has the same
bird houses i'm sorry stop no i'm not gonna just go i'm out there is my house
okay now i'll be protected see we have the same bird houses look can't take this job when you're
wanted by the law oh it's too bad i would have just cut wood while they killed me there we go
this is my house get out of my house army of the dead wait what what are these are these buried
under the house what what the hell is what is this okay just go to bed it'll all be over
i'm just gonna pay the fine come on if it was up to me i'd ban all use of magic
i'm trying all right the stream is over by the way the stream is over i'm trying stop i'm trying
to do something is this a captain i'm not evil okay that's it i'll see you guys later get him
no i'll get all right i'll get him hold on didn't mean to shoot the guy over on the right i really
didn't are you gonna beat the game later um it's not gonna auto save is it no right uh no there's
no auto save no all right we're good all right yeah i'm gonna call it here i'll see you guys next
week i pro i don't think i'm gonna be realistic with you i don't think we're gonna play fable 2
again um i think i got everything i wanted out of it the last two days but in the event that you do
see it again and we'll play it again but i'll see you guys on sunday sunday is gonna be interesting
i'm gonna tell you what's gonna happen but i would not miss it 60 completion yeah i mean the things
that are really left to do that could be interesting or i think there's a few more interesting things
to see i don't know maybe we'll see if i get the itch i'll get the itch if not then i'll play
power washer simulator or something what time on sunday that is a really good question uh probably
keep an eye on the sus because i'm gonna make it uh precisely the day precisely the minute
precisely the hour uh i kind of need to do a little bit of um i'm gonna talk to a person
involved and see exactly when they want to do it uh but keep an eye on the sus it's gonna be sunday
probably evening sunday afternoon to evening depends i'll let you know precisely how late
it's not going to be an early stream let's just put it that way it will absolutely be after like
four or five o'clock pacific that's a guarantee i'll see you next time have a good week thanks
for watching as always hope you enjoyed the stream it was a lot of fun fable 2 is a lot of fun
i talked a lot of shit about the the shooting mechanics it was all in good fun though i don't
mean half of those things able it's a great game it's a i remember it was a very fun game it was
very ambitious but it was um i would put it up there is it is absolutely worth playing it was
very good very funny it's just a fun experience it really is okay so i am gonna dump you guys on
lidwig like pokemon pokemon platinum has banned 147 people today is that what that is well don't
be part of the don't don't make it to 150 uh go say hello i'll see you guys later have a wonderful
rest of your week thanks for watching again go say hi to lipic let me get the ending screen up
yeah there it is and and by the way you got to get this raid over at least six or seven
thousand to make me look good come on come on well come on what's going on
ego maniac come on give me six give me 6200 and i'll do it i mean i want to make you look bad
less than 6000 raid omega low come on say erin and we will erin erin yep erin i just increased it by
one but i probably decreased it by 10 so i need 20 more of you all right there you go you're
almost there you're right there you're right there no no people stopped people clicked off
damn it all right we're good we're good we're good good come on 10 seconds i'll see you guys
on sunday get it to 6000 come on it's right there do it no come on