Perfect timing. I just oh, I didn't have any music playing
perfect timing
F 099 cool. Oh, all right. How do I do it? Just queue up?
Your ranking is visible. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's fine. Okay, so I've never played f0. This is actually really fun
I'm really into this. So there's some basics before your first f0.99 race with players from around the world
Okay, steer boost accelerate and then sliding just focus on steering
That's how you get health probably. Oh
Should I be drifting or something?
Okay, boost there's a while accelerating keep in mind boost drains your power run out of power
You'll be in danger of crashing out. Oh, I see. It's like an indicator up there
But don't use it again
Colliding with barriers and opponents drains power, but you can recharge power in the pit area. Avoid people
Whoa
Okay, well that was that wasn't good, okay slide to avoid players
It's a strafe
Super sparks drop by gold bumpers and from collisions between machines to fill your super meter
Okay, press a when your super meter is charged to fly on the skyway
Okay, so I need super I need a super boost. Ah
That's cool. You essentially get your own track
You fall off of it. No, but you do that with a hundred people. Let's go. You're ready
25 pilot race
Okay, let's do it. You got some practice to do. It was my machine. Oh
I want durability
wild goose
I'm doing wild goose. Okay. So are these real players of these bots?
So what you're saying is I should absolutely come in first place, but go accelerate to avoid slipping around
I was gonna ask that spin attack
That's cool. Let's do it. Now. I get it. They don't have coins. Wow
How come they're not golden? Oh, the strafe is actually good to use on turns. Sometimes
Just killed that person. My whole face is itchy, but I can't do anything about it. Okay. No, I
Tried
I'm okay
Cool jump. Okay, so I did it slow down in the pit. I could have slowed down
I just figured I want to keep up pace. I
Did it now it's time for the real players
50 pilot race not quite
Task failed successfully. We're good
What is a grip the road with a fast one back speed for 62 for 78?
big blue
Different track I think starting now. You'll have to finish within the safe rank of each lap to continue
Oh, that's I like that. This is cool. I get it now. Okay, try to finish in the top 35
Do it. Let's really screw this person's day up
Not bad. Hmm. Is there a break or is it just gas get out of the way?
Oh my goodness get out of the way. You're just ruining everything
Get this shit out of the way
Okay, you have to be in 40th place. I'm in first place. I'm good
So this is a way to mess with the person in first place. I get it start passing people. I think very soon here
There you are. I don't even need the boost just drive
Okay, so you can die I was not aware that you could explode and be out
I thought it was gonna like key to me and just put me back on the track in like 15th place
Okay, good to know stay on the road good
So if I cross to the next lap, am I eliminating people that are in those bottom places?
Is that how that works? Because if you're real you try as hard as you can you just eliminate people. Oh, wow
That's crazy. Okay, cool
Okay, no, all right just drive I'm way ahead of everybody
Don't I just somebody else's blew up. I should be pretty far ahead. All right, there we go
People up. All right, we're good. We're good. Fine. That's fine
There's a lot of red. I knew you're gonna hit by that
That was not fair. No stop. Oh my god. What the fuck?
You can just get exploded
Okay, let's do it turn it up a little I'll turn it up. This is so fun, though
Is that too loud or is that good?
Don't even try hard. Why am I trying really hard just wait to the last lap and then boost past everybody in the last two
Seconds, what if I never played a racing game before?
Just stay within ten places
Top ten, you'll be fine
Just look they're all gonna drive into the red things always stay in 10th place
Collect all this bullshit
Good okay, but I'm 10th place hurt dude. You just gotta do a little bit of an excuse me right there
honey help I
almost have a
Super meter. All right. I'll win this right here
Watch out for the explosion stay behind let him do it. Let him hit it
But watch that turn how we now we punch it. Okay, I get it now. This is fun
I should really like this a lot. This is time for the real deal. Your last trial will be a 99 pilot race
final tutorial
Feel like I like it's a little more a little more durable. Yeah
It's not Mario Kart timing wait until right before the race starts
Okay, I'll try it. Oh my goodness. I'm so sorry. This thing just almost fell down
What is this?
You'll now be racing against rival pilots of similar skill ratings
Okay, if you finish with a higher rank than your rival your skill rating will increase
Straightaway, I don't think this boost in this one
Good job. It's a rival it is these are boss. You said right still I can't let my rival beat me
She's driving like shit and I'm still not ahead of him. There we go. 10th place. That's what I want
It's place. Is that okay? Oh
Two rivals defeated
machine
You receive ticket points based on how well you do in each race
Collect enough ticket points and you can earn tickets to allow you to enter grand pre and mini pre events
Now this is the real deal. Now. You're ready to race online
You'll need three tickets to be in the grand prix
Special event pro track taking the most dip. No
All right. Let's just do it for real. This is it, right? All right, let's go
I'm gonna stay on wild goose. So what's considered a win? Is it like hearthstone battlegrounds top four top three top five top ten
What's considered a win just don't die off 80 does just survive to be honest. Oh, wow. It's that difficult. Okay
Oh shit, I'm going against the Joker. All right, I'm gonna try to get in
25th or above place
Yeah, this is a mess, but I like it just get all the coins. I'm not doing super boost till the last second
How come nobody drives on the road?
85 what place my in people have to be getting pretty low on health. How do I miss that?
Alright, somebody's exploded
Please oil slicks. Oh, I was avoiding those the whole time. I thought that was oil on the ground now
Alright, let me try that again. Now knowing that that's not what that is. I thought it was oil
Just survive. Okay, nice
Grand Prix starts in
12 minutes. I can do that. I got enough tickets, right? Oh 12 minutes. Okay. Let me practice. I've practiced
try
Each race is four or five minutes. Oh for a track big blue. Why not? These are the rivals. We're all C-
It's okay. Good luck everybody. All right, I'm just gonna drive and not even worry about anything else. I
Didn't get that. He's dead already
It's so rich when this it's ridiculous when there's this many people on here
Hey better than last time. Hey, I don't want to die big opportunity here lots of people dying right now
All right better than last time 43, I'm a C
driver
Drive time for another couple. So what's the strategy to actually get in first place?
Does it just try to get out in front is I'm gonna try that this time
I'm gonna try getting out in front really really quickly use all my boost just get to first place
Again, no one to use the highways you kill another you get a full boost
Use the skyway on tight corners
It's all about knowing when to boost it's fun regardless though, even if you're in 40th place top 50, that's the bet
I could do it again. I'm just gonna stay with the group. It's hard to stay with the group
Shit. Oh, I want that. It'll be useful if I can get it
Skip everybody. All right, get it again. I freaked out for a second, but it's fine. Oh
I forgot I forgot I forgot I forgot him. I'm dead. Oh, man. I completely didn't repay attention to the bar. I
Completely just I got into complete tunnel vision. It was like just boost to try to get up to like 30
And what I had it to
About this one. So how long do you when you boost for the final time?
Are you just susceptible to dying in one hit when you take yourself down to the to zero?
Maybe even just avoid that part. Honestly the very beginning. I
Don't overdo it
Dead already, dude. All right, so I
Got passed by everybody and I drove on the road
I drove like on the correct part of the road and they all blew by me
Okay, if you just boost over it's don't even do turns
Yeah, that's what it is. I don't even you don't drive on the real road
Yeah, I'm just gonna try to stay alive way too early. All right, I need this bad. Oh, how did it miss?
Wednesday Grand Prix two minutes. Do I have time to wait? I'm gonna wait
I'm gonna get I'm gonna destroy it on this one
Go in practice. I
Kind of want to do this though. I want to see it
Select it right now. Oh
Let's go. I'm going back to Wild Goose
It's good for me
What is port town to
Hey, I might get lucky because if these tracks are really really hard then people might just explode
All right. Here's I'm gonna just do old lady driving. I feel like it's gonna be helpful. This is not Grand Prix
This didn't set up. I just had a countdown on it. Didn't oh
I thought this is the one they leave
Oh
Well, why did this one have a countdown I can do it after
Sneak by that one
Whoa, whoa, should I touch those? Oh, they're sucking us to them. I get it. I thought I was supposed to touch those
It's getting hard now. All right, just don't die. I almost have one. Come on
Give me this. Oh now I know why this is a pro track because we still have to be on
I should have drove like an old lady. My god. I've no experience with these things. It's scary
Can they see my health? I hope not. This is a big deal if I can hit this
Great about 50. I did it. So do I get to stay in the race?
Got a lot of tickets
brand-free
night league
Test your metal in the ultimate five race series
all right, I'm gonna do this and
We are going to this be it I'm gonna call it after this
Stay on goose. The bet is for the first race. Will he reach top 50 in the next race?
That's what you're betting on. All right, let's do it. These are difficult. No, it's okay if I lose I'm sorry off 80 advance
That's all I'm I'm gonna drive like an old. I don't care about winning. I just need to get to number 79. That's it
That's all I care about watch this. What's all these watch all these weirdos watch this. They used to get all drive
How would you do that need to get to 80th place? Oh
You guys bet that's right
My bad my bad. I could I'll try I'll try
That's right. Sorry
Hey, don't be stupid I can get up to 50 in one second at the very end here. Oh, I have to get up now
Good I made it I made it I made it. I'm fine. I'm fine. Oh
My god, that was terrifying but we're good
Yeah, almost I tried I really did not bad though I
ranked up
Okay. So now there are 80
Honestly, my strategy is just to stay in the very back
Whatever the maximum number is
Try to get to this very very slowly try to get to top 20 top 40. I have nobody pay attention to me
So this is top 60 fast
I'll try to get to 50 at the very end
I'm gonna try to get as high a place as I can
Okay, now we do it now. I'm gonna hang out in this thing here good place to do it. Fuck out of my way
Come on, give me those coins
Yeah
31 I'm in the bees now
Top 50 now top 40 good race
See, this is where it gets weird because I've gotten top 50 a few times but top 40 top 20
This really might be actual grandma mode for real this time
I'm gonna try to conserve boost as much as I possibly can
Whoa, that was weird. Where are we going? Oh, we're crossing over each other
Easy hold this for now, you know
I'll stay in 10th place. I don't care. I got a kale
Grandma, you got to drive better than this
All right. Here we go
I'm not doing anything stupid. I had to use it because I want to stay up here with everybody. All right, just drive
I'm still safe. Just gotta get to top 40
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Top 30 that was my nephew you KO'd
You threw so bad. No, I got full boost just started spamming egg
This is okay. Cool. I'm doing all right. I got B pluses as my rivals now. This one has wind. Top 20 advance
You know what?
That's fine. I don't got to be in first place. I just have to get into 30th place. My camera's tilted
I don't like it
Stay up here. I gotta stay up in 30
Am I safe? All of you fucking clowns get out of the way
It's happening, but I hope I'm doing okay
All right, just heal heal heal. I'm fine. I'm just gonna bump the fuck out of this thing. Yes
I need coins
Dude, I need coins
Give me that coin
Fuck oh shit. Oh, I
Had it too. That was really fun. Oh fuck. Oh shit. It got bumped too many times. I would have made it too
Too bad
All right, let me do one more race one more. I don't want to watch this like fall guys
I don't want to watch the people jump on the cubes for like fucking 40 minutes. Do I have to sit here?
This is the final though. Oh, that's true
Spectate. Spectate leader. Let's see. Let's see how well you do
Seriously, what is the secret here? Show it to me. Not bad. Ah, there's a shortcut. Is that a shortcut?
I don't know. Who's number one? All right, this is
Bronze is in a first place again
Still in first place. So you take a left you gotta hit that jump
Risky, but saves a lot of time
I'm asleep behind. Yeah. All right. Ooh
Almost just hit the red
Good recovery good recovery. Oh
Still top four
Use your attack more does the attack use boost? I've been afraid to use it. It does not. Okay, just a cool-down
It's really actually awesome. Oh
And bronze pull it through not going for the risky play going for the continuous just stay in fourth place. Oh
And that's it it's a good idea stay in fourth, all right
Let me do one more because I actually really do like this. GG. Nice job. So they actually
Wow, it's only
two hours
Those are special cool special event team battle. How are your team to victory? I don't want to drag somebody down
Alright one last bet for the night
Don't really care where we go, but why not?
What is a top 50 I
Think it's doable now. Oh bronze is right in front of us. I was gonna stay right next to bronze the whole entire game
I don't even know where he is
That was pretty good. We've just freaked me out and I'm the one that hurt him
He bounced off the wall and hit me and it freaked me out
way worse
That one doesn't count I'm really I'm like exclaiming really a lot today
Feel like I'm watching a boxing match like whoa, don't dodge it. Whoa
Popcorns going everywhere. All right. This is the real last one. I was almost in the 25 to final last one
You're at three to one odds. You got to take the dark side. You got to try to make that uh, make those channel points
That's funny. I like that
Yeah, let's check this out
I've been I've been just
Been faking it the whole time watch this. I'm gonna get top 20. I'm gonna be a nail-biter. I
Just grabbed the wall and ran my head into it over and over again
Wait a shit
Give me a minute
Sir, I'm in a good position right now. I actually am that's how we that's called
Good
See you later suckers. So long suckers
I did it. I got it. All right that unlocked one more
actual final for real the last one
I'm just happy
Tried to be the team one
All right, we'll do team battle and that'll be the last one
Race aggressively with your team and fight for victory highest team score wins
any ko's
Go fast. I don't know which one I prefer probably this one
Okay, pink team versus a green team earn points and lead pink to victory, okay
Pink team takes the lead. It's a good amount of points so far
Losing surrounded by greens
Okay
Come on pink. All right, I'm gonna farm this
Okay, I'm not gonna touch it once this is what I meant to say. Oh
That was a good good hits good hits
we win
pink wins
Yes, we did
Surely one more. Yeah, it might as well just go out with one final one. I got it. Did I get a new thing?
Wait, how do I?
Might do that
No, that's not what I wanted. Okay. Well, um, I tried to go to workshop and it bounced around and
Let's go
Okay
Just a mini Grand Prix. We're okay. You don't have to end the stream. No, we're cool. I'm cool
I planned on stopping around like 730, but no, we're good. I'm good. Just chillin in the background right now
there's just like the
trading floor of the New York Stock Exchange
You guys are all just screaming at each other about buying and selling. I gotta get to at least top. Back in the green
full charge almost
here we
here we go
Perfect actually perfect
perfect
Perfect. Okay go. I did it top 25. Nice
Now I gotta go from top 25 to top 10
these are
Just done very quickly, too. I like that a lot. So does that put me in a better place?
I imagine it probably does is this top? It's top 60. That's it. Very addictive. It is I love it though. This is great
Yeah, okay somebody's dead that always sucks I have to do it now
Final lap coming up. I just need my super boost for the final lap and I'm good. Got it some health
I have a lot of time left. Let's do it
It's
All right, this is the last one
I've never seen the end probably top 50 for the last one. Where does that put me overall?
24th overall
that accurate
This upcoming level sucks. Prepare yourself. Oh, this does look really really hard
that you tell me I have to go through a fucking queue from
Roller roller coaster tycoon that could have been a much cleaner joke
You know what I was saying, you got to go over the jumps it's really important not that not bad actually
Could have been way worse
I didn't mean to do that, but it's okay. It's a really bad place to use this but at least get across this part. Oh
Just me and you Matt
Me and Matt hanging out in the very bottom. I'm dead. This is this is ridiculously hard
That was fun. That was fun. Machines
fire stingray
decals boost
Level five. What does that do?
There's a different boost
Yeah, we have to see what it looks like
grandpa playing knockoff Mario Kart
I'm surprised how much I really like this. Where's my
That wasn't me. They're adding some more maps at the end of September just melt pac-man 99 was like this too, though
I got really really addicted to that for like a whole night a couple nights
Played it. You could did it off stream, too
That's what I did for like three days straight off screen
And I got so mad at one point that I went
Fucker and I put both my legs up and put both my heels down. I went through the ground
although at the same time I
Would use it, but I'm not going to
Perfect placement. That was pretty good
Hey
Collect these so I can do it at the very end
I'm gonna be good at this might be actually really great
Let me get top 15. Let me get top 15 right here
Yes, everybody avoid me top 15, let's go
Getting better. I'm psyching myself up big time tonight. Somebody's behind me. That's the spirit. Yeah
All right. Well, I can't go until you lose. I think that's the good philosophy here because I did I just did 22
Now I just did 13
If I go if I place under 13, then I'm gonna get out here and get there. It's dinner time
Let me take out one headphone because I'm like speech jamming myself here. There we go. Are you listening to yourself?
No, it's just sometimes when music and noises in both ears. I can't hear myself talk. Sometimes I go. Where am I?
Cannot hear anything. All right, I gotta get at least in the top 12. All right, I'm getting a little too cocky here
Oh, I didn't get the kill for that
Time to I go drive like grandma until next round
Shit. Oh
Well, this was a bad one speaking of the one to lose
Nobody touch me. Nobody touch me. Don't touch me. Nobody touch me. I finished it
All right. I'll see you guys later
Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out
probably
Looking at the calendar
I'm gonna be seeing some family. I will not be around. I also have some work stuff to do
So the next time you see me
Will be probably at the I want to say Tuesday of next week gonna be visiting family
And then we'll probably we'll probably end up doing a couple streams
next week
Probably Tuesday and Sunday. I want to get a couple in next week
Because there's a there's a couple things. I really want to do. I want to play armored core. I
Really want to do
Yes, it is my birthday this week as well. And hey this thing family for my birthday. So that should be that should be nice
Yeah, I'll be back on Tuesday and then we'll do armored core probably
We'll figure what we're gonna do on Sunday. Maybe browser games
Let's get back to the goofy browser games on Sunday of next week
Been a while my 38th birthday. Yes, it is
Getting there another few years another couple of years and I'm gonna be I don't know. It's gonna be weird
Two more years till the judgment day at 40
Did you queue again? No the the computer took over you
Leave the controller on the table for a few minutes of the CPU takes over kind of like left dead
I wonder how they do food mode fog
Yeah, I'll see you next week
Ending on 69 was not good enough for you
It was it was good enough, but I kind of had to do it differently
Don't booze not right now. I'm in 30th. I'm fine. Okay final lap drive good
Take it easy. I didn't get credit for that. I didn't hit shit
Oops wrong button, but I'm okay. Oh
That's bad. Oh, that's very very very bad. I got I just got destroyed
Lucky bumper, what am I doing?
I get to be I want to play one more. I
Want to play one more and I'm going to because it's my birthday
And I'm also almost 40 so I get to dictate when I stop screaming
And when I want to go to bed, and I'm not ready for bed yet. I
Want to keep playing
Understand I'm gonna go a new strategy on this one, and then this is actually the final one for real
There's no joking around right now. Actually. I'm gonna leave after this. It's a fun stream though finally be breath of the wild
Did the punch-out thing like this did goldenite gold my controls were awful
If I play that again, I definitely want to switch it up for the other ones
Still fun to do facility again though if I just hit L&R and inside of all that big group
I kind of just mess everything up don't I yeah?
I'm fine sitting right in the middle for now
But let's go ahead and use this right
Avoid all the bullshit
Okay, that's good. That's good. All right now. I just want to get leveled up
Yeah, there we go all right last lap I got a lot of boost don't waste it. Oh, I forgot that was the last lap
I got top 50 so I don't know why I was thought that was one more
Okay, all right see you later. I said it out loud. Yeah, but
It's different processing versus saying something that one didn't even count you're right
He's never gonna end I'm ending after this
But you guys put me on this game, and I can't get away from it
Did the other one still exists like the Mario one the pac-man one Tetris?
Because I could seriously play
These for an entire stream just all night
They don't exist anymore
Better start don't talk all right no talking this whole match, and I'll get the top line here. We go
Pump me out of that. Oh my god. What a disaster
Okay, here we go final lap and I have pretty much full boost probably get it again
Stop 25. We got it. Bye. Good night top 25. That's how you go out
You come in not first place not second place not third place not even 10th place
You go so far down, but they don't give medals anymore, and they haven't in a very long time
Let's go
Okay
What if I did this one of the goofy boys or something you guys would like that right
I turn it on
Hello, I go up to our sometimes. It doesn't work
You act like you're not gonna sit and play this off stream. Anyways. Do you get it?
You know exactly what's gonna happen
It's gonna happen is I'm gonna take this in the bathroom and drop the biggest dump of my entire life
Well, I beat everybody in this game
How many people in this lobby right now are sitting on the toilet? It's 99 people here. I'll be like 60 people
I gotta be aggressive. No, I care way too much about that thing. Yeah
Well, I I wanted to end it. Anyways, did I just am I safe?
That's fun. I will see you guys on Tuesday. Thanks for watching. Always Pac-man is going away in October
Oh, that's sad. Yeah. Have a good night. See you guys next week. We'll stream twice next week
I think I could get a couple in there. Maybe I'll play the Pac-man one again
I feel like I really like that check. Can I just I think I'm just gonna do that on Tuesday. That sounds fun
Maybe I'll play this again on Tuesday play Pac-man 99 on Tuesday. Maybe some armored core. Maybe some sorcery. I'll see
Yeah, Pac-man is gone on October. Yeah
Okay. Well, that was fun. Hope you had a good time everybody. We'll see you in a little bit longer
but got some birthday stuff I'm doing and
It'd be nice to see some family. Thanks for the birthday wishes. Appreciate it
Mm-hmm. No, there's no music. I'm just in here breathing. Oops. He's just awkwardly breathing into the microphone
There's the heart guys. See you later. Just waiting to the
crystal button
Now see you guys Tuesday. Take care. Call your mother. See you soon. Have a great one. See you later