Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight gonna be playing with the Huntsman Sniper.
Something I haven't done in a pretty long time. I think the last time I played Huntsman was when I was in North Carolina for helping my sister and being there for Thanksgiving.
So my goodness, that's been November, December, October. Oh my goodness, it's been a long time.
And I actually have a really interesting topic for this video, and it's something I want to talk about, something really cool I was thinking of.
And it has to do with, first I'll tell you the loadouts. Loadout's gonna be the Huntsman, the Jurati, and the Bushwhacker.
And I kind of feel naked with this setup, because I really like having the Darwin's Danger Shield.
And without it, I really do feel like I'm outside naked in my underwear in 20 degree weather.
I mean, but honestly though, I just like having that extra bit of security, that extra health to counteract enemy snipers.
If I get body shot, I probably won't die. And of course, if a stray rocket comes in and takes me down to 15 health, I'm not gonna die in that situation either.
But you're given your take though, because the Jurati is a fantastic item, and I use it once or twice here to get some assists, and to kill somebody with the Bushwhacker.
So it goes hand in hand. It doesn't matter what you put on, as long as you're putting something on.
Alluding to my naked argument I just made, two-set, whatever.
So this commentary is going to very, very, very, very much so focus on primary weapons like the Huntsman.
Now I don't mean all primary weapons, or the rocket launcher, or the syringe gun.
I'm talking about primary weapons that totally change the direction of a class.
I don't think there's any other item in the game, besides the Huntsman, that totally changes the default weapon that is supposed to be there.
Now that's the only way I can really describe this. It's the default weapon that is supposed to be there.
Let's take for instance a rocket launcher for the soldier. They have rocket launcher, rocket launcher, rocket launcher.
There's nothing else besides the rocket launcher for the primary slot.
The sniper differs in an amazing way, because of course he has three or four sniper rifles, but he also has this damn thing.
And I think it's so amazing when Valve takes some of these items and they create different subclasses with the primary weapons.
And I wish I would see it more often.
No other class has a weapon like this that totally differs from the default.
Like I said, the sniper rifle, sniper rifle, sniper rifle, bow and arrow. Whoa, what?
It's amazing. And I kind of wanted to make this video to get some of your guys' responses and some of your feedback.
What would you put in this game for some of the other classes?
Let's say for instance the heavy. He's got of course the miniguns.
So what would you guys in the comments section let me know?
What would you give, not only the heavy, but what would you give the other classes to make it sort of like the Huntsman versus the sniper rifles?
And I was thinking about this in my bed the other night. I was going, you know, the soldier.
The soldier should probably have some type of maybe assault rifle or something like that, or maybe a different type of grenade launcher,
or maybe something like that. I was just kind of going all over the place.
But it really gets you thinking because they've already done it with the Huntsman and the sniper rifles.
There are two totally different weapon classes.
And really the only other one I can think of besides the Huntsman is probably the shortstop or maybe even the pompson for the engineer.
But those are still kind of in the same category as their default counterparts.
So just wanted to throw that out there. And hopefully we see some more of these cool items.
Hopefully Valve throws us some more cool stuff.
But it just got me thinking and I of course wanted to get your guys opinions because when I'm rolling around in bed thinking,
okay, that sounded really bad. Let's redo this.
When I'm in various modes of deep contemplation and in undisclosed locations,
I like to throw the ideas off people and you guys always bounce back with some really good responses.
And I do read every single comment.
So if you throw a comment at me and you don't think I'm going to read it or it's too long,
and he's not going to read this, I will read it. I read everything.
And I can't reply to everybody.
And that's just because the sheer amount of people sometimes that leave comments on these videos or in PMs or whatever.
But really do keep in mind, I do read every comment and I do appreciate every single one of those comments,
whether it be constructive criticism or whether that be something good.
I appreciate all of it, guys.
And I know already that I'm going to get so many good responses to this particular video question thing.
And yeah, I'm looking forward to it, guys.
So that is going to wrap up this particular video.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I forgot to mention, this is a one-life from start to finish,
where I complete the entire round without dying.
I forgot to mention that.
So one-life gameplay is the Huntsman sniper.
And I will see you guys all soon.
So take care, everybody.