Hi, my name is Mr. Traff.
The herd. Let's go. I can't. I'm like up to the elephant's ass.
You're going to change the view a lot.
Let's go find somebody to rough him up.
Let's go rough somebody up. Elephant style.
This guy. This guy.
Get him. We can't hit him.
We don't know where my body is. We got him.
All right, he's dead.
Can we eat the flesh just like elephant do?
Yes.
All right, you hear the one about the two elephants?
Get in. You're doing the dancing.
There are seriously no, I'd love to make a couple of jokes or something, but this is like,
there is nothing that can be said.
This elephant dance is just perfect. He just leaps over, taps his foot.
Hold on a second. What is this going to look like? Get on this bike.
It's like they dropped like a dead elephant on a bike.
All right, let's go.
His butt's so crutched up.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. One more. I got to.
Oh, you're the giraffe now?
We're zoo pals. Zoo pals make eating fun.
Oh, zoo pals.
You just disappeared.
I love zoo pals. I love animal crackers.
The elephants didn't want anything to do with it.
What the fuck?
Okay. So, oh, look at this one coming down the street.
He's going pretty fast.
I wish he drove through this whole crowd.
Why are they such psychos?
Why aren't these elephants doing anything?
I don't know.
Oh, they'll be back.
No, no.
No, get in.
Later.
All right, I got this elephant.
I'm tracking down an elephant.
Elephant on a bike.
He's going pretty, pretty goddamn fast.
Here he goes. Do you see him?
Oh, you're getting to chase on the elephant.
Oh, I don't want to go that fast.
Wow. He really is.
He's flooring it.
How is he weaving out of traffic that well?
Probably not that well.
He's all right. He got back on track.
He just came out of the fence.
He's more interesting.
The elephant's gone now.
This guy's way more interesting.
Get him. Get him.
Kick his ass.
They all want this one truck.
Who's going to win?
They are all just fighting over the same car.
They really are.
There's other cars.
You idiots.
I'm trying to push it to get one of them out of here.
As soon as they get thrown out of the car, too,
it's like they don't want to drive anymore.
Yeah. Whoever's the last person that gets in
is the one that's driving.
Oh, maybe not.
I don't know.
One out of the herd.
What the fuck are you doing?
You dicks.
What is up with these psychos?
The winner.
Is your feet up the truck?
Oh, I'm passing out.
Hold on.
Get in.
I can't.
I can't breathe.
Get in.
I can't.
I'm so confused in the city.
Oh, that's a 10-4.
Bye.
Where are you going?
I'm just trying to find it.
Can you breathe?
I think my game broke.
Yeah, you didn't respond.
What was the movie?
Dumbo Drop?
What's the movie?
Quick.
What's the name of that fucking movie?
It's Dumbo Drop, Dumbo Drop and Disconnected.