You know, when I, when I come in this room here, I go over to the chat and I'm still just kind of preparing to walk in here with a coffee, Randola bar and naked and I see that the webcam's light is on and I look in the chat and I see, shh, we can hear him.
I can hear him. I think that's the most panic inducing thing for any live streamer is that I pressed, I turned the button on somehow.
Like I pressed it or I clicked it and I just didn't realize it. I'm just broadcasting live, just me being weird.
Like I'm not concerned about like the quote hot mic, right? Like a hot mic, he's saying something hot, he's saying something bad.
No, no, no, I'm concerned about the pre hot mic. Like the pre, like the stream, like the thing is not even on yet and I'm walking around naked. Pre hot mic.
Yeah, cause you, screen cap. At the age of the screen cap, if something, if like something happens on like TV, see like, like 30 years ago, if something happened on a piece of video, it wasn't like 15 million people could just screen cap and they would, they would have it right there.
You had to like hear about that in the news later or have been recording it on VHS for some reason. 15 million viewer Andy.
No, I'm just saying like the, the act of like if, oh no, no, no, it's okay. It's okay. I was only naked for like two seconds. I sprinted out of the way and like whatever, nobody saw it. It doesn't matter, right?
I mean, people saw it, but like, okay, that's fine. No, if that happened now in like 2021, not only would it be like, oh no, people can't just forget about it, whatever. Like there would be memes of me with a clown wig on and like, you would like me, I'm not even gonna say the rest of it.
I was gonna say something. I was gonna say something. I was gonna say a clown wig on and you know, I was gonna say something else. It would be photoshopped a thousand times and it would be everywhere.
And now it was just like, it can't just be like a thing you hear about on like the, the channel two news once a week later. Say the whole thing.
Okay. No, I know I'm not gonna do that. I was gonna say put a clown nose. Forget it. Let's move on. We're gonna move on. We're moving on.
I'd be in a clown wig, a clown nose. You'd put like, I don't know. No, no, no, no, no. I have this all wrong. Here's what actually would happen. You would run my naked body through like the AI generators, like AI face generator.
Let's like run his, what does he look like? And it would be like cropped images of my face and stuff, like the AI generator. That's what happened.
You know how many like weird like the thing faces would come from that screen cap? People, people in this, you guys would probably ask me to make it an emote.
Hey dude, when are we gonna get Jerma's screen cap naked as an emote? I don't know, dude. Why would, no. What are you talking about?
Anyways, how you doing? How are you? Welcome to the stream. I didn't even tweet this. I don't even, what didn't happen? I've been like just talking.
All right, I'll bring it back. I'm gonna tweet. Let people trickle in. We'll discuss. Bring it back.
You know, I promised my mother I'd be less vulgar on stream. I gotta, I gotta, I gotta keep my mother's, my promise to my mother.
All right, let me tweet this and we'll talk about the plan over the next couple of days. I'm still kind of fucked up.
For those of you that are unaware, I've been on an antibiotic for a while and it's given me stomach gastro problems. It's given me like headaches and shit.
Uh, they're still here, but like I want to stream and I want to just not do anything.
So we're gonna, I'm gonna, until, until I'm like not feeling great, maybe we'll see. I'm hoping I can be here for at least a few hours.
Delay plans. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, well actually that's true. We did, uh, the plan with italics got kind of screwed up.
Antibiotic Andy. Thing you just did. And Andy. Take a sip of coffee. Coffee Andy. I have to go to the doctor. Dr. Andy.
I'm gonna play Darkest Dungeon today. Darkest Dungeon Andy. It's such a, so it fills anything. It really is like the, it's so, uh, it's funny.
Terrible title. Yeah, I know. I just, I, it made me chuckle for a second and I was just like, whatever. Fuck it. I don't care.
Okay. Um, I didn't capitalize the D in Dungeon, so everyone please, please scream at me.
Okay. Uh, we're gonna play Darkest Dungeon 2 today. It's in early access. Play Darkest Dungeon 1.
Uh, on this stream years ago. And I think a little off stream too. I played through a lot of it.
I thought it was good. I'm obviously gonna play the second one, so here we are.
So that's today. Tomorrow, if you want to mark on your calendar, tomorrow we're going to do Public Domain Movie Night.
For those of you that have not, don't know what that is, maybe you haven't been here for the last few weeks.
Public Domain Movie Night is we find movies in the public domain, specifically because Halloween, horror movies.
So old, like 1930s, 1950s horror movies. And we're gonna watch them.
As long as they're in the public domain, they have been selected. There's about 10 of them.
I don't think we're gonna be able to watch all 10, so we're gonna have to prioritize them a little bit.
So we're gonna watch at least probably 4 to 6, 5, 6. And there are, I don't know very much about them.
All I know is that they exist. And we're gonna watch them.
And no, it's, and no, unfortunately no Ritz Brothers.
The Gorilla is the only Ritz Brothers movie in the public domain. It's, I, I, I'm surprised. No Ritz Brothers.
Is it, here's something really funny. I was contemplating.
I didn't do it because like, it's just like, I, you guys know Community Jake, right?
I was contemplating just calling Community Jake.
And just being like, hey, Community Jake, um, how, how do we get the licensing rights for me to stream the Ritz Brothers content?
And I feel like he would just be like, I don't, what are you talking about, man?
But it was an idea. I wonder how much that would be.
I feel like that might be either way too little or way too much. And maybe I should find out.
Like imagine getting the licensing rights to stream like two or three of the Ritz Brothers movies.
I don't know. Bionicle. Yeah, I can't, Bionicle's not, look, we are, free does not mean broadcastable in the public domain.
Free on YouTube does not mean public domain film.
Bionicle with Joe Biden. No, that's, that's a funny meme. That's a really funny joke.
You know, you guys are putting the bar way too high. You guys are putting the bar too high.
Like, oh, you should do like a mukbang stream where like you eat all the different fucking fast food restaurants.
No, no, no, no. I want you to stream with the president of the United States of America.
And I want you to watch a movie that you legally cannot watch.
And you have to find a way to do that and license it.
Streamer.
The bar, that bar is too high. I'm never going to cross that bar.
You'll just get pardoned.
Can you imagine? Like I start the stream and like Joe Biden's just in the chair next to me.
I'm just like, hey, by the way, President Biden, Mr. Biden, I'm going to, I'm about to do something legal.
I'm going to stream Bionicle right now. And he's just like, it's all right, man. Don't worry about it.
Here's the deal. I'll just pardon you after this is done.
And like I get sued by the Bionicle team and then Joe Biden just like waves his hand like Jedi master style.
And that's it. That would be that would be like the funniest goddamn thing ever in the history of the world.
But here's the unfortunate thing. Really, really think this is not possible.
I'm sorry. It's fun to think and make up funny scenarios like it's fun.
Or he does it. What if he doesn't pardon me? What if he doesn't pardon me?
We do the whole stream together and he like puts his sunglasses on and stands up and just like, good luck, man.
Hey, have a great rest of your stream.
And he leaves and I'm like, Biden, Biden, what about that pardon?
He's like, what pardon, man? I got work to do.
He's just gone and I just lose everything. I get sued by Bionicle.
Come on, man. It's funny to say that I love coming up with scenarios like this.
Like this. Right. Yeah. But but OK, that's we can move on now.
That's a what if a German cinematic universe. What if I haven't seen any of that, by the way, and I want to.
I don't spoil anything or you're going to be fucking banned permanently.
All right. What was the plan? Plan is today we're going to play Darkest Dungeon 2 and then for a while.
See how long it depends on how much I care.
And then tomorrow we're going to public domain movie night or no stream on Halloween, by the way.
So tomorrow is the Halloween stream.
If Biden doesn't want to even watch Bionicle, sits down and say, hey, you know what I was thinking here.
Here's what I was thinking. Can we watch the funny memes that I used to watch in school?
Forty two on YouTube. I'm just like, OK, no, no, no.
I want to watch clean memes to show your grandma.
Unusual videos compilation is seven hundred and I do it.
Family guy. And he is laughing his ass off at every joke and big like laugh with a big smile.
He's laughing. He's having so much fun. Play the game.
I know. All right. Here's the game. Start. Wait.
OK. Darkest Dungeon 2 is on the Epic Games Store right now.
It's an early access game. Now, here's now here's the deal.
Here's the deal. All right. No, there's no more Joe Biden shit. Let's go.
I got when Darkest Dungeon 1 came out, I didn't play the very early, early access version.
I played it pretty deep into early access, I think I remember.
So apparently this is very early. I hear very mixed things about it so far.
I'm going to give it my own opinion and give my own assessment of the game.
This is Darkest Dungeon 2 early access day one and then brackets plus two plus three.
It's kind of loud. All the bad reviews are just people that are bad.
OK, that should have been the stream title. All right. New journey. Let's go.
I can't wait till he says confidence searches as the enemy scrambles, whatever it is.
Quiet.
Pleat your confession.
I hereby acknowledge and accept the fullness and severity of my mistakes. Denial.
Play cinematic.
I opened it once to just capture it. So let's do cinematic. Quiet. Everybody shut up.
Terrifying new access and everywhere unbridled consequence.
The world is a wasteland of failures past and yet you must ride out into it unafraid.
Confident searches as the enemy crumbles.
Take this. It is hope. The very last of it. It is yours now.
You were bold once, once more.
That was average.
It was below average actually.
Fix your gaze on the horizon and face the fearsome truth of the Darkest Dungeon.
This guy's voice is so distinct.
Do you think he just puts on his resume Darkest Dungeon guy and everyone goes, holy shit, I know who that is.
Like, vocal range, right? Like, oh, what about your resume? Vocal range. Darkest Dungeon guy.
It's like, oh, okay, yeah, I know exactly what you sound like.
And you're hired, by the way.
Okay, complete your confession. Denial.
I sign my name.
The stagecoach. Left click view, right click. Okay, the stagecoach.
The stagecoach is your carriage, your coffin, and your confessional.
Okay, that's kind of extreme.
Press W to drive the coach forward, or double tap W for auto drive.
Use A and D to steer, plus one letter grade.
I mean, I have to, if that's going to be a thing on this channel, we have to stick to it.
That's plus one full letter grade.
Press Z to bring up the stagecoach view.
It shows what upgrades are currently installed on the coach.
Upgrades can be changed at the wainwright who is present at each inn.
Okay, so this show, you can upgrade the stagecoach, okay.
Let's just go.
The flame. Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Flame.
Stagecoach carries the flame, which is the last hope for the world.
It will gradually diminish, as the torch, right, as you drive.
But various actions can refill it.
The lower it gets, the harder things will be for the party.
It's just like the candlelight thing in the first game.
And when the flame gets below 40, things start to get significantly more dangerous for the heroes.
Monsters get combat bonuses, they can get surprised or whatever.
There are increased chances that battle modifiers, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
When the flame reaches zero, heroes are ambushed by the fiendish cultists.
If the heroes survive the fight, the expedition will continue with a tiny flicker of flame still left.
All right, so that's more important than the last game.
The game is really hard.
I beat Spampton first try, so I think I'm still on that high.
I'll be fine.
Crossroads, all right.
Do I have to pick guilt, loathing, failure, regret, disgrace?
Okay, the crossroads.
Okay, is this just the party?
The party.
Four heroes will join together on this expedition.
Our salvation rides with them.
Party creation.
Click and drag hero portraits to assemble your party of four heroes.
Hero in the rightmost position of your, yeah, he's in the combat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can rearrange your party order while driving by clicking and dragging their portraits.
Party order determines what position each hero is in when the battle starts, right?
Yeah, just like the last game.
The furthest hero to the right begins at the front of the, yeah, I know.
I know.
All right, so is this just who we have?
There's only four possible people.
So click and drag them, or are they just here?
Oh, it's down here.
Man in arms is like the tank slash protector.
Guard, yeah, you put guard on somebody and they block attacks.
A highwayman usually goes kind of in the back, right?
It's the ranged.
High damage, yep.
A plague doctor throws the grenades, right?
Throws the poison grenades.
You want this person right in the back.
Brave robber has stealth, right?
You can like stealth and then do like a big dive forward.
I remember the first one.
I played it a lot.
Don't let Joe Biden backseat you on this.
Okay, whatever.
Here we go.
I got my party.
This is where they should be.
Let's go.
Stop pretending.
Let's get out of here.
I just like, I just put made the, I put the party into tutorial positions.
41.
Can you crash?
What if I crash into these leaves?
Is that going to be bad?
Is it bad?
Mike, do I get points for hitting things or not hitting things?
This is a tight turn.
Oh shit.
The academics cash.
Supplies.
Coach of lie.
Clear all corpses.
Do you have an inventory in this one or is it just a giant stagecoach with tons of room?
Dartboard.
High chance of improving affinity.
Very small chance of harming affinity.
Minus one stress.
It's an in item, okay.
Boxing gloves.
Minus one stress.
Chance of positive or negative affinity.
Blocked by bum leg head.
All right.
I'm just going to take it all.
Should I just take it all?
Whatever.
I'm taking it all.
Why do they have, what's this?
Why do they have notifications?
I'm just going to do auto run.
Nine leagues to in.
This person's driving crazy.
This is worse than I was driving.
Desperate few.
Encounters, treasures, inventory.
Hold on.
This is like a choose your own adventure game now?
All right.
Wait.
Encounters.
We got a lot of reading.
Settle down.
Like this one, heroes will voice opinions on a course of action.
You must choose one of their wishes.
You can hold on a choice to select it.
The results will be previewed at the bottom of the screen.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, boy.
Hold on.
Your stagecoach is limited in how many items it can carry per se.
Okay, I is just the stagecoach inventory.
All right.
Your shared inventory is split between all item types.
Some items stack well, whereas others take an entire slot.
Okay.
Use the inventory tabs to easily see each item type.
Some stagecoach upgrades increase stacking limits.
All right.
That's good to know.
The stagecoach becomes full.
You may wish to discard less important items.
Just click and drag them out of the window.
All right.
Read me a bedtime story.
You're doing the reading joke.
Yeah.
Good night.
Have a good rest.
Hey, don't worry.
I'll wake you up when I scream because one of my party members dies in the first round.
Don't worry.
You'll be up soon.
Have a nice nap.
Items cannot be sold anywhere, so throw away what you don't need.
Discarding items earns a small amount of hope, so you can't sell anything.
If you don't, you just have to throw shit in the trash.
Trinkets, combat items, in-items, and I almost just said Sasquatch will help you on your quest.
Yes.
You'll also find relics and baubles, which can be used to purchase supplies from vendors.
All right.
Trinkets are from the first game.
I remember these.
They can have two.
They offer bonuses.
They can be swapped at any time.
You click and drag.
You equip them.
They're in the trinket menu.
Combat items are equipped into a dedicated skill slot on each hero.
Okay.
That's different.
Click the slot and then double click or drag the combat item.
There's a skill slot.
Okay.
Mastery points.
Mastery points are earned mostly through combat victories.
Imagine going to your teacher in college or something, and they are reading the syllabus
with you, and they sound as confused as I do.
The streamer is supposed to be the confident one.
Like, I'm supposed to be the confident one telling you these things, but I'm just up
at the front of the classroom and I don't even know what's going on.
It's like I'm a math teacher that they moved over to the science department and they said,
good luck.
You start tomorrow.
Mastery points are earned through the combat victories.
Each point will upgrade one hero skill.
We're almost there.
Relics are the main currency of the land.
Used to buy most supplies.
You find relics mostly as spoils of battle.
All right, so relics just like the first game.
Just need to make sure I understand.
Bubbles are used only to purchase trinkets.
Bubbles come in different forms for each region.
Am I going to do the thing?
I have to say, can they tell the story real quickly?
My mother used to read me stories in bed.
All right.
And I could tell when she was getting really tired and she was like falling asleep.
Her eyes were almost closed.
And I would like nudge her arm when she started to fall asleep and she would kick back up again.
She'd be like, bubbles come in different forms for each region.
All bubble types are worth the same, but take a different nudge in your inventory.
Your total bobbers are shown by the triangle like symbol in the inventory.
And they nudge.
I would like keep waking her back up.
That was last week.
I didn't even process this.
Let me start timing people out that say process this in fucking capitals or whatever they're saying.
When you choose a hero's response, any heroes that agree with the acting hero have the affinity increase.
Any heroes that disagree struggling with the acting hero will have...
Oh, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is important.
Nerf this.
Heroes often have vastly different opinions about how given a...
Okay.
Any heroes that agree will have their mutual affinity increased.
A gold glow.
Any heroes that disagree will have their neutral...
Okay.
So people don't agree on things.
All right.
Each region is overwhelmed with local evil, resistance encounters, or battles with these monsters.
Winning resistance encounters is the primary way in which you can gain mastery points.
Earn treasures that will make the heroes more powerful.
It also reduces loathing.
Battling evil is not without risk.
But if you avoid all resistance encounters, you'll find the party ill-prepared to tackle the mountain.
Okay.
Will you even remember all this?
No.
I probably don't.
Honestly, I don't even remember opening the game.
I remember talking about Joe Biden sitting next to me.
And, like, him not pardoning me.
That's all I remember.
But that's not even part of the game.
Right?
Like, that's...
Whatever.
Assistance encounters bring the heroes face to face with the giant Toronto local populace.
These forlorn creatures are in need of help and often have valuable supplies.
Okay.
You just help the locals.
Cultists are evil and you have to attack them.
They emanate from the mountain and the great evil contained therein.
Cultists encounter always tough fight, but the rewards are very valuable.
Stave off the evil.
Reduce your loathing.
Let's go.
All right.
So what's...
Help us.
Let all kind folk unite under the banner of our light.
It's on us to carry the torch and it's a long road.
Hope is contagious once it catches.
The grave robber didn't even want to say anything.
Um, hope is contagious once it catches.
I feel like...
Do they have to...
Do they get in the car?
Let's see what happens.
Nudge.
Let all kind folk unite under the banner of our light.
Everybody say yes.
Yes.
They all like that.
That's 50 flame.
Okay.
Slime mold?
Restores 10% HP minus 10% disease resist.
Okay.
Make...
Might make...
Whatever.
Go.
I do...
I like the art style.
I think it looks, um...
They're kind of like all grown up.
They're all like...
They have like big long arms and stuff.
And the other one over there is kind of torsos.
Um, they were like kind of short and stumpy in the original one.
Right?
10% again.
Let's go.
Heroes.
Hero status.
Critical information.
If I have a question, I'm going to ask you.
Oh.
Oh, this looks good.
This looks really nice.
This looks amazing.
Okay.
So here we go.
Uh, pick to the face.
Uh, throne.
Dagger.
What do they got?
They're...
Is that blight?
I imagine.
I assume it's probably the same from the last one.
Blight.
All right.
We're just going to go...
It's probably just very simple.
Let's just do...
Uh, pick to the face.
Back.
Great pull.
Big crit.
Um, pistol shot's probably better.
Or actually, let me see.
Oh, this is where you dive forward.
Take aim.
This marks people, I think.
Yeah, let's just...
We fight together.
Plague doctor has the grenade.
What's this?
Ounce of prevention.
This is plus 10% resistance and...
Okay, so it's just resistance?
And this is a blight.
Do they have blight?
Yeah, this might not land, but whatever.
Is there something...
Anything different?
There might be something different.
Current base.
Yup.
Current order is based on speed.
Right?
It is.
Fortress actions.
You need to have a lot of...
Yeah.
I know.
I played the first one.
Skills.
Skills can be used for heroes in the correct launch rank.
Yes.
Yup.
I know.
I played the first one.
Effects.
Yup.
Most of these effects are known...
Shown by tokens.
Most over the token.
Okay.
Token view.
This is different.
No, it's not.
Okay.
What's this?
Well, what if that's really important?
I don't know what it is.
Dots.
Okay.
Monster death's door.
When a hero's reduced to zero HP, they're at death's door, right?
Okay.
And if you take damage after that, there's a chance you're gonna die.
It rolls it, right?
Wait, there's death blow resistance.
Was that in the first one?
Some monsters have death blow resistance, just like heroes.
When a monster's on death's door, each further blow has a chance to slay it.
That's new.
Executing the target.
Some trinkets.
Oh, what do we got?
We got Ludwig coming in?
We got Ludwig coming in right now?
What's up?
Tutorial Andy here.
Doing Darkest Dungeon.
Thanks for the raid, dude.
Hope you're doing well.
Good to see you guys all again.
My name is Jerma.
Do the raid song.
We don't do raid songs incoming or outgoing anymore.
If you're doing raid songs still, you're on like season two of like eight seasons.
You can't, you cannot go, you can't come into a stream on season two and start talking
about season two stuff.
We're on season eight, man.
We're talking about the characters and stuff going on in season eight.
All back raid.
No, thanks a lot, dude.
Welcome, guys.
Darkest Dungeon 2.
It'll be a very boring 20 minutes, I think, first, because I just started and love goes
right back to Ludwig.
Season eight's episodes released too slowly.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
Look, it takes whatever.
All right.
I got a token.
Let's just kill this guy.
Season eight is the worst season.
I've already talked about this.
I talked about this already.
We're on season 10 of Jerma 985.
Once you cross seven, eight, nine seasons, that's when people start to go, oh, the show's
not very good.
That good anymore.
I have to be careful.
I'm at that point.
This is money.
They're all relics.
Okay.
All right.
That was good.
End of the season voice.
Season one was the best one.
I don't know.
I feel like seasons two through seven have been really good.
I think seasons eight through 10 have been fantastic as well.
Oh, God.
Where are we?
This is the inn.
Glimmer of Hope in the Quickening Dark.
Heal to 100%.
Should I do that?
Travel log.
Barristan and Audrey became more friendly.
Izmiss and Audrey became friendly.
Barristan and Horacellus became more friendly.
All right.
So they're all like friends.
Inn items.
What is this?
Comcast season was my favorite season.
I mean, that season was pretty good, but I really didn't like how in the middle of every
episode it went to a black screen for four hours.
And then came back.
I didn't like that.
High chance of improving affinity with very small chance of harming affinity.
Comcast.
All right.
So two targets.
These are my currencies.
Relics, mastery, and baubles.
All right.
Do I need to buy anything?
Or should I save my money?
Artboard.
Let me just just get it.
How much does it cost?
Inn item.
Oh, wait.
That's my inventory.
Is that my inventory?
That's what you have.
You potty.
You just call me a potty?
Like a baby potty?
That's a new one.
Okay, so this is what I have.
All items.
Oh, I can use these in the inn.
I can only use them in the inn.
Okay, that makes sense.
I don't think I need to use any of this.
51, 50.
Yeah, I don't need to use any items.
Mastery trainer?
Learn what can be taught, and you may stand at the end.
Upgrades?
How much does it cost to upgrade?
I don't want to click anything.
I'm afraid to click something.
What about?
Oh, it's click and hold.
Okay.
So this is upgrading.
Is it one point per skill upgrade?
It's one per ability.
Okay.
I usually like the plague doctor.
I love the dots.
The grenade dot is like one of my favorite moves.
So if I'm going to do something, I want to do that.
Where is it?
Noxious blast.
There it is.
Wait.
Is that it?
Is that a dot?
Damage two to three.
Target four.
How do I see like the...
It's four per turn, right?
Bounce and prevention is a great upgrade.
It is.
Heal.
Hold on.
Target HP less than 50%.
Heal 20%.
Does that mean if they're under 50%?
Yes.
So if they're over 50%, it doesn't heal.
That's kind of terrifying.
I'm going to go with this.
I'm going to upgrade Noxious Blast.
I love dots.
It's like one of my favorite things.
Like Affliction Warlock was my favorite.
A wild reference.
I'm sorry.
I got electrocuted.
Somebody hit...
You guys hit the button at the same time.
That only activates if fucking 5,000 people hit the button at the same time.
I'm so sorry.
Ow.
Ah.
My like neck hurts.
Okay.
I'm going to do this.
I make wild reference.
Don't press the button again.
I just said the fucking name of the game.
Relax.
Okay.
So now this is...
Did it go through?
Okay.
You need stress relief.
Um, okay.
It's a sex thing?
Okay.
Storage trunk.
Plus four inventory slots.
Ooh.
Okay.
So this is upgrade...
Stagecoach upgrade pets, trophies.
But did that upgrade this?
Six.
Ooh, that's really good.
I love it already.
All right.
Select route.
The faux tour or the tangle.
Rupting or booty.
I feel like I just upgraded the guy.
Uh...
This is bad, right?
Yeah.
100% scout chance for academics cashes.
Oh, plus 250.
The other one I think is gonna get resistance from the plague doctor.
I'm ready to go.
Let's go.
Burning onward.
Yeah.
Use the end items?
I... should I have...
Faux tour.
Whoa.
That's long.
That's...
That's so long.
What?
Oh my god.
That's long.
What do you guys have this thing on your...
Oh, trinket.
Do I have trinket?
Oh.
Okay.
Can I even do...
How do I do that?
Combat skills.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Here we go.
Clear all corpses.
Yeah, sure.
You're in the back.
You take that one.
Um...
Combat items.
I'm gonna give these to people.
Why does this sound like Spider-Man 3 music?
Oh, shit.
Do I have to pick one?
Assistance encounter?
I don't know.
Unknown.
We're going.
Oh, nope.
I can't.
I can't say it.
I was gonna sing it, but...
We just got raided and I have to, like...
I don't want to sound like a fucking weirdo.
I was gonna go...
Into the unknown!
What's that?
Should I touch that?
I don't know what that is.
Are there no torches?
Light.
Bright light.
I don't want to touch the...
Okay.
I need to see what happens.
Nothing.
Oh, shit.
Bandages?
Um...
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Medicinal herbs.
If target is bleed, or if target is blighted, or if target is burned.
This is a cure-all.
This cure is something.
Did I get it?
Moderate heal.
I think I'm gonna buy this.
I might be wasting money, but whatever.
I don't know.
I'm buying...
Guys, when I played Darkest Dungeon, I used to buy, like, 30 food.
And I never had any money.
I just was terrified of runs.
Minus three stress.
I want that one.
Okay.
Ooh, what's this?
That's 25% of resistances.
I don't have enough baubles for this.
All right.
Let's just go.
I got some stuff.
Let's go.
How do I go back?
Okay.
The hoarder.
Now, from here, Hero Shrine.
Continue a hero's story.
Or to unknowns.
Hero Shrine.
Oh, no.
Here comes Herobrine?
What?
Isn't that the Minecraft guy?
It's like a nightmare out there.
Is individual story progression for each character?
Wait.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
I know this is, like, video game Andy, gameplay, tutorial gaming Andy stream, but I need to
know this.
This is the mini-map.
Okay.
Um.
In items.
Let me read this.
Heal, de-stress, or do buffs.
Change the affinity between heroes.
I guess I have to draw.
I get it.
All right.
Target hero.
Okay.
I don't remember even all four heroes at once.
Wainwright is the only place where you can install or remove stagecoach upgrades.
Okay.
Region, choice, matters because you've got affinities, right?
Yeah, I need to know how to play.
Yeah, guys.
You know this double-edged sword here.
Okay.
If I grab, I'm gonna, I have to grab both ends of the sword at the same time and just,
like, bite the sword and use it in my teeth and cut my mouth too.
Like, if I don't do the tutorial, I'm gonna get my ass kicked and you guys are all gonna
make fun of me.
But if I do the tutorial, everybody says this is too slow and then everyone makes fun of
me.
So I have to just bite, I have to bite the sword with my mouth and just go.
Ooh, okay, hold on.
This echoes of the past.
Falls will never again hold me.
My ambition outflanked my fellow officers at Sawyeri's and mock skirmishes.
Tradition drove us into each other's arms, or estates rather.
The jeers, the whispers, they pushed me deep into my studies.
You.
Good student.
Hmm.
Is this, am I in, like, a different game?
A good student.
Is he hearing, like, this story?
Do you think people, like, leaned back and put their head forward really hard and drove
this into people's heads with a weapon?
A headbutt from a plague doctor would be horrible.
Rewards.
Oh my god, yes.
What is this?
Do us for the taking plus one mastery and emboldening vapors.
What does it do?
Target.
Cooldown.
One.
What is it?
How do I look at it?
Just, is it a magic trick?
Do I just throw, like, gas in the air?
What is this?
Is it a party buff?
I want to see, how do I see what it does?
It's an attack buff?
Oh, you're shitting me.
I'm gonna get to the end in this first playthrough.
Sorry, my real voice came through.
Uh, alright.
I'm sure, look, it's like, it's like Dark Souls, right?
You just, you have to just play.
But I want to, how do I look at what it does?
Troll, shift?
I want to know what, is it, is it, does it know just nothing?
Just drink some more water?
Ooh, cash or cultist encounter?
I can't just take the easy road, right?
I kind of have to do one of these.
Hold G.
Oh my, okay.
Wow, that's actually really good.
I'm just going with the money.
If you can make it.
If you can make it?
Tell us another.
How do you get, is there no torches?
Each hero has an affinity value which describes how positive or negative they feel towards one another.
If the affinity bar fails, the two heroes will eventually enter a relationship.
What?
I need to read this.
When the affinity bar between two heroes becomes fully positive or fully negative, this will immediately trigger a new relationship between them.
Relationships dramatically affect hero stats and actions that the hero may perform.
Virtuous relationships make heroes fight and work together better.
Whereas afflicted relationships can cause no end of problems to a party.
Really?
Okay, well.
Wait, hold on.
If the way ahead is scouted, these icons will be revealed, right?
Heroes may voice their own preference for the route shown by corresponding icons above their portrait heads.
Beware, choosing a destination different than what a hero wants will cause them stress.
Oh shit, I'm glad I read that.
Where is the money?
There it is.
The academic's cash.
An impressive haul.
Ooh.
And to good use.
Finish it for me.
Come on, finish it for me.
I want you to finish it for me.
Finish it for me.
There it is.
Thank you.
Nice.
Fuck yeah.
Okay.
Uh, can I take it all?
Relics.
An eiker bomb.
Very large attack blight.
Negative token or if.
I feel like I'm in logic class again.
Negative token or if this.
Then remove all.
This is just logic.
And my brain can't do it.
All right.
Take all.
A lovely little turn.
Logic actually was really fun.
It's kind of complicated as logic got.
It was actually really fun.
Uh, all right.
We have to fight somebody.
Let's go.
We're going this way.
Did you fail it?
No.
What the fuck is this thing?
Oh shit.
Okay.
What do you do?
Seventy five blight resistance.
That's fantastic because I just upgraded her.
It's your defense.
Is there a defense?
What's defense?
All right.
Let's go with.
Should I?
I'm going to mark.
Hey, game.
What?
Whoa.
Wait, what?
Hit.
Dammit.
Should I take aim?
What's this do?
I don't know.
We're just going to.
We're just going to shoot him.
Oh.
Confident searches as the enemy crumbles.
Uh, what about we got?
I got to take this person out.
This person spree's me out.
No blight.
Ooh, that hurts.
Oh my God.
That hurt.
Uh, blinding gas blind.
Should I do it?
Will it work?
Stun.
Added.
I kind of read what these all do.
All right.
Yeah.
Nice.
I get it.
All right.
Should I have a heal?
Ulster.
Remove.
I don't need to do that.
This is a knockback.
Then let's just go.
Let's just try to kill this guy.
These guys aren't doing that much damage.
It's fine.
I need to heal.
Oh, I didn't equip the combat moves.
Oh, fuck.
This is bad.
Uh, wait.
Self.
Self-heal.
What?
What is it?
Minus what?
Wait.
What was that?
Is that not minus less than 50%?
Okay.
That's weird.
All right.
Um, wait.
If my...
I don't...
That's weird.
If you're...
I can't heal you unless you're under 50%.
Am I supposed to...
How do I tell?
Is that...
Are you under 50%?
Okay.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Does that work?
I'm used to just spamming that move on people.
All right.
Let's keep this up.
Let's do pistol shot.
It's long division.
It's not long division.
I just...
Like, I...
And that's how you fucking win games, by the way.
Nobody is under 50%.
I won't let you use it.
Round three of five.
What does that...
What do you mean three rounds remain?
I have a finite amount of time to do this?
Yeah?
What?
What happens if I don't finish it in this round?
There we go.
Death's Door.
Give me a break.
That doesn't kill it.
What?
Oh, God.
After five rounds, the cart drives away.
What?
I should have read the tutorial.
Ow.
I'm grabbing one end.
I'm grabbing the other end.
My hands are covered in blood.
I can't even grab the sword anymore.
I'll get it.
Are you impressed?
Oh, we like each other.
It's a lot of stress.
Shit.
I might not do this.
I can get this one, yeah.
Aye.
This stress is going way too high.
Do they have a de-stress on clear corpses?
All right.
Death blow.
Let's go.
All right.
I'll get it.
I just need to kill this guy.
Aye.
This is it.
Right here.
Last move.
Okay.
Yeah.
I got it.
I'm fine.
Final round.
All right.
We got it.
10% to whatever that is resistance.
Chance to spawn dodge.
I always said doge token.
Chance to spawn one doge token each turn.
I'm just whatever.
Okay.
Memories.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Stress.
All right.
I need to equip combat items.
This is negative.
Okay.
Very large poison attack.
Moderate heal.
Oh, up here.
Let's give you a bandage right now.
I want to give the plague doctor the bomb, right?
Might as well.
And then man-at-arms will take the...
Yeah, that's fine.
All right.
Everyone needs to have something.
Why is the title woo-woo mode?
I don't know.
I got...
I just typed in confidence searches as they get to be crumbles.
And that's what popped in.
I don't know.
I pressed enter.
That's good.
How far up the line am I?
Read your title out loud.
Okay.
What does it say?
It says, remind yourself that overconfidence is a swore and insidious killer.
Plague eaters.
Not every fight is our fight, so we leave.
Dagger sharp.
Is this where I die?
Let's do it.
I don't like that.
They're probably plague resistant, but that's fine.
This is not...
Okay, I've got as much time as I need.
What's this?
Consumable by other plague eaters.
Okay, so they can eat each other?
They have a bunch of blight resistance, but I'm still going to go for it.
Because, I mean, it's 50-50 shot, right?
All right.
We got heal.
Doesn't she have a buff?
Ignores defense.
How much health do you have?
24.
Yeah, let's go for it.
All right.
50-50 chance.
Let's go.
Fuck.
Remove...
I've got to read these.
All icons.
Is this crit?
All right.
Dodge.
Self.
I feel like I'm reading astrological fucking signs.
Like, what is this?
Crit and...
What was it?
Crit and dodge.
Next skill has a 100% chance to crit, and 50% chance for me to dodge my next attack,
but it removes the blind from them.
So, somebody has to be blinded.
Okay.
What is this one?
Counterattacks the next damaging...
Okay.
So, I can go forward.
Let's do this.
So, now I'll counterattack, and then I'm going to move backwards.
Beating to...
Oh, shit.
Regen.
No!
All right.
I've got to use the...
Hold on.
Hold the line.
What the fuck are these symbols?
Shield and...
This is Isaac.
I just hit escape in Isaac, and I'm like, what the fuck items do I even have?
Okay.
Shield and, like, bat thing?
What kind of shield is that?
It's a regular shield.
Take 50% less damage from the next hit.
Press alt, and it's an immobilize.
And that move will be moved.
All right.
I don't think I want to...
I guess I could do that.
Yeah.
So, I move forward, and then I can't be moved.
Okay.
Slippery.
So, I probably should just heal.
Heal 33%.
Yeah, I have to.
Let's use it.
Let's just kill the dogs, right?
That's probably the best thing to do.
Then ignore...
Let's just...
We got to kill these dogs.
They can be eaten for regen, right?
So, I'm going to have to go for it.
50-50 shot.
Yeah.
What?
They're goats or something.
Whatever they are.
Mmm.
He's never even seen a goat before.
This has...
Look at...
What are you talking about?
This is a goat.
Oh, shit.
That was awesome.
All right.
Good.
Now you can't do any of this.
You can't heal.
Oh, that's not good.
Oh, boy.
Don't die.
Does anybody have a heal?
Who has a blight remover?
Isn't that a heal?
I swear to God that's a heal.
I thought it said to heal yourself.
Okay.
I need to...
It wasn't below 33%.
Okay.
Under 25%?
Oh, I am now.
If a skill can heal, it will show.
Okay.
I get it.
I'm not going to use that.
Will this heal?
Alright.
Who should I do this to?
I'm going to do this to you.
Two bottles of absense.
This person is blasted.
Kill.
You can eat the bodies?
Oh, well.
Not anymore.
You should die from next attack.
Remember, make sure you put mastery on ounce of prevention.
That shit will carry you the entire game.
Anybody have a heal?
No.
Really?
Goddamn it.
Alright.
Die.
Yes, door.
S***.
All right, here we go.
Ounce of prevention is stress heal, okay.
Ooh.
Okay, if Target is burned, Cure is burned.
Okay, so Cure is burned, heals 10% HP.
I gotta put these trinkets on.
And this is a trophy, currency?
They have baubles, ooh.
All right, can somebody, do we have any heals
or anything I can use right now?
Conditions, relationships, on that.
I need some, well, you need some stress healing.
Everyone's kinda getting too high.
Is it doing any stress heals?
I don't.
You heal HP as you travel.
That's useful.
I think Grave Robber has a heal for destroying corpses.
Maybe.
This torch is going down.
Am I gonna scream Slime Rancher 2?
Oh, you better believe it.
Trinkets, yep, you're right, forgot to put them on.
All right, 25% light resistance, that's what I want.
And I want you to be the, cause this is the healer.
The healer has to be able to stay alive.
Towering Feast, oh God.
Quick tactical retreat, or retreat is the obvious option.
There's blood to spill.
It's minus 15 torch, it's two to one.
Run away.
Torch equals hope.
I'm running away.
You wanted to run away too, what are you talking about?
What?
We should run away.
Yeah, I agree, we should run away.
All right, let's run away.
Hey, I didn't want to run away.
What?
He wanted to fight.
Oh no, it was the other guy, sorry, my mistake.
I just caused drama for no reason.
He wanted to fight.
All right, yeah, I thought it was the other guy.
I just like caused drama.
Lair, hash or resistance?
I don't think I'm gonna go to the Lair.
In fact, I'm gonna read what Lair is.
Lairs are where the region bosses dwell.
To reach the boss, you must first win your way
through two century battles.
You may retreat from the Lair after each battle,
but the further you delve, the more loot you'll retrieve.
Bosses have rare treasures
that can't be found anywhere else.
Wait, there's a hospital?
Oh shit, okay, that's where you remove quirks.
I'm not doing that.
So we're gonna do either a regular fight
or I'm just gonna go to cash.
Yeah, there's a lot of supplies.
Okay, that's a party wipe if you do that.
I'm not doing it.
Wait, didn't I get a mastery point?
I can't, wait, I have to do that at an inn, right?
Raid wipe, yeah.
The screen that pops up when you open the game,
the game gives you a warning.
This Darkest Dungeon is a game
where it's very hard and impossible.
Your characters are gonna die all the time.
Don't get too attached.
The game is really hard
and you're supposed to die over and over again,
especially considering if you're in the tutorial,
you're probably gonna lose your first and second,
even third round of the tutorial.
Be careful.
In fact, it's a good thing if you die.
Ooh, what's this?
Coach upgrade increases stacking for relics.
That's actually a big deal.
Minus two stress, minus one stress.
So, okay, I'm starting to understand how this is working.
You have all these inn items
and the only way you can really remove stress
is at the inn or with a combat move.
So I have to essentially just spam this on people
when we get to inns.
So that's, I get it, okay.
You're gonna stream Elden Ring?
I don't really play those kinds of games.
All right, left or right?
Left or right?
One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four,
one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four,
one, right.
Must you breathe through your mouth?
We never seem to make any progress.
What, where was it at the end?
Enemy ambush.
Five rounds, all right, what do we got?
These, everyone can be blighted, perfect.
That's good.
These guys are ranged, they're usually awful.
We're gonna try to get, I take out that backer up.
Confidence surges as the enemy mouth breathes.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here, what?
There's throw the grenade.
Oh, it's an ambush, right, right, right, right, right,
right, actually got any crumbles, yeah, exactly, okay.
I have to move.
I don't want you in front, you gotta move back.
What, I have to, oh, shit.
Fuck it, fuck it.
What happened?
What, doesn't it hit everybody?
What did he just do?
He just like sprayed him in the face with like,
what was that?
Wasn't that a bomb?
I thought it was, it's a single target bomb.
Oh, I thought it hit everybody.
Oh, fuck, this is bad.
Okay, I have to move forward.
So let's get this, let's do this.
Please get back in where you're supposed to be.
That was a run ending decision.
I don't think so.
That's not even, whatever, that helps actually.
Now you'll die from this, they'll die from the dots.
I didn't put the healer in front.
The healer, I got ambushed and they surged into us,
which caused us to crumble our perspective on the fight.
Stop saying things that aren't true.
He'll die from the dots.
This first, they're gonna have a heart attack
or whatever happens.
Dot kill, dot kill, just you.
Oh, fuck, that's not a big dot.
All right, do you have anything that moves forward?
I know this character does, but not,
I don't have the move.
All right, you need, it's a heal self.
Throw the dagger, yeah, let's kill you.
Oh, please.
Yeah, that's fine.
Everyone's dead anyways.
I do need, I'm gonna heal though, hopefully.
Oh, I can't.
Yeah, whatever.
All right, we're good.
Invisis, no gains insignificant.
Cool, cool.
Ooh, plus two crit.
I wanna give that to the highway man.
You're gonna move the fucking PD.
Listen to me.
We got ambushed and I got moved around.
Look, I played Dark Stungeon 1.
I know people might come to the stream
to see that the streamer has like the plague doctor
in the front.
She's, I didn't, I didn't put her there.
Press the move button.
I know, but listen, I could, you just relax.
It's gonna be fine.
Okay, you have, there's no burns so far.
Okay, I want that.
Or maybe not.
There is, ooh, no, I want that.
Nobody's bleeding.
Yeah, I want you to have crit.
I want you to have, yeah, you take that heal.
All right, I don't even do the clear corpses thing.
Give me something better.
Okay, my target, negative token or if combo.
Okay, triggers additional skill effects when targeted.
Negative token or if combo removes all negative tokens.
Clear corpses feels so much better in this game.
I don't like the game so far.
I can't, I can't even, I don't think I could tell you that.
I think I have to wait a little while.
It's too early for me to tell you.
And if one of these, all right.
Well, I have, I think I have to fight this.
We must continue.
Fall on them quickly, drive them into confusion.
What is that peace thing down there?
Stealth?
Plus one stealth?
Whatever, if I die, I die.
Who cares, let's go.
Frenzied enemies.
What do you do?
Okay, this is a maid, plague eater.
Five, okay, you're very, very resistant to blight.
Okay, what about, and I don't know what you do,
but we're gonna, you get 22 health.
I'm wondering if this is the same scenario
where I have to kill these guys first.
I wonder, can't give a rating, Andy.
You can't, oh hey, it's Mike Michelson
from Online Entertainment Magazine.
I'm here to review Darkest Dungeon 2.
And let me tell you something, guys.
I have 12 minutes in the game,
and let me tell you, it's a six.
I really don't like what they did with it.
It's a different design, just philosophy and choice.
I actually don't even know what the tokens do.
I didn't even read half the tutorials yet,
but you know, I've got about 14 minutes
in the game so far, so it's a seven, I think.
Wait, I have, you give me,
I have to play for like a few hours, at least.
Burger King made the chicken palm sandwich thing
you were talking about.
What, did they really?
Wait, they made the chicken palm sandwich.
That's insane.
It's the heart.
Vulnerable, okay, remove vulnerable and bolster defense.
I think I'm gonna do it.
I mean, just might as well do it.
I can't just like press swing at guy.
Swing at guy.
No, we gotta use the actual other moves, all right.
I'm also gonna do this.
I don't, it's like Doctor's gonna die.
You leave me in the wind.
You have full health, relax.
Oh, that was cool.
Blinding gas, I think we need to just heal again.
Yeah, oh, drama.
Good, so I'm noticing something.
The stress is only going up by one.
Before, stress could go up by 10.
Five, 20, 15.
Is it just each one of these is one tick?
Is that, I think I'm seeing it.
It's just one out of 10, that's it.
They're just tokens now.
Interesting, interesting, okay.
Damn, that hurt.
Well, you need to go forward.
Ah, you don't have the move.
All right, well, good to you.
That's teamwork, there it is.
Higher stress will make relationships fall apart.
That's not good.
What does this do, three, five, 5% crit?
Yeah, I gotta get back, this line is all messed up.
Well, that was not a good.
Is it riposte, riposte, how do you say it?
Riposte, riposte.
Oh, I can't, I'm in the wrong spot here.
This whole line got screwed up.
You have to roll the R, riposte, something they don't.
Ooh, I got spoons, I got a super spoon.
Plus 20% max HP.
Nice, that's going right on him.
Stimulants?
Add one strength and plus five speed for two rounds, cool.
Nice, take it all.
That's really good for him.
Over encumbered, oh, you must equip, yeah, all right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm about to equip it right now.
Where's the trinkets?
100% max HP, which puts him at 61, that's good.
All right, I'm running out of space.
I gotta start to use this, I almost called it crap,
but it's not.
Okay, I gotta start equipping this shit.
You have to use stuff, you can't just hold onto things.
Even if it's like a bad idea, just use it.
Bandages, no, give you this one, that's a good light heal.
All right, I gotta start using these items.
Equip the combat items, I got them on,
I just have to use them.
What?
26 out of 25, speed bag?
Whatever, I don't even, just throw it away.
New plague doctor skill, I'm begging you, dude.
Can I, I can't, I have to do that at the end, don't I?
I don't think I can put this on.
I think I have to do it at the end.
You can do it now?
Oh, I can?
Oh shit, okay, I get, yeah,
you don't have to be at the end for that.
So this is just an attack buff.
What am I not, I'm gonna get rid of probably this.
That leaves the blinding gas, the heal,
the resistance buff, then whatever this is.
Bro, he's begging you, I just did it.
I was also a little confused
because it was four abilities in the last game, wasn't it?
Am I misremembering that?
Ended by God, what is this?
All right, this is scary.
This thing, we gotta get rid of the dog first.
All right, it's time to strategize.
This thing gets eaten by this plague eater lady.
I can't blight anything here.
We have to kill this first,
because then otherwise she'll heal.
No idea what you do, but we're gonna find out.
So, again, should I just use this on you?
Let's just buff.
You got, what are you doing?
Eating time, yeah, that's fine.
You can heal, I don't care.
Mother's embrace, oh shit, that's not good.
No, stop messing up my line.
Next attack deals plus 50% more damage.
So, can I, okay, so if I do, so much health, 50%.
So if I go slash, four to eight.
Yeah, we need to just, we gotta take this dog out.
Take aim, take aim.
Oh, it's the next attack, not the next move.
So, technically, if I take aim,
I take aim and then I shoot this guy in the head.
This is bad.
Enemies are forced to attack this target.
Oh, I gotta change that.
What are you, you don't have any moves?
Where's the blind?
This is bad.
Kill the dog.
Rip, run, don't say that yet.
It's not over yet, not over yet.
So, you're being taunted,
but you have to go through me first.
You're still under 25%, what?
How is that not 25%?
Not over, no, of course it's not over.
Can't blight.
Even if it doesn't heal, what is it?
It does, yeah, I'm gonna use this.
Because even if it does, what's this thing?
Yeah, I'm gonna use this.
You died to the cart enemy, omega low.
No, took my buff off.
Stop doing the YouTuber voice.
All right, now, plus, if I take this, can I do a move?
This is plus five speed and more attack.
Does it stack?
Holy shit, okay.
Wow, that was 15 damage, that was a lot.
I think I'm gonna be okay.
Who has something bad?
We good?
You're still defended?
Yeah, just kill this.
Ooh, not good, not good.
That's not good.
Oh, he's still under 50%.
Um, whatever, I don't move forward, do I?
No.
Shit.
Uh, uh.
All right, that's good.
Just don't hit anybody in the back row.
Dodge, bad, he's okay.
All right, all right, heal, heal, heal, heal, heal, heal.
Did you even do the tutorial?
I'm gonna scream into the mic, I'm in it now.
I'm in it right now.
All right, we're gonna protect the healer again.
Yeah.
Inhuman, oh, what's that bullshit?
What was that?
Are you kidding me?
That was horse shit.
What?
We just have to burn this thing down.
Or should I deal with it last?
Use poison darts?
His blight resistance is 85%.
That's not gonna happen.
We just kill it.
We have to just work together and kill it.
I don't think I can kill this in the car.
Uh oh, what happens?
Meltdown.
End it now!
What just happened?
Final round.
I can just last, right?
And just leave?
I don't think I'm not strong enough to kill these guys.
They're gonna still not die.
Oh, somebody get heal, please.
Heal.
Meltdown.
Hope has forsaken me.
Oh, they're all having meltdowns, okay.
Oh, I can't heal.
He's dead.
Everyone say goodbye to Cornelius.
I don't even know what this person's name is.
Flying to Gash.
You have anything to do to stay alive?
No, just go for the kill.
I don't care if you die.
You're gonna miss, you're gonna miss, you're gonna miss.
We're good.
I'm not supposed to be able to win that.
You are?
It's not what the intro said.
The intro clearly said,
you're gonna lose your first game at least.
Let's see if it gets to the end.
Ooh, desperate few, okay.
They want relics.
Lose relic loot, but you get mixed loot,
food loot, and flame.
Cough up, we're not in the mood for games.
Let's get loot.
We can trade with the little we have.
Lose relic loot, but gain a bunch of other stuff.
So we're giving up our relics for mixed stuff?
Do I even have enough room for this stuff?
30 flames seems nice.
Yeah, it does.
I'm gonna do it.
Dismiss?
I can't, how do I dismiss?
Oh.
Unexpected find.
All right, cigarettes and all right, so heal.
I can only use this at the inn.
If something then removes that.
Okay, take it.
I don't have enough room for this stuff.
I just took that to throw it away.
I just traded for loot
and I'm gonna just dump it out of the side of the cart
while we drive away.
Stealth remove is trash, just throw that away.
Is it?
Make a little fake fan.
What are some of the things that I don't care about?
They're the corpses.
I don't really use it, but I feel like I'm gonna need to.
What about the extra storage upgrade?
Can I do that?
Damn it.
Can't do it here?
You have so many slime molds.
Yeah, I know, because it's a heal.
Get rid of this one.
Eat the mold?
I can't, I have to eat it at an inn.
I have to eat it at an inn.
That's a very weird sentence.
Eat it at an inn.
Gamer mold, eat it at an inn.
Eat it at an inn, eat it at an inn, eat it at an inn.
I wanna keep the stress stuff
because I feel like it's important.
I'll get rid of this, whatever, moldy fucking screamer slime,
whatever this is.
Hero shrine or supplies?
Can I continue the, okay, I'm gonna continue the,
we're going to do the hero shrine.
I'm gonna do the plague doctor again.
Ooh, that healed.
What?
We have to just, we have to survive, we can't do this.
Thought I was doing the hero shrine.
In the way, this is really bad.
I think this might be the end.
Oh, this is bad.
This is very bad.
This is horrible.
Another meltdown.
We weren't meant to win.
We're a sacrificial meat.
Relationship is tested.
Resentful to Mitchellus.
What does that do?
Meltdowns.
Okay, there's a wait, relationships tab.
To Mitchellus, to Mitchellus, whatever.
I, whatever, I'll figure it out.
It's a random bad effect during combat.
I'll give you a break.
You have to move and you're stunned to shit.
They're dead.
She's dead.
It's over.
Can I last five rounds?
I don't think I can.
Bumbling fool.
Oh, this is not what you intended?
Wait, they're just in an insult line?
You tap you on the shoulder.
Hey, you're a fucking idiot.
Oh, you tap you on the shoulder.
You smell like B.O.
You tap you in the shoulder.
Your breath stinks.
Where's, what is this?
These have to die.
I shouldn't have attacked that first.
Fuck, whatever.
But you need to move.
I have to move.
Is there a forward move?
No, yeah, there is, okay.
Tap, tap.
Worst scream.
And I go, oh, and I go forward.
I just push the person in front of me
into the fucking ocean that's in front of us.
This is over.
Hateful.
Hateful, they all hate each other.
Everyone just hates each other?
So all right, I lose this run.
Congratulations, you got to this point.
Now we keep all of our items
and upgrade the coach and upgrade the characters?
How do I do this?
I think I'd rather have you be alive.
Hey, I could just self-heal.
I mean, this is the tutorial boss.
There's no boss here.
I guess I have to kill this guy.
I have to.
I could defend you, but at this point,
either I lose or I don't.
Not bad, huh?
Oh, they actually like that.
Let's do it again.
Just heal yourself.
Oh no, that's not good.
Don't die.
Don't die from the blight.
You're gonna be fine.
We just have to last another two runs.
This is just edgy me-topia.
That's so stupid.
Like that's not, I don't, whatever.
That's funny what you just said, but it's not.
It's not true.
This came up before me-topia.
Oh no, there you go.
Goodbye.
Take that, you filthy cur.
You happy that this person died?
If I can maybe last, right?
No, Dismas.
Yeah, Dismas is dead.
You can still make it to the shrine.
You're fucked.
We were never meant to survive.
Now what happens if they, can they double hate each other?
The end.
Wait, can I, don't, hold on, where I lose?
I need to read the end.
What does that say?
The end.
The expedition ends when all the heroes die.
Dead heroes remain dead for this entire expedition,
but will be available for use again on your next try.
Wait a minute.
They don't leave and they don't get replaced by somebody.
It's just them again.
Your hero has died,
but you have unlocked additional hero classes
on your profile.
A reinforcement hero will await you at the next inn.
This replacement hero will be randomly chosen
from the classes not selected at the start of the expedition.
When the journey ends, via victory or defeat,
you are awarded hope.
Based upon how well you did,
hope is used to increase your profile level.
Even when an expedition is surely lost,
it's often worth pressing on to get more hope.
Hopium.
A zero hope run.
As you accrue hope and increase your profile level,
new heroes, items, and quirks become unlocked.
These unlocks make future expeditions easier
and also give you more opportunities
to develop personal strategies for conquering the mountain.
Yes, I'm just supposed to lose.
Interesting. Okay.
So should I just try to,
you just have to go as far as you possibly can.
You and your roguelikes, you knew this, didn't you?
Not really.
Trying to stay alive right now.
Okay.
I can't even heal.
Great.
I mean, these, they all have light resistance.
I'm just gonna have to do this.
Whatever, just try to stay alive.
If you survive this fight, discard your entire inventory.
Why would I do that?
For hope? What?
You do it for hope?
How is that hope?
Hey guys, the expedition's not going well.
Throw all of our supplies out the window.
What?
I'm gonna make it.
At least one more.
Fake confidence.
Oh shit, he retaliated and almost killed him.
All right, we're done.
Round five of five, that's it.
Watching you disgust me.
Okay.
He's gonna, all right, we made it.
Slippery.
Okay.
So you tell me to throw all my items in the trash.
Just discard everything?
Where are we on the map?
22 leagues to the inn.
What can I discard?
Yes, discard items, discard all.
But I get more points by throwing out all your items.
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
Heroes, shrine, and then unknown.
This is a huge joke.
Yeah, I'm not, I don't, I'm not gonna do that.
You liars.
Throw your entire inventory away?
Get out of here.
That's unbelievable that you would even suggest that.
Read the tutorial.
No.
Map, scouting, inventory.
Full inventory.
Items cannot be sold.
So throw away what you don't need.
Discarding items into, oh shit.
Not another ambush, right?
Come on.
What the fuck is this bullshit?
This is two, what?
How do I run?
This is like a brand new enemy type
with like super powerful moves.
What am I supposed to do?
Your torch is at zero.
Oh, well shit, how do I, we run?
I guess stay alive.
Not over.
I mean, it probably is over.
I think it's over.
No, there's no round one out of five.
You have to kill them.
It's over, we're dead.
There's also no round timer.
Oh shit, it's over.
Gonna break.
I think I still have a lot of health too, don't I?
28, damn it.
It's never over, Hopium.
That's right.
That's right, Weasley.
It's not over.
It's never over.
Yeah.
That's my favorite part about Harry Potter.
My absolute favorite part of Harry Potter
was Voldemort's strange sounds he would make.
He never yelled.
It was like.
I don't remember that noise.
But watch the entire series again.
You'll hear it like 15 times.
I loved it.
I loved that noise.
Like at one point I had that noise as a ringtone.
I'm sorry.
There's no sounds like that in the entire Harry Potter script.
I am not gonna get gas from Saw again.
I'm sorry.
That happens a shitload of times.
Voldemort makes that exact noise
at least three times over the course of the series.
This is not gonna be the same scenario.
Trust me.
Just, you'll see.
Yeah, and now why is weird Voldemort sound
gonna be in the Harry Potter script?
He just downplayed 15 to three.
This is a negotiation, okay?
Oh, okay.
Why did somebody make a compilation?
Somebody made a compilation of all the awkward grunts
and yells from Voldemort.
This is a sick ringtone.
That's not the one.
I gotta find the one I'm thinking of.
There it is.
They're like.
That's not even half the video.
You made this video for this joke.
I did not.
This is like 400,000 views.
If I made this video like a day ago,
in no way it wouldn't have gotten that many.
You go play the sounds that I just made.
The ones I just made.
Play them.
I wanna hear it.
Clip it, I wanna hear it.
I wanna hear them back to back.
I win.
I win this argument.
That's my favorite part about Harry Potter.
My absolute favorite part of Harry Potter
was Voldemort's strange sounds he would make.
Like what?
He never yelled.
He was like.
What's my favorite part about Harry Potter?
I win.
It's not as close.
Yes it is.
That's what I did.
And I didn't even play the rest of the video.
There's more.
It's not.
It's Homer Simpson.
It's not Homer Simpson.
Oh.
Hold on.
That's so stupid.
Voldemort was such a crazy character.
It was a great villain.
Like it was very well acted.
It was like, it was great.
But, I mean.
I'm never gonna be able to think of anything else.
I will never be able to think of anything else ever again.
Besides Homer Simpson.
Ralph Fiennes is such an amazing actor.
Like unbelievable fucking actor.
Unbelievable.
Like, un-fucking-believable.
But just ruined everything.
Just ruined everything for me.
I can't.
Okay, let's just lose already.
You said Ralph?
I've.
Wait, what did I say?
Did I call him Ralph?
It's.
Whatever.
You know what I'm talking about.
Jesus.
The actor is, yeah.
Okay, turn this volume back up
before I fucking puke.
Aye, aye, aye.
Okay.
Can I, I'm not gonna be able to last this at all.
I just didn't lose.
If she does this, that's unbelievable.
I don't ever.
I know.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
You get it now.
Finally.
It's so much better than a regular scream.
It's, I love it.
I wouldn't be talking about it
if it wasn't my favorite thing.
It's a spell.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I just leveled up.
Okay, so they already died.
I got to level two.
Minus 50% healing received from skills round start.
Rewards.
Got trinkets.
And I got some, reduces flapjacks.
Everybody likes flapjacks.
Rare.
Okay.
So now what?
We just go again.
Do I have the same party?
Wait, do I have the same team?
Rare, rare, rare, rare.
Oh.
We just, this game is just a road trip
with a bunch of arguing kids.
So what does a pancake upgrade just peels?
I need, okay, I need profile level three.
I need to unlock the hellion.
Where's my, where's the abomination?
That's my favorite.
Just making sure I understand here.
Where's the abomination?
All right, the leper's here.
Leper is second favorite.
I actually probably would say leper's probably
my favorite character to play with.
Abomination's my favorite, like, lore-wise character.
I loved the abomination.
Needing to decide when you were gonna turn
and everybody kind of freaks out
but you know you're really powerful.
I love that.
Okay, so it's just the same team.
Are these the same people?
Hold on.
Did they hate each other still?
Did they come back to life?
Or are these different people?
Master of the sprawl's advantages, sprawl.
Knowledge supreme over all, okay.
They don't die, it just loops.
No relationships reset.
Your skill unlock progression stays, okay.
Know you're thinking about the Voldemort scream.
I'm gonna be thinking about it for a month, every day.
Okay, this is the team we're gonna use
so I gotta go to the inn now, right?
And equip the stuff.
Upgrade ounce of prevention this time.
Harry Potter public domain night.
Well, if I said a Harry Potter public domain movie night,
that is just a lie in the title.
And then I would get a cease and desist sent to my.
What do you want me to do?
I would get cease and desisted.
Okay, so we're taking all this shit.
Okay, we're going to the inn.
Let's equip some shit.
Just counter-assue them.
Okay, yeah, sure.
Yup, let me get this straight.
You want me to counter-assue Warner Brothers if I do that?
Or what, what, like damages?
Guys, my lawyer that would go to the proceedings
wouldn't even have a tie on.
I would get screwed.
What are you talking about?
You'd be over.
Okay, so all these are the same.
These are all the same thing.
Food reward, they're just food and flame.
I guess we're going to do this to whoever.
It doesn't matter, yeah.
That would be good content.
I mean, it would be the talk of the internet, I think,
for a little while.
And not in the way that I think everybody thinks.
It wouldn't be funny.
It'd be like this streamer is a fucking idiot
and it's going to lose everything.
I guess maybe there'd be enough like Reddit comments
for people to laugh about like how stupid
that was for me to do.
Like I streamed the Harry Potter series
and counter-assued them when they like said,
don't do that, that's illegal.
And I would be like, no, it's not.
That'd be funny for a week until everyone
forgot that I did that and nobody cared anymore.
Yeah, like that would be,
everyone would talk about that for like a week
and then I would go to jail and everyone would just move on.
Pardon, get a pardon.
It doesn't work like that.
A week is a long time.
Let's do this.
Actually, no.
You guys have blight resistance?
You do, let's just play.
You're gonna miss.
What?
Would you recommend this game?
I don't know, I don't know.
I still don't know.
Do the character stories.
I did the plague, plague doctor.
How much damage is this doing, two?
All right, we'll throw, just throw a knife.
We'll duck and bleed, okay, that's fine.
And you're gonna shoot and hurt this guy in the head.
Go for it, come on.
Nice.
You've streamed for two hours and you don't even know?
Well, I mean, two hours in a game
that you could probably sit here and spend a hundred
is like 2% of the game time you'll have here.
Would you be willing to listen to somebody
that has like 1% game time?
I don't know about that.
Would you trust me?
I mean, it's very simple for me to say
it's too different, I don't like it, right?
But that's not necessarily the case.
I'm starting to understand what they're doing with this one.
I'm starting to understand the practice here.
But no abomination, no buy.
I already bought it, but you know what I mean?
Okay, so everyone's friendly.
This is where I have to do stuff, right?
So this is improving affinity.
So I should just use these.
Is there any downside to using these
for all of these?
I just, why would I?
Let's use it on Audrey.
I won't cheat this time.
What just happened?
Did it work?
Lightship is tested.
Ooh, inseparable.
What did that do?
They're inseparable.
What does that mean?
I don't get to keep those inventory upgrades.
They're friends now, okay.
How long have I been streaming for?
Have I really been streaming for two hours?
Holy shit.
I've been streaming for two hours.
Wow, okay.
I'll take a few break, yeah.
I'll pee.
I'll be right back.
See you in like two minutes.
I got lost.
Eight minute piss, da-goom.
Had to go through his maze.
Okay, let's go.
Let's do it.
So I've got, how many points do I have?
One point?
I feel like I don't want to just upgrade one person though.
What does this do?
Ounce of prevention, target.
Is that minus one what?
Is that minus one, what icon is that?
It's minus one stress?
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
I feel like that's almost required.
That's kind of required.
Remember, what is your blood type?
It's for a school project.
I don't even know.
Every time I've ever had my blood tested,
I've always in the back of my mind said,
I want to ask them.
I keep forgetting to ask them, but I never ask them.
It's something that I'm always curious about,
but I just don't, I don't know.
And every time I go to the doctor
and it's like time for some blood work,
remember to ask about, hey, what's my blood type?
I don't do it.
All right, so now this is a stress hill.
That's good.
So, okay.
It's like a route.
What about, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Anything else I can do?
You get to keep your trinkets too, don't you?
I'm gonna put these on.
Where's provisioner?
I feel like I probably need some of these.
I mean, these are just very obviously.
Aren't those, this is just like kind of food, right?
I mean, I'm just gonna, I want a shitload of them.
Should I not have done that?
I always overbuy everything in these games.
Could you tuck me into bed?
Yeah, sure.
Just hold on.
One, two.
Well, you hit the ground.
But I was aiming for the bed.
Sorry.
I think this is fine.
Bat country or erupting?
Bat country.
Isn't one of my characters good at this?
All right, minus three stress.
I should probably give this to somebody, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna give this to you.
And somebody has to put this shit on.
20% blight resistance and bleed resist.
Who do I wanna make sure has that?
Who should have that?
Probably the plague doctor?
The healer has to have the most resistance, right?
I think that's very important.
Speaking of heals, I want people that don't have a heal
to be able to use heals.
Fine.
And you can take the, you know, I'll give it to you.
I think I'm ready to go.
Plague doctor already has high plague resistance.
Yeah, oh yeah, we wanna make sure it's impossible.
What's my favorite soup?
Broccoli, cheddar, made of basil.
French onion.
Yeah, that's probably it.
Pick a noodle.
Missed her own.
All right, let's just go.
Kind of stressed, but whatever.
I have the stress heal now.
Anything else I need to do?
I'm just trying to get the hang of this.
What is this?
Is this some kind of, was this some kind of thing or what?
Is this some kind of thing or what?
I don't understand.
Oops, wrong button.
Is this some kind of thing or what?
Is this some kind of thing?
I don't know.
All right, I'm sorry about that.
I don't know why I just did that, but whatever.
Embark.
I don't know why I just did that, I'm sorry.
I can't be trusted with a microphone.
I'm the fucking guy that if you hand a microphone to me,
I'm just gonna put it up to my mouth and be like,
la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
And like production is gonna be like,
cut that person's mic, that person's fucking,
what are they doing?
I'm sorry.
You put a camera on me and I'll give me a mic.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna do, I'm just gonna start talking.
If you really want to keep me occupied,
just have a microphone in a corner.
It doesn't even need to be plugged into anything.
And just sort of allow me,
plug me in into a corner and just sort of,
just sort of allow me to get on the microphone here
and just start going.
Yeah, give me a microphone and I'll do anything.
Hey, how you doing, everybody?
How are you?
Good to see you again.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh yeah, we got somebody in the crowd over here.
Looks like they are, hey, you two together?
You sure are, you sure are.
Hey, when was the last time you guys went to Target?
Just give me a microphone.
All you have to do is give me a mic and I'll just do this.
Just sit me in the corner.
Just give me a microphone that I can talk into.
I'll be there for four hours.
I will be, I'm the easiest child to take care of.
Cut his mic, cut his mic, cut his mic,
cut his mic, cut his mic.
What, you didn't think that I had on hand a microphone
that I could just talk into and say hello to you?
Oh no, we're currently, I'm currently in the stratosphere.
You give me a microphone that has like funny sounds on it
and that's all I have to do is just talk into it
and say how you doing, ladies and gentlemen, how are you?
What, the face cam on?
Oh shit, I have to, just everybody stay there, don't move.
I was gonna turn the face cam on,
but I don't have any clothes on.
Wait, okay, I'm back.
All you gotta do, I'm serious.
All you gotta do is give me access to a microphone.
Hey, who do we got back there in the chat room?
Hey, okay, okay.
I don't know why I have it.
Nice sweater, nice sweater, nerd.
Hey, hi, all students, welcome.
No, what are you talking about?
All students, welcome to the assembly.
We just wanna make sure everyone's aware
that the school lunches are gonna be changed this week.
We're gonna be having a meat pie instead of a sandwich day.
I know that's a disappointment to everybody,
but just wanna make sure that everybody's aware.
And is there a reason why all mics sound like this
when you're at school?
Is there a reason why all mics are at school?
I don't get it.
It's like $15.
It's like probably 50 bucks total to get a microphone
that doesn't sound like this.
It's the speakers.
Maybe it has to be.
I look deranged today.
Why do I look so deranged today?
Chief, what are we guys gonna do?
All right, this is what we're gonna do.
Fuck yeah, you ready?
I want everyone's gonna be, this is gonna, hold on.
This is, this is, this is, this is,
I don't know if that's supported.
Okay, I'm gonna pretend that my mic broke.
And I'm using a different mic.
Everybody be in on this shit.
This is the last thing that I typed in.
Ow, that hurt.
You know, how many times have I done the like
write on text a description thing?
And I'm gonna be unintelligible.
And I want people to be fucking furious.
Remember, this is just for like the 10 people
that show up in like five minutes for nobody else.
Okay, I want a different color though.
I want this, I don't want the, oh, there we go.
You ready?
Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna take my shirt off real quick, hold on.
Okay, this is just, there we go.
Okay.
Okay, so.
Okay, okay.
So I'm going to, I'm gonna go for it.
I'm gonna try to get out of here.
This is fucking stupid and I fucking hate this.
Move it over right here, bro.
I haven't cleaned this.
Yeah, but I have to make do, guys.
You can't just.
Okay, all right.
So I'm going, I'm gonna start going.
I'm gonna start moving forward here.
So let's go.
I can't fix the mic, the mic is fucked up.
I can't do it.
The mic, my mic is screwed up.
I have to use this one.
Should I go left, right or straight?
Where should I go?
Fix it, fix it, fix it.
There's nothing to fix, I can't.
I can't, don't you get it?
I can't.
The mic that I was using just broke
and it doesn't work anymore.
I have to get a new one eventually,
but you have to deal with this for now.
Sorry, what the fuck?
Sometimes, you guys don't understand
the fucking technical problems, seriously.
Some of you guys just need to shut the fuck up.
It's fucking annoying.
I'm not gonna turn the stream off.
I'm gonna just continue to do what I use.
Stop being so fucking irritating.
Okay.
So if I go this, I'm gonna go straight
just to get the chest.
You stand, if I don't put it close to my face,
you're not gonna be right next to my mouth.
I can't take it away from my mouth.
If I take it away, fucking idiot.
You are a fucking idiot if you think that I could do that.
Just let me enjoy the game
while we deal with the technical issues.
Stop streaming, stop streaming, okay.
No.
What is, I don't know, I just pressed a button.
I just did something, whatever.
Okay, let's go this way for a fight.
I think there's a fight this way
if I go straight down.
My wealth of position.
Even worse, your mic actually sounds better.
Fix the echo.
Some of you guys are seriously not listening to me.
And I have the nerve to put it on.
I could have a cash, this is pretty good.
We should be able to avoid this anyway.
I'm recording this is not really necessarily,
but I'm really trying to look forward to it.
Although some of this is quintessentially
the play doctor, I think so.
Fucking annoying.
This is the most annoying thing is this is like
a $7,000 mic and for some reason I can't find it.
Piss me off.
I need a pop filter.
Just wait, hold on.
I need to play the video game.
Everybody stop talking.
Okay, I have to put the controller down
so I can play the game.
What's the problem, what's going on?
Erin.
That's a good, you're right.
Erin, Erin, Erin, Erin.
No, run away.
Erin, Erin.
Erin.
I almost just shit my pants when I did that.
I actually almost just shit my pants for real.
I'm not kidding, that was actually almost,
I almost shit my pants right now.
On, thank God it wasn't on camera.
I need to go wash my mouth, I'll be back.
Like, I don't know, I've never washed this before.
I have just put this all over my mouth.
I'll be right back, I have to wash my mouth.
Do you guys have any idea how many times
I've brought that mic to a party
and turned the echo on and farted into it?
To be like the funny guy at the party?
Are you serious?
What else would I use that for?
Oh my God, that's incredibly funny.
What the fuck, what?
You don't know what I'm talking about?
Whatever.
Oh, this would be a great time to do...
If I didn't have a running...
If I didn't have a...
All right, I'm gonna play the game now.
We relax.
All right, this does four.
What do you love when you see perfect shit like that?
This is gonna die from the fucking blight.
Done, you're gonna move.
Hey, you gotta get out of there, okay.
Finishing blow, what the hell?
I mean, they got like five turns each,
what's going on here?
You gotta take the person out in the back.
Really?
Oh shit, the text on the screen.
How is this a different mic?
Is this cure, bleed, or...
No, flame.
You threw the run when you missed the hit.
I don't think that's accurate.
Is this defense for everybody?
I think this is...
Yeah, is this for everybody?
I think it is, right?
Is it not?
It's for me.
Is this guy talking?
Yeah, I've been talking.
Whoa.
Oh, that's their perk.
They're inseparable, right, okay.
Cool.
Yeah, defense.
All right, is it defense or defense?
How much defense do you have?
Which one do you think?
What do you guys think?
Defense?
I think it depends.
If defense is the only word,
or one of two words or three words, it's defense.
If defense is in the middle of a sentence, it's defense.
You didn't have enough...
My defense was too low.
I say defense, yeah, it's defense.
All right, let's do the stress heal on you.
Wait, it's on everybody.
Holy shit, that is a must have.
I thought it was just one person.
That should be the first thing you buy ever in the game.
There's no reason to ever buy another move first.
That's mandatory, yeah, it has to be.
Did I actually not kill him?
Cultist encounter.
All right, we're gonna do the cultist encounter.
How's everybody doing?
You good?
Everybody all right?
Inseparable.
Cool.
Combat skills.
You still have that.
Target stress or stress less than 0% cures...
Okay, you know, I really kind of feel like
they don't need this first line of text.
That first line of text is almost confusing for some reason.
If target stress or stress greater than 0%,
why isn't it just cures one stress?
It's two separate things, but it's not though.
It's horror, not stress.
So if target's horror, so if their horror is above 0%,
or their stress is above 0%,
then it cures horror and one stress.
This feels really weirdly worded.
Like cures horror and minus one stress.
Oh, whatever.
Garlic brain.
It's not garlic brain.
It's like showing your work.
Well, I don't think you need to show your work.
What's that?
What is this?
Oblivion's ingress.
Oh Lord, what does this mean?
We advance relentless, they'll perish.
Strength and or escape.
Let's go.
Relationship is tested, you don't like each other anymore?
Ooh, respectful.
Okay, so they all actually like each other.
Okay, so spawn encounters.
What are the inseparable?
Take my hand.
Okay, so 28.
These guys probably need to go first
because they probably do something weird.
All their blight resistance is pretty low.
Let's get that started.
Good.
Are you eating baby back ribs on today's stream?
I'm not eating baby back ribs ever.
Tracking shot.
Requires that the target has,
the dodge increase ignores the dodge
and removes the dodge.
Is that good?
Guess, maybe it's a debuff, I guess.
I don't know.
Nice.
I'm just gonna keep using this over and over again.
Tomorrow's stream is the public domain movie night.
I'm not doing like eat ribs on stream.
This horror, have that thing, I didn't even equip it.
What does horror really do?
Because it's probably different in this game
than the last game, right?
Where is it?
They're not on here?
It's the same stress each time.
Okay, it's the same.
All right, good to know.
Let's stack the dot because that will,
oh, fuck you.
Don't die.
I have a heal.
Heal.
Use the salve.
I need to give that to somebody.
Probably you.
I, what?
Let it remove, let it remove blind?
Am I crazy?
It's only on self.
Yeah, but didn't he, I can still on him.
Public domain ribs night.
This is gonna do two damage, so let's just kill this.
Okay, well at least I'll die.
Oh, another good relationship.
Hopeful.
There's a group that's gonna make it.
It's this one.
This is to make sure they don't die.
Okay, this person's gotta go.
All ribs are public domain.
Ooh, nice.
Okay, so I think I'm just gonna swing
because that's gonna, I'm gonna do more damage, right?
So it ignores this.
Good.
I'm gonna heal or throw their grenade.
No.
Ah.
And you pretend to be a fat bastard singing
I want my baby back ribs.
From Austin Powers?
I should probably take that off.
Too far away for this, so I'm just gonna heal.
Or stress reduce.
The bad guys aren't even a problem.
These guys are the big problem.
They do so much damage.
These guys gotta go.
Come on.
Well, I gotta heal.
You do a Shrek impression.
I feel like if I do a Shrek impression,
you're just gonna mistake it
for a Gordon Ramsay impression.
No, stop it.
No, what are you doing to my Wellington?
Stop.
No, what, come on.
Come on.
What are you doing?
No, what are you doing to my Wellington?
That's like, if you go to his like TikTok,
he just like watches people make food
and just goes, oh, stop it.
Stop it.
No, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you doing to my Wellington?
They're like cameos.
Kill this.
No.
You never watch Shrek?
Who has not watched?
These people are gonna die
because I can't hit anything.
This person has so many buffs.
You just said this was the run?
Very well could be.
Death's Door.
Now, what are you doing?
It's usually somebody making like a Skittles,
ham, turkey and chocolate Wellington.
And he's just like, oh, what are you doing?
Stop it.
There's no time limit.
Just as long as I can heal the stress, it's fine.
It doesn't matter how long the fight goes.
God, what the fuck?
I don't think I've hit a melee attack in like five turns.
Come on.
50% of 50% is 50%.
It's a coin flip.
I haven't gotten one heads.
We're just going for a fucking headshot here.
I probably should have taken off the debuff
or the buff, whatever.
You're gonna dodge this, aren't you?
75% chance to dodge, fuck.
All right, I gotta remember this.
These guys just dodge each other
and he has to take it off.
I'm gonna, I'm just gonna try to hit you with this.
See if it hits.
Okay, you can hit, but this is, you can't.
All right, I can't throw the grenade over here.
Just do this.
I need to remove this.
Like seriously, how long does it remove?
God, give me a break.
Removes, okay.
You don't have it, but I have to shoot the guy in the back.
Finally, thank God.
Wait, what?
Well, you put a dot on that.
That's cool.
I can kill you, please.
All right, now take this shit off.
You wanna play chess?
I can't do chess, I'm sorry.
Who has the remove dodge?
Somebody does.
God damn it.
Yeah, heal your tank.
Remove, I don't have it.
I guess I'm just gonna defend
or I'm just gonna try to,
I'm just gonna miss, what, 70%, 50%?
50% dodge seems like,
that seems insanely high.
Okay, ignores that, but he doesn't even have it anymore.
Heal him, I got a salve, I'm good.
I had like two or three other people, what are you talking about?
I know, I got a salve.
I knew he had a salve.
Slash him.
Die from the poison.
The death door on enemy's thing.
I can't say I like it.
What the fuck?
Yes, die.
Oh shit.
If dark impulse is equipped, you get plus 40% HP.
Unlocks the potential of cultist trinkets?
What is that?
Oh shit, all right.
That's good.
Damn, all right.
Okay, okay, hold on.
Should I put that on him then?
Is this a negative though?
69 HP.
Okay, that seems like a really good item.
I really don't wanna mess this up.
Healing salve's good.
Need something new.
Yeah, put the horror on you.
And then clear corpses on you.
That's the second best cultist trinket, really?
Holy shit, all right, let's go.
This is a cultist encounter.
All right, I have to be careful.
I really wanna try to do well here.
Is there anything else I can do for now?
No, I gotta be careful.
Heal?
I think they automatically heal, right?
No?
Heal, heal, heal.
You can't heal on the road.
Shit, okay, another one of these.
Oh, now that I know what these guys do,
it's all about dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge.
No, I got a fight coming up right here.
I feel like that's not a good idea.
Academic study or watchtower.
Academic study.
The academic study is a foray into the abandoned towers
of these cosmic obsessed learners.
The word items you'll find within can yield great rewards,
but not without commensurate dangers.
And then a watchtower.
Watchtower scouts every future location in this region
is usually well worth the detour,
especially early in a region.
Think I wanna do that one.
They all wanna do the watchtower, so that's where we're going.
Okay, here we go.
New enemies that I need to learn about.
Five rounds who are the pit fighter.
They look like they're on fire.
Person in the back is very fast.
I think they have to die first.
They have really low blight resistance.
So we're gonna go ahead and do that.
Come on.
And the middle.
Just trying to get this guy down if we can.
What the fair?
Huh?
They have 20 resistance, like 20%.
What the fuck?
Okay.
Well, they're not gonna make it.
What?
You don't know that.
I need to think that, let's take that off.
You're a police designated corner of the screen
for bird watching videos.
That was actually really funny.
Okay.
Poison.
Thank you.
Bird watching videos.
No.
Did I heal or should I just take?
I feel like I don't have very opportunities
to do anything.
I guess I'm gonna try to kill the person in the back.
What is this?
Next turn will be delayed to the end of the round.
25% fire resistance.
I wish I could make a team.
Okay.
I guess I'm gonna have to just put defense on.
Yeah, I think I'm just gonna put defense on.
I think it's a 50% chance to miss that guy.
Or just make it five rounds.
At least confirm or deny that you use TikTok
in some capacity.
I don't use TikTok.
I've seen TikTok videos.
Six.
Is that enough?
Fuck.
I thought it was gonna be enough.
50% doesn't go away till you hit him.
We want birds.
I can't just play bird videos.
I guess I'm gonna just take a swing.
You'll die from the poisons.
Just in the corner.
Is there like just a bird watching video
you guys want me to put on?
Die from the poison.
You have that on.
I need to just like queue up like an anti-defense or something.
Let's go for this.
Use advance?
Oh, yeah.
Slow suffering begins.
Jesus.
I feel like I just wandered into an area
that's way higher than I'm supposed to be.
Cracking shot.
What is that thing?
Oh, it's the repulsive guy.
We'll do it on you.
This is gonna do more damage.
Heal her?
Yeah, I knew I was gonna have another shot.
I don't want to use the salve unless I need to.
I only have like two or three more.
Is this person gonna die from a turn already?
God, I'm gonna have to use it now.
Thank you.
Should I even use the?
I don't think, I only have one more round to go.
Should I even use the salve?
I'm in trouble here.
I don't die.
All right, hold on.
You want birds on screen?
Ultimate bird video for cats to watch.
Just in case your cat is watching.
Okay.
Why can't I not move?
Are you happy?
Just to survive.
Put your face next to the bird
and act like you're going to eat it.
No.
I don't, I just have to survive, I guess.
We're just done after this if somebody, if you stay alive.
Well, this is it.
The fucking bird video is distracting me.
I keep looking at it.
I keep looking over here at these birds.
Pretend like you're eating the seeds with the birds.
This feels like I have so much.
Okay, let me ask a question.
Be honest.
I feel like I have so much further to go.
I'm just not gonna be able to get there.
Are you like supposed to not be able to do this
for like the first like five to 10 runs?
I feel like you're probably not, right?
That's the whole point of the game is to not, yeah.
Because in the first one, it was like broken up
into different sections that were short dungeons.
So this is like the whole thing.
And you're realistically only supposed to get like here
or like here and maybe you get like really lucky
and go all the way.
Hero shrine or insistence encounter?
Hero shrine.
Wait, where are the birds?
There they are.
Okay, this is only two guys.
This should be easy.
All right, let's, you already have a plus attack.
So I might as well just use it.
And this is, let's just break the hell out of this guy.
Humbo.
Let's try to kill him.
Hey, get out of there, that's not yours.
That's not for you.
Stop eating the bird's bird seed.
I'm more interested.
Wait, I'm, he's like, hey, get out of here.
This is our bird seed.
Have some, thank you.
I'd have some more, please.
What are these, seeds?
Yes, I love seeds.
Mm, delicious.
Let him have some.
How much can they eat?
Where does it all go?
And what, the birds are so weird, man.
Birds are in times 10 speed.
Look at that, the beak moving up and down.
I feel like this video is moving three or four times speed.
That like, crunch.
The fact that they've ripped their bodies around,
slow it down.
You're proving that people think that the birds
are more interesting than this game.
That's not true.
He's getting closer.
He's gonna get close.
Oh, look at this.
Look at how close the one in the middle is getting
to the camera.
Birds are government drones, though.
And why did they make them shit?
Think about that.
It's a, that's data dump.
Because it's funny.
Okay, I'm moving this.
This is, what a great video.
All right, what was it?
Okay, I gotta kill these people.
Six damage, I'm gonna just load up on,
I gotta do this, stress heal.
Good luck.
Hey, just get rid of you.
Make the game small instead of the birds.
No, no.
You're gonna determine your primate brain
is just barking at the sight of birds.
What are you talking about?
You're causing from Boston.
45 leagues to the end.
What's going on?
People talking?
I thought they were talking in the carriage.
I was like, they have voice acting here?
Squirrel's back.
Hey, get out of there.
No, I like these seats.
You're not supposed to be over there.
I know, I'm having so much fun.
You're not supposed to be having fun over there.
Get out of there.
This one's a good, this one.
That one is scrumptious, that one's juicy.
Mm, what's over here?
That's a leaf.
What's this one?
Mm, that one tastes like tomato.
This one tastes like dirt.
Mm, that's what it kind of smells.
I don't know where it comes from.
It's more than, look at how cute his face is.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
All right, I gotta do the funny thing
from Otto's Big Adventure.
Yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Okay, you're distracting me, stop it.
This is much better, I'm sorry.
No, stop saying that or I'll never stream ever again.
I'll quit tomorrow.
Let's go here.
You enjoy the birds?
I do, birds are so fun.
They're just so cool.
All right, echoes of the past.
I was the smartest, but wisdom was not on the syllabus.
Yeah, I want plague doctor.
We have to turn this off for a minute.
Look, the plague bearer has a bird beak.
What is this?
Disprove the professor, are we doing Ace Attorney?
Review notes, hated rebuttal.
Sit down, disprove the professor.
This is a mobile game ad.
What the fuck?
Try minus three, sit down.
Students, what the fuck?
Review notes, I think I lost.
How many times do I need to review the notes
before I can rebuttal?
I don't understand, I don't get what's going on.
Rebuttal after the conclusion.
Okay, so conclusion, conclusion.
Your digestive system needs to be looked at.
Okay, rebuttal, did that work?
Symptoms of terminal illness.
What the fuck, did I hard lock myself out of winning?
All right, here we go.
Anxiety forms insidious spheres.
Then this should kill him, pop him to death.
You poisoned him with your knowledge.
That's the move I've been waiting for
since I started the video game.
That's the one I wanted the whole time.
Death by fact and logic.
You're almost out of the tutorial,
I'm out of the tutorial.
The whole game is the whole tutorial, what do you mean?
I wanna activate that, cause that's the move I like.
Cause that's the one that throws the grenade
into the back row.
What have I not used that I don't really care about?
Probably this, like who cares about that?
This is for the front row.
This is to blind people in the back and this is to, yeah.
I like that, that's good, that's good.
Hoarder or academic study.
What is academic study?
Where is it?
Did I go by it?
Oh, okay, the foray into the abandoned towers.
I think I wanna do the hoarder.
Yeah, okay shit, I don't know what these guys do.
All right, I got my grenade.
These guys have bad blight resistance.
This is how I turn it around.
And you dodged it.
Okay, watch restoration videos next.
You guys really want, I mean, honestly,
we'll see how, a public domain movie night,
people are looking forward to.
Who's, what?
I was like, who, what happened?
I'm just like, who is,
I keep thinking that's somebody in the game.
Okay, let's get back to reality here
and I'm gonna double up poison on you.
Go, bird video.
Okay, so you've got five poison.
This will kill you eventually.
I don't care about you anymore.
Now we gotta worry about this bastard
and I'm sorry I'm using that language.
Hey, I think I wanna use,
no, let's just queue it up.
When are you gonna do a bird watching stream?
I really wanted to just do a turn it on,
just be out in the wilderness somewhere
with binoculars.
The problem is, how do you see that?
I would need to have a huge telephoto lens
connected to like an IRL backpack.
Okay, what does that do?
I'm gonna go right here.
But then I think about, I mean, I, cameras,
I would probably need to hire somebody
that was really know how to use a telephoto lens.
An actual like animal photographer.
And I would just walk around and just make comments.
Just eat like sandwiches.
Just eat like bologna and cheese sandwiches
while they zoomed in on birds.
You'll die from the poison.
It's time for you.
You have that.
I don't like that at all.
But you have that bullshit.
But that's what a BBC Earth documentary is.
But it eats a sandwich
while the other people zoom in on birds.
Okay.
Nine.
The fire, what?
The fire rises.
Oh yes.
And that man there, you are in the dark.
But I've been in the darkness longer than you have.
Today, we have a thousand people here.
And we will crush it.
Today.
I'm gonna try to get minus two
for like five straight minutes.
Oh, you think darkness is all I like.
But I lived in the darkness.
I grew up in the darkness.
And you are blind.
And that's when Batman does a little bit of industry.
Sell it.
Sell everything.
Check this out.
Boom.
Do the whole playing sequence.
So it's a put on subtitles
and just sit there and word for word
say exactly at the exact same time
every word that Bane says.
I can't play like a movie on stream.
You don't understand like it's.
My God.
I'm turning the bird video off.
I'm turning off the.
Put it 50% opacity over the birds.
That was a great video.
All right.
You're dead from the poison.
I need to, what the fuck am I gonna even do here?
Or just swing at the guy.
There's defenses.
50, 50 chance.
I haven't gotten it once.
This is, I can't even hit.
This person's not gonna get hurt.
Please.
Kind of like how Twitch couldn't play a Pokemon movie
during the Pokemon marathon.
Really?
Yes, Dore.
Get out of here.
Come on.
Are you serious?
And there's nothing even on him anymore.
Oh, that sucks.
That sucks.
I have to.
Come on.
Just fucking die already.
Put on monkey videos.
I don't, where am I even gonna find that?
I don't like this like 50, 100% dodge shit.
I don't like it.
Where are the monkeys?
All right.
Let me see if I can find one.
What would I even like monkey?
Like, what would I even, how do you title?
Oh, what about I title this?
Because if I type in monkey video,
I get like funny monkey videos.
Like what?
Like a zoo?
I don't know.
No, I'm, we're done.
I'm not doing this shit right now.
I'm not doing this.
I'm not doing this right now.
I need to, I can't hit anybody.
I'm gonna defend.
I get, I'm just gonna bolster my defenses.
I'm going to, I'm going to bolster my defenses.
I'll repress it.
Ah!
Fuck!
Ow!
What about electrical shock?
My toenails hurt now.
Why am I, my toenails are sore from that.
No, oh, the distraction didn't work.
When he said no amount of funny voices in quotes,
it's gonna make us forget about
you didn't put a monkey video on.
And you put it in quotes too.
Birds are better, I'm leaving.
Run baby sensory videos.
I can't, stop.
You know, everybody, okay.
I have a better idea.
Let me do you one up.
How about an entire stream
where we watch baby sensory content
and see how it affects me.
See what it does to me.
I feel like that would be a fun,
like you laugh, you lose challenge
with baby sensory videos.
We'd have to do like a bunch of different categories, right?
Okay, there it is.
Yeah, haha, and it would be funny
if you wore a diaper, haha.
Okay, I need more.
Can I do the upgrade of the coach wagon thing?
I need just heels.
Are there any heels?
Okay, so I got a question.
This is if the target is burning,
it cures the burn and heals 10% HP.
But if the target's not burning,
does it heal 10% HP?
They have to be burning for the second thing to happen.
Has to be, right?
Okay, cool.
These are all in items, combat items.
I want one of these.
This was really useful last time.
Necessary acquisition.
In item, wait, hold on.
I don't have any baubles.
I thought you kept the baubles between runs, no?
I feel like these people were burning.
They were people that were burning.
All right, that's enough.
That's enough.
You had a pacifier too.
All right, you need to time people up
that are doing that.
Immediately.
All right, so people wanna go to the academic study.
This is the lair.
So this is the lair.
There's no way I'm gonna go this far.
High risk, high reward, mysterious.
We'll check it out.
We'll go this way.
Yeah, I need to de-stress anyways.
You joined my Minecraft world.
I tested everything,
but I'm not sure if I port forwarded right.
Can you just join real quick?
No, I don't know what the fuck you're doing.
I don't know what you're doing.
It's a cannon.
I mean, you may as well have just said,
hey, can I have your IP?
Like, you might as well just said the same thing, right?
I mean, the answer is no for both of those things.
Well, I can't.
This takes 75% less damage,
but you bleed and stuff goes through that.
A blight goes through it, right?
Nope, nothing does.
You kind of just have to die.
Kill this guy.
You have a VPN though.
All right, just forget it.
Someone try to kill this guy as soon as possible.
Is anyone controlling this unit?
Loading the shot.
Okay, so when he dies, maybe this thing can't be used.
Not bad, all right.
Um, debuff?
Oh, um, I can't hurt this guy.
Can I?
One?
Oh, it was just for that one hit.
Okay.
Oh shit, this is not good.
Type in monkey compilation.
No, I'm not doing a monkey compilation.
Missed fire.
Ooh, that's good.
Everyone's happy about that.
Kill it quick.
Ill.
Gonna load the cannon
and I'm gonna have another opportunity here.
Nice.
I'm not doing a monkey compilation.
Why is the audio so weird?
Why is he throwing poison grenades at an inanimate object?
I, I'm not gonna do the thing that everybody wants me to do.
And if you want to know what that thing is, it's the chat.
I'm not gonna do the, I'm not gonna do the monkey video.
Chat, I am not gonna open up a monkey video.
And then I open up a monkey video in like 10 minutes.
I can't give you the satisfaction of like the joke
that is my mannerisms and how I act.
I'm not going to do it.
I am not gonna, I am not gonna,
I'm not, it's not gonna happen.
I'm not going to play a monkey video.
And this time for real, actually for real this time.
No, he's becoming self-aware.
Yeah, cause I see that copy pasta everywhere.
And then I think about it, I go,
fuck, I actually do that, don't I?
No, I don't.
Okay, this is the unknown.
This is beyond me, let us continue.
Mixed quirk, combat stress damage flame.
I don't think I should do this.
I don't think so.
Nope, goodbye.
Hospital, here, hospital.
Wait, everyone's fine.
Part three of plague doctor.
What about a sensory monkey video?
What, a sensory baby monkey video?
Yeah, I'm gonna watch baby sensory videos.
I'm going to have a notepad.
I'm gonna write down like my exact feelings
at the moment that I feel them.
I will have a notepad on stream.
And I'm gonna just type like exactly how I feel.
All right, we're gonna do another,
I feel like we're doing this story.
Extra credit.
This video made me feel very goo goo gaga.
The research was at a critical point
and regular supply raids of the university laboratories
have become necessary.
During one such expedition,
she stumbled upon her professor,
awkwardly slumped over his podium,
a bloody kerchief on the floor.
Isn't that me?
Here then was her ideal cadaver,
a long awaited opportunity.
And she would not waste it.
Somebody, no, this is not John Goodman.
It's not John Goodman.
Somebody asked if it was John Goodman.
Hey party boy, thanks for the 20 subs.
Requires target less than 50% HP.
10% healed per positive token.
Heal 10% remove all positive tokens.
So for every buff that the person has,
you take them all away, but you heal 10% per thing
and you get a mastery, okay.
I didn't have to do anything.
Sorry, I called you a goblin earlier, my bad.
It's all right, all right.
Hold on, this is new stuff.
Everybody have a combat item?
We do.
I'm almost at the end.
Let me just get to that.
I've been once in this whole stream.
It's been four hours.
Hate monkeys and it would be so sad
if they were shown on stream.
My day would be ruined.
Field hospital, how's this work?
Field hospital is the only place
where you may cure diseases, remove negative quirks
or reinforce positive quirks.
What the, why can I not say that?
Positive quirks, that was weird.
Anybody have anything?
Wellness, pharmacy, okay, wellness.
Horn rotator cuff, I'm gonna get rid of that.
Minus 5% max HP.
Knowledge supreme overall, I don't know what that means.
Not motivated to do all that much.
Probably this one.
Let's see, do you have heels?
Don't have just regular heels, oh well.
What are you doing with this blue dot thing?
How do you peel a banana?
You take the long kind of stick stem part,
turn upside down, pinch the bottom
so the two edges of the bottom go and split
and then you pull it out that way.
Hey, thank you Groob in Sky.
Thanks for the 15 community subs, Groob in Ski.
15 subs, thank you.
I don't think I wanna buy anything.
I'm gonna get rid of this.
Which way is upside down on a banana?
I don't know if there is,
is there an upside down or right side up?
I'm getting close, Livian's Rampart.
This is new, what is this guy?
Block two hits, takes 75, okay.
Ignores defense, what do you have for resistance?
Boom, thank you.
Flame spreads, they're getting,
I think they're moving closer and closer every turn.
That person has to die now.
Good, that's gonna be five.
Yeah, you'll die before you get there, good.
Let's go ahead and do, go right in the middle here.
He moves forward, I might just kill him.
Let's see, how many skeletons could you kill
before they got, I thought it said guts,
it said something else.
I thought you said until they get to your guts
and I was like, okay, well, I'll answer that
but you said a different word
and I'm not gonna respond.
This is five, three turns, one, two.
Yeah, let's just stack it.
Seven, yeah, this person will be dead.
I have to keep moving forward, I don't care.
Stack it on this guy too, resist, damn it.
Ignite, oh shit, that's not good.
Seven, two turns, three.
How many skeletons still are they able to up?
How many skeletons would take before they,
how many skeletons could I fight and win?
I'll answer that question
because they're asking all kinds of fucking weird shit.
Listen, I would be able to take,
I would say, does the skeleton have a weapon,
if it's like the character from Killer Instinct,
that character's trained.
It was just a skeleton walking towards me,
like lumbering towards me.
I would just have a baseball bat
and I would just break all their bones,
I would just swing and smash their bones in half.
Probably quite a few, at least five,
I think I'd be able to take.
Full bat swing on a skeleton,
it's just gonna have a forearm, bone.
It would break in half, there'd be nothing to stop it.
You wanna talk about weapons?
I would go blunt weapon versus sharp weapon
any day of the week.
A sharp weapon doesn't work on stuff
that's not like flesh and blood, you know?
Blunt will work on everything.
I would have like one of those battle hammers.
It works on everything.
You're dead in one turn anyways,
so let's go ahead and stack the poison on you.
Really?
Does silver do extra damage to skeletons?
I don't think so, that's a werewolf.
Blunt will work on anything.
If you're getting surrounded by skeletons
and you have a sword, you can't cut a skeleton's bone.
I mean, you'll be able to hit it
and it'll be like ding!
But if it was a big heavy blunt battle hammer,
it would just shatter the bones.
You're using RPG logic.
Well, if you wanna use real logic,
the spear is probably the best weapon ever invented.
It has range, it has sharpness, it has maneuverability.
The spear is probably the best weapon across all of history.
I don't understand what I would personally like to use.
Get rid of this stupid thing.
This is three and three.
You'll dodge that, so fuck that.
What'd you do?
What about the gun?
The gun was our way of cheating, you understand?
We just invented cheats in battles.
Oh fuck, I should've, I'm an idiot.
Spear, oh wait, hold on, this is a good relationship.
Amorous, 50-50, whatever.
What about the bow and arrow?
Yeah, but the bow and arrow was,
okay, so you have to put the bow,
well, they had to load muskets too.
But no, but I think bow and arrow is harder to use
than a gun, because those old blunderbusses
just shot in fucking random direction in front of you.
It was just a big like, pshh!
Jeremy, you can't deny the bow.
What does this looted proceed to the next battle?
Ardian, next rewards, what's this, advance?
Oh, this is the tower thingy, right.
The bow is the precursor to the gun.
Yeah, but the bow is harder to use than a gun.
All right, what do you got?
I have to poison you.
Crossbow was the first sign of cheating, yeah.
That's true, that's true.
Crossbow was the first sign.
I need to load, let's go like this.
How did you resist that?
And those old muskets and those old blunderbusses,
I would be so afraid to use them.
I would feel like I would shoot that thing
and it would explode in my face and just kill me.
Ah, this is, I gotta be careful here.
This is not looking good.
Need to do the stress heal.
Why are you mad about that?
Yeah, keep moving forward, that's fine.
All right, I need to, you need to die.
Or team spirit's going bad.
Yeah, it is.
What about the poison blow dart?
Imagine the lung power that it took to,
yeah, that is not cheating.
Shooting a blow dart, like a quarter of a mile,
and hitting somebody in the neck?
Yeah, that's probably one of the hardest things
in the world to ever do.
Oh shit, I'm an idiot.
They weren't shooting for the neck.
Yeah, but in everything, in every piece of media,
when a blow gun is used, it's always like,
yip, and it's like, and the person's neck.
And they're like, ah, and then they drop to the ground.
Everything Jerma learned about blow guns
comes from Ace Ventura.
Okay, well, I have to be very honest with you guys,
because I hope I can be.
That's my only reference.
Another one does not exist for me.
All right, let's poison, sure, you.
Now we can go.
Oh, you had, I keep not, I need to pay more attention
what's under their cards.
You'll die.
I'm retreating after this.
Where's the burn heal?
Somebody does, not you.
What about opinion on throwing a shoot?
I don't, unless anything can be used as a weapon
if you throw it hard enough.
I already, what about throwing a monkey YouTube video?
What about choking someone to death with your VR cables?
What scenario?
Oh shit, an intruder's in the house.
Oh my God, I gotta find a weapon.
Let me unbox my VR headset, get the long cables out
and use that to strangle the guy.
What?
You're just running, dragging the headset,
just bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum onto the ground?
No, I'm picking up my PlayStation
and I'm gonna smash the person's head.
Easiest weapon, easiest weapon.
If somebody's just like boom in your house, I'm ready.
Just run up to your TV, fucking grab the PS4
and smash them into the head with it.
You understand how dense and heavy a PlayStation is?
These things are fucking like, they're like nine to 10,
they're like eight pounds.
What if it's just your mom coming in?
Whatever.
Mom comes in with like a couple bags of groceries
and just sprinting out with a PS4.
You would know, but you would know it was your mom
when she walked in with the groceries.
That doesn't make any sense.
This person's still alive.
Ah, this is about to be bad, I had to do that.
Just die.
What if she's wearing her Halloween costume
from her work party?
This is not gonna happen.
Ooh, another positive.
What if she dressed as a monkey video?
Yeah, that's true.
Oh my God, just kill this guy.
Why you...
Who has the...
Death's door, death's door, death's door.
Oh, we're on death's door.
Oh no, we're on death's door now.
Fucking God, just kill this thing, kill.
It's taking forever, kill it.
Thank you, I am...
That was pretty cool.
In crisis, no gain is insignificant.
All right, get me to the inn.
I'm pretty much there.
I made it to the first end of the game.
It took me five hours.
Nice job.
A new trinket.
What does it show me here?
Oh, relationships, I see.
I wanna kill that.
That is really, really bad.
I need to start using that a lot.
Yeah, I never clear the corpses.
Why haven't I put it on?
You get that one.
I'd rather have, yeah, that's fine.
All right, let's go.
Do the grave robber story?
I did it, I actually made it here.
That's very surprising.
I'm surprised that I got all the way here.
Sprawl is hard.
Cool.
Gain to cork.
Everybody's pretty much friendly.
What is this?
Loathing howls.
25% flame drain.
Maybe battle advantage.
I'm getting all this bullshit.
Okay.
So, minus one, two targets minus one stress.
High chance of improving affinity.
All right, so we need to put that on you.
Like two recipients, okay, you two.
You're nice.
Minus three stress, we're gonna use it on you.
You idiot, I clicked and held it.
Oh my God.
I like clicked, I didn't, I was trying to,
I wanted to put it on her.
Plus bleed resistance next in.
Probably you.
Minus 10% disease resist.
I like that.
I'm going for it, fuck it.
Fuck it.
Be going with full heals.
All right, let me do the stage coach.
Each improvement.
Grease is stacking for relics, that's good.
Reduces flat jacks, which I'm not sure what that does.
Got three points.
Here's the question.
Whoa, what is that?
Oh, I want the dot.
Play grenade, I want it.
I'm upgrading this.
And I'm doing it again.
I can't.
Shield guy needs an upgrade.
Bolster target.
This is removes stress.
Bolsters a stress heal.
Okay, yeah, that's a good idea.
Um, do more heals.
I feel like I need to upgrade the heal.
That's probably really important.
What is this?
Mr. Green has a message for you.
Hold on, there's a message from Mr. Green.
Let me see what it is.
Okay, what is it?
Why is this so small?
Response required.
Good evening, Mr. Albertson.
Sponsored by Greg Greens.
It's come to our attention
that you have yet to make a debt payment
since May 8th, 2021.
This letter serves to notify you
that continued non-payment will have consequences.
You have one hour to make a deal with Chat
to remove a portion of your debt balance.
Failure to comply with these terms of results
and repossession of all Funko Pop vinyl figures
in your possession.
Chat writes a ban from all Greens affiliated gambling
companies, as well as a lawsuit from Warner Brothers
for copyright infringement.
We hope you make the correct decision.
Sincerely, Greg Greens.
Okay.
Appreciate the letter.
Can I play a monkey video?
No, I said I wasn't gonna do that.
Not a monkey video.
I'm not playing that.
Something else.
I'm not playing a monkey video.
Nothing else.
You want me to fulfill the meme destiny
is what you want me to do.
How much would you take off?
Just make your own monkey video?
A hundred million?
Come on.
Okay.
I picked a random one.
We're gonna, we're only gonna watch a little bit.
I promise.
Baby back rib stream?
Brush your teeth if you don't wanna go to fucking jail.
Okay.
A hundred million off the debt.
How much off the debt?
500 million?
250 million.
This monkey's smoking a cigarette.
What?
I don't wanna watch this one.
I don't wanna watch that one.
I, what the fuck?
That was, what do you mean no deal?
Hold on.
I'm buying a different one.
Do monkey reacting to magic strings?
This is stupid.
Why?
Okay.
Monkeys reacting to magic tricks.
I feel like I've seen,
hasn't everybody seen this video like 10 times?
Get the fuck out of here.
What the fuck?
Stop.
I don't wanna keep clicking.
I put on ad block.
I don't know.
I don't, I had ad block, I think,
but I don't have it anymore.
Let's see what this funny monkey does.
He's built into the video.
What?
He just ate it.
What did he just eat?
I swear to God, if a monkey starts smoking in this video,
I'm just running away.
There better be no smoking monkeys.
All right, that just,
I'm not even a monkey and that just freaks me out.
I'm shocked by that.
And I'm not even the chimpanzee.
That's pumped in fake audio, by the way.
That's a fake audio.
Why would they need to?
I've, everyone's seen that one.
He's like, no way.
He's scratching his butt.
He's like, I don't even care.
Go west, do it.
He's ignoring you.
Okay, do it.
He's a paid actor.
He's done with the monkeys?
That looked fun to do.
Wait, what?
What happened?
That's not a magic trick.
That's just like, you just fucking with the monkey.
Where is this?
Is this music coming from me?
I don't know where this music is coming from.
Do I have another video open?
I thought that was a big pipe in his hand.
I was like, not another smoking monkey.
Thought that was a big Gandalf pipe.
That's not, that's a kitten.
This is not monkey's reactive magic.
What is this?
This cat's looking at toys.
I think they, did you run out of monkey magic clips?
And you just be like, you know what?
I got a few of these.
What do you mean the deal is off?
That's not fair.
Why are the cats, the cats are getting mad at each other
because the, what the fuck?
What's going on?
Why are dental companies lobbying
to make this toothbrush illegal in the US?
Toothbrush illegal?
The US Army just sold the device
to give Americans the dental care they deserve.
What is this?
And he destroyed the $300 billion
dental monopoly in the process
with a device that can deep clean your teeth
in just 10 seconds.
What's happening?
Stop autoplaying.
Illegal toothbrush.
Okay.
I did what I needed to do.
I did it.
There you go.
It's been done.
Let me, I need to pay back.
Okay, I have another skill point to put somewhere.
I don't know where to put it though.
What do you think?
What is this stream today?
Yes, it's been all over the place, hasn't it?
Yeah, I don't know.
But tomorrow's is going to be way weirder.
Because again, to remind you,
tomorrow is public domain movie night.
We're just going to watch a bunch of public domain movies.
Horror themed, obviously for Halloween.
Should be very interesting.
I think I want to do the heel.
Or is that, doesn't seem like very much.
Heal 25% to 20 for a point.
That feels like not very much.
Can anybody else have a heel?
Maybe I should upgrade this.
He feels, he feels kind of lackluster.
I will go and just poison, poison, poison, poison, poison.
Poison, poison, poison, poison, poison, poison.
That's four, right?
Yeah.
All right, route.
This is tangle minus 20% resistance to that.
Well, I just, I don't want to do that one.
What time is, oh yeah, this is important.
So the stream tomorrow is not going to be at two.
I want to do it at night.
I want it to be in the evening into the nighttime
because we're watching scary movies.
So we're going to start tomorrow around 5 p.m. Pacific.
So 8 p.m. Eastern is when we're starting.
It's going to be a scary night.
He hates EU.
It's my, it's the Halloween special.
I'm not going to stream at like one o'clock
in the afternoon on the Halloween special.
No, I wanted to do it at night.
I want it to be scary.
I can't help that you're plus like 12 hours ahead of me.
Your Halloween will already be over.
You already got to do it.
No, it'll be Halloween day at that point.
Yeah, wait, it'll be Halloween day at that point.
I'm zones aren't real.
If you cared, you'd wait 12 hours.
I live in West coast United States,
which is the furthest away from Europe
in America you could possibly be.
That's when I stream.
I'm very sorry.
But I wanted to be in the evening
because I wanted the sun to be down
and the lights to be off
and I want to be fucking terrified.
All right, is it time to go?
I've created everybody, right?
Did this.
Oh, do I have enough to buy anything?
Don't.
West coast Nevada is landlocked.
Yeah, but it's on Pacific time.
Use your in items.
Didn't I use them already?
Yeah, I used them.
All right.
How about minus one stress?
Yeah, we'll do that.
What do I get to the?
Stop his leagues away.
Plan accordingly.
Okay, you need, it's you.
Minus one stress, minus one stress.
Locked?
Locked.
What?
Why?
Okay, well, that's annoying.
I'm ready.
Journey onward.
I think I'm gonna get to the boss.
Are you gonna do a face cam tomorrow?
Maybe for hearts.
Wait, wait, wait, what's going on?
Wait, what's happening?
It's a new, it's a new thing.
Oh, I completed it.
No, I just didn't do the boss.
Oh shit, all right, we'll see how far we can get.
An elementary problem.
Is it not?
Hero Shrine, all right, they all wanna go to Hero Shrine.
Except for you, but whatever.
I might be able to complete the plague doctor's story.
I should do somebody else to get into the move.
Face the half-remembered horrors of death.
Okay, so who should do it then?
Highwayman?
Do Highwayman.
I want more damage.
I feel like I can't kill anything.
Chapter one, freedom.
Can't ignore fart allegations, apologize now.
People fart all the time, man.
What do you wanna say?
People fart all the time or they hold it in all day
and then they have a stomach ache
and they fart like 12 times in their bathroom
when they get home.
Don't do that.
Like, you know what I'm saying?
Everyone does it.
Relax.
Defeat the guards to escape.
Lunging cuff?
I guess I'm gonna, he's gonna punch him.
Executed with impunity.
Round two, ready to sound the alarm.
I gotta get rid of that.
I got a huge dodge chance.
Big, big, big.
Fart on stream and you dead as a race.
How about I fart into the microphone with the echo?
Just put it under there.
That's cleared.
The dead is now clear.
That's clear.
Let me sit.
No?
With a question mark.
Shit.
Get, get, get.
Don't do it.
What's that mean?
Anxiety formants in city spheres.
Can I throw, I have to go back.
Can I go back?
I see.
Push me back.
That's actually not good at all.
I need to kill these guys now.
How do I go?
I have to walk backwards I think.
Not yet.
In a minute I will.
God, I can just move back.
You're right.
I got too cocky and I didn't move.
Whoops.
It's okay.
No, no, no, what I did, ah.
I'm fine.
Crit.
Crit him.
How much health does he have?
Four.
He's dead.
Yeah.
Point blank shot between front and back.
We'll have.
At least it should be.
Additions.
Oh yeah, this is bad.
Let me put that on.
Because now the new strategy with this guy is
you lunge forward and then point blank shot.
We need to move, can I make,
I want to move with party members around.
Take aim.
No, move forward, take aim, point blank.
What should I get rid of with this?
Because these are all useful.
Okay.
Go.
If you hope to heal, you have chosen wisely.
Let's try that tactic.
This is a stress heal, right?
Or is it 50, 50 shot for a stress heal?
Let's try this thing that I want to do.
Boom.
Take aim.
Get somebody in the head.
That chat.
Your chat is going crazy.
Hey, relax, relax, what are you doing?
It's all right.
Out of here.
No.
This game is balls.
Sorry, bud.
I'm getting to the point where I have an assessment
of the video game.
Can I make an assessment of the video game, please?
I killed that motherfucker.
Condition blocked.
That's weird.
He'll die from that.
And then we just have to realize
that there's only one skeleton left.
That was pretty clean.
Didn't even get to use point blank, whatever.
Twice.
Executed.
Let's play it off stream to give a genuine, real judgment.
We fucked it up.
Field hospital.
Handcakes?
Oh, you just make them.
Interesting, okay.
Somebody has a really bad illness.
And stress damage.
Oh, it's the blind one.
Where is it?
I don't think I can afford these anyways, no.
Only eat the flapjacks at the...
Who said gym?
What happened to the blind thing?
Did it get taken over by something else?
I don't think I need to do anything.
Maybe I'll...
It's a disease, not a quirk.
Oh.
Right.
Okay.
Let's go.
Can't afford to remove the disease now, I couldn't.
What does it want me to do here?
Can I get a new trinket?
Why do they have, I don't know.
The loathing house.
Every time I kind of progress a little more,
I get another one of these.
It seems like a negative.
Oh, is this the end?
No.
Comfort in company.
Here we go.
In stronger enemies, are you blight resistant?
Kind of.
Eh, go for it.
Roll the dice.
50, 50.
Eh.
Yeah, you're gonna die.
Hopeful.
Fine.
Yes.
The animations are cool.
I think it's, yeah.
The one thing, okay.
You ready for this assessment, Andy?
Okay, here comes assessment Andy.
This is, I think everybody thought Darkest Dungeon 2
was gonna be Darkest Dungeon 1, but with more stuff.
And this is a very, very completely different video game.
This system here is kind of the same,
but it's a lot, it's a lot different.
So, instead of them doing that same formula
from the first game and making it bigger,
they made essentially a whole new,
this reminds me of like Slay the Spire.
I feel like this game, okay, so what,
this stuff here, like block,
50% less damage from next hit.
Evade.
Crit.
These, it's kind of, almost like these are cards,
like this is a card game.
I feel like I'm playing Slay the Spire.
It's literally the same system.
But it's not though.
It's Slay the Spire with a dungeon,
Darkest Dungeon coat of paint.
Especially considering that you don't make a party.
You just kind of start with a party
and you have to go as far as you can
and then do the whole thing all over again.
It removed the whole, like it's a very different game.
This system is intact,
but it lives in a different kind of universe.
You do make a party.
Well, I mean, you make the party,
but you don't really, okay, correct me if I'm wrong.
You could have like two plague doctors in the last one
because you just had a shitload of people
would show up at the Hamlet.
Do you get to have just one of each particular character?
Can you have like two plague doctors
or two highwaymen or whatever?
Can you still do that?
Or is it just one?
It's one of each.
Yeah, it feels, I don't know.
I still, I'm still working on how I feel about it.
I do personally miss.
You'd go to the cart and be like, who's here today?
I'm like, oh shit, okay,
I can run these guys through the level one dungeon.
I'll make a party of like fucking two plague doctors
and like two abominations, fuck it, let's go.
This feels more like a, you start like this
and this is the way you're going to start.
And like, good luck, the run might be like two hours.
It feels, it feels.
And you know, maybe they, okay.
So Darkest Dungeon is amazing.
All right, let's break this down.
Darkest Dungeon is awesome.
It's really, really, really good.
You have to consider maybe that the dev was,
devs are probably saying to themselves,
everybody fucking loves Darkest Dungeon 1.
It's a complete, amazing experience.
If they did Darkest Dungeon 1 again
with better art style and the same exact systems,
maybe it's possible that they don't live up to that game
and it's just kind of like a bad version of the first one.
Right, like maybe they get to that point where they're like,
fuck, are we just going to make another Darkest Dungeon
and but what if it's not as good as the first one?
So, all right, let's try something different
and see what happens.
Let's try something new,
not just kind of make a potential,
even if they made a better version,
so we still have that one.
I can see where people are sort of confused
that like, why do we have a gigantic like 40 thing
like lay the spire tree?
I want to make my five,
I want to make my four highwayman team.
Like a lot of, I think, choices, at least in party
and kind of where you decide you want to go
are chosen for you.
Yeah.
I mean, Dark and Darkest Dungeon one got a bunch of stuff,
a bunch of contents.
Like one was unintentionally that difficult,
but it was meant to be hard.
Two is intentionally radically hard.
Well, we talked about it earlier.
I feel like it's,
if you're going to have a game that you do a one run
and then start the whole thing over again,
it kind of has to have some aspects of like,
you can't really do it on your first try, right?
Otherwise you would just beat the whole thing
in your first go.
So you hate it.
Here's the thing.
I imagine that once you play through this game,
like 10 to 20 times,
you do like 20 runs,
maybe the game is kind of opened enough
where a lot of these complaints might not exist anymore.
Because right now we're all taking this,
I got Darkest Dungeon two, here we go.
Oh man, I'm going to have like fucking 15 people.
They're going to all be doing different things.
Some of them are like in the asylum.
Some of them are getting their disease treated.
I got these guys.
It's like, well, here's your party.
Now play the game for four hours in one run.
I think we need to see the rest of it, right?
Because this just came out in early access.
I wonder what else they're going to do
to maybe alleviate some of the concerns people have.
You're the only one who thought that.
It's only chapter one.
But yeah, that's what I'm saying.
I'm just trying to give benefit to the doubt
of why maybe some people are saying
that they don't like it.
It feels like we need the rest of the story,
the rest of the kind of world to be built.
Because I get what they're doing.
I get where they're going.
They want that like one run sort of like Slay the Spire,
like Isaac, where you start, you go,
and you just, can I fucking get to the end?
Rather than, I have like four or five different groups
that are doing these small like 10 to 15 minute dungeons.
I don't know, it's like a one and done let's go.
How far can you get?
Have you ever played Slay the Spire?
No.
I downloaded it on my Switch and I played it for 15 minutes.
But listen to me talk to you.
Like I have someone with experience
and I'm someone to listen to.
Like you should be listening to me.
I'm talking really in a way
that you should be paying attention to every word that I say.
I don't have any money so I can't do anything.
But it's different enough, but still kind of similar.
I'm very hopeful that over the next whatever year or so,
however long it takes me to finish this,
or maybe even more than that,
that a lot of these systems and a lot of these areas
and a lot of the characters get added and fleshed out.
And I have pretty decent hopes.
I think it's gonna be all right.
Chunky Vlogna, thank you for the 20 community subs Chunky.
You doing well?
Make a funny noise, please.
All right, you're stealth, I can't hurt you.
All right, poison.
All right, the one real complaint
that I really truly have about this game
is I kind of missed from the first game
being like confident in my ability to complete dungeons.
Because you, like if you just went to a level one dungeon
to like kind of grind for some stuff,
you were like confident
that you were just gonna be able to clear that
and get like money and relics and stuff, right?
This is one of those like you've got to play, play, play,
play to make your characters better.
You can't really do it in one go, you really can't.
I much prefer the ability to kind of at my own pace,
decide how difficult I want to make the experience.
Opinion Andy, that's me.
I mean, you have opinions sometimes.
You absolutely can beat this game
when you're first run ever.
I'm sure you can, but it's exponentially more difficult
than just running a dungeon in the first game.
I feel like a lot of things have to go right.
It gets a lot easier with unlocks.
Oh yeah, I'm certain it does.
But easier is probably the wrong word.
There's more options to be able to do things.
What do you have?
All right, you're dead.
I definitely like it.
I like it.
I'm very intrigued to see more.
I want to see more.
I want to see what they do with the rest of it.
It's just, if you really loved the first game,
you kind of have to like just forget about it
and try to play this one and enjoy it.
It's like everyone else is doing.
I am comparing every single thing
to the experience I had in the first one.
Which I mean, obviously it's Darkest Dungeon 2.
It's not like Darkest Dungeon colon, right?
This is not a colon experience.
This is a two.
If it was Darkest Dungeon colon,
da da da da, da da da da,
then it'd be like, okay, wait, this is a different thing.
So I understand that we're in, it's two.
Like Darkest Dungeon colon on the road to insanity
instead of Darkest Dungeon 2.
Shut up, Redditor.
Okay.
Okay, fine, I'll, let's just play.
How much torch do I even have?
No, I don't want it.
My torch, look at the torch.
47?
Are you gonna play the Outer Wilds DLC?
Probably not.
How far, how far am I?
Order.
Where's the lair?
I got a P, I'll be right back.
Every piss is a huge Tom Hanks
leak of their own hangover pee.
It's the most specific reference I've heard
since I started broadcasting on Twitch.
That was, what an insane reference.
Let's keep going.
I'm just gonna, avoid the hoarder.
Oh, shit, did I, I got it?
Nice, academic cash.
The Wainwright await eager to ply his trade.
Trinkets?
Ooh, I'll take it.
Okay, avoid the hoarder.
So let's go, let's go left.
Oh, let's do it.
What do we get?
Dude, the last time we were here, you all died?
These enemies are a lot easier than the other ones.
Like, I'm destroying these guys.
That first zone that I was in,
or the second one, was ridiculous.
Was I not supposed to be there?
You eat something crunchy for us.
No, half people in the world love that,
half people in the world hate it.
I think I'll abstain from doing that.
All right, let's do a little dash.
Blank this guy.
Stress heal, on yourself.
Oh, come on, what is this?
Well, the blight still hit, if I throw it.
Oh, even if you're stealth, okay, cool.
Are you gonna beat Orphan of Kos on stream?
No, crunchy, what's the crunchiest shit ever?
Hmm, let me see, what's the crunchiest thing
you've ever eaten?
Probably those little bread ovals,
those little crostinis, if they're a little bit stale,
they feel like they're gonna break your teeth
when you bite it and you snap off,
and that's probably the crunchiest.
Oh, you didn't like that.
We learned to face the future.
Who wants to put that on?
You do.
I'll take it.
Say booms, it'll be funny.
Booms.
Did I ever tell you this story, booms?
There, the academic study,
I kinda don't wanna do this.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Prinket chance?
Oh, let's leave.
Academic study, hero shrine.
Yeah, let's do hero shrine.
I'm thinking we do the plague doctors last,
or no, maybe somebody else.
Eye of the Man again.
Man in arms.
Prove you're real.
Okay.
Face cam, I already did a face cam today.
You have a military career,
or perhaps as treacherous as war itself.
The one tested in combat.
Yeah, can you prove you're real?
For advancement.
Why do I have to do it and you don't?
Dubious campaign of influence and intimidation.
He had a blast claimed to coveted command
and was eager to bask in the glory of the victories
that were sure to come.
I passed the capture.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I didn't have to do a capture, I'm streaming.
Hello.
This is remove the post and minus three speed.
It's everybody.
Cool.
Hospital or unknown.
I don't think I have enough money to do anything.
I think we're going, who's the lair?
We'll do unknown.
I don't need to go to, I don't need the hospital, unknown.
Are you a prerecorded Andy?
No, not right now.
Oh, you shuffled me around.
I don't like that.
Really?
You really get the luckiest road battles?
That's a good thing.
Wait, did you just point blank shot somebody
that was far away?
How does that make sense?
I want you to move.
What?
There it is.
Yeah, you're dead.
Well, you can't do anything.
Bork effect bark disease.
What?
Bork effect?
Bork effect bark bark.
Nice.
Rest, he's stressed.
It is ours now.
Ooh, 10%, I'll take that.
You should definitely put that on.
I want you to hurt things, please.
I think this is carrying the whole run.
This is your conscience speaking.
You want to order a long chicken from Burger King tonight.
I don't.
I really don't.
I'm on this antibiotic and it's fucking me up.
What's going on?
What happened?
Did you get ambushed or something?
Give stimulants to you.
I want you to go fast.
I want you to bolster.
I want you to take aim.
I want you to go forward.
Oh no, no, no, they have this stupid thing on.
I gotta get this.
How do I get it off?
My dear, my love.
Two large fries.
Did you really just fuck everything up?
We need to start doing some blood bleeding here.
Dodge, 75% dodge.
Jesus.
This sucks.
How am I supposed to take care of this?
I can't.
I didn't dodge it.
That was actually really lucky.
Holy shit.
All right, now give me a repost.
All right, shut that down.
I just go for it.
Now I'm gonna take aim
and I'm gonna blow this guy's brains up
after we get rid of that.
Are you talking like that?
What am I doing?
Okay, or you're dead or you're almost dead,
but this is a 75% chance.
I'm not gonna be able to go through that.
God damn it.
We're just gonna have to take,
we're gonna take this off you.
Come on.
How do I get that off?
Take that shit off.
Thank you.
Oh man.
Good night, speed.
Ulster.
Point blank.
That's really good.
I thought this was a bird watching stream
but you've changed.
Yes, I have many times over the course of my life.
You're right.
Guard the highway man.
What happened?
You do a 10 hour birdwatching stream.
That's not gonna happen.
You might get a three to four hour birdwatching experience.
Maybe one day if I feel like it.
You're definitely getting the baby sensory video stream.
That's absolutely.
I'm gonna try to do this as fast as I can.
All right, death's door, but you're gonna blight.
Death's door again.
Come on.
Start already.
40 flame, nice.
Ooh.
Just have the ability to put on a trinket.
You have to do the don't call Jerma at 3 a.m. video.
Can I buy this game right now?
My finger's on the button.
I mean, do you like, I don't know.
I can't tell you what to buy and what not to buy.
Vulnerable.
Yeah, let's go.
Not seeing this guy.
50% more damage from the next hit.
This is huge.
Oh, come on.
You're gonna play Outer Wilds DLC?
I'm not playing Outer Wilds DLC.
Holy shit.
Okay, I would say if you're a big fan of Darkest Dungeon
and the Darkest Dungeon lore and world
and a lot of its core gameplay mechanics, yes.
But everybody else I would say maybe wait
a little bit longer until they flesh out
some of the things they wanna flesh out.
But I like it.
I think this is fun.
It takes a little longer to do things than the other game,
but I feel like that's intentional.
I don't know.
I think it's pretty good.
I am enjoying it for what it is, right?
I don't want to say that the game sucks
or that it's fantastic because you can't just read.
Okay, if I came up with a book
and that book was called The Life and Times
of Jeremy Albertson and it was a fantasy novel
with an adventure with Otto
and I released the book and I said,
hey, it's not done yet though.
And you guys are like, what does that mean?
And you go through chapter one and chapter two
and I say, it's gonna be a 20 chapter book.
And at the end of chapter two,
there's just 150 blank pages.
What would you say?
Well, first of all, I would have just like scammed you.
But on every page it says coming soon,
next chapter coming soon, next chapter coming soon,
next chapter coming soon.
Like you don't know what happens.
You just know what happens like very early on.
And for some cases, I mean, this is very early, right?
There's a lot more of this that's gonna happen eventually.
Oh, and by the way,
throughout the whole first like two chapters,
this typo is everywhere and it's got weird odd spacing.
But the story and the thing that you're reading
is actually like, this is kind of good.
This is all right.
Triple spaces after periods, not sponsored.
No, it's not sponsored one.
And with all that being said,
I will tell you, I said it already.
I fur the other game.
I like just like constant upgrades everywhere.
The currency of being like,
do I wanna upgrade the carriage, the characters,
the healing places that I like the Hamlet
and like using the portraits that you get,
the relics that you get it.
I love that system.
But this is a different, completely different system.
I prefer the other system.
That doesn't mean I don't think this game is any good.
It's just, I have a preference for the other kind of system.
TLDR, I'm not gonna read what you said
because I don't wanna say that out loud
because I don't believe it.
All right, we need to get rid of this.
Why is that still on?
That shouldn't still be on.
That shouldn't have taken it off?
Well, whatever.
Not to say I like the game.
Irma hates everything.
Yeah, the first game was managing people and a place.
And this one is managing your trip
and like you're managing your time, I think, right?
You're managing a trip,
not managing like your people or your place.
Holy shit, he's gonna die.
Oh, oh.
Oh, no.
I gotta get that.
All right, heal.
Should you blind it?
You can blind an inanimate object?
What just happened?
Ignore armor.
I wanna use the absence.
I need to heal somebody.
Oh, come on.
Oh, this is bad.
I don't have any heals or anything.
I'm in a lot of trouble.
What should I do?
Who's more important?
Probably the healer.
Okay.
Ignores armor.
God damn it, the shit is in the way.
Or, you piece of shit, give me a break.
Okay, can I...
Fuck you.
What?
Why didn't I heal?
Because I was trying to blind it.
Everyone, you guys are saying blind it,
blind it, blind it, blind it.
Everyone was saying blind it.
Didn't I say that you couldn't?
Why is everybody telling me to do that?
Everybody was telling me to blind it.
I have to move.
Die.
Cat IQ has room temperature.
Cat, chat, chat can't rotate a cube in their brain.
You know that that's one of my favorite comments ever.
I don't know who it was.
I don't know who you were.
You might be here right now.
But the chat can't rotate a cube in their mind.
It was just such a funny comment.
It just was.
The defense is back on there.
Ben, something going on between you two?
Wait, because they're in a relationship?
Wait, what?
Ignore defense.
All right, there's two different...
There's ignore shield and ignore other shield.
Guarded?
Is this guard or block?
Block, okay.
Die.
Can't do it.
I have to just use this.
Ah, you missed.
Jesus.
That sucked.
I need a healer.
Oh, what's at the other end?
That's pretty lucky, yeah.
I don't want to do this.
Today's oversight is tomorrow's regret.
Nope.
Hold on.
That's another thing, too.
I feel like I'm not strong enough to do anything.
I don't want to go in there
because I don't want the run to be over.
We must keep moving.
See, before, I didn't care if I threw four random dickheads
into a dungeon and they died.
I don't want to do that
because I'm afraid of having to start
the whole thing over again.
Does it make any sense?
Just going straight.
How do you know you can't beat it?
I feel like I'm not strong enough.
I don't have any confidence.
Feels bad to lose when you're playing for this long.
I don't know.
I need more time.
I need more time to process it.
I can't give you what I really believe.
I feel like I could change.
But I don't know, I feel like I'm not,
I feel like scared to do anything
because there's too much at stake.
Okay, these are just regular skeletons.
There's actually nothing at stake.
Well, I'm, yeah, but you have to fight now
so you can beat later.
Yeah, I'm holding on to like the fact that these,
I don't want these characters to die.
So I'm just trying to play safe and just try to get,
but playing safe is not going to do much for me.
None of us believe in you, Jerma.
You can fail as much as you want.
It's okay.
Oh my God.
Brutal.
That was brutal.
Is it possible that game sucks?
It's too early.
I don't know.
I can't, I don't know.
It's too early.
I don't think I can say that.
No.
It's better than Hades?
You can't compare apples to oranges.
I mean, Hades, I thought Hades was unbelievable.
But look, you can't say better,
what do you mean better than Hades?
Those are two completely different genres.
I want to kill this guy.
This is way better than Monkey Ball.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean, Outer Wilds DLC is better than Hades.
I, okay, but that's too, that's tough.
I mean, it's like, okay, is Bambi better than The Departed?
I don't, I mean, the two completely different movies,
the two completely different things.
Do you guys remember The Departed?
Oh, The Departed.
I remember the, can we talk about The Departed
for a second, just for a second?
If you haven't seen the movie, then just,
I mean, I'm gonna end the stream after this anyway.
The Departed, The Departed is a crazy movie.
The last, like, 20 minutes of The Departed
is some of the most wild, like, ridiculous shit ever.
Can we talk about it?
Sure, can we?
Okay, if you have not seen The Departed,
then it's, I would say it's probably time for you
to close the stream,
because we're gonna talk about The Departed.
Boston movie, takes place in Boston.
Crime movie, about cops, it's about fucking crime.
It's about fucking informants.
It's about everything.
It's about having a fucking informant.
Okay, so let me just tell you,
hey, wait, I'm gonna talk about this for a second.
I'm telling you, there's spoilers for The Departed incoming.
Here's your warning, your final warning.
The last 20 minutes of The Departed
is a bunch of characters in a row
shooting each other in the head.
Like, one main character to the next main character
shoots them in the head.
It's like the stupidest thing.
Like, four people get like the,
oh yeah, like bang.
It happens like four times in the last 15 minutes.
Omega Lul, Shakespeare ending.
Yeah, I remember watching it,
and just saying to myself,
after they did it like the second or third time,
they don't do it for a while,
and then they like end the movie
with it happening like a fourth time.
And you're just like, what?
Oh, it's fucking The Departed.
I'd shoot you in the head, main character.
I shoot other main character in the head.
I have a main character.
Shoot you in the fucking head.
Hey, it's the end of the fucking movie.
Hey, you made it all the way this far.
We just told you about all the stuff,
all the crazy stuff that happened.
People died, there was informants,
there was like drama going on
between like three or four different characters.
I think I'm gonna shoot this guy in the fucking head
to end the movie in the credits roll.
It was the whole last 20 minutes of the movie.
It was insane.
If you've never watched The Departed,
it's worth you watching
just to watch the last 10 to 15 minutes.
Somebody that was planning to watch The Departed
just join the stream.
Oh, we're in trouble now, all right.
I think we'll be all right.
Let's get a plate safe.
Well, now I wanna see it.
I mean, it's one of those movies
you kinda just have to see.
All right, these have to die.
Let's plan this out.
I can't do very much blight,
but I could try and do the coin flip.
I'm gonna actually go for it
because I'm gambling weirdo.
But let's just start this off by,
let's just kill the frontline.
Also, the rat survives to make all the rules.
Do I heal or, let's just go for it.
Here it is.
Sometimes you gotta do the 50-50.
Why did I do that?
They can just heal.
This is bad.
Although maybe they'll waste a turn eating
and not attacking.
Come on.
Point blank, point blank, point blank.
Oh, don't, this guy, he's gonna die.
24 damage.
Oh, actually, by the way, we're not,
oh my God, why is it doing so much damage?
50%, these things have to die.
I don't want to point blank that.
Oh shit, that's really ugly.
What happened?
Hopeful.
Oh shit.
Review the Godfather.
What do you mean, review the Godfather?
Cat puke sound waiting room.
I just didn't even look at what I did.
I just got distracted.
Yeah, I just did.
How am I supposed to review the Godfather?
All right, go for it.
Damn it.
Just review it.
All right.
Just say it was better than Hades.
Okay, the Godfather, the movie,
is better than Hades, I guess.
That was good.
A speed and dodge, good.
This move sucks.
What's the point of this move?
It's actually kind of awful.
That one should have been mine.
You're coughing up blood, you're almost dead, man.
Is Godfather better than the rat movie?
Well, that's up to the critics to decide.
Die, die.
Thank you.
I am not continuing.
Escape.
I've been on this run.
This is only the second run I've done.
I've been on this run for the whole stream.
Spent half the stream looking at monkeys and birds.
Yeah, I don't know if I wanna do this.
This might be the end.
Can I survive?
Just move back.
Smite better than the Godfather part three.
Maybe?
It's healing for such a little...
What the fuck?
That's so much damage.
I hit the enrage timer on this run.
The dollhouse stream better than the Godfather movies.
I don't care.
Kill the goats, quick.
Kill them, quickly.
It's not over.
Not yet.
Not over yet.
Everybody just focus on the goat.
There we go.
Respectful.
You can tell he's bored out of his mind with this game.
I'm just playing it.
I'm just playing the game.
I gotta move back.
Here it is.
Why are you guys doing this like an either or thing?
What do I get to eat?
A Burger King long chicken.
Respectful.
We're streaming 2021?
No, that's not how it works.
Because if you don't like a game,
it doesn't work that way.
You don't get to decide.
We do.
It works however we say it works.
Goodness.
Oh my goodness, guys.
Oh my goodness.
Controlling much here?
Excuse me?
Don't forget who has the keys to this house.
Don't forget who has the keys to the car.
Don't forget.
My mom does.
Takes very good care of us.
So, come on.
We don't, come on.
Hey, come on, punk.
You don't want to be late to dinner.
Coming, mom.
Be there in a minute.
Escape.
Quiet vessel, review Godfather 2.
Sure.
Think.
Yep.
Almost at the end.
What's better?
Squid game or ASMR YouTube videos?
I think I die here.
Ulster.
Or crit.
We laugh at those.
Oh shit.
This is bad.
They all have us.
Oh shit.
I have to go grenade, right?
Just hope it hits somebody?
No.
That would have been a big hit.
Aura.
You say?
Salmon.
Dead.
Oh, excuse me.
I can't believe he's still alive.
Holy shit.
He's bleeding though.
That's bad.
Can I heal you with anything?
Somebody bandage him.
Somebody do something.
You have a bandage or anything?
No.
Hi.
Oh, come on.
Somebody band that person.
Why is that from the drunk wine thing?
Help.
Don't die.
I think he's dead.
Oh, oh my God.
This guy is invincible.
He can do anything.
All right.
Do not kill him.
Oh, bark, bark, bark.
Next door.
Oh, that's right.
Good.
Good gamer.
Good gaming.
Stay alive.
Now do not do something stupid
and just kill him in one hit.
Don't believe we have done it.
Run saved.
And the inn is right around the corner.
Very nice.
To the inn.
Too much shit.
I need to get to the inn now.
Way too much stuff.
What junk did?
Yeah, get rid of this.
Get rid of this too.
Made it.
All right.
Heal to 25%.
Plus 20% damage next region.
That's actually, sounds pretty nice.
Finally, I can spend some baubles.
All right.
We got supplies for the quest.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right.
So I have four pancakes.
Minus one stress.
Okay.
Plus resistance till next inn.
Let's give it to you.
And then high chance of plus two.
Oh fuck.
Okay.
Well, hopefully it doesn't happen.
Nice.
Did he skip the boss?
I think I might've.
I don't know.
Whoa.
I got seven points.
You may stand just a little taller at the end.
Point blank?
Yeah.
Let's upgrade that.
Point blank.
Do list for sure.
And then see what else we can do.
Might as well.
What do we got?
Bend.
Yeah.
Pistol shot.
Poison dart's already upgraded.
Roe dagger?
Probably.
Can you only upgrade stuff once?
I feel like that's good.
I feel like this is all fine now.
Take aim.
Ooh, you get a, yeah.
Nice.
Okay.
Your coach must be maintained
if it is to carry you where you must go.
Plus lots.
Trainer's done.
Select route.
All right.
Do I want to do bad country or corrupting?
Plus 500 hope.
Let's do this one.
Precious.
77.
All right.
What do we got?
Time before the end.
Combat start plus 70.
Holy shit.
That's good.
I think I want that.
25% health?
I want this.
I can upgrade.
Max HP until next in.
Yeah.
Nation.
Stress.
Salves.
A regrettably necessary acquisition.
Yeah.
And yeah.
Each improvement.
Unvariable.
All right.
Minus one stress on you.
And you.
Then max HP on you.
And who else?
Probably the, yeah, you.
Oh, hell yeah.
Look at that fucking match HP.
Is there any heals?
And what you can.
Your wealth no longer has meaning.
If indeed it ever did.
Let's put this on you.
Plus resistance on you.
Cause I'm about to just like give you
a little bit of a slurp here.
Try to negate what we just did.
All right.
Holy shit.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
We're gonna do the back country.
Which is intense.
And civil wars.
Do need, yeah, here we go.
Okay.
Let's go to you.
Like I don't do this.
Do this one.
I don't do this that often either.
That trinkets not coming off.
Okay.
Okay, I do.
Go with healing salve.
Healing salve.
No, no, no.
You shouldn't have that.
You should have.
What do you stack?
No.
You have the cure.
But no, no.
You have that anyways.
I have too much shit.
I have to throw away some of this stuff.
I have too much stuff.
Trinkets.
Start with the 75% defense.
Who should I give that to?
Tank?
That makes the most sense.
But ooh, no, we can't do that.
Probably the healer, yeah.
Ax HP on the healer.
Yeah.
And then plus 10.
What is that?
Already have one of these on.
You crit.
10% damage.
Take the resistance.
And I think that's good.
Nice.
People who remind Jeremy to end the stream
are like students who remind the teacher
to assign homework.
Let's go.
How long have I been streaming for?
Like five and a half, six hours?
Six, just about.
But does it save?
I don't know.
This is probably, I don't know if I should start this.
Resignation.
So yeah, I don't think I should start this.
Stop entertaining us.
Ban that student.
Yeah, I mean, six is perfect.
Six hours is a good place to stop, I think.
But please confirm with me that if I like exit,
is it gonna abandon the run or is it gonna be saved here?
I hope I'm saved, right?
It does, you're saved, okay.
All right, good.
Cool.
All right, it's fun.
I'm starting to understand how interesting it is.
I prefer the old system, but look,
you can't have everything you want.
It's definitely new.
Might take a little bit of getting used to, but we'll see.
We'll see what they do.
Thank you so much for watching, everybody.
I am going to end the stream now.
We'll see you tomorrow.
5 p.m. Pacific time for public domain movie night
to Halloween edition.
We'll see you soon.
Thanks again for watching.
That was Darkest Dungeon 2.
We had a big raid from Ludwig if you're still here.
Thanks a lot, Ludwig.
And all Ludwigs chatters.
Thanks a lot, guys.
Have a wonderful rest of your evening.
We'll see you tomorrow.
If we don't see you tomorrow, then have a happy Halloween.
Be safe.
Don't be stupid.
We'll see you soon.
Thanks to all the subs.
There were a lot of gifted subs today too.
Appreciate it, guys.
Don't be stupid, don't be an idiot.
Yeah, 5 p.m. Pacific.
Check your local time.
See you tomorrow.
And we, let's see, let me see, let me see, let me see.
Let me see.
What time is it right now?
It's eight o'clock.
I'm sorry, can I get a costume in time?
Is it still possible for me to get a Halloween costume?
It's only eight.
I think I have time.
Yeah, I got time.
It's eight o'clock.
See what I can do.
Use the Naruto costume again?
I don't even have that thing anymore.
All right, good night.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a great night.
Take care of yourselves.