Digital Monsters, Digital Monsters, Digital Monsters.
Hey guys, welcome back to another edition of Digital Monsters.
I'm your guide. The emote is here. Yep, I've been hanging out in chat for like an hour or so.
Popping in and out, just popping my head in here. I was gonna hold off
and have a few more come out this next week, but I decided, you know, whatever.
Just put it out. I think it looks pretty good.
Ah, so today we're doing a extra stream. No, it's not even really extra.
Just another one in a row. Only had a small, you know, three to four hour, three and a half hour
stream on what was it now? A couple days ago. So I figured let's complete it and let's put,
you know, another three, four, five, six, however long. Just chill out with the MS-DOS
video game archive. There are 4,334 MS-DOS games on this website, first of all.
Second of all, it is you who will pick the games I will play.
Let's just make sure it works for the purpose of the stream.
Go ahead and start clicking on the screen. I want to make sure it still works
and it does, doesn't it? This is going to be a smart click stream. Now, is there a way?
All right, so do me a favor. Get like all four corners. You know, go like top left,
top right as far as you can go. Give me some corners here. All right, so top and top right
and top left work fine, but it's just not that bottom area. I wonder why that is.
There's nothing really I can change about it either. Should be okay though.
Get out your laptops, mobile users. Yeah, this should just be fun.
Just wanted to do it. Sam and Max will return this coming week here.
Let me take a look at my calendar. It's like that because of the Twitch UI for full
screening. I see. I still remember you calling me an asshole yesterday. No, I was just
fucking around. I was a little hangry last night. I'm sorry. I was hungry and annoyed.
I was hangry. I was. Only at the very, very end though. I don't know. It just kind of
clicked in there. What happened? Nothing happened. I was just being, I was just,
I was irritated because I don't know. I got, I'm just a human, all right?
And sometimes you get irritated. Maybe you should eat some food,
asshole. See, somebody called me an asshole. I can't, what am I supposed to do?
No, I'm just kidding. No, no, no, no, no, no. Smart clicks work. To be fair chat can be,
no, all I did, I was responding. Somebody said that this stream today was going to,
was going to be a shitty idea. And I said, Hey, Hey, that's it. I didn't say anything else.
That was, that was it. It's a new day though. You know, if you give up a home run,
you don't think about that home run every single time you play. You gotta get struck out sometimes.
Well, the pitcher doesn't get struck out unless you're playing in the national league.
Think about that home run. But all right, let's, uh, let's get going.
Just be funny. No, that's not forehead. No, it's not. Do not, no,
germapop is not intended to be used as a forehead. It's intended to be used as an
ice cream to eat and enjoy. Oh, great. So here, this is how it's going to work.
Let me turn off this for a second here. Will we get in a minute? Okay. So let me make sure
this is on correctly. It should be. And as you see here, would you look at that? Here are
some of the thousands of video games that are on here. So very important. First little tidbit
of information here is the reason why it looks like this is because this area here is if you
want me to scroll. This is the archive. From my understanding, and this was a recommendation,
by the way, from my understanding, all this stuff is like abandoned vaporware on like the
archive website. It's on like archive.org. I think this is, this is all like kind of
shit that doesn't, like doesn't exist anymore. How about this? Anything that's like still
copywritten, I won't play. So, okay, here's your criteria. Everyone gets to pick. You guys
get to pick what I do today. No copyright stuff, no porn games, no games that are rated R,
no games that require anything to do with a mouse, and no games that have loud sounds.
So you've got to pick wisely here because I don't want to get in trouble. So out of
this four level, how many? 4,000, this 4,334, you probably have a choice of between like
maybe 40 different games. But the reason why this is down here is because I'm going to
just start at the top here. And by the way, I get full veto. So if you're going to want
me to play like Sim City illegally, I'm going to have to veto that one. I'm just going to
have to do that. If you want me to play, for instance, Stunts, I'm going to have to veto
that one too. This is copyrighted. I'm just kidding. It's not illegal. It's very illegal.
Because I don't want to be like on an illegal stream. Any Twitch staff in here?
Any Twitch staff in here that tell me this is like illegal? This is all puppetsarchive.org.
You got like Aladdin. Oh, well, the new movie's coming out, right? It's a game library. Yeah,
it's at archive.org public game library. Well, let's put it this way. If like Twitch
staff comes in here and says, get out of here, I'll be like, all right, man.
And then we'll pack it up and go to a different streaming website for like an hour.
I'm kidding. That's a joke. Don't, nobody hold that on me. All right. So remember if
you let's get started. If you want me to scroll, it's an infinite scroll, by the way.
This is already off limits. I'm not going to play a porn game. So don't click that one.
Here we go. Please click on the thing if you want me to scroll down. And by the way,
a scroll down means all of it. I'm scrolling down here. So if you want that scroll,
you better know that's what you want. You know how this is going to end. Not yet. I don't.
Please click the screen on the thing you'd like me to play. All right. Already vetoed the porn
game. It's not porn. It's a porn game. This game starts off at porn. It's a porn start.
It's a porn start. It really isn't. I don't know. It could be a porn game.
Can you guys not click over here? You should be able to click on the right side.
No, you can't. I'm getting baited. Yeah. See, if you want me to scroll,
you click over there. Make sure you click on the same spot because I have to do addition.
All right. So now that we know the rules, now that you know the rules, we're going to do it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, slow down. Add an arrow icon. All right. Yeah,
that's a good idea. You know, when people just think of good ideas, I love it. So let's add
like a down arrow that you have to click on. Well, I'm just going to put like a circle
or something. Look, how about I just put the popsicle up there. Put a down vote. No,
no, no. All right. If you want to scroll, click on the pop, the new emote. This is where you need
to click if you want to scroll down. All right. Here we go. And play elevator music. That's too
much for me. How are new viewers going to know that? They, you know what? They won't.
You're right. I'm still lost. Wait, why is it covering up the, hold on a second. There we go.
Okay. You want me to scroll? No, everybody just clicked it because I put the face up
there. You don't actually want me to scroll. It's just, it's just like bugs to a light.
It's like, oh shit, click a face. Only click once. We want ice cream. Oh shit. At least
the bug lights are working. Well, it looks like we're going to do the Oregon trail.
And I kind of knew that was going to be what we were going to do at first.
I figured that's what we were going to do. Oregon trail it is. So here we go. Let's do
the Oregon trail. It might be loud and I apologize in advance if it is. Here we go.
Don't worry. I've got it set up so I can do this. Hey, should I gotta get the image off
the screen? No fuck. I can't get them off the screen. All right. Here we go.
I'll copyright 1990. I'm fucked. Just keep, I have to keep them there for the first month.
You may travel the trail, learn about the trail, see the Oregon top 10, turn sound off,
choose management option. What is N? What is your option? Choose the trail. Travel the trail.
So how many, many kinds of people made the trip to Oregon. You may be a banker from Boston.
Yeah, I mean that's the easy one though. These are difficulty settings. Be a carpenter
from Ohio. Be a farmer from Illinois. Find out the differences between these choices. I
know that the banker just gets the most money and I gotta be, it says Boston. I have to
click it. What is the first name of the wagon leader? What are the first names of the
four other members in your party? All the people that are like in this house.
Did you get my multiple split personality? My roommate, my girlfriend, and my dog. Yeah,
these are correct. Do you sleep with Jax in the same bed? Yes, it's me. It is 1848.
Your jumping off place for Oregon is Independence, Missouri. You must decide which month to
leave Independence. It's gonna be too hot in July. It'll be a little too rainy for me in April.
May bugs come out. We're going in March. Before leaving Independence, you should buy equipment
and supplies. You have 1600 bits in cash, but you don't have to spend it all now.
Okay, 1600 bucks. You can buy whatever you need at Matt's General Store. Hello, I'm Matt.
So you're going to Oregon. I can fix you up with what you need. A team of oxen to pull
your wagon. Clothing for both summer and winter. Excellent. Plenty of food for the trip. Ammunition
for your rifles and spare parts for your wagon. Matt's General Store. Okay, oxen. Total bill
zero. Amount you have. Which item would you like to buy? I eat a lot, so let's make sure
we get some food here. I recommend you take at least 200 pounds of food for each person
in your family. I see that you have five people in all. You'll need flour, sugar,
bacon, and coffee. My price is 20 cents a pound. How many pounds of food do you want?
Oh, god damn it. This is one of those math problems. If Judy eats 400 pounds of bacon
and Kim eats 200 pounds of sugar, how many pounds of bacon will it take to make one
bag of flour? I don't fucking know. Let's go with like 5,000 pounds. No, how many? Two, four,
six, eight, a thousand? I eat a lot. I eat like, okay, I eat like six times a day.
You wonder why I get so hangry. My body is just burning calories constantly. I can't stop it,
no matter what I do. When I'm lying in bed, my body is just like 400 degrees. Kim will roll
over to me and be like, god, you are like a fireball. And I'm just like sweating like, what?
Oh, sorry. And I'll turn over and Jax will be on the other side and he'll be like,
I don't see the problem. I think you're a little cold actually. Because he's like
30,000 degrees hotter than I am. So, okay, we need a thousand pounds. But I eat more,
so I'm gonna get 1200 pounds. Like, I eat for two, you know, like a pregnant guy.
Food, 200, total bill 240. Oxen. There are two oxen in a yolk. I recommend at least three
yolk. I charge $40 a yolk. See, it's doing, this is like children's math. Okay, I need
three, so two, four, six, six oxens. How many yolk do you want? More, right? Anytime you
recommend, I want four. Four or five? I'm gonna do five. Clothing. You'll need warm clothing
in the mountains. I recommend taking at least two sets of each clothes per person.
Each set is 10 bucks. I don't trust this matte person. Why? Because he looks like
the old version of the ice cream that is on the screen right now. I mean, that's weird,
I guess. Because he vapes. That's a pipe. You're getting scammed. I'm not getting scammed yet. I
haven't signed the check. Okay, you need warm clothes in the mountains. I recommend taking
at least two sets of clothes per person. So, 10 sets of clothes. Let's go with 12 sets of
clothes. I'm a banker. I got a lot of money. Okay, ammunition. I sell ammunition in boxes of
20 bullets. Each box costs two bucks. How many boxes do you want? A lot. Because you
have to like shoot squirrels and stuff and bugs. I'm gonna say like five boxes. Okay,
maybe try to get more than that. Hold on. That was only 10 bucks. I want 10 boxes. Okay,
spare parts. It's a good idea to have a few spare parts for your wagon. Here are the
prices. Wagon wheel, wagon axle, wagon tongue. You have a lot more money. Yeah,
because I need to invest it. I don't want to spend every single cent that I own. It's all
the money that I have. I want to invest it into fucking, I don't know, I'm gonna put like
a call option on Tesla to expire. Hopefully, hopefully in the money in like two or three
weeks. I'm an investment. I'm playing the part. What do you come on? All right, I want
how many wagon wheels do you want? I want 12. No, that's too many. Wagon wheel. It's
a good idea to have a few spare parts. A few. Five. Your wagon may only carry three
wagon wheels. That's bullshit. I got 500 bucks. I want another wagon. Buy another wagon.
Three. Can I do five axles? All right, what was gonna do the max? Three, three, three.
Total bill. Okay, I have like a thousand dollars left. Should I buy more? Should I buy more
animals? The wagon has too much stuff. Everyone's gonna have to walk. All right,
I'm gonna buy some more. I'm gonna buy five more of oxen. No, no, no, no, no. Okay,
that's not adding. That's total. I'm gonna six yolks. Ammo. How many boxes do I want?
Let's go with like 20 boxes. More than that. Let's go with 100 boxes. It can't
even count that high. 50 boxes. All right, now what about clothes? Maybe some extra
clothes. Um, 10. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Um, 20. That's less. Oxen. All right,
how about like 20? 15. 15. It won't let me buy more. I can only do single digits.
Eight. There we go. I think we're good to go. More food. No, I don't need more food.
How many pounds was it? 2,000 pounds. All right, that's 2,000 pounds of food.
More ammo. More ammo. All right, I'm gonna say 75 boxes. More clothes. I guess I'll do a couple
more clothes. 30? Less oxen. Okay, I guess I'll. Well then, you're ready to start. Good luck.
You have a long and difficult journey ahead of you. Okay. I knew there was sounds. That's
very, that's very loud for me. Hope it's not loud for you. Uh, independent. March 1st,
1848. Which one of them is me? Oh, look, there's Otto. Oh, like, I know what you guys are gonna
say. It's cold. Health good. Pace steady. Rations filling. You may continue on trail.
Check supplies. Look at the map. Change pace. Stop to rest. Let's just go on the trail.
Talk to people. Let's go. From Independence, it is 102 miles to the Kansas River crossing date.
It's cold. Let's go. Press enter to size up the situation. What do you mean,
size up the situation? What are we talking about, like MTV's? It wasn't gonna knock me
out? Size them up? You wanna come, you wanna come, come at me? You wanna come at me?
Situation? That was pretty good. I liked that one. I don't care if you didn't. I liked it.
Press enter to size up the situation. Severe blizzard. Lose one day.
Hmm. What do we got for supplies? 16 oxen. 1,500 bullets. How do we already eat 50 pounds of food
in one day? We're good. Cold. Health good. Food. Severe blizzard. Lose a day. Go. What I used
to do in math class is I would change it to the fastest you could possibly run and skip
every single scenario and I could never get to the end and I never knew why. Press enter the
size it up a little bit. Rations, filling. Let's, hold on. No, no, no. No, everyone's not just
gonna eat and fucking scrape a bunch of potatoes and carrots into the trash. That's not gonna
happen. Okay, filling meals are large and generous. No. Meals are small but adequate.
Let's go with two. Okay, change pace. A grueling pace. I always love to do grueling
pace. Only for like a few minutes though. Not that long. All right, let's go continue on
the trail. Snowbound. Lose nine days. Did we go, is it an avalanche? Go. You are now at the
Kansas River crossing. Would you like to look around? Yes. I can't do this one. Sorry. It's
pretty nice. All right, Kansas River crossing. Talk to people. Is anybody around? A stranger
tells you, can't afford to take a ferry. We're making our wagon into a boat. We'll turn it
over, cock the bottom and sides with pitch and use it to float our goods across. After swim the
animals. Hope it don't rain. The river's high enough. Okay. Anybody to trade with. You meet
another emigrant who wants one set of clothing. He will trade you 76 bullets. Are you willing
to trade? No. 76 bullets. That's bad. Let me check the supplies. We're good. I got plenty
of food. I got some money. Let's continue on the trail. You must cross the river in order to
continue. The river at this point is currently 613 feet across and 2.8 feet deep in the middle.
All right, so it's almost three feet deep and it's 600 feet. Three feet deep. It's cold
though. You may attempt to ford the river. Cock the wagon and float it across. Take a
ferry across. Wait to see if conditions improve. Get more information. We're gonna take a ferry.
Take the ferry. The ferry operator says that he will charge you five dollars
and you'll have to wait four days. Five dollars. That's it? Are you serious? Pay the premium
every time. That's five bucks. Oh yes, we're going. Look at all them swimming over there.
Hey, sorry. We're just trying to go the speed limit over here.
Get me more cigarettes and coffee and chocolate on my fucking massive
mansion boat. There's only six football fields. He's rich. Who's the guy on the right?
I forgot he was there. All right, from the Kansas River it is 82 miles to the big blue
river crossing. Health good. Weather warm. Food plenty of food. Grueling. We're good.
Everything's fine. You are now at the big blue river crossing. Would you like to look around?
Yeah, let's get another song. Um, ma'am, I'm not entirely sure. As a doctor that's been in this
field for over 35 years, we've never had somebody hooked up to a machine
we thought was gonna die real soon and then this shit started happening.
Just gotta get your camera out and Snapchat it. This is unbelievable.
So we got check supplies. Let's see how we're doing. Snapchat is the most boomer thing
you've ever said. Why? You guys don't like Snapchat? I haven't used it in a while.
All right, we're good. Uh, I would like to continue on the trail. Everyone's fine.
You must cross the river in order to continue. The river is at this point is currently 248 feet
across and five feet deep in the middle. Uh, I would attempt. Where's the ferry? I can't pay.
I don't, I don't want to go in there. Excuse me, I don't want to go in the water.
No, my things will get wet. Where's the ferry? Excuse me, ferry to take me across?
And this is the part of the TV show or the movie where all the people I laughed at
are walking by me now and are looking and like scoffing like,
he's got to do it this way now. And I'm like, no, I can't. I don't think I can.
Uh, how much is, let's see. He's role playing in the Oregon trail. Yes, I am.
I'm not going to forward the river. We're going to cock the wagon and float across.
We're going to turn into like fucking bread box.
No. Okay. I'm dead. The way I get tipped over while floating, you lose 25 sets of clothing.
What did I have all the shirts on? Three, well, all right, hold on a minute. This doesn't
make any sense. Was I just hoarding all the t-shirts? Would I do it in like a t-shirt
challenge video? And then the fucking boat tipped over?
That's why I drowned in four foot deep water. It wasn't even, no, it was less than that. It
was like four, it was like three and a half. I was way down by cinder blocks apparently. Okay.
Whatever. I don't need to be alive as long as one of me is alive. I don't care.
Oh, that's unfucking believable. All right. It's 118 miles to Fort Kearney. Let's go.
Lose trail. See, no, you don't have me here. So I was good at navigating.
All right. Let's, people can eat now because I eat way too much.
So now I can increase the food because I'm not around to eat at all
and do a YouTube challenge videos and then drown myself with 25 different t-shirts on.
Change food. Let's go filling. Pays can stay at grueling because that's what we're going to do.
Continue on the trail. Let's go. Press enter. Now we're good. Cool. Health is fair. Why?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Why is health fair? What's wrong? Oh, I'm not even close.
Okay. Let's just get to Fort. Let's get to Fort Monopoly. Ah, shit. I gotta pay this guy
60 bucks. He's got a hotel on here already. Fort Kearney, what's that worth?
Here, now at Fort Kearney, would you like to look around? Yes, I would.
You died in your, you literally died in your neighbor's yard. No, I died in my neighbor's
pool. Why did I have to drown? All right. Let's check the supplies. I got, I only have five
sets of clothing. I have to get something. I have to trade. Attempt to trade. Can I,
can anybody have any clothes? You meet another immigrant who wants one wagon axle. You don't
have this. Yeah, because I dragged it all down with me. Buy supplies. Okay. How much money do
we have? You have $335 clothing. $12 per set. What's this fucking premium bullshit?
A couple, one, like two, three more, four more. Okay. No more. I need, I need axles too.
God damn it. How much are they? Did I lose anything else?
Check supplies, axles, guts, clothes. Now I've got plenty of bullets. Nobody knows how to use a
gun in this troop. How many, anybody know how to use a gun? No, no, no, no, no. Oh, let's
take 1500 bullets. No, Jax doesn't know how to use a gun. Jax only knows how to use pretend
guns. He's a video game star. Okay. I think we're good. I'm going to stop to rest though.
At least get, like bury me. Am I, what am I? We'll put, at least put something somewhere to
remember me. Uh, how many, okay. We'll take one day off. Okay. It is 250 miles to Chimney Rock.
Cool. Health is fair. Got plenty of food. You're still floating in your neighbor's pool.
Wrong trail again. I wouldn't have done this. Somebody's stress eating because they lost the
trail. Who is it? Oh, we're going to get to a stump. I don't even feel invested anymore.
I don't even feel involved anymore. Yes, I would. Happy new year, everybody. It's April 18th. Why
would they play this song? I would accept like, like December 31st, 1848. I can't,
I can't get out of this. Okay guys, I can. I'm going to, I'm going to change the pace.
We're going to go, we're going to do strenuous. Let's take a look at the map.
Okay. Your route, rivers, mountains, land marks forts. Okay, let's keep going. It is 86 miles to
Fort Laramie. Yes. Severe blizzard. That's okay. It's snowy. We can make it. Don't need to size
it up. I got plenty of food. I was corrected by you. Pass a gravesite. Would you like to
look closer? Yes, I would because I would like to be buried here. I would like to at
least remember I told you here lies. Uh, can we just like, we just like put me on there too.
Hey, hey, hey, come out and play. Am I supposed to know who that is?
You are now at Fort Laramie. Would you like to look around? Uh-huh.
That's just a baby toy that plays random songs. Oh, it comes with four songs. Uh,
how are we doing? Let me check my supplies again. I got plenty of bolts. I got some
money left. Pounds of food. We're good. We're good. 190 miles to Independence Rock.
Severe blizzard again. Weather warm. Interesting. Now, as sure this isn't like ash coming from
a volcano. Fair health. Fair warm. Fair. Here comes the rock. Get there. Come on.
You are now at Independence Rock. I would love to look around. May 5th.
If you smell. All right. Let's, uh, talk to somebody. Uh, Big Louie tells you.
Goodbye, Platte River. Goodbye, Sandy Hills and White Buffalo Sculls. Now we climb the
Sweetwater Valley to cross the continental divide and self-pass. Once across the Rockies,
we'll make a steep descent into the Green River Valley. Find wild fruit. Do I find it?
Size it up. Hunt for fruit. Enter key to start or stop walking. Point the rifle.
Novice hunters to point the rifle expert hunters and space bars fire.
Well, I'm a novice hunter, so yeah, I told you you shoot squirrels. Oh,
fuck. That squirrel was coming for blood from the animals you shot. Got 923 pounds of meat.
What? How big was that buffalo? Was that buffalo as big as a car?
Buffaloes are huge. Holy shit. I, I don't know why that I can only carry a hundred pounds.
Who cares? Actually, yeah, they are. They are huge. Aren't they? That just seemed like such
an enormous, unbelievable number. This is what happens when you live in this current day and
age. That's sad. I did not believe that for a whole 10 seconds. 900 pounds of meat. Click
this link, link, link. Hold on. What do you mean? Hold on. First of all, I can't, my mouse is
locked in. At least I got, did the video, did I public the video? That's fucking fast.
No, I died. Well, hopefully someone will public my t-shirt challenge.
All right. Continue on the trail. I can't believe I only have, which rock is this one?
You are now at South Pass. Let's look around. Did they talk about me when I'm gone? Do you
think? Plenty of clothes. Look at the map. I'm getting there. I'm going to get there. I'm
going to get to the whole of Oregon. Talk to people. A young girl tells you. My father is
very sick and we are resting here until he gets better. We have been pushing too hard
and our health has suffered. When my father is able to travel again, we will go at a slow
pace. Sorry. My father was fairly wealthy. That was the Otto voice. No. Hi everyone,
this is Otto. That's the Otto voice. That was, I just, no, that was Otto. Yeah,
that was Otto whispering. You were right. And you know, every voice of the, hey,
Germa quotes four voices, quote Elberton. Otto's cousin. The trail divides here. You
may head for green river crossing, head for Fort Bridger, see the map. Let's take a look.
This is our first ever choice. What's the, how do I go to straight as hard as possible?
It's not Fort Bridger. We're going straight as far, as fast as I can. Let you guys vote.
Okay. Hold on. Okay. Let's you guys can vote. Don't do it yet. I said, don't do it yet.
Don't do it yet. You have to wait cause I have to switch between like three screens. Stop it.
Okay. Don't wait. Stop. Here we go. Ready? Don't do it yet. Don't do it yet. Hold on.
Don't do it yet. Do it now. You see I have to wait cause I have to get it like squared up.
How the fuck am I ever going to know when you're clicking on? No, this is not going
to work. Hmm. I think they're clicking on one, two or three. I can't zoom in because my
mouse is locked in the emulator. So I have to stay here. If I hit escape,
I pull out and it screws the whole thing up. It looks, it let, that looks like one to me.
That's one. All right. Thanks for voting. Hold on. Let me get like this off. I have to hit
the BRB. Thanks for pointing. A straw poll would just be easier. Yeah, it probably would.
Okay. We're back. We're going one. That's the one I was going to pick anyway.
Another river. All right. You're now at green river crossing. Let's look around.
This looks like a big river. Okay. Check. How are we doing? Talk to people.
A Shoshone Indian tells you when wagons first started coming through here, we did not mind.
We even found it good to trade game and fish with the travelers and help them cross the
rivers. Now there are too many white men and too little land for grazing. I mean we did,
we did like, I mean, I mean the Native Americans, like we, like we fucking,
we fucked them. You know what I mean? Like that's like, it was bullshit.
They got a bad fucking deal. It's true. It's true. But let's cross. That's not political.
It's not. That's just, that's just, that's just the thing, right? I'm not going to afford
it. This is 20 fucking feet deep. You must cross the river in order to continue. The
river at this point is 400 feet across and 20 feet deep. Take my money. You know what I
mean? Take my money and get across safely. Take a ferry across. Use my money. I live on in my
money. I live on through my capital. Take the ferry. It's only five bucks. Why could I not
take it before? It's only five dollars. Yeah. Take my money. Get over safely. Start a family
with Jex. Kevin Jex. Virgin Jerma. Chad Jex. Oh, fuck. From Green River Crossing,
it is 143 miles to Soda Spring. People are good. Health is good. I think we can turn it
to grueling. No, I'm not going to go hunting. I don't need it. I've got my money. Very little
water. What do you mean very little water? Yeah, drink from the spring. Oh, Otto sure got
big. I know who's been eating all the food. Now I know who's been stress eating.
This is Inspector Gadget. No, it's not. Gadget.
Everything is Inspector Gadget, apparently. Okay, we need to see if we can trade with somebody.
I got plenty of autos. Plenty of clothes. I might want to get some more food. Who wants
Okay, look, look, look, look. We don't need bullets. 418 bullets.
He will trade you one ox. Do we need any more oxes?
Five community subs just came in from Cole. Thank you, Cole RG for the five community subs.
What? Why? Hold on. Somebody just wrote, why do you have so much of everything? You casual
bank of fuck. What? Jesus. Because it said from Boston. I had to click it. If it said
that you're penniless from Boston, I would have clicked that one. All right. Are you
willing to trade? No, it's my money. All right, let's go. Let's go fast. Really fast. Go. 57
miles. Inadequate grass. Inadequate grass. Yes, I'd like to look around. Big boy. Ego. Thanks
for the five community subs. Five subs. Thanks for dropping in with five. Thank you.
Thank you, big boy. I think it's time to buy some I want to buy some more food.
No, I don't. Well, holy shit. This is a nice thing. No, look at that.
That's pretty cheap. Is it? All right. No more. I've got to save my money.
Because now I need to take ferries every time. Talk to people.
Fellow traveler tells you four voices. This one. No, this one. No, two.
This one. Three. I think four. Oh, which one? Hey. Fort. Fort Hall is a busy fort.
The wide stretches of meadow grass here are just what our tired animals need.
As for me, I'll fix up the wagon leaks. Amanda's real anxious to wash all the clothes
and linens in one of those clay streets. Five. I got five now. I got five voices now.
Uh, rest for two days. Go. Inadequate grass. Bad water. What does that mean?
Find wild fruit. Cool. There was just you just ate it. There was this grass right there.
Bad water. Bad water. Health poor. Impassable trail. Oh, what do you mean? Bad water.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm stopping here to rest. No one wants to trade with you today.
Okay, fine. Jeez. All right, we're gonna slow it down. Change pace.
We're gonna do steady. I'm also going to rest here for like three days. Three days. Health. Fair.
Okay. Continue. One of the oxen is injured. Okay, that's why I bought 15 of them. Bad water.
Bad water. Very little water. We're almost there. Just get there. Very little water.
We're at water now. Find wild fruit. Why did that just pop up? You are now at the
Snake River Crossing. Would you like to look around? Yep. June 20th, 1848. Okay. How are
we doing? Talk to people. A frantic wife tells you. Every, every time I do a, okay, every time
I do a female voice, they're always British. Why? It says right here. Then it says, I don't
know how to do a female voice. The only, Paula Dane is the only female I can do. That's
not it. No, female voice. That's not Paula Dane or like Keira Knightley. There's Elmo. Paula
Dane is Elmo. It says right here in the Shiver, Shively guidebook, you must hire an Indian to
pilot you at the crossing of the Snake River, it being dangerous if not perfectly understood.
But my husband insists on crossing without a guide. That's pretty good. Well, your husband's,
your husband's dumb. See you, see you when we get to cross, when we go across. I will take
a, you must cross the river in order to continue. The river is at this point is
currently a thousand feet across and six feet deep in the middle. Okay. Attempt to
forward the river, cock the wagon and floated across higher. We're going to hire somebody.
A guide says that he will take your wagon across the river for exchange for two sets
of clothing. Yes. Can I give you like five? Thank you. Let's go. Made it. You had no trouble
floating across the river. No, we didn't. Pogchamp. Pogchamp. Venuschamp. Jerma Venus
Pogchamp. Jerma Venus Pogchamp. Fogchamp. Let's go. We're almost there. I'm going to
get there. Otto has exhaustion. Go to sleep immediately. Five days. Metallix has a broken
leg from sleeping. Did you break your leg in bed? Ah, shit. I really twisted my ankle
to a point where I shattered my bones. And one of the oxygen has died. Inadequate
grass. It's okay. Metallix has got like gay for death. Yeah, you got to get up,
man and stretch. Be careful. A thief comes during the night and steals 36 pounds of food.
How? Broke a bone playing Fortnite. A thief comes. All right. Well, you got,
whatever. I got plenty of fucking food and money. I don't even know what happened.
I've got so many pounds of food. I just, I can't even count it. How do you count 900 pounds
of food? It's just huge in there and it's just whatever. What am I gonna have today?
Broccoli? Cheese? Meat? I don't know. It's just there. Tons of it. Let's look around.
That's Kim. Otto. And there's a baby, Jax Jr. Already had a kid. It didn't take you very long.
Didn't take that long. I mean, I've been died for, I've been died for like
up to a month. Wait a minute. Wait, is that, hold on. I've been dead for a month or two,
right? But the baby, that's a newborn. Takes nine months for, that's my, that's my son.
I didn't, I can't even see my own son. I'm gonna beat this even as a banker casual.
I've never seen the end of this game. No, that's Jax's kid. No. Buy supplies. How much money do I
have? I need food. I'm gonna buy whatever I can for food. How many pounds? 100 pounds of
food. Shit. 50 pounds of food. How much, wait, how much money do I have? Wait. No, I got 15
bucks. That's, that's three more ferries. Okay, we're good. Leave the store. Talk to people.
Aunt Rebecca tells you, at every fort along the trail, prices have been higher than at the
previous fort. This is outrageous, y'all. They're taking advantage of us. If I had the
chance to do it again, I'd buy more supplies and independence. And I'd put a little more
butter. I can only do, I can only do a fucking Paula Deen. That's it. I can't do anything else.
Do you need Paula Deen for your next project? I'm your guy. You need anything else? Just don't,
don't call me. Cowboy Elmo.
I thought this was a fucking bug. Reasons for camera to be on one, two, or three.
Hold on. Let me show you this. Okay, this is fine. Just look. I thought, I don't know why. I don't
know what the fuck is wrong with me. This is how you know that I'm fucking crazy. The shirt is
ripped, but it's okay. So I have one earphone in, right? I don't know how I moved. I don't
know how I moved a certain way, but this like came down and hit me in the chest. I don't,
I don't know how it happened. All I saw was this. I saw this like fall in front of my
face and hit me in the chest and I screamed. What's with this shirt? Because I put my,
look, when I was putting the shirt on, this shirt's like turning into cheesecloth because
it's so old and my mother drew it. So I like put my head on and I ripped through right here,
but I don't, I'm not getting rid of it. I'm not getting, this is, I love this shirt.
I accidentally ripped my hulk to my head through it. Fix it. No, I don't need to.
Just be lucky that I didn't even wear clothes today. This just happened. This didn't happen
like three months ago. This happened like four or five days ago. I already have my sewing kit
available. I just said, yeah, let me like take this t-shirt that I got, this old t-shirt.
Let me sew it together. Huh? But that's, I thought that was a scorpion. We got reports
that there's like scorpions now and I'm like fucking freaking out about it. I'm like,
wait, where are they? I've seen one already. Here we go. Uh, weather. Cool. So we're good.
I can't, no more supplies. We're going to continue on the trail from Fort Boise.
It is 160 miles to the Blue Mountains. Go, go. Very little water. I can't buy water. Where
do I get water? Health, poor. Health, poor. Oh, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Stop.
Rest for like three days. Still poor. You can't, I can't buy water. Are we going to have to
vampire somebody on the cruise ship here? Whose blood are we going to drink? We have to
vampire somebody. Uh, look at that. We're almost there. Just go. Come on. Get there.
One of the ox has died. It's okay. Come on. Got wild fruit. There's water right there.
There's water and fruit. Nice. Thank God for those random babies. You're now at
Blue Mountains. Would you like to look around? Water up on that mountain.
Let's talk. No, talk. Uh, Marnie Stewart tells you,
We followed the edge of the desert from Fort Boise to the forbidding wall of the Blue
Mountains. The hills were dreadful steep, locking both wheels. And coming down slow,
we got down safe. Poor animals. No grass or water for days.
Six voices. Going right for Boise. Head for Fort Walla or Fort, or head for the Dallas. Hold on.
The Dallas. That Dallas. Straight on. Straight on. 125 miles. Go. Heavy fog.
Should I just, should I just start sprinting? Yeah, we have to start sprinting.
Just go get to the finish line. You find an abandoned wagon with the following three
sets of clothing and 21 bullets. Thank you. Broken wagon axle. Would you like to try
to repair it? Yeah. You were able to repair the wagon axle. Thank you.
You find an abandoned wagon, but it is empty. Was it mine? Water right here.
You are now at the Dallas. Would you like to look around? Yes. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Let's have the conversation. We're at the Dallas. We're almost there.
Amy Witherspoon tells you,
Cousin Lydia engaged. Passage down the Columbia with
Indians a canoe with 17 people in luggage. The wind blew so heavy they had to lay by.
New dark high waves came up over their heads. Finally they made it to shore safely.
Seven. Well, four. I'm Hugh Bliss. That's what I was just doing. That's what I heard it.
Yeah, that's, that's what I've been hearing. We've heard a lot of Hugh Bliss talking.
Interesting. I wish I was between Derma's vocal bands. What? Why? What does that mean?
Seven voices. All right. We're almost there. Look at this. Oregon city. I'm going to sprint
as fast as possible. Change pace, grueling, change food rations, eat as much food as possible.
Eat, just, just stuff your face forever. Go. The trail divides here. You may float
down the Columbia River or take the Barlow toll road. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
Float down the river. Can I pay for it? Is it my money? Can we take them down?
Toll road is money. Toll road. That's five bucks. You must pay $12 to travel on the
Barlow Road. Are you willing to do this? Oh, thank God. Thank God. I'm still living.
You thought I died in the first five minutes. No, I'm still alive. 12 bucks. Let's go. From
the Dallas. It is a hundred miles to the Willamette Valley. Go as fast as you can.
Sprint. Heavy fog. Lose a day. Who cares? Impassable trail. Lose four days. Go.
Just sprint. Just go as fast as you can. Just no clip. You find an abandoned wagon.
Three sets of clothes. Excellent. I made it. Is this Oregon? Congratulations. You've made it
to Oregon. Let's see how many points you have received. Four people in fair health.
1600 points. One wagon. 14 ox. Nine spare parts. 23 sets of clothes. 1500 volts. 342
pounds of food. Free cash. 1800. 13 points. Let's go. So this is just a fake leaderboard.
It doesn't mean anything. Banker doesn't count. All right. Type your name. I beat the Oregon
Trail. Banker doesn't count. Banker doesn't count. Banker doesn't count. Banker doesn't
count. Count. You guys are fucked. All right. Here we go. Let's check. That's it. That's
that. I beat it. I did it. I win. Let's pick another one. That was fun. I never even
like played that game all the way through. I always just died in the first like 15 minutes
every time. All right. Let's go back to the list of games. Like this. Here we are. Remember,
if you want me to scroll, you click on the German face. Popsicle face. Because we are,
I mean, we just, we just did the Oregon Trail. That's it. I might not ever even see
past this page. All right. Here you go. Click. Let's determine. We want me to scroll. We've
got to click the face. Go for it. Okay. I should have done deluxe first. I didn't pick.
Oh my God. Oh, this is all fucked up. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. There we go. Now go
for it. There was like 20,000 clicks. People could just spam. Fucking Oregon Trail deluxe.
Just, we just did this. All right. This is closing in 10 seconds. Five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten. Oh, come on. Don't do this to me. Do I have to flip a coin?
It was, I guess we're going. We're scrolling. I have to flip. I have to
flip a coin. I have to. That's fair. That's the only fair way to do this.
I stopped it and it was tied. Let's flip a coin. I don't have any coins up here.
All right. We're going to flip the wine cork. Okay. If it lands on wine stain side, then
we're doing Oregon Trail deluxe. If it lands on clean cork side, we're doing a scroll.
Here we go. Ready? Wait, what am I? What is that going to do? No. Okay. Yeah. If this,
if it's pointing up, whatever one's pointing up. Okay. So ready? If, uh, what was it?
If the clean's pointing up, it's, we scroll. And if, okay, clean pointing up scroll.
I didn't want to play this. Another, I'm going to, okay. I didn't, I never said I had to play
it well. I'm going to try to die as fast as possible. I actually have a mouse this time.
Hey, you're about to, you're about to begin great adventure. Traveling the Oregon Trail
across the rugged landscape of North America. Your covered wagon pulled by a team of oxen
will travel from, why didn't we just do this one first? Uh, why didn't you? I don't know
because this is what you guys voted for. Uh, I'm going to be a doctor. No, a teacher.
We didn't though. What? This is what you guys clicked on. They clicked scroll. Well,
I closed the poll and like 15 seconds later it came through. I got to close it at some
point. Can't sit there forever. And I flipped the cork. No, not Junior. There you go. What?
Oh, there he is again. All right. Let's, uh, uh, do you have 400 bucks? That's it. 10, 6, um,
who cares about bullets? I'm not going to use them. And, uh, 800 pounds of food,
500 pounds of food. Let's go. Let's go. When do you set off? Uh, what's the worst month
to do it? August. This one looks so much better. I, oh, a song. Oh, a song. I don't care. Uh,
what was I doing? This is cool. Uh, okay. Status. Money. I'm a teacher. Map. Continue.
Talk. Trade. Pace. Ruling. Pace. Continue. You've reached the Kansas River Cross. We just
did. This is just a better graphical version. Talk. With crowds of people waiting to get on
the ferry, we should be, could be stranded here for days. Hope there's enough grace for
all those animals. Not many people carry feed at other weight though than cross a rickety.
Okay. We're going to afford it. We're good. We made it. You made it across,
but got stuck in the muddy river banks. That doesn't matter.
Kim was bitten by a snake in the water. It's been two more days. Kim is turning purple.
Yes. Oh, we got to go. I can't rest for like, I can't rest for like a hundred days.
Time out. What do you mean time out? You must cross the river.
Didn't I just cross the river? It's only one feet deep. I just did this.
Wait, somebody stole 15 bucks from the wagon? Who? You made it safely across. We're fine.
It's a different river. Oh, rest for a day. Here we go. We're going to get to,
have I beat both? Kim's died of...
Yeah, number 700 has dysentery. Of course they do.
All right. Time out. Time out. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Turn down the rations. Rest for a minute here. We can't have everybody just die. Three.
This is how I used to play it back when I was in middle school. I didn't understand.
Are they still eating food when I'm sitting here? Hey, what are you doing? What? What's
going on? Why isn't playing itself? You had a wagon wheel break. You're able to fix it.
You've reached the... I didn't do anything. That's not how living works. Health is poor.
Hold on. Rest. How many? Let me check my my shit here. Hold on. Rest for two days. Time out.
Don't just go. Status. Everyone's in poor health here. I only have 200 pounds of food?
I need to change this. That's okay. I need to trade. What do you want to get by trading?
I want pounds of food. Like a hundred pounds of food. Sorry, but nobody here's got a hundred
pounds of food to spare. Talk. Jimmy Rock by Moonlight is awfully sublime. Many Indians
came to our wagon with fish to exchange for clothing. We bought a number. They'd understand.
Okay. Okay, let's go. Hunt. I can hunt for food. You can't go hunting because
you don't have any bullets. Oh, I didn't buy any bullets because I didn't use them last time.
Oops. Dermot Jr. is suffering from exhaustion. The baby? No. Let's rest for like four days.
Rest. Rest. Rest. I still don't... I need food. Okay. Rest. How many days have gone by?
There we go. Timeout. That's what's the status now. Exhaustion. Poor. Poor. No bullets.
I only... Okay. I'm doing all right. He's 20 years old. He's 20 months old. Do hunting,
please. Otto has cholera. Okay. I need bullets. Buy. How much money do I have?
I have five dollars. Bullets. Okay. I can get a box. I can get one box of bullets,
which is 20 bullets. 20 bullets at the store. Hunt. Hunting is not allowed near the fort
because there are too many people around. Okay. What was that? I keep thinking that
somebody's breaking their legs. There's no grass for the oxen. Dermot Jr. got sick and died.
All right. Well, okay. Well, hunt. Who's still alive? Otto and who? There's no bullet?
There's no travel time? Pretty sick Sega Genesis sounds. How much meat? You shot
2800 pounds of food and used 20 bullets. You can only carry 200 food back. Well,
what's the point of shooting that many? All right. Everybody rest. We're going to rest for
a long time. Nine days. Didn't Otto die? No. No. All right. Everyone. People are recovering.
Okay. Let's do a strenuous pace. Rations. Let's go up to stay meager. Let's talk.
Goodbye. Flat river. Goodbye. Sand hills and white buffaloes. We already read this.
Well, we already saw that. We're almost halfway there. You found some wild fruit and
BIA 700 broke their arm pulling it out. Otto was bitten by a snake. He's dead. That's a
death sentence. How do you, how do I cure his snake bite? Can I get poison cure? He's just
dead. Otto died of a snake bite. BIA number 700 is the only one left. He broke his arm
picking berries. What? That was so fast. Oh, Otto died of a snake. Otto got bit by a snake.
Oh no. A few days later, Otto died of a snake bite. BIA 700 just got sick and died immediately.
We got to Independence Rock. Who's alive? Is it just the oxen? There's nobody alive.
There's nobody on the way. It's me. I'm still alive. I made it this whole time. All right.
Rest. Rest. All the food is mine. Nine days of rest. I'm taking this dead seriously now.
I only need to, I have 300 pounds of food. I can eat as much as I want too. This is great.
I'm going to make it. Yeah, I'm going to make it. All right. I'm, everything's fair.
I'm eating my fill. I'm just steak and mashed potatoes and green beans. It's perfect.
Got to South Pass. Can we hunt? No, I don't have any bullets. I need to try to buy.
You can only buy supplies at forts. What about trade? Bullets. I need like five. Nobody's got
five bullets to spare. I find that really hard to believe. Head to fort to buy supplies. Take
the shortcut to Green River. How much money do I have? I have two bucks. I can't buy anything.
All right. We're going to take the shortcut. The water. I'll get the water soon.
Come on. Go. The water is right here. Almost there. Yes. All right. Now I'm going to sit
down. I'm going to rest for a couple days. Resting. We're now at fair. 219 pounds of
food. River is 400 feet wide and 20 feet deep. I don't have enough money to get the ferry. I need
the ferry. Cock the wagon and float it. Yes. I did it. You thought I was going to crash.
No, I wasn't making a YouTube video this time. I'm getting all the way there.
No, wait. Stop, stop. No, no, no, no. Rest, rest, rest. Four days. Come on,
get over the cholera. Just eat more food. Have more chicken soup. No grass. What's this?
Soda springs. Okay. Let me trade. I need bullets. I just want, I only need five bullets.
Nobody's got five bullets spare. Okay. Anybody have one bullet to spare? I just need one. I
didn't need to shoot one thing. Sure. I'll trade you one bullet for one set of clothing.
Is that a deal? Oh, you fucking asshole. I was going to say, I can't like bum a cigarette
off somebody. One bullet if you didn't have it. Here we go. Hunt. Shot has to count.
No, it's going to be a buffalo. Don't shoot the rabbit. You're going to miss. No, don't shoot the
squirrel. I need a big animal like an, like a buffalo or an oxen. This will do. This will do.
What? Wait, hold on. That didn't connect? How did that miss? There's no way. That's unbelievable.
I'll trade you one bullet for one pound of food. Is it a deal? Yeah. Let's go. Fair. There
it is. Done. That's going to be like 200. 100 pounds of food. Thank you very much. Let's go.
Derm is well again. I'm doing just fine. Okay. Trade. Five bullets. No one has five in the
fort. No one has five. Everyone just has one. One bullet. Sorry. Nobody's got one bullet to
spare. It's a blizzard. Stop. All right. Just rest in the blizzard. Just wait it out. I'm
all right. I'm okay. I'm back to being poor. Fair. We're good. You lost the trail. That's okay.
I'm still doing fine. I'll pick it up again though. How many days is it going to take you
to do this? Three? Two days. Three days. Three days. Four days of losing the trail. Five. God.
Another fucking blizzard. Health is good. All right. Go. I'm almost there. I'm going
to do it. Oh, just you backer. You're so easy. What about on teacher? I only had like
$400. I'm going to make it. I will make it. I will persevere. I will get there. I have diarrhea.
Slow down. You can't die of diarrhea. I mean, you can actually, but it has to be a lot,
right? Okay. You've reached, you've reached the snake river crossing. That's such bullshit.
Where's the guy that bought 1500 bullets last game? He's not here. Okay. Uh, how
many, how much company? How many sets of clothing do I have? Yeah, I don't need all
these clothes. Let's go safely again. We make it safe again. I, I'm, I'm, I'm okay. Gruelling. Go.
Oh my God. He almost didn't make. I were, but you were able to replace it. Okay.
I keep thinking that's my neck. Derma is doing just fine. He's well again.
All right. Trade. One bullet. Can I just buy one bullet box of bullets? I can't just buy
one. Let's talk. Anybody. You'll not get your wagon over the blue mountains, Mr. Leave it. Cross
your goods over with a pack animals. Get yourself a couple of good mules, pieces of wagons,
litter the trail left by them. Folks who don't need good advice. Thank you. Appreciate it.
Trade for dollars. Um, 15 dollars. What do you want? What does anybody want?
15 bucks for one set of clothing. Absolutely. Let's go buy box of bullets and, um,
27 pounds of food. No, what am I doing? I don't need to do that. I can just shoot.
Why would I buy food? Whatever. I'm going to make it. I don't know why I did that.
Don't shoot the rabbits of both bullets. Waste of bullets. Move. Is it only rabbits?
I'm a bit panic shooting. All right. That's it. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Yeah, go type. No, I have typhoid fever. Just go sleep for nine days. You'll be fine.
That's how typhoid works. I'm fine. Just have to go to bed for a few days.
Everyone's Spider-Man goes to sleep for like five days and he thinks it's been like one
night and he gets his like powers. Remember that episode of the cartoon? All right.
All right. The home stretch. This lady's a white walker. Uh, okay. Let's, um,
I want to see the map. Here we are. That was like piercing blue eyes. I think I'm good. I
don't need to rest. I'm in good health. Let's go shortcut. I have a fever. Sleep for nine
days. Just go to bed for nine days. Works every time. Don't even do that. Are you telling
me that I can get typhoid fever and get better from typhoid in nine days, but I have
a fever and it won't. Okay. That was going to say. And only prescription is more cowbell.
Reference for those Saturday Night Live fans of you, of you out there. An ox wandered off.
It's all right. I have like 10 of them. Shut up. Broken neck. It's all right. I'm almost there.
An ox is sick. I made it. I did it. I just have to go through here. I got food. I, how
much money do I have? I have 35 cents. I don't have, it's $12. I can do it. I just have to
raft down the river. I don't have the money for the toll. Trade for cash for one ox. I have
six ox. Oh yeah. Toll road. $15. I'll see ya. I'm coming home. We're there. I did it. I made
it. I made it. I did the Oregon Trail. Did I die? I thought I died right here. I did it.
Germa lives. I just, yeah, I die in the next episode. Celebratory, celebratory dysentery.
Yeah. And I think that was a teacher. Less points than last time. Got the teacher bonus.
Pretty cool. All right. Let's, uh, thankfully that's, oh, there are no more Oregon Trails
on here. So I think we're fairly safe in getting out of this. Let me go here. All
right. So I don't know if we're ever going to get out of here. Click the Germa face
if you want to scroll. Remember. Remember. Let me get right, right here. Hold on. Let
me get this restarted. Okay. Oh, wow. A hundred percent. One hundred fucking percent. That's
a lot. Sorry, Wolfenstein. Doesn't look like it's going to be your day today.
A hundred percent is like basically everyone. Basically. Yeah. All right, guys. I think this
is just an absolute no contest. I'm going to scroll and scrolling means this whole page
goes down. So we are going to go all the way down here to here, as you see. Here we go again.
Ooh, we're indecisive this time. Leaning towards Batman returns. A lot of people want to
scroll too. I think it's going to be Batman. No, Doom the Roguelike. He's rigging it.
Doom the Roguelike. What is this even going to be? All right. That's it. We're going to play
Doom the Roguelike. Let's open it. I'm going to remove this now because it doesn't need to
be there anymore for the sake of right now. All right. Doom the Roguelike. All right. I guess
let's open it. Hold on. There we go. Major changes since Doom Roguelike. Let's see also.
Okay. Enter name. Choose a trait. Iron Man, finesse hell runner, tough as nails,
son of a bitch, son of a gun, reloader, eagle eye, cat eye, or brute. Pick banker. Hit points
by 10. Iron Man, finesse, hell runner, tough as nails, increases damage by, I like damage by
one. Firing time minus 20 percent, son of a gun. The trip was long. You thought it would
never end. Hell, a job as a Marine Reserve is so boring. You hate UAC. Nothing happens here.
Even now, you have to wait for your fellow Marines who are supposed to check what happened
on Phobos. Not knowing what to do with yourself, you just sit near the comm console and listen to
the news from your fellow Marines. Okay. Enter. Hell, what a bloodshed. You hear from the comm
everywhere. What happened here? Look, there's someone there. Oh no, God. Gunshot. This can't
be true. Help. I'm Jake. Is this how Doom starts? Is this the beginning of Doom? No.
Slurp. Well, alien. Welcome to the Doom Roguelike. Is that me? It's one of these.
It's actually like an old school text-based adventure. There's a small med pack lying here.
How do I pick it up? Unknown command. Oh shit. Getting stuck. Key bindings. Walk. Wait. Run.
Go downstairs. Pick up item from floor is G. Drop item. Open. Close door. Toggle. Look
boat. Fire equip weapon. Fire equip is F. You just tab to switch targets. So F and G
are what we need right now. F and G. No. What are we doing? Escape exits. Does it? I can't
get out. I can't get out of key bindings. I can't get out of here. Escape. No, it's not
backspace. It's escape. Well, hold on. Let me. What if I press escape again? There we go.
Okay. It can't be in full screen. All right. We're good. We're back. So it was F and G,
right? Picked up a small med pack. Small med pack. You see germa. Unhurt. You see floor.
Fire. Choose target. Fire a more constructive way to commit suicide. Wait, what? Oh, I tried
to shoot myself with a gun. Fire at the rock? Oh, fire. Okay, I see. Fire at the ground.
I only have five bullets. I'm just testing my gun. I think that's a door up there,
right? Okay, there's a door here. Press X to enable the music. There we go. Open the door. Boom.
Hey, whoa! The former human fires. You're hit. You're bleeding. What human? This H? Since when
did the Sesame Street letters stop fucking fighting each other? Okay, the former human.
Fire. The missile hits the former human. You lose blood. The former human misses you.
Fire. The missile hits the former human. The former human dies. Oh, god damn it. Okay,
what do you have? There's 10 millimeter ammo. Grab. A former human fires. Another former human.
Behind cover this time. Behind the door? The missile hits the former human. The former human
hits you. Fire. The missile hits the former human. The former human dies. Fire. The
former human. The former human. You hit the former human. The former human hits you.
You hit the former human. There is 10 millimeter ammo lying here. You hit the former
human. The former human misses you. Your weapon is empty. Grab the millimeter. You hit the
former. You miss the former human. The former human misses you. Your weapon is empty. How do
you reload? You reload the pistol. The former human misses you. Former human. The missile hits
the former human. The former human dies. Boom. A former human hits you. Choose target. A former
human. The missile hits the former human. The former human dies. Boom. The missile hits the
former human. The former human. You see a former human. Heavily wounded. The missile hits
the former human. The former human dies. All right, how do I use a med kit? There's a pistol.
Picked up the pistol. There's a pistol. Ammo. How do I use a med kit? You reload. The former
human sergeant. Sergeant misses you. The missile hits the former human sergeant. The
former human sergeant misses you. The former human fires. You are more. How do I keep going?
More. Former human sergeant wounded. The former. The missile hits the former human. The
former human sergeant misses you. There's 10 millimeter ammo here. The former human sergeant.
The missile hits the former human sergeant. The former human sergeant dies. The former
human fires. Boom. The missile hits the former human. The former human uses a small med
pack. The former human looks healthier. The missile hits the former human. A former
human almost dead. The missile hits the floor. Human. The former human dies.
Reload. All right. Med kit. I need to use. How do I use a med pack? Health. There's a
shotgun. I'll take it. I want to equip the shotgun. Prepare the shotgun. Is it I? Small
med pack. E. Did not. Son of a gun. Wait. Back it up. No items. I. F. I don't know why
that's not working. I. U. For use? To where will press the desired item letter? The F.
That doesn't use it. How do I get out of here? I cleared this whole area. What is
going to go down? Is there a staircase or something? It's the down arrow.
It's the V. How do I go downstairs? I'm going to check the keybindings. C. Run on. Okay.
Go downstairs. So it's actually that. You won't be able to come back. Drop item. Show
inventory. Toggle look mode. Fire weapon reload. Special reload. Use item from
inventory is U. U? But I can't. That's weird. So I have to do. Let me go U. Ah.
All right. Okay. Let's go. I did it. You shiver from cold. What is the I? The imp
fire is boom. The imp misses you. There's a shotgun lying here. Shotgun. F. You shot
the barrel. The imp dies. The imp dies. Nice. Okay. I did it. The form of human
fire as you were hit. I have. Hold on. I don't have any more shotgun ammo. You
prepare the pistol. The form of human fire as you're hit. Form of human. The
missile hits the form of human. The form of human fire as you're hit. You're
bleeding. The missile hits the form of human. You use blood. Choose target. The
missile hits the form of human. The form of human dies. You lose blood.
Weapon is empty. Reload. The pistol is already loaded. Am I still bleeding? The
form of human sergeant reloads his shotgun. Get me out. What did I just do? What just
exploded? The form of human sergeant fires as you die. He was reloading. I was trying
to get in the room. I didn't level up. Yes I did. Level two on the bottom right. I
leveled up. I leveled up. Map level two. I know it's the map. That was actually
pretty cool. I didn't hate that. That was fun and interesting. All right. You
know what time it is. Click the face if you want to scroll or click
something else. Go for it. There's a version with graphics and sounds. All
right. We got a little bit of a fight here between Batman Returns and
Scroll please. 31 31. Don't make me have to flip the cork again. Dwarf Fortress.
All right. Don't let the fucking scrollers win. Um anyone that's going to
click on the screen has already done it. I think that's it. Five four three
two one. That's it. Batman Returns. Thank you for voting. Batman Returns. Let's
open it. Bitcoin miner. I've played this game before. This game sucks.
I appreciate the fact that they made this in Mario Paint. All right. Anything
else? Did I beat the game? It's just the song. It's just the song. That's
it. All right. Next. That was fun. Game over. Guys enter doesn't do
anything. I beat the game. We just had to hear the Mario Paint soundtrack.
Game over.
There's no way it's the before credits. I'm pressing enter x w q
Chevrolet. Oh the after credit scene. Are you fucking kidding me? It's a
point and click adventure game. Main computer. Oh my god you are slow as
shit. Batman. Batman doing a great impression of I'm pretending to work
at the office. All right. What? News broadcast. Evidence. Why is he dressed
like Batman right now? You don't have to be dressed like Batman.
This just in from Gotham Plaza. A gang of hooligans dressed as circus
performers have attacked the crowd gathered to watch the annual tree
lighting. Our communication lines in the area have been disrupted but as
told the violence is is the city council released a report today
predicting that the Gotham City will suffer a record deficit in this
year's budget. Revenues are far below projections and high expenses are
higher than expected. The slumping economy bears most of the blame
according to the computer guy. What the control the crime is up. The
temperatures are down and so are Gotham City's SAT scores according to the
board of education. The average Gotham student score dropped by 25 points.
No explanation was given for the sharp decline in scores. The arctic
weather which has left Gotham City numb depressed and weary. A bunch of
shows no signs of letting up according to the US weather bureau
forecast. Life sucks right now. Temperatures will remain below freezing
for at least a week with more snow a possibility. The long range forecast
calls for below normal temperatures for the rest of the winter.
Why is this the music we're playing on this broadcast? I have no idea. It's
scary horror music. Unemployment continues to climb in Gotham City
reaching a record high last month. Everything in the world sucks
according to a report from the human resource commission. The trend
shows no sign of reversing. By the way a computerized forecast
predict a controlled climb as the city loses an estimated
thousand jobs each month. This just in from Gotham Plaza.
In breaking news a gang of hooligans dressed as circus performers have attacked
more people. Oh my god that was a lot. Evidence.
What's in the evidence folder? Uh enter. No evidence to enter. How do
you get evidence? Extrapolate. No evidence. Uh video.
Select video. There are no videos. All right let's get out of here.
Get up from your fucking gamer chair Batman. Let's go.
Now where? Uh I can go this way. Wayne Manor.
The vault of the garage. Garage. Now he runs. All right jump.
What? But you watch TV. You're going to watch TV while you're driving.
The city council released a report today predicting that Gotham City will
suffer a record deficit in this year's budget.
Revenues are far below projections. You don't.
Why would you watch TV while you're driving?
Two TVs. He's playing like Clash of Clans over here with his iPad.
Batman injects from the Batmobile and he soars through the air.
Oh the driverless Batmobile carries through the streets.
Hitting people and...
Why? Why can you ghost ride the Batmobile
into people and into and explode it and shit?
Oh they just didn't give a fuck.
Oh that's the best game I've like ever played.
I gotta see. We can't just leave right now.
No. New game. I'm sorry that can't be how it ends.
Let's check the vault. I want to see what's in here. How many batsuits does
he have? Suit two defensive capability.
Put on suit three? They're all the same thing.
Why does he have a Peter Griffin closet of the same outfit?
Utility belt computer. Grapple. Gauntlet. Rope. Knockout gas.
Knockout gas. Rope. Smoke bomb.
And a bolo batarang? How many can I take?
Oh I can take like everything. All right.
I'm decked out. So now let me just... Let's go to Wayne
Manor. Have you completed everything you want
to do on this day? No. Why is this like...
We're gonna... Okay go back into the Batmobile.
Two scanners. One for each hand. Yeah. What is this thing?
Gotham Plaza mayor's office. Let's go downtown.
What's going on downtown? Street. Time. It's 6 47 pm. Street.
What is that? Is it a bird? Jewelry. Is it a robbery? What am I doing?
Roof? Am I gonna steal from the jewelry store?
He's looking through. I'm walking a tightrope. Doesn't Batman have
gadgets? What's the point of doing this?
He's just a cosplayer. This is not even real Batman.
All right. I don't think I can do anything here. What?
Why didn't you just do that over here? I don't even know where I am.
I can't go this way. The only thing I can do is go back. I guess I could go
to the street level from over here. Okay down to the street. Okay.
Liquor sale. 50% off. Nobody here. All right. Back to the
Batmobile. There's nobody here. Gotham Plaza. Oh my god. There's a bunch
of people here. Shrek's. All right. Let's go around.
It's not a yo-yo Batman. All right. Down to the street. What's going on?
What the fuck is going on? How do I fight?
I can't move the mouse up here. I can't fight this guy.
It's just easy. Normal. Fierce. Fierce. Yes, I want to interrogate.
Category of the question. Batman is high as fuck right now. Now I get it.
A leader. Tell me who you're working for.
A real fish lover, that's for sure. Try one.
What? Another fight.
I don't know what any of these do. Smoke bomb.
I'd stomp. Is there any more?
This music's gonna kill me. What time is it? It's 7 50 p.m.
Did I kill these people? Go up. Wrap back around.
Oh my god. No one's here. It's a fish for sure, right? What is it?
Clue? Oh, here we go. Satan? He's dead. I
killed him. These are all lethal somehow. I think
I cleared them. Back to the Bat
mobile. I got some intel. What about the news?
Hey, let me take my eyes off the road. The riot which broke out in the
plaza several hours ago has now spread to the downtown area.
Costumed monitors are terrorizing citizens and wrecking property throughout
downtown. Police seem unable to quell disturbances.
The city council released a report today predicting that Gotham City will
suffer a record deficit in this year's budget.
In case you forgot, revenues are fucked.
No one's making any money. Jobs are gone. Okay, downtown.
I don't have any more equipment left. Yeah, I do.
Just, just punch him. Punch him in the face. Fierce.
I keep killing them. I need to interrogate them, so just knock them out.
Come on, Batman. This person's not even attacking. Just punch them.
Just punch, just punch her in the face. Just punch them in the face.
Oh, I guess so. Oops. Use the bat gun. No, I don't want to hurt. I want to
interrogate somebody. No, they're gone. There's nobody here.
All right, get me out of here. I need more news.
Crime is up, the temperatures are down, and so Gotham City's SAT scores. This
guy just can't get over that. I'm not going to eject. All right, how
do I get back to, like, I gotta go back to Wayne Manor.
Bat cave. Mayor's office? What's on here?
Evidence? Nothing. Oh, there ain't nothing here.
Go back to, just go back to Wayne Manor and end the day. Get back in
your car. Yeah, just broke into the Mayor's
house. All right, back to Wayne Manor. Let's end the day.
Does he ever take off the suit? Wait, evidence, right?
I learned about the fish. Okay, evidence.
Evidence. Enter evidence. Frozen fish. Collected evidence. Entered.
Okay, a few frozen fish. Species Simonus frigidus,
native to the icy waters off the coast of Antarctica.
Okay, extrapolate. Not eaten by people used primarily as food for arctic avian
species such as penguins. Only known for
very obvious fish in Gotham City is Tony's fish market. Evidence.
All right, go to bed. All right, Wayne Manor, end the day.
A new day begins day two. Let's go. We've got the evidence we need.
I'm gonna go to the fish market. Fish market.
Interrogate. There he is. Batman, what can I do for you?
I understand that you sell fish called Simonus frigidus.
Yeah, what about him? Sold any recently?
A couple of days ago. I sent a crate load over in the old zoo about once a week.
Zoo. Thanks for your help. Zoo sounds...
Sorry, I'm so fucking high right now. Zoo? Did you say zoo? Old Gotham Zoo.
Arctic world. Well, what else is over here?
Oh, a videotape. Take it. Take the tape.
We have some evidence now. Oh, what's this? Circus poster. Take it.
All right. Oh wait, we're gonna fight a clown. Normal.
I don't care if this guy dies. Just kill him. Just batarang him in the head.
Try something else. Anything else will do.
Anything will do. Both of you. I think we froze to death down here.
Would you like to interrogate? Yes. Location.
Where can I find your boss? He'll be visiting the bank tonight making a withdrawal.
Okay. I'll be sure to stop him.
Bank. Where's the bank? Where's the bank? Mayor's office downtown.
Gotham Plaza. Fish market. Where's the bank? Is the bank on this side or the other side?
Jewelry. Do the music louder or am I fucking insane?
You might not be insane. I think it just hurts to listen to this or it just
feels like it's getting louder. Bank. 750... Am I early? I'm too early.
759. Is this real time? 801. Is it eight? What time did they do this?
I can skip time? How do you do that?
Advance. An hour. Two hours. Return to game.
All right. Are they here? Let's go. It's 10... 11 o'clock.
Here we go. It's the penguin. He's a cunt. Quick throw a batarang in his eye.
He blocked it. Fierce. Get in there. Get in there and stop punching.
Why is the penguin this good at fighting? The penguin's not supposed to be this good.
Fierce. Get in there, Batman. Take him out. All right. A couple more of those.
Why is he here by himself walking in the front door?
Don't you think you would do something differently here in Justice 3?
All right. Please don't lose this. How many punches in the face is the penguin gonna take?
End this. Don't let him get the best of you. If the penguin can beat Batman in a one-on-one
combat scenario, it might be time to retire. There you go. Get in.
Is Fierce the... Okay. His top henchmen. Here come the clowns. Why can I do this so well?
I just... I did a backflip off of his face. I'm doing like weird karate mortal combat
moves and shit now. I was afraid... Look at these moves. Why was I not doing these before?
Oh, would you like to interrogate? Yes. I want the location.
I want your boss. Where is he? Where is he?
I don't know, but he'll be making a withdrawal later tonight at the bank.
Later tonight? At the bank? Okay. Where is he? What time is it? 1130? Okay.
Uh-oh. Mirror match. I chose...
That was a backflip. I punched you so hard you did a full backflip.
This is an old lady. This is clearly a grandma. Just push her over. Push her. Just shove.
What's this? What's going on? Why is this blinking red? Why is my stone blinking?
What does this mean? Is this a bomb? No. I don't know what that means. I have to wait at the bank.
What time is it? It's 1150. He's going to make a withdrawal. I just have to hold on.
All right. Wait an hour. Okay. Here comes the withdrawal. Here we go. Here he comes.
I came back. I forgot. I was going to deposit a few checks too, Batman.
Bruce, you might want to do something here. Bruce, get in there. Easy. Should I put it on easy?
No, this is too defensive. Get in there. Normal. You are so bad. Fierce. At least you were
landing shots. How many times do I have to hit him? I think I have to put... Okay. I know
what I have to do. I got to put it on easy when he attacks because that means I block
and then go back to fierce. What a bullshit strategy that's working. It's not fair.
Look at that reach. Batman, do something. Anything would be... I would take anything at
this point. I'm just relying on dodge rolls. Get in there. Finally. Punch. Oh my god.
Where is he? Oh, he's going to be making a deposit later tonight.
It's fucking 12 30. Batman's going on no sleep. No, they're gone. All right. Back to the... I
gotta watch the videotape. Put the tape in. Let's see what it is. Remember that time when
Batman fought the penguin for three hours outside of a bank twice? Okay. Video. Select
video. No, do I have to administer evidence? Okay. Enter evidence. Red triangle circus
poster videotape from zoo. Collected evidence. Entered. Video from the zoo. Play. My god.
The penguin man of the sewers. What? Shut up Max. You know you and I have a lot in common.
We do? Of course. We both crave respect and power. You can never have too much power.
You're right. I've been hiding in the sewers for too long. It's time for me to ascend.
And I want your help. I think I can work out a welcome home scenario that will benefit both of us.
Transmit to the police. Wait, who am I transmitting to? Am I putting this on TV?
Did I just pump into every cable box? Quick, put it on the air. It'll embarrass them. I guess
I'm transmitting this. Yeah, why were they recording this? Why would you re record your
damning conversation? Yeah, they're standing very okay. I did it. I transmitted it. Apparently.
We've got big bits coming in. Cure. Cure, thank you for the $55. Cure. 55 bucks.
Huge money drop right here. Cure says, hey, I love it when you play shitty old games. Brings
me back. You're me and my brother's favorite person on the internet. I've been watching
you for a long time and it seems like you just keep getting funnier. Keep being you. As long
as you having fun. We always are right there with you laughing our asses off.
Thanks for the years of free laughs. Here's me giving back a little. Thank you so much.
That means a fucking lot. Thank you. It's my pleasure. And yes, I do have a lot of fun
when we play these games. Thank you so much Cure. Say hello to your brother for me too.
So, and that Batman music just like blasting in the background.
All right, I get this is gonna drive you crazy. Um, videotaping is one of the two
principals apparently likes to keep a video record of his meetings. They have formed
an alliance and appear ready to use devious means to gain power. When he videotapes
every meeting, I would not be okay with that. There are many rumors linking the red triangle
circus to criminal activity. It's likely that at least some of the members turn to crime
full-time with the circus characters involved in the ride of the plaza.
Let's see what's on the news today. Another La Crona just gave 50 dollars.
Oswald Cobblepot foiled a kidnap attempt on the mayor. Little is known about Cobblepot's
background. He appears to suffer from a congenital deformity that gives him a very
penguin-like appearance. The arctic weather which has left Gothamites numb, depressed,
and weary. What? Now we're going in this loop again. Uh, La Crona says eject. 50 dollars.
Thank you. Back-to-back 50 bucks. Thank you, both of you. Uh, okay. Let's- I'm not gonna eject.
I'm gonna go to the vault. I could- I have to replace my bat suit. This one's broken.
See, look. Ready? 100 percent, 100 percent, right? 70- Offensive capability zero. What do
you mean zero? Is this suit made out of concrete? I don't get it. Wait, there's a
link that I need to look at? You went too hard. Hold on. Wait, a link I need to look at. Wait,
wait, wait. What's the link? You even put my nose bump in that photo- in the image.
That's the best part about that. All right, here we go. We need to go to sleep. I'm
gonna give this game like another 15 minutes. I don't know how much more of this I can take.
Okay, and we have the mayor's house. Gotham Plaza mayor's office.
We're gonna go to the mayor's office. What time is it? 6 p.m. He's not here. Just wait here.
Oh, hold on. Party pictures. Scan. Scan them. Scan. Just take them. All right, I got some
evidence here. All right, get me the fuck out of this. I don't want to look at his desk
anymore. Okay, pictures. What's in the pictures? Does he take photos of himself, too? Is it weird
that I want to do this again on the next stream? I feel like we're just touching the ice break
here. Evidence. Oh, maybe like do it next weekend, too? Okay, uh, enter. Photos of
the mayor's son. A pack of photos of the mayor's son's birthday party. No useful extrapolation
can be made at this time. I think, I think we've, I don't know what to do.
I don't know what else to do. Watch the news. Unemployment. No, we already know about the
unemployment. No, not the SATs again. What the hell is there a reason for the eject button?
There is no reason for the eject button. It doesn't, it just explodes the car. All right,
last day. Make it count. Gotham Zoo. Batcave. Mayor's office. Downtown.
Fish market. Let's go downtown. Nobody here. Steal something. I can't. I'm Batman. Batman
doesn't steal. What about over here? We saw a light just turn off there. Down to the street.
If there's nothing here, then we're going to move on. I don't think this, I think,
I think we're stuck. We have to do something specific. Yeah, I think that's it. I think
that's it. It was fun. One more try. I'm going to go to the fish market.
They closed. Ah, damn it. What time is it? 8 58. They close at nine. Bullshit. God,
I drove all the way out here. Fuck it. Well, that's it for that one. Well, thank you,
Batman Returns for the, probably the hardest I've laughed in two or three weeks at least.
That was a classic. I am going to go pee. I'll be right back. Hello. So, yeah, I think
uh, what do you guys think? This is what I think. It's uh, 4,400 games. That's uh,
I feel like we could make this like a Saturday night thing. You know what I'm saying? At least
for like a couple weeks. Just do I have to have this be just something fun to do like
Saturday night? Just to check out some old DOS games, you know, whatever. On top of other
streams, right? Because this, this is four this week. So I don't see why I wouldn't do this
again. This is fucking, no, I'm having, this is a lot of fun. Maybe not permanently,
but at least for like the next maybe two or three weeks. Try it. But uh, speaking of stuff,
I, here we go. We were, uh, we did not choose to scroll. We were right here.
The last one was Batman, right? We didn't choose to scroll. Was it here or was it,
it was here, right? Uh, let's keep going. Probably gonna drop a lot of frames.
Another reason why I started an hour or two early, because I'm trying to beat the internet problems
that start at like five to six, seven o'clock. So at this point, we're probably going to start
dropping frames. Apologize in advance, but let me get the thing here. If you want to scroll
down another set of pages. Here we go. Are you ready? Click the screen. Don't use the image.
I'll, I'll make it something else after this. Just so people like, oh, I'm going to click the face,
right? I see what you're saying. Here, while you guys do that, I'll do this.
This means scroll. So, uh, what are we doing here? I think we're scrolling. I think we're
doing a scroll. We are. Stop it for now. We're doing one full scroll to here, which
gives us this new set. And let's wait, wait, wait, rigged, rigged, what time? Wait, what
happened? Rigged. What are you talking about? Was it, it was 30, like three percent, right?
Hold on. Did I, did I fuck that up? 70% was not voting. Reset the vote. Okay. No, no,
you're right. Okay. Okay. All right. I see what you're saying. I see what you're saying. No,
I see what you're saying. You're right. No, you're right. You're right. You're right.
Because I, there are people that may have just clicked the face. Well, if there was
ever any indication of what people wanted, I think we've got a clear indicator now.
I don't think this is one guy. I think this might be, uh, 58% of all one guys in the chat.
58% of guys. All right. That's very clear. Let's go again here. All right. By the way,
this is off. I'm not doing this one. X. X that one. I'm not doing that one either.
Not doing, not doing that one. Good thing I caught that. No way. Not playing soft porn,
too. You're wasting your vote right now. We must know. And my channel, if you understand,
I can't stream porn on Twitch. I don't know if you've ever read the terms of service,
but porno porn is not streamable. Uh, even if it is probably like two bits that are,
it's just text. You think I can roll those dice? I don't know what that is. It could be
like a good flashing image of like something crazy. No, I ain't clicking that. I'm not clicking on
porn. Now you got, I'm telling, that's it. Monopoly Deluxe is the winner. No, no, no, no.
Sorry. Sorry. Sim Ant. I already played Sim Ant. No, Veto, two Vetos. I played Sim Ant like
three weeks ago. No, I played Sim Ant like a year ago. You want me to play Sim Ant again?
All right. All right. Well, I'll put up Sim Ant. That's the one. I'm not clicking the porn one.
Three weeks is a year. No porn. All it takes is for one thing to flash on that screen.
And bingo. I'll see you guys in two weeks because I get terms of service banned.
Sim Ant. We're not going to report you. All right. Sim Ant. This copy of Sim Ant is
registered to Robert. I don't know who that is. That's not me. Stolen.
I don't know how to play tutorial. Welcome to the Sim Ant tutorial. Just follow the on-screen
instructions and you will learn how to play the game. All right. In Sim Ant, you are the
yellow ant that you see in the window before you. First, you will learn to control your ant.
Try double clicking somewhere in the brown dirt near the yellow ant.
Is that the queen? Good. You've just learned how to dig a tunnel. Try digging some more to get the
hang of it. What's wrong? What are you doing? Now go outside and explore the surface. Double
click on the blue area at the top of the window to dig a tunnel to the surface.
Oh, shit. Okay. Now you're outside. This is called the surface view. You can die up here.
To move in the surface, just click on the ground and you'll move. All right. Yeah, I can
move around. When do we get raid? Hey. Hey, easy. That's right. Now click on your ant to
re-send to the window. Just go off on an adventure. Good. Now here's another way to scroll the screen.
Move the mouse cursor to the far edge of the screen. Yep. Yep. Yep. Oh, boy. Now it's about
time to find some food for your colony. Under the window menu, select MAP. The window is a
view of the whole patch. The green dots in this window are food. The yellow dot is your
ant. You may see other things moving too. Eject. Get a bearing on which way the food
is located in the patch. Then select edit under the window menu to bring up the close-up
view of the surface again. All right. So I gotta go right. They're gonna go this way. There it is.
Try to get some of the food.
All right. I got the food. Very good. You made it. You are probably hungry by now,
so double click on a piece of food. That tasted good, didn't it? Now you feel like a new ant.
Now it's time to bring a piece of food back to your colony. Double click on another
piece of food. Pick it up. Would you guys just let me get through the damn tutorial?
What? Like, let me just at least do that. This is what was voted on. You have to give it at least
a few minutes. We can't just be like, I want you to play SimAnt. Get out of SimAnt quick.
You put me to sleep. All right. So I have a piece of food. We voted for soft porn. Yeah.
All right. You know, that's true. You're right. You wanted soft porn too. I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna turn the screen off and I'm gonna see what it is. What was that? Now pick up
the food. Wait, watch out. He's coming after me. He's coming after me. He's chasing me.
Hit the food up. All right. I need a map. Where's the colony? I don't remember what my
colony is. It's up here. Colony. Found it. Good. Try to get back to your nest. It should
be somewhere to the left. Yeah, it's right here. All right. I got food. Food. This is
food for you. Double click the tunnel to drop the food. Try a few more things. Just hold
on. I'm interested in it for a second. You're gonna get your porn game in a few minutes.
Hold on. Look for a small rock that looks like this. This is cool. Build crude walls
for defense. A shitload of them just showed up. Click and hold on your ant and select recruit
10 from the pop-up menu. Recruit 10. I got. Oh yeah. You thought this was gonna be boring?
Take a look at this. I got an army now. We're gonna go fight the red ants. Where's
their colony? Tap the zero key. No. I want to see where they are. There they are. Let's go.
Let's fuck them up. Let's get in there. Just get the queen immediately.
In. Invade. Invade. I'll find another. You have been reborn and the stream continues.
All right. Sim ant. Sim ant. Sim ant. Never gonna stop playing this. This drops a cent.
Sim ant. Sim ant. Sim ant. Never going to stop streaming. Sim ant. Engage. Engage. Exchange
bodies. Now you're in. You control any black ant with this command. Okay. What's this thing?
Can we kill this thing? All right. Back to the map. Okay. You got one more minute here
for me just to check it out. This game's cool. You guys don't like this game?
Where you are in the world of Sim Ant. Click on the yard icon. Oh shit. This is somebody's
yard. You can only transfer to a new patch in a full game. This plans for zombies. We're
going to invade the house. The screen is where you will reproduce and spread new
colonies across the yard. Just watch out for the lawnmower. Now click on the bottom labeled
house. Can we infest the house? Guys, we can infest the house. You're objectively to invade
and take over the inside of this house. You don't. Okay. That's pretty cool. Okay. B. Behavior
control. Dig. One minute. It's got like 30 seconds left. This is really cool. I highly recommend
Sim Ant. This is fun. This is actually pretty cool. Now let's play porn. Oh, they're coming
to steal our food. Wait a minute. I can't stand for this. Look, they're taking all
of our food. Get over here. How do I? Oh, I get this is my last thing I'm doing. No,
I don't. Hold on. Wait. Recruit 10. Get over here. More. Recruit 10. There's only one
here. They're taking all of our food. Get over there. There we go. All right. Charge
in. Let's go. Get them. Scare them off. Come on. All of you. Somebody fight this guy
so I don't. I've been reborn. The counter resets. No, this is all right. This is
fun. I like it. Next. That's fun. The red ants are too powerful. It's okay. Get
that off screen. This is fun. This is cool. I recommend it. Go play it and tell me how
it is. I'm going to click the porn game now. I'm going to turn the audio off. I need
to. I'm just going to see what this is. Okay. I'm clicking on soft porn 2. I'm
opening soft porn 2. Okay. Hit any key. This program contains explicit material
that may be found offensive. Are you over 18? Do you wish to continue? Do you
need instructions? I can't show this. There's a whole list of commands. Just
say what's on screen. Well, the program collects relevant information regarding
you and your partner. You direct the action by giving commands such as
something. Have her something something. Have her something my wand. Don't get
discouraged if you wipe out on the first couple tries. This is much more
complex and much more difficult than soft porn 1. There are 22 different
endings and only one is the real winner. All right. How about this? I will show
you guys the TV edit of this game. Okay. Here comes the TV edit and hold on.
Vilemi gave $53. Forget soft porn 2. Give us Jazz Jackrabbit. Thank you for
the 53 bucks. We're going to do the made for TV soft porn 2. Okay. What is
your name in this story? I'm not using my real name. Dave. Yes. Um, I
don't know. Uh, Cindy. Carol. Carol. What color is Carol's hair? Um, I don't
know. Uh, bra bra brown. Brown. The color of Carol's eyes. Uh, red. What
is Carol's? Um, I don't know. I don't see what. Um, I don't I don't I don't
know. Seven, eight, 19. I don't know what that means. 19. Uh, one. I don't
know. I, why do they want, am I tailoring a suit for this person? I
don't. Um, 32. If you want a freak show, go to the circus. Well, one.
What is Carol's hair? I don't know. Eight, six, five, four. What is this?
What is Carol? 19 waist measurement. Six hip measurement. Six. I don't know
measurements. I don't know. I don't know what it is. I know I'm a 32. What
is Carol's bust measurement? I don't know. I've never measured a bust
before. 40. What is Carol's waist? I don't know. Girls have different.
It's different. Like a six, right? It's like zero to six.
Kim. Is Carol creative? Uh, sure. Is Carol domineering? I don't know what
that means. No. Is she discreet? Yes. Is she expressive? Yes. Are you
expressive? Yes. Is Carol intuitive? Yes. Are you talkative? Yes. Are you
easily aroused? Ah! No. Yes. No. Is Cal, I don't know. No. Is
Cal proud for breasts? Uh, yes. Are you...
All right. All right. That's the end of that one.
What the fuck does this mean? That's all I can handle at the moment. If
something comes up, ha ha, I'll be in touch. Ha ha. What does that mean? I
can't. Okay. I'm going to read this because I don't want it on the
screen because I'm going to replace words.
Uh, there's, there's no doubt about it. You are, uh, you're dominated
by a sense of want and lust. Uh, you, you, uh, as you pace the
streets of Hoboken. Hoboken? Sir, you deeply, almost, you're almost
unbearable horniness. I'm done. There's so much here that I can't
read. It's infidelity here. She has a husband. All right. Where
should we go? Carol asks. The circus. That doesn't sound quite
right to me, Dave. Where should we go? Uh, I think, I think we
should bed. I think we bar. Bar. That doesn't sound quite
right to me, Dave. Where should we go? Applebee's. That doesn't
sound right to me, Dave. Bed. Um, train.
Carol becomes bored by your inability to handle the situation
and leaves. You will never see her again, but sometimes she
sends a Christmas card. You really blew it, Dave. I said,
let's go to the bar. Let's go to the Applebee's. Let's go
to the club. Let's go to bed. What? How many more
things? What? Should I say bowling? I, wait, I can do it.
We don't go. Oh, she left. She left. Oh, but there was soft
porn too. You got it. It was a lot of fucked up shit. I
couldn't read. You got your, got it. There it is. There's
your made for TV version. Let us go back. Shall we? All
right. So that was here, right? Uh, that's correct,
right? We didn't move on from here. All right. Ladies and
gentlemen, if you could do me a favor and put your mouse
over the screen in a certain place. The red arrow
means you want to scroll down another page. Good luck.
Hmm. Interesting. Interesting selection. Uh, question for
the audience here. Do I have to play a full round of
Monopoly? Why would you want me to do that? Is that you
want me to? Okay, hold on. A third of you guys want me
to play a full round of Monopoly like a 25 year old
version by myself versus the computer. That can't be
right. I just, that can't be right. I don't think that
can't, that can't be right. That is correct. Yes.
Democracy sucks. What do you, what do you mean
straw poll? There's a interactable straw poll on the
screen right now. Straw, I just did it. Okay, do a
straw poll. The people have spoken, guys. I could
veto it, but I'm toying with the idea. I don't
understand chat sometimes. I don't understand this
chat sometimes. No one would actually stay and
continue talking if a full thing of Monopoly was
played. You'll get up and leave. You'll get up and
leave it on in the background, which means you
aren't fucking watching. If you're here to watch
someone play a game, pick a game, sit down, shut up
and watch him play. 65% don't want Monopoly. Yeah,
but look at all the other, look at, you're evenly
spread out a bunch of other games. How about this? I
will at least get, I'll at least go to jail in
Monopoly. You know what I mean? And we'll get that.
Don't you be coming back here now. It has
commenced. Monopoly. Okay. If I gave 15 minutes to
SimAnt, I will give 10 to Monopoly. There's
going to be like a five round Monopoly. They
always do it like this. Watch. I can pick the
amount of rounds, right? Well, this isn't Mario
Party. What? This one always works. All right,
let's go. How do I play? Monopoly. Go. New
game. All right. Player setup. I'm going to be
the guy in the green car. This is a human. XT
clone. 386 30. Okay. Why? Why can I play
against a microwave? Human, a calculator, a
computer or a microwave? Okay. Take 500. This
is going to be the calculator. Give. What
does this mean? Take five. What does this
mean? Zoom out. Oh, fuck. What does this
take 500? Give dice. I don't remember this
being part of the rules. Do I just drag
him out? Give. I'm human. Player setup. How
do I add the player? Zoom back in. No.
What? This is, what do you mean this is
too advanced? Does anybody else figure
this out? What's it? Whoa, what's doing?
He's coming out of the fucking ground.
What? Why is it the ghost Monopoly man?
How do I do that? I just want to add
the player. No sound. You rolled and now
you can move. Three. What? Anybody know
what's going on? Why do I get to roll
again? Four. The distinctive design of the
game board is whether it's each of the
distinctive pieces and elements of the
board. The pieces in the board
Monopoly are trademarks of Parker
Brothers Division of Tonka Corporation
for its real estate trading game and
the game equipment. I don't want to see
any more. All right. Now we just have
the credits just popping up on the
screen forever. Now what? Wait. I think
it is out of them. Human? Just make
them all. Who cares? We're going to
bet. I got it. I know what I'm doing.
I got it. I know it. Are we ready?
Watch this.
They're all going to be calculators.
Start. Got it. I got it. And we're going
to put a hat on.
And we're going to do a dog. They're
all going to. Okay. Bet. How many
people can you play? How many people can
play Monopoly?
You can't have fucking 10 people play
Monopoly. Why does he keep waking up
out of bed?
Hold on. Is there speed? It's got to
be speed, right?
Fast computers. Let's go. I can't even
do a one-minute game.
Well, how did I just add? I just
added players in the middle of
Monopoly and made it a one-minute game.
You can't do that. There we go. All
right. One minute. Who wins? There's like
30 pieces on the board. It's just like
you have the whole family come over.
Everybody gets to play. This fucking
30 pieces on the board.
It's like a D&D campaign. The game's
limit has been reached. The player with
the highest total assets wins the
game. Who won?
Congratulations, dog. You have the
most assets.
It just picked a random person that
didn't get to roll.
Dog takes victory lap. Good job, dog.
Well, this was terrible. Please vote
again. Vilemi.
50 more dollars from Vilemi. Oh, fuck.
Hold on. Stop.
Uh, ignore these Philistines. Play Jazz
Jackrabbit. That's not up to me. If it
were up to me, I would have played
uh, soft porn 2 for the next 12 hours.
It's not up to me. Holy shit. Really?
You're enabling them.
Lost to a calculator. Uh-oh. The Jazz
Jackrabbit votes are getting divided.
Jazz Jackrabbit and Jazz Jackrabbit
holiday hair in 1995.
So, um, you guys, you gotta come to a
consensus here.
So that's 20, that's 19, 29, 30,
that's 12, like 40 percent want a
version of Jazz Jackrabbit.
You guys, just, you got, why do half of
you want to see?
Uh, you guys gotta work together.
You split the vote.
We're scrolling. I'm sorry, guys, that's
not,
that's not how it works. So here's what
we're going to do.
Before I turn the stream off, we're
going to come back and do a final
vote on Jazz Jackrabbit, uh, or
Jack, Jack, Jack, Jackrabbit holiday
hair in 1995.
We'll do it before we leave. But, uh,
it's, whatever has the highest score
and people want to scroll.
You should have, um, had the
consensus there, but it's okay. You'll
have a chance again
in a little bit. Here we go.
Split the vote. All right,
here we are. I think we, uh, yeah, we're
in the right spot.
See ya in a second. Please choose. I've
got
some votes on Tetris. We have most
votes on
Cool World. We also have Mario's Game
Gallery,
and we have Ski or Die. Y'all are
thirsty.
I can't understand the chat sometimes.
All right, it looks like we're going to
be going with Cool World.
Thank you for voting. A lot of you want
Cool World.
We're gonna just have it on in the
background while he plays.
All right, let's go. Cool World.
Wasn't this a movie?
This is a movie game, right? Is it a
licensed movie game?
Ooh, I think it might have crashed. No, not
quite.
Blood? Is it Cool World's, the game
with the, um,
with the spot, right? The like red dot
thing?
The red, is it like the glass, the red
sunglasses?
That's a cool spot. All right, what?
Stop it. Let me go.
All right, use key. Hold on. Wait, wait.
Redefine keys.
Press key for up. Press key for down.
Press key for left.
Right. Fire. We'll make it, um,
I don't know,
C. Or, uh, yeah, C.
Pause. Space. Map.
Uh, M. Here we go. It's Bart Simpson?
What the fuck? Boss, get over to Spark's
place as fast as you can. He's trying to
jump into the real world. You must stop
him.
That really is just Bart Simpson. Was
this, was Bart Simpson in the movie?
It's just, it's, it's doing oof. This
is where they got the oof sound
effect for him.
This movie was okay, I guess. I don't,
I don't, I didn't even see the movie.
And why, why am I dressed like this?
Has, okay, somebody check. Has anybody
speed ran this game?
You're not welcome here, Harris. Ain't
you got
some better things to do with your
time than harassing innocent
doodles? How am I not welcome?
He's trying to go to the real world.
How do I stop him from going to the
real world?
You're not welcome. What's with the,
why are there demon doors?
You guys got click faded.
Oh, there's a girl on there. She's
dancing. Get that one.
Oh, sorry. It's a side scrolling
Bart Simpson shooter. Do I need more
money?
Money? What about map?
All right, um, up? I can't go up?
How the fuck do I get out of here?
All right, how do you, I gotta go up
and to the left and
I can't go up? It looks like I can go
up from here.
I can't go this way. Can I go up
through here?
Okay, here we go. All right, now we're
just gonna go right.
This is the door. I don't like your
money, Harris, but you've got enough
of it. Step inside, sucker.
Um, this is just a Sonic the Hedgehog
level.
I remember I hated this level. This is
like the casino level. This level
sucked.
This is the one where you could
drown and it was really easy to die
in like five seconds.
It's a good level. No, no. Wait, am I
thinking the right one?
Is that the one where you, it's
really easy to get trapped and die?
Real world comic books. No, I'm
thinking the wrong one. Oh, no, that's
chemical plant. Oh, that level sucks.
Can I make it?
I think, you know, the casino level was
awesome. I have no idea what the fuck's
going on.
I can't open the map anymore? Danger.
Danger.
Invalence is too great.
Did you do me a favor and click on the
screen where you'd like to see us go
next?
Wait, wait, I just influenced it. I
just, I just, I just, I just, people
are gonna click on that now. Hold on.
Wait, I just influenced it
accidentally.
Three, two, click girl.
Ten percent of you guys click girl. I
see girl.
Uh, Mario's game gallery looks like it's
gonna be the one.
This might be an illegal stream. Yeah,
that's gonna be it.
Uh, Mario's game gallery. Okay, let's
go.
Ugh. Interplay. What? What do you mean
interplay?
Interplay. What? This is blowing my
mind.
Along with presage, proudly present.
This is not real. Is this real? Use a
game gallery.
Wow. A nice game of
checkers. He's talking. Hold on, get this
off the screen.
This motherfucker is doing false
sentences. He's never done that before.
Matt Gaiman. What does he yacht?
Mario versus checkers. That's a great
game.
Wow, this is awesome. This is worth
going to jail for.
Nice to see you again. Do you want
to play
as Yoshi or as Koopa? I would like to
play as
I'll play as Yoshi. Yoshi, Yoshi.
The chosen one. It's your turn.
This is weird perspective. I don't think
you can do that.
What? No, that's, the mouse is like
laggy.
That's what Yoshi's ass looks like?
Move. That's not a legal move.
This is not a legal stream, Mario. Why
can I not do anything?
I could. You next. Set him up for this
one.
Set him up for this one. Oh, fuck. Yoshi's
dead.
Oh, you're so good. You got Mario
confused.
Eat him alive. Kill him. Let me think.
Don't ever move the back row. What
happens if you get king? Do you get
two Yoshis?
Hmm, all right. Okay. Hmm,
no, no, no, no, no, no. It's Mario's
move.
I'm setting you up for this one.
All right, now check this out. He
thinks he's one.
His brain is not even remotely as
mutated as mine. I've already seen his
next five plays.
Mama mia. I'm a no.
Okie dokie. Your move. I'm just setting it
up.
Mama mia. How about this?
Okay. It's your turn. That's third moves
in.
Three moves in. You must make a jump
now.
I don't. What are you talking about? Oh, yeah.
We're gonna play by those rules? Oh,
playing by shitty rules, huh?
You have to jump? I hate those rules.
That's for low brain.
Low IQ brains. Go ahead. Go over there and get
kinged.
You can't win against Mario. Like
Mario's dumb?
Mario, Mario has like 180 IQ.
He's very smart. Yeah, come on.
What? What? Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey Mario, as you say in your patented
licensed video game.
Okie dokie. You got the jump you can make.
Do it. Mama mia. See you later.
I'm not gonna move this guy ever. Or
this guy.
Good luck. I'm a no. This...
That's... I don't like that. That's
terrifying.
He's gonna have to come out sooner or
later. I got it.
It's your turn.
Ooh, Mario, Mario, Mario. What have you
done?
What have you done? It's my turn now.
Let me think. Mama mia.
Congrats. It's my turn now. Level up.
Wait, we could have done... We could
have had it free.
I'm just like clicking random
squares. I'm gonna be real.
But it's all right. I got a
Giga Yoshi. Your move. It's my turn now.
What's wrong with that Yoshi? I just
don't... I like...
I was making stupid moves in the
beginning for like laugh out loud
comedy moments and then I couldn't
salvage it so I just figured oh who
cares.
I can still win. Okie dokie. Crown me.
The good old... Wait, I turned into Bowser.
I want to see what Bowser could do
too.
I fucked her. I fucked off too much
in the first 10 minutes.
You can't go there. I can't go
backwards. I'm gonna lie just to lose.
Let me do it again. Hold on. I want to do it. I don't want to
fuck around this time though. Let me show
you that I'm not stupid.
Great. I'm a liar. Go fish?
I'm gonna prove that I'm gonna play
Go fish. I'm not gonna... I'm gonna win
this round.
Just wait. I'm so happy to see you
again.
Shut up and steal the cards
motherfucker.
We'll go first. Do you have any
reap than a fishy?
I don't even know what that one is.
Hey. Oh, right. I would like to have your
Bowser's. Mario, go fish.
It's supposed to be like a
five-year-old. Wait, what are the rules
for Go fish?
In Go fish, you and Mario will try to
have...
try to make as many books of four
of a kind as you can.
You are dealt... I don't remember how
to play Go fish. I haven't played it
in like 30 years.
You are dealt seven cards which
appear along the bottom of the
screen.
To ask Mario for a particular card, look
on a card.
Uh, I haven't played in a long time.
Go fish.
What? Please give me your reap than a
fishy.
I don't have any. I don't have any.
Mario, go fish.
Ah, I guess I'm gonna go fishing.
It's your turn.
All right. Do you have any Koopas?
Go fish. You have to...
What do you have for cards? Give me
a break.
A fishing for Luigi's.
Don't have any. Mario, go fish.
Looks like it's time to go fishing
again.
Okay. All right, you gotta have some
ba-bombs.
Yes, I'ma have two cards. Mario is
getting
destroyed. It's your turn. Hey Mario,
uh, you got any blue fucked up
Yoshi's?
Go fish. I'd like to have your
Koopas.
Sorry, tied up. Please give me your
Luigi's. Don't have any. He really
wants Luigi's. Mario, go fish.
Come here fishy fishy. Here fishy fishy.
It's your turn. Yeah, uh, I'd like
your rip van winkles please. Please, I'ma have two cards.
Thank you. Okay. All right,
so let's talk about how many toads
you got.
Go fish. Oh, I got two toads. You got what you wanted.
It's your turn. Mario, are you looking at my
cards?
So he's been cheating the whole time.
He's cheating in checkers too. He had
extra pieces.
Fine. Okay, that's fucked up. Go fish.
I'ma fishing for piranha plant.
The house always wins. I'ma looking for
Luigi's. He probably only needs one.
Give me your Luigi's.
I'ma guess I'ma go fishing. Mario has
this like fucked up
cheating casino. I think he has a game
promoted for two years.
His finance with illegal money. All
right, uh, he wants Yoshi's doesn't he?
Give me the Yoshi's. Yes, I have one card.
It's your turn. Okay, so
what about Goombas? Yes, sir. Yes, you
do. I have one card.
Hmm. Okay. I don't think I can do
anything else. Bob-ombs maybe? Maybe
he got another one.
Or a boo? Maybe he has a couple now.
Ooh. I'd like to have your Goombas.
Mario, go fish. Looks like it's time to go
fishing again.
All right, what'd you get? Mario gets to
go again.
Oh, fuck you, Mario. Do you have any
Luigi's?
No. Mario, go fish. No, he's gonna
he's gonna complete his deck.
Here, fishy. That's one book for Mario.
Oh, come on. What book was it? I don't know what to ask for.
Oh, you asshole. I'ma fishing for
piranha plant. Mario, go fish.
Come here, fishy fishy. Here, fishy fishy.
Okay. Can I play now? Do I get to go?
Do you? Yeah, I think you may have gotten
another sleepy. I could complete a book
here.
Go fish. I can get it though. No, he's
gonna ask for it.
Oh, rexes. I'm looking for
Bowser's. No, I don't want to go fish. Looks like it's time to go fishing again.
He's gonna complete the deck.
It's your turn. Come on, you get me. You had to have just got one.
Oh, brother. You got three of them, don't you?
So, one book for you. K. Check this out.
Yes, sir.
That's another book for you. It's your turn.
Hey Mario, you got any Yoshi's in there? Go fish.
Oh, I'll be getting one right now.
Oh, I would just start
punching the table. I'd like to have your
Piran. I guess I'm go fishing. Oh, you're so good.
Thank you. It's your turn. Oh, and guess what? Hey, the Yoshi you just took
out of the deck. I'll take it. Yes, sir. I have one card. Oh, would you like it?
I love it. I love seeing it. That's another book for you.
Mario think you fantastic. Okay.
Go fish. Mario, I don't think you beat me.
I'm fishing for... I get a Bowser's from here. I get
five books. Mario, go fish. Looks like it's time to go fishing again.
Mario's going easy on you because you're playing as a five-year-old. I really
enjoy playing with you. Oh, fuck. He really is. It's your turn.
He's complimenting me after every single
card he takes. He's saying really nice things about me. He's
letting me take his cards. Shit. Oh, no. I got three cards.
And I'm so excited about it. It's another book for you. Somebody would be mad about
this, but he's like, oh, no. We know. I love you. You're the
best. You're so smart at this game. Oh,
good. Yes, sir. I have one card. I'm cleaning
him out. I really enjoy playing with you.
It's your turn. Hey, you got any booze? Go fish.
Please give me your... He's not even trying anymore.
Mario, go fish. He's playing with an actual four-year-old.
I'm go fishing. You can't beat a four-year-old in any game.
I get another turn. You're a bad person if you do. I'm
looking for Bowser's. Anybody under the age of eight,
if you do any activity, you have to let them win.
Otherwise, you are a bad person. If you play,
let's say, for instance, like Connect Four
with a five-year-old, and you win, and you're like, yeah, I won.
Hold on, Mario.
Relax. Give me some time. Go fish. Somebody's three.
I'm looking for... Oh, shit. Big booze.
But now he's here. Do you have any rexes?
Mario, go fish. Mario, I got it.
I guess I'm go fishing. Mario, thank you.
Oh, okay. Thank you. Give me a coach.
Go fish. Okay. That's my favorite card. I love Mario.
I'm fishing for big booze. He just got them.
Mario, go fish. Come here, fishy, fishy.
Here, fishy, fishy. Oh, you're so good.
It's your turn. I really am getting played
as a four-year-old. I have one card.
I'm beating him by so much. It has to be intentional.
I really enjoy playing with you. It's your turn.
Go fish. That's so funny.
Where are you getting these cards? I'd like to have your rexes.
Mario, I haven't... I haven't had rexes in like
seven turns. Change the age in the options menu?
Fantastic. Shut up. That's not real.
I thought that just said change age for a second. I was like, there's no
fucking way. Change age.
Go fish. Please give me your booze.
Mario, go fish. Looks like it's time to go fishing again.
Oh, you're so good. It's your turn. Look at that. I thought you said
pretending gaze. Go fish. I should get a Goomba here. How many cards are in the deck?
I'd like to have your Mario's. Fine. Please give me your big booze.
Mario, go fish. Come here fishy fishy. Here fishy fishy. I really enjoy playing with you.
Okay. Um, this is actually the kind of scenario where like he's being held
hostage and he is trying to communicate with me somehow.
This is like the the type of shit. Look at him.
I'm really enjoying playing with you. Oh, you're so smart.
Okay, it's your turn. I really enjoy playing with you.
You're so good at this. Hey, I'm having a great time here
at the table. What's it take so long? Go fish.
Fishing for rexes. I'm a gaze. I'm a go fishing.
That stare too. They're like, I guess. That's another Mario.
Mario think you fantastic. Okay. He starts like winching his face and
like Mario think you fantastic. Wink over here under the table.
There's a gun pointing at me. Yes, I have two cards. That's another book for you.
Oh, you're so good. It's your turn. He's asking for Bowser's the whole time.
I got three cards. I know it's Bowser. I'm just beating him so bad.
That's another book for you. I really enjoy playing with you.
It's your turn. Go fish. Last card is going to be the goomba.
No, he's going to get the booze. I'm looking for big boos.
It's another book for Mario. No mercy.
Your rexes. He's going to get another book.
Sorry. Here fishy fishy. Here fish. It's another book for Mario.
I guess I need another card. What if he just keeps completing?
Fishing again. Is this where I get sharked? Do you have any goombas?
Oh no. Did I get sharked? No, I win. That's another book for Mario.
Hey, you won. Help me. I did it. Told you guys I was going to win.
Hey, how about another game with me? No, bye Mario.
What? And here's the thing. I don't know how to play
any of the rest of these games. I don't. I only know about
dominoes. You set them up for like six hours and you knock them down.
They do a cool thing. They spin around around your sofa and like over your
fridge and stuff. I don't know how to play this.
Like the actual game dominoes. I don't know.
Backgammon is, again, I have no idea.
And yacht is an expensive boat for rich people.
I don't know what that means. I'll try it. You guys have to help me here.
That is what this is. Okay. Mario, you are fucking enormous.
Why are you like 80 feet tall? He's huge. I'm gonna go first.
I don't know what this means. Oh, it's just, is it just like poker?
Like dice poker? You got a full house. That's going on the full house
line. Okey dokey. Your move. This is yacht. I've never played one game of
Yahtzee. All I know is I see people play
Yahtzee in TV and they don't just shake the thing around. They go
Yahtzee and they high five. I don't know what they're doing.
All right, so we need, uh, let's see. One, two, we could get a full house.
Choices, sixes. Hold on a minute here. What is going on?
Just re-roll, yeah, just re-roll the one, right? Because I could get a full
house. Does that mean I'm holding them? Does
that mean I'm rolling them? Click to hold. Okay, so roll.
Oh, I can try it again. Your turn. Hello. Oh wait, fours, choice?
Way to go. What is choice? It's my turn now.
Oh, you have to pick something, okay. I got it. The three threes,
come on. Yeah, Mario's got extra dice up his
uh, clubs. I'm gonna roll these ones again. He's gonna get five, okay.
Mario's gonna put these on the deuces line.
That's not that much. Your roll. The stream always devolves into some
form of gambling. We're not betting any money here. I'm playing
a children's dice game with a made-up kid's cartoon character. That was just
gambling. Mario's not real. All right, so we're
gonna go with the, I'm gonna try to get five of a kind.
Wait, can I do a straight? One, two, three, four. Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I could get a big straight, small straight. Let's go with one,
three, four. I just need two, right? I'm gonna roll for the two, because
that would be a small straight. What would, a big straight is the whole
thing. Yeah, fuck it, dude. No, let's go,
let's go for two. How is that a small straight? That's
one, oh shit. I just need five. One, two, three,
four, five. I still have the small straight.
It's all right, it's all right. This game's fun. I've never played it
before. This is cool. I like this. I'm gonna play this tomorrow.
I'm gonna roll these ones again. What do you mean, no, it's not.
Uh-oh. I'm gonna roll these ones again. So if you get a full house,
you can't do it again. Is the goal to get every single thing,
or just points? That's going on the aces line.
It's your turn. Oh, that's gonna go on the aces.
Yeah, at most points. I got, all right, bingo, we got two, we got one,
two, we got twos. Let's just try to get some twos here.
We could do one, two, three, four, five, six.
No, there it is. What do you mean, six is fives,
three is deuces? Sixes. It's only one six.
I don't... Oh no! It's my turn now. You just get six, you get six points.
Okay. Let's see. Well, I'm kicking the shit out of
him, so I'm all right. Fives. Don't get five. Don't get
any more. Yes. Mario's gonna put these on the
fives line. Stop hurting Mario. It's your turn.
I didn't do anything. That's pretty good. That's a pretty good chance for a full
house. I don't have it yet, so come on, give me
a five or a six. It's not a five or a six.
I wanted to get the five guy. The five...
Where is it? Aces. You want me to do aces?
No, no, no. Ones don't matter. Yes, yes, do it.
Minimize loss. Minimize loss. Aces max at six points.
Save fives. I don't... I don't... I don't... That's the first time I've ever
played this game. Just tell... Just help me.
Okay. It's such a simple card. I've never seen it before.
I know you make like cards like... Stop yelling at me.
Save bigger scoring categories. Yeah, that's... Yeah, that's true. I'm gonna win.
Don't worry. I got it. That's going on the little straight line.
Small straight. Okay, this is my chance. How do you get a... What's a yacht?
Yahtzee. Yahtzee. I get it now. All right. Here we go.
So the... It's five of a kind. Do I go for the full house here? That's not
going to be enough points though. That won't be a lot of points.
Does it... It depends on... Because it matters the denomination.
Yeah, that would be a waste. All right, there we go. Well, there's the full
house right there. God damn it. Should I just save the threes and
try to go for another... More threes? Or should I just keep this as a full
house? Because... Because what... That's not...
All right. I'm gonna take the full house.
That's a good move. It's my turn now.
That's a poor man's full house. Well, it might be the only one I get.
Is he going for sixes? Oh no, this is bad.
I'm gonna roll these ones again. Do not get a full six, Yahtzee.
Let's see. Mario's gonna put this on the sixes line.
How much money points? 18 points for three sixes.
Oh my god, okay. Okay, we can do fives. There's also one, two, three. One, two,
three, four, five. What's a big straight?
All of them? One, two, three, four, five.
Oh boy, come on. Give me a four. I could have had it.
It's not that hard. It's not a bad chance. He's going for the ones.
What? Oh no. I'm gonna roll these ones again.
He's going for a four or five of a kind. He really wants those big sixes.
Oh my god, game sucks. That's going on the
Yahtzee. How many points is that? 50.
Okie dokie. Your move. Oh, I'm never gonna win now.
That's like the, that's the best thing you could possibly get in the whole
game. There's no way I'm gonna win. It was all sixes. I just feel defeated
now. Lost to Mario. I just beat him though,
whatever. Um, I'm, I guess I could go for,
doesn't matter. It's just like being at the blackjack table and a guy
next to you does like a five hundred dollar hand and he gets
blackjack and you've lost the like the last five hands in a row and you
lose again and he's like yeah oh my god blackjack and you're sitting there like
fun games we're having here fun having a fun time
here we go this could put me back in two three
four five six give me a two well do i try to beat him in his own game and
do sixes and fucking throw the dice in the
air i sometimes gotta do a hail mary play
it's your turn ah fours it's only one in six chance and i've done it
like three times i can't win okay oh i got it oh sixes
one in six is unlikely no i don't say that
he's gonna do another what is he looking for here just straight
well he didn't get it mario's gonna put this on the
choice line okay i'm sorry i already did the full
house so fives i guess try to go for five five five five give it to me
one two one two ah one two three four five no
five four three no i can't no ah
no can i just not click any of them do i have to click fives or can i
just say pass okay it's my turn now i don't think i
can win this at all got it look at this this is bullshit
he's gonna get a big straight here oh my god
what the hell is this i was gonna say that's going on the trees line
it's your turn uh i don't i don't think there's a reason for me to
play right now unless i get a big straight and sixes
one two three four five so just hold up hold the sixes and just
fucking go for it who cares go for the straight
six five four three two two three four five six just need four
he's back in the game i really enjoy playing with you
it's my turn now back in it let's go mario
all i need i just need good sixes and i gotta go to i gotta get a
yahtzee don't know one good mario's gonna put no wait no shit
oh no it's your turn
there's no way i can win is there a surrender
well when can i go uh well played and then blow my character's portrait
up are you so good i gotta get four of a
kind he's going for kind right here you
better not get it he's not gonna get it don't give it to him
if he gets this i lose no matter what oh you fucking
stupid game that's going on the four of the kind
i'm gonna do it again it's a great game
well played requeue good luck i'm gonna go first do it
mario's gonna put this on the four of the kind
line okey dokey your move wait it's not over yet
oh we can do a big full house here or i could go for the fives no full
house what go for the fives fives baby fine oh throw it right
back in his face five ah so i do know fives fives fives
not four of a kind i'll get that with some of the little shitty ones
take the four of a kind but should i take the i should take the fives right
four of a kind but what if i but should i how is four of a kind 22
and why is four four for the five it's 20
i don't know i'm not an expert on this it's more just more points but
what if i get a bet what if i get a better
four of kind is harder to do oh you're so good
all right i'm gonna listen to the i'm gonna ask the audience you know
this is a game go to fall that's a shit full house i hope you get it
you're going on the juices line your role all right let's go
something big all right all right all right all right
two three four five six give me a five
don't hold the six why not two three four
five six two three four five five don't take the one to the six
chance but that's how you got to you got a big bet and you got to do big bet
every time you're killing me here don't do this don't do the same thing that i
do mario's doing it see mario's doing it
on the little straight line okey-dokey
your move it was it was such a bad odds mario wouldn't be doing it
oh bingo i'll take the aces here give me the aces
i really enjoy playing with you it's my turn now
that's not bad though let's see no no no no i'm gonna roll these ones
again it's not gonna happen he's not gonna happen
he's gonna take the sixes here the iris four of kind
good it's a full house going on the full house line
thank god these were ones your role uh do i just take the small straight or
do i try to get something better do i just say i'm done take the big
straight two three four five six or one come
on i can get this i have a much higher
chance here there it is get out of town i'm really
enjoy playing with you i'm still losing i got it he's going for
the straight going for a big straight yeah
you're brave he's gonna get it he's gonna get it's gonna be six
oh you fucking asshole gonna put this on the big straight
mario i need a big i need a big i need a yahtzee or i need a really
i don't know i gotta get some sixes uh well we're going for the fours come on
don't make me take 12 points for fours thank you
thank you you listened for at least a second oh you're so good
it's my turn now mario owns the casino you can't beat him in his own casino
again mario savage casino owner that just is savage against everybody
let's see that's going on the brutal casino owner
who's brutal against everybody i'm just saying the same thing twice in a
different way i think i'm just gonna take this hold on
we got a i'm gonna opportunity here four two three four five
it doesn't matter though i'm just gonna take it oh you're so good
it's my turn now i need a yahtzee oh i always get the sixes and then
reroll them i get them every time see what are you
gonna put these on the sixes oh mario you special magnetic weighted
dice oh i already took the i have to do
fives or go for a full house
this is a terrible full house though a one and a two
full house that's so bad i'm just gonna go for five
that's embarrassing if i try to take that i'm just rerolling fives
now i got the fours i already did the fours
choice his choice is only 19 full house with a
i don't think it's gonna happen i'm depressed i need a five
if i get a four this whole thing fucks up knock knock
hey all right who's there pizza pizza who
pizza the heck out of me i have i had a drink i would throw it in your
face um i'm gonna have to take choice here
that's still winnable it's not bad damn it what and this is what he needs too
he always gets what he needs i'm so lucky
yay oh god i think this is over going on the fives line this only is
possible if i get your turn a big yahtzee
that is not a big yahtzee that is a bad
threes i don't want to i'm not taking that full house
no that's so bad one and three all right all right well i all right i got
it i got it i did it that's i'll take it should i take it yes
ah yeah thank you i really enjoy playing with you
i but i'm just behind still oh let's see what does he got here he's looking
for his aces i'm gonna roll these ones again
okay it's gonna be a low score no matter what it is
three sorry mario's gonna put these on the aces line yeah he he doesn't have
very many opportunities for points he really has to get fours or threes i
can win this i just need a good sixes round i can win
and that's how you get it this is how it starts this is how i win
we are going straight up sixes and i need at least
four of them three or four of them it's not come on
don't make me choose this you gotta give me at least three
this is a winnable game now it's my turn now
i got a real chance here he just has to get some bad rolls
no it's fine he already took his uh sixes all right just give him one
only one no fours no fours he's gonna get screwed here come on
no fours and i win the game no fours no fours oh that's fine
that's going on the fours line it's your turn it's gonna be close
five but i feel like i don't want to do the fives until i get
at least two i can try again i'm um no i'm doing three
because i if i want to get we're gonna do three i'm gonna three
i'm going for three oh god damn it it's okay
oh no i can wait i can still do this no i don't know what to do
should i do all the fives now that i have two or stay with the threes
because uh but it could be it could be like it could be another five
this is crucial to win the game for absolutely crucial
i hope i don't regret this i hope i don't regret this if this rolls
a five a couple fives i'll be so upset
selected the line to score okay i just need it
i need okay he's gonna do what is he going for a yasi you're not
gonna hold the three good give him a yasi with ones
what is he gonna do mario's gonna put this on the
trees oh you just wow zero points your move that's it this is gonna be game
over i just need fives anything none of
those are fives throw the whole fucking thing away fives
what are you doing to me i just give me a five
just give me one five oh i got one i got one one five
i win okay it's my turn now he's doing the ones again i win i
win he's not gonna get anything
i win i win that's going on i won by two points thank you
good game that was this is that was intense this phone
i love this game i'm gonna play this at like my family reunions
uh we're going for i mean it's i might as well just grab the five
imagine if i didn't get one five that last time
okay you got the better score you win hey how about another game with me
i mean i kind of have to do best two out of three
this game's fun
god is i have to settle the tie i have to settle the tie i'm sorry guys
i have to settle the tie i'm doing it again
let's go this is for it this is me versus mario whoever wins
it's to have the new console named after him the switch two
he won i won let's go he's playing fast now he's doing it he's pissed
what's it gonna go for threes oh he got a full house it's all right
i can beat that it's fine it's all right twos we're going for the uh
we're going for the twos here we could do one two three four five
we could do one two three four five
i'm going for it we're going for big plays this time go we go for big plays
big plays give us a three big plays the play has sucked
i have to i gotta do choice that's 18 is not bad that's not terrible 18 is
actually pretty good or i could do the terrible aces
yeah that's a good let's do aces aces
it's all right i fucked myself there it's all right just uh just
focus back at the table let's see cocktails cocktails let me get a
drink can i get a vodka pineapple please
thank you come on you got nothing going on the aces
again we got one extra point that i did who cares your role
who didn't have to do anything didn't have to do it hold on yeah i
didn't do anything 30 points that's a good straight to have
oh brother he's shaking now he's like oh
30 points again put the fear in him let's see it's all right
these on a d it's all right little straight line
how are you still playing this because this is my favorite game
all right hold on here we could go for the threes
oh we could do one two three one two three four
or we could do three four three four hear me out of this one let's go big
plays three four five six i'm going for big
plays small straight big plays three four five
six say let him mario i'm going for big
plays small straight is just four right that's i got it i got a really good
chance big place let's go a big place big
place i don't even need to roll the other one
it's my turn now oh oh no he could get a yahtzee here
how much is uh aces yahtzee okay that's all right here
it's going on the four of the kind oh that's a terrible four of a kind oh
you lose mario you got too greedy bad play mario
bad play any yahtzee is 50 bad play though with ones
i wouldn't have done that i what an idiot you know what i mean i've been
playing this a lot now we go for the threes mario you
may as well fucking just give up mario i mean like you may as well
just give up uh oh uh oh is right i'm gonna
roll these ones again uh oh this is bad
he's not gonna get it let's see mario's gonna put this
that's the second time he's done that your roll that's the second time he's
done that that's uh that gets hairy here all right
we can do twos let's try or we could yeah
come on give me a few more make this good it's all right
better than nothing better than nothing that's a great move
it's my turn now still ahead that four of a kind is gonna kill him
oh i'm gonna roll these ones again come on not good it's all right
three is not terrible i could get four oh no he already fell he already did a
full house that's a pretty average score not bad
speaking of fall houses i wonder if this is worth getting or if i should
go for fives but i'm an idiot never mind i thought
that was a three come on i can't just get three in
every category another one yes oh thank you for playing my game
that's a that's a yahtzee it's my turn now
we're almost at the level of uh unachievable to win
unless he gets one if he gets a yahtzee the game still goes it's
still good it's still very possible my top three
scores are the best you can get mario's gonna put these on the
uses line didn't you say you were done with this shit
i did say that like an hour ago but it's too fun
give me the sixes all right could just say get a choice do choice here
take the 23 points i think i'm just gonna take the 23 points
and just and roll the two you know i'm saying
you gotta get it i gotta get a good choice at some point or roll the
sixes yeah i could get more sixes guys oh
boy it's my turn now let's see re-roll the four it i i'm i'm i got
the high from the casino it doesn't matter i win
he's not gonna win see that's going on the choice
oh boy wow 15 points for a choice yeah
oh mario well here's your sixes let's go for it let's put it out of
reach it's out of reach now and that's a
full fucking house look at that full house you ain't gonna
get much better than that that's a great move it's my turn now
in fact yeah you can't get better than that that's the best full house in
the game oh your big straight is gonna really
help you here i think he's just depressed
i think he gave up i think he's just realizing that it's impossible for him
to win he took the loss all right well let's
go for um it's i mean the game's over one iq mario
look at that look at him if that look at that face he is so
fucking angry right now look at his lips just fucking pushed
crushed together just look at his hands his body language
clasping his hands together no no mario fine
i'm gonna go for sixes just because like fuck it why not
not anymore whoa should i just do it uh-huh yeah
i'll take it that's a free three sixes can he i don't think he didn't he can't
win the game's over that's going on the straight
line it's not possible for him to win it's your turn
i mean i guess if i didn't get anything
it might be possible sort of something really bad would have to
happen uh we could go for four of kind
but that's not gonna happen we need to go for fours oh god damn it
now i gotta go for fives i could just take the four
i could take the four okay it's my turn now no yahtzee and i
went he ain't gonna get it i would have beat
him with the five oh because the points right
it's all right for him to get a yahtzee right now would be
like you know that's literally getting struck by lightning
that's getting struck by lightning while you scratching a lottery ticket
and you win he's not gonna get it fives or four of
a kind um i could go for the uh i went see you
late mario that's over that's it i win i won the world series
i won mario and sonic at the olympic games
i win mario and sonic at the casino oh brother even if you get a yahtzee
here mario that's it yeah if they'd be a bit he'd be
at 201 mario is really fun i win see if i can go over
certain amount of points here oh damn i mean kind of you gotta go for the four
kind of sixes just to rub it in his face right
hey you won 240 why does she look so angry
hey how about another game with me no uh best best three out of five
that's five out of three no sorry how's it
this five out of seven three i just won three no three yeah that would be three
to five three mario need uh a snickers
he hungry don't do math very well well that's that one does he have
clickable things on him he does can i stretch his face like
in the n64 one all right well that was that was fun
that was really cool i'm surprised that this game exists to be honest
dominoes i don't know anything about dominoes i can't play dominoes we'll just
look at it great i'm like dominoes
this is what i was talking about you just push them over it's a play
i don't know what any of this means i don't know why are we skype chatting
why am i doing facetime with them like what if we can't be in the same
room i don't know what any of this means
the first doublet have to match the number right i think
you three i don't know what the goal is though
i've no i have to absolutely no idea what's going on
i don't know what's a correct play i don't know what point system i don't
even know match the number right match the number
can i do it on my own or do i have to do it on his
why can i not i can't do this what you have to do it on the end
okay
you're such a good player
what is that okay fine i can do that too
it's a good move it's my turn now maybe i'm should draw from the
boneyard drop in the boneyard what does that mean we have bones
we have a boneyard here's your bone are you so good it's my turn now
maybe i should draw from the boneyard i got it he just drew so like six times
is there and you can't can you draw as many times as you want
um maybe i should draw from the boneyard here's your bone
such a good player this move here's your bone quick help
he won't tell he's not gonna help me
you know play you i never played it before i have no idea
i'm just i'm gonna beat him watch i'm gonna embarrass the fuck out of him
i'm just a i'm a four-year-old just placing tiles and i'm gonna win
watch this maybe i should draw from the boneyard
maybe you should draw from the boneyard let's see
dumb what a dumb thing to do no more dominoes in the boneyard you
lose mario's got to pass oh no you gotta pass
i can keep going
what do you got oh i win mario that's it
i'm lost yeah oh you're so good
i had no fucking idea what i was doing and i still beat him
how about another game no no no no bye see you later i win
backgammon no all right we have to see backgammon fine
great i'm like backgammon oh my god ugly sound ugly
oh it's a play do you want to play as a yoshi or as a koopa let's roll to see
who goes i don't think i can uh bullshit my way through this one
i don't think i can does anyone know how to play
backgammon i don't think anyone in the chat knows how to play this looks
like a mario go first good luck i would be surprised if even
five percent of everybody here knows how to play this
this is i seriously i'm like reading of an alien language right now
say your turn five four seven um four i don't think you can go there
i don't think you can go there i don't think you can go there
i have no idea this was fun what a fun little game
this is cool i can i don't i don't even know what it's trying to tell me
uh yahtzee is definitely i love that game my first experience of the yahtzee
and it's like what a fun game now i know why it's been around for like
185 years all right i'm gonna pee one last time
we'll do a few more and we'll go from here i'll be right
back just gonna go pee and grab some water i'm
waiting for you i'm waiting for you i'm waiting for you
i'm waiting for you i'm waiting for you i'm waiting for you
i'm here what do you need mario what do you need what do you want
no no no i'm mario i don't want to play yahtzee again no no mario
uh he's not really listening to me when i say mario i don't want to play
yahtzee again i've already won and i'm going to go first
uh okay um i don't mar i it was a wonderful evening i had a lot of fun i
got it i got to work tomorrow i got like stop i can't play nice no
good job um you win i guess you can win because
sorry mario sorry mario not gonna happen all right let's go back
so we have here uh we have not voted to move on from this page so
we're not going to do that yet the vote has not come in to move on so
if you could please remember if you click on the thing on the right the arrow the
red dash that means you want to scroll
down a page good luck that was i was gonna say no
way 100 of people i'm not gonna play cool world again
no i'm not gonna open cool world again
it's gonna be the next one below that i just already did it
click click all right well it looks like
oh if you guys want 43 percent all right you should do three games a screen
that's kind of what we've done so far we've done at least two or three per
screen but this is a little trial run for what
we'll do it again because there are so many of these
guys like we're gonna do this again all right here we are i'm not doing
that one i'm not doing no no no no hey all
right hold on hold on hey hey hold on i'm not i'm not doing sex vixens
from space just if anyone was curious i want to make
sure your vote will count here i'm not going to do that one i already
skirted the line there with soft porn too i'd like to keep my twitch
uh partnership and my twitch channel alive
please choose again oh for the love of god
no all right no strip poker no sex vixens no
please vote again are there any more like sex games on this list that i'm
not seeing i don't think so all right try again what program is
this this is uh is archive.org if we can't have sex then let's get the
fuck out here scroll uh this is on the archive.org that is
a compilation of abandoned ware and old
vaporware and even some stuff i think that's still around and there's
more than four thousand of them there's a lot and um
that is not doom that is demons gate 666 new levels for doom by the way
i was probably i was gonna just do this on stream
dragon's lair is a game that i was actually gonna play
so it looks like we're doing uh doom doom 2 demons gate
thanks for voting i wonder what the soundtrack will be like
hopefully it's good downloading game this was big this is 228
megabytes that's a big one this thing is fucking huge all right
move it over to the actual screen doom 2 all right uh new game how do you
control it end game messages graphic detail high
screen size of smaller okay how do i play
no no no no how do i new game choose skill level i'm too young to
die hey not too rough hurt me plenty ultra
violence or nightmare i'm gonna go with um i'll go with
night are you sure this skill level isn't even
remotely fair i got it i'll be fine how do you play
space shift enter control uh there's a thousand people over here
no mouse aim is there no there's no mouse aim
is there any health can you strafe all right let's try again
uh here we go chainsaw that wasn't that effective
game journalist i'm on the unfair difficulty
i'm on the unfair a game's not fair oh yeah game journalist nightmare
because he got peer pressure there's chat room i'll get through this ready
you hold alt you can strafe nice thanks for the tip oh i gotta get down
this fucking hallway okay i did it i can wait i i did i did it
i did i got through the hallway all right nightmares bullshit even all
right well i'm gonna take it off a nightmare
i have to redownload the game i'm not playing on nightmare anymore
that's one of 666 levels holy shit all right well i'll i'll take your word for
it i'm too young to die hey not too rough
just hey not too rough this is a game this is a video game showcase not
there's no enemies even here holy shit there was so many that spawned here
before this is just a video game showcase
oh he's inside the crate nice how do i press the button
alt enter shift space there it is whoa wait wait wait do i have to go up
there oh nothing else up here all right
you might just call me old and shit but using the right hand for my arrow
keys i heard like it's giving me arthritis
my fingers it's i really is i win thank you up 55
kills 88 percent items zero percent secrets
power is 30 minute 44 all right we'll do one more level
it's what's up it's my right hand on the arrow keys
entering under halls let's do this fast like i see on the
screw tube screen ready go i don't know where to go need the
key yep let's go a whole four pixels wait what did
that open uh my fingers hurt well now your back's gonna hurt
because you just gave yourself landscaping duty what did that even
open i don't get it what did i what's that what
what tell me i'm crazy it opened the gate outside
oh literally blind doom how do you jump is there jumping in doom
there is no jumping in doom you have to go upstairs fuck how do you get
over here it's escape it's not escape you have to
run is there a run can you run in doom where did that guy come from
game sucks doom is actually like a classic
fantastic uh paved the way for every video game
game i'm just kidding don't take that to heart i really don't mean that all
right so uh anything else on this page you'd like
to see hey stick to mario yahtzee stick to mario yahtzee kid
it's a uh nom 1965 1975 so it's gonna be a war game all right
there we go this is archive.org let's open it now i gotta take this
off turn off that uh whoops uh all right so
there it is this doesn't look like it's lined up
correctly hold on okay this is nixon johnson what
what am i looking at here this is um that's a notebook
um nixon okay i gotta better get ready hold on
ready up time no return presidential decisions
maps troop commitments withdraw troops withdraw troops
all of them uh southeast asia reports i'm just zooming in we're just going
in like google earth style and it's where this is the
equivalent of what a computer it would look like if a computer threw up
uh let's go back to reports troop commitments 11
how do i get away from nixon uh military aid and economic aid
a thousand million of 999 trillion dollars
999 trillion proposed this all right now here we go propose air support
new aircraft strategic percent um being president is easy this is just
like a simulation raise the taxes by five million percent that's easy
oh okay so they're there now what do i do how do i get out of nixon's office
all right you just have to you have to do watergate
okay that was uh that was vietnam war let's go fun time are a hundred
percent never it never happens of course sex
vixens is gonna get a few clicks all right uh i
veto everybody because i'm sorry i want to see what
stunt driver is so everyone's getting vetoed for a minute
i need to know what this is there's that person talking of course
quiz on course five what is the piece
what is the piece at location d11 this is not stunt driver this is
hello was that was that a capture on course two
page 42 what is the piece at locations in order to run the game you need to
run the file it's pretty hard to guess i had this
game and as soon as i got the quiz i remembered it all i believe this is one
of the games that got me to save all my
boxes with the documents inside they don't click the virus bibliotheca
bibliotheca dot missio eight bits dot es
i don't know what this is this could be a fucking pot this could be a virus
it's a fire ah no no i'm not clicking the virus pdf
go ahead do it again it means library i don't know i don't know
that word yes i'm it's foreign to me i'm scared
it could mean virus this is i know i'm just
fucking around all bubble bob bubble votes are now registered as
down arrow votes why don't worry i'm gonna come back in place don't
drive before the stream's over we still have to play the jackrabbit game
too all right let's let's go down because
i did veto it and you know it was just it was just fun
i'll try let's scroll down how much do i have to need
how much do i need to scroll so we need to go like this we're going to
get a bunch more like this okay hold on let me just make
sure there's no porn game so i can okay don't click this one
i'm not that's not i'm not clicking on strip poker 2 plus
by the way it also looks like the cable boxes used to look
when you used to go to the porn channel on old tv
it was just scrambled like that uh fat bossiant thank you bat fat bossiant
for the 50 dollars 50 bucks from fat bossiant
hey jeremiah i haven't seen a stream since finishing sakiro thanks to being
a eu pleb i just wanted to know bloodborne or sakiro bloodborne every
time all right uh remember i'm not clicking
this one but thank you for the 50 fucking bucks
it's a lot of money i really appreciate that
but bloodborne i would say every time no i mean that's fine you can click
it but your vote doesn't count you're literally just walking into the
ballot and just dropping your vote into the trash this is a
protest vote that's not a candidate that's on the
ballot uh so it looks like we've got
dangerous dave and rogue are in the current running here
if we could get softball we can get strip poker the thing with strip poker
is probably images on the screen close i'm gonna close it here in
about five seconds five four three two
one dangerous dave in the haunted mansion
okay look if you want to play if you want to play the sex games you
can go ahead and do them if you're over the age of of 18 25
whatever it is wherever it's okay for you to accept
pornography onto your computer that you got the website i don't need
to show i don't need to play this i want to experience them with you
that's weird you want to experience the
porn game with me i want i want you to say that out
loud all right here we go dangerous dave all right we got um
spaces to go on the title screen to begin arrow keys to move control is
jumping all to fire it's weird okay here we go
uh a soft disk production programming by
by who go back john carback and john romero
is it a joker is that is that real holy shit
i think it's real let's reload yeah this isn't bad for dos it really
isn't i could say this is a saturday morning
flash game it's doom 2d well that's a cool piece of history
there then john carback and john romero when did this release
like 90 i didn't see it i haven't done an ammo they
can aim up too oh i'd have to jump up it can i go
in the doors nice i got the secret can't shoot through walls though i'm
gonna appear right here i gotta shoot this guy around the head
it's got the controls tight they're pretty good oh they can walk
downstairs zombies are smart stop playing this i want to play it when
the stream ends you can you still you still can do
that this game looks sick it's actually very good
can i make this jump i don't think so what knife i think i have to do
that jump got the egg all right hold on wait he's gonna throw
another one i have to make this jump huh damn all right let me see if i can
get it oh oh oh can i jump up from here
oh no this is these are stairs i thought this was a curtain i wonder if
there's a boss i kind of want to see what's after
the uh first level oh the fucking arrow is there i'm sorry
sorry about that all right level oh god there was seagulls over bags of
money i didn't get the bags of money
i missed the money i thought they were so it's one hit and you're dead
they're not fucking around i only got two more daves slimes
new enemy type why can i not shoot up shoot i can't shoot up
is there a reason why okay oh okay i can shoot top right but i can't shoot top
left why uh oh that's weird i think i'm gonna
run out of daves i'm dead ah damn last one maybe it's a
keybinding conflict that's fine maybe let me go this way
all right p dave ooh i can go in oh fuck
oh i'm safe wow no
oh anybody do i have my quarters i have my quarters that's good that's
really fun i highly recommend it that's called
dangerous dave 1991 john karmak john romero cool that was
really cool you could dump lots of time into these
so we are still here right we are no we what happened why did i
get it i got i got a refresh of the new
stuff no this is was this stuff here before
no this uh there no why why did i come all the way down here
that's weird oh that's like kind of a spoiler no this is not right
this this is like the top of the page here well because this was down
yeah i might have to well we were here i don't think anything was on here i
think this is pretty much everything was on here it's good
all right here you go click click on what you'd want to do
we're only gonna do a couple more of these i think a good stopping point
is six to seven hours of this come back
to it again rogue didn't we already do rogue we
did another version of rogue
i love this multi trip gave 10 thank you for the 10 books multi trip
10 bucks they say i had a dream that you couldn't get any of these dos
games to work and got really frustrated and just streamed
mordhau instead that feels like it could have been real
very real what a lame dream what do you mean that was
that's cool all right let's do rogue here's the plan all right listen
here we're gonna do we're gonna play rogue then i'm going to get the stunt
man game to work then we're gonna do a final vote
for jazz jack rabbit then i'm gonna wind the stream down okay okay let's
open up rogue and we're gonna do this again absolutely
this is a lot of fun i'm having a great time it's a fucking blast i love
seeing all this old weird shit and all these old classic games so
let's open up rogue and give it a try i'm gonna have to learn this one's
probably real quick because i we're just doing this again
uh rogue adventure game made possible by public domain by the code busters
significant buster contributions by ricky
thank you ricky 1984 what's the rogue's name
barney it's a happy face look at that face
you found 45 gold pieces what is this door is there like a help ace a
select item to eat escape to cancel oh it's gonna do that every time in the
d there's something there already enter illegal command uh is it like a f1
oh god rename something inventory for possessions
the ne key supervisor key enter key down right up down rest go up a
staircase drop object dare find something read paper throw
something zap with a wand where's open door put on ring
run down and left search for a trap door secret s
there's more zap i have to try it let e e what do i do how do i stop
e from getting me e every time i move it moves get away
from me oh shit it comes s this the snake
swings and misses you you scored an excellent hit on the
snake you defeated the snake the emu scored an
excellent it's an emu i killed the emu all right what is
you have two rations oh here comes h you found 21 gold what do i do about
h s h e e h s zap him i don't have zap which
direction you don't have anything appropriate
the hobgoblin misses you which direction you don't have anything
you swing and miss the hobgoblin the hobgoblin misses you
you've injured the hobgoblin you've defeated the hobgoblin
you now have leather armor c e hit the emu
defeated the emu and achieved the rank of guild novice
for gold a plus one plus one mace a plus one plus zero 29 plus zero plus
zero d f no i i guess kind of put on the
bow please specify a letter between a and f
what c a a b which object do you want to
wield a you're now wielding two rations of
food okay it's a long hallway b oh b i'm gonna get ambushed from e
you don't hit the emu the emu doesn't hit you you don't hold on
d you are now wielding a one one mace
okay kill the emu what's b why is it standing still
you don't hit the bat do you swing and miss the bat
the bat misses you you miss the bat the bat barely misses you
you miss the bat the bat i'm just like swinging violently trying to
grab it excellent hit on the bat bats dead
emu wars okay the kestrel hit you you don't hit the kestrel
you excellently hit the kestrel gold pieces and a magenta potion how do i use
it pew to drink you feel stronger what
bulging muscles it makes you bigger well i've explored everything
now how do you go down the stairs oh okay
you now have scale mail d b plus one ring mail
scale mail drop the scale man i'll pick it up
where select item now that's willed tab capital w you're already wearing
some you'll have to take it off first
drop well drop the t t which direction what
i threw the mace that's throw capital t
you used to be wearing a plus one ring armor you aren't wearing any armor okay
now where the scale mail all right we did it
we put it on uh-oh he just kind of appeared in nowhere
i wonder if my health is down there defeat the kestrel
you don't hit the ice monster you swing and hit the ice monster you
defeated the ice monster what can i do with gold is there
like a shop or something you found 51 gold and an emu
dead in one hit and a slime mold this is a cute little game you now have
a scroll titled miv fug jug finque
okay i don't speak that language apparently i'm gonna have to learn that
language at some point hobgoblin is dead there's a
a black potion um can i how do the bat has injured you
you don't hit the bat hit the bat uh how do i
select item to quaff you can't move you can move again you don't what's going
on it's paralysis potion of paralysis now i
know what it is okay cool got the gold let's keep going i mean
i'm just gonna go till i lose you know why not this is the last one
anyways before we do the uh jack rabbit in the stuntman
that's how rogue works i like this this is fun
it's fun sort of quickly experiencing games i've never even heard of well i've
heard of this before but i never really was able to play it
i didn't get it a long time ago nothing even here
oh shit i i just opened the door i hit him with the door in the face
you missing the orc the orc misses you you swing and miss the orc
swings and misses you score an excellent hit
that's dark in here that's cool what is this
potion of strength let's go across hobgoblin
oh fuck i'm almost dead i gotta be careful i have four hp
i need to yeah i gotta drink a potion potion of
strength d shit you've injured the cast where
you defeated the casserole where i need to eat food
what do i oh what i eat eat eat uh cancel cancel
no i didn't want to drink that i was hitting c for cancel
like an idiot um with food whatever what the hell's going on
okay i've got two rations of food on this food tastes awful
well it's food it'll keep you going that's all that matters
it's the kestrel all right dark very dark down here
ooh is exit nice make sure i see everything just in case
level three you don't hit the rattlesnake
where am i oh on the bottom left oh shit
this is not good i need to drink a potion i don't hit the rattlesnake
what do i do oh boy i'm gonna die what do we do um
rest in peace barney killed by a rattlesnake 216 au 2019
oh that was today actually he was right in the front door
i couldn't go around him that was cool very very cool
this is that's one hour from now okay so that leaves us with and we're
gonna do this again don't worry we're gonna
try to leave off right where i did i should be able to because i just
was going i was going by like views right
oh we'll just roll the dice every all the time you know there's all kinds of
shit to do all right let's get jack rabbit on the
screen jazz jack rabbit and guys
i've got something for you take a look at the screen right now
there are three jazz jack rabbits two three forget about these those
aren't here this is not here either i literally
typed in jack jazz jack rabbit i typed in
jack rabbit so here's how this is going to work
if this is a dead vote this is a dead vote
i'm only going to consider these three that's it
i'm not going to play a third oregon trail
there is no scrolling so just which which one of the three jazz jack
rabbits do you want to see half of you are just
throwing a bowling ball into the pool that's all right
seems like the original jazz jack rabbit you're pronouncing oregon wrong
oregon oregon yeah it's oregon but it's the oregon trail
that's just kind of how that works in my in my off my tongue there
oregon trail the oregon trail if you put a the in front of it it becomes
oregon for me the oregon trail no it's the oregon
trail oregon oregon oregon nevada nevada
tomato tomato potato potato it's okay
so we are going to do the original jazz jack rabbit i never played it
before i'm interested to see how it is and
then we're going to do the stunt game which i will get the password for or
maybe i'll just guess all right so it's a ninja turtle rabbit
this is raphael epic mega games presents a game by
cliff blisinski cliffy b cliffy b what order info
okay setup options music volume change keys let's see so it's left
cursor left cursor right cursor up like mouse cursor
jump is alt fire is space special is control
okay where do you have to use the mouse
this turtle has kidnapped this rabbit in order to conquer
this planet okay this rabbit to destroy this rabbit this turtle
with this gun to save her and this carrot
welcome to jazz jack rabbit jazz is a speedy colorful action game unlike any
other on the pc in order to play jazz you must understand
three rules run like the wind shoot everything that
moves if you can't shoot it take it if you run into any problems type
help me at the dos prompt this will bring up full troubleshooting
instruction the notorious leader of the turtle
terrorist devin shell has kidnapped the beloved rabbit princess ever ear
long and has inhabited the galaxy with his goons
is all hope lost away enter jazz jack rabbit the galactic rabbit want revenge
and it's your job to extract it you have to save ever along and prevent
devin shell from financing his maniacal plot of turtle elimination
by swiping the goods out from under his slimy beak
this is how you move oh so it is that okay
jump blaster toaster rf missile launcher tnt cycle this is cool
what orbs and or vets for ammo all right i think we get it
oops oh look it's sub badges that's three months this is six months
this is eight months and here's a year if you get even more angry
holistic bunny rabbits wow that's creepy
rabbits revenge gene machine this is like bubsy sonic and the ninja
turtles all had a baby this one's okay you can pick any
level let's just look this turtle terror
loading diamonds level one here we go is there a cut scene
what i'm gonna say is mega man you go really fast
it's so fast really rabbit stink rabbit stink toaster plus toaster
wait what hold on you can combine weapons
toaster plus toaster uh i kind of want to
alt is not a good button to have his jump i couldn't lawbreakers just
be like this yeah i know right cliffy b you should
just remake jazz jack rabbit put him in fortnight wait he has
nothing to do with fortnight anymore does he
but you never had anything to do fortnight to begin with i don't think
he's even at the same i don't think he's even got that same company
i'm just gonna go fast that's what i'm supposed to do right
that's what cliffy like would have wanted right for me to go fast
can't go up there he's not what what no i'm saying
that's not what i mean i mean like in 1989 when this game came out guys
no don't die fuck i'm dead okay try one more time
fast oh no i'm down i'm back to the default blaster again
that's not good is he saying meow definitely that doesn't fit
all right come i gotta get the boss loading come on let me see let me
see a boss i can't pick this up i can't do toaster
plus the machine gun thing music's obnoxious
i can't change it oh missiles these are cool
i can oh there's a switch right okay the controls are really strange
alt is jump space is fire i should just switched them
all right get to dr robotnik there's got to be a speedrunner in this game
it has to be whoa this is cool it is done
which is not as well made and i don't mean that in a mean way
it's also much older than sonic i got the windows noise is that supposed to
happen oh what's that with guns lives
infinite blaster blaster no get uh the game's controlling itself
i have control of the game anymore oh god
move no move this way i can't oh no he's breasted to fortnite
dancing oh i got it no i'm okay he's auto
firing my hands are in the air pre-recorded
gameplay
oh no he proved it it was pre-recorded the whole time
all right let me fight a boss but i have to do your shirt i explained it
earlier i i went in too fast and i
hulked through the head accidentally now we're in 3d
this is some mario kart shit right here oops
i didn't i thought it's okay all right that's enough of this one
that was really fun though that was a good game for ms dos
that was cliffy b's voice wasn't it he's eating a carrot he's gonna say
like what's up dog all right i'll play this level for
30 seconds
electric eyes watch it ooh launcher grenades that's cool
secret wall oh shit i thought i what are you doing
rf missiles oh he won't turn around anymore
uh oh i'm gonna get killed by this little baby turtle
that was weird okay i'm gonna stop all right it's
i don't know why it won't let me move all right there it is
jazz jack rabbit it was cool finally we're going to do a stunt driver
i'm gonna get the code i'm gonna look up what to do
all right so oh jesus christ i'm not gonna how what look at this shit
this is like an ikea blueprint um replace this line with your specific
cd rom driver line you only need to use this line with
dos 6 on a cd rom to book
pre-race setup use this on the racetrack head to head
track instruction course one course quiz before playing the game you'll be asked
to identify a piece of track from one of the five courses
ignore the page reference use your mouse pointer to the correct piece
a 10 g 7 7 hold on let me stunt driver hold on let's
let's do this together course quiz on course two
page 40 on course two what is the piece at location question mark at course two
what is the piece at location i5 course two i5
i can't is it one two three four five it's a straight line
with a little oil can on the right straight line with an oil can on the
right i think it's this one all right here
we go how do you drive i got my hand on it control alt p q r
r is fucked it up it's all right
you're going the wrong way turn the car around
q how do i gear it into got it get it out of neutral i can't put it in
first gear oh no watch out for the skittles
we're in the eminem's candy world oh my god
d s a d f w e w r q
tab shift space press one oh not the candies oh i just ran over
everybody you're going the wrong way still
all right the race can start uh by the way this is just like binaural beats
two i need to go to second gear holy shit that's fast
what happened second gear
marty we're going warp speed marty i don't know about this doc
marty two three i dad's gave me a headache
i have a headache no uh well uh that was that no one more one
more uh no that's a good one to go out on
feed your yahtzee addiction encore encore
no we're gonna do this we're gonna do this like once a week i did i was
i was mcdonald's ba ba ba ba
i'm loving it oh why did i have to go out on that one
that shouldn't have been the one to go out on you could hear halfway
through my voice start to give out on that one you did you
know you know but sometimes you have to commit
even though you know it's like that's this is a stupid reference and no one's
gonna like this it was a nightmare tear joke oh no
oh no i better wake up i gotta wake up no
no not a nightmare tear but uh that's gonna be it i will see you guys
on what's today saturday i'll see you guys on tuesday
tuesday afternoon reno i'm gonna read the bits we'll hang out for a little
bit i'm just for the people that want to
take off but this was a little trial test run to see how fun something like
this would be and there's a lot to still play
i might change up the format a little bit i might pick a screen
and then we have to pick uh like two or three games from that
screen i think that's better that way the scroll can still be there but it
will pop up i mean maybe it'll just after we do three we'll just scroll
instead of rather than just because i feel like maybe
if you want it to scroll you may potentially throw in a vote away to pick
a game that was already on the screen so maybe per eat per screen we would do
three and then i would just scroll down
but you'll see this again we'll probably do it next week we'll do
some other stuff next week too thank you for joining me
i'll see you on tuesday take care much love to you if you're leaving
let's get to the bits let's go to six and a half hours ago here
all the way back all the way back here we are we had
three dollars from mr comcast mr comcast you sure do like to give me a
lot of money how about three and then an option to
scroll that's a good idea too we'll play around with the idea uh
mr comcast hey germa john comcast here so sue me for being thorough
i want to know that you know what the plan is look seriously mate how
many artifacts do we need to steal before you trust me with these jobs
well i just want to make sure you know what's happening we're gonna get
the treasure we're gonna get out of there
and we must get it that's the most important thing so beyond your a
game we go now also make me fight cox in the germa rumble
he's old and fragile and i'll no you guys are gonna be on a tag team
it's gonna be cox and comcast and a tag team
and there's gonna be a major spoiler that i'm not going to say but
something happens in the middle of that fight
just pretend i didn't say anything but thank you uh john comcast
a uh why dna thanks for the 16 dollars
hope you don't die of dysentery i didn't i got dysentery at the end of
the end of the game there but i didn't die
from it i just got it thank you the 16 bucks almost 20
dollars thank you it's a lot of money we also had five
community subs from coal five community subs from big boy
ego thank you guys for your community subs
the great lord walden gave 10 dollars here's 10 dollars for a new shirt you
fucking hobo i'd like it this shirt is it's i
like this shirt this is a sentimental value shirt i
got too many shirts actually kim and i were talking about
this i'm probably we're probably gonna do a donation bag
and give it to do a donation of clothes because i have too many just
random t-shirts and then nice i don't have too many
shirts i have 10 shirts to one pair of
pants to a giveaway on stream no i don't
want anyone to buddy you guys i have my clothes
something about that i don't know but something about that's weird to me
you should sew the collar i don't want to do that i'd rather be able
to put it on two different ways but thank you great lord walden
for the 10 dollars uh zake thank you zake for the 250
hello german 985 just want to share a cute picture of me and my dog
let's take a look uh i this is a interesting picture
it's a very uh is that you in the picture uh
that's interesting it's you and a uh it's you and a dog butt that looks
like an old fucking picture too this this is
like a crumpley crumpley picture what do you mean
what's the thing i don't know he's a baby he's a
baby he's a baby right this is this is not even you and your
dog is this not you and your dog this is no it's definitely you and your
dog just hanging out let's see what it is
thank you for the 250 that's a picture of me
well uh no that's just a boy a boy and his dog hanging out
stop uh thank you for the 250 hey michael thanks with five bucks
here's some dosh for an unchewed shirt
it's not chewed it's it's a little crumbled but that's fine
thank you though michael for the five bucks i'm i'm i'm
gonna replace my shirts with better shirts
okay does that make guys happy uh john cena for life thanks to the
three dollars hey german did you see the final fantasy 7 remake trailer
that recently came out it looks great also did you have uh also did
or have you played any other final fantasy games good keep up the good
work thank you uh i'm actually not really that
interested in final fantasy 7 or the remake
the original one is good but it's not really i wouldn't put that in my
top five top 10 really it's not that i don't think the game is any good
it's just not kind of anything i really
cared that much about it's a great game but
uh final fantasy wise i played the old ones
fantasy one two three uh but for the most part i was a
i'm one of those chrono boomers i'm one of those like chrono
series and hipsters that loves that series more than final fantasy
and every time somebody mentions final fantasy x
final fantasy whatever it doesn't matter i'm always the one that goes
i just wish they would make another chrono god damn it i think it's one
of my favorite series ever i'm a chrono hipster it's not
chrono hipster it's chrono normie wouldn't final fantasy be the normie
and the and chrono trigger be the hipster
chrono trigger has two games final fancy has like
30 there are like 34 final fantasy games
chrono loser no chrono is not mainstream
just because they've re-released it 12 times doesn't mean everybody bought
it but uh yeah i final fantasy is a
cool series i like the original ones i'm not a big fan of the
later ones though just wasn't my thing i hope it's good i hope
final fantasy 7 remake is good i remember when the the movie they did
that weird sequel movie and i remember that was a huge
deal i watched it the uh 3d animated one
that was a huge fucking deal when that came out no not mega mind
it was like final fantasy set advent children there it is yeah that was a
big deal mega mind was bigger well yes his
mind was bigger but thank you john cena for life
hopefully final fantasy 7 remake is good and hopefully lives up to your
expectations hope so hey gnarly thanks for the five
dollars jerma i hate being a goblin give me your beauty tips
um beauty tips let's see eat more uh eat more fish it's good for your
skin talking like oily fish talking salmon
um sardines anchovies make sure you drink enough water
nobody drinks enough water replace two or three
sodas or two or three juices with water drinking up water
um beauty tips get enough sleep try to sleep at least
six hours a night sleep in less than four or five hours a night every night
is just it's not good for you um what else what else what else
stop drinking no no no another one stop drinking so much alcohol
alcohol is good but it really it's like inflammatory like fucking
you drink drink as much as you want if you're of age but
replace replace a couple of beers or some waters
really just actively try to take care of yourself on a day-to-day basis
now that means yes you can eat burger king but if you eat burger king maybe
the next day try to have like a like a salmon
salad with like a bunch a good couple of sides you know just
balance yourself up it's really easy just to order this
same bad shit all the time i do it all i've done it i do i still do it
like balance yourself up and just drink water forehead yeah
uh table row thanks for the 10 bucks table row
hey germa bud you don't need to tell you how many lives you improve thanks
germa i'm honored and thankful that anyone
would ever say something like that thanks
so much if i improve your life just by us hanging out here and playing
games and just broadcasting the video stuff
then i'm thank you that's awesome i hope you
i hope you're doing good but what if you make my life worse
with a smiley now can i get a couple of germa pops in the chat please i
just want to see them because i just put it up there today if you didn't
know if you just got to the channel here
but thank you table row also we had a bunch of 50 dollars
50 dollar donations come in 55 dollars from cure
50 dollars from lacronda 53 dollars from vilemi 50 dollars again from vilemi
130 103 bucks from vilemi total 50s all around
from lacronda a lot of money came in over the course of like an hour
there so thank you guys all of you uh the jack thank you for 250 who do
you work for credit two doopie foop on discord we have
we thought we saw this earlier i was saying you even got like the
bump on my right side of my nose or left side of my nose actually it's
mirrored that was fucking hysterical that was
the funniest thing i've seen in a while
the ghost ride the batmobile into a fucking sit it was just
unbelievable that you could do that thank you though we also had
250 from frody and weapon what the hell
is a vodka pineapple and where can i get one also happy saturday
love these ms dos games uh germa heart and then germa pop can we get a couple
of germa pops please thank you a vodka pineapple is pineapple
juice and vodka that's pretty much it or you can do
pineapple juice orange juice and vodka as well but it's just pineapple
juice and vodka it's pretty good if you like pineapple juice happy
saturday to you as well and i also enjoy the ms dos
it's a before time right great canadian fuck club
coming in with five community subs the fuck club that has returned
they have gifted 747 subs to this channel
they are responsible for 747 subs that's insanity does that count
right now or is that total forever always
is that what you currently have right now i think that's yeah i think that's
total i don't think that's um like current right like
whatever the case is it's 750 fucking subs 757
thank you so much for your insane contributions
and thank you for the five community subs here right now thank you
it's frack oh oops oh great canadian fuck club
sorry germa lied about wait when thank you k
thank you kd econ war econ war kdecon war i think that's how i'm saying it
thanks for the ten dollars ten bucks hey germa i don't usually have the
money for a regular subscription but i came into a bit of extra cash and
wanted to show some love just graduated college and i've been
stressed trying to find work but i always come to your streams to
chill out with a stream by a genuinely good and relatable dude
with a good head on his shoulders stay frosty out there germa well
congratulations for getting through college it can be rough
it's work it's a lot of work but gratz on that first of all and second
of all i i'm i'm a good and
relatable dude with a good head on his shoulders
my mother would love you
thank you for the incredibly kind words i'm gonna stay as frosty as i can
thank you for the support and thanks for hanging out
thank you for the ten dollars son of janova three dollars from son of janova
hi i made this did you though mario on the outside
mario on the inside i promise it's not a dog asshole
mario on the outside mario on the inside
i didn't even know that that game existed what a cool game
mario has been able to stay so relevant forever
they should we should just like elect mario to congress
mario normie a there's no there's no such thing
no no no no no no there's no such thing
that's gonna happen in a video game movie just watch mario's not a u.s
citizen he's a world citizen he will govern us all from his
ivory tower chrono mario you guys are funny
uh thank you dais mortay for the 250 hello jeremy
you've kept making strange noises during yesterday's stream
so i thought i'd throw them in this song i threw together in an hour
enjoy germapop
so after tomorrow's ace attorney stream we will pick back up on
wednesday
that is an oof that's a big oof right there that's a big one
hey okay but what about sam and max give me some credit for saying i told
you guys i was playing max for a while and i kept put it off but then
i did it and we were doing it we traded ace attorney for sam and max
you can play both i could i could
but will i no yes i don't know i don't think i'm gonna play ace attorney let me
just rip the band-aid off i don't think i'm gonna do it
i i checked it out i don't know if that's a game that i want to stream
i'm see i ripped just take it off rip the band-aid off yeah didn't we have
this discussion already yeah but you know
something a lot of people on this channel
there are thousands of people and maybe you didn't hear it and maybe you
don't know you know it's it's not easy to keep up with everything
it's not that many ego maniac what what well that's not true do my eyes
deceive me you're crashing the stock market
sell all stocks quickly before they go to zero but i don't i don't
think so i don't want to keep putting the
carrot in front of everybody maybe next time maybe next time no no
i invested in germa and i'm down 3k did you invest in key wall like i told
you to remember i told you what did i say
specifically put all your money into key well i said that
that key will key well stock is up like fucking 500 i told you
you should have listened to me did you play the game yes i did
i did play the first ace attorney for maybe
15 20 minutes i'll tell you i'll tell you something that
i really don't i didn't i didn't like i don't know if you can turn this
off but the screen flash it seems like every
10 seconds there's a like a white flash on the screen
and i it was kind of giving me a headache i'm just i'm just being
completely honest during like the dialogue it's just
like white flash white flash white flash white flash
it's dramatic and it's kind of just getting flashed in the face
that's why no that's not why i just there's somebody asked if i
tried it and i did that's not why i wasn't going to
play it just was it seemed like it seemed like it was going to take a
long time to and it would go and almost solely
relied on the dialogue which i would have to read
and instead of something like sorcery which reading was
i could kind of put my own spin on it and we could choose different things to
do it it's more of just a kind of a visual novel
i would much rather play that comfy like under my blankets
with a t and just sit there silent and like investigate then
stream something like that is what i kind of came to the
determination of but yeah i i don't want to
you know obviously that i don't think it's a bad series that's no way
no way just don't think i want to stream that game
or the series i'm sorry i'm sorry do i play games without streaming them
yeah i actually just played forager for a little while
for like four or five hours over the last like couple weeks
it's fun i don't really you know talk that much about the random stuff
i play off stream he's cheating on us how do you
find the time to do it i uh it really depends like
sometimes well 90 of every game i play is on
stream but i only have a few hours sometimes
just jump into i actually restarted sakiro
not yesterday the day i mean like a couple then maybe like three or four
weeks ago i like restarted it and played it
like kind of casually off and on to do the other
stuff and i'm just still kind of letting it play out
does it feel weird to not talk while you play no not really
the game has no replayability well it doesn't have
in the traditional sense no but there's a
couple of endings that you there's like three or four bosses that i
didn't see so this content that i didn't get to
play and i would get to play it if i did
through go went through one more time right there's something like that has
like four or five different endings there's like
other content and bosses and stuff that you can get it with a different
stuff maybe from what i understand that is
replayability yeah but not in like the the dark souls kind of
replayability where there's the bosses are oh you can go and do
whatever you want but you can pick a different weapon and take a
different class and try a different spell and
you can replay through sakiro a few times maybe twice three times maybe if
you want to get all the endings and but the game stays
the same unless you know obviously i don't want to
keep i don't want to keep having i want spoilers to not be here
anyone that hasn't played it yet but there's like three or four what plus
endings right i've ever played enter the gungeon
yes i have depends on how much you like it whatever floats your boat
oh yeah if you like something and you do it and you want to play it
through more than three four five six ten times how
you know it's it's your time and it's your money right like if you buy
something and you want to spend the time doing it
absolutely is this the is this vod worth watching
absolutely yes all right bye sure is it vod worth watching
we got a question here hey hey hey what wait wait no you're memeing me here
what about we have a lot of fun with that what about
batman all right just skip the batman part
and then rewind and watch all the rest of it because it's good
i can't believe i i clicked a porn game i actually did that tonight
holy shit well it was text only and these are our imaginations and chat
really had to use their imaginations because they didn't get to see anything
no but all jokes aside i i loved it i had a lot of fun tonight
and we're gonna definitely do it again so yes go watch the bot don't
come on uh hey thank you too uh we got multi-trip earlier thanks to
the 10 bucks multi-trip i had a dream that you couldn't get any of
the dos games to work and got really frustrated
and streamed more to how instead that would have happened that's probably
exactly and now we probably just went to sam and max if this was a catastrophe
stream i would have just went right to episode three
in a second it would have taken one second but thank you the 10 dollars
thank you the jack for the 250 if you decide to give jazz jack
rabbit 2 a try there's a fan project called jazz
jack rabbit 2 plus that adds a bunch of fixes and
quality of life improvements including xbox controller support
to like a 25 year old game holy shit how do people even do this
some big brains out there i will definitely keep that in mind though
i guess we'll be doing this again i got sam and max in the back pocket
always but i'll keep that in mind thanks
to the 250 the jack uh freudian weapon thanks to the 250
i'll be honest i've never played chrono trigger
but i've had so many friends geek out about it that i feel inclined to
check it out sometime it is the best turn-based rpg that
has ever been made it's just it just is it was very well
before its time i think it's the best turn-based rpg
i i that's i don't that's just my opinion
here comes a back pedal no no back pedal
i think chrono trigger is the best rpg turn-based
remember we're not i'm not talking action rpg that's diablo 2
i'll do it for you turn-based rpg chrono trigger
uh action rpg diablo 2 what are the rpgs are there role playing rpg
no um what's another what's another one mmo rpg
oh that's a tough one i'd have to say world of warcraft
the frozen throne wrath of the lich king that's the best mmo rpg
what's the best fps rpg uh fps rpg fps rpg let me think about this
i mean they really only are a kind of a handful is like the fallout there's
like borderlands which i would not put borderlands even on that list
i don't think so um i don't think borderland i don't think borderlands
is like a top like two or three i i wouldn't
put borderlands in the top three for me
for first person shooter rpgs i put new vegas would be there
but new vegas is also not you can do that in third person
um might and magic dark messiah yeah that's number one
bioshock is yeah that's not really an rpg cyberpunk
well when cyberpunk comes out i think all bets are off borderlands
borderlands 1 was cool borderlands 2 was all right it just they kind of did
the same game three times they did that like borderlands pre
sequel and it's just like what the fuck are you doing
and then borderlands 3 it's just like all right it's i
i like borderlands 1 like borderlands 2 it's just kind of like i
it's we're kind of if you like just loot
boxes and shooting and different combinations and yeah it can be
addicting i just kind of got sick of it after
the second game i have heard the telltale borderlands
game is that weirdly enough i have been told that
tales from the borderlands is the best borderlands game
i've been told that a couple of times yeah i've been told that at
least twice it's easily the best telltale game
yeah um i'm trying to think of what other
first-person rpgs exist it's definitely dark messiah
that game is just so hilariously interesting
um a skyrim but i don't know if that does do the bethesda games
count because they don't they're not first person was dark
messiah actually a good game it seemed like a meme no it is it
i mean it is a meme but it's still a really fun game
fallout 76 those servers still on i'm actually serious
i don't know if they are or not uh we got some news today out of
uh the game development uh nhl 2k11 nba 2k14
fantasy star online 2 and fallout 76 have had their servers
discontinued today oh fuck really that's too bad
what's my favorite animal armadillo that's an easy one next question
but yeah there's a few games classic wow
yeah it's gonna be fun i think unless if blizzard could just
fuck it all up my faith in blizzard is
right at the front door it's just right outside at this point
it's like if you all right you come are you gonna what are you doing
here come on in show put put the put the
like roadmap of your game up on the glass
before i let you in the store just go to my like you know just
hold it up
all right come on in road maps are a lie
no blizzard i think blizzard's in an interesting scenario here
where they've made like two or three really really like bogus bonehead
plays in the last three four years that
wow classic needs to be good because they had
war warcraft 3's remake and wild classic coming back need to be pretty
good or they've got to announce something
that they're working on because a lot of people are not
happy it's going to be wild classic yeah but
i weren't they talking about how they were thinking of changing some stuff
weren't they saying that they were changing things and they were trying to
make it like more streamlined they they did mention that they were
going to do stuff to it right it's i don't think it's just wow
patch 1.2 so who knows they might they went back on that did they did
they go back on that i don't know we'll see what they end up
doing diablo is doomed wow expansion's bad
hawts is dead overwatch is kind of hanging on
overwatch is on death's door it's a shame yeah
they just they dropped the ball at least a few times
they kind of pulled a valve but valve just before they made a bunch
of bad plays just like forfeited the game you know what i
mean wasn't these glasses although valve
is slowly slowly they've been working kind of behind the scenes here
with this whole vr stuff and they got at least three or four games in
development here that are going to be exclusive to
the index right yep yep fuck me right i think i'll
get the htc vibe all of a sudden hey the index is
coming out it's gonna have like three exclusive valve games
they're not exclusive thank god i was so scared there for a second
but valve got to that point where people were like hey what the hell's
going on here what's this what's this thing that you
released that i'm not very happy with they were just like i quit i'm done
making games forever bye and then it's like
slam the door and like put put up like an out of order sign
blizzard had that same scenario except they were like what about this game
uh that's i don't like that what about this one this one's that kind of stupid
too no we don't want that what about this
one this one sucks no we don't want that either
and now they've kind of buried themselves hey yeah we gotta go grocery
shopping oh shit that's right we're gonna go grocery shopping
we're almost done we're almost done uh but
gabe newell actually said something like people not liking mass effect
three caused him to stop deving on half like three really
valve doesn't have investors to answer to so they don't have to
pressure to output games yeah i think i think valve made the
right call with that because if they didn't think they
could make good products then they weren't going to make them
i think that's been their mo for a long time it's kind of it's
sucks that you don't we don't we don't get it left for dead three we
don't have like a big huge tf3 or team fortress
update right that's changes the game that much
we got artifact but i don't i don't play i don't that doesn't do it for
me at all it's a card game i don't really play them
and then they they just kind of went into the business side of games which
you could argue is you know might not been the greatest
thing in the grand scheme of things because that's how we kind of invented
the whole open boxes for money thing that was
valve valve kind of paved the way for that
the open up loot boxes for cash was like a team fortress and counter
strike thing tf2 crates and yeah even they took
that from like what those old japanese
mobile games right fifa yeah fifa with the card packs
but not like a box with stuff in it be like the card packs were just uh you
opened up card packs right fifa is patient zero but valve
really perfected that open up the box and get an item for the game
it's the same it is the same idea but the fifa cards didn't affect
anything in the game right did they did they wait hold on the
fifa cards i thought it was like you just opened up
cards and had like a card collection with like golds and stuff
you actually do you that's how you get the players
oh my god fifa is paid to win no really wow holy shit
okay well that's unbelievable but uh the ea fifa even as early as
you know team fortress that all the kind of open up boxes get new weapon or new
skin right they expire oh my goodness that's evil
if they expire you have to keep opening them
holy shit but i think that will they'll turn
well there'll be a turnaround here regardless of all the you know the
crazy fucked up shit that's happening in this industry right now
in the last four or five years and there'll be a
turnaround there'll be some there'll be there'll be some new
shit that's interesting that i think that some of these companies
are going to start to realize that people
are annoyed by this kind of behavior they don't like this shit nobody likes
this shit so unfortunately the people that
are playing the games that have been playing games for the last five to
ten years kind of had to be the the guinea pigs for all this stuff
until everyone was like hey could you stop doing this to us please
oh shit i'm sorry i didn't think that you don't like this
fucked up kind of behavior yeah i guess we'll stop
did you beat mario and checkers yet i smoked him
people love this shit it makes all the money yeah but
people like to gamble too you know it it's all that's all it is it
scratches the same itch as pulling like a slot machine lever why
how do you think casinos are so popular
it's the same idea a potential random generated thing where you could
get something awesome or something terrible
you're the expert on gambling i see i'm telling you i know
but i uh i gotta get out of here gotta go to the grocery store before they
close so let's get through the last uh handful
of bits let's get the credits on the screen too
we can sit here and talk for hours about uh the state of the game
industry i'm not necessarily an expert on all
this but i do have some opinions as you've heard
but get the credits on the screen here come all the new subs and all the
resubs for today thank you everybody there were a lot just don't play bad
games but that was a big one that was
like three or four at the same time does somebody think it was vinnie's
birthday today i mean if it's vinnie's birthday we're
gonna is it vinnie is it actually vinnie's
birthday or is somebody just uh somebody's messing around actually
vinnie's birthday is it for real can we can we
confirm that before i send 1500 people to this channel to say
happy birthday google it but okay what is vinnie
vine sauce's birthday holy shit it is well not yet not yet tomorrow it's
tomorrow well i'm not i'm not gonna see him
tomorrow does it just say happy birthday tomorrow
he has 7k viewers he doesn't care about your 50
viewer raid jesus uh it's actually like 14
1500 i think that's a lot more than 50
oh no it's in new york right so 10 11 12 oh okay yeah no it is
new york happy birthday to vinnie it's it's it's 12 it's think that one
o'clock in the morning happy birthday vinnie
50 viewer raid geez man some of you guys are vicious
all right so we're gonna raid vinnie but we're gonna do get the last bit
so there's like two or three more uh but the chrono trigger kind of
tangent was from frody and weapon that got us on there 250
play chrono trigger it's an amazing game snooze and copter thanks to the
250 i know i could have put this in recommended
but i want to hear direct thoughts on it in chats too i really want to see you
stream a game you know and played before
and just show us that haven't played its secrets and whatnot
just guide us through and show us why you enjoy it so much
games like resident evil 4 chrono trigger whatever game is up
in your top 10 i mean i could do that
if people really wanted me to do that i could do it
play like mario rpg and show you everything and why i think it's so
cool and fun play chrono trigger it's it's an
interesting idea that'd be cool it'd be different that
sounds like fun yeah let's we'll plan on it let's plan
on it could be nostalgic mario rpg i would probably start with
mario rpg that's my favorite game ever made
so i would probably start there the drama classics
well i didn't make them but that's a great recommendation thank you
snooze and copter i've toyed with it we've talked
about it a few times i just never pulled the trigger on it because i
just don't know if people want to see somebody
just go oh i know what's here i know what's over here go look this is go
watch this part hey you should watch this part of the movie this is where
this is the part where you get to where he dies
you know i feel like i'd be that guy at the movie that tells you the cool
parts to watch but you know it is um it is what it
is maybe i'll take the uh take the dive
the neverhood neverhood's hard to get to work past a certain point
i just wish they would release it remake it somebody got gg is not on
top of that that's surprising but fraud in weapon
thanks for the 250 how dare you tell me to take care of myself the nerve of you
to be nice to me but seriously i love you streams and
everything germa pop here here thank you uh
froding you've been around for a long time you've given a lot of money
big part of the stream community especially when we hang out here at
the end so thank you and of course i'm gonna be nice to
you the nerve of me how dare i and fraud in weapon 250 one
more thing the bit readings are probably my favorite part of these
streams because of all the funny jokes chat comes up with
and i guess in germa heart and germa pops for chat germa heart germa pop
yeah no i like the ending of the streams it's like a 45
30 to 50 minute experience where chat slows down we can talk about
stuff we can people write funny shit easier for me to read it i agree i
also love it too and that is gonna be my time i
will see you guys next week on tuesday no no not tuesday wait
saturday today's saturday right yeah okay i see you on tuesday
tuesday the 14th get some rest we next week we've got more salmon
max to do we're gonna do some more ms dos games
and i'm gonna throw in something that we haven't done we've been doing a
lot of um the last like four or five streams
we've been doing a lot of uh continuation of series like dreams
sam and max so i might throw in something else
kind of like the labo well i'm not gonna do the labo but
like something like that where it's not like a series but take
care yourself see you tuesday take care everybody thank you for
watching have a great rest of your evening and a great rest of your
weekend i'm going to raid vinnie let's do stream legends and then
we're gonna raid vinnie tell him happy birthday from the
germamites and let's do stream legends too while we're at it
oh i can't it hasn't been 24 hours since my last stream
and i'm about to go grocery shopping so i'm definitely gonna forget
when i get back to do that so uh if i remember i'll do it
if not then i'll try to remember happy birthday vinnie raid what the
raid vinesauce take it easy guys see you tuesday ta ta for now