I want you guys to tell me if you can hear the music that is about to start playing.
So let me know, because otherwise there will be no sound. So, ready? Let me know if you
can hear the medic music. Oh yeah. You hear that? Good to know, because that means I set
the audio cable thing up correctly. So that's good to know. Loud and clear, Berga Boy. Alright.
So tonight, first of all, happy Saturday. Hope you guys are having a fantastic Saturday.
Second of all, of course, Grandpa is tonight. There's a lot of things going on tonight.
There's a lot of things going on in the world of Jeremy. Did a video, doing a live stream.
Grandpa's is tonight on Machinima. A lot of crazy stuff. So I've been all over the place
today. Flomi, let him explain himself. Let him explain himself. Alright, Flomi, you have
ten words to explain yourself. Ten words. And ten words or less. Two plus two is four.
Alright, so let me just... Where's my phone? Oh, I always am losing my damn phone. It always
happens. Hold on. I think it's across the room. There it is. Hello, phone. Alright. Oh, if
you're watching this on YouTube, like eventually when I upload this tomorrow, if you're watching
this on YouTube, go ahead and you can skip like two or three minutes while I set this
up. I know I put an annotation there, but sometimes people go, whoa, when do you start?
So go ahead and skip a couple minutes if you're watching this on the YouTubes. Okay. Twitter.
Hello, Twitter. So yeah, Team Fortress 2 and Binding of Isaac. And you're probably wondering
why am I playing that crazy, ridiculous, disturbing game. Well, because there's DLC for it coming
out in like a couple days. So I want to get back into it because I love that game. So
let's see. Streaming TF2 and Binding of Isaac. Oh, come hang on ya. HTTP colon slash slash
www.twitch.tv. Don't ask me why I always do this on my phone. I just like don't feel
like opening up another tab. Like it's probably faster if I did it on my damn computer. It
is that. It's that. Alright. Ready to go here in a second. Just going to put a Steam message
out to the Steam community. Have to be, oh my, oh what, new name apparently. Massive
Bus Accident is my name on here. Well, that's one way to have your name be. Whatever. Massive
Bus Accident. Oh, weird. Streaming TF2. Oh, why do I think that's so funny? Oh, screaming
now. Colon slash slash. Streaming. Actually, I should put this here. Oh, man. TF2 and Binding
of Isaac. Streaming. Yeah, open mouth, faceless party. 15 minutes. Alright. Oh, God. Oh, no.
Oh, no. I just like dumped a drink on my floor. Oh, God. Oh, you know what? It's staying there.
It's staying there. I'll deal with it later. God. What a pro. Okay. There's like a cup
of milk on my floor right now. That is not cool. Whatever. The show must go on. Let's
do it. That's that. And here's the tweet. I can't believe that. Milk doesn't body good.
Unless you dump it on your floor. Done. Geez Louise. Does that work? Let's find out. Nice
like Avatar. Alright. We're good to go. We're good to go. Okay, now I'm going to make the
chat so I can see it. Good Lord. Well, that was not cool. Let's get a server with zero
people in it. And my TF2 server is coming along. I know I said last week it was going
to be done this week, but it's not. It's close though. I have to talk to the guys at gameservers.com.
We have to have a meeting. Some type of meeting. What's up dudes? If you're just joining us,
I just spilled a cup of milk on my floor and it's going to stay there until I'm done screaming.
Hope I don't like ruin anything. If it like seeps over near my computer, that's going
to be really bad. It might have to be like an emergency stop. Alright, let's go to...
No, no toot fort. No, Dustbowl. We played Dustbowl too much. How about... I'm a gravel
pit. I'm okay with gravel pit. Let's do gravel pit. This is the server. Ladies and gents,
head there. Gravel pit. Yeah, Dustbowl is a little overplayed, but I love it though.
I love Dustbowl. That's because I'm an old school TF2 player. I mean I've been playing
since 2007 and I remember that. There used to only be Dustbowl, two fort, turbine, gravel
pit. There was only six maps when TF2 launched. Two fort, Dustbowl, gravel pit, turbine. What
were the other two maps? What the hell were the other two maps? Can somebody in the chat
throw that out there? Oh, well and granary, right? Those are the only six that came out
at release. Let's go blue. Let's go attacking tonight. I feel like being an attacker. No,
we're going to start with medic. I'm starting with the medic. Alright, let's get the audio
good here. Game audio good. Voice audio is it? Are we getting overpowered? You can never
tell. Oh yeah, high five baby. Alright, let's push this point boys. If anyone wants to duel
me I will accept it. I'm not going to promise I will win the duel to anyone watching the
stream but I will try my best. I gotcha, I gotcha, I gotcha. Follow me doctor. We go.
We need this uber or what? Are we good? We're good to go? You know what? I'm going to go
not that way. I had to use it. I had to use it. Oh no. Oh no. Oh I shouldn't have left.
That wasn't my bad. I screwed that up. James A-hole. We're okay. That guy's going to try
shooting the window. We got it, we got it, we got it. Oh give me that sandwich. Spy,
where are you? Bastard. There you are. We got to get out of here. We're going to get
destroyed. Thank you for saving my life. I don't want to say your name Holland. Very
quiet. You're very quiet. What? What? What? I knew I got him. Alright, let's push it.
I love your outfit man. I think I said this before last stream but your outfit is unbelievable.
It's when we... You know I'm going to protect this guy too. Because for fun. Oh attack.
Oh it's the guy I'm dueling. Oh god. That's a spy. That's a spy. Oh get away. Oh damn
it. I didn't even know that was the guy I was dueling. I just walked up and punched
him in the face. Yeah if you got a duel throw it my way dude. I will duel you. Just a positive
elutely. We're going to get A. Let's get A. Oh I have to duel you. I don't even know
if I... I don't think I have any duels. I think I gave them all away. Here we go again. Give
me that uber. I'm going to be able to push this. Alright crowbar. Let's see what you've
got baby. No. No. No. Where are you? Oh no. Get out of my way. Okay. Hi guys. Hello. Get
away. Damn it. Oh damn it. Do you see like that whole group of people that were running
up the stairs? That was terrifying. Good morning. Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. People need heals. Oh burger boy. The dump machine. Oh no. Oh no. Two other
people to heal. I need the quick fix. Oh my god he's coming after me still. Oh my god
how did he get me? Dude that guy was like in a bubble. He was in a bubble of invincibility
right there. You know I'm going quick fix. Do I even have the quick fix? After my backpack?
Oh no that's right I unboxed a strange one. Forgot. I unboxed this. Might as well put
it to use right? Let's go scout I want to be able to run fast. Run. Run. Run. Run. Quick
fix. Oh yeah. Quick fix. Get him. No. No don't kill the medic. Come here. Run to me.
Oh my god die you bastard. Oh my god dude. How many hits did that take? I got a new one.
Let's push through this. Let's push through this nonsense into the quick. Quick fix over.
Oh what you know about the quick fix over. Come here. Oh you jumped away from me. What
the hell? Nice job guys. Good game. Good game. Jerma do you like the yogscast? I don't really
watch it to be honest. The yogscast is kind of like a minecraft thing isn't it? Or at
least predominantly minecraft? See I have no idea. This is me just I have absolutely
no idea. They seem like nice guys. They seem like cool guys. You know I don't. I'm changing.
I want the critscreek. I want the critscreek. Can I get it charged before? Well I really
I don't have an opinion on it to be honest. Oh I can't high five you. Let's go burger
boy. Optimus Prime is like standing there like a statue. Alright burger boy you better
be ready to unleash hell on the world. After this critscreek I'm going to. He's dying
over here. Alright burger boy. Watch out burger boy. I'm holding on to this. I'll come back
to you. Overheel peeper. Spy here. Spy here. Spy. Put your thing down. Am I a fan of Shibby
2142? I love Shibby 2142. He's like a friend of mine. He's like a good bud of mine. You
are. Not real. Oh he's still here. He's still alive. Me and Shibby 2142 are broskies. Just
shoot a bunch over there. Oh my god. Never mind. I do know Star as well. I'm not as
close with Star as I am with Shibby but I know Star. We talk. Speaking of Star. We may
actually be doing videos together sometime soon. Sometime very very soon. He's a cool
guy though. Stimmy D? Yes. I know Stimmy D. Stimmy D is a bro. Pretty much if you can
name me like a Team Fortress 2 channel I probably know them. Like I probably like know who they
are and I've probably spoken to them at least once or twice. Stay alive derp. Do you know
German985? No. Who's that? He sounds like a real loser. Get rid of this guy. Get rid
of this guy. That's a spy. What? Alright so my brain just exploded. I walked towards that
engineer the real one and then I turned around and I thought it was him again and I thought
it was real so I got fell. That was a good spy. Why are we screaming? But to answer the
question yes I know most of the Team Fortress 2 channels. I don't know all of them. I mean
there are probably a few that I've never really had a conversation with or something but for
the most part I've had a conversation with all of them. Alright that's a spy. No it's
just a dump machine burger boy. No stay alive dude. I got you. Oh the medic chain. Oh my
word. I'm getting a little bit of trouble here. I shouldn't be walking out that far.
Oh just give me one more. I use it? Yes. Oh everyone died. I gotta use it. Oh crit rockets
everywhere. Spiders ugh. I hate spiders. They scare me. Alright I'm gonna go to... do I
even... I don't think I even have a Huntsman. No I don't. My Huntsman's gone. Oh forget
it then. Wait wait wait what the hell was that? What? What? Oh hey I'm just the floating
sniper head. There we go. That was weird. Let's go scout. All defaults. Uh no I'm alright.
Optimus Prime. I'm cool. Not right this second. Maybe after when it's all said and done. But
for now I want to focus on the Zestreem. Just give me a strafe thank you. Yeah we'll do
it in a minute thanks. You know what I want? I want a strained Huntsman. Oh crap. Ah still
alive. Is there even a strained Huntsman? Can you even get that? Ah damn it. They have a
much is a strange Huntsman? 40 keys? It's 40 keys for a strange Huntsman? What? Oh my god.
What crate do you get it in? What do you... crate number 40? Wow man. Wow. It's a salvaged
crate. Oh it's a salvaged crate. It's one of like the rare ones. That's insane. 40 keys.
If I get a strange Huntsman I know I'm gonna keep it. That's crazy. What's up Millennium
Boy exoskeleton bug body? Just landed on his head. I got blowed up. I got blowed up. Oh
sorry Millennium Man. Yeah it's gonna be fun. Well after this round Gold Chain servers.
Can I... I don't want to use the pistol. Oh I still have the Criticola. Let's put it on.
Yeah I love all the scatter guns. Except for the Force of Nature it's not my forte. I'm
not a big fan of it. Let's see if we can't crit some people. Oh my god. That was a death
wish. I just wanted to see how many hit markers would just pop up. I don't even think I have...
I don't have... I gave away my backpack. That's the only option I have right now. Where's my...
What happened to my Mad Bill? Oh right. I probably gave that away. Yeah I gave that away as well.
Let's close this out boys and girls. Potentially. I want to get that good couple kills with this
thing Jake. That's a death wish. I'll go the other way. I shall go the other way. Anybody
over here? Not that I can see. Anyone gonna come out this way? Oh god. I don't think that guy...
I didn't even see him. Run away! Oh my god. See getting stuck just like saved my life right there.
I would have got shot right in the back. I would have got shot right in my behind. Crap.
I'm bumping into somebody. Bumping into somebody. Yep there he is. Help me! Wow! The dead ringer.
Anybody? Anybody? Oh nine damage. Thank god I did nine damage. Oh man this is bad news. Bad news
right here. What am I thinking? Oh god. I tied it up at the very end. Oh my god. Right at the very end
I tied it. Holy crap. Alright good game guys. We are going to change servers now. So thanks guys
jumping in this one. Don't want anyone. This... I gotta clean this milk up. I gotta clean this mad milk up.
Viaduct? No that's... I don't know where that is. Five gorge. Could be cool. What else we got?
Granary? I might be feeling granary right now. I think I'm feeling granary guys. Sawmill or granary?
Alright. Sawmill or granary? Hmm. Granary it is. We're doing granary. In the reddit server apparently.
Copy that. Here you go. There's the new server. Granary is one of those maps that you never feel
like playing on it but once you're actually playing on it you have a good time. I don't know why. Every
single time I play granary it's like oh do I want to play granary? I don't think so. But then when I
actually get on it it's like oh this is fun. Oh it just changed to well. Well that's cool. I feel the
same way about well though to be honest. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Here we go. Here we
go. I'll go red because I was on blue last time. Maybe not. And maybe so. Nope. Let me join red.
This time we're gonna play demo. Default demo man. Okay. No no no no no no no no. Strange lock
and load. Almost forgot. I almost forgot. Mission begins in one second. One. Go! No millennium man.
Get a better internet. Let's see. Can I kill somebody? Oh man. Millennium man. Will I be
selling admin on my server? No. I plan on just having people be able to play and I'm sure that
if you play there for long enough and you're a good supporter of the server I would just give it to
you. You wouldn't have to pay for it. Save your money. That was a bad jump. And now I'm gonna die
like instantly. Where is everybody? Where is everybody? Whoa whoa whoa whoa. He's behind us.
He's dead now. I thought he was gonna walk out the door. It's alright. Let me out of here. Oh no. Oh
no. What's going on? No. I'm gonna drown. Oh my god. I really thought I was gonna drown right there
guys. I'll die. Watch out behind us. Behind us. Yikes. I got wrecked right when I got over here.
Damn it. Oh my god. I didn't expect this. Oh I didn't. I didn't even look. I should have been
looking. I'm an idiot. It's my bad. Top isn't it? Nice job guys. Nice job. Gentlemen and ladies.
Good job. Gentle ladies and gentlemen. Oh who's that? Who is that? Who am I doing a repression
up? Oh jump. Mission begins in 30 seconds. We're going across the top. Oh my god. Look who it is
ladies and gentlemen. Burger boy with like a chocolate melted in his mouth. Oh what am I
doing? I shouldn't have came this way. Why is that up here? Why is that up here? Who got up here?
What? How? That must have been from the last round. Oh I'm never gonna hit him. Oh he just like jumped
into that. Where's my spray? I want a spray. Come on walk all over this. Come on. Come on. Oh let me get him.
Well at least we got it. It's a pallet. Go this way. Go this way. Go this way. Careful for spies.
That might be a spy. I think it was. Yes it was. Cartoons. Cartoons. Cartoons. Be careful. We're
entering the enemy base. Oh man. We might be like a team scramble. Oh get out of town. Oh damn it.
Oh I thought I thought if I would just be in tryhard mode right there I could just be quietly
killing my battle. Oh the teams I guess aren't that bad. We could probably use a scramble. Maybe
not. We'll find out. Going this way. Going this way. There's a dude right here. Oh boy. Heads up.
Heavy. Oh I thought I was gonna hit him. It's all about that little area. A little corridor. Oh I
thought he didn't get hit by that. What's up with that? How can we? Oh we're defending this point.
Oh my god. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. Help me. Somebody help me. Oh suicide. I'm gonna die.
The heavy baby. Uh actually I talked to DJ like last night about it and he's working on more stuff.
He's a hard worker man. He's got a lot of cool ideas. He's working on a lot of stuff.
It's coming. It's coming. Well you just scared me. Thought you were an enemy. Oh no. Why did I do
that? I got behind everybody and no one knew I was there. What is wrong with me? Oh what does
the matter with me? If I had just like not been a freak show I probably would have had a couple
of kills right there. Whoa. Oh come on. Come on. All right we're going pyro. Pyro with the flare gun
and I don't. I do have an agree switch still. I have an agree switch. You gotta use the
console to enter the server. Enter the server IP. I think it's the tilde key. You have to enable it.
Hold on a second. I've got to appear offline. Just so those notifications stop popping up
because nobody wants to see the notifications. They want to see Team Fortress 2. Oh damn it.
So much stuff going on. No no don't die. I'm trying to save the heavy. What? Who got hit by the bus?
Somebody got hit by the bus I think. Yeah this is the tilde key if you want to know how to enable
it. Go to options. Go to advanced and then enable developer console. I want that checked and then
once that is checked by default it is the tilde key. The thing under escape and it looks like this.
Then you type in connect space then the IP and then enter and that's it. And that's all she wrote.
Massive bus accident. Got hit by a train. Oh my god. Oh no. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it.
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. I'm gonna spell it out. D-A-M-N-I-T-E.
I have never played TF2Ware. I've heard it is hysterical though and I am absolutely
willing to try it. They're pushing us back. They have pushed us all the way back.
Oh good. I'm hanging out here. TF2Ware is like a WarioWare mod for Team Fortress where you
get like five seconds to do like a little mini game. It's very funny. I've seen videos on it.
It looks really entertaining. Jump with them. Oh damn it. Oh god it's chaos. Shoot at me.
Somebody shoot at me with something. No that was just chaos. Gotta move that gear up.
Yeah actually I own Garry's Mod. I'm not very good at it though. I know a lot of people in
Garry's Mod can make ridiculous things. I'm not one of those people. Like oh I made this
boat that's actually a car. That's actually a house and it moves and these mouths are animated.
I can't do anything like that. I wish I could. Oh my god. Oh my god. Retreat. Wow. No. No. No.
There's nothing I can do. Damn it. New server guys. We'll do one more new server and then
we're going to hop over to Binding of Isaac probably. The last empty server. Where are we
going to find you? Auxiliary Operation. What the hell is that? One of the 32. No actually
this one's one of the 28. Badwater. We can end it on Badwater. There you go. Join that server
right now ladies and gentlemen. That's the new IP. I'll post it again and there it is again.
Oh man. I'll go defense again. Gonna go big sentry engineer. Oh man this is depressing.
Where's all my stuff? This is all I have. Where's all my like hats?
At least I have this. I can look like I can put this on. Wait I can wear this?
Oh cool. I didn't know I could wear that. That's awesome. Hell yeah I'll wear that.
I'll wear my ring. Big sentry engineer. Get that built. Get it to uh you know what? Just do an
entrance. I'm good. I'd rather have like the return to glory. But thank you though Prime.
Appreciate that. Where's it going? Let's go right here. This is a pretty safe place. Now you know
what? This is going over here. That's going over here. We're going. We're going. Oh yeah we're on
fire. Fire. Fire. Fire. Hey knuckle heads I'm talking to you. Bonk. Oh what?
Okay that just scared the crap out of me. That just scared me. Like I really got scared by that.
Like it was like oh man I'm sorry you guys. If you were in that server and you just got in and
you I'm I really am sorry. Okay well let's this one is no no I don't want to 12 people in it already.
Damn that was that was dumb. All right dust bowl. No this one's bad. This is this bots here.
So if we start to join this it'll get rid of the bots right? That's usually what happens. I'm pretty
sure that's what happens. So let's try this one. Bad water basin. Hopefully this one doesn't just
turn off. Insta turn off. I hope you're enjoying your time because it's about to insta turn off.
All right I'll stick with this. I'll stick with this. Going over here though. Oh you're already
over there. All right you got that coming. I'm cool. I'll stick with right there. Why is burger
boy so fat? Hey that's not nice. That's not a nice thing to say about burger boy. This is a bad spot
for that. I don't know why I put that there. I need to move that eventually. Somebody right there
can just shoot at it. You know what? I might move my... I'm gonna move it. I'm going up here.
I'm gonna go over here. Looks like they're not capping. Come on come on come on come on.
Oh damn it. Damn it. Damn it. He doesn't have the staffer. He doesn't have the staffer. Somebody
take care of that. You know what? I'm gonna go gunslinger. I have a feeling that's gonna happen
a thousand more times. I'm gonna give my dispenser to this guy. I'm gonna put it over here in case
somebody comes and uber charges and kills that. He'll have this backup one in case he needs it.
There you go sir. Go get some more. I'll be out. They'll be okay. I'm gonna leave. Whoops.
Didn't mean to click. Ah hell. Run away. Too many sentries in the same spot. That's a double
mini sentry a lot. Damn it. I got too many spies. Too many spas. Oh engineer. I'm not gonna play
with you. I'll go soldier. Soldier with the strange liberty launcher and the italian's backup. Why not?
Might as well. And the strange has to touch. Do I want a vintage huntsman? I'm good. I'll be okay.
Thank you though. I'd rather like I said before rather you guys keep your stuff as you could use
it too. Oh my god. It's fantastic. I'm dead instantly. I didn't even see them. Oh they're
gonna win. Well no. No no. I want the. If I would. I mean any weapon of my choice if I would have
wanted. Strange huntsman everyone was just talking about. My god it's worth like 50 million dollars
or something. Worth 500 thousand million trillion dollars. Let's get on a streak here. What do you
say Jerma? Let's get on a streak. Reserved shooter would have been like a better option.
Oh pull here. Be careful. Oh boy he's in trouble. Watch out man. He's trying to pull us. Oh this is
a losing fight. This is a losing fight. Gotta get away. Oh come on. Look at his health. Look at his
health. Should you use your three refine to craft a hat or should you trade it? Um it depends what
hat you want because if you go into a trading server you can for a lot of a lot of the time
you can get one hat for one refine. Like one of those craftable hats. It really depends if you want
just a hat. Because you could potentially get like three hats with three refine. Or if you want to
like just make a random one and potentially get one of the new ones. Got a new email apparently.
Check that after I die. Well he's going up here. You're not a spy. Oh my god there's a sentry. Oh
they're gonna get it. They're gonna get it. Gotta get rid of that sentry. Even if I die damn it damn
it damn it. Oh he's standing right there. The difference between dirty and clean items I really
don't know. I'm not a real big trader so I'm not really sure all will then go. I think clean is
when it doesn't say who crafted it. Isn't that what it means? Oh uncraftable okay. I think we're
good. I think we got it. Oh run. I don't have my equalizer for spy too. I didn't even see what
I'm sorry. I'm looking back and forth at the chat in the game. What hat are you talking about?
Let's see do you want the hat Jerma? Just read. I'm like wait what hat? I would I would like it if
I you guys don't have to give me anything. I got I got plenty of stuff. I got plenty of options
where I can get things. You guys hold on to your items. They're your hard earned items. You guys
deserve them not me. There's a lot of people right there. Oh crit. Oh. Outside 100 I have a setup
video. If you go to my YouTube channel and you type in 4,000 subs. I did like a 4,000 subscriber
thing a long long time ago and it's a setup video and it's got the same I got the same computer so
I'm probably gonna get a new computer at some point in the near future. I would assume probably
in the next couple months I will get a new computer. Well it's over. You failed. You failed.
All right so I think I'm going to transition over to Binding of Isaac for like one life or
two lives or something like that. We'll see what I do. Binding of Isaac is a really weird really
disturbing kind of uh it's it's made in flash I think but it's a steam game you can get it's
five bucks it's very very disturbing and very screwed up so I will put that disclaimer out
there before uh I stream it but yeah thank you guys if you were just here for the tf2 then
thank you so much for coming and watching you guys rock and roll and I'll catch you guys probably
next time and oh I'm being hit in the face by a frying pan okay all right let's do some Binding
of Isaac no hold on to your hats hold on to your hats hold on to your seats now let me see if I can
stream this actually got to change this on here too on the dash the dashboard dashboard playing
Binding of Isaac update yeah I gotta change my background actually you know what let's change
my background because this has been my background for a very long time let's change the background
all right so let's do personalize uh desktop backgrounds desktop background all right so do
I want like the space needle oh god am I might be like breaking the stream maybe not let's see
okay I'm not I think I like the space needle put up a photo of grandpa what about the ice one
oh sleek oh what about this one oh man oh this is that's that this is the one this is the one
I'm keeping look at this thing that thing is beautiful save changes look at this gorgeous
gorgeous screen it's like a painting all right it's okay so let's play Binding of Isaac so uh
disclaimer Binding of Isaac is an incredibly messed up disturbing crazy insane game uh so viewer
discretion is advised I'm going to say that before playing because obviously this game is uh ridiculous
hopefully uh the stream doesn't die I don't think it will
audio is gonna have to come down okay change this screen's gonna go black black screen screen
region this stretch it out all righty Binding of Isaac so I'm pretty good at this game I've
become pretty good at this game I love this game it is so much fun it's just so addicting go with
the cane got the eye patch all right let's do it the reason why I'm playing this again is because
the DLC is coming out in the next couple of days I think the Binding of Isaac DLC should be out soon
in the meantime I'm gonna run around like a psycho so if you like games that are they call these
roguelikes don't they have roguelike dungeon crawlers the real blizzard 10121 how do you
become a mod on the stream um usually the mods are people are people that I that I'm like friends
with that I talk to all the time and stuff like that but yeah I mean if you if you've been coming
for that long and you know I'll probably set up some type of way to get a mod uh a way for you to
get mod or wait for people to get mod if they want it but it's hard to give mods to people
because there's just so many people that that would want it so it's very very difficult to say
oh yeah you can be a mod sure oh triple shot this is gonna be a good game this is gonna be a good
game it's but it's it's hard to give out mod specifically because it's just so many people
want it so if I were to give it to one person and you know somebody else would be like well I want
mod too and it's like uh yeah it's a very tough decision to make so but eventually I will probably
do I will probably do a some type of way to get it I don't know how though triple shot is incredible
get triple shot extra damage more tears you're talking about absolute chaos let me get that
bomb and open up a secret room for crying out loud spread gun oh no it was the troll bomb fly
contest mod giveaway you know what I pro you know what we're that's a will do I'll do some type of
I don't know I don't know it's hard I'll tell you one thing for those of you that are hanging out
here I'm going to do I'm gonna make a video I'm gonna do a video on this in the next couple of
days next week's stream it's going to be very very interesting because I'm gonna do a game show
I'm gonna I'm gonna uh let me try and explain this I'm gonna buy like another like 30 or 40
keys and get a bunch of crates and what we're gonna do is we're gonna do like a trivia night
where I have the screen open it's on team fortress 2 so the screens open on team fortress 2 like 40
crates with 40 keys and I'm gonna ask trivia questions like basic like gaming trivia questions
it's not gonna be all totally team fortress though so it might be some other general gaming
questions and if you get it right if you're the first person to get it in the chat then you get to
pick which crate you want to unlock and I just thought I thought about that the other day I was
like you know that would be actually really cool it'd be fun so that's the plan for next and I'm
gonna make a video on this if you're watching this on YouTube and you're like oh wait wait wait what
I want more details there's gonna be a video made about that very very soon yes you will get what's
inside if you open if you get the trivia question correct you can open up whatever's in whatever
crate you want you get whatever's in there it doesn't matter if it's a five million dollar
unusual or paint you're gonna get it oh no no no no get out of my way I don't want to tie this
early triple shot yeah if you want if you guys have crates I mean I know I did a crate people
donated a lot to the last one but if you have crates if you have you know I've series 20 and
above anything lower than series 20 I don't think I would want but it's just a way to involve
everybody because I think that'd just be fun like a trivia night you know what I mean like all right
in what level of like Legend of Zelda do you like just anything like that do you find the
Master Sword or something just general basic trivia questions a lot of people would get involved
it'd be really fun and hopefully somebody gets something cool sloth what you got nothing on me
you got nothing on me my triple shot baby there would be a lot of Team Fortress questions though
like oh in what crate can you get a strange Jirani oh I'm gonna die I'm like too busy talking about
what I'm doing though my next stream I'm like not even paying attention to this one
I have to use it oh what am I doing I didn't have to use that I could have used it in a
whatever whatever that's me being a really really dumb stupid person but you know what
at least I can see everything get room see the rooms right there what I need is I need
damage up I know I have a stealth I know I know I know so is the music too loud right now I feel
like it is or am I just freaking out oh come on hit him okay because you know I have headphones
on so it's kind of tough me to decipher how loud something is or not and open up that secret room
baby three dollars or three pennies not dollars that's not a total waste of a secret room how do
you get the crates to me I'll probably set up some type of way everybody doesn't have to give them
though because obviously I only need like 30 or 40 of them I want to give you stuff should you get
this game I'm going to 100% absolutely 100 million percent say yes yes yes a million times this is an
incredibly fun incredibly addictive game it's just like a like 17 and up like this is this game is
not designed for like younger people to play only because of the incredibly like blasphemous
and ridiculous imagery that is associated with it but if you don't care about that then this game
is one of the most fun addictive probably one of the best games I've ever played that's under
ten dollars this game's only five bucks this game is five dollars on steam yikes that's insane
this was actually supposed to be ported to the 3ds but Nintendo said uh uh uh that's not happening
I don't want the kamikaze thing do I even have enough money for anything I don't think so it's
not even worth opening this door not even worth opening the door I don't even have enough money to
get anything in there oh come on hit him I got the triple shot why am I missing so much yeah
Nintendo said because of religious and blasphemous the game is just really very very dark so it is
only on the only place you can get it I don't think it's on xbox live oh look a sun card might
as well like waste it this boss's butt give an eye I'm like tempted to just use the sun card
and not have to even fight this guy but you know what I'm not gonna do it we will do this the right
way I'm trying to get rid of the baby first I don't think I can though I need more tears
not shooting fast enough something from the future I unlocked some now in the basement speed up I
would use the sun card but honestly it's just it's a uh it's a oh crap moment like I'm gonna die I'm
gonna die use it I'll bank I will take whatever is in there take that key thank you very much
how do you play this game it's just with the keyboard and you just go from room to room
clearing out all the monsters just like legend of Zelda or star tropics or other games that are
around the same design philosophy once you kill every single thing in the room you see in the
top left of the map and see what rooms are open that you can go to fight the boss you kill the
boss you go on to the next level and if you die it's over cannot continue there is no lives there's
no continuing you just die I have to start all over again this is gonna be a room where I might
have to be just take this nice and slow I'll be okay I might not need to use the sun card there
we go yeah you big fat red bastard oh question is I'm gonna do it I'm gonna do it the coin and
the bomb back huh hmm I'll take that yeah money money lots of money now if I see an item room I
will open the door pills Kane is the best with pills take them oh god damn it if I had only known
that blast damage increased oh I hate this item because it like freaks me out look at it look at
my guy that looks really screwed up should I go in the mob room oh and more pills they are I'm
not gonna use them yet man I'm shooting way too slow this is like messing with me need faster
firing speed these guys make a really weird oh if I could just kill them faster die oh come on
they don't shoot fast enough there we go oh come on you freaking bastards god oh my god
let's see what this is oh no that was so that one more place and I have the secret room probably
right here maybe either right here or down now it's gonna be down here secret room thank you very
much eggs I will take these eggs oh easy as pie these guys are nothing the hanged man oh this
one's kind of I don't really need that right now but I will blow up this machine for sure and I'm
gonna can I do with the kamikaze I don't even know if I can the emperor what does the emperor do I
forget what MLC stealth what does the emperor do what do I how do you how do I what do I do
what does this one do I forget still takes you to the boss okay I'm absolutely not going to
pick this back up the sun card don't even not gonna try and get it sticking with the sun card
oh oh my I'm using it that was just I thought it had bad news written all over it okay 10 bombs
you know I'm doing it I'm absolutely doing it and I'll get the key too and I'll get the heart
I'll get it all I'll buy your whole damn store up hang man actually what no I don't want the
emperor oh you know I will take the emperor card you know I because there's no more other
rooms to go in let's go versus you know blow up I'm gonna use these bombs on them actually no
that's not a good idea I'm gonna be in a lot of trouble because I'm sure I'm shooting way too
slow this is way too slow of a shot god at least I did that okay now get out of my way I'm I just
saw what you said lizard I just don't want to die so I'll address it in a second okay German would
you like any steam games I got um I uh I do I don't I have oh tears up tears up tears up yes
awesome that's exactly what I needed uh I don't have Gotham City Impostors but I I own serious
Sam 3 so you you don't need to give me that I do not have Gotham City Impostors I keep hearing
it's fun though can you pronounce my name xxx latha one xxx if I even came close or at least I got
faster tears this is way better keyboard is getting stuck my keyboard stop getting stuck
but I've heard nothing but good things about Gotham City Impostors I heard when it launched
it had a lot of problems and I think it still has connection problems correct me if I'm wrong but
I remember people talking about that being like I can't even play the game sesame it's me all right
let me read the chat somebody had said some dream will you be doing playthrough borderlands 2 I
probably be I will probably I mean that game's not coming up for a very long time though I think
September right so I'm not sure exactly who I'll play it with I have no idea but yes I'm assuming
I will play where's the DLC for this game talking about new releases when are we going to get the
lamb the wrath of the lamb whatever it's called the DLC oh my god you know what eat bomb eat bomb
I used the kamikaze and it killed me I hit the space bar and it oh my god dude I accidentally
hit the space bar and it killed me I can't believe I had this stupid item I cannot believe it I
can't I am I am so mad right now I could put my fist through the screen like what I my finger
happened to slip over the space bar and touch it I can't believe it I can't believe it I can't
believe it I can't believe it oh I went like this oh oops I hit space oh god damn that was
god that was a good run too I was doing fine all right it's time for co-op that just I come on I
am so upset right now freaking internet connection it's time for co-op that's this that's just I
I can't believe it I'm sitting there doing I'm running through Binding of Isaac without a problem
and I hit the space bar because I have the damn kamikaze well we're just gonna kill you
how about I even pick that item up what a worthless item oh well you know whatever
it was bound to happen it was absolutely bound to happen that dat rage do a new window
hold on oh hold on a second whoopsie daisy add screen region yeah here it is co-op co-op co-op
co-op co-op oh I'm still mad about that I'm still like upset about that all right we gotta have
another co-op song let's see if I can get a co-op song the only way I play this game is if I can do
like a co-op song so here we go ready
we gotta play
crop is the only game we play when we play every day today we got a crop crop crop crop crop
wow we got a crown to crop with a slop and a blop and that song sucked that song sucks
all right we'll do another one okay it's gonna start it's gonna start like this ready
crop is the only game you play when you want to pray every single day to slug you gotta slug
the only time you play you gotta say crop is the only game you play when you slug today as a slug
as a slug and I can't even I can't even move I can't even move today but that's not the way
we say today we pray we got a new disguise I can't even think my mind is like all over the
place right now I'm like looking at this guy's legs it's freaking me out all right I gotta get
past 15 meters dead dead dead dead dead dead dead slug slug slug so slug all right I got past 10
gotta get past 15 oh yeah baby what do you know about that oh my god oh my god oh my god I just
was doing it I was doing it guys I was just doing it now we're doing it now we're doing it
oh I got it I got figured it out I figured out crop I figured out how to play crop
all right last try last try last try come on I gotta get back into that I had it I was going
I was running I was legitimately sprinting son of a bitch oh hey strange love strange love 23
come on you slug bastard all right if I get by 10 I'm good nope okay whatever
oh that's gonna be it guys that's gonna be the end of the stream nobody dreamed dream of the
dream stream we gotta go go that's the end of the stream thank you for coming to the stream I hope
you enjoyed the time with me on the stream now we got a slug one more time to say goodbye
everybody see you later guys go go go go go go go go go go go go go go that's it all right ladies
and germs I'll see you guys later thanks for coming out all over 200 are you guys still here
you guys are amazing thank you so much catch you guys later guys peace and oh I forgot to mention
grandpa is going to be it's going to be on machinima respawn in like 20 minutes so if you
want to see the new grandpa trailer it's pretty ridiculous it's going to be there in like 25
minutes so machinima respawn 20 minutes and yeah thanks so much guys I'll see you all later
and take care everybody