Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some live gun game.
This is actually on the newer map for gun games. Arms race, whatever you want to call it.
Come here you.
Come here. I'll get this guy. Bang! Get slotted. Come on, come on, come on.
What's up, dude? What's up, dude? Keep it going, keep it going, keep it going here.
Whoa, whoa!
What? How did I not kill that guy? Oh, that was a bunch of BS.
That was a bunch of HE double hockey sticks. Isaac Clarke has killed me. He spent time away from... Whoa, behind us.
Oh, that was lucky. Come on, come on, come on. I don't know anything about this map. Where, what, it's like a snow map?
What the hell is this place? Oh, damn it. I'm not that far behind. I can catch up. Like that. Come on.
Where you at? Oh, looks like they spawn over here, maybe? I don't even know.
Ooh, there it is. No, no, no. Oh, damn it. Come here. Oh,
God, I'm so bad. Oh, so bad. Oh,
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? I gotta keep this going here. I could win this if I keep it up.
That's a teammate. Sorry.
Let's go back up here. No, come here you. Come here. Got an achievement too.
Hell-freaking-yeah. Top. Yeah, he's a guy.
I'm falling behind here. What? How is it even possible? I should have hit that guy right in his teeth. There we are.
Come on. I gotta string some together here. Get two, two, three in a row. Two, three, two, come on, come on, come on.
There's a guy right out here. Drop down. Nope. See up here. I'm so scared. I'm still in this. D'oh!
That guy got turned on big time right there. Oh, they spawn. Spawn. Where is he? I have no idea where that guy is. Oh,
shit. What? How the hell did you get up there, dude? Come on. Show yourself. Show yourself. Did he kill him? Oh my god.
I'm losing it now. All right. Try hard mode. Here we go. Oh, this guy's got 15.
I'm gonna scream. There it is. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Of course. Of course I run into the guy that said
invincibility. I'll give you invincibility. Gotta get that headshot. What's more have I got right now? 12 and 10. Yes.
That's a teammate. Don't want to shoot the teammate in the back. Oh, damn it. I'm going up top. I'm going up top here.
I will get a good vantage point up here. This guy right here is so dead. Wait, what? That's a shadow.
That's the guy's shadow I was gonna shoot at. If that guy turned around and killed me, I would have been so upset about that.
16, 21. Damn it. There we go. There it is. Come on. How many times have I said there it is?
Probably like 80. Is he right here? Where is he? Where? Oh, where? Top. This guy's gonna be on knife in a second here.
They're up on the roofs. The roofs. Such a bad gun to be doing that with. That was such a bad idea.
I gotta go up and under. Where? Where? On the roofs?
Everybody's on a roof.
We've got to catch up to this guy. Pick that guy off. This guy's gonna be on knife. It's alright. It's alright.
As long as that guy does not get a knife kill right now. That's the guy right there. There he is.
Don't get knifed. Don't get knifed, man. Don't get knifed.
Where? I keep...
He's through the door. Oh, we're gonna lose this I think. He's gonna get it right here. No.
Just don't get knifed. Yeah, that was him right there. That was the guy. Oh, I'm so lucky. Gotta get some more picks.
Oh, that was so...
That poor guy. I can still make this happen.
If that guy wasn't with me, I would not have killed him. Thank you, dude. Oh
No, he got it. That guy was 27 and 7. Oh my god.
Well, that's gonna wrap up the video guys. Thank you so much for watching. Really do appreciate it. Go check out this new map.
I believe there is another map as well, but it's not arms race. So go check out this new content dudes.
It's free, free download, and I'll see you guys all soon. And of course, take care everybody.