Hey, what is going on everybody. Jerma here with Super Meat Boy Chapter 5, The Rapture.
And this is going to be probably the ragiest episode. Well, I take that back.
You might be watching this in the future after I do a few more of these episodes and go,
Jerma, well, three episodes from now you throw your controller against the wall and punch your brother in the face.
Well, you know, I'm sorry, but I will. Let's just go.
Rapture Chapter 5. I'm not looking forward to this, guys.
So let's start the cutscene.
We're climbing. Oh my God, my whole body hurts.
Time to get revenge.
Yay, I did it. I kicked that asshole off the edge.
The Rapture.
Here we go, guys. Level one.
I only have four Band-Aids. My goodness gracious, that's bad.
Let's try and get this warp zone. I don't think I'm going to have enough time to get it.
Oh, listen to that music.
Oh dear Lord.
Already level one. It's like impossible.
Here we go.
I got to remember there's like a very specific way you do this. You go up.
And then, oh my God, I don't remember.
No, I do. Now I do. Now I do. Now I do.
Let's make this...
I'm gonna die so many times in this game.
You have to go very fast right here. It's like that. No!
Well, welcome to the 97 minute video.
There we go. There it is. Warp zone. You know what? Forget the warp zone.
I know for a fact I'm going to be very mad at myself.
Oh my goodness gracious. That was just level one.
That was level one.
Level one, folks.
That's one way.
Forget what you do here. Definitely this.
That one wasn't so bad.
Go. We got to jump over because it pushes you down.
Jump. Oh dear God.
Jump. Jump.
No.
Speaking another language now. German, apparently.
Okay, get this right this time. Just float through it.
Float through it. No! Oh!
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
What you got? I can't believe it didn't register again.
It usually doesn't happen two times in a row like that.
Oh, for the love of...
Here come the swears.
You know, if you are an old subscriber of mine, you know that I typically don't use a...
How come this...
You know that I typically don't swear very much in my videos,
and that's because I like to keep my channel PG-13, essentially.
But when you're playing Super Meat Boy, sometimes you just have to scream the F word.
Okay, here we go. Let's do it. Come on.
Oh, boy. It's going to be a long day.
No, I'm not going to make it. Not going to make it. Not going to make it.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on. Come on. My whole body just moved.
Oh, I am doing something wrong. You know what? I need to stop on that platform.
That's what I'm doing wrong.
Oh, boy.
I hope this isn't like a nine-hour video.
All right. No. Right here. Stay there.
That's not what I wanted. That's not what I wanted!
Okay. Who knows? Guys, I really might puke.
Oh, my word. There's no way I'm going to get this.
This is impossible. This is impossible.
This is not possible.
I might as well just jump off the damn edge.
Whee. Yeah, just jump off the damn edge.
Come on. Get it.
Okay. Okay.
Now, I can't let this happen like this again.
Oh, I forget how you even go about doing this.
Go, go, you smelly.
Okay, I cannot mess this up, or else I'm going to be very bad.
There was a lot of deaths there, and I skipped them all.
I'm sorry.
No, I got to come across like this.
Just...
God.
God, no.
My whole body hurts. This is like level three.
I don't even know what level this is.
Well, I didn't make that.
Now I know what to do exactly, though.
Get it this time. I'm going to get it this time.
Here we go.
Oh, for the... I'm going to punch a piece of puke in the face.
I hope I'm not peeking my microphone.
I got to go much higher than that.
Like that.
Come on. Come on.
Time to switch.
Time to switch to commander video.
Oh, yeah.
I just fought off edge, I stupid.
It's like so much worse.
Oh, just get me over here.
It doesn't even matter. I can't even...
You know, I really need to unlock a couple of characters.
That's like the big kicker right here.
What if I do this?
Is that going to help me?
No, it's not.
Absolutely not.
What? I'm stuck.
Come on. There it is.
There we go.
Finally.
No.
How am I...
There's no way.
There's no way I can do this.
How am I going to make this jump?
That was my head exploding.
You know, I'm probably doing something wrong.
And this is what happens when you play the game blind
if you're not playing for like a year or two.
No, I'm doing something wrong.
What am I doing wrong?
I will never know.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What if I...
Do I jump up there maybe?
I just don't know.
Oh, that's what you have to do.
You got to like hang out on it for a second.
All right, I got it.
I got it. I got it.
Man, this is just going to get so much worse.
No, I just tried to do the same damn thing I was doing before.
All right, so how long has it been?
Like 30 minutes and I'm on like level six?
Oh, don't you dare.
Don't you dare.
Oh, I got an A plus.
Level five.
Oh, my goodness.
Good.
I'd rather play on this level to be totally honest with you.
This thing is a piece of cake compared to the other ones.
I can't.
Go, go, go.
You slippery bastard.
And cut this thing off.
If I can make it up there.
Good, good, good.
Let's string a few together, huh?
It's been a while since I've been able to string one of these together.
The real question is I need to...
Oh, I'm like not paying attention.
Does that stay open?
No, it doesn't.
Okay, go, go, go.
Whew.
The fallen.
I should have grabbed that key.
Like, you know, I got to get that key when it falls like this.
Like that.
Hmm.
Don't know what's down here.
Nothing.
There's nothing down here.
Except the button.
You have to...
They're training you to catch that key.
That's what that's all about.
Isn't that just fan-freaking-tastic?
Die!
You just have to die if you don't get it.
That's the worst part.
This whole game is just about playing the level over and over and over again
until you memorize the pattern.
And I got it.
I got it.
Let's go back now.
Can I even go back?
Yeah, I can.
Whew.
Oh, I didn't have enough speed!
I didn't have enough goddamn speed!
Meepo, you're supposed to be all about speed.
What the hell, man?
There's the speed I need.
A little bit of speed, that's it.
What?
Oh.
Imagine if I just fell down right there.
I would probably take a dump and a brick would come out.
Good.
Give me 50 of these levels in a row.
I can handle these.
No, I can't.
Eh, famous last words.
I've got to be easy here.
Just a pattern.
That's all it is.
I'm going to go left, stand left, and then go right.
It's all just a bunch of mathematical problems.
Oh my god, what am I thinking?
Very easy.
Just be easy.
You've got to be smooth.
You just got...
Why did I just let that hit me?
I just stood there with like a goose with a thumb up my butt.
Just like...
I don't know what kind of relevance that has, but...
Oh my god.
I can't take it anymore.
I need to utilize my jumps.
I have the damn jumps.
Like, why am I not utilizing them?
I was in the clear.
I'm going to drink gasoline if that happens again, but not really.
Oh, I got ultimate rage party.
Who wants to be invited to the ultimate rage party with me as your host?
Oh, it's not even over yet.
Not even close to being over, probably.
And then you got this little dumb jump.
A+.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey.
Whoa.
What did I ever do to you?
Leave me alone.
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you're doing?
You know, I'm running you back here.
You're a real nuisance.
Get out of here.
I'll let your other buddy out too.
You guys can play hide and go seek together for all I care.
Get away from me.
Oh, and now there's three of yous?
I can't wait.
Let's have a party.
All right.
This one's not that bad.
I just got to keep these guys at bay.
Get this thing.
Drag this idiot over here.
Come on.
I know you're all about jumping around like a freak.
Just like me.
We could be best friends.
Thank you.
Grinding mill.
Wow.
Okay.
Cool.
I'm trying to like just cheat.
Can I jump up to you?
What am I?
Oh, now I remember.
You need to, you need to last this entire time until they all fall down.
Get out.
Oh, hold on.
Headphone just fell out.
Headphone fell out of here.
Emergency.
There we go.
It's back in.
Just standing here dying over and over again.
That's fantastic.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'll take all of you on at the same time.
Yeah.
Look at this.
Exploit.
Another question.
What is this?
Exploit.
Another question is how do I get down?
That's the actual question now.
Like this?
No, you have to go back and forth.
It's all about just going.
Oh, you had to have it spawn right there, you son of a bitch.
Give me the key.
Give me that key.
Now that they're all spread out, get away from me.
No more spawn, right?
Oh my God.
Come on.
Oh, I'm going to punch someone.
I'm going to punch myself in the face.
It's waiting over here.
No, no, I can't.
Just keep moving.
God, it's so much anxiety.
Make it.
No.
Come on.
There is no escaping this.
I need to get this going here.
I need to get this going.
Give me the key.
Everyone get over here.
I swear there's a tea party over there on the right side.
Now I'm taking way too long.
Go.
I got it.
I got it and everything.
Oh, I just send me to hell.
Wow.
That's yeah.
Okay.
Hi, guys.
Oh, I did.
I did take a break after that one.
Hold on.
Give me 10 seconds.
We'll watch all these deaths.
Oh, holy crap.
That is a way to have your stomach erupt in flames.
What?
Oh, hey.
Hey, leave me alone.
Go.
Get them.
I can get them killed, can't I?
I'm not sure I can get them killed.
Hit the button.
Oh, you troll.
This is this game was just created to frustrate people.
And that's why it's so fun.
Get me up there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There it is.
Wait, where's the?
Oh, no, I got to hit the button too.
Let's try this again.
There we go.
Yeah.
Get smashed.
Thank the high heavens.
And go.
I wish these guys would just go away.
I can't imagine what this is like in the dark world.
There's no way I'm going to get up here.
Yeah, there is.
Come on now, man.
I was there.
Go.
Oh.
Hoo.
The lamb?
What the hell was this level just called?
Go.
Oh.
Hands.
Hands are getting sweaty.
That's how you know you're in a lot of trouble when your hands get all clammy.
Go.
Jump.
Oh.
No, wait.
I can wait here.
I can rest here.
Go.
Come on.
Oh my god.
I think that just took six months off my life.
I really think so.
I remember these guys.
They chase you around.
These guys are really annoying.
They remind me of the thing in the...
A lot of things remind me of the Mario Brothers thing, huh?
I want to go off that wall.
Yeah.
Come on.
Get that key.
I've got to go back up here now, don't I?
No, I don't.
You know what?
I kind of want to go up here and just launch off just to get away from this guy, but I'm
not going to do that because I'll probably end in certain death.
So I'm just going to do it again.
Don't get st...
Oh, I got stuck underneath.
You know, I'm just going to do what I want to do in the beginning, just jump off the
whole thing.
Nope.
That didn't work.
I had it too.
Why did I come all the way back here?
Why did I do that?
That was such a dumb move.
And so was jumping into his mouth right there.
I don't know where anything is.
No.
Ugh.
God.
Jump.
Jump over him.
Yeah.
Come follow me this way.
Anglerfish.
Whatever the hell you are.
Freak of nature.
Get away.
Oh, now he's just going to hover here.
I hate this guy.
Oh, he's stuck over here now.
Oh, man.
This is bad.
Oh.
I got to get over here.
Ugh.
Let's watch the deaths.
Everybody goes.
There actually wasn't very many people.
Only one survived this long though.
And it was this guy.
The flood.
Oh, the flood.
Oi.
The flood isn't coming.
You have to run from the flood.
I should have ran already.
Yeah.
I should have ran before that.
Like right now.
And I shouldn't hit my head on the ceiling.
Like a butt head.
Now I'm in a lot of trouble.
Gotta go fast.
Stop going slow.
Ugh.
I slowed down again.
Good.
Oh.
If somebody were to cut together all the noises I've made in these videos, you'd probably have quite a symphony of noises.
I hate plus.
I think I've only gotten three or four of those this entire time.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Hey, look.
She's right there.
Yo.
What a troll.
Aye.
Germa powering down.
Germa is powering down.
Ugh.
Backup power initiated.
Really?
You just gotta have to jump over there.
Just into her.
And you just get launched down like that.
That's how you do it.
The only question now is just getting over here without getting crushed.
I don't even know what's over there.
I have no idea.
Hey, why didn't I just jump over there?
And what am I doing?
What am I doing with my life?
This time I'm just going to jump.
I'm gonna go to commander video.
I have a feeling that he might be a little bit better on this particular stage at least.
Oh, just go straight down.
Oh, that was just...
Oh, come on.
You're gonna do that to me like that.
You're gonna play with commander video.
You gotta go a long way.
I didn't...
Where is my jump?
There it is.
And now I brought this guy.
Great.
He's absolutely going to kill me.
Not if I do this.
This is not healthy.
If I went to my doctor and told him, like,
Oh, hey, doctor.
By the way, I'm playing Super Meat Boy right now.
He'd probably be like,
Don't play that game.
That game's gonna give you a heart attack, son.
What the hell are you thinking?
And I'd say, well, I wanted it to have fun.
And he'd go,
Get out of my office before I slap you.
I don't know why my doctor's slapping me.
Something ill is going on there.
I can't even, like, figure this out with anybody.
No, no.
Oh, I know what the title of this video is gonna be.
Uninstall game is gonna be the title of this video.
Oh, Super Meat Boy.
Uninstall the damn game.
If that's not the title, then I don't know what should be.
No, I was there.
I was there, man.
How are you gonna do me like that?
I'm gonna get Game Genie
and put the cheat codes into this stupid game.
Now you know you're starting to get mad
when you start to call the game names
and say it's bad and not a good game.
That's how you know that you're really getting pressed.
No, whoa, whoa.
I just had, like, a little bit of lag right there.
What's going on with the lag?
Can you guys...
No.
Oh, my good God.
I'm gonna hire somebody to come beat this level for me.
1-800-get-someone-to-beat-the-damn-level-for-you.org.com.
slash.edu
I...
See, right now, I'm just so bad.
I can't even concentrate on what I'm doing.
And this isn't even the hardest thing that's gonna happen.
This is actually pretty tame.
I gotta get that guy away from that.
That's the number one thing.
Get this guy away from that.
No.
I...
Now I'm just getting sad.
I've been on this level for, like, 15 minutes.
Now I'm just making careless mistakes.
By the end of this, I'm gonna buy a new controller
because this one is going across the room.
Hey, Wall.
Nice to meet you, Wall.
My name's Jerma's Controller.
I'm about to be thrown into you
and shatter into a million pieces.
All right, I'm gonna be totally silent.
Oh, crap.
Just...
Is this the last level?
Screw this.
Is this the last level before the boss?
Oh, no!
There's, like, four more levels after this.
Gotta get that guy away from that.
Okay, he's gone.
Okay, okay, okay.
Easy, easy.
Don't lose it here.
Oh, my God, there's even more.
There's even more.
Oh!
Now this guy's over here.
He's gonna get me.
Now, how am I supposed to get this without...
Oh, you have to jump a tiny bit.
Get out of here.
Oh!
Oh, come on.
Just get her.
Wow.
Could you give me some other level to deal with?
I don't care.
I'm so, so sick of dying on that last level.
Oh, of course.
I run right into that.
Oh.
This is the sound you make when you're depressed.
When you're depressed, you...
Come on.
Now I can do this.
It's getting close, guys.
I'm getting really close to either biting, throwing, or punching everything around me.
My whole desk is going down.
I'm going to drop a nuclear bomb of just destruction on my desk.
There's going to be no remnants of this desk.
Go!
Yeah, go ahead and shoot your saw blades at me.
Do it again.
Oh, there's so much difficulty in these levels.
So much difficulty.
Literally, I think that really the only way you could beat this game is if you play each level 5,000 times.
That's really the only way you can successfully get through some of this stuff.
Shoot it at me.
Why didn't you shoot it at me?
I don't even want to know how long this video is going to be.
This is going to take like 16 hours to upload.
General Plays Chapter 5.
Whatever the...
F...
S-H-I...
Capital D-A...
All right.
Last time I was quiet.
I did it.
So time to be quiet.
Shoot at me, you mother...
How did that get in there?
Shoot it.
This is not even turning into a...
This is turning from a let's play into a whirlwind of fury.
You know what?
That's actually a pretty good title.
I think that's what I'm going to call this video.
Whirlwind of fury.
I just got to get up there quick.
Quickly.
Shoot it.
Get another break.
Whew.
Where's auto?
I need like...
I need comfort from my dog.
That was ridiculous.
Almost done.
Two more levels.
That's it.
Hey, I got the band-aid.
Oh, I can only imagine how terrible this is going to be.
Wow.
No way.
I totally forgot about this level.
This level is atrocious.
Please.
No.
I had...
Why did I move?
Why the...
We're sorry.
Jerma is experiencing technical difficulties.
He is currently about to scream every swear he's ever heard in his life.
Almost.
That was close.
Seriously.
I'm going to put a cereal box.
Never mind.
Oh, I got the band-aid.
Girl, good.
You're great.
Good thing you got that band-aid.
Let's go.
Just be easy.
Be careful.
Because this next part...
That was my hand on the desk.
This is the end of the game, right?
This is like the end of the, like, actual game.
I'm pretty sure about that.
All right.
Time to be silent.
Just going to sit right...
Never mind.
This is so horrible.
This is horrible.
I wish I could just stand, like, just bob up and down here.
I could probably be easier dodging things.
I'm going to get hit with a missile.
Not yet.
Now get in there.
Get...
Oh.
Ooh.
Happy time.
Happy...
Just think about a happy place in your life.
Think about grandma's cookies.
Think about how delicious grandma's cookies are and how much you love going to summer
camp when you were a kid.
And you gotta think of your favorite ice cream, my chocolate, and how much you want to strangle
you.
No, no.
We gotta think happy thoughts here.
No.
We gotta get happy thoughts.
Will you blow it up already?
Oh.
Would you blow it up already?
How did...
Oh, wow.
That was a stroke of just weird luck that it didn't hit me.
Okay.
I can take a second here.
Take a second.
I don't care about the A+.
Just want to go.
Go.
This guy.
Don't even think about killing me.
Don't even think about it.
Okay, guys.
We have successfully made it to level 20 of Rapture.
And...
Dude, this guy is relentless.
Get out of here, man.
You know, I gotta get these guys out of here.
This guy cannot be over here with me.
I gotta get him all over on this side.
So you come up with me.
Go ahead.
Come on, you piece of crap.
Come on, you stupid piece of crap.
Just this and then I have to beat Dr. Fetus, I think.
Oh, all three of them.
Come on over here.
Why not all three of you?
It actually turned out to be for the better, apparently.
There's still...
All three of them still here.
Oh, this is not possible.
This is not possible.
This is impossible.
Oh, and the blade kills me.
You guys just go fast so they can't come near you.
Get back over here.
I'm going to...
Not good.
At least there's only two now to just smoke me in one second.
See there's like so many other nice things I could be doing like right now.
I could be going for a walk.
I could be singing a song on like karaoke machines.
I could be at Burger Boys laughing.
But no, I'm stuck on level 20 of Super Meat Boy Rapture.
Oddly enjoying this though.
I don't know why.
Typically when I rage at games, I get very, very mad, but not right now.
But you know what?
It's time to shut up and beat the Dlamia level.
Let's go.
Get...
Oh my good gravy.
The inside of the dish, it's thick and it's gross.
Even though gravy is actually pretty delicious.
I want to find a guy that created this character.
Whoever like made this character, I want to punch him in the face.
Because this is the most annoying thing I've come across in this entire damn game.
God damn.
Finally get the...
Get away from me.
Now I just don't die here like an idiot.
And he came with me.
No surprise there.
Over here.
My hand hurts.
I really am curious as to how many people bought this game and then just never played
it ever again because of these levels.
I can't imagine the amount of people that have been like, oh, let me get Super Meat
Boy.
It looks like a fun game.
I can't beat it.
Oh, that was a miss.
I can't believe I didn't die from that.
Now just run back and forth.
That's it.
Drop down.
Go.
Don't die here.
Don't be a complete idiot.
No, that wasn't that.
That wasn't not what I wanted to do.
Go.
Oh, at the boss now.
Housers.
Larry's lament.
Let's go.
Where am I?
There's a button I'm going to press and you're going to be in trouble.
Locked in.
What the hell is this?
What?
What the hell is that thing?
Well, you're weird.
I know.
And so is my brother and my other brother.
And we're all twins.
Did you know?
Can you notice?
Yeah, I noticed.
Let's go.
I remember how to do this.
Kind of.
They pop out of different places in the map and you got to run them into the blades.
That's all I remember.
Somebody jump into it.
Somebody jump into the blades.
No.
I'm going to stand right here.
Hey.
Well, why don't you come over this way, you bastards?
That's one.
Then they run along.
I know they run across the edge.
I know that's one of them does that.
All right.
That was so close.
I can't even begin to tell you how close that was.
Watch out for the little ghouls.
Ghosts.
Got to stand right here.
Oh, I had one dead.
I had one dead.
I just did it.
I prematurely did that.
Can't stand there.
That's going to be trouble.
Should have stood there.
I should have stood there.
Come on.
Right here.
Do it.
No.
Split second more.
Just got to get rid of this one.
Come on.
Oh, poo in my breakfast.
I'm a broken man.
Yeah.
Land in that.
Just got to get your other, your siblings to do the same damn thing.
What even hit me?
What just hit me right there?
I'm going to rewind back and I want to see what actually just hit me right there because
nothing did.
Over this way.
I should have waited.
I never wait, though.
No.
Oh.
Damn it.
That was a big mistake because now he's going to be alive.
No.
I just wanted to.
Yeah.
I just.
Stay here.
Have him jump into it.
Now, you just got to stay on this thing and then somebody else will launch into that.
Well, not right there, but they will.
Oh, they will.
Come on.
No.
There's a pattern here that I'm missing sort of maybe kind of not really.
I can't believe I did not.
I almost died with that.
Over here.
Come on.
I don't get all day.
He's going to do it again.
Whoa.
My game just froze.
That was that was that was really bad.
Game legit just froze right there.
That's what I needed.
All right.
Now do it.
Do it.
Huh.
I'm not even touching them.
I didn't even touch that guy.
Oh, for the love of everything in planet Earth.
Somebody give me.
I got it.
Just don't do anything stupid here.
And I got this.
Yeah.
Jump over him.
Come on.
No.
Do your little dumb scream.
Get over here.
Come on.
Do it.
Please.
Just jump.
You're not jumping like I asked.
Oh, I did it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I killed these guys.
You killed my minions.
Now you're going to really pay.
Oh, no, dude.
You're not getting away this time.
I'm absolutely jumping up this cliff and I'm going to grab onto this and you're dead.
Come on.
Did I get it?
You got it.
OK, guys, that is the end of that.
Now I think the final thing, the end, is coming up.
So I think there's only a few levels here.
Don't worry.
We'll see it next week.
Only five, six levels, but they are all going to probably take me as long as this video
has taken me already.
Oh, thank you for watching, everybody.
Really appreciate it.
So hopefully we can trek to the end of this and I can beat this game without breaking
something.
Because I don't want to break anything.
I came so, so close to doing bad things with this controller.
But in the end, it's all right.
It all worked out.
So thanks again, guys.
I'll see you all soon.
And of course, take care, everybody.