How's it going? How we doing? We doing good? He's early. Yeah, I am early. I am- I'm very early. I
am at least four minutes early today. Very interesting. I could- I could be way earlier
too, couldn't I? I could have showed up at 3.50. You know, I saw the messages. It's always late.
It's always delaying. But you know what? Not today. There is a lot of stuff to talk about today.
Let's start. The first thing that we're going to talk about is Katamari Damacy. I'm going to
be finishing it today. We love Katamari. We love Katamari. I was going to do some beanies,
but pre-stream chose differently. That's what it is. Why are you doing this? You could be eating a
big bowl of soup right now. I think soup is probably the worst stream snack. I don't think
that works very well. Imagine some streamer is eating a bowl of fucking soup in the middle
and soup does not work. You ever have a bread bowl? Yeah, they're amazing. Bread bowl and
broccoli cheddar soup. Pretty good. Yeah, we have a lot of stuff going on today. So we're
going to do Katamari. Finish Katamari. And later, Final Fantasy 16 sponsor segment for the demo.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. We'll do that after. We're going to finish Katamari
before we do that. We're not going to jump right into that. Hashtag ad. That's right.
Do you like Final Fantasy? I have not played a Final Fantasy in probably 10 years, but this one
caught my attention because it's action combat. I think the last time I played Final Fantasy
I was probably, I don't know, maybe Final Fantasy 4? Final Fantasy 5? But it's kind of like DMC.
Really? Interesting. Can you play something else? I don't want to be spoiled on Katamari.
It's all good. Katamari is fine. What about TF2? Yeah, that's the idea. Eventually maybe
play some Man vs Machine. Let me clarify the record here for a lot of people that probably
were expecting. Like I said the words TF2 and I think a lot of people were like,
he's going to play TF2 again. Hold on. I don't know. I think I want to play Man vs Machine.
I don't know if I want to. I don't know what's going to happen with that.
So it's just an idea. He confirmed it. What about Peggle? You know we're playing Peggle.
Just not Peggle 2. We're playing the original one. What about Zoombinis?
Well, Zoombinis is the next game we're playing. The next game we're playing.
So here's how it's going to play out. Katamari Debassi today. Final Fantasy 16 sponsor segment
today. Zoombinis. Another day. Like in the next few days. After Zoombinis. Sorcery. Lined up.
Sorcery. I told you we were doing it on the 24th but I lied. We're actually doing it. No,
we're probably still doing it on the 24th. Somewhere in the middle of that. There's more
shit to do. Something else. Dress that time you did a wet fart? Um, nah. It happens. It's all right.
When are you going to play Skyrim? Okay, this is not the game request hour. We're just going
over the schedule for the next, like the things that I want to do for the next week or two.
Remember, what about the something else? Oh, what about the something else? Yeah, there was
something else too. Forget what it was. What was it? I don't remember. Is there something else?
Stalling? No, not really. Just chilling. Just waiting for people to come in. Because we're
going to play Katamari. Oh, and something else. Not, no, I don't think I'm ever going to play
Yakuza. I'm really sorry everybody, but I don't think that's going to happen. It's been so long.
What's the, you guys have been watching, some of you guys have been watching for years.
What is the period where if we cross that period, there's no way I will do it. No way.
Let's say I play something and a certain amount of time goes by and I have never gone back.
A few days? Really? A few days? No, it's got to be like a week. Really? Yeah, it's at least
a couple of weeks. I know. I just move on so quickly. I really do. It's been nine months
since you played Sorcery. Yeah. Open up Street Fighter real quick then. Yeah. Are you done
with Breath of the Wild? It's been a few weeks. Oh shit. You're right. It actually has been a
few weeks. Who cares? Who cares? Yakuza zero one the rumble. It is owed as an extra stream. Yeah,
it's not fair. It's genuinely completely fucking unfair. I do have something I want to talk about
though. This is the something else. The something else is what I'm about to tell you. So I've been
stalling as of right now. Are you ready for a major, major fucking announcement?
This is a major announcement. Okay, here we go. He's going for it. He's going for it.
As of today, I am now the official chief creative officer of off brand. Let's go.
Oh shit. That was kind of loud. Chief creative officer for off brand. If you don't know what
off brand is, this is good news. This is really good news. This is great news. I don't know why
people, why are people expecting bad news? Off brand. If you know Ludwig, Ludwig started a company.
I want to say a year ago now or so. We've been talking back and forth. It's been a long time
in the making. No, I'm not pregnant. So I think I want to, let's just talk real quickly about this
because, oh shit, I'm still on my like starting soon screen. Oh fuck. Oh God. Hold on.
Over the last couple of years, I think a lot of you guys have, you know, I didn't even set up my
webcam. Oh no, this is not good. It's all right. Whatever. It's all good. I'll just turn this off.
It's all right. It's all right. It's all right. Here. Well, I'll give you something else to look at.
There you go. Okay. There's like birds in the background and shit. Okay. Here we go.
So I want to say like two or three years ago, we talked a lot on this stream about where I
wanted to be in the future. And this is all kind of real talk right now. I don't want to,
um, little jokes aside, I want to kind of get real for a little bit. I want to say two or three
years ago, I talked on stream. I want to say over the course of three or four months about I want
to do shows. I want to make stuff and I want to help people make shit too. And I floated the idea
around of like after streaming, right? Like what did I want to do when I was done streaming? And
some of that, you know, I remember talking to some of you guys in the community being like,
hey, what if I helped people make shows? What if I got, I try to be in a company and be a creative
director or a creative consultant or something like that. And I was approached by off-brand
to do that very thing. So I am insanely excited to work with the off-brand team, the off-brand
productions team with obviously with Ludwig, with stands, with, uh, there's all kinds of people
in this company now. He's doing his career voice. Let me tell you what this is not. Oh shit. It's
no, no, no, no. Okay. So I know that I knew that a lot of people are going to be saying that. So
let me, let's address it. Let's address it. Company Andy, company Andy. Okay. The streams going forward.
I'm not done streaming by the way. I don't know where you're getting that from. I never told you
that. I'm still here. I ain't going anywhere. I'm not going anywhere. No. Yeah. Still here. But I
think my focus is going to be obviously I'm going to be splitting time and I want to spend a bunch
of time with off-brand because there's a lot of shows to do. There's a lot of things that I really
want to bring to the table. Do you have a speech ready? This is the speech. Uh, streams are going
to operate pretty much as normally. I don't think there's going to be a pretty major change, at least
right now. I mean, there's always a but, right? I definitely want to spend a lot of time on the
project that they're going to be putting me on. So I am very, very excited. I, uh, I've been,
do you understand how hard it's been to not tell you guys this? I think off-brand was going to
fucking strangle me, but I, there's been so many times where I'm like, Oh, when I tell everyone,
can I tell people this? They grow up so fast. No, no, no, no. So what this means is there's going
to be a lot of things that you're going to see that comes from off-brand that I will have had
a hand in. If you saw the Ranboo show, Ranboo show was not part of off-brand. I'm just giving
an example. That was a little bit of this already kind of working with Ranboo and talking to him
and being like, what do you want? What's your vision? What do you want to do for this scene?
And for this part of the show, whatever, breaking down scenes and writing stuff and helping with
creative direction, I am so fortunate and so happy to be able to say that that's what I'm
going to be able to do. Now I didn't have that huge of involvement in Ranboo show, but I, you know,
I was consulting on a few things, but now as a creative officer and a creative director,
whatever you want to call it, I'm going to be involved in almost everything that off-brand does.
And it's great because they're all awesome. I get along really, really well with Ludwig, of course,
obviously, with all the rest of the off-brand group. I'm going to cry. No, don't do it. Don't
cry. You're going to, I'm telling you right now, you better not start crying. I'm fine. I'm so glad
the fucking webcam isn't on. Now I'm excited. This is going to be really cool. We'll see how it goes.
Do a face cam sobbing stream. Yeah. So, hey, when you see that off-brand is working on something
in the future. Yeah, this is official. I got to retweet it too. And this is all still very new.
So obviously there's still a lot that has to happen with I got to get completely onboarded
into the company. We have a lot of meetings to do before it's like I actually start working on
something. So we're in the very early stages, but it is official. So let's just keep doing what we
were doing. I guess the only thing that you guys really need to know in the future is I am going
to continue to stream and I'm going to continue to stream kind of when I want to and when I feel
like it. And when I think it's going to be a fun thing. Now, let me reiterate what that means.
That could mean anything. That could mean five days in a row. That could mean once in a week.
That could mean, I mean, think about when the Elden Ring DLC comes out. You're talking about
literally that's going to be all day every day. But I do have to make it really clear that I
have a job now. He still hasn't tweeted about his card game, by the way. I've got a few tweets
I've got to make. All right. I've got a few tweets. Oh, this motherfucker went corporate already.
But yeah, you're not going to see that much of a difference. I'm just telling you, I am an employee
of a company now and I have duties that I have to do. So this is not, I'm still here. We're obviously
streaming right now. We're obviously streaming. I'm not going anywhere. I don't plan on it either.
Keep it real. I'm keeping it real. Yeah, I'm keeping it real right now. You better watch what
you say now on stream. No, no, no, no, it's fine. Look, I'll prove it to you. I just announced that
and I'll just say a bunch of bad words, right? So then you know that this is like not changing
anything. Poopoo penis poopoo. See, it's fine. I still have a job. Wait, I just got something.
Where's this from? Off brand corporate, was it? Whatever. Now, I don't want to give you guys,
I'm insanely excited. I cannot wait to get started on projects and I hope I do a good job.
I hope I actually do a good job. That's what I really want to do. I really want to work with
creators and streamers, YouTubers, whoever that wants to do something that will come through off
brand and we'll talk and we'll develop it. I'm going to do my best. Hopefully I can make everybody,
especially everybody here that's been watching the shows and watching the stuff that I've been
doing for so long. I just hope that you like the stuff that I do over there too, because I'm going
to put the same effort, the same time. I'm going to put as much as I can into each one of these
things. Let's play Katamari. What's the process going to be like working for off brand? Well,
that's a good question considering today's my first day. So, okay. What do we do? I was going
to walk into the office with a cup of coffee in my hands and be like, all right guys, what do we do?
What do I do? What do you want me to do? I'm going to have a whiteboard. I'm going to just
pull off the top of the whiteboard pen with my teeth to be like, all right, I got an idea.
We got you. We're going to get you up on a podium. You're going to be given a presidential
presidential speech. That's where it starts. I'm going to write presidential speech, right?
And I'm going to go bullet by bullet, right? Bullet line to bullet line.
Fuck, I have to retweet that. Yeah, I'm looking forward to it. I know I don't want to repeat myself
that much, but the whole studio seems like it's going to be a really, really great venture.
Let's go ahead and retweet this because come on, look at that. Chief creative officer. Come on, Ma.
Hey Ma, I got a job. Hey Ma, I got a job. Oh yes, it only took him until he was 40.
It only took him until he was 40. But yeah, let's just keep going. That's the news. That's the thing
I've been wanting to share for a little while. It's shocking. I haven't told you it yet. This
feels like a milestone. I think it kind of is for me because I mean, we do make the 40 year old joke,
but I think there's still a lot of stuff I really want to do. And there's a lot of things that I
really have left, I think, to say. No, I'm not quitting streaming. I know a lot of people think
that's what this is. That's not what this is. Welcome to the workforce. It's the job that you
said you always wanted. I think that's the most important thing to take away from this. This is
like I told you a couple of years ago, I've talked about it. This is the thing that I really wanted
to do and I hope I do a good job. And if it is, if it goes the way that I think it's going to go,
then I'm ready to work. The job is chief creative officer at off brand. Those of you that are just
trickling in that didn't hear or didn't see the tweet. White collar, white collar Andy. Yeah.
Are you going to move? I don't, I, I don't, I don't know. All these things have to be taken
into consideration eventually in the future. I don't know. I'm just going to take it really
one step at a time. Wait, he's the chief, he's the chief creative officer. That's right. He's the
chief. No, I like Vegas though. I think I'll probably stick around for a while. Let me turn
up the chief Elvertson. All right. Hello, honey. You're so floating. You make it look easy.
Flying is actually hard work, isn't it? But roll up clouds. We thought this was about flying. When
did we finish talking? Like you can even roll up clouds. I want to be like the king when I grow up.
My gosh. Don't give up. Clouds can be rolled up. No doubt. Of course they can.
Come to think of it, we did in Katamari Damassi. Crew chief Elvertson. Are you still going to do
your own event streams? Yeah. Stuff. I, I know I, I want to make sure I've, I'm a broken record
on this, but I want to make sure I'm very clear. Me working for off brand and being a position at
off brand does not mean that I will not do anything anymore. That is not what that means.
It just means that I'm going to be spending a lot of time working on shows with off brand.
A lot of those shows that I would want to do too, will probably just be with off brand.
Of course they will. Right? So it's, it's mainly a, I have another set of duties to do that are not
just streaming. That's what this announcement is about. All right. We have way. I'm already this
big. He said duty. I did. Why did I have to scream let's go after I announced it? I just like,
I was like nervous. The one like clippable moment of like, I am chief creative officer for off
brand. Let's go. What the fuck? God damn it. Oh, I'm all the way up here. Let's go. Great.
Wait, how, how do I pick up anything? Oh, I see. Are you going to star in some off brand
shows or will you be mainly behind the scenes? It really depends on what it is. I just want
to participate. I can't pick anything up. I only have three clouds total. Which ones can I pick up
and not pick up? I'm going to know what the fuck is going on right now. Oh, it's these little,
little ones. Hey, dude, you're going to watch the golden Knights game tomorrow. Yep. Looking
for the sweep. Can I go fast up here? All right. I might have to redo this one. It's not going to
be a sweep. Yeah, it's all right. Here we go. Wait, get this guy. One thing. Let me check one
thing real quick. Sure. I didn't miss anything here. Okay. Good. I haven't even grown at all.
Oh yeah. I had to check my work email. Where are the clouds? I get, wait, cousin. Work email is a
weird way for you to pronounce solitaire. I don't even know how to play solitaire.
All right. So let me just correct that. I don't understand how solitaire works. And anytime
somebody tries to explain to me solitaire, I just stopped paying attention after the first 10 seconds
because it's just like, I don't, I don't even care. This was pretty bad. It's all right. It's
not even 200 clouds. This is an embarrassment. Chief creative officer of off brand Kansas
and not have to have a display like this. You know what I'm saying? I have at least 250.
I was thinking about, I didn't want to be like a weirdo about it or anything, but I was thinking
about going live and just being like, oh yeah, chief creative officer for off brand and just be
wicked mean for the whole stream. And then you'd be like, uh, yeah, uh, you're talking to the chief
creative officer of off brand. Like, do you know what the fuck you've been talking about?
And just have it just be like a nightmare. All right. That's all right. We're just getting started.
That would not go well. That's how your normal streams are. Massive ego. I'll move the cursor. I
got it. 60% possibility of rain. There's no Katamari Damacy without fans. Well, let's roll
up more clouds. All right. That was pretty 57%. It's not good. Should we add chief creative officer
at off brand to the stream tags? Yeah. Yeah. That sounds pretty good to me. Yeah, definitely.
A hundred percent. I like that a lot. Who would ever type that in to the search on Twitch?
Okay. Twitch show me streams of chief creative officers of off brand. Oh, there's only one. Oh,
okay. Do they know that you only have a 98.5 IQ? Yeah. Hey, they didn't hire me because I'm smart.
Maybe they did. Who said clearly? All right. Whoever said clearly timed them out. I made a
little joke and they said clearly and I want them timed out for five minutes. You're creative officer,
not intelligent officer. Chief creator of shitting pants. That would probably get more hits on the
tag on Twitch than that one. Let's do who's new. Are you new? Who's new? You're new. Nice to meet
you, your highness. Katamari Damacy is really fun making stars. That's so cool. So I kind of ended
up, I missed it. I can't get the, I really want to see a new Saturn that fits this ring just right.
Your highness, I'm totally asking you, please make a new Saturn, please. All right. This one's
actually really good because this is just like a, all right. You just like, you twisted the knife
a little. I like it. It's funny. Chief, where is it? It was funny. Chief visual learning officer
at off-brand. Yeah. Come on. All jokes aside though, I'm going to try to do as best I can.
I really am. There's a lot of people that have a lot of cool ideas. I would love to develop them
with them. Hope I do a good job. We are what we are because of our tights, safe and snug,
fit and fab. That's how we'll make this Katamari. And you do a Microsoft Excel stream because now
you're an executive. Well, I don't know how to use Excel. Okay. 20 centimeters is about this big.
Ready? Here it is. Okay. So that's how big it is. All right. It's all yours. Okay. So I have to make
a 20 centimeter ball. I have a no time limit. 20 centimeters, by the way. Do you even know how to
use Microsoft Word? I know that a popular belief would have you think that I write all of my ideas
and all of my shows on like a bag of a napkin. That's kind of, I mean, that's somewhat true.
Ludwig tweeted. What did he say? Derma being my coworker is now the coolest thing about me.
He's such a cool fucking dude. He really is.
Oh, I'm excited, man. Let's, let's do some cool shit. My first order of business
is in the company break room. There must be mini M&Ms. Not even fucking looking at the game.
I've been just walking into walls, just reading chat and looking over at bod chat.
It's a big day. All right. Like we're going to retry. It's kind of, it's kind of a wild day today.
OK, I need to make it 20 centimeters.
Oh, there's no time limit. It's OK. But I wasn't paying attention. Now I'm going to
pick up the chocolate beatbox now. OK, this is me.
If we were in the break room. Hold on. What are you saying?
I'm sorry. It's a big day. If you were in a break room, you would have another apple juice.
What? Oh, you mean like I would take apple? Well, whatever. They already know all this.
This is getting close. I wouldn't say it's there yet. I think after all these glues.
What do you think? It's almost there. A little bit more.
I think this is good. Yeah, this is it right here. I'm going to say that's it.
Might be too big. Who knows? All right, let's find out. I just show up to work
and your boss is never wearing pants or underwear. Wait, what? Why did I read that?
Wait, why did I just read that? Why did I read that? I read that so nonchalantly like it was
just a regular message. Oh, man, there's no wear pants and no underwear. What the fuck?
I didn't want to read that. I just kept reading and reading and reading and reading and it just
didn't stop. Why do you read the most unhinged messages? Well, I don't know, because everyone's
writing salad right now and there's one fucking weird message in the middle. Hey, wait, wait, wait,
14. OK, OK, wait, wait, wait, wait. I can do. Yeah, I can do better than that. So it has to be much
bigger than that. OK, let's do it again. Move the cursor or I'm going to call or I'm going to call
your boss. OK. Oh, baby crying sounds. There he is. Cool. I want to do that one again. Which
one was it? This one here? It was this one, right? 20 centimeters. I can do it. It's two meters next.
Is it? Oh, we smell. Wait, this is different. Oh, they change it up on you. They don't want
you to be able to go in and just grind it. All right. Two meters. That's way. That's huge. All
right. I got to. There's two or three versions of every level. Oh, cool. Why did you just fake
excitement? I add that was genuine excitement that I turned into fake excitement because I
didn't want anyone to bat chest me because I was genuinely excited about having three different
levels per level. And I was afraid because I was excited about something on the Internet.
And I thought I was going to get yelled at for it. Oh, you're just just give me more power.
Give me more of them. All right. Two meters. Take my energy, Jerma.
I just joined. Who the fuck is this guy? Oh, you from the tweet? Well,
my name is Jerma985, Chief Creative Officer of Okran. You might know me as the guy that did that
dollhouse stream one time. You also might know me from such unbelievable bangers as meme image
I didn't make as the most popular thing that's ever happened to this channel that had nothing
to do with I had I didn't do it. Somebody else did. They stretched up my face and made put me
like in an Among Us cartoon. And I also talk about food. I'm pretty strong. I think I'm at
two meters. You may have seen me at Team Fortress two long time ago. Oh, they put it up in the
discord. That's funny. OK, did I do it? It wasn't even close. Shit. I thought I was going over.
You play Life is Strange? I did. I played the original long time ago. Pretty much when it first
came out. All right. Well, these ones are hard. We'd like that in a Saturn. Let's pop it up.
I guess it wasn't that far off. 1.4 to 2. It is. What's this one? Oh, Your Highness really is
resplendent. Yeah, I love studying. So I haven't played Katamari these days. I'm really sorry.
Anyway, I study so much that they cut it off. Cut off the electricity to my apartment.
I do nothing but study so I don't earn any money. That's why I didn't even notice.
But I do want to study when it's dark at night. Your Highness, can you help?
They're sharing an image in the discord right now that I cannot publicly share. But they're
sharing it nonetheless. I cannot publicly share that image. You know, it's kind of a brand issue,
I think. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I thought that was real. I was like, what the fuck? Somebody said, just check the website and
look at the picture they used for you. And it was me sitting naked in the chair. I was like,
did they do that? No. All right, it's edited. Oh, shit. I was like, what the hell? I was like,
all right, well, that's the direction. Yes, it's a little brighter. What? No, you're talking about a
van? We forbid it. It's all about us. So much larger than life, you're the king of all cosmos,
all right. Larger than life? I agree. That's no good. Too dark is no good. Somebody said,
I have to admit, that would be a creative photo to use. Okay, what's going on in the game?
Anyways, this is our bookish fan studying by nothing more than the light of the moon.
Let's give this boy a brighter future. Yes. Roll up a bunch of fireflies, then roll him up in
the Katamari to brighten things up. If you can manage it in this time, that would be romantic.
We know you can do it, honey. Fireflies. So just make it really bright. I'll take it slow. I don't
want to go too fast because I'll miss the little crunchies, whatever they are. Oh, fireflies. No,
they're not crunchies. Do not eat these. No, don't eat these. That's right. Okay. It's still very
dark. Looking at some other questions and stuff. Just looking at questions. If anything rolls in
that I can answer, I will answer it. I haven't really started. So there's some things that
off-brand is doing that I have not really participated in because obviously this announcement
today and some of the other stuff, right. Um, this is kind of starting as of production stuff
for like as of now forward. I can't climb that. You're going to wear a suit every day. I was
thinking about wearing a suit running on the face game and having like super Mario pajamas on my
pants and stand up at some point to get a coffee and you guys can see I was like, but I didn't have
very much time to, I had to, I had to get out of here and then come back with like a super Mario
ice cream or something. All right. It's still dark technically. Yeah. I can't, I'm going to answer.
All right. So here's the thing. I will answer questions like, hmm, so what kind of, no,
that's such a softball question. What kind of projects do you think you'd be the most excited
about? Like, all right, did you just, did you just give me a fucking layup? Is that really
somebody? Yeah, but I'm sorry. I'm not. Hey, Gerber, what's your, how much money are you making?
No, I'm not going to answer these questions. It's his first day. It's my first day.
It's my first day and I'm playing Katamari Damacy. Oh shit. I'm going to get in trouble.
Oh, hey guys. Where's, where's Gerber? We're doing our, our, you know, day one company meeting.
Where is he? Oh, he's like joking about being naked and playing Katamari Damacy. The meeting was
at 4 30. All right. If I get to bright, it should be fine. Right. Is there more over there? I don't
know. Hey, what's the best part about working with off-brand? Ah, let me answer that. Hey, Gerber,
what would you say your level of excitement is right now? Well, I would say it's definitely at
least like a nine or a 10. Working with off-brand to me seems like kind of bright, kind of bright.
It's got to be pretty good. Right. Oh, um, I am itching to go. I'm itching to just get started
on a project and just start typing, get involved. If I was your intern, would you make me use me as
a human footstool? No, I wouldn't. Is that, is that from a TV show? I'm not reading chat anymore.
Hey, I got to look, I got a sponsor segment coming up. So you can't, you can't write that shit
anymore. Hey, I'm goddamn chief creative officer of off-brand. Okay. Let's clean it up a little.
Ooh, look, wait, it's bright. What's wrong with it? You can have this thing. Oh, it's, it's,
it was bright. So what do you guys think? Let's get some feedback here because I all jokes aside,
I genuinely am really, really happy about this. What does off-brand do? Off-brand is a company
that facilitates multimedia reductions. You need flashcards? No. And also to a lot of these things.
I know a lot of people have a lot of questions and I know what we're jokingly, we are jokingly
answering them, but I be honest, I really, I need to see, we need to see how this plays out,
what the workflow is like, what, um, how long I'm going to be spending on certain things and what,
who I'm going to be working with every day. And I actually, I, it's so new that I probably could
answer a lot of these questions in the next few weeks, but all I can tell you now is that I'm
excited. Yeah. So, uh, referencing somebody mentioned a good point, um, like the baseball
stream, the Christmas stream, the dollhouse show, those are the kinds of things that I'm,
I want to be working on. And not just that either. There's going to be a lot,
there's a lot of projects that are going to probably come through off-brand that are not
dollhouse streams, dollhouse level streams. Um, I've made it pretty clear that if some,
if there's a cool project to work on, I, I want to work on it. I don't care how much it costs or
what, if it's, oh, well, that's not going to be that expensive or that's going to be too expensive.
I think it's just pretty much anything and everything, whatever I can put my hand into,
whatever I can try to make, um, it better if I can, whatever it is, I'm going to try to.
Will you still stream? Yes. Uh, if you missed the first part of the stream, I did
go over that a little bit. Streams are not stopping, but I do have a job
that I have to do and I'm going to have to pay attention to. So not going anywhere,
not stopping streaming. Okay. I like this one. Can I show this one? Is anybody from off-brand here?
Can I show this one, the me as the vampire? Can I show that one? That's all right. That's like
company policy. That's fine. Right. It's me as a vampire as, um, well, you'll see it in the
discord. I'm going to show it. I don't care. It's too good. It's just, it's just too funny. I have
to show it. Imagine if they used this. It's stupid. Like that's, if I've requested that,
that would be like a personal request. What was the most important thing that led you to
this decision? That's a really good question actually. Thank you. Person that obviously did
not get planted there to say that. They really didn't. Like, I'm just fucking around. They
actually asked a good question. Uh, so I have my most fun when I'm coming up with something to do
and as much as I love, I still genuinely enjoy hanging out and playing games and, you know,
spending time with the stream and doing this stuff. I am at my happiest coming up with it and trying
to execute on something just kind of wacky. Uh, and that again, that's not to say that I don't
like streaming. What just happened? A bear for sure. Finally got one. Want to go home now?
Oh, well, I think I'm supposed to avoid the bears. You know the rules. All right. Good luck. What
would the wait, what are the rules? I have to avoid them, right? You need to get the, how is there
a bear in front of me? Okay. I need to get a huge bear. Well, that's not fair. Okay. So I just have
to get, I have to get huge without touching a bear. Look at that. I love my favorite thing.
What? Oh, it's cow themed. You guys are fucking just absolutely roasting me in the sub stream.
So many of these images are popping up. It's like, I can't even keep track of them anymore.
Like so many of these with just a different fucked up image is popping up. What? Where?
Oh, okay. I'm done. That was a fun one. See you tomorrow. So true. Bye. What's this Katamari?
You caught it while we were on the phone. Seriously? The cow bear? By honey? For real?
We apologize, Mr. Cow Bear. We're rolling up such a small bear. There's no point in having such a
small bear at the ranch. Pay attention to your surroundings when you roll. Stay calm and focused
when rolling. Hey, it's really okay. You don't need to say you're sorry. Should have just caught
them myself really. Oh, well we get to keep it. So we said, hey dude, why are you so popular?
Um, I don't, I don't know. I don't know. And I don't know how popular I really am.
Yeah, I don't, am I? Is that dog still in the select plaza? Woof, it could work out. Woof.
Oh, there's a bunch of those King of the Cosmos missions too. Dog, I want to roll up the brightness.
Somebody else just wanted to do that too. If you found someone you considered funnier than yourself
and had the chance to trade fame with them, would you? No, absolutely not. No, 100% no.
If you're good, that's, that's good. I'm cool with being where I am. I don't,
I don't want to trade places with anybody. What about trading consciousness with someone? Um, no.
We have a dog among our fans. Yes, and she talks and talks this dog. Hmm, what did you say?
Woof, want to roll up? Woof, roll up the sun. We heard it. We heard it loud and clear. Yes,
we weren't hearing things amazing. Yes, our course is clear. Off to the sun we go.
Oh, are all the main missions done? Okie dokie. Want to go for the sun? Want to roll the earth
and roll up the sun? We know you can do it. I don't think I'm quite ready. Well, however you've seen
this channel over the years, whether you like it or you don't, hopefully you can take something from
it that at least, I don't know, makes you feel better. If you don't like the stream, if you don't
like me, whatever, that's fine. If you do like this place, if you do like what's going on here,
that's great. Cool. That's all I really will ever say about it. I'm never going to be bigger than
the sun. I think I've tried over the years to, I don't know. I'm just trying to do as best I can.
That's it. It's all it ever was and all it probably ever will be. You're doing great,
sweetie. Thank you. Oh, oh, oh, oh, am I big enough? Unfortunately, you peeked at coffee
Cheetos chicken. That's some truth to that, I think. Well, there are no more, let's see,
there are no more planets. Let's see if I can get it. Did I get it? Oh, shit, I got it. Rolled up
the sun. It's a huge deal, but there's something else that's kind of, you rolled the world into one,
you know, we don't really know whether that's a good thing or a bad thing. But
it's powerful global news. Earth must be going nuts now. Oh, you were rolling Earth.
Wonder if our fans are all right. Ah, we feel something. We're feeling the presence of each
and every fan. Earth is fine. Don't worry, your highness. That's what they're saying. Oh,
what a relief. Come to think of it, this game mission was to roll a Katamari to, you know,
rant fans their wishes. There are still other fans on Earth. Maybe we didn't grant all their wishes
yet. But then again, rolling up the sun is such a happy thing. So we're going straight on to the
ending. The king decrees it. So now here's the profoundly moving ending coming up fast. Not the
end. I have to get ready. We'll just go on ahead. See you later. I know the curse is on the screen.
I can't get it off. I can do better than that. Anybody here? Namco. Didn't the creator of
Katamari going to make a couple of the games? Oh, come here. I can't, I can't have people come
with me. Oh, come on, cousin. Run. Run, cousin. Don't show the vampire anymore. I'm gonna get a
word in the letter. King of Ken. Wait, they're making another one? Are they actually making
another Katamari? Oh, not, not Katamari. Okay. Turn the volume up, by the way. I'm turning the
song up. Oh, I got grabbed. I told you to dodge. I didn't know how to dodge that quickly. You
fucked it up. Okay. You can replay it. I'll replay it and I'll dodge. But there's more levels. We're
not done. There's at least four or five more levels to do. When are you gonna play Monster
Rancher DS? That sounds really fun. What class should I play in Diablo 4? The Sorceress.
The only one. Or uh, yeah, Necro. Druid all the way. I tried Druid. I tried Werewolf Druid
and I got to like level 20 something. I was just like, I hate this. And then I changed to
Sorceress. I was like, this is kind of fun. This game's kind of fun. Is it gonna be loud? I'm
turning it down. Let's go. Oh, you were so close. Just a little more. Just a teeny bit. Just a
squash. That's always the way it is. Just a little bit more. Cool. All right. So now what's this one?
Hello. It's been a while. It's we met in Katamari Damase. That was a great experience. Looks like
it also put the Hoshino family on the map. But wait, who cares? Earth is in danger. Your Highness
is the only one who can save us all. Please, we need your help. Okay. Earth is blue. A very
beautiful star, yes. Hope that it can hold a candle to the great cosmos. Oh, honey.
Hmm. Giant asteroid is headed towards Earth. Oh, sounds like fun. Please help us. We're all
waiting for your Highness. All waiting? Oh, so you really were waiting. All righty. We'll totally
save Earth. Danger. Earth is in danger. Trouble of the planet is in big trouble. If you don't hurry
up and roll a really big Katamari, Earth is going to have even more problems. This is going to
smash into Earth. Sounds bad. Honey, you have to hurry or Earth is toast. Somebody help. Oh,
you're picking up all the countries. Okay. Cool. Come on. How many countries are on Earth?
Shit. I gotta get like all the islands. Oh my goodness. There goes all of... Okay, but that was
all of Europe? Africa? It's almost here. Why is the Earth round? What's this one? Where's the...
I should have said, where's the United States? I know where it is. I just... I'm going to get...
This is all of Africa. I have to get 100%. All right. Oh my god. It's right here.
I got USA, Canada. Oh, I got Brazil. What's left? Am I not big enough to pick up? I can't pick up
Russia. Get it. That's it. Wait, there's like one island. No. Oh, no. The Earth is gone. No more
Katamari to bossy, I guess. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. Control the Katamari
properly. Next time will be different. We have a brand new Earth ready to go. We'll definitely
save this one. Seriously. Okay, let's go. I cannot go fast. Retry. All the islands around me. Move
your mouse, please. I'm telling you. I can't do it. I got to stay around here and get the islands.
It's a good start. Good start. That's a good start.
Come on. Can I get the United States yet? No. Sorry. South America.
I can't get Brazil. I'll come back for it. Come on. Hurry up. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. What am I missing?
What am I missing? Okay. Good. The pace is fine. The pace is fine. The pace is perfectly fine.
I got Australia. I got China. This is Russia. All right. I got it. I got everything. Did I get
everything? Did I get everything? Get the meteor? Holy shit. I didn't think I had to do that.
I thought I just did a save or everything. That's like two pixels away, isn't it?
It's a little further than that. What should I make for my birthday dinner?
Buffalo chicken. If you like it. If you can handle it.
Buffalo chicken subs. 100%. Everyone on our earth is all right. We just confirmed it.
It turned out well. Cool. Tell you the truth. I'd given up, but we all managed to survive.
It's a token of our gratitude. We'd like your highness.
Seriously. Fabulous. Thank you. We are so pleased. What should we do with it?
Sorry. I'm just imagining it being... I'm just thinking if I was a teacher,
it would be such a pain in the ass to get the class to just shut the fuck up and
pay attention again. Do you know what I'm saying? In the middle of teaching in a classroom being
like, okay, kids. Be like, what was that? It was, I had a late lunch today. Be like,
everybody stop talking now. Stop talking. That's enough. Streaming is so interesting because
you may have just laughed out loud at me and I have no idea. I'm just still going. We're just
going. That was kind of a small Katamari. Let's try it again. What did you say? Did you forget
that you have already told us? I already told you what? Imagine if you could hear all of us
like a laugh track. That'd be so awful. That one time I went into discord and there was like
about 200 people in that call. Times that by 10. We are not that easy. All right, so we did this
one before but I think it has to be big, right? We're not big. This one has to be... We're sick
and tired of just making it bigger. So we had a notion. We had a notion even though we're starving,
just try rolling as quickly as possible and get it to about this big. You can do it. We know.
All righty, good luck. All right, just get it to 50 and then submit it.
Do the teacher noise. I don't even think I could anymore. I have to be like really excitable to do
it. I have to be super excited. Try it. I could probably do it. Shit. All right, good. I'll be
happy if I can do this in two minutes. Damn it. This is it right here. Under two minutes. Come on.
Get it. No, I'm not going to get it. Hurry. Okay, 220. That's not great. That's not bad.
I'll try to do it. Turn your volume down because it's probably going to be annoying.
You guys ready? Ready? Definitely turn your volume down. 50 fucking years old. I still got it.
Hey, don't ever ask me for that ever again because I won't do it.
Do you understand? Oh, shit. Sorry. I was looking at like off brands Twitter. It's like, oh, cool.
What are people saying? Do a moment? No, that doesn't. We don't need a moment for that.
Hey, you guys pumped for Final Fantasy 16 demo sponsor segment coming up very soon in the next
probably couple hours. I want to do some of these because these are new.
Ballerina hunt study time. Is this seriously your last stream? No, I just told you we're playing
zoom beanies in like two days. Extra special training. Night school. Lots of wheels. Let's do
night school. Oh, that one is the last one. No, I just told you we're playing sorcery after that.
Like three days after that. And then that's the yeah. Okay, I see what's going on.
Hurry to the school and get them. All right, so I'm the king of the cosmos right now.
Okay, don't be afraid of ghosts. Just hurry and get the forgotten instruments. Five in total.
If you touch a ghost, you have to leave. What? I need to get the five instruments.
Are they in this room? There's one here. Hey, quarter. Oh, shit.
Can I leave? I can leave. Oh, my God. I'm just gonna hug the wall. All right, take an observation
first. Where is it? Hey, there it is. How do I climb this? Okay, wait, can I even get that?
Do I have to get bigger? Oh, I'm done. Don't touch the ghost. I bounced.
It'd be so funny if you played Five Nights at Freddy's. That would be actually pretty funny.
Okay, what about lots of wheels? First, collect the tires. Run and run into the sunset. Become
a charming king. You get presents for these. Oh, cool. I'm into that. You got the Katabari
faster than usual. Run, just run. Get lots of tires. Oh, you gotta be big enough to do that.
Four minutes? I'm too small for that. Tires. I only have nine tires. I need to be big enough to
pick up cars. I'm taking pick up cars. It's all over. All right, come on. Level up. All right,
I'm gonna be upgrading in a second here. Give me these. Oh, well, there's a whole tire factory
over here. I need to be big enough to pick up the actual cars. There we go. Hurry up.
Not big enough. Shit. All right, where? Somebody said I was missing tires. What about all this?
What about these Minecraft houses up here? I got 200. There they are. 350? 20 seconds. I
can pick up cars. No, I can't. Damn it. It's all right. Barely passing. The real test starts now.
Shut up. God, did that happen? We think we were better than that. We aren't a prince.
50%. That's it. That's a challenge mode. Okay, so I did this one. I did this one.
Extra special training. Stop skipping salad. I don't think there is a salad in this one.
I'm gonna do the 17 minutes to make a huge one again because I think I can do better than I did.
Collect fighting spirit and seize victory. Become a brave king. Yeah, these are new. These
missions are new as of the remaster. Shadow boxing boxer. Very sexy. If you get burning
fighting spirit, your punches will get stronger. Roll until your ashes. What is that?
Okay, I'm imagining... Does it get... Okay, the water does not affect it. You just have to get burnt?
Street Fighter 6. I'm not picking anything up besides the fire. Is this a mistake?
Oh, hold on. Look at this. There we go. This song's pretty good, huh? Yeah, I think I have
this set to favorite songs. That's why it keeps playing. This is one of those songs.
This is such a summertime. Windows down. Volume up. Cruisin' kind of song. Not too loud.
Not too loud. Loud enough to enjoy it, but not too loud to distract your driving. Not too loud.
Centrist Andy. Yeah, turn it up. Turn the volume up. Let's go pump it. No, but not too much volume.
Maybe a little more than halfway is fine, though. Battle Damacy roll time. Oh, you got your salad.
Yeah, there it is. I have not completed one of these. These are tricky. Salad. I think both
quiet and loud volume have pros and cons to consider with that face of me moving around and
talking quickly. No, that is accurate. What you're saying is the truth. There is a time and a place
for low music and loud music. I'm sorry. I'm sorry if I offend anybody here, but if I go out,
I'm at an establishment, and I want to go out and have a couple drinks and talk. I want to be able
to hear you talking. I'd like to hear you speaking. Here we go. Here he goes. Here he goes. Here he
goes. I would like to hear you talk. A lot of establishments play very, very, very loud music
to the point where you're talking over a vacuum cleaner for the entire night. I propose a separate
room in every establishment that is closed off. That is the same building. It's just a place to go
to get away from the loud music. This place can be decorated the same. It can be the same spot. It's
just, hey, this is a room here that's a little bit quieter. You can have a conversation if you want.
No, I'm not talking about a sensory room. What do you mean a sensory room? I didn't even pay
attention to what this was. What? No, I'm saying it's this.
Wait, what? And then you turn your head, tilt, and aim your ear at their fucking mouth.
Huh? I have to aim my ear directly at your mouth talking and lean in and lean in and put my hand up
and tilt. I didn't pay attention again. Don't give up. Won't allow it.
Roll Katamari until you collapse. Become the king of all cosmos.
Anytime I'm in a place where there's a bunch of music playing, like a bar or it's just like,
I want to hear you talk. Let's go out and have a few drinks and talk.
Let's do some interpersonal communication.
I just asked if I wanted to get fucking pizza and then I said yes. And then everybody at the
end of the night. Everybody at the end of the night sounds like this. Yeah, yeah, no, I'll call
you to see what you're up to tomorrow. Yeah, give me a call when you have a chance. I'll probably
get up at like 11 or something. I want interpersonal communication. Hey, look, I get it. Sometimes,
sometimes you just want to just fucking rock out to some music and you don't want to talk to
fucking anybody. I don't want to talk to some fucking asshole. I just want to rock out. Yeah,
that's fine. Absolutely. Go for it.
I was supposed to be picking up ballerinas and I have not found one. You know how places do like,
oh, we're doing loud music Fridays. I would love for a bar or like a place to go like hang out
or anywhere. Never be like, hey, this is quieted down Fridays where we play the music 50% softer
and quiet reading time. You guys don't want this? No, it's not a library. They would be playing
music just loud enough where you can actually talk to people. Look, I like loud environments,
too. It's not that I don't like a loud environment. It's just there's an environment where I want to
talk to people. And when you stand around in a circle with four or five buds and you all have
a cocktail in your hand and everyone just kind of looking at each other because I know I'm not
going to be able to hear you. So I just kind of sip the drink and nod at you. Sip and nod at you
and then walk the other direction. Do you start every conversation with I would like to start a
dialogue? Bro, just go to the grocery store. No, but I'll tell you the grocery store is a good
example of the kind of level of audio that I am looking for. That is the level of audio that I am
looking for. And look, every now and again, you know, when they play, you know, when they play
tequila, it's like, all right, turned up. I'm talking to you and we kind of have our drinks.
Yeah. So I think about that business meeting. I'm going to be like, all right,
we you understand what this is going to get loud. So we're going to rock out, right?
I'm rocking out to tequila. And by rocking out to tequila, I mean putting the straw up,
sipping, sipping the drink and just like moving my shoulders left and right. Yeah, tequila.
And then someone does the Pee Wee Herman and everybody freaks the fuck out every time. You,
I'm telling you right now, if you want to make sure that you are, you are awesome at one of these
at a party or something. If tequila comes on and you do the Pee Wee Herman dance,
you just made like 10 new friends. At least I'm not doing this right at all.
Everybody knows that intro. What the hell is the Pee Wee Herman? It's the two fists closed,
right foot out, sticking out, bent at the knee. And it's you go forward, tap, tap your fist
closed together, hitting your thumbs together. And then you go back with the right foot behind
the back with the fists. I would show you, but I don't have pants on. That person that said that
was right. All right. I got to find ballerinas. Just, just go to YouTube and type in Pee Wee Herman
dance. That's you'll find it. How big are these ballerinas? This is kind of like people like this
or are they smaller or bigger? I, how do I, what am I looking for? Exactly. I know what top left,
but I accidentally picked one up early. I don't know. Let's focus on getting bigger first.
This game is fucking fun. But here's the problem though. Make sure you're the first one to do the
Pee Wee Herman because someone's going to upstage you. You'll know because the second that that song
comes on, someone's going to put the drink down. They're going to be like, oh fuck, this is time.
Like, can you hold this for a sec? Like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you don't. No, no,
I'm not going to hold your drink. And then you go, Hey, hold my drink for somebody else.
You got to make sure you do it first. Cause if you're the second person to do the Pee Wee Herman
tequila dance. Ooh, come on. You know, Joe already did that. You got to make sure you're the first
one. Who's Joe? I don't know. Go put some fucking pants on and show us. You already know what it is.
You just want me to embarrass myself on his webcam, which I get it. I can understand you.
I understand where you're coming from. No, no, dude. I don't get it. How does it work?
Look at this fucking idiot. Okay. I think I'm big enough. This game just became a hidden object
game and I'm not very good at it. Have you guys seen any so far? How would you do this in under
two minutes? Oh, right there. This one's weird. What the hell? I'm not big enough.
Still too small? How am I still too small? I see it. I just can't, I cannot pick up the ballerina
to get a little bigger. These fishes were just dancing. I just saw the Pee Wee dance. It looks
like cringe. What do we do with them? You know what I mean? Like what? In mod chat, Pee Wee dance is
just the first Fortnite dance. It actually is. That's true. Prove them wrong then. Prove them
wrong. All right. This is only for you. This is only for your guys ears only. The next time that
I show up on camera, I will do the Pee Wee Herman dance to any music that pops up. And I'm talking
about, I could be with a bunch of other people. Like I'm doing the Pee Wee dance and the next
time that I'm on stream, this one or whatever one, if music starts playing and it's danceable music,
I will do the Pee Wee Herman and see what happens. Okay. Now I can definitely pick people up.
Okay. There we go. There's two. Probably out of this area. Do you see any? There's one. All right.
One more. Way too much time on this, by the way. Way too much time. I would avoid the person doing
the Pee Wee dance. That's all right. It's all right. Me and the buds will be having a grand
old time. We'll be having a good old time. Where? Where? By where you started? We're going to hold
you to that. That's fine. No, that's fine. Please hold me to it. Over here? Oh, right here. All
right. Well, that was so long, but I did it. Okay. As long as me and the buds are having fun.
Take eight minutes, five minutes. You do you. Okay. So this last one is this one study time.
Can we please restart the debt arc? The debt arc never came to a conclusion.
You want some insider info of the debt arc? I tried to close that joke a half a dozen times,
at least. And I kept failing the bets and kept making the price higher. Trust me, I tried. It's
like, oh, okay. Oh, a billion off the debt. If I do this and I just wouldn't do it, I would fuck up
every time. It would never happen. I was always increasing it. Even when I thought I was decreasing
with something I knew I could do and did now solve the solve it. I'm so glad you stopped talking
about it. Well, it just got to a point where I kept screwing up, clean up quick. And oh,
I only have a minute. Minute? How am I going to do this in a minute? Actually, it's not that much.
I did it, right? Yeah, I got enough. Barely passing. It's still passing.
Please can I, um, whatever you guys, you guys are on today. You guys are on point today. Cool.
All right. I want to go do, I want to go do this. Did all these. That was pretty fun. I want to do
some more of these. Where's the big one? The elephant, right? I have to get that one much
better. Oh, something new over here. What's new? Is it you? Cousins, second cousins. I want to play
with them all. Hurry and roll them all up. What do you mean? Get a bunch of cousins? All right.
Here we are. No, I need them all. Oh, I need them all. Okay. Uh, was it the elephant?
Where's the elephant? I'm going to use this character. I like that. Where's the elephant?
What's the Katamari Memorial? Oh, okay. Hey dude, can you do a stream where you fulfill all the
promises you made in rapid succession? Now that's a really, really, really good idea.
We have a list of these. Okay. Who's been, somebody's been keeping track of this somehow.
Okay. Let's go over these. Um, second Catboy stream, Paper Mario, D&D with stir, Mega Milk
shirt stream, playing neon white sorcery, the monster breeder browser game, iPad stream night,
M. Dickey stream night, Bionicle building stream, pre-recorded stream, children's entertainment
stream, remake autos big adventure, yoga stream. Interesting. Hilux two, ace attorney, Tony Hawk's
underground two, BLT sandwich stream. I thought that said during surgery. It says during sorcery.
Bugleberry audio book, man versus machine, zoom beanies, Peggle, Pee Wee Herman dance,
next face cam stream. Not that many. You want me to do each one of those in five minutes?
I'd get, I would get sick. Battleaxe? Yeah. Don't worry. Hey, hey, off-brand. Hey, chief
officer of off-brand. You don't think, you don't think a battleaxe will show up at some point?
Come on. Where's the elephant? How come the elephant's not here? You passed it already?
How did I not see an elephant? How do you miss an elephant? It's called the screen is showing
lights and colors at me, but information is not being processed. I am just up here in my head.
Nothing else is going on there. The screen is just colors and lights. There's nothing on it.
When I start talking and we just haven't just looking at chat and stuff. All right. Let me
try to make this one big. I want to get this one done right. I'll do it right. There's no way you're
dodging a battleaxe. You can think that's fine. A thousand meters. Oh shit. Okay.
Play last of us. Oh, I feel like I've missed. I missed that big time. Why are you just skipping
over the laugh? What laugh? What laugh? The mouse have to scream. There we go.
Oh, we can talk. It's still just three meters. You're going for a thousand. Well,
with such a long way to go, how about having some fun with the rolling? Like roll backwards
the rest of the way, but trying a roller too with your eyes closed. Of course there's no
benefit whatsoever, but it could be kind of fun. Maybe. Get over here now. I never played stray.
I know I didn't. I'm not ready to go that way yet. You unironically promised paper Mario
thousand year door back in 2017. Okay. Well, I'm going this way. You also said you're going to
play arc two when it came out. No, I did not. You, that's reaching. You are reaching really
far into the memory bank here. No, I never said that. When did I say I was going to play arc two?
Get the clip. Get the clip. There is no clip of me saying, yeah, man, I'm really excited to play
arc two. I don't, I don't think that's ever came out. That sentence has never been formed out of
my mouth. I definitely didn't say it. Careful. You never played the Barbie horse adventure game
either. Yeah, but you got to give me a little, give me a little bit of slack here. Here's how
many video games exist ever? There's a lot. There's a lot of them. Are there more than 500,000 video
games that have released? I made just about a thousand YouTube videos before I started really
streaming on Twitch and I've streamed like what, like two or three thousand times. Like at least
a couple of thousand times. That means I've only played like 3% of 5% of every, every video game
that exists. What is this shit? He's laughing already. What's even funny? I really am Beavis
and Butthead combined as one person. What are you talking about? Two Vin Diesel is the character.
I don't understand what we're watching here. That was a fan fiction. Like they made that.
Somebody made that in Blender. What? I didn't say I was going to play it.
I have to play that day one. Well, you're an idiot for saying that.
People pulling out these receipts. So Grump Clump, you said you were going to play Billy Hatcher and
the Giant Egg. It looks fun. I'll add it to the list when slash if a GameCube night comes back.
This is a year ago. You should do an ice cream making stream. That sounds actually really cool.
I like that idea. Thank you. I got it. Don't happen again. I'll try. Jesus. Settle the fuck down.
I could read you guys the list of games that I have and it dates years back and some of
the stuff I just have never opened. That sounds fun. Put it on this list and then I never open it.
One day we'll also have to go over the retirement retirement. I definitely want to go over with you
guys all the ideas that I wish I could have done. I just didn't and we'll just kind of go over them
and rank them on a tier list of what you guys think would have been the best one and I'll do
that one. Do you know what I mean? We'll go over the, I'll open my fucking notebook. We could go
over like the 30 different stream ideas that I've wanted to do and we'll rank them and then I'll do
it. I'll do the one that's the highest rank. You're streaming until you drop dead. Okay.
You fucking maniac. You're streaming until you drop dead. No, I have an idea. I know what I'm
doing for the retirement stream. Oh, I know. It's been, I've had it ready. It's been up here. I know
exactly what it is. It's going to be humorous. It makes me laugh. It makes me laugh every time
because I don't know. It's kind of, it's kind of like fucked up, but whatever. Not really,
but it is. It's just, I think it makes me laugh. So I don't care. I want to tell you one of the
jokes so bad, but if I do actually go through with this and it'll be worth it. You just not
and just waiting till whenever that happens. It's kind of fun to just relaxingly play this game.
Just like roll over stuff and get bigger. This is fun. I like this one. Yeah. No, I'll show the
Aaron fart video before I retire. I promise. I'll release all of my draft tweets. No, I will
stop making promises. You're not going to keep any of these.
We talk about candy or something instead. No, don't worry. Don't worry.
You're going to dig in your grave here by making all these promises.
How's your talkie addiction going? Oh, actually. So here's a funny little story.
I started drinking beet juice and I like, I don't want to say like 12 hours later.
Beet juice. E as in Barry. E as in Barry. E-A-T. Beet. No, B-E-E-T. E. How many E's?
Chief creative officer of off-brand. How are you? Good. Nice to meet you.
Take my hand. There you are. Yeah. How do you spell beets? I don't know. B-E-E-T.
B-E-E-T juice. Not meat as in M as in Mary. OK, the whole punchline with this is I peed
bright red and I thought I pissed blood and I freaked out and I thought it was the talkies
that I ate. I was like, no, can't we ask me the talkies? Talkies are red. But no,
I did not know this. Apparently some people, like 20% of the population, if you drink beet juice,
or if you eat B-E-E-T-S, you pee red. No, you don't. If you drink beet juice, your pee is red.
Weird. Somebody lied to you? No, they did not. Because every time I've drank beet juice,
a day later, I have a full red piss. Like, well, that's a lie. It's like pink.
I'm embellishing because I'm a fucking live streamer and that's all we do.
You are fucked up. I'm really not. I think I just eat some beets and then tell me how you feel.
Probably will feel pretty good because they're really good for you. It kind of tastes like
dirt though. I think I can get a lot of these buildings here now because it tastes like goat
cheese. It's in that same world of goat cheese flavor, where it has that kind of very soil-y
dirt. It's kind of like dirt. Name five historical landmarks on this map.
Taj Mahal, Great Wall of China, Statue of Liberty, Eiffel Tower, and the Leaning Tower of
Pisa. And then, Big London. Oh, I love this no time limit routine. That's great.
Big London is the name of the bell. Cool. Have you ever really gotten mad at chat before?
Oh, yes. Yes, it has happened. I have been screaming for like seven years.
Yes, there's been at least one or two times where I've been like, what the fuck are they saying?
Do they know? It's had to have happened at least once. Getting there. When we're full of
contrarian Andes, he gets sassy. Can I get? Nope, not yet. You spent two minutes mocking
me one time because I said that one of the nerds in Sam and Max sounded like you.
Um, okay. But we're, this is a two-way street. It's not like, oh yeah, remember that time that
Jerma got, yeah, yeah, Jerma gets mad at chat all the time. Remember the time that we raided him
until he fucking got angry at us? You're leaving out a very important part.
Yeah, I remember that time that Jerma got really upset. Yeah, it was weird. I just said his hair
looked like shit and he smelled like yellow M&Ms. And that I think that he, his eyes,
his eyes are too close together. That's all I, I don't, why did he get mad at us?
Why did he say? I don't understand. Why was he so upset with us today?
What's the maddest you've ever been on stream? I don't know. I'm trying to think of some real
genuine moments where I was actually really, really unhappy. They're very far, few and far between
because I mean, all right, no more jokes. Let's be real. I treat this stream. I mean, like the
whole point of this stream is kind of just fucking around. I just like having fun. It's
fun to mess around with a bunch of people. It's fun. I don't take what I'm doing here.
Well, I do take it serious. I take fucking around really seriously. Does that make sense?
I take messing around really seriously. But besides that, I just treat this as like a
fun space where I'm not really, I know that we're all kind of messing around for the most part.
So yeah, sometimes somebody comes in and just like, oh, this guy's a dickhead. And it's like,
okay, whatever. But like 99.9% of the time, it's just like, it doesn't bother me. And I know people
just have fun. I'm going to assume this person's accusing me of being bald. Let's see. What did
you say? Be honest. Is this the reason why you haven't had a face cam on? Oh, wait, what? Oh,
I thought you were going to say, be honest. Do you have not have a face cam on because you're bald,
that you don't want to show anybody? No. But the answer to that. Self-reporting? Yeah. It's
going to happen. I wonder, when I do start to really show, when I start to show that I'm going
bald, which I don't think I'm going to, I don't think it's really going to happen, but what do
you think is going to be more important to the community? Bald guy or short guy? That's a
conundrum. I wonder, I wonder how, how you guys are going to take it. Will it always be like,
oh, he's like kind of short or will it be bald bald? He's bald guy. Bald would be fresh.
Why can't you be bald and short? Maybe you're going to, you know, you're going to pick one.
I know you. I know you. When I turn the webcam on and I'm bald for the first time or like balding,
you're just going to write bald. You're not going to write short and bald. No, no, no,
that's far too much. You're just going to write bald. That's it. I'm going to make it really hard
for you. I'm going to, I'm going to stand next to like a measurement tool that says like five,
five on it, but I'm going to be balding for real. Thank you, George. Yeah. I don't even care.
I don't even care. Said by the person that very much does. He's crying. I don't actually care.
I'm very confident. I'm very confident in who I am. I'm, I'm who I am. I don't care.
I'm super quick. I'm very, very, I can have explosive energy. I can fit in a lot of really,
I can fit in a lot of spaces that normally, you know, a lot of big tall people can't fit in.
I don't give a shit. And nevermind. And what? And what? There is no and 20 minutes. Well,
this isn't relaxing. Hey, what's the point of this game is to be, nope. Oh, brand awareness.
No, we're going to have a lot of fun. I can't wait till the first company meeting where me
and stands have a friend ending argument. And he throws a coffee in my face. No,
we've already talked a bunch of times and I think we're all kind of laser focused on trying to be
trying to make us go to stuff as we can and have fun doing it. The group is very much
on the same page completely. Yep. I know I don't want to keep, you know, I mean, obviously I do
want to keep reiterating it, but for people that weren't here at the beginning, uh, yeah, I've,
I am now officially an employee of off brand as the chief creative officer of the company.
Can I keep going? Oh, I didn't get to roll up everything. Finally got a job. That's right.
I'm looking forward to it. Yep. Again, I'll make it clear. The role that I'm going to have in off
brand is to be essentially creative director of most of the stuff that comes through.
So if you have a show and you want to do it through off brand, we're probably going to talk
extensively to develop out some of those things. So essentially it's like a, it's like a creative
director of the company. That was fun. Are you going to give ideas or just help other ideas
happen? I think it's kind of going to be everything. A little bit of everything.
If I have something that I think I could add or that I want to do that I think would be great,
maybe there's people that would want to do it. Help develop somebody else's idea.
That sounds really fun to me. That's nice. I would do that to write up my alley land of mystery,
small bang. And also working very closely with the production team. I, my responsibilities will
probably develop a lot over the coming period, but I'm imagining it'll probably play out something
like how I do it for my own shows. I write a bunch of stuff. I say, Hey, I want it like this.
I want it to be like that and like that. And it should be like this. And here's like the whole
document of how I want it to go. And we take that to production. We see how it can fit in,
go back and forth a lot. It's essentially just sort of the, the, a lot of writing, a lot of
a kind of onsite direction, I think too, which is what I like to do. That's where I hope to be.
Are you just an ideas guy? No, no, I'm going to be like on site for a lot of these shows.
And I'll be writing probably a very large portion of a lot of stuff that we're working on, I imagine.
So no, but it's, it is that too. It's kind of everything that you're describing that I'm
describing. Oh, he's a writer now. You can have it. I can't ever tell anybody I'm a writer.
I just can't. I'm because I'm not. Did I beat everything? I think we're done. He's going to be
an on the scene e-clown. I'm going to walk over there and be like, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, hold on a second. That was, you need to say it with a little more oomph, a little more oomph.
You need to squeeze your nose afterwards. Like there's no, we don't have a clown nose in this
scene. Why not? How could there not be a clown noise in every scene? Do you worry that you'll
be so busy with projects that you'll run out of creative steam and won't be able to work on your
own stuff? No, I don't think so. Because my own stuff at this point is going to probably be,
is off-brand. That's a lot of the point, I think. You're only 45% finished. What do you got? What's
this one again? They all have alternate versions, right? So it's also, so it's just a change in
focus in terms of where stuff like baseball stream will be coming from. I think it's both focus and
sort of the evolution of where I really wanted to be. This is something I've always wanted to do.
And I can continue to stream and still do this stuff. Working on a show and working on a project
or something and doing all these things with off-brand is, it's going to take up a significant
amount of time, but not all of my time. So I still can do this too, sort of in an evolved way where
I'm putting time here and putting time over there, putting time here. Because I genuinely love doing
this. I love to stream. It's fun. It's a lot of fun. In the mod chat there's a comment that says
I need to respond to this. Okay. Jerma, will you ever have to for when you are going to in the
future, will you be able to wanting to have that or no? I don't think so. I think what matters is
how I feel about what you're describing. And I think how I feel about it is I feel like this is
just the natural way that I would have done it anyways. What a really good question. What a really
good comment. Use your left and right. Wait, this is the tutorial. Wait, how come I'm doing
the tutorial again? Is there a reason why I'm here? That guy was the tutorial. I thought he
had a different mission for me. Jeez. Oh, I want to do another car one. That sounds fun.
I played this yesterday. It's a good game. You can fly now beyond. What? You want to roll up cars?
I've also talked to other streamers and YouTubers over the past year or two and just been like,
you know, we should work together. We should do some stuff together. And now this is my job now
is to do that. So I'm really hopeful and excited that anybody that I've really talked to over the
years of like, hey, we should do something like, oh, yeah, we should. Okay. Well, let's do it.
Let's do something because it's really easy to get into that mindset where, oh, yeah, we'll do
something. Yeah. Oh, yeah. And it's like, I'm like, I got my own shit going on. And I something else
happened. And yeah, maybe some baby. Well, maybe one day. Yeah. No, well, let's just do it. Let's
do it. My job here going forward is to make sure I follow up on those things. Because that's the
point now. But yeah, I want all those. Oh, this one. Oh, that's right. This one has all forward
momentum. I can't stop. What does that sound? I want there is your favorite cousin.
The ball tennis ball. I think I did pretty good there. Two minutes and 16 seconds.
Yeah. That's pretty cool. Oh, shit. That's right. So we're talking about are you still eating
Takis? I thought the Takis is what made me read. And I looked it up. It was the beats all along.
Oh, they actually like it this time. You like it. Oh, got a good score.
No more salad. When are we doing the final fantasy 16 stuff? Um, just whenever. Whenever I feel like
switching over to it. So it's just the demo. I think we're also going to watch one of the
trailers for the game, too. But I am actually I'm very curious if I like this or not, because
Final Fantasy is I never really got into very much Final Fantasy, by the way, Chrono Trigger
and Chrono Cross, the most important media in human history. It's up there.
But Final Fantasy has been something I haven't really paid that much attention to for,
I want to say, since like, I don't think I see 10 on a fantasy six or something.
Well, I'm going to do one more level and we'll switch over. Chrono Cross is mediocre.
I agree. I agree. But I will tell you Chrono Cross is soundtrack carries that entire game.
The Chrono Cross soundtrack is is so good that I can handle the kind of kind of wild kind of
convoluted storyline. And don't put spoilers, please, because a lot of people don't know what
I'm talking about. But if you know, you know, it's kind of messy. You needed to experience
a text based adventure game before playing Chrono Cross to get the actual story of how the game
worked. So talk to that dog. I did before, didn't I? Another nice day. Didn't I already do the sun?
But Chrono Cross's soundtrack carries the whole game, except for the battle music,
which is unfortunate because you hear the battle music more than anything else.
You really rolled it up. You rolled up the sun really and truly. Oh, we are impressed.
We have a dog among our fans. One more time. One more time? I can't say no. Do it till the end.
Do only this. The battle music is OK. It has no lasting power at all.
I think it's just kind of the tempo is sort of out of whack with the game. It's just like that.
Oh, my God. I just get the shit out of myself without somebody in my room.
I was hitting my desk and something fell off the desk to the left and fell down.
And I was like, oh, shit, there's something in here. I thought there was an animal in my room.
Sorry. That fucking sound from Devil May Cry, I swear, has permanently fucked me up.
Prey instincts. Corn nuts. Yeah. But what I was trying to say is
this is too fast for battle music. This is too fast for battle music.
Let's go to the other one. Let's go to Chrono Trigger. Ready? You hear the tempo?
Here's that. You hear that, right? That's proper tempo.
I think that Chrono Cross's tempo of it's just like it's too slow down too much.
There's a lot more planets here. What about Doom Eternal?
Doom Eternal is not a turn based RPG. Oh, what did I get? Pega and Altair?
Those cousins. He doesn't know the stars. Ursa Major and Ursa Minor.
Orion. Capricorn. Icee's. Big Dipper. The Little Dipper.
I'm a big fan of the Little Dipper, by the way. The Little Dipper is, you can see the,
I can make out the Little Dipper before anything else. What kind of food do you think they ate
there? Did you watch the Starfield presentation? No, I have not seen a single clip from any of the
summer game stuff. I don't even know what got announced. I got everything right.
I'm not going to pick up every single star. Elden Ring DLC trailer? No, no, sorry. I have an alert
on my phone that will ping me the moment that happens. So I'm sorry. I would have been the
first. I would have been the first person to tell you that. Every single morning I wake up and I
just refresh the Elden Ring YouTube official page at 6 a.m. But what if the announcement drops at
8 a.m.? No, then I just won't see it till tomorrow. All right, so now I will try not to lose in the
credits. And then we'll move on just to give you those of you that know it's going to be a sponsor
segment. We're going to chill. We're going to just hang out with the demo of Final Fantasy 16. We're
going to watch a trailer and we're just going to fucking hang out. If you want to join us, please
stick around. If you don't, then we'll see you at some point soon. Thanks for playing. Thanks for
hanging out. Final Fantasy 16 coming up. All right, I'm not going to get hit by the ping this time.
Try the lies of P demo. I actually saw Charlie playing that for a little while.
It actually looks fun. It's actually good. It is good. I'll definitely try it. I mean,
when does it come out? Maybe I won't play the demo. Probably just wait till it launches.
Probably this summer, right? Yeah, September. I can wait. Okay, I have to be careful now.
Everything is coming out in September. Yeah. What about Trey Pang 2 when it launches?
Oh, some of those Steam demo best things are coming out now, aren't they?
Okay, I'm not going to mess it up.
I'm going to turn it up. I'm going to turn the volume up because it's like a
big crescendo of the song. Here we go.
Oh,
shit.
Oh, no. I thought it was high enough. I was going to say why is this character not in
Smash Brothers? I thought there was room above. All right. Well, we got at least the first verse.
That's all right. We got through the first verse. Do better. Time to play Final Fantasy.
Final Fantasy. Final Fantasy. All right, let's move to Final Fantasy. It's been like three hours.
This is what I kind of planned on streaming for like three-ish hours and then move.
To Final Fantasy. I'm going in. You look like Richard Lewis. All right. Cool. Cool.
Hell, yeah. That's kind of cool. Save the game. No, I'm probably never going to play Cyberpunk.
All right. Let me take a quick break. I will come back. We will start the Final Fantasy 16
hangout sesh. I'm going to watch the trailer first and then we'll play it. So again, this is
going to be we're going to slow it down. This is going to be kind of just a chill part of the stream
because it is the demo. The demo is also available right now if you want to play.
I'll be right fucking back before I do. Let me just make sure this is ready.
I'll check it real quick. Yeah, make sure this is good. Yep. Oh, by the way, I got a PS5 now.
So that means also I can play the Demon's Souls remaster remake. It only took me like two years
to get one. So I'm excited about that. All right. I'll be right back.
Going to take me probably like a few minutes maybe. I'm just going to set up a couple of
things. There's a nightbot timer. Give me a minute. I'll be right back. Bye bye.