Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with some more gray the half-life 2 horror mod
This is part 2 welcome to part 2 if you missed part 1
I'll make sure to put an annotation on the screen and a link in the description if you missed it
So let's just keep going here whoo pipe. There's a pipe on the ground over there. I pick it up. Oh
first weapon of the game
Physics engine. All right, let's break. Actually, you know what? I'm gonna make sure there's nothing over here. I don't want to miss anything
Yeah, there's my light. There it is. Oh
What about in here? The lock is jammed just like everything in this game every door is locked
Get out of my way. All right, what we got? We got any monsters?
Doesn't work apparently
Let's go this way this way toolbox
Don't care for the toolbox. Do not cross
Don't cross what? Oh
What?
What about his smash it? Oh
Okay
We should have said do not smash me. Oh god. What is this thing? Oh
Hello lady. I don't want you to get me that thing's gonna stand up. Look at this thing's eyes, man
Oh, it's gonna stand up and it's gonna stop running at me run
die that thing I know for
Oh
Seriously seriously now
This is not it. This is
Whatever. Let's just can I oh
damn
Can I please get me out of the sewer? Get me out of the sewer?
This is the worst part of playing in a game like this. I just don't know where I'm going. I'm so scared
I don't want to get that eaten by this guy. It's door. There's nothing's opening over here
He's not over here. Now. He's not over here now. He was sitting on this
What am I going out? Okay. I'm at least I'm out of that
Nonsense, I can't break into that. No
Open this door open that door
What do you got in here for me anything? No, we don't have anything for me
Exit like I found the way out good found the exit. It only took me. I
Closed the building for the working hours
I don't want strangers walking around if you want to leave for something the key is on the top of my locker
The caretaker. All right. Where's this guy's locker? Where's this like dirty like gym shorts? It's definitely somewhere in here
No, not that way boxes break them
Where's this guy's locker? Oh, yeah, just like go find my locker in this deserted desolate place. Thanks a lot, buddy
That's just like trash
Whoa? All right. I'm cool with breaking all that so I got to go back into here. I'm gonna find this guy's locker. Oh
Great just a couple of vents this little place here
cool
Make sure you look both ways before you cross the street. It's my motto another one of these
No locker though, at least not in here
Maintenance is this the guy's locker? Yeah, I found your key
Found the key man, let's go back across
Cool. Is there anywhere else I can go over here? No, doesn't look like it. All right. I've got your key
Forget where that freaking door was though is over here and straight ahead
Right here the exit. I got the key. Don't need to read your note. Let's just go right out the door
Mm-hmm. All right, let's keep rolling here. Let's go up the stairs
Leon's furniture. All right. Whoa
Excuse me, mr. I think I'm gonna have to club you to death in your face because I
He's not here. Okay. Good. Good. He's probably gonna be right here though
So I'm probably gonna have to punch him in his face with my club my lead pipe can't open this door
For anything
Trash is why the houses are so damn cheaper on here
Really? All right
This guy's sure got a lot to say
Going through whoo more pills. I don't even know how I don't know what those things even do
What are those things do? Oh orange juice? There's a body good
Can I move this get out of the way? I want to get in there. No doors locked and this door is locked, too
How is that make any sense? Oh
What oh this door was locked and this door is locked now the other one
Great great
That just scared me this painting of this dude just scared me. Okay. Can I go out here? I can't okay. Oh we go
Trash bags trash barrels. Let's get in here. Whoa
What the hell is going on? What the hell is going on? Why can't I go in here?
What the hell is going on? Can I not? Oh, that's like freaking me out. I gotta get oh
What is happening right now? What is happening right now? Oh
Why do you oh
Oh god, come on get me out of here that was weird. Oh
Whoo then here there it is come home, honey. We have to talk about this. I've got a gun now
This is my mother's hand. It's my mother's handwriting
Couldn't be I don't have a choice though. I have to follow it. All right got a gun
Can I smash the fuse box?
Break it. It's got no use. I got no use for it now. Okay, this door opens to go down the stairs
Fuse box. Is this the fuse box I can break or something? Okay danger 240 volts. I just did it good good good good good
Hey, oh
My god
My god. Oh my god. Oh
There's somebody else here. Whoa, my god. Wow
Wow, I could still hear something. I only have two bullets
Are you absolutely kidding me to get?
the game okay, can I just I gotta say this right now this game has been a
Sort of slow and it's been you know, do some tasks do this and that I come up here
Oh, there's something weird going on with with this this fuse box go touch the fuse box
That was one of the most ridiculous things ever right there. Like I seriously almost died from that Wow
That was just so unexpected. I did not think that was gonna happen. Holy crap
Now where do I go?
That means it's probably more that's gonna happen again. Oh
I don't have any bullets. No, no. No, this is so cramped. Oh
My god, is he attacking? He's attacking me
This game just got so horrible. This game just got so bad
This game just got so scary. Oh
No, oh
No
Wait, do I have no, that's two is that?
I agree. Oh damn those guys with the knives. It is so horrible
My god guys
guys, seriously
seriously
What's that this noise that's in my head right now this like
I'm so on edge right now. It's not even funny
some guys
Those enemies
Scary scary I've ever played in my life
You haven't seen a scare Saturday like this in a while. I haven't been this
Freaking out at a game. I don't got any bullets left. Hallelujah
My god, oh my god, what's that noise? Oh my god, what the hell is this little thing? Get out of here, man
I don't even know where I am or where I'm going. I have no idea where I'm going where I am
What's even happening? I don't have a clue. I've just been
wandering around aimlessly
So yeah, I highly recommend you go download gray if you want to scare
The poop out of your pants takes a little while to get there, but it is here and it is here in full force
Is there a spider? What the hell was it? It's a spider on me right now. Oh my god
Did you see could you I want to see if you can see that in the camera?
I think a spider just landed on my shoulder
Really really you're gonna throw you I'm in this game right now. You're gonna throw that at me, too
insane
Absolutely insane. I don't even know where I don't know where I'm going guys. I have no idea
I need to get out of here. Once I get out of here
I'm ending this episode because I I seriously I need I need to like go take like a bath
I need to go take like at like five showers because I just like need to clean the scare off of me
Well, that's gonna wrap it up here guys for scare Saturdays
Part three will be coming next week. Thank you so much for watching
This last like two or three minutes was some of the most ridiculous two or three minutes ever so
Thank you so much for watching everybody. I'll see you all soon. And of course, take care everybody