Oh, no, that was a shpee. He just jumped out to try to stab me in the face.
Get out of town. Arc those bullets. Yeah
Right click is sandwich. All right, these guys put the sentry on top of the point. Oh
Get it. There we go. We got one more point to cap. Sentry, sentry, sentry, sentry. Look out, look out, look out
There's the sentry. God, it's so hard to arc these bullets. I'm almost dead
Look, what if I just sit here and spam over there? Oh, they disappear. There's actual range on these. Good to know
Please
Kill him, kill him
No
What? The pyro looks like a skeleton. Look at this like scream mask he has on. He looks like an anteater scream mask
What the fuck is that?
Let's go air blast some motherfuckers right now
Come on get in range. Air blast. Fuck. I don't have enough ammo. God damn it.
I gotta get a couple of kills with the pyro. I mean, come on. There it is. Oh, let me get that last hit
What the hell was that medic doing? Medic, that was not a safe choice
Capped this last point. You want to go Engie? I should probably stay on that. Oh spy. I got the spy
Don't let him build that sentry. Nice job. Nice job. You have no health
Let's hope you don't get destroyed. We're gonna win. I saw that spy. Yeah
Get burnt. There we go. Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
Let's go scout. What are these like generators? Double jump. Cool. Cool. I love this jump noise
I kind of want this in regular TF2
I'm gonna like figure out how to like mod that and like put that in as like a jump file
Too many people on red
Too many red people. Too many red team. Too many red team. Gotta play it like you actually play scout
Are there any unlockables in this game? Gotta try hard. Hold on. Oh, I gotta double try hard. Oh, he blew himself up
Fucking god, that's the second time that's happened. This guy with his like direct hit bullshit
Oh, Jarvis getting a little mad here. Calm down. It's okay. It's just gang garrison. Is this the guy? This is the guy
How many shots does it take to you get to the center of a goddamn soldier? That's what I want to know
I got him at least I got him. That's all I care about all I care about is I killed that guy now make it to
Their generator room just run by everybody. You're the scout. Jerma. Come on. Let's go here. There it is generator
There's a got up. They got a century in here
David this guy's trying what?
What I killed a spy how the hell did that happen?
All right, I want to get this guy. This guy is just causing me all kinds of trouble
Yeah, let's go. Why is the engineer? There it is. This thing is almost dead. We're gonna lose
We're going to lose right now. I can't even get in that room
We need like somebody to take out that century. I hear the two soldiers again
Oh, bye and there's a century in here still in here. Yeah, it is. I'm so dead. Goodbye
Go down to like the sewers. Yeah bait him. That's what you want. Do you want to bait him? You want to bait him?
Get baited. Yeah, this guy knows I have like no HP. Come on shoot me
What a pain in the ass I am
No, damn, I would have probably would have killed him
Something tells me it's gonna be really really friggin difficult to place by because it's only on a 2d plane
Somebody's just gonna spam over here and like I did earlier and just kill me. There's no disguise. I don't think I'm just cloaked
Looks like the cloak is infinite though. So that's good. That's good. What is that friendly fire? No way
It's gonna get behind enemy lines and wait for some sorry sucker to come over here. What is that? The cave story guy?
All right, the 10th class you heard it here folks is the 10th class is confirmed the cave story guy
Okay, okay. Okay. Here we go. Gonna get the backstab right here. Oh my god
That's so slow. Oh
I did it
Big step. All right. I got him big step
I actually got both of them makes them shit. I
Can't believe I actually
know get him I
Kind of like spy spy is a lot of fun. Let's follow this. Let's follow this asshole up here
How does he know I'm here didn't bump into me? How does this guy know I'm here? There's no way he knows
I'm cloaked right now. What a bastard. I can't even make this jump. Anyways, all right, he's gonna come back up here
Here's another scout get over here screw it. We're going this way. It's bubble gun bullshit. What the hell you can't what?
How am I supposed to combat this? It's just a but it's cool. They have like these D made maps. That's very interesting
Very interesting. I'm going down below. Forget this. I'm gonna come up from the pine
Or we can just spawn camp them that will that'll work, too
This guy is legitimately just firing into the spawn waiting for someone to appear. Oh my god, this is awful
Spawn camp city come on now
Who am I to say that? I'm probably gonna just jump down and try to backstab someone
Well, we got striking similarities between TF2 and gang garrison. The spawn camping is in both games
striking similarities
You gotta be kidding me