Hey, what is going on guys? Jerma here with SCP-087. Now, if you don't know what this
game is, this is a freeware game. The link will be in the description. It's a horror
game, and apparently it's one of the scariest damn games ever made. Now, I don't do well
with these types of games, and as you can see, I'm down the first flight of stairs and I
already don't want to play. But I have to, and I figured it would be fun to have the
face cam there in case something crazy happens, which I know it will. So, let's get started.
And to try not to psych myself out while I do this, I'm going to give you the backstory
of the game. So, pretty much this game, I already don't want to do this. So, pretty much this game
was made in two days by a guy, some programming designer or something. He said he did it on
coffee breaks, and it's a stairway... Somebody's coming behind me right now, I don't want to look
up there. It's a stairway simulator game, where this is really all you do, and... God,
God damn it. Get me out of here. I can't stop moving now. I don't know how long... This could
last like less than three minutes, and I might just rage to quit. Damn it, I hate this. But you
go down a series of stairs over and over again, and that's the game. And the goal is to see how
far you can go down, how many stairs you can go down. I'm at floor number six, and I'm almost
ready to just quit this game. And it messes with you, too. I keep on repeating myself, probably,
but that's because I am terrified right now. I can't even play Resident Evil without having
somebody else in the room with me, let alone a game like this. Floor eight. You know what? I need
ten people in the room with me to all be hanging out, because this is me by myself with headphones
on. What the hell was that? Floor number nine. Wait, wasn't I already on? The stuff is getting
louder, too. That's the worst part about this. Stuff is getting just loud and horrible. See,
it's so much repetition that you're doing the same thing over and over again, and you know
at some point something horrible is going to happen. You just don't know when. So I'm going to...
If you hit escape, you end the game. Hitting escape ends it, and that's going to happen,
definitely. Nineteen. It's actually, it's really... Oh my God! You knew it was going to happen at
some point. You just didn't know when. I'm at floor 20. I'm done. Can't give up that easily.
This stuff is going to get much... I don't even want to go down. God... God... You bastard. You son
of a bitch. I don't think I'll be able to... I don't think I'll be able to go past 30. Somebody's
right there. That was something. What is that? Oh, it's the shadow. It's the shadow of the...
That's the first time I saw that. That is the first time. 27. See, the shadows are really
starting to mess with you now. The shadows are really starting to kick in and really start to
freak you out because I didn't notice them before. I can't even look at the screen. I can't. I
seriously can't look at the screen. My whole body hurts right now from what just happened.
What is that? That's a face. Oh my God! Okay. See you next time.