Hey, how are you? Vod, yeah, well, I mean, this is the start of the Vod, you're right. How are you
doing? Give me one second. Did the tweet go through? Let me check. Yeah, it did. Good afternoon,
everybody, or good evening. Show us the green. Today is not the green screen stream. The green
screen stream is scheduled for Thursday, so Thursday will get you a solid time. What's
happening today? Well, I figured we'd just hang out for a little bit, chat and talk about,
you know, about my taxes. And maybe you guys can help me with them.
Trying to figure out what is and was it is in an expense, you know, it's hard stuff.
Now, we're probably gonna play LA Noire and Red Dead 2. And then maybe a little bit of
of the new, what was that new? Not Binding of Isaac, whatever it was. Both games? No,
I think we're good. Oh, there I am. Oh, hi. Hi, the webcam works. Delta, oh,
that Delta rune. That's what it was. Binding of Isaac. Why did I think of Binding of Isaac?
Strange. Anyways, we'll just take a minute here. I can turn off the intro.
Oh, no, maybe the intro should stay on for a little longer. What do you think?
I'm weird about my intros, man. I believe my normal streamers, right? If you're a normal
streamer, how long do you have your intro on for? More than five minutes? One minute?
30 minutes? 30 minutes? Oh, it's been three minutes. Should I give it five minutes? I don't
have any time frame here. 30 seconds. Well, regardless, 10 minutes is good. Five minutes
is all right for me, I think. So, I mean, we're at four minutes now. You're always talking
before I get the alert and come in. Well, all right, so I need to learn how to do this
thing. I need to learn how to stream. So, I hit the start streaming button. But I want
people to know that I didn't accidentally press start streaming, you know? We could turn it
off. Let's just get to what I want to do. I want to hang out for a little bit.
I don't know what this is. This is different. This is like vertical video on a cell phone.
And no, there's no green screen back here. Take a look. See, it's not like, oh,
he's going to fall through it. This is just, see? This is a wall. This is really a wall.
How weird would it be if I was inside of a box inside of a green screen?
Well, whatever. I like your Nightwing shirt. I did too. So, today, I just figured we just,
we wouldn't really do much. Probably sit around and do it wider. I don't feel like doing it.
It's too far away for me. Chill stream. We're just going to hang out, talk, relax.
Do you feel a little lazy, you know? Feel a little bit lazy today. That's kind of what
we're doing. But LA Noire is on the list. So is Red Dead 2. But we haven't had an opportunity
to do this, just to sit here, you know? It hasn't been a very much of an opportunity for
us to just kind of hang out here because, I mean, sorry, I've got a little bit of wine
here. Don't mind me. This is wine, you know? I only drink wine during one particular type
of stream. I'm not sure. That's nice. That's fruity. That's got some notes to it. That's
got some blueberry in an oak cask. But, you know, the only time that I ever drink wine
on stream is when I'm doing something very particular on camera. Why am I not? Why is
it not in a cup? It isn't a cup. But let's speed it up here because I think a lot of
people are probably really curious as to what the deal is. I'm going to go ahead and switch
it over to LA Noire because that's exactly what we're doing. And we're definitely not
doing the Nintendo Labo vehicle kit. Yeah, that's right. We're doing the Labo today.
Anytime. Anytime I put wine in a glass. Let's go ahead and put me down here. Down
here where I belong in the corner here. Oh, what's that out here? Do you guys
hear that? You guys hear that? Oh, okay. Where is it though? It should be here.
The best part of both is I was supposed to do this
yesterday. You understand? I was supposed to be in the middle of LA Noire and just
open this box and start doing it. So you didn't really work out because I
there's a couple of problems there. But who gives a shit? Like we're here now and we're
going to do it now. I'm excited for it. I know like 60% of the audience is like,
I can't believe I'm doing this again. But let's go ahead and open it. I need to move
this forward. Whoops. Oh boy, this is a little I don't know how I'm going to like
do this. I don't have enough room for this. This is so you guys understand this is like
I don't have anything. I can't move. I'm stuck here. You understand like this is locking me
in. And the camera's right here. That's good wine too, by the way. Oh, what kind of expensive
wine are you drinking tonight? Well, you know, the finest fucking box wine. I gotta
be careful with that though. Because like, if that shit like I can't spill any of that.
So say goodbye. Honestly, do you think there's gonna be like a spill the fucking wine
joke tonight? No, no, no, no, I'm not I know that's not gonna happen. I can't afford that.
Anyways, we're gonna just get this fucking thing out of here. Let's do make because
I'm ready to go. Am I having problems? Please take a picture of this QR code. There we go.
Okay, so I don't know what pieces I need. This is gonna be apparently from all the reviews
I read. This is apparently way way more fun. It has the games are actually like three or four
times better than I don't know why three or four is the number of new here. Apparently,
it's like three times better game wise than the other labos. This is apparently the other
labos with dog shit in comparison. So we'll find out. I got my I got my controllers here.
Okay, I'm ready. Let's go ahead and make. First, we'll practice. I don't need to practice.
I already know how to make the fucking popcorn holder. I don't need to do this.
I'm gonna change this from like the from just chatting to Nintendo labo vehicle kit.
Vehicle kit. Let lab go. Let's just have a vehicle. Fuck is that person running?
How about a making car automobile factory? Well, it's not just cars, vehicle factory.
Vehicle factory one worker, right? Because I mean, that would be kind of fucked up. But that's
that's reality here. I gotta make them all. Okay, labo. Okay, that's done. I'm ready.
This is actually kind of good. This is a red blend California red blend from black box
premium box wine. My plan is, you know, to stall. No, don't stall this. This shit
takes like eight hours to build. Don't stop stalling. It's gonna be like a nine and a
half hour stream. Look at how good I look right now. I look fresh. I look well rested. Fast
forward seven and a half hours from now. I bet you my hair is greasy. My face is watery.
And like I got stains under my armpits. $50 just came in. Baked flakes. Thank you for
the 50 fucking dollars. And he says, italics says you have small cups. How dare you force
germicides cups onto your housemates. Eat these bits on stream. This is this is eight ounces.
This is a this is what a human being is supposed to consume for a serving. Six to eight ounces.
Just stop going to Burger King and getting the large like 38 ounce fucking beverage. It's
gonna kill you one day. This is the amount of ounces a waffle one serving. You know,
you drink those bottles of water, those are 16.9 fluid ounces. That's two servings.
Call a doctor and ask him. Call a doctor. Call a doctor and ask. I don't even think
he can hear me. But thanks for the $50 man so much. Seriously. I don't need practice. Thank
you baked flakes. It's a lot of money. We already know this part. Okay, that was weird.
Go. Go. I already know this part. Is there a way to skip the baby shit? I think we have to
do this. Yeah, if you hold this, I don't even need this baby shit. Yeah, hold these and go
back and forth. Or baby shit. It's a game for little kids. Actually, one of the reviewers said
that it took him and his son a very long time to make it. He said that, you know, it was
really hard for me. My son was there too, but I thought it was pretty difficult at points.
And I'm like, okay, well, all right. Stop making things up. I swear to God, that's a
review for this labo. Just type in labo review me and my son or something and you'll just find
it. Do like how people find anything on the internet. You're the father. Congrats.
Shave your scruff. Listen, anytime that I shave, I only have to shave like once a week
because my face should be grow so slow and so radically thick. And I have sensitive skin,
right? I have sensitive teeth. So I need special toothpaste and any special shaving cream
because if I shave, I get red and itchy and it's bad. So I have to use sensitive toothpaste
for my sensitive teeth and then sensitive soap for my sensitive face. I don't want to shave
every day. All right, so we're going to make a petal. 60 to 90 minutes. We're going to be
here all day. This is going to take a long fucking time. 90 minutes for just a fucking
petal. This is a mistake. This is like, this is a 10 minute joke that I wanted to make
and now it's a nine hour stream. Do you have chest? I don't have any chest here.
I guess unanimously people, okay. So there's, there's like the before and after labo streams,
right? Before labo and during labo, it was okay. But like after labo, it was like,
don't ever do that again. So like now, now we're just, now we're going to put on like a
high heel. I'm ready. Four steps. You need a complete base petal frame joy con. I've had
some practice. I'll be able to get this good. What do I need? And turn this fucking shitty
music down, Nintendo. There. Perfect. What was this? This is the best kit. That's what
I've been told by the guy that had the sun. The guy that had the sun. I told you.
Okay. We need the big, uh, Yoshi face, the big spitter from Jurassic park. That's what that is.
That's the, just that look at it. The spitter from Jurassic park. I don't care what anybody
says. That's the image that's on the screen. I would, I would have passed like the Rorschach
test or where is it a pedal a and it's the, it's the Rorschach, uh, Yoshi face.
This is the, looks like the one right here. Now I also need to move some stuff because I
can't trash this room. This is not a funny break stuff room because I just bought it.
You think I'm going to break it? I'm going to move this
sidewards. You know, let's move this, let's move this sidewards. Okay, I guess fine.
I want this trash bag. You know, make sure to put the trash bag in the table,
like underneath the legs and just drop it under the table. No, that's too much work.
All right. So I need to punch out, don't ruin these two pieces from sheet A. Don't forget
the tiny piece on the bottom. So this little thing right here. So how, how does that look?
Does this need to be adjusted? Let me adjust this camera because it is, it's, uh,
lights are changing in here. Shit. BenQ, why do you have to have these fucking touch pad
things? Just put buttons on like a regular fucking company. Okay. Where is it? Is there
a reason why I can't configure this? What the fuck is going on here?
Yes, I'd like to configure that video, please. Why the fuck is going on here?
Why can I not configure? Configure! I just did it. Do I seriously, are you going to piss me off
this much? I don't even have it on my task bar or anything. I just can't even open the
fucking Logitech software. What the fuck was that? What the hell was that? My camera just
got struck by lightning. Configure. Thank you. Jesus. Who runs these companies? All right.
It looks good. And how's that? That's better, right? You can actually see what's going on here.
Looks good. Okay. Let's go ahead and do it. That's that camera. That's that one. Move
this back so I can see it again. All right. BenQ. I have an idea for a great company
innovation. Instead of buttons, make really finicky touch buttons instead and waste electricity.
There goes that sponsorship. Hey, okay. Now I can see. Get it out of there.
60 to 90 minutes and it's already, we've already wasted 20. Is this good? Piece here and then
the little guy right there, a little dumbbell. Excellent. Make sure to put this in the,
do it. Don't be lazy about it. Put it in the trash. Well, recycle it because this is
going to go in the recycling. I don't need anything else from this, right? It comes more
like length. We have to like fold this shit and like pack it away neatly. Put it in the trash.
No, this is going into the recycling. Come on, guys. Come on. All right. We got the
first piece out. Just get like the first few pieces. All right. So we need this one from B.
So that top one B with the here. So which one is it? B. Is this not the right thing?
Looks like it is. Why does this look wrong? Oh, it's like a giant treasure map. Okay.
This one. All right. That's good. Save that for now and let's start the assembling process.
Kids, don't forget if you have any trouble, you can use the back button. I know how it
works. So let's get started on this. Oh, the pedal. First up is the big piece here. Make sure
that you read Family Circus because that's the mother from Family Circus, which no longer is
even in print anymore. I don't think I think it was discontinued back like two or three years
ago. But man, it was it was a that was that was a that was in the funnies. All right. Make
sure you have plenty of space when working on big pieces. It might help to put away tiny
pieces you don't need. I know how to don't I know how to work this. Thank God that
comic sucked. Yeah, that comic really? Seriously, like I hate this. I hate to like continue the
stall here. But I don't even need to stall. But seriously, that comic was just you guys think
Garfield was bad. Was it Family Circus? Like three panels and it was like boy is out playing.
Mother calls boy in for dinner. Boy comes in for dinner. That was it. There was no comedy.
All right, let's go. So we're gonna go this way. Nice increased. All these folds have to
happen. All of my this is not my first time, man. I just I can't it's too far. I'm just gonna
put it here for now. We have to vacuum this room. Come in for dinner. Okay. And he comes
in and he's like chocolate all over his mouth. Did you eat chocolate before coming in for dinner?
Yeah. The kid looked like Bobby Hill. Like shrunk. Family Circus. Okay, dad. But that
trope is only happens when you're one or two years old, by the way. No, no, four or five,
six year old is getting like the giant mouth of chocolate all over their face.
It doesn't happen. You ready for that satisfying satisfaction? It's been a while since we've
heard that noise. How about the next one? What is wrong with me? I'm like embarrassed
right now because I saw the screen. I'm turning red. I saw the webcam. You can't hear it.
Look at the fucking dickhead in the car. That guy is probably a nice,
wonderful person. Who cares? So we got one, two, three. Same thing on the other side.
Is he drunk? I've had the equivalent of drinking like a glass of Welch's grape juice, guys.
That's not how it works. It's wine. That's not my walnut desk. Shit. Okay, that's all
right for now. Fuck you. All right, let's go. I got them all folded. Do we get these little
knobs here? All the little ones too or no? Yeah, I gotta go with the small ones. And then
bring in the big guy. Here we go. Wicked. Turmoil is never the same after moving to Vegas.
The Labo stream was like three or four months ago. The first one. So it came with me.
And the best part is I don't have to like destroy these. I can put these on, I'm gonna put them on
a shelf when I get like some of these, the pedal done. This is, this like size eight shoe
is going up on a shelf up here. I don't have to get rid of it. I don't have to like recycle it.
I recycle, yeah. Fucking problem with that. All right, over here. These have to punch out.
I'm just gonna say fuck it in a vacuum later. That's just the way it is.
Can we have a joke please? All right. Like you mean like a knock-knock type joke? What do you
mean like a story? Look at, look at how funny this story was. What? Did you, you didn't see
that part coming in the middle? Which kind? Anything. Okay. How about knock-knock is there.
It's, it's the police. Police who? Open up. You are, you killed somebody. Now you're under
arrest. We know the body's in the fridge. All right. So wait, wait, wait. Let me get this
right. Like that, right? Okay. And this part comes down, snaps into place, and then this one
folds. Okay, that's what this little one's for. Let's, let's go. Oh, I'm sorry little one.
Connect from here to here. Right. And good. Make sure it's snug. Oh, this is way better
than, this is way better than the other two. This is way better. Sorry. This one folds,
right? Where's that? Over here. This sticks into the, it's going to go in that slot right
there. Guarantee. I fucking guarantee it. Watch this. In she goes. Right in here.
Sunny side up. Can you guys see? I'm going to make sure the class, you guys are following
along, right? See the thing is, one of you guys got this for your birthday like a month ago
and you were like, holy shit, I'm never going to use that. But you're like, oh,
thanks grandma. It's been rotting in your closet for like two or three months.
And, but then you saw this stream turned on and you fucking sprinted as fast as you could to go
to the closet and grab it and like do it with me. Three of you did that. Okay. Beautiful.
Let's put these connected pieces to one side for a moment. Why would I need to take a break?
Take a break. All right. Well, there it is. Put, put two things together. What's,
what is Nintendo's obsession with breaks? Look, if I want to drink a box of wine
and play with a children's toy, I'm going to, I'm going to do that. Okay. Don't worry about me.
I'm going to be just fine. Like it's like Wii sports all over again. Are you sure there's
enough room? No, I'm not sure. I'm going to ruin my house. I'm going to start smashing stuff.
I'm going to break the vases and I'm going to break a couple of windows. I wasn't sure.
Thanks for reminding me. Okay. So you did these from C. Did they do that because they think
someone's going to sue them? You got to say, Hey, make sure you don't break any windows in
your house with the wii mode. Well, people would sort of actually do that. Can you imagine
if you like threw your wii mode into your TV and you were like, Nintendo did that?
What the fuck, Nintendo? Why'd you do that? You're going to waste the energy to call
and like get a lawyer. You're going to get a lawyer. Imagine explaining that to the lawyer.
Oh, yes. This is a PD Richards and sons. How can I help you? Hey,
I whipped a fucking heavy object into my TV and broke it and the company that sold me the thing.
I want to sue them. Hello. These two. All right. Is that all we need? Just,
just these one, two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four. Sorry. And this counted.
That's it, right? Thing is I don't want to get rid of these just yet because I need,
I need to track them down later. I had so much fun. God, I miss this.
You will need the rest of the pieces and see later. Is the music too loud? I'm turning it down.
Sort of like a pair of spoons, aren't they? I mean, no. Spoon. These are spoons.
Sort of like a pair of spoons. Okay. I'll flip them over to the other backs. Have you got
them facing the right way? I don't know. You just said they were spoons. How can I trust you
ever again? Okay. So now they're facing the right way. Fold them up. Wait, I gotta take,
I gotta take care of this. I love the people that are trickling into the stream right now.
I just looked over at the chat and I saw not this again. Oh yeah. Make sure you, hey,
make sure you grab yourself a box wine. If you're at least the age of drinking in your
particular region or time zone. Drinking is by time zone. Specific time is allowed to start
drinking at five, four, five PM. Eastern time is not allowed to start drinking until
like five PM Eastern, which is, you know, it's by time zone. It's three 30 in the afternoon,
his Pacific. Oh yeah, it is. You know, like tons of information is racing through my brain
right now. Literally everything I've ever done is like racing through my mind. I just like,
I just had a vision of me doing this and being like, holy shit, what a weirdo.
He's having, I'm having a crisis right now. It's happening. I'm too self-aware. I need to like
install like the 2013 German emulator and like run it in a virtual machine in my brain
because I'm like, I'm, what the fuck is happening right now? Old age. All right.
Wait, hold, hold this. I'm not breaking it. Was it a break? It's designed to be folded.
Half a glass of wine and already drunk. Listen, buddy, that ain't how it works.
Back in my heyday, I could drink this whole box and puke and be sick. And it was awful.
And it was never fun. It sucked every time. Don't fucking do it. It's not cool to drink too
much to the point where you fucking black out and get sick. Don't, it's not fucking fun.
Don't do it. All right. I need to, this could take like all day. I had this vision
in my brain that this was not going to take this long. Where's that piece?
He's at the fold up like that. Okay. Same thing with the other one. This is hard to do.
I'm sure I'm just seeing things. No, just don't, just, just be, just know your limits.
If your, if your limit is a box of wine, know it, know what it is.
Violent boomer destroys Nintendo Labo. Ah, I don't see anything destroyed at the moment. I
see a lot of, um, well-crafted, nice, very taking my time boomer playing with the Nintendo Labo.
So then these go through here. This is going to turn into like a little grill.
These fold, fold both of them. One is elf bowling. Just, you're going to have to get
the emulator for that one. Remember they're going to destroy this one like the piano.
No, I destroyed the piano because I didn't like the piano. Okay.
I like this one. Time to start putting everything together. Stand up with a bit like this.
What if you don't like that? I'm going to like this one. I already read the reviews.
Will you let me pay attention? So this one has to go. I like, this is cool. So this one
sticks in there like this, like that. That feels actually really nice. What a piece of shit.
All right. Looks good. Flip it around. It is all the, it is satisfying. It is.
Flip the whole thing over and we've got someone looks like to be at the twin.
It goes in here like this, right? Did somebody? No. Somebody gave money though.
$10 just came in from Shpee. Shpee shawl. Thank you for the 10 bucks, man. That's cool.
We need to, I need some more light. Don't you just see my information?
That's too much. And you will rise with the sun. No, that's, you can't see anything.
I just needed to point this way for a second. That's that one. All right. That looks okay.
That was a, that was not what I wanted to do. Like there. What is this? What is this? What is
this for? What is this for? What, what is this for? I don't know what this is for.
What do you do with this thing? It just sits there and looks nice for a second.
The box line is in the way. That's the problem. I'm like at a campfire.
Oh, forget it. It looks, it's fine. Crack this open a little bit. Just give me a second
because it's like, it's too dark right here. There. Incoming joke. Nope. Incoming more light
so you can see. But I need to turn that off. I don't, I don't know what Phillips, you need to,
I need to ask somebody at Phillips a question. You've got a great product here.
Why am I so concerned about this? Like don't look at my password. Like what are you hiding?
Okay. That's better. All right. Back to it. Where's this going to go? Right here. That's
fine. Needed more light. All right. Those are both on. Let's check everything's properly
in place. Are your pieces neatly lined up like this? Yes, they are. Now we need from sheet B.
Wherever the hell, wherever the hell that is. This is sheet B. Show you taxes.
So I don't think, I don't think so. So we need the little M's. So we need one, two, three.
Build me a waifu. Well, this is a pedal. I don't, I don't think that's what you're asking
for. I'm sorry. Let's go. It's a fan blade triplets labeled one, two, three, and they're
eager to join our slot party. Good thing we've got some more slots along the big pieces. Okay.
So I'm assuming we're going to go one, two, three. I know how to do this. It's going to go
bang, bang, bang. Look at that. Beautiful. So bang, two, bang. Yeah. Look at that.
Look at that. Okay. Gift subs. Oh shit. Pocket Pondling has gifted five community subs. Cheers
to that, man. Thank you. Thanks to the five gifted community subs. You're the man.
Congratulations to those five lucky contestants. Finally bring back the pieces we started off
with. This thing. Get that over here. And this is going to be the guts. This is going
to be the real guts. Oh, this is popping out. Oh, fuck. Somebody. Okay. Matters of
Darkness. Thanks for the five community subs. We've got 10 gifted subs here from
Pocket Pondling and Matters of Darkness. Thank you both. Big subs coming in. Thank
you guys a lot. More gifts. You can't. Come on. They're gifts. All right. So lay them
out flat and place our slotty structure on top. It's a little tab. Should fit right into
the middle holes. What the hell are you talking about? Right here. Okay. That sticks just in.
Does it though? This tab is poking out. Those are in. As in as they can be. Okay. Looks just
like the on the box on the picture. Now fold it all up. This is the part that I love.
This is why you are all watching. To see this right here. This the skeleton closing
it over the muscles. The bone marrow, I mean. There you go. You ready? How many people would
have just left if I did that? You think? That was very satisfying. Okay. So then there's the
base pedal. Beginning to look like a proper base. Now grab this piece. The little hand glider
from B. This one. Ah, okay. There it is. See the labo writing on it. So that one,
let's punch that out. Okay. Okay. That was inherently satisfying. It was.
Here's a pro tip. Skip. All of it is going to fall. Fold, fold, fold, fold, fold, fold. Up,
up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. And then it's going to go in.
How does it go in? This is the part where he fucks it up. No, I got to get the camera
in a good spot after this because this is like, we're making a car. You better believe
I'm going to bring this to the green screen stream as a wheel and like a pedal. I'm gonna
gonna have a wheel in my hands. Okay, so that's that. This is a bird. This is
gonna be a petal at the moment. Alright, where does it go? So this part turns
this way so you can see inside, and then flip the whole cover piece and we're
ready to get constructing. Like that. And then that goes, first is up with the
two tabs. The tops lie them both in at once. Like that. Okay, let me get
this folded. What about back here though? They all fold up. Okay, this is the part
where he fucks it up. Not quite. Not yet at least. Okay, then the bottom tab goes
in. Slide it. Snap. And then side to side. Easy enough. Okay. Wait for the
crunch. Wait for the crunch. Oh, that was a little too much of a crunch.
Alright. Done. Ruined. I didn't ruin it. What are you talking about? It's perfect. Lo and
behold, we've completed the base of the petal. Alright, thanks everybody for
watching. That's gonna be the end of the labo segment of the stream. Now we're
gonna go on to part two. Oh, make sure you got your dongle bag. I gotta get the
dongle bag up here. So wait, what do I need? What pieces? Part two of 183.
Okay, making the actual petal. Make sure you've got the special dongle part
bag. You don't have to open it yet. Just know where it is. Okay, that's
fine. I know where it is. Remove this one piece. This is a big one.
Almost there. By the way, this is a game in itself. If I spill wine on the ground
tier, I lost a lot of money. So, like, just keep... That's a game,
essentially. What the... Pocket Polly just gave 10 community subs. Pocket
Polly coming in with 10. Holy shit. That's a lot of money. Well,
congratulations to the 10 people that got this massive amount of community
subs given away by Pocket Polly and others in Matters of Darkness as well.
That's a lot. Thank you, dude. So what is the... Is there any criteria to get
the random sub? Or is it just... You just get it randomly. Someone in the
chat does. It just happens. Damn. You just can't be subbed. Okay.
That's pretty cool. I didn't really know how it worked. You probably have
to be following. I mean, I don't have any settings set up like that if
they exist. Whatever they are, they're a default. But thank you, dude. Thanks
so much for your massive amount of subs that you've just gifted. So we got
this piece. I'm going to give 10 more. Hold on. What are you doing? Oh my
God. There's another 10. There it is. 10. That's 20 community subs from
Pocket Polly. Holy shit. I'm going to put this out of the way for now
because we've got another piece here that we need to work with. But damn
Pocket Polly. At the end of the day, thank you, man. Like, that's
that's a lot. Is it 26 now? Well, congratulations to the lucky
double dozen here. Oh, he bought the actual labo this time. I had the
other labos before. I just did... I did the pizza thing because it
worked. That'll be good. Well, there's a couple more little tabs.
You know what? I have one complaint about the labo. Can you pre-tab it?
Can you pre-punch tabs? I mean, I know it's a bit cheeky and oh no,
but it's fun to like punch out the little tabs. It just makes a mess.
I already got enough for cycling. Now I got to find all these little
bits and pieces. Oh my Lord.
Ragharnoi. Ragharnoi just gave out 10 community subs. 10 from
Ragharnoi. Thank you so much, dude. Oh dear. That's like 40 subs in.
That's like 50 subs almost in like fucking 10 minutes. I better make
like a good stream. Jesus, man. Thank you. Thank you so much.
That's a lot of money and a lot of people. You guys are fucking awesome.
Thanks. Hopefully you're having a good time.
Let's head back into this. Then I'm already getting like greasy.
All right. Folds. All of them. I know they're everywhere.
All right. So fold everything. Oh my God.
Are you guys having a gift sub fight? That's 10 from Multi Trip.
Holy shit. I don't know what to do about this.
Like Rampaging Scrub, five. Multi Trip, 10.
Rampaging Scrub, five. Time for slime, five.
Five, five, five. This is madness.
Madness, darkness, another five.
Oh, whoa. All right. Hold on a second. Hold on a second.
That was just 20. I saw 20 from Kairatobi.
Kairatobi just gave 20 community subs. Madness, darkness just gave another five.
Oh, like dude, it's like drink. Okay. Thank you all for so much.
I thank you. I hope you think it's worth it.
That was like fucking almost 100 people.
InstaGator just gave out five. Thank you InstaGator for your five.
Kairatobi, 20. Thank you so much, everybody.
Such concludes the gifted sub portion.
It blows my mind all the time, guys. Like seriously.
That's five from Jamie. Jamie2803. Throwing the hat into the party here.
Five more from Jamie. Speech, speech.
I don't have a speech. I just hope that the next year that you watch
you think is worth the money. I hope the next month, the next 30 days you watch
you think is worth it because obviously it's every 30 days.
And if you don't think it's fun anymore after 30 days,
then you should not pay me money. You know what I mean?
I can't, I just can't believe that people, that's 10 from Visual Warlock.
Thank you for the 10 community subs. Thank you so much, dude.
Thank you, all of you. 10 fucking subs, 5 subs, 20 subs, 10 subs, 10 subs.
That's a lot of money. I think sometimes it gets like lost.
You know what I mean? Like just how much of money that is to give to somebody.
Ramshackle gave out, giving out five here.
Thank you so much, dude. Thank you Ramshackle for your five community subs.
Thank you, everybody. Like I'm essentially speechless at the moment
because every time something like this happens, it's like, it's a weird feeling.
Another five from, from Vertibral Giant.
We're getting, this is, this is definitely over 100.
Am I doing this right? Am I doing the level correct?
I just saw somebody was angry because of this.
I'm sorry. I, I don't want you to be angry.
I want you to have fun.
You guys are fucking, this is like ridiculous.
Oh, the gifted subs are stalling.
Oh no. Oh my God.
Pocket Pauling just give a hundred dollars right now.
A hundred bucks. One hundred dollars.
You'll see it in a second.
There's so many subs coming through Streamlabs.
They can't even like keep up, I don't think.
Holy shit.
Well, Pocket Pauling, that's, you've, you've dumped at least two to plus three
hundred dollars right now.
Thank you for the hundred dollars here.
Hey, Jeremy, it was my birthday yesterday and I got cash.
So I thought I would be cash money of me to gift subs with the money I got.
Thank you for being a positive force.
And also thank you for drinking box wine on stream.
It's validation.
And, and I support you.
Cheers, man. Happy birthday.
I hope you had a good one.
I, I'm shocked and honored and I don't, I, every kind of emotion that you
would want to give me your blank birthday money, dude.
Like I, thank you.
I, I hope you had a good time.
I hope you were taken care of and I hope you took care of yourself.
Much love to you.
Because that's a lot of fucking money.
Um, and don't ever forget that because like I was about to say, it gets lost
sometimes like, oh, like 10 bucks, 20 bucks, like two dollars, one dollar,
one dollar, 20 bucks, a hundred bucks, a hundred bucks, a hundred bucks.
It gets lost in like a river and in a lot of cases.
And I really don't want that to ever be the case.
So I hope you never feel that that's the case.
But it, you throw your money in a river.
No, I hope you know what I mean by that.
But happy fucking birthday to you, pocket polling.
I hope it was a great one.
But anyways, thank you for, thank you for just like giving me a guy on the internet.
Like right now, like four or $500 probably right there, whatever that was.
I will put it to good use.
I promise.
So, uh, why, where were we here?
Going, we'll go into more box wine.
That's, that's correct.
So we've got all these pieces, all these things.
Everything needs to be folded.
I got those.
I got this.
I got this one.
So then where does this go in the grand scheme of things here?
Did I get that?
I did.
Hey, remove the five piece from sheet B.
So sheet B only has one more piece after this.
And it's the weird like toaster looking thing in the bottom right.
Celebratory dab.
Fine.
That initiated notes for a second.
The madman.
He's gone crazy.
Wow.
You stopped drinking.
What a lightweight.
I just filled it like not even 10 minutes, five minutes ago.
Do you know how many, how many glasses of wine are in this fucking box of wine?
29.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's 29 wine enthusiasts say this is their best buy award.
There's three liters in here.
Nintendo Davo.
Jesus.
All right.
Got these five pieces.
Flip it over.
Of course, rip all these little knobs out.
Compact liters.
Three liters.
Derma has a strong neck.
I don't, my neck always hurts.
Is that what that means?
The $400 dab.
Three liters is two glasses.
Three liters is like 20 glasses of wine.
Like at least 15.
So then this folds in half.
And then all these stick in the middle here.
Okay.
So pocketpalling just gave another $50.
Thank you for the $50 on top of all the other huge amount of money
that you've given today.
Pocketpalling.
50 bucks.
Thanks for the birthday wishes, everyone.
Also, Derma, please don't make yourself sick.
I'm drinking box wine right now, but that doesn't mean you should.
Sorry for giving more money.
Don't, you don't, don't apologize.
Just, I appreciate it.
I really do.
I hope you know that he's, he's drunk.
He's drunk and donating two things you never want to do.
Drunk and donate.
Oh my God.
People are like giving money now saying like, sorry.
Somebody stop him.
No.
That's okay.
Just I'm drinking.
We're drinking box wine together.
It's a box wine kind of day.
It's always a, this is like, guys, this is so cheap too.
You don't have to go buy the most expensive bullshit.
People go, but here, cheap doesn't mean bad.
You could go buy Fireball and that's bad, right?
We all agree on that.
But like a box of wine, it's like, this is like $17, but like six days worth of alcohol.
All right.
What do I do with these?
This is, this tastes good.
This is, this is, this is good.
I'll give it a stamp.
Black box premium wines, the red blend.
That's, it's good.
If you, if they're watching right now, why would they be?
It's not like a, this is not a video game.
This is not like a game.
Oh, the dev is watching right now.
Why am I that much of a fucking ego maniac?
Like, oh yeah, you know, black box is probably watching right now.
What?
This is like 2,900, but there's like 50 trillion people on earth.
You think like the black box fucking wine smeller is watching this right now?
But yeah, red blends are always the best.
Always buy a red blend.
If you don't like red, you'll probably like a red blend.
Wait, what?
This is just a money stream for, okay.
First of all, Boston, Boston game gave $55 and 50 cents, $55.
They just say, sorry, don't say sorry.
Thank you.
Boston game for the huge amount of fucking money.
And then RT, RT game crowd came in with a hundred bucks.
Thank you.
RT game crowd, a hundred bucks just to make sure you don't recover emotionally.
But for real, thanks for the years of content, man.
You're my all time favorite creator and a massive influence on my own content
and wanting to drop a hundred on you for ages.
Go get yourself some more wine and cardboard.
Thank you, RT.
That's insane to hear that.
You're doing a great fucking job, dude.
Like, you really are.
Those of you that don't know who RT is, he's fucking killing it.
You're doing great, man.
I'm more than happy for you, for real.
But is Jerma okay?
I'm fine.
I'm like, I'm very happy right now.
How could I be not happy right now?
But thank you so much.
That's amazing to hear.
I just got like $700 in 25 minutes.
I'm kind of like, I don't really know what to do.
I hope you guys, look, I say it a lot, but this here, this,
no, this is, this is, this, this is number one.
Nothing else takes place of number one, except for my dog.
And like, I don't know, like my mother.
And like, I don't know, maybe like my girlfriends up there, like number one.
My health.
So maybe not number one.
You're probably like number like four, but you're like in the top five, right?
Under mom.
You guys are under mom, right?
That's a pretty big deal.
We're number four in the top five.
But all jokes aside, the only thing I care about with this stream
is making sure that people have fun.
And if you don't, then I hope you tell me.
Like right now, like I'm sure people are like,
this probably leads to a thousand people here that are going like,
you're going to build the fucking thing, dude?
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, just wait.
I'm going, I'm trying.
But for real, you guys mean a lot to me.
The stream does the whole thing does.
So I've never thought differently and I never will.
So, okay, much love to you.
Are you going to build that fucking thing, stupid?
It's hard.
It's cardboard for kids.
Boston game, Boston game, give another $50.
Sorry about the sorry, but in all seriousness,
I've enjoyed your content for years and this is the least I can do
to repay all the joy and entertainment you've given me.
I mean, what about my repayment to you?
You don't even like, look at where I am right now.
I moved to Las Vegas and I'm like working with a studio
and I'm going to be doing a bunch of shit on like,
who like, who made that happen?
You know what I mean?
Sure, I run the stream and like I make the stuff,
but if there weren't people here,
supporting the stream and giving the fucking money
and then if there weren't people here,
then I wouldn't be able to do it.
Don't forget that.
It's important.
But I've been on the same step for 40 minutes.
Well, but there were like some extenuating circumstances.
Like a thousand dollars came in
and I'm going to give it the attention that I believe it deserves.
So I'm sorry.
There's so many subscribers.
That subscription noise is going to happen
for like the next 20 or 30 straight minutes.
I created, I made this.
Oh my goodness.
That's, that's from, that, that's how many notifications,
pick up all the notifications.
That's from probably like 20 minutes ago
and five more subs from bet three.
Cheers everybody for real.
Smoke if you got them.
If you don't want that smoke, smoking is bad for you.
All right.
So these all need to go.
The, am I doing this the right way?
I think I am, right?
Because, right?
That's the correct way, right?
The piece is the wrong, wrong way.
That's not, well, you match it up with the, like, okay.
No, that's okay.
They were right there.
You're right.
Right.
And when you're right, you're right.
You just are.
Why is he taking an hour to do this?
If you just jumped in or if you were here like an hour ago.
Okay.
So that's it.
I got to, I got to explain.
But the people that, I should have just been staring at this.
Like, I don't understand how this, how does this work?
Like, all right.
Well, I started this and then there was, there was a lot of money came in.
So I, I had to stop for like a while.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Check your work.
Work looks good.
Everything up on the side looks all right.
You tell me.
That's bad.
That was a bad view.
Time to join up to the big fat guy.
Fold up this edge.
Maybe we're the right way.
No, we're not the right way.
So that goes up.
This goes through.
Streamer sucks.
Don't be so mean to me.
All right.
So then this part.
I changed my mind.
Can I please have my $700 donation back, please?
All sales are final.
Whoa.
Hold on a second here.
There's RT's money.
Big money is getting to him.
No, I don't even want that to happen.
I need to continuously proud myself.
I can't.
I won't.
Okay.
There we go.
So that's not sitting still though.
Why is this not flat?
This is not flat.
Mine's not flat.
Why?
That's the Vegas gambling stream money.
This is freaking me out, man.
This like popsicle stand looking shit here.
Okay.
This goes up.
I want you guys to be able to see.
So that goes up like this.
Like that.
And then it folds all the way.
I never did this one.
Fuck, I never did this one.
There it is.
Okay.
Hold on.
I need to make sure that's tight.
Should I get the little flaps here?
Can you get a casino stream?
I would probably do something like that for fun,
but you cannot film in a casino in Vegas.
You will get slapped in the face.
If you, if I was just sitting there like,
oh, hey guys, should I hit on black, I got blackjack.
It would be like, it would be bad.
Hold the side.
You rolled up with one hand like that.
Like an ice cream sandwich.
Flip this one up.
Use a hidden camera.
I'm not going to jail for our stream.
All right.
Well, I need to pay attention.
This comes up.
Do it for views.
Look at that.
This is going to sound so nice.
That goes in there, right?
Come on.
Tell me it does.
I know it does.
I've seen this movie.
For content.
That's not a hidden camera in a casino is not.
How is that like content?
Just go watch cops.
You'll see the same material from the side.
All the taps come up.
I don't think I folded these yet.
Build a labo in the casino.
I'll tell you what I was actually going to do.
What I thought would be funny.
I'm sorry that I'm going to spoil this
because it was a really, really good idea.
I was going to, there are a lot of mountains around here.
There's like two that way.
There's like three that way.
Vegas is surrounded by mountains.
And I thought it would be funny.
This is not going to spoil it.
Don't worry.
I thought it'd be funny if I built the labo
like on the top of like the summit of one of the mountains.
Like, oh, we're doing a labo today.
Labo.
And then it's just me like wind gusting
and like trying to build a labo on the summit of a mountain.
Like Las Vegas just has so many mountains everywhere.
So in every direction do it.
I there wasn't enough time.
I'd have to like, that's a huge project.
Way more than I think anybody realizes.
I don't think I would even be able to have internet up there.
That was a huge problem with the hot air balloon stuff too is
you just don't fucking have internet.
Like it's just not possible to like get it
actually like the way that I really,
really, really would want it to happen.
Try to climb Everest so you can build a labo.
Please come in.
Oh, oh no.
Okay.
Is that supposed to happen?
It is.
Just use a really long cable.
This is why people give you money.
Well, it's kind of, it's a cycle that
you know, I use the money.
So if somebody, like for instance, this money right here,
this is probably going to go directly.
Oh, the way that I get paid from Twitch
is like every month I want to like,
you know, do something that something different
or that costs money or that's where the money goes.
If you're curious as to where like,
oh, where do I, where does my sub money go?
Where does my like bit money go?
I mean, I'm going in front of a green screen in like five days
and I have a shitload of props
and we're doing like a whole green screen community event.
That's kind of like, that's kind of where it goes.
Every like 30 to 45 days I try to
think of something to do, you know,
and why can I not do this?
Am I doing this wrong?
This comes up.
Okay.
I was like, what the fuck am I doing wrong?
There we go.
Yeah, now look, I'll be completely and totally
see-through about this and I'll be transparent about it.
Of course, the money also goes to me living out here
and me living and expenses and eating and food and groceries
like, but a huge amount of it goes to the fuck
right to this room, right to immediately back
because I always told myself years ago
if I was ever in a position to be able to
do something like this,
but I was going to try to do it, right?
And I wanted to do the things that I wanted to do.
What the fuck is in there?
Can you see that?
Oh, you can.
Okay.
So it's this these come up because it okay.
So that folds in and that one goes in like that, right?
So wasp in your labo.
Put it out.
Put it in.
Show finances on stream.
Let me get a refill.
If you want, if you want like money information,
the green screen stream will probably be about
in total probably 1200 bucks to just to get it done.
And that's that's really reasonable considering all
the shit that I'm going to be doing.
I'm going to stop donating.
He's getting too powerful.
Was that a hundred bucks?
Add that to the green screen list.
By the way, I have to do that.
Pocket Pauling given to the hundred dollars.
Thank you, dude.
Jeremy, did you know I'm running out of things to say to be honest.
Thank you for being my favorite YouTuber
and you deserve every single cent.
You deserve the world.
Also shout out to blue 2018
and also my pronouns are they and them
for future reference, transgender pride.
Absolutely.
Thank you so much.
Pocket Pauling.
I don't know.
I don't think I deserve the world.
I really don't.
I just try to do my best,
which I think is something that
that's all I care about.
I just want to do my best.
And if my best is good enough, then it is.
If it isn't, then it's not.
But for the future, I will keep that in mind for sure.
And yeah, you give it a fucking shitload of money.
I don't want to take over the world.
I wouldn't want that.
I feel like I don't think it would.
I don't think it would go well.
I would replace every M&M.
You know, that'd be the first thing I would do.
Oh, what's the first order of business?
Oh, well, you know, we got health care.
We've got, we've got like taxes.
No, I'm going to replace every M&M,
which is with with green M&Ms.
That's it.
I like that.
That's gonna take a long fucking time.
It's gonna take a lot of work.
A lot of work.
All right.
What piece am I on?
Why would you do the green M&Ms?
Because those have the best candy coating flavor.
That's it.
Done.
I'm done.
I did it.
Why am I trying to yell to him?
All right.
First flip the...
We got two now.
One, two.
Yeah.
Jerma, everything you know is a lie with that attitude.
Now we have to lick it shut.
It's like an envelope.
Which piece is this one?
This one.
So wait a minute.
Shut up, Nintendo.
Oh, stomp on it.
I'm not gonna...
Why would I stomp on this?
I can't fuck this place up.
Okay.
So then this now...
Now lay the base on top of the pedal.
I'm sure it can handle the weight.
Okay.
Roll the whole thing over on its side.
That bottom flap should tuck neatly under.
I am going to break this.
It probably will happen.
So roll on its side.
Like that.
I don't know what...
It wasn't the absolute heck fire.
Do you want me to do here?
Lock the pedal and base together.
So this folds down that.
And then this goes in like that.
Okay.
So they're right.
Am I doing that right?
Is that correct?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
Everything looks nice and secure.
Make sure it matches on what's on screen.
It does.
Flip it over.
That one goes down and this one goes...
Oh!
Uh-oh.
Is it lined up correct?
It might not be lined up right.
Yeah, it is.
That's in.
Looks nice, secure.
I hope it matches what's on screen.
It does.
It does, Nintendo.
Turn the whole thing over so you get the eyes.
And this is the part.
I didn't fold this part.
Yeah, it did.
Down, in, in, up, secure.
You got it.
Up, in, in.
Pedal is done.
Done.
Here it is.
Hey, am I making a shoe box?
No, this is a...
This is a...
I was gonna say United States Postal Service pedal.
What?
Okay.
Final check.
Get everything in the right place.
Pedal is getting tired of supporting the base,
so let's flip them right way up.
That's it.
All that for this.
And that's our base and pedal all joined up.
Here's to a long and happy relationship.
Now we're gonna need some rubber bands.
Okay.
There are two types to make sure you got the big ones.
Crack it open.
That was the slowest pedal.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
It's been an hour and 25 minutes.
I gotta...
Come on, we're gonna get snappy here.
Don't worry.
Where are the big ones?
There's only a few.
How many do I need?
Oh, there are worms in here!
Oh!
That's not funny.
Don't do that.
I mean, there are three big ones?
There's only three big ones.
Hopefully they gave me enough.
Do I have a defect?
Fucking defect, Nintendo?
All right, so we got three.
First, flip the whole pedal wide open.
Wow, so flexible.
Whoa, easy there.
Can mine do that?
What if mine can't do that?
I can't go that far.
Ah!
Ow!
I can't go the...
Ah!
It hurts.
I have 50 more dollars.
Ugh!
I can't believe these people
are still giving me this much money.
You guys are fucking incredible.
DivUSP gave 52 dollars.
Hey, Jerma, since this is basically a money stream...
I just want to donate, like, fuck it.
LOL.
But seriously though,
wanted to thank you for everything.
These past few months have been really bad.
Just depressing, stressful, and painful as hell.
But as of recent,
things have been getting slightly better.
Finally getting a job, building opportunities.
And even though I don't want to get my hopes up,
I feel like things are slowly improving.
I want to say thanks since your stream helped me out a lot.
First of all, I'm ecstatic
that you're starting to see some opportunities
and that things are starting to look up a little bit here.
I'm shocked every day, man,
that people...
I can help you, honestly.
I'm more than humbled and more than happy to do it.
I really hope you do well.
As a 33-year-old man, let me tell you,
it takes a long time.
It takes more than you think.
I remember 10 years ago,
when I was in my early 20s,
I was like, holy shit, what's happening?
What am I doing?
What do I have to do with my life?
I need to get a job, right?
I'm just in a college.
I had a fucking illness, right?
And you figure it out.
You just, you kind of do.
But thank you so much.
I hope you're on the right path.
I hope you are on the path that you want to be on, right?
Take care of yourself.
You're the most important person in the world,
especially up here.
So take care.
Thank you so much for even being here, man.
That's advice that I needed.
It's advice that I needed, too.
When I was 25, 26, 24,
as somebody that's, you know, a little older,
you kind of figure it out.
It took me like seven years straight.
I'm just like skipping the movie here.
Okay, hold on.
But thank you so much, dude.
I wish you the best, for real.
You don't look 33.
That's great, because when I'm 40, I'll look 30.
But I'm losing my hair,
so that's another problem entirely.
All right, so we're going to do our stretch here.
So those of you guys that stretch,
how far can you go?
I can't, like, this is my,
I'm lying on my back,
and these are my legs straight in the air.
So like, I can't do this.
Like, that hurts, right?
I could do that, but like, this hurts a lot.
Okay, so where's the rubber band?
This goes through here,
through the little rubber band slots.
I'm assuming that's what those are.
Make sure it's perfect.
I tried stretching and accidentally broke my mother's neck.
Be more, be careful.
What?
That goes in there?
Am I wearing a toupee?
No, it's real!
Not a toupee.
I actually, I had a huge confidence boost.
Wait a minute.
I had a huge confidence boost.
I want to get my hair cut, right?
So I got a haircut,
those of you that didn't notice.
Didn't even notice my haircut.
So, in the haircut place,
as I'm getting my haircut,
haircut lady says to me,
to my face into the mirror, right?
Because I'm looking in the mirror,
looking at her face through the mirror,
she's looking at me through the mirror.
Wow, you have really nice hair.
How old are you?
What'd you say?
33.
It was great.
And then I walked out of there like,
like I was a fucking maniac,
you know what I mean?
On top of the world.
My mouse is not there.
Those of you guys that caught that,
I'm sorry.
And now my mouse doesn't do this.
This does.
All right, lift the pedal all the way up.
The rubber band's not twisted.
No, that looks fine, right?
It's perfect.
Now let's close the pedal back down.
That's much better.
The pedal and base are complete.
Time check!
60 to 90 minutes?
It's been, it's been 90 minutes.
They say that to everybody.
They're like, don't know what they say.
I mean, I gave her a good tip.
Is that what she was,
is she wanted the tip?
Did I get like,
did I get like tip scammed?
No, I was like,
hold on, how much you want?
Hey, take that.
Whatever.
She still said it.
So part three, this needs to get,
we make the frame.
Let's get this out of the way.
We need D.
This can move as well.
D!
Oh, it smells like gasoline.
Why?
Oh my God.
Pocket Pauling.
Jess gave another $50.
Pocket Pauling says,
if there's one thing I actually want from you,
from my B day actually,
it'd be for you to tell us one thing.
Just say this one thing.
It's very important.
He's a no life nerd who's never gotten something,
a cat before in their,
a cat before in their entire life.
The full, okay.
What is a cat?
Cat is a cat.
Okay.
Cat.
What is a thesaurus for a cat?
Kitten.
Cat.
Feline.
Garfield.
Pussycat.
Ding ding.
Said it.
Wiser words have never been spoken before or since.
No, I'm sure they have.
Just edit it.
Just do the fucking sentence mixing.
Try to run from my past.
He's socially awkward.
I am not socially awkward.
You ever meet me in public?
Hey, fine.
You want to talk socially awkward?
Those are your eyes.
Like walking down the street here.
Danny.
Danny, what's up, man?
Danny, how you been?
It's good to see you again.
Are you, yeah, both shake your hand for sure.
I got a good grip like you do.
We both have good grips.
Both not socially awkward at all.
So you still at the printing company?
Nice, dude.
Nice.
Awesome.
Me, no.
I do online media.
It's like a thing where you, it's online presence.
An online presence.
Online.
How's the printing company going?
See?
That's how every conversation I have with people goes.
Not socially awkward at all.
Nice job.
But pocket polling, thank you so much.
You've gone above and beyond at this point monetarily.
I took them both out and I wasn't supposed to.
I fucked it up.
Whatever.
We'll save it.
Just need these two.
You missed my donation?
Those of you that are, almost hit the mic.
That was the right one, right?
Yeah.
Those of you that are somewhat new to the channel potentially,
I don't read anything really during the stream unless it's,
obviously, if it's $50, like 20 subs.
Those are, they're huge amounts that I want to obviously address immediately.
But we do a hangout after the stream where I go over all the bits,
all the bit messages and everything.
So I just don't do it during the stream.
He only reads huge donations.
It's not untrue.
So I can't be like, no, it's not untrue.
Fix the Discord integration.
Well, I'm a moron.
So, but I haven't done that yet.
I will someday.
All right, I'm ready.
This goes like this, like this.
Good.
Let's fold it all up.
I know how to do that.
You guys can still, you might need to turn the brightness up a little bit here
just because it is getting a little dark.
It is 440.
It's, why is time, I'm time traveling right now.
Oh, what happened to Lego Island?
Okay, so let me explain this while I have them in it here.
So everyone wants me to play Lego Island.
And I bought some, I got a raspberry pea.
I got a raspberry pea.
I was going to do a thing where I built a raspberry pea computer
and install Lego Island on it and play.
And that was going to be the shtick.
Make sure you do your research before you buy anything.
This is, it can't run Windows on here.
You can't install it.
You have to go through.
And there he goes.
You can't install Windows on your pea.
So now I just have a pea.
What am I supposed to do with my pea pea now?
That I don't know.
Somebody wanted me to prove it and it was there.
I can run Linux, but Lego Island does not run on Linux.
It runs on Windows.
So I would have to get Linux installed on my pea.
And then install a virtual machine on Linux for Windows 98 on the pea.
Which is already slow enough.
It would be like 0.02 frames a second.
But that does not mean that I will not use that for something.
I'm going to build a dumb computer at some point.
I have all the peripherals.
I'm going to build a fucking computer with that thing.
And we're going to do something with it.
I don't know what we're going to do.
He's saying it wrong.
I'm sorry.
Oh, italics told me last night to make sure I didn't say pea.
I said it.
All right.
Let's fold the Raspberry Pi.
Whatever.
I can't even fucking run Lego Island.
What's it worth?
But it actually came with a, so the original original plan was
that's like a Google voice recognition box.
And I was going to make that on stream.
We were going to make a robot that I could talk to on stream.
And it uses a Raspberry guy.
And oh my God.
It's a 100.
The instructions are 100 steps long.
There was no way I was going to, there was just no way.
And it needed my IP address.
And like, I'm not going to show my IP address on stream.
That's like a death sentence.
Oh, by the way, here's my IP.
See ya.
Like you needed to, it has to like link up to your internet and show it.
All right.
So that's all folded.
It's fine.
It needs an internal IP.
Oh, that's yeah, that's fine.
It would just connect to like a router.
But I, I don't, I, we just got our internet fixed.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You know what I'm saying?
All right.
So make pizza, make pizza.
Oh, I didn't do it.
I thought it was in the slot.
Oh, got it.
What if somebody guessed your IP address?
There's, I don't, that's not even like a fucking reality.
That's like somebody trying to guess cryptocurrency wallets.
I'll get it one day.
Looks good.
What is that?
When is the poll for the green screen stream?
That is a great question.
And you will get it.
I will tell you at the end of the stream.
I forgot to do it.
What do I need?
The big one.
There's only one, right?
This is the only one.
I guess.
You guys can narrow it.
I don't, what, just relax, man.
Like, come on, relax.
There's no need for this.
All right.
So now we're going to need the grip stickers from the bag.
Their rough surface will help our pedal from sliding around.
Okay.
What is the purpose of the handles on the table serve?
So a grip sticker.
If you have trouble spotting the gas between the stickers,
try gently bending them a bit.
Okay.
I do.
I see them.
Kind of.
We've got to get some brightness in here, I think.
Not yet.
Relax.
So how many would just do one strip?
Let's take a look at where the sticker is going to go.
It's going to go in the pizza.
Just don't say food items.
I'm hungry.
So one, two there, and then one all the way in the back.
There.
Move a long sticker from the sheet.
Careful you don't get it stuck on anything.
Where does it go so I can prepare it?
One into the sticker there, and then it's going to wrap around
all the way around and then there.
You got it.
You got it, man.
How'd you like that?
Oh, okay.
So let's go thumb side first.
Right here.
Flip it around and then this goes along the edge.
That, that, and like that.
Sweet!
Okay, big bits.
We got, we did, we did have, we had $10 from a free iPod.
What the fuck do I do with my life?
I'm stuck.
Boat.
And hearing you say that figuring shit out takes time really helps.
With the anxiety that comes with those thoughts.
Wish I could join in on the big bits, but I'm broke,
so just take the rest of my bits that I have lying around.
Thanks for making the best content.
Thanks to the free iPod, first of all, and the $10.
Yeah, as somebody that did not even understand the position
that I could even possibly be in,
five to ten years ago, I was just up in the air.
I just had no idea what was going on.
I didn't know where I was or where I was going,
and you just kind of figure something out.
It just kind of happens.
And it might be something you don't even know.
If you, it's like, oh, I'm going to do this,
and I'm going to do this, and I'm going to do this.
That's probably not true.
It might be something else entirely.
So thank you so much for your iPod.
How did I sustain myself before Twitch?
I had all kinds of odd jobs.
I did videography.
I was a substitute teacher.
I, it was mostly videography.
I filmed weddings.
Just freelance.
I did that for a long time.
I did, I worked at, I was like an aide.
I was a teacher's aide for a long time as well.
But subject, I didn't teach a certain subject.
I just was a substitute teacher for a school district, so.
But you just kind of do whatever
until you find out what you're going to do.
And sometimes it is, it kind of comes out of left field.
I had to teach math once, right?
Yeah, I've had to teach math a couple of times,
and it was just, I had no idea what the fuck to do.
It was bad.
And it always sucks because when you know that
the students know way more than you, and it's very clear,
it's just embarrassing.
It really is fucking embarrassing.
I remember a kid shit himself in class.
I, why would, no, first of all, I did not,
I need to fold this like that.
You teach freshman driver's ed and it's hell.
I could probably teach driver's ed.
I'm a very good real life driver.
This goes right in the middle, right?
Like this, all the way through.
It's a tight fit, but you can do it.
And then all the way through.
I feel like I'm in candlelight right now.
One side and the other.
There it is, nice and snug.
Oh, I gotta pee.
Don't go anywhere.
Don't go anywhere, I gotta pee.
How do I turn the BRB screen on?
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's the wine.
This is the wine, this is the wine spigot.
Hold on, hold on, I got it.
All right, be right back.
I'm back.
It's like I never left.
Oh yeah, you think this is cool?
Watch this.
This chair was way too expensive.
It's not even good.
All right, now it's time for the lock.
The left frame on the pedal base.
Get over here, pedal base.
What?
The ones of this over here now.
We spent three hours on the part that says it'll be one.
Um, it's only been an hour and 55 minutes.
And about 30 of that was the huge amount of money that came in.
30 minutes or so.
So really only been about an hour and 30 minutes on this part.
What are you getting three?
Blame the donators.
Turn up the volume.
No, sure.
Don't listen to them.
Do what you want to do.
But what if they leave?
I don't fucking care.
Do what you want to do.
All right.
So left is this one over here.
Like this.
What the fuck does it do this?
Stand with the frame and base piece.
So stand this up.
That's standing this way.
And then I got a tab here.
So it's got to go like this.
We need brightness.
All right.
I'm going to say, do I need brightness?
And then I want everyone in the chat to say yes or no.
Do I need brightness?
Okay.
That's all I needed to hear.
Well, that's too much.
That's fine.
Make sure we don't get a little ghosting.
You know what I mean?
And turn the lights up probably a little bit higher.
That's good, right?
Not 15 FPS.
I don't want to keep it like that.
That looks fine.
Let me do the other one here.
This is what happens when you start streaming in the light
and it turns into dark.
Just kind of does this.
It's not 60 FPS.
I can't handle 60 FPS.
You can't even see faster than the human eye 24.
Let me break.
All right.
Where's the level?
Right there.
Okay.
Nice shirt.
Thanks, man.
All right.
So this goes in like that.
Stick it in.
And then the tab closes.
So this has to go in like this.
You can't see 4K.
Then you can see 4K.
And you can't see 4K, but your TV can.
Ooh, that fell.
That went in.
Hopefully that's the right way.
Yes.
Is that a Mani shirt?
No.
It's like a $12 bargain bin Nightwing shirt.
That's it.
And Rage Grandpa just gave $10.
Thank you.
No message.
No, it's Nightwing.
I was going to be Nightwing for Halloween this year,
but I was too fat to be in the suit.
I looked ugly.
It looked shitty.
It was like my stomach hung out and it didn't look good.
And if you go out, if you're going to go out
and you're going to wear like a Nightwing shirt
or you're going to be like Nightwing.
Oh boy, you bet you got to, you can't just,
you can't have like fat stomach.
It was like, and like, wow, look at, I'm like,
look at how sexy I can look in my fucking Nightwing spandex.
No way.
Like if I shook my stomach, you'd hear fucking liquid.
Nightwing was a loser.
All right.
Whoa.
Let's keep going here.
Oh, you read that one.
Yep.
I did.
I read them all, guys.
German, does German pay attention to chat?
I read them all.
All of them, all of them, all of them.
That one, even this one, this one.
Yep.
He won't read this.
Yes, he will.
All right, let's do the,
let's get this one hour and 60 minute piece done.
Okay, there's this one.
I'm going to need another one.
Okay, I know this one.
I can do it quick.
Let's move this out of the way.
We don't need it for now.
Fold, fold, fold, fold.
If you read this one, scream Inspector Gadget.
I'm not going to scream.
I just said Inspector Gadget, which proves that I read it.
All right, the whole thing folds up.
Just fold, fold, fold, fold, fold.
This is the other side of the pedal.
How am I going to get the camera set up so you can see everything?
That's going to be weird, isn't it?
One hour and 50 minutes.
Don't you mean two hours?
No, two hours would be one hour and then 60 minutes go by and that's two hours.
So it has not been two hours.
It's been one hour and 50 minutes.
Well, it's been two hours and two minutes.
So that's wrong.
You said 60.
I know one hour and 60 minutes have to go by for an hour to be counted.
Somebody said two hours, one hour and 50 minutes, but that's not it.
There's an extra 10 minutes there, man.
So an hour passed.
No, I'm making the point that somebody said that it had been two hours
and it was an hour and 50 minutes.
One hour, 59 minutes, and 60 seconds.
That's correct.
God, I'm glad somebody gets it.
Eat the cardboard.
I don't think I will.
All right.
So I always see you guys have to give me some info here.
I always see people say like, oh, eat that.
Eat cardboard.
Eat Weibo.
Chew on glass, right?
Are there streamers that you go in their chat and you say like, oh, eat pants.
And they're like, okay.
And they just talk.
Do they do that?
Is that like a thing?
Do you guys convince people to eat shit they're not supposed to eat?
Is that like a Twitch thing?
Vinny did it one time.
Oh, and Vinny ate his pants on stream.
Did?
He did.
Why?
Why did he do that?
I need more context.
Now I have to do it.
Why would I?
What?
Why?
I don't have to do it.
Is that?
Okay.
Make sure I did that right.
Did.
It was crazy.
He's a real mad man.
Open your window and scream out of it.
Okay.
I will.
I'm not going to.
I'm kidding.
Same thing with this.
Goes right there.
We're almost done with 5% of the whole labo.
Are you guys prepared?
Are you prepared?
Fix your posture.
My posture is flawless.
Okay.
We're fine.
Posture.
Look.
Anytime somebody says, oh, fix your posture.
You guys just go like, okay.
People don't sit like this.
Lick the cardboard.
I paid you.
Like talk to bottom or like how do you want me to do it?
Have I been gnomed today?
I haven't been gnomed in like a week.
Two weeks.
All right.
We did this part.
We're good.
Shave your beard on stream.
I already did that.
I already showed my fucking skills.
Where's that piece?
Read a book.
No, I'm playing the labo, man.
This is the only other time I'm ever going to get to do this.
You guys, you realize that, right?
This.
Hey, look.
I'm playing labo.
Gotcha.
Like I can't do this ever again.
So just let me have this.
What's it like getting the senior discount?
It's fucking awesome, actually.
You get like 20% off literally everywhere you go.
Well, what's it like saving money everywhere you go?
That's great, man.
It's great.
We want to say it sucks.
Well, that sucks.
I hate saving money everywhere.
Status quo on the green screen Thursday.
It's locked in with the studio I'm working with.
Thursday is the green screen stream Thursday afternoon Eastern time.
I'm going to get a haircut next week.
If I want the same as yours, what should I tell her?
Tell her you want the single piece swoop.
And she'll have absolutely no idea what you're talking about.
So this goes in like that, right here.
The default Fortnite dance has to happen.
It's not negotiable.
I'm not doing a Fortnite dance on a green screen.
I will be dead in 100 years, right?
Well, probably way sooner than that.
But I don't want a keyable Fortnite dance
that you can just anybody into.
We're talking like 80 years in the future.
I don't want that to be available for anybody to have.
No, why would I want that to be available for anyone
in like a thousand years?
All right, here comes the next piece.
So this comes down here
and we're going to do the same thing on this side
that we did on that one.
Stick it in here, right?
Wait, wait, wait.
Blue or blue facing in?
Nope, okay.
Yeah, I can't do that anyway.
Shove it in.
Shove it in there.
You got it.
Hope it was right.
Oh, I don't want to do it so bad
but people will cringe at me and shit.
But that's the point.
Take me to your leader.
You know what's going to happen.
Everyone's going to say it.
Everyone's going to go, oh, ho, ho, ho, ho.
I knew it was going to happen.
You didn't even.
Now it's all the only thing in the chat.
It's the only thing there.
It's the only thing in the chat right now.
You did this.
You did it.
Looks good.
This got it.
This got sick, dude.
All right.
Your pedal's been standing up for straight.
Why don't you lay it on its back?
This seems off.
Is it?
All right.
If you need time to take a rest,
now's my time to honka-chukka, honka-chukka.
Like, at the spell out.
Look, let me show you.
If somebody was snoring,
like, that's spelled out like this.
Like, I just said it as a word.
That's my favorite Pokemon, too.
Can't see the computer screen.
It's right here.
What are you talking about, man?
What are you talking about?
All right.
Let's fold it up.
Fold the tip.
I'm doing it.
I'm really doing it.
Okay.
Fold the tip.
I already did it.
Get a wax figurine of myself.
For what?
Yeah, that'll be like 25 grand.
You're folding it wrong.
I'm not folding it wrong.
You are.
No, you.
I'm not folding it wrong.
All right.
That comes up.
Both of them come up.
This fold.
I got it the wrong way.
This has to fold up.
Fuck.
Okay.
And this folds in.
Fuck.
Hold on.
I need this to be tighter.
Fuck, dude.
Okay.
This comes in.
Fuck.
Okay.
It goes all the way around.
And then it closes down.
There.
Folds down around and that sticks in there.
What ingenuity.
Same thing on this one.
Check it.
Look at it.
There you go.
There's your fucking shitty park bench.
Go easy on the wine.
We're good, man.
I have.
I'm having so much fun.
You know?
That's it for that.
Fold in the tip or refund all donations.
What are you talking about?
It's perfect.
What do you mean?
The top.
Fold the top.
The top is folded.
That's not the top.
That's an arm.
Fold the left arm is what you should have been saying.
Not fold the top.
This is the top.
That's the top.
This is the left arm.
Somebody just read.
Really?
I have way too much fun when I do this.
I really do.
I'm not even kidding.
I'm having like a fucking great time.
This is like I love this.
Okay.
So this goes like that.
This Nintendo Labo signature watermark goes down.
And that sticks in up here.
Weird, though.
Weird.
Like that?
Strange.
Interesting.
Weird, though.
How?
Slide into the slots in the frame.
You can do it one side at a time.
Okay.
Boom.
All right.
Earthquake test.
That's good.
We're good.
I'm not going to break it.
All right.
Logos down.
Attach the bridge to our rubber band from before.
Turn the whole pedal around.
Stretch the rubber band out.
Hook it over the bridge.
Now you're getting weird here.
All right.
So this has come up and then has to go through those slots.
Turn the pedal around.
So wait a minute.
One side.
Get out.
No.
Now it's twisted off.
Turn the pedal around.
And can this take this?
Stretch it out and around underneath.
This just feels...
This feels taut.
Ah, this is gonna break.
You'll control the toy compatible with your foot.
Try stepping on it to check how it feels.
Let's try it out.
That actually feels pretty good.
See?
That works, right?
I think it's done.
That's...
That's it, right?
Do you feel the tension?
I do.
I do feel the tension.
So we're good.
What have I done?
Get out of here.
All right.
Let's go.
Come...
The pedal is complete.
The whole pedal.
Two hours and 19 minutes.
Now we're gonna put the Joy-Con in.
It's time to take a quick little pedal.
Joy-Con.
Get the Joy-Con.
Get the blue one.
This one.
For those of you keeping track at home.
Those of you at home.
Shut up, Nightwing.
Wow.
I guess this comes all the way down.
Push the pedal all the way down with one hand and hold it there.
And it goes in like this.
That's gonna break, man.
Slide the Joy-Con into the hole with the minus button sticking out.
Make sure it's in.
How far in does it have to go?
All the way.
That's what it said.
That's what...
I can see.
What the fuck?
You just got rid of the blockage.
All right.
Good.
A little wonky but it's all right.
Why am I doing that?
All right.
Step on...
Step on me all you like.
Play now.
There's a game to play?
Hold on.
Wait.
There's a game?
What about Game Right Play?
We get to play a game already?
Yeah.
Come on.
I did it.
I got first place.
Ow.
It's just...
Okay.
It's that game with the little...
You have the trigger and the hold of your...
You know what I mean.
You got...
That's a weird foot.
Hold on.
Let me get...
Let me get my foot up there.
I can see my hands.
It's okay.
You can see me.
Never mind.
All right.
That was fun.
I want to build the rest before people scream.
No, I didn't want to exit.
Titan Quest?
All right.
It works.
So let's get back.
You can have more than one person play this.
Slot cards.
Circuit.
Pedal key and spray can.
What does this mean?
Meet the team.
Oh, there you are, Jeremy.
That's how it's my name.
I've been watching you through your webcam.
Are you spying on me?
You'll never take me alive.
I'm a little busy.
No, I wanted to make the rest.
Sounds great.
No, no.
Sorry.
No, but I can sense your enthusiasm.
From this day on, you are officially the fourth member of the Toy-Con development team.
Okay.
Technology wizard.
Just knows all kinds of things.
Oh, now let's introduce fucking Phineas.
From Phineas and Ferb.
They're all from the same fucking show.
Okay.
Am I locked in a basement?
I'm just like, I don't want to do it.
No, no thanks.
I don't know where you're doing it.
No, this is a spoiler.
Is that my hand?
This is a spoiler.
I don't want to see the spoilers.
B doesn't do anything.
I have to press let's get started.
All right.
Back, back.
Now, this one is only going to take 15 minutes.
This is the easy one.
Wait till I elbow drop that before the stream is over.
No, time me on this one.
I'm going to put a timer on it.
No, yeah.
Yeah, that's what's going to happen for this one.
I want a fucking 15 minute timer on the screen.
How do I add one?
Let's give me 20 minutes.
I have to get like a plugin or something, I think.
I don't think I can do it from just an OBS.
Just recount for you.
Okay.
Yeah, use your phone.
Use your phone.
Damn it.
I almost just locked my phone out for like three days.
Okay.
You ready?
Wait, hold on.
Two steps, key and Joy-Con.
I'm going to move this out of the way.
So it starts when I grab the paper.
So I need C.
This one is C, right?
Okay, so I grabbed it.
Okay, go.
Can you see it?
That's such a bad...
It's going to turn off.
That's going to turn off.
Like it's going to go to like my home screen.
I can see it.
Okay, let's go.
What do I need?
Empty, right?
Empty.
Okay, all right.
All right, let's go.
I'm almost one minute.
Let's start with the key.
This key.
This is the key.
This one here.
That's a key.
Make sure the piece...
Printing on it.
Flip it.
There's so many folds here.
It's going to take 20 minutes to do these folds.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Time!
One minute and 30 seconds.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Two.
Three.
All folded.
All done.
Go!
What's next?
Stop doing like a bad posture thing.
Like I'm doing like...
I'm trying to get you guys to go bad posture.
I don't know why.
This comes up.
Slides through.
Like that.
Then in.
Nice and snug.
That knee.
This.
Same thing on the other side.
It goes down and around.
Makes a little cube.
Like that.
Use a locking piece to hold everything in place.
Flip a piece over and fold it in half.
Three minutes.
That's not going to...
I'm not going to be close.
So it goes like that.
This one popped out a little bit.
Okay.
So then it goes in here like this.
So that's locked.
Spray through.
Just a moment.
Take a check that yours looks like this.
It does.
The two knobby bits poking up from one side.
It's in.
It looks like that.
It looks beautiful.
Looks better than your picture.
Dickhead.
All right.
No.
That was mean.
Now this piece may be small but it's tough.
Be sure to fold it cleanly and firmly.
These long thin bits are a bit tricky.
Use both hands.
I can feel the bass drum in my brain.
Is it loud?
Should I turn it down?
I don't know what the music sounds like because I can't hear it.
Somebody said that.
I didn't say that.
Four minutes.
No one said...
Yes they did.
I can hear the...
Scroll up.
You'll see it.
I want the guy that said it.
Come clean here.
This piece just won't come out.
Just perforate it already.
Why do I have to do this?
All right.
Fold it back.
Back.
Like this.
Oh this is...
I gotta be careful here for real because this will rip.
This one comes back.
Oh man.
There's so many little tiny pieces here.
Okay.
Just fold them all.
What's that thing from Roblox?
Wash your hands.
Wash your hair.
What are you talking about?
My hair is clean.
I take a shower every day.
Every single day.
Every tiny little piece needed.
15 minutes my ass.
This even...
This little folding bit alone is going to take 15 minutes.
You don't take a shower three times a day.
Who takes a shower three times a day?
Do you work in like the mud pits?
Like I don't...
Like do you work in like the mud?
You know what I mean?
Like you got that...
You got...
That's like...
I can understand if you worked like in like a place where you need to do it.
All right.
That's done.
Now where does it go?
Wine should not be on the table.
Nice fucking walnut desk.
I can't even put it on this.
Seven minutes.
Am I doing this right?
Yes I am.
That piece sticks in there.
Right?
Okay.
Fold, fold, up.
Fold, fold, up, in.
And then what the hell does this thing do?
In and then down?
It's in.
Okay.
Look.
Examine my work.
Okay.
Now check the other side.
You should see the tip through the opening.
Do I?
Kind of.
Yeah, I do.
The main part of the key is complete.
Mine's not even kind of fucked up.
847.
Some sort of many armed alien.
This piece requires extra clean folds.
Be sure to crease carefully along the fold line.
It's just like on screen.
The end result might surprise you.
Extra clean folds.
Can you think of anything else that has four arms
and two heads?
I can't.
Are we dealing with a new life form here?
If I had wine in my mouth,
I would have spit it into the camera.
All right, hold on.
Three showers per fold.
Extra careful.
Wine drunk.
Wine is great.
You want to talk crap about wine?
You ever have a red blend before?
No.
I want to have a fucking vodka Cosmo drink.
Oh, please.
Drink a red blend, for Christ sakes.
Oh, yeah.
Do you guys make a sex on the beach?
Get fucking red blend for once in your life.
He's a mean drunk.
I'm telling you.
You'll drink cheap.
So this now goes in here.
Which way?
So the prongs out that way, like that.
And it's going to shove in 10 minutes.
See, there are two different tabs on the button.
One with a notch, one without.
Look carefully at the screen when putting it in.
I know what I'm doing.
So right through here.
I mean, it can't really go anywhere.
It just sits here like that.
Unidentified life form approaching.
Red alert.
Red blend.
Place it right over the button.
It looks right at home there, don't you think?
I mean, kind of, I guess.
That's in there.
It's not really secure, though.
Fold both of these top arms down so the tabs fit tightly into the openings.
We're starting to get this alien out of control.
Okay.
Come on, Nintendo.
You can do better than this.
Okay.
That's fine.
So that's in.
Both in.
He's riding on whatever this is.
Now, just to be sure it won't escape,
let's fold its head down between its arms.
I didn't fold these.
I don't think I do, though.
Look at that.
Ooh.
That fits nice.
Eat dinner on stream or it's pre-recorded.
I'm not going to eat fucking dinner on stream.
Fold the arms down, same thing.
We're going to do the same thing on the other side.
Eat dinner.
Why would I do something like that?
Okay.
This is kind of loose.
It's supposed to be like that.
Keep 13 minutes and 19 minutes.
Stop.
Thank you.
15 to 30 minutes, huh?
I fucking owned that.
How do I put this in?
Get the Joy-Con arm ready.
It's the one with the plus button.
Yes, I know which one it is.
I can hear the baits in my brain.
So open this slot and it looks like a Pez dispenser.
And then this goes in.
Close it and put the key in like that.
That's in.
And then close this and fold it back and stick it in there.
Done.
I win.
Try pushing the button and the key.
If it pops back out after you push it, we're good to go.
Is that?
I don't think that's good to go.
Maybe it is.
No, it is.
It is.
It's fine.
It's going to be fine.
Toy key is complete.
We got the key.
We got the pedal.
I'm ready to start fucking losing it.
All right.
Time to make the car.
Welcome to the next four hours.
150 to 210 minutes.
See you guys in the next 10 hours.
I'm doing it all.
You know what I mean?
I don't care how long this takes.
I'll be here in one spring.
This is not turning off until it's done.
I'm fucking ready.
Let's go.
Wheel.
Wheel base.
Seven steps.
Make the steering wheel.
Remove this one piece from sheet A.
It'll form the steering wheel for your car.
For some reason, my changer sucks.
I can't like, gotta do it the right way.
There we go.
I got it.
I need to like figure this out.
All right.
Don't forget if you have a fucking problem, call somebody.
You'll be able to play Adventure as soon as you finish building the Toy-Con car.
Adventure.
What does that mean?
Family circus.
I can't, guys, here's the fucking problem.
I can't skip.
I can't go fast because the key is in here.
What piece do I need?
Oh, he did a funny noise.
Now I'm making a call back to the fucking dumb family circus thing I said like
four hours ago.
So I need the whole entire enterprise here.
The whole thing is huge.
I gotta get the whole pizza.
He just elbowed me.
Come on.
No.
That's it for this piece.
There's nothing else in here.
Just a spike trap now.
Okay.
There it is.
I hate that it's in here.
Get it out of here.
I'll put it in later.
Fuck off for an hour.
All right.
Here's the steering wheel.
Let's put it together.
Don't forget if you have any trouble, you can use the back and forward buttons.
Sure.
You'll be able to punch these out.
Pizza box, Labo, all over again.
Why is everybody freaking out?
What happened?
Like, why is everybody, what's wrong?
Why is everybody freaking out?
There's so many random pieces to pull out of here.
I was rude.
Wait, what did I, what did I do?
What did I say?
What did I, what did I say?
I was mean?
How was I mean?
What did I say?
I yelled at the key.
Oh, I'm sorry, key.
I'm so rude to you.
I just ripped it.
Fuck off for an hour.
I was talking, I was talking to the key and not, what?
There's so many little pieces.
I'm gonna have a field day fucking cleaning this up.
And I said I didn't want to mess this room up.
And here we are, messing the room up.
What do you know?
What else is new?
Different states, same bullshit.
Still ruining rooms.
2018.
Is that it?
This middle thing has to come out somehow.
Can the middle thing even come out?
Okay.
I mean, it's getting close.
Oh, all the HDMI ports have to come out.
All the HDMI ports have to come out.
2018.
Looking closer, right?
One, two, three, and all the pieces.
Just these corners.
These corners come out too.
Are you stoned?
I don't think so.
I don't believe I am.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
That's fine.
Okay, I'm ready.
You missed an HDMI?
Fuck it.
We'll be fine.
Okay, let's go.
Before we turn the piece off, we'll want to crease
the four lines on these four tabs.
Boop, boop, boop, boopity boop.
That's all four.
Okay.
That wasn't a funny voice.
Guys, I wouldn't be doing this.
I would be doing this if I was alone too.
I would be saying Thanos lines.
It's done.
Flip the whole thing around.
Just gives us this.
Got any more brain busters, Nintendo?
Oh, whoops.
We got five more gifted subs.
Five gifted subs from Bet3.
Thank you so much, dude.
Even more subs on top of the ones that were from before.
Thank you guys so much.
You guys are fucking amazing.
Thank you.
Bet3.
Fold every single one of these.
God.
Can I put this in a machine and have it do it for me?
Buy it pre-made.
One skit.
I gotta go all the way around.
It's gotta do it, you know?
You gotta put your pants on.
You gotta do it.
It does sound really nice when you do it each time, though.
So I have a question for everybody that's here.
Am I the only person on Twitch that's done this?
On stream like the whole thing?
All of them?
No.
I want to meet that person.
Matters of Darkness came in with five community subs.
Thank you so much.
You are literally the only person to ever do it.
That's big, big community subs coming in from Matters of Darkness.
On top of the ones from earlier.
Thank you so much, dude.
I don't want to-
I really don't know what to say at this point.
You guys are fucking too much for me.
You're not the first, but you're definitely the slowest.
How many total community subs tonight?
Probably 150.
Something crazy.
Go around the inner circle.
And the-
In the-
In the core, too?
We gotta go in the core!
Look how patronizing he's being when this wheel is trying its best.
That's one of my favorite comment of the whole night.
That was great.
All right, let's go.
Each individual piece has to come up.
I'm gonna feel so satisfied
when I smash this with the sledgehammer that's back there in the closet.
You didn't know?
That's the big joke at the end of the stream.
Sludgehammer?
He bought a sledgehammer for this?
Yeah, he sure did.
And boy, is it gonna be messy.
Whoa, cool.
Whoa, holy shit, he sledgehammered the labo.
What the-
He still has it in his hand.
The adrenaline's like getting to him.
Wait, hold on.
He's sledgehammering his computer.
What the fuck?
What face?
Did I break it?
No.
Did I?
Dude, he sledgehammered his computer?
Dude, he's sledgehammering his walls.
What the fuck face?
Everything has to happen.
Dude, he ran off camera
and I still hear crashing and smashing.
Whoa!
There's that HDMI port I missed.
I should just do these at the same time.
This is gonna feel really cool putting it together though
because all these slots have a home.
Every single slot has a home.
They-
Slots go this way and they go into their home.
One of my fucking-
Can I show you something?
I can't.
Almost all-
Half of my fucking wall paneling is falling down.
Command strips, don't do shit.
Another one just fell down.
Okay, we are done.
It's time to put it all together.
Here's the 130 minute stream that they were describing.
They weren't kidding around when they said it was gonna take 130 stream minutes.
Put it all together, right?
Or wrong?
Good red blend.
Wrong.
Okay, this comes up and then these go down.
That.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's the second one.
So this is, you know, in the middle.
I feel like I'm gonna get cut.
This is like a saw blade.
That comes down and then these pieces here fold like that.
And then in.
Oy.
In.
There's so many tabs to put in.
Nintendo Labo like katana saw blade.
Fatality.
Just do them all.
Did I, did it flip over?
Why did, did I do this wrong?
No.
Friendship.
Again.
Blind streamer.
Blind.
He's blind.
That's an unknown reference.
Go play Mortal Kombat 3, you fucking idiot.
You know, I'm kidding.
That was a joke.
I'm, that was, I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
He's getting toxic.
The more wine he drinks, he becomes more toxic.
No, that's in Mortal Kombat 3.
I was just kidding.
Look, hey, come on.
Rewind to yesterday.
Oh, sleepy.
Everybody calls me an idiot when I'm like walking around in Red Dead.
Oh wow, you're an idiot.
Why is that okay?
He sounds so, I'm kidding.
Stop ignoring my question.
Tell us your sub count.
I don't, I don't know.
What is it?
65,000.
Like, I'm not ignoring your, what?
Stop ignoring my question.
How much money is in your bank account?
I'm probably gonna have to do all these, right?
Yeah, I've got to do every single one.
That's more than everybody here.
Yeah, there's like 3,000 people there.
That's correct, right?
I think so.
Yep, right.
You knew it was gonna have to happen, right?
Tax returns.
Look out.
Oh, a plane went by?
Yeah.
Vegas, man.
People all over the place.
I heard a cat outside yesterday.
That, I thought it was like a weird like high-pitched voice.
And I was like, what the fuck?
It was like, give me all your money.
And I was like, what the fuck is this?
It was high-pitched.
And I went and said it was a cat holding somebody up on the street.
It made no sense.
And he had an eye patch.
I was like, holy shit, we're in Vegas, man.
Done.
In an iPad.
All right, that's it.
That was just a Jay Leno joke.
Yeah, it was.
He probably made that already.
Don't look at me.
I'm not here.
I got a cup though.
You see that cup?
Pretty deep.
All right, we're on step two of already step two.
We're getting there.
A place to put these when they're done.
That could go right down there.
I need B and C.
Why does Jerma always over-emote?
What?
Over-emote?
What do you mean over-emote?
Over-act?
Over-emote?
I don't know what you mean over-emote.
Empty.
And this laundry dryer washer thing.
Stop over-emoting.
I haven't typed anything in the chat at all.
I've been talking to you guys, but you know.
So this is, I'm going to assume, is part of the base of the wheel.
Right?
Emo-streamer wants to be Nightwing, but he's too fat.
All right, flipping around.
All the folds, every single one, all the HDMI's have to come out.
When is my collab with Critical?
Right now.
Welcome into the chat, guys.
I have him on Discord here.
Critical, say hello.
Critical.
You hear him, man?
Ah, I must have had a scheduling conflict with him.
I must have had a scheduling conflict with him.
Shit, hello.
No, I was going to hit him up, actually.
I was going to hit him up very soon.
When am I going to stream with Logic, Rick Morty, and Ninja?
That's all I got to say about that, is just, oi.
All right.
So, make sure I'm doing all this right.
This tab has to come up.
When are you going to collab with Jerma?
No, that guy over emotes.
I don't think I want to be in the same stream as him.
He has a really commanding presence.
He over talks and talks over everybody.
I don't follow his humor that really at all.
I like Jerma.
Jerma's not bad, but like, it gets to a point, man.
You have anything else besides, like, I'll try to do the voice.
Like, don't have any cards, I guess.
Like, he does it all the time.
It's like, you have any other tricks up your sleeve, dude?
That is not meant to be like mean to him or anything.
I think he's like, cool.
I think he's funny.
I saw his Castle Griffith Steed video.
I mean, that was pretty cool.
I heard he pays for bots to view his channel.
I'm going to go down that road.
All right, let's go.
Unsubbing, because you hate him.
No, I don't hate him.
He's like, cool, I like him.
Am I going to play Smash with Vinny?
Fuck yeah, if he wants to.
When Smash comes out, I'll play it with anybody.
Because they're actually going to have,
they'll have regional matchmaking,
which is something that they've like never done before.
So that's huge.
Plus, you ever spend more than a couple days
in somebody's dryer before?
Not fun.
I mean, I spelt real clean when I came up.
I'll be honest with you.
Every so often, he would, it was weird,
because he would turn the dryer on.
I was in there for probably 12 hours at a time.
And he would turn the dryer on.
And I'd be fucking flipping around and shit.
He would throw a couple sheets in there.
And he'd be like, you smell pretty fresh, don't you?
And I'd be like, fuck, I guess I do.
He'd throw hamburger meat in there,
and the heat from the,
the heat from the dryer would actually cook it.
So I would have to wait probably maybe 20 or 30 minutes
for the raw hamburger meat to spin around with me
until it was cooked enough where I could eat it.
So I mean, he was nice enough.
He like helped me out a little bit there.
Both sides there, yeah.
Same, oh, I didn't, whoops.
Fucked that up down here.
Who's my smash man?
It's Pac-Man.
I mean, I was going to say Gino, but whatever.
Life sucks, apparently, for Gino.
There we go.
This comes down.
Yeah, I was one of those people
that thought the Grinch leak was real.
And I was like, oh my god,
this is going to be the best game ever made.
And then you got to remember, it's,
everyone I was just trying to fuck with you
before a game comes out.
Of course you did.
Well, I mean, it looked really, it looked so real.
There was so much backstory.
So much time went into somebody making that leak
that it was just like impossible for it to be fake.
And here we are.
Did I, same thing on this side too.
Smash characters.
Uh, no, but I mean, Pac-Man, it's always Pac-Man, right?
Pac-Man is just always cool.
A couple of other characters look interesting.
I don't have to give spoilers or anything,
but there's a certain plant-based hero
that looks really stupid.
Kind of right up my alley.
Uh, okay, check the six little tabs
we popped into the openings.
If they haven't all popped into place,
go back and fix them.
I mean, these, this looks right.
Just going to go like this.
And then we're going to get this piece.
Uh, it's going to be a shit character.
Well, we'll see what they do for DLC.
Because apparently, they already have a plan for DLC.
I guess still, who else is left to put in that game?
You know what I mean?
They have every single Nintendo character ever.
Has spirits and trophies and characters.
Like, what the fuck?
There's five more characters they want to put in.
Third party?
Yeah, I mean, I'd be nice if one of those
third party characters was, you know, Gino.
Technically third party character.
Let's see here.
Carl Griffinstein.
If Nintendo ever hit me up to like,
pay for the rights of Carl Griffinstein.
Oh, excuse me, Mr. Albertson.
Yes, I'm writing this email to offer you a lump sum.
I have a reply to the email as fast as I could.
I don't even care what the amount was.
And I'd be like, yes, yes, yes.
They'd be like, take it, take it now, take it.
How many bits is that?
How much is that in bits?
One dollar would be worth it.
Am I putting this in the right way?
It's got a snap in there.
Paid you in potato chips.
It'd be worth it.
I never have to buy them ever again.
Easy.
You should do a rumble of all the Smash characters.
That's a lot.
That's a lot of characters.
Steering wheel has a seat.
So we need to move that down here because that's done.
C and D again.
Everything else from all of it, the whole thing.
I lose it.
Where did it just go?
Where did that go?
Oh, it's all the way down there.
And the two pieces down here.
How's the elaborate pie box going?
Actually, it's going pretty well.
I think it's going pretty well.
What do you guys think?
You guys think it's going well so far?
A Labo stream without alcohol.
What kind?
Excuse me.
You were saying something.
Show the box.
I showed the box earlier.
It's black box.
That's pretty good.
Is that sangria?
No, it's a red blend.
It's California red blend from black box.
Cheap, affordable, tastes great.
Why am I turning them all over?
What are you doing?
And then we need something from D.
The whole thing?
No, just this left part.
Oh, put a sponsor warning in the title.
I'm not sponsored by black box.
I just bought it and like it.
That's it.
Do you really even have to like it?
Chill, chill.
What, like you guys don't drink wine
if you're above the age of 21.
You never had wine before in your life
and you want a decent alternative
to buying like a $50 bottle of wine
and it is three liters in here.
And it's quality wine.
A funny story here.
The guy that helps produce
a lot of the video stuff
and the guy that helped me make
almost the whole rumble.
We bought this and we wrote
the whole rumble drink
in the whole box of black box wine.
We also wrote four other skits
and ideas completely drinking this one.
So it's kind of like a little,
it's my heart somewhere, you know.
It's funny juice.
Buy it up.
The bits circled in the picture below
shouldn't be folded.
There's a reason they don't have fold lines.
All right.
I didn't fold them.
Maybe I did.
What, what?
Okay.
Well, I got apparently I do fold.
I once, honey chain says
I once drank an entire bottle of wine
and puked all over my friend's porch
and then he power bombed me through the sink.
Well, I believe the first half
but the second half was sensationalized
to make it seem like it was like,
wow, it's crazy.
I don't think the second part happened.
Yeah, I think you puked on your friend's sink in you.
Um, you know, you're trying to sensationalize
a little bit because you called him out.
I believe him.
You're the only one that's allowed to make things up.
I'm the only one that's allowed
to lie and make things up here.
Don't you understand?
One dollar.
You sound presidential.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Move on.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, okay.
We're good.
Let's fold it down.
I did.
This one too.
I just heard my dog bark at me.
Otto just said like, hey, shut the fuck up.
He's like downstairs.
These both, these all come down.
Those come all the way down.
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
These tabs come up.
Like this, like that, like that.
Sick.
That square is not going anywhere.
Next, roll up the first loopy,
rectangular bit so that the tab
comes down to the rest of the room.
It's not in there really securely though.
You know what I mean?
Like, fuck.
You demand a ho-ho.
So eat a ho-ho.
Go to a convenience store
and get a fucking, get a Yahoo,
whatever they're called.
The tab's poking out.
This one is not, but that one is.
Okay, they both now.
No, that's fine.
Folds over.
So they back up again.
And all this flipping making me dizzy.
Now roll the piece up from left
until it looks like this.
So that comes up and then that comes over.
And then the whole, that comes down.
Shit.
That, this, this way.
And then this tab comes down into there.
Oh, you little punk.
Come on.
Done.
Remember, the bits weren't supposed to fold.
Check that all four of them
are still nice and straight.
They are.
Yeah, that's right.
This one's a little fucked up.
No, that's fine.
Okay.
Uvey the steering column.
Next, we'll attach the steering wheel
to the steering column.
Make sure you've got the wheel close.
I do.
It's right here.
Fold the two colored flaps
in the middle of the steering wheel down
and out of the way.
We'll be inserting the steering wheel
column from above.
Here comes the column.
Straight down like this.
Before you insert the steering wheel column,
make sure it's facing the same way
as on the screen.
The printed bits on each side should match up.
Good deal.
All the way down.
We did it.
All right.
Steering wheel and steering column are done.
Beautiful.
It's done.
The steering wheel is done.
Now, fit these two parts together.
So, lift the steering wheel part up
and insert down to the base.
Well, it just sits down in there.
And that's it.
What have you done?
Okay.
So, just go down like that.
There.
That almost felt like winning
the crane game at an arcade.
Where's our stuffed animal prize?
Now, we're going to turn
the whole thing over.
The bits aren't all fixed together yet,
so hold everything carefully
to keep it in place.
Turn it upside down.
Here.
Okay.
This here piece is called Captain Crunch.
Captain Captain.
He caps the steering column,
then turns to keep it securely in place.
What the fuck are you talking about?
All right.
Then that goes.
Spin the captain around
so that his two dents are facing
as shown on screen.
Then slide him down
on the end of the steering column.
So, like this.
Ahoy there, land lovers.
This is the captain speaking.
You'll want to hold...
Why is this Garfield?
Anybody feel like this is
like Garfield's bits?
I feel like we're hitting it
at Garfield's bits.
Ahoy there, land lovers.
This is the captain speaking.
You'll want to hold that wheel
nice and steady when you turn me around.
What do you want?
Around I go till the cross lines up.
Like this.
Like that.
That's it, right?
They don't call me captain for nothing.
You know, I wish I was part
of the Toy-Con submarine,
but a cardboard can dream.
This is...
Scarfield wrote all this.
I'm convinced.
Captain Capturn has four mates on deck.
They're called quadruple lock quadruplets.
They help keep the captain in his place.
So, flip them all around
and fold them all in half.
The one time Garfield's not here.
That's unfortunate.
Everybody loves Garfield.
All right, so stick them in half.
Flip them in there
and stick them in the slots.
First mate reporting for duty.
My siblings and I were destined
to do everything together.
Quadruplet power!
Slide the first mate down from above
and lock her in.
That's the first lock down.
That's it.
Do that to all four sides.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm not reading this.
Nice messages.
Uh, fourth mate.
They may spell, but they're together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Just that one.
Okay, one more.
So that is locked in.
You're missing out on labo lore?
Do you really care about labo lore?
You want me to go back?
I ain't going back.
Get ready to use these two stubby
T-shaped pieces.
They look a bit like sweaters.
I only have one.
Why do I only have one?
No, I don't.
Why?
All right.
Flip them up.
Spin them around.
Okay.
Uh, let's attach the first sweater.
Fold the arms so that they're ready
for a hug and then slide them into
the openings in the steering wheel.
That goes back around.
You fucking idiot.
All right.
Right there.
Like this.
Yes.
This is, you need like little hands
for this.
It's in.
Right?
Looks good.
Time for a second sweater.
It gives the steering wheel
a hug from the other side.
It's a steering wheel sandwich
on a sweater bread.
Garfield.
Excuse me?
Did you hear the dog?
I'll go get him.
I'm gonna go get my dog
because he's probably being
really annoying.
He's probably being super annoying.
Wait, how does this get in there?
Auto is never annoying.
No, I'm just kidding.
He's my special little boy.
So that's done.
It's in.
Secure.
The steering part is now
completely secured to the base.
Let's check to make sure
that everything moves like it should.
This is where the Toy-Con key comes in.
Oh, what do we have here?
There's a hole.
That's the perfect size
for the Toy-Con key
to slide right through.
I'm not gonna need the mode
in there right now.
So this goes like this.
Perfect.
Yes, it does.
Try spinning the steering wheel
around slowly.
Does it go all the way around
without stopping or catching?
Yes, it does.
Once you're done checking
the steering wheel,
remove the Toy-Con key for now.
It might get caught a bit the first time.
So make sure you remove it carefully.
I got it.
Somebody said other way.
Yeah, that's good.
It works.
All right, on to the next step.
The steering wheel base is finished.
The steering wheel is complete.
This would be a great time for a break.
They don't take breaks.
Here, three of seven.
Making the engine compartment.
I need to move this out of the way.
Don't take any more breaks.
Tell you this.
Auto, one second.
You have to be somewhere
that's not right in the way.
Okay.
See, he just want to be in here.
He's good.
He's currently like back there
where the door is.
All right, so we got this.
I have it already.
We're good.
Make sure you get the special parts.
All right, I'm going to eat.
I thought we were going to lie in the blanket.
What a good dog.
Huge piece.
Do I need the whole thing?
Almost the whole thing.
Jesus, this is huge.
This looks like somebody's rib cage.
It's like a Minecraft breastplate.
Should I wear this?
I'm going to need this later.
So, okay.
Show auto.
The cameras are like set in such specific.
Can you see him?
He's right there.
See, right here.
Auto.
Hello, Auto.
Hello, Mr. Auto.
There, he's right there.
All right, so let me take out
the little pieces that I need to punch out.
We'll continue on our vehicle quest.
I ripped it a little bit.
You know what?
Who cares?
Uh, that's it.
No, up here.
Pet him.
Where is he going?
He's under the blanket.
There's a little blade.
He just like stuffed his body underneath it.
Mr. Auto.
He's such a good dog.
He's the best dog ever.
All right, so let's do this.
Out of the way.
Uh, six, seven, eight, nine.
It's like 10 o'clock Eastern.
What day is it?
Saturday.
It's Saturday night.
We're good.
It's not even 10 o'clock.
All right, so get it out there.
The engine compartment comes from it.
What's wrong with me?
Okay, it doesn't really have an engine on it,
but it's fun to pretend.
Folds.
Pretty much all of them.
All the ones in the top.
All the ones in the middle.
Every single little piece.
All of it has to be folded.
Every single piece.
Okay, let's begin.
What kind of dog is Auto?
He's a Dachshund mix.
I don't know what he's mixed with,
but there's been plenty of guesses over the years.
Chihuahua, Beagle, Rottweiler,
Jack Russell Terrier.
Don't know because he's a rescue,
so I don't really know.
I have no idea.
There's been plenty of guesses.
He's a tiny boy.
He's actually kind of big
for a Dachshund,
but he is a very good dog.
It's an old classic German question.
What kind of dog do you have?
Yeah, I mean he's, I don't know.
Thought about doing one of those doggie DNA tests,
but I've read a lot of things
about how those things are bullshit
and they just send you back a random DNA test
that doesn't even mean anything.
I don't know how true that is.
Might be true.
It might not be.
Ooh, that felt good.
Do your own DNA test.
What?
12% ferret.
You might have some ferret in them.
Old, bold, right in the middle.
We got one, I think I see two here.
One, two, one, two.
Your dog is a purebred rat.
Well, then I'm sorry to tell you this,
but he's not a dog.
Your dog is a rat.
It's not a dog.
That's good.
Mess over here.
All right, so done, done.
One more piece.
So many little pieces in this big boy here.
Ever thought of getting a pet rat?
I have over the years.
My one issue with the pet rat is
they're wonderful,
they're really intelligent,
they're super sweet,
they're really fun,
they're really smart,
but man, they really only live like a year.
They live like two years.
I get so attached to any animal
that I ever have.
They used to have hamsters
and gerbils and all that shit,
and it was so tough after fucking a year.
A year and a half would go by,
and it was like right
when you're beginning to start a relationship
and like, oh, this is my animal, my pet.
It just sucks,
but they are really good pets.
They're really fun to be around.
They're really energetic.
They're really funny,
but just unfortunately they don't live very long.
Didn't get this piece.
So all the way up.
All the way up.
There we go.
So pull this in.
This big piece comes up and goes in here.
I can handle it.
God damn it,
he actually jebaited the labo stream.
Yes, I did.
I did.
You're right.
I did do that.
All right, we need,
it's time to introduce the eyelet.
It's got two parts.
The bit on the left is the grubbit
and the washer.
So how many of these do we have?
Do we need one or two?
How many do we need?
Take one of the gray eyelets from the bag.
Get over.
I don't want to take everything out.
Give me a grommet.
We forgot the crackers.
What do you mean?
What crackers?
What the heck do you mean, man?
What the fuck do you mean?
All right.
Oh, take the grommet
and push it into the hole from the outside.
So on the back of our easy bake oven,
this thing here.
So it goes through here.
So this snaps on through here.
Yes, it does.
That's the way it goes, right?
Snap the washer onto the grommet from the inside
and it'll make a snap.
Tell me if you hear it.
Nice.
Okay, good.
We need an adult.
What's the point of that?
Okay.
Sheet F.
Just as good as the first set.
All of it except for the bottom part.
You guys having a good time?
You having fun?
You guys having fun?
I'm seeing some nose here.
I'm gonna have to eat paint on stream.
You know what I mean?
Like I'm seeing some nose.
What do I do with this?
What do I do with my fucking airline puke box?
I'm running out of space.
Don't turn this piece.
Don't, don't, don't, don't do it.
Fold these flops first.
Go say hello to italics.
Just tell me if you can hear this on his stream.
Did you hear me?
He has like the sweetest face right now.
I have to show him.
You see here or no you can't?
Move camera.
I can't move the camera.
It's like in the worst possible one.
Maybe I can.
Hey, what are you doing?
He's so cute.
He's my special boy.
You guys couldn't hear me?
I made like a bird noise.
Oh well.
I mean that means that we have good sound dampening.
That's good.
Is this in a good spot?
I hear is good right there.
That's all right.
We might have heard you.
We thought it was auto.
No, I went like pretty loud out there.
You're supposed to watch italics's stream
and see if you heard it.
All right.
So wait, don't fold these yet.
Fold them back.
Now the fact when you're freezing the big fold,
be careful not to fold this little mushroomy part.
All right.
Don't fold the mushroomy part.
Fold it all up.
Left, right, up, down.
Fold it in here.
Thumbs up.
Careful.
It's a weird swing that that does all the way across.
And that folds up and then goes into the little tab
that's down there.
Do you see it?
Do you see it, folks?
That?
No, I don't.
Something on this side.
Back up with a little mushroom.
I did such a good job.
Okay.
Now turn the whole piece to its front
and check to make sure that the ends of both tabs
are sticking to the other side.
They are.
Okay.
Although this one's a little torn.
No, they are.
Looks fine.
Congratulatory wine chug.
I agree to that.
That piece is done for now.
We'll eat it again soon.
What soon?
Isn't soon enough.
Be patient.
Oh, this piece.
That was the weakest chug in the world.
Okay.
I can't spit this out.
Never mind.
Hey, great job.
It's a new emo.
Now, do I fold those?
I don't know.
I didn't let the video game tell me.
Watch out.
This piece has a bit in the middle
that you definitely shouldn't fold.
Try to keep that in mind
when you're folding the other bits.
I won't.
All right.
Fold this like that.
Looks good.
Armpit sweat.
Give me a break.
It's been four hours.
It's four hours.
But drinking wine, it could be much worse.
Let me tell you.
I'm fine.
It's just perspiration.
I'm wearing a long sleeve shirt.
I'm in Las Vegas.
You know how hot it is here?
It's like 42 degrees out right now.
It gets cold in the winter.
All right.
Fold it, fold it, fold it, fold it,
fold it, fold it, fold it.
It's fucking cold out right now.
Vegas is fucking chilly.
As like the kids say, as fuck.
You know what I mean?
Do I fold this?
Hold on.
Oh, I got to...
Chugging wine is like...
Nobody did that besides Bacchus.
Nobody chugs wine except for Bacchus.
It's the only person in history to ever do it.
All right.
Do I fold this one down?
I don't think I fold that one.
I don't think I did the top one down.
So this goes...
Oh, man.
That's a hard blink.
Why don't you do webcam?
How come you never do face cam?
That was a hard blink.
Soft blink is...
A hard blink is like...
I'm lost.
I didn't do it.
It's fine.
What if I faint on stream?
I'm not gonna...
Why would I faint on stream?
Did I miss a tab?
No, that's correct.
Right?
I got it.
We'll insert it into the part we finished just before this one.
Fold the flap at the bottom of the long gap here.
Down and out of the way.
What does it want me to do?
Fold the gap out of the way.
You said...
You just said it.
What is...
Where is it?
That goes down.
Look every at the screen.
Make sure that the part is facing the right direction.
Then insert as far as it will go.
It kind of goes in like this first.
It's like a D battery.
I didn't even fucking need the tutorial.
That's fine.
That works.
Now the sun stand will probably stand the piece up.
Hey, it doesn't look a bit like a koala's face.
I mean, it does.
Okay.
Is the piece facing the same way as on screen?
It'll be tricky to fix later if you get it wrong.
Double check.
I got it, right?
Yeah.
Everything looks good.
Let's lock it securely in the place of this piece here.
A long lost cousin of the quadruple.
I don't want to hear the fucking whole thing.
Turn it over and fold it in two.
Now it's ready to be locked.
Lock, lock, lock.
Lock, lock it.
Here's a lock.
Lock the thing.
Okay, great.
How did I chug that fucking line?
I was just going slow.
Shit.
I did it.
I think.
Hold on.
I gave it a BRB for one second.
Shit.
That was deer in headlights.
I fucking hate face cams.
I wasn't ready for it and I pressed it.
I get embarrassed real easily.
All right.
Here we go.
Here, look.
It's a koala.
Right, Nintendo?
Ta-da.
It's all done.
I did it.
I finished the whole thing on stream.
It's over.
Where's that?
All right.
Get in there.
Stop it.
Okay.
So here we go.
Fold it up and get it in there like this.
Why is that off?
Why is this turned off?
Battery's dead.
Don't throw your phone behind me.
Okay.
What are we doing?
Here.
I was, it was, it was fucking dark in here.
I was like, what the hell?
Okay, so that matches up with here.
So you guys can see.
See what I'm talking about?
All right.
So the tabs need to, this comes down.
Whoa.
That, I get the other one quick.
Was it right?
Is that correct?
I hope it's correct.
It is.
The engine is complete.
Wait, wait, wait.
What'd I tell you?
I got stains under my armpit.
Look at how good I look right now.
I look fresh.
I look well rested.
Fast forward.
Seven and a half hours from now.
I bet you my hair's greasy.
My face is watery.
And like I got stains under my armpit.
Look at how good I look right now.
I look fresh.
I look well rested.
Fast forward.
Seven and a half hours from now.
I bet you my hair's greasy.
My face is watery.
And like I got stains under my armpit.
Look at how good I look right now.
I look fresh.
I look well rested.
Fast forward.
Seven and a half hours from now.
I bet you my hair's greasy.
My face is watery.
And like I got stains under my armpit.
Look at how good I look right now.
I look fresh.
I look well rested.
Fast forward.
Fuck that guy.
He doesn't know shit.
Oh, I lost it.
Wait, where did it go?
Where did it go?
It's gone.
I don't know.
I can't get it back.
Where's the other cam?
Where did the other camera go?
I actually fucking lost it.
Hey, hey.
Let me tell you guys something.
Fast forward right now.
Three or four hours from now.
I'm going to look fucking way worse than I do now.
My face is going to be greasy.
I'm going to be way more drunk than I am now.
I'm going to have like a fucked up hair.
Water's going to be pouring down my shirt.
It's going to look really bad.
Just remember this.
Like three or four hours from now, okay?
Remember this.
Making the levers and lever holders.
That's my favorite part.
Get down there.
All right, forward.
I said we're almost done.
Okay, levers and holders.
D and G.
Okay, I'd eat D.
Last part from D.
This is D, right?
Oh, shit.
This one's F.
D, you got it.
Okay, D and then all that shit up there.
I don't know what that's for,
but it's for something later.
Watch out.
Oh, you know, you just want to like stuff your face
and your dog's body and just smell his dog's smell.
I want to do that so bad right now.
People writing question marks right now.
Excuse me.
Give me a break.
The savory dog smell.
Am I fucking out of my mind?
What are you talking about?
You guys know what I'm talking about.
Do I really need to talk about that?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand the people that are writing question marks here.
I really don't understand it.
Oh, I'm seeing 50-50 here.
You're a psycho.
What?
It's the dog, like the Frito's dog smell.
What are you talking about?
You guys not have a dog?
I'm being fucking annihilated right now in chat.
For what?
I can't believe it.
I'm being annihilated in my own chat.
Chat, I'm being annihilated.
Why am I, like I'm in an opera?
All right, let's go.
I'm surprised.
The levers of the secret sauce for the McDonald's number one
is the best item of any menu on any menu.
You find it in the play section.
Whatever, fuck off.
All right, let's go.
Oh, fold the lines with both hands.
It'll make sure that the McDonald's number one
Big Mac is the best menu item.
Okay, like that.
Savoring dog sauce.
What was this?
I don't know.
Okay, don't fold this part.
Take the pole.
Okay.
Dog smell.
Yes, shove your face in it.
No, you're drunk.
And by the way, I mean,
when you get bailed out from your own community,
60% of the vote.
Yes, shove your face in it.
60%.
You still don't understand.
61% now agrees.
39%, that's not even like,
that's a vocal minority.
No, that is a voting majority.
I'm sorry, but that's a majority.
Don't even need to look at it anymore.
I voted.
What am I making now?
Two guys going like this.
Dog breath is gross.
It's not dog breath.
It's the savory sleepy dog smell.
What?
How do you not know what this is?
If you have a dog and the dog is sleeping
and you walk over to your dog that is asleep
and you pet the dog's back
and the dog wakes up for a second.
Whoa, savory, sleepy dog smell.
I don't understand how you don't get that.
No idea what I'm talking about.
No idea.
People have no idea what I mean by this.
I don't, I don't, how is this possible?
I don't, I don't get it.
You're weird.
I'm not weird.
What the fuck?
This is real.
You're making this up for views.
I don't do that shit.
I feel like I'm being attacked.
Dog sniffer own facts and logic.
Okay.
Believe me.
Here we go.
I thought everybody knew what that was.
I thought I was going to be like,
oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
but I'm like the weirdo apparently.
Kim talks about this shit too.
I want to take this to the fucking supreme court.
Does the dog smelly dog sleepy smell exist?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
This is not going to even leave your district.
Oh, okay.
See you in court.
Guy that won't show up.
That's some kind of fucking currency thing.
Is my hair purple?
My hair is like a dirty blonde.
Brown.
I don't smell my dog like a lunatic.
Reddit slash dog lovers.
Reddit slash pet owners.
Thank you dad hunter for the $20.
Hydrate.
I did downstairs.
Don't worry.
Don't make me fucking get in it.
Don't make me get a variable in here.
I'll go get him.
I'm gonna go stop his stream to bring him in here.
I'll say your stream is over right now.
You're coming in here and fucking talking.
We'll get to the bottom of this real quick.
Is he still streaming?
Lock your door.
Don't worry.
Minus will bark.
He'll let me know what's going on.
Lock your door.
There's no locks on the doors in this house.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, doctor.
God damn.
Dogs have a savory, sleepy smell.
I'll call her.
Call her right now.
No, she's working.
That's not smart.
I'm stuck.
Dogs have a savory.
Ah, he can't hear me.
Okay, hey.
So, uh, Nintendo Switch.
Okay, so folding lines and it's real.
Somebody get it.
What's a poll?
Where's that poll?
Somebody link the poll right now.
Critical has a dog?
He fucking gets it.
Guaranteed.
I guarantee he gets it.
Ask Critical next time he streams.
Does a dog have a savory, sleepy smell?
Like the savory dog smell?
He'll fucking get it.
I know he will.
I don't have his phone number.
Call him.
Call.
I don't have his fucking telephone number.
Is Jermuff weird?
This is two votes.
We're gonna read it.
Wait, wait, wait.
We got a Reddit thread here.
Is it weird to smell your dog?
I made a poll and got some responses.
Spelling the dog full face style.
What are your opinions?
Okay, let's see what Reddit says.
Is this some kind of currency?
I like dogs sniff the savory dog.
That helps.
That helps a lot.
Look, fresh.
I look well rested.
Wrong, wrong thing.
Call Critical.
I don't have his telephone identification number.
How did my dog get outside?
He's like, hey, let me in.
I got it.
I know I'm right.
We ask who's streaming now.
Okay, looks good.
Pull the flap down like this.
I can't go in.
First lever is done.
Ask Discord.
I know, I know what I know, okay?
Ask UberHackZeroNova.
He would know too.
I'm not sniffing my dog's ass.
Okay, first of all, I just did the Adam Sandler gibberish thing from Billy Madison.
I'm sorry.
Critical said you're sick.
Get him in here.
Where is he?
Right now.
I'll talk to him right now.
Where is he?
This is a PlayStation.
That's PlayStation.
What did I draw?
Get it?
Where is he?
Oh, don't hit the escape button.
Don't stop streaming.
Critical said smell my asshole.
Really?
This fucking Reese's commercial.
He's playing RuneScape right now.
Try this in Tob.
Let's check out this fucking Twisted Bone, Tob.
Any other games tonight?
You made Buzz and Soul Calibur.
I'm excited to see them.
I can't get anybody.
I can't get a goddamn person on my side.
Oh, that was Critical.
He's a fucking swell boy.
What am I doing?
Jerma is on a mildly drunken tirade
to tell people, to show people
that dogs have a different smell when they sleep.
All right, you can tell him
that he can smell my asshole.
So we're almost done with the engine.
Getting close.
Getting close to the engine being done.
It's a...
No, hey, we're not over the engine.
Oh, we're part of the engine too.
I'm doing more Adam Sandler.
I can't get...
What does Star have to say?
Where's Star?
Star's streaming?
I can get him.
He's off one.
Get him.
Like, no, no, no, no.
I mean, like, I'm the engine of the Nintendo.
Charlie just called me thin skin.
That shit to me.
Well, tell him I'm fucking busy building a lab ball.
I missed it.
Streamer battle?
Fine.
Ask him if he can do that.
Can Charlie do that?
Can Charlie do this?
Didn't think so.
Careful of dying.
I'm not dying.
I'm fine.
I can't even get a streamer to back me up.
Where's RT?
I don't need the headphones.
Is RT still here?
RT game proud?
He's down for the challenge.
Critical is down for the challenge.
There's no challenge.
I'm not challenging anybody.
I was just going like this.
End quotes.
You better watch out for this.
He's destroying me.
No, he's not.
Get that fuck out of here.
Give me those headphones.
He threw cards at me?
Cards?
What's he saying?
Give me a clip.
I know people that dogs have a different smell when they sleep.
All right.
You can tell him that he can smell my ass.
That's the same one.
What am I getting challenged to?
Jerma wants to know if I can karate chop my hand.
Like what?
Some type of fucking outraged child going through an episode?
I can do something so much better, Jerma.
Here.
You tell Jerma this.
If he wants to throw down, I'll fucking hit him with these playing cards.
Gambit style.
Oh, fuck.
I don't know.
I'm a fucking fearsome fighter.
I fucking fucking get after it.
You see this, Jerma?
Huh?
I'm not dealing with an amateur here.
I thought I was dealing with an amateur for a second.
It's fine, Charlie.
I'll get you to do this.
You couldn't even tell how fast that was.
That was so fast.
I couldn't even tell.
That kick may have been 2,000 miles per hour.
I would just be careful.
I gotta be careful every time I do that.
I have no allies.
I don't need allies.
You see the kind of fucking man I am?
Oh, I lost.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't need allies.
Stronger than all of them combined.
What more needs to be said?
Nothing.
You know what I mean?
It's it.
What more needs to be said?
Call Joel.
Joel, like, Vinesauce Joel?
I feel like he'd be on my side.
I mean, like, he's a fucking talented, funny man.
I feel like he'd be on my side on this.
Of course he would.
Look, I'm just trying to fucking build a labo.
Joel is streaming.
I'm sure he's streaming something fucking fun
for all of you to enjoy.
I'm gonna leave.
Stop invading streamers.
I didn't.
I didn't invade anybody.
I was told...
I didn't invade anyone.
You want me to invade?
I'm giving you fucking invade.
Excuse me, Otto.
Can you move just one second?
Just move right here, Otto.
Otto, you need to move out of the way.
He's being a good keeper.
Better not be coming in here.
I told him my office was off limits.
He better not fucking come in here.
You know what I mean?
You better not fucking come in here.
See?
Can I finish the fucking steering wheel?
Piss my pants.
Where's the other piece?
I found it.
Relax, Charlie.
Yeah, I was on your podcast.
It was fun.
It was like a lot of fun.
You're like fucking cool and shit.
You're like nice.
You're like really nice.
You're like a wicked nice fucking guy.
This is a lot of fun.
Okay, so let's go.
We're in.
The little sticky outy bit on each side
pops into the gap here.
That's why it was so important
for this bit to stay unfolded.
Charlie, let me...
Ah, fucking rubber bands.
I'm muted?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, I'm fine.
Can't wait to do this,
bullshit Nintendo.
Great fucking in feature you got there.
What is this?
Yes, a visitor.
Okay.
I was getting a drink,
but I've been stopped at the door.
Did you come in here for a reason?
Small rubber bands.
Why am I sending people to other streams?
I don't give a shit.
Ah, I just dropped one.
I broke my fucking desk.
Look, if you want to watch somebody,
I love that you want to support other streamers.
Watch Charlie.
He's good.
Italic's good.
Star.
Don't watch him.
Not that good.
It's pretty bad.
It's not good.
Vinny.
Yes.
Vinny's a fucking talented guy.
Star.
To be completely,
all complete honesty though,
Star's a great guy.
Don't think otherwise ever for any reason for real.
Okay, let's go right in the middle here.
Right here.
Natalix is not talking shit.
That's in.
I told you I had a drink to play these games.
Labo especially.
What the fuck did he say?
Wait, wait.
This is important.
I will go off.
I don't know where the fucking headphones are.
What is this clip?
Where are my headphones?
Oh shit.
That's an Xbox controller.
Fuck it.
I'm curious.
Xbox sucks.
What is this clip?
Look at this tiny table.
That's like the little wood table from the living room.
Is that what he's trying to build the Labo on?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Whatever.
It's so small.
We talked about it before I started streaming.
It was like, I don't know.
Where the fuck am I going to build this?
This is what Joel said?
What did Joel say?
Another incredibly talented fucking live streamer.
Thanks for letting me know.
I really appreciate hearing about Germa, but could you chill out?
Thank you.
Joel got like mad.
Don't fuck with people if they don't want it.
He's a fucking funny like really good streamer.
Don't like make him pissed off.
Like don't like harass other people.
If they're like Charlie's into it.
It's Alex is into it.
Like if they're not just leave him alone.
He's he doesn't know the fuck is going on.
Joel's angry.
No, he sees it.
It's fine.
He's fine.
But don't just spam other people.
Please.
Oh, the the the me and Charlie and me and italics.
Yeah, that's definitely like for fun and everything.
But if Joel is trying to run a stream, don't like don't fuck with him.
It doesn't deserve it.
He's fucking a great guy.
So yes, they probably know what's going on.
But I have no idea what's going on here.
So Charlie and italics aren't great guys.
That's not what I said.
Just don't go after some random person.
We haven't we haven't I'm having fun.
You're having fun.
Charlie's having a lot of fun.
But like Joel had nothing to do with this at all.
Like he's just trying to run his broadcast.
Like don't don't like fuck with him.
You know what I mean?
Where are we here?
No, I have a lot of respect for Joel.
Like please don't get me wrong here.
I think he's one of the better streamers on Twitch.
There you go.
Uh rubber band two.
Sure.
I did that one.
Do how many?
What do I do?
Both sides.
Is RT game gonna get a shout out?
RT game is fucking awesome.
Literally the dude's blowing the fuck up like crazy.
Good for you, man.
For real.
I hope you're having a great fucking time.
It's a good fucking dude.
All right.
What do we got?
Same deal around the sides here.
Okay, okay.
I did it.
I finally did it.
We've been talking about dog smell.
We have not.
We invaded people's dreams.
Let's roll down.
This one is too, right?
Get it in there.
That doesn't want to stay.
A grown man has done something a child could do in 20 minutes.
He also invaded fucking critical.
What's he saying now?
No, don't.
He's, everything's, he's fine.
Joel, is Joel actually mad?
I hope he's not.
I really hope not.
I fucking hope not.
Is he actually?
No, don't fucking say that.
He seems mad.
Fucking goddammit.
Don't do that.
Yeah, he is.
I hope not.
Like, support his stream.
Don't fuck with it.
You know what I mean?
Like, please, guys.
For real.
He's having tech, okay.
Well, that's a different story then.
He seemed mad about stuff beforehand.
Chats just trolling.
Don't, please.
Come on, guys.
Like, he's, he's actually a really fucking good streamer.
Don't like, don't put this bullshit on him.
You know what I mean?
He thought chat spam was malicious.
I hope, I hope he doesn't think that.
For real.
Well, Joel, if you see this clip,
I hope you don't think that.
Because we were just having a good time.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm actually really sorry about that.
He knows.
Okay.
So he's having like actual technical issues.
All right.
I don't want to piss people off.
I like, respect everything he does.
So like, I really hope that's not the case.
All right.
Pinch these two together.
Get off of that and get on this.
The levers are done.
All right.
We need E.
E.
Oh, what have we got for E?
I don't know.
E.
Get, why do I have these in my ears?
I'm not listening to anything.
F.
This is E.
Where the fuck is E?
Oh shit.
Is this E?
This looks like, yeah.
This is part of it.
But we had our fun.
Uh, I would reiterate this one more time.
Our fun does not need to bleed into somebody else's stream.
Let them do what they want to do.
Right?
Where's the other half?
There it is.
Can you re-
I didn't have any fun.
Can you rewind?
That's it, right?
Okay.
All right.
Uh, this is done.
This moves over here.
Internet sucks.
It's been pretty stable, I think, for a while now, at least.
Let's go.
Ah, I'm going to piss my pants, though, for real.
I'm going to go pee.
Uh, I'll be back in like two minutes.
Hello?
That needs to come back.
Okay.
All right.
So I've got these pieces now.
It was actually two minutes.
I know, right?
Pretty good.
I got to get all this shit out of here.
There's some of these little knobs.
Get the fucking vacuum in here.
Why won't you come out?
What are you doing?
Why?
It's broken.
All right.
Relax, Jeremy.
You're fine.
I'm so fucking goddamn invested in this labo.
Me too.
It was 80 bucks.
So I better be so expensive.
80 bucks for cardboard.
All right.
We've got-
No, they're good.
Scuffed labo.
All right.
So this rolls over.
So roll, roll.
And then this comes down and these pieces go in.
Damn.
This is tight.
I spent money on this?
Yeah.
Fucking labo, dude.
Give me a break.
Where does this go?
What?
This goes across.
Like that?
Like that's it.
Okay.
I folded this.
That was a mistake, apparently.
That's okay.
It looks fine.
You spent 80 and made a thousand.
I can't fucking believe it.
People are so generous.
I don't even understand.
Just go to the green screen stream.
Maybe that'll be worth money.
All right.
Don't fold these.
Fold this.
Damn.
This part down.
Oh, it kind of crunches.
You know, I can sound like a broken record all I want,
but if you don't think this stream is worth paying for,
don't pay for it.
If you're like,
no, this ain't worth fucking $5 a month.
Don't do it.
I respect it.
Let's go.
How do you pirate the stream?
You just open it.
Same deal.
Fold it up.
Put it together.
Slot into slot.
I will never have a sub goal for you guys.
I'll never have a bit goal.
I never tell you guys you need to pay money.
I'll never tell you guys I need you to pay me.
If you think it was worth it,
that's a decision that you need to make.
I'm not going to make it for you.
You wouldn't pirate a stream.
This thing needs to flip around.
More merchandise.
I talked about it before.
There'll be two t-shirts that will be available
to purchase for the first time since 2014.
The glue man shirt will be coming back
as well as a planet shirt.
A solar system shirt will be available as well.
It'll be a new shirt.
If you want it, it'll be 20 bucks.
It'll never be more than that ever.
I will never charge more than $20 for a shirt
for any fucking circumstance literally ever.
And that's the way it is.
It'll be there probably in December.
Probably around Christmas time.
What about inflation?
Whatever.
That's a little nub.
Damn.
What about tax?
That's why I want to make it $20 only.
Flip it around.
Flip it all up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It looks good.
It'll be on Teespring if you're curious.
I got business marks releasing during Christmas.
Well, I figured it's a...
I did it like three years ago at the same time.
So can I pay you in cardboard?
No, unfortunately, no.
Get the first straw ready to go.
Big old robot hug.
The straw line should face like you see on the screen.
Like this.
Look at that.
Not down.
So does it go straight through this slot here?
Okay.
Then what?
All the way?
Okay.
You told me to do it.
Put the shirts on the EU site as well.
That's why I will never have a shirt more than $20.
Because it's crazy to ship internationally.
So if a shirt is like 30 bucks,
you're getting fucking screwed during the shipping process.
So those of you that are at EU,
a shirt will never be more than $20.
So if you get fucked in shipping,
it's not going to be, you know, super, super terrible.
Okay.
It's in the right spot.
Here it is.
So this has to...
Wait, wait, wait.
This comes up and around like this.
This goes down and in?
Damn.
Okay.
Dreadful diapers?
I don't think this would sell very well.
Cross them down.
Mine looks fucked up.
No, I have the opinion of
if you were to go to any store
and buy like a Star Wars shirt,
which is arguably...
And arguably this is just for real.
That shit is...
That franchise is worth like hundreds of millions of dollars.
And those t-shirts are like 15 bucks.
Me selling a German 985 shirt for like $32?
No.
No fucking way.
Not even close.
That looks good.
All right.
You'd buy it for $40.
Even if you would, it doesn't...
I don't care.
I'm not selling a shirt for more than fucking 20 bucks ever.
That's a huge amount of money.
$50 from Swiggity Swanky.
I just got back from a long day at work
and had to walk an extra three miles
home after my car died.
And now I find you doing this.
You're my favorite streamer on Twitch.
I hope you got your car situation taken care of
because that sucks.
Holy shit, dude.
Swiggity Swanky, thanks for the 50 fucking dollars, man.
It's a lot of money.
Thank you.
Hopefully your car is all right.
Hey, we're building a car right now.
Maybe you can use it.
Thank you so much, dude.
50 fucking bucks and you're having like car trouble.
Please help me take care of yourself first
because that's a lot of money.
But yeah, I don't just do merch for no reason.
If it's fun, if it makes sense, sure.
All right.
You thought you were done.
Flip this piece over.
Which one?
But multi-billion dollar companies
have an advantage of market penetration
and worth and width.
Economic status quo does not equate with real
or perceived value and any economist
that tells you otherwise can't see that.
You're blowing my brain here.
No, I think 20, 25 dollars is asking a lot.
It's a lot of money.
25 bucks for a t-shirt.
That's the kind of money you spend on
like a band t-shirt.
Am I like as popular as a band?
No, I mean, I don't think so.
On drugs.
That's good.
This piece has to fold this way.
Wait, wait, wait.
Spin it so the hole is up this way.
Why is it telling me to do that now?
This is gonna break.
What?
All right.
That's it.
That's good.
Locked in.
The first straw has been powered up.
Good.
That's great.
Am I making Thor's hammer?
I wish.
You have more subs than Matt Keefe
from the band Trivium who's also a streamer.
Yeah, but why if that was the case
then why would I want to tell people
to spend a shitload of money on me?
You know what I mean?
If there are people that are spending
five dollars a month on this stream already.
Hey, oh, I got a t-shirt.
It's 32 bucks.
Bullshit.
I don't believe it.
Why did you pay more for German expensive?
Yeah, they all get folded.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
$20 is good for a t-shirt.
I agree and it'll never change.
If you ever see a t-shirt on this channel
that's more than $20, link this clip
and tell me to go fuck myself.
For real.
All right.
Does that include shipping?
It does not.
Unfortunately, I'm sorry.
Same deal.
This goes like this.
Rapid inflation.
It's not that rapid.
Very true.
Did he comment on it at all?
Comment on what?
Did I comment on what?
What are you asking?
Hyperinflation.
Whatever.
Wait, do I have this right?
I do.
Comes in like this, like that.
Okay.
Death Grips is an anime podcast.
Well, that would have got me maybe like a year ago
but I know what Death Grips is.
Although I don't really listen to their music.
I haven't really listened very much.
That's good.
Up and around and we are closed.
Done.
So why is this one different than this one?
But the shirt that you are talking about
is a planet shirt.
It'll be like right here.
All the planets or at least most of them
most of the ones people care about should be fine.
A limited number.
No, there's no limited number of shirts.
It'll be available for about a month.
Oh shit.
Uh-oh.
Uh, this is a real...
I don't know what that is.
Got it!
Italics, I got it!
So this is fold one.
It was in here.
Fuck off, dickhead.
All right.
Uh, looks good to go to me.
Oh shit.
No, that's not good.
That's not good.
It needs to be like this but shit.
That.
Okay, that's good.
The white blip needs to be up.
Got it.
Uh, favorite band is Gorillaz?
Yes, it is.
That is for sure.
I need them sticker sheets and things.
I dropped.
All right, I need, I need, I need some water.
What are we doing here?
This is not right.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
Oh, I got two.
Okay, I got one here.
You want me to go above it?
What the fuck do you want?
What are you talking about?
Yes!
I'm so good.
I'm so good at what I do.
Close it all up.
I'm, I can't talk.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is too much.
Yes!
I'm sorry.
Can you not?
Stick it in.
Uh, which way does it go?
I'm so sorry, everybody.
I thought it was funny for five seconds.
That's it, right?
Looks good.
Cheat!
Fucking idiot.
Tiny table.
Jesus, there's a lot of fold lines here, Nintendo.
Somebody said italics is drunk?
Not my stream.
Good luck.
Nothing to do with me.
Somebody else's stream.
Not me.
If I had a pet rat, what would I name it?
Um, Grento.
What the fuck is this?
Stubbier?
Stick it into here.
Fuck off, Nintendo.
Be a break.
What?
I give up.
I'm going to bed.
I'm going, I'm going to bed.
Good night.
I lost viewers.
No, I did not.
Don't say that.
No, I did.
Getting late.
It's like fucking 9, 10.
It's 1130 Eastern, guys.
I get it.
You want to go to bed.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not going to bed till this is done.
Fuck you.
It's supposed to look like that.
I don't think it's supposed to look like that.
No, I guess it is.
No, it is.
It looks like that.
It's 830 in Vegas.
Yes, it is.
But it's like fucking midnight Eastern.
That's a lot of people go on Eastern time, man.
Eastern is the time people go on.
It's a fucking red blend, man.
Lost of viewers.
It's all right, though.
I get it.
I do.
Don't worry about it.
It's not about the viewer count.
It's about how much fun you guys are having.
It's all good.
If you're not having fun and you leave,
I'll see you next time.
I'll try better.
I'll try harder.
All right.
Done.
Using money.
That looks okay.
That doesn't look right.
Yeah, it does.
Right.
That's correct.
All right.
Put it in the engine.
Whoa.
Put it into a V.
And then what the fuck?
I can't.
I'm going to bed.
Good night.
No, I'm just kidding.
We're going till we're done.
That's it?
G.
I need a G.
Got it.
Relax.
All right.
Let's go.
Losing viewers.
Oh, well.
We tried.
All right.
Here we go.
Apparently, it tells the Toy-Con key which Toy-Con it's inside.
Viewers went up a bit.
I hope you guys are having fun.
Oh, what is this bullshit?
What?
Where is the?
I don't know what that is.
That's the fucking tar stuff.
Where's the?
Ow, my face.
The big square.
All right.
I can't.
I can't do it.
I don't think I can do it.
Okay.
Right here?
I think Jerm is drunk.
I think Jerm might be too drunk to do it.
I think Jerm might be too drunk to do a perfect fucking square.
I think Jerm is too drunk to do a perfect fucking square.
I can?
Where does this dumb thing go?
Let him have it.
This is cool.
You better not fucking come in.
This goes down around here.
Cool.
Now you lost me.
Stretch the rubber band on the right-hand lever up and over the tabs and it sits in the notch.
Fucking shut up.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Okay.
So like this over here.
I'm so good at everything.
Same thing on the other side.
Can I get it?
Fucking everything he does is perfect.
There it is.
Just look in there and tell me I fucking couldn't do this shit on my own.
Now we're good.
All right.
Check the right rubber band.
That's why you guys are the number one community on Twitch.
Somebody caught that.
I don't know how you did.
All right.
We're almost done.
Only three more steps.
G and H.
That's it.
H.
Uh, left side here.
Got it.
He's not coming in here.
Let me get all the nubs out.
Let me get the nubs out there.
Okay.
Looks good.
Now let me go.
I'm gonna go over here.
Uh, three nubs, four nubs, five nubs are out.
Okay.
Looks good.
Uh, have you dropped frames?
Uh, like a couple thousand right now, I guess.
So I'm sorry about that.
Why did that increase your viewers?
I don't know.
I don't, I don't have an answer for you.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
We're good.
Oh, okay.
We're fine.
Just check, just checking the vitals, you know.
I gotta check my vitals sometimes.
The vitals need to be checked.
All right.
What are we doing?
Don't let him re-watch this when he's sober.
Do you think it's any different than when I'm fucking not drinking?
I have nothing to hide.
Do you think I got something to hide?
Oh, wow.
I really was weird on Twitch last night.
Whatever.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that weird stuff on Twitch.
All right.
So that's good there.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
So Twitch fails.
What have I done that was a fail?
I didn't do anything.
I did a fake clown horn.
Perfect.
Bring this over here and fold it up.
Where does that go?
Right in the middle.
Top live stream fail.
I didn't do anything.
Looks good.
All right.
Next up is this piece.
Let's see it.
I did fail.
How?
How did I fail?
What are you talking about?
No, I get it now.
I get it.
Sorry.
I feel grilled.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Is this correct?
Yeah, it is.
What the fuck?
What are these for?
That looks good.
Part H.
The last little bits here.
And then two.
What'd you miss?
You're gonna fight with Charlie.
That's pretty much it.
Looks good.
And lost.
It's funny that you think that.
Whoa.
Wee.
Wee, I'm on a swing.
Mom, push me more.
Push me a little bit higher.
That's you.
No, that was me doing that to Charlie.
Not to you.
What are you talking about?
Don't put words in my hands.
That's not right.
How many figures am I holding up?
Um, whatever.
Best of live stream fail.
What the fuck is this?
Better not fuck with me here.
Don't fuck with me.
Your friend is dying on camera?
I guess I'll have to watch that later on live stream fail.
It'll probably be the top like best of live stream fail.
Don't do that.
Hey, Shadowlight, what's up?
But yeah, I'll look at that later.
I don't care about that.
All I care about is this colony.
I have an undying.
Don't fucking.
I don't belong on there.
I didn't do anything weird today.
I didn't do anything to belong on there.
Nice people on there sometimes, you know?
But whatever.
I didn't do anything.
So I didn't do anything weird today.
How much is the rent in Las Vegas?
$20,000 a month.
That was weird, but that's not like live stream fails weird.
I'm not weird.
I'm not.
I'm just fucking around.
I'm not weird.
What is this clip?
Nice people on there sometimes, you know?
But I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
So I didn't do anything weird today.
How much is the rent in Las Vegas?
$20,000 a month.
That's not weird.
That's me stating.
Hey, let me tell you guys something.
Fast forward right now.
Three or four hours from now,
I'm going to look fucking way worse than I do now.
My face is going to be greasy.
I'm going to be way more drunk than I am now.
I'm going to have like a fucked up hair.
Water is going to be pouring down my shirt.
It's going to look really bad.
Oh yeah?
You think so, Jeremy?
Has it been two hours?
Hour and a half?
Let's take a look.
Hey, let me tell you guys something.
Fast forward right now.
Three or four hours from now,
I'm going to look fucking way worse than I do now.
Do I though?
My face is going to be greasy.
I'm going to be way more drunk than I am now.
I'm going to have like a fucked up hair.
Water is going to be pouring down my shirt.
It's going to look really bad.
Just remember this.
Like three or four hours from now, okay?
Remember this.
Hey, say it again.
Let me tell you guys something.
Fast forward right now.
Three or four hours from now,
I'm going to look fucking way worse than I do now.
My face is going to be greasy.
I'm going to be way more drunk than I am now.
I'm going to have like a fucked up hair.
Water is going to be pouring down my shirt.
It's going to look really bad.
Just remember this.
Like three or four hours from now, okay?
Get out of here.
He's wrong.
I look the same.
All right, grub comes up.
Snap comes down.
Looks good.
All right.
Looks all right.
Has your box magically formed a nice little roof like this?
If it hasn't, go back and check.
I got a nice little roof like that.
Why am I wearing?
I'm not wearing any headphones.
Looks like Mr. Rootbox has got a hole in his forehead.
We're going to cover that up for him.
Where are those?
It's right over the lid there.
Nothing goes in there.
So it just goes up like that.
So it just goes over the whole thing.
Okay.
Don't fuck with me, dude.
Don't fuck with me here, man.
Oh, Jeremy's too drunk to do it.
All right.
Natalix is fucking shit faced.
Rubber band.
One of the little ones.
Small rubber band.
Two holes.
Well, it's been fun.
See you guys never.
I'm deleting my Twitch channel, my YouTube.
I'm deleting my Instagram, my Twitter.
It's all getting deleted.
Sorry.
Somebody said good.
Fuck, dude.
Good.
Damn, that makes me like sad.
Fuck.
So that's in there.
That's it.
Wait, why is it?
So that's the way it looks.
Okay.
String.
Oh, worms.
What the fuck?
It's a worm?
It's gone.
Oh, I needed that.
I need that.
I need that thing.
Okay.
I got it back like this.
Like that.
Like this.
Who just gave a hundred fucking dollars to this terrible stream?
Thank you, Deuce the Gamer for the $100.
I demand you do the submarine next.
Germa expensive.
Let's see.
Thank you for the hundred bucks though, man.
Holy shit.
That's a lot of fucking money.
We'll see.
Submarine.
You got it.
What do I do with this?
Not the end of the spring just as shown.
Oh, pretzel.
Pretzel.
That didn't work.
A hundred bucks from Kyra Toby.
Hey, Germa, I like your hair.
So much money.
Do you like my magic trick?
Jesus.
Thank you.
Two hundred dollars for eating and regurgitating string.
Thank you, Kyra.
Thank you, Kyra Toby.
And to Deuce the Gamer, both of you guys, for real.
They liked your hair.
Thanks, man.
I still got a hairline.
Still there.
I'm thirty-three.
Thirty-three.
I'm fucking good for thirty-three.
You know what I mean?
Look, let me tie a fucking knot.
Please.
How do I do this?
I did it.
In case you're having trouble, here are some step-by-step images.
Have you made a proper knot?
I have.
What happened?
Deuce the Gamer gave a hundred dollars.
Also, the helicopter, too.
Thank you, Deuce the Gamer, for the hundred fucking bucks.
And the helicopter.
Yeah, fuck yeah, dude.
I'm not turning the stream off till it's done.
Bebraham gave twenty community subs.
Twenty of them.
Twenty.
Holy fuck.
Okay.
Thank you, Bebraham.
That's a fucking lot of subs.
And thank you for the hundred.
Two.
Three hundred dollars.
Deuce the Gamer, Karatobi.
Deuce the Gamer again.
That's a lot of fucking money.
Thank you.
No messages, really, or anything, but...
Besides, to make the helicopter and make the submachine.
Gun.
He's gonna wake up tomorrow and not know what those stacks of money are from.
Thanks.
Cry.
I'm not gonna cry.
But cry, you baby.
What?
I didn't do anything.
I just didn't cry.
For real, though.
Where's the puke string?
Where's the string?
There it is.
Kidding, I'm not gonna do it again.
You guys are too fucking kind.
Seriously.
Thank you for the massive, obscene amounts of money.
Obscene.
Obscene amounts of fucking money.
Thank you.
How does this go through?
If you were rich, you'd buy me a car.
You don't have to buy me a car, man.
So many people gave so much money to this fucking stream that, you know, don't worry about it.
It's fucking hard to believe sometimes.
For real.
No jokes.
Where does this go?
This smells like the inside of my mouth.
Right.
I got it right.
Done.
Got it.
Rubber band.
Oh yeah.
$15 from Butterderp.
$10 from Rionic.
Thank you.
Jeremy, I've been watching your streams on your YouTube for a while.
I figured I might as well join in on the meme.
Wish you the very best, as you always stay true to being a down-to-earth dude.
I can't pretend to be anybody else, so thank you.
I'm glad you think that way.
Thanks so much, man.
Enraged Grandpa with five community subs.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I'll just fucking shit-faced over there.
I can hear him.
All right, that looks good, right?
That looks correct.
What are you doing?
Fifty.
Five zero.
Community subs from Tora T.
Holy shit.
I can't even fucking comprehend this right now.
Show us your dick.
I read that.
I read that out loud.
Uh, no.
Uh, Tora, Tora, that's an insane amount of fucking gifted subs.
That's an in-fucking-sane amount of people to give subs to.
Uh, don't make it a competition.
I hope it's not.
Don't treat this like a competition, guys.
Uh, it's not.
So, uh, that's like, that's $250 somebody just spent right now.
Tora T.
So don't, don't let me get away with this.
You know what I mean?
And here's what I mean by that.
Uh, there's like 10 different, like, huge streams I want to do.
Uh, don't let me just like, oh, whatever, whatever, whatever.
Oh, I just didn't do it.
It's a lot of fucking money for someone to have.
And I want to use it.
Don't, don't let me just fucking take your money and like rung.
Because you deserve, uh, you deserve to have something to show for it.
I can't fucking imagine spending two, three, four hundred fucking dollars on somebody.
I hope it's worth your while.
I'll try.
Thank you.
Uh, Tora T for the fucking insane amount of subscriptions.
And then Tiny Cactus comes in with five, five or fifty, doesn't fucking matter.
You guys are all fucking insane.
You guys are all incredible.
Do we have a date for the green screen?
Yes, Thursday.
Thursday is the green screen.
There is a date.
All right.
We need the engine.
I don't take this shit for granted.
I try not to.
I really don't want to.
It's a lot of fucking money.
Somebody has to fucking make that money.
Somebody has to work for that money.
Somebody has to make that fucking money.
You know what I mean?
That money comes from somewhere, you know, for free.
I hope you realize I don't fucking take that for granted at all.
Drugs, drugs.
This is, this is me working for that money.
If you say so.
I just, we've talked about a thousand times.
Let me at least try to make it fucking worth you being here.
I'll break it.
That's correct, right?
Oh, even more subscription.
Nat Kitty gives five community subs.
Thank you.
It's never ending, Tim Allen.
It's not going to stop for a long time.
Don't underestimate the power of entertaining someone.
Yeah, but money, it's a lot of fucking money, man.
Some of you guys pay 10 bucks a month for Netflix.
I got to at least try.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I got to fucking at least try.
You're more entertaining than Netflix, to be honest.
If you say so, I hope so.
Thank you.
Well, you do what you do without a salary.
You guys pay my fucking salary.
So that's what this shit is all about.
Just look at the last 20 minutes.
You guys pay my fucking salary.
It had better be worth it.
So where are you, boss?
In a sense, kind of, yeah.
Novi came in with five community subs.
Five community subs of Novi.
This year, cry.
I'm not going to cry.
I'm not going to cry, okay?
Cry, cry, cry, cry, cry.
Bebraham gave 20 more, so thank you, Bebraham.
I just want you guys to leave each stream and say that was fun.
That's it.
I'm going to cry.
I'm not going to fucking cry.
Whoa, am I still on this?
People are giving a lot of money.
Somebody said wimp.
I didn't, that was a pretend.
All right, what do I do with this thing?
Thank you for the 20 fucking community subs, dude.
Jesus.
Just wait till the green screen stream.
That's going to be a ton of fun.
Week or two later, we're going to have a fucking movie night.
Then like two weeks later, there's going to be something else.
Christ.
Thank you, Kairatobi for the 20 subs.
20 community subs from Kairatobi.
A lot of fucking people and a lot of subs.
20 people even is a lot of people.
Proud pleb forever.
And I'm, I, that's fine.
That's fine, man.
Like it's, it's fine.
Like I don't, you don't have to subscribe.
Did you have any fun?
If the answer was yes, then that's fucking fine.
You've made $250 an hour this stream.
That's more money than a fucking doctor.
Do you understand?
Sometimes people, why, why do you feel this way?
Why do you act like that?
And people are just giving you money.
That's like more money than a fucking surgeon.
So sorry that sometimes I can be like, I hope it's fucking worth it.
Cause I really believe that.
All right.
Thread the ring.
It's way more than $250 an hour.
I can't even fucking comprehend it.
Earning more than a mosquito doctor.
Way more than a mosquito doctor, dude.
A thousand times more.
$900 over six hours.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Right, right.
You make me sick.
L-U-L.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I'm trying.
This year, 2019 especially.
He's close.
I'm not going to cry.
Cry.
How do you make a knot?
Yes, you are.
I'm not close to crying.
Tie it off completely.
This is what the real thing should look like.
Does your knot look the same?
It's a little long, but it will get the job done.
Cry or pre-record it.
Crying will make you feel better.
Put a round.
All right, leave it.
I'll get the hiccups now.
Oh, I got the fucking hiccups.
This goes through here, there.
All right, so that is situated.
It's done.
He's trying to hold back the tears.
Seven years ago when I made my first YouTube video.
Never in a million fucking years did I think I'd be sitting down in Las Vegas
with a ton of fucking supporters.
Just giving me fucking money.
Never in a million years.
Ever.
He's getting reversed cyberbullying.
I got a free vibe this video.
Well, if you never think it's worth doing, don't up your subscription.
I've said that before and I'll say it again.
If you watch and over time, over months or six months, two months, three months,
one month and you're like, I don't care anymore.
This is not fucking fun anymore.
Do not pay me any more money because I wouldn't deserve it at that point.
Hi.
That's it, right?
What's next?
I got two of these, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you butterdurk for the $15.
Jerma, I don't leave your stream saying that was fun.
I leave your stream saying no, please don't leave.
It's a unique feeling.
Nothing else has ever replicated.
Thank you.
Uh, also, uh, nksaur says, I like that you hold,
you like that you must hold you accountable for making quality content.
Well, what else are you paying for?
You know what I mean?
Think, like really think about that.
Like think about it.
Like, oh, thanks for the sub.
Thanks for the sub.
Thanks for the sub, man.
Like, what are you paying for?
You have actively decided on your own free will to continuously,
continuously for a lot of people, pay to my bank account a monthly payment.
At some point, you have to think about like, what, what am I paying for?
Just, oh, I want to give you money because I'd like you.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
But what are you paying for?
That's something that I fucking think about all the time.
Which is why?
Oh, do this.
I want to try that.
I want to try this.
I want to try something like that.
I want to do something new.
I want to bring something new.
I want to let's, let's do a skit.
Let's do a fucking community event.
That's why I want to do that shit.
That's $500 from Deuce the Gamer.
What you've
five, that's some, I think that's the most amount of money I've ever seen in one bit.
That's fucking ridiculous, man.
That's ridiculous.
That is like a month of fucking like a part-time income.
Like two or three weeks.
Uh, and Deuce the Gamer says, uh, oh yeah, before I go, please do a Fortnite dance.
I told you my favorite for entire.
Uh, yeah, this one, the one with the fucking kid with the backpack on this one.
There's a lot coming.
Uh, and a ton of you people have paid for it.
Already like a ton of you guys have paid for it.
I hope the things that you will see in the next couple of months.
Do you think of fun?
That's all I can say.
The power of Christ compels you.
Streamer does anything for money.
It's five fucking hundred dollars.
I can't, I still can't fucking believe it whenever it happens, man.
That's the most I think I've ever seen in my life.
Show your dick.
Why would I show my dick now of all the times to ask for that?
Why would that happen now?
I can't even pay attention to this.
All right.
Where did these go?
Make his dick cry.
I need, uh, I need the engine thing back.
Where does this go?
Circle through here.
I'm just glad you find happiness in this stream.
I don't have much else to say.
I could go off on like a tangent about it.
I've done it a couple times already.
There are some streams that when I end them, I'm lying in bed
and I look at the ceiling and I just say to myself,
holy fucking shit dude.
How, what happened?
How was that even possible?
This is gonna be one of them.
What, what happened?
Why are you not crying yet?
Because there's no reason to cry.
There's no, I don't have a reason to cry.
I have a reason to be very happy.
And incredibly importantly,
I have a lot of reasons to be very, very, very happy.
And a ton of the messages that I read from people are about,
hey dude, uh, my life like sucks.
He's getting close.
And it's like, fuck man.
Like, oh, like I've had such a hard time.
Like this stream is so much fun.
And you don't think that I think about that?
Like all the fucking time?
You know what I mean?
And then I see like huge, fucking huge amounts of money
coming to the stream.
It's like, god damn.
It better be fucking worth it.
It better be.
I'm just happy to fucking hang out and be here, man.
You're trying to get it.
You almost got it.
It was close.
It was real close.
You made yourselves cry.
But that's for real.
I actually, I saw a clip of Creparian who mentioned something similar.
And I have a lot of respect for Creparian.
He's kind of an OG in this space, right?
But it's like, whenever I hear something like that,
I start to internalize it, you know?
And I try to think about, you know,
I want to make sure that person's all right.
I mean, the person's having fun.
The person's okay.
You know what I mean?
It's something that you think about a lot.
It just got to that donation now.
Yeah, there it is.
Five fucking hundred.
But yeah, if you think of that,
that's something that I'm not the only one, you know?
There's plenty of other streamers and content creators
that take a lot of, you know, pride
and a lot of, they're like, wow,
I'm actually helping somebody.
Like, it means a lot to hear that.
I heard Crip say that the other day
and I was like, holy shit.
I'm like, all right, well, respect for you.
Just increased by fucking a thousand percent.
You know what I mean?
But Crip is Crip.
You know, everybody knows who that is.
He's going to retire.
Not in the plans at all.
Who is preparing it?
You don't, Crip?
You don't know who Crip is?
Come on.
You don't know who Crip.
He's like Hearthstone, Diablo,
Path of Exile.
I've never heard of that person in my life.
Crip is a salty baby who cries over children's card games.
Well, excuse me.
What am I doing right now?
What is this?
This is, this is an adult game.
But for real, you guys are fucking awesome.
Don't ever think differently.
There's so many different kinds of people.
So many different points of views.
So many different fucking people here.
I don't even know who Crip is.
So many different points of views.
So many different fucking people here.
This channel is, over the last three years,
has grown a lot.
And it's gotten to a point where there's so many people here.
Just happy you're fucking here.
And that's it.
Let's finish the car.
I am a people.
Cry, cry, cry, cry.
All right.
What is this even here for?
Get this out of here.
And there's so many streamers and so many people
that are doing the same things.
So many people to support.
So many people that are worth your time.
It's just remarkable that a lot of you are here right now.
This late as well.
Through and down.
We only liked your hairstyle.
We almost made it, you almost, almost.
It got real close.
I could feel like the, I could feel the fucking chest pain.
Where it was like, hey, I'm good.
But it's something I think about a lot.
And if you think that's just a joke,
I'm sorry, but that's not part of the routine.
I found out you were streaming and I've been here since.
I can't, I wouldn't rather be anywhere else.
Thank you, Butterdirt, for real.
As long as we're all having fun, right?
That goes in, that goes forward, I hope.
Does that look right?
That looks wrong.
No, that's right.
That's right.
I got it.
Can't wait till you, we're here till 6 a.m.
Well, for however long we're here, we're here.
All right, hold on.
I gotta look at this.
I need this thing back.
I need the little fat one.
And there it is.
A little bump right across the bump.
Close enough, I would say.
Jerma, here's a dollar for your crippling chicken nugget addiction.
It's fucking crazy, dude.
I'm sorry, I know.
The roof still goes up.
It does.
All right, we don't need these anymore.
So where the hell does this go?
This goes in here with the, oh, this is not right.
Yeah, it is.
Ah, that was a loud noise.
Don't!
Uh, Tiny, thank you, Tiny840 for the 10 bucks.
I can't give nearly as much as some people have here.
But I just want to show my appreciation for what you do for all of us.
Keep it up.
You never expected Tiny to give a fucking huge amount of money.
Ever.
Don't ever feel obligated to pay the stream money.
Just, if you're here, you're here.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
Two dollars, one dollar, a hundred dollars.
Like, it's all the same.
Somebody decided to give money to me today.
Because I think about me, right?
If I was in a stream and giving somebody a hundred fucking dollars.
You know how it is.
Thank you.
Cry.
It almost, it almost happened.
It was really fucking close.
It was so close.
You don't have any idea how close that was.
That was like...
Here we go.
Lock it in.
Push him over the edge.
Somebody give a thousand dollars.
Don't do that.
Do not give me a thousand dollars.
For any reason.
I mean, ever.
All right.
So I can turn this.
Okay, it's turned.
This goes in there.
Somebody give him a thousand dollars.
Get him over the edge.
Maybe two rubber bands.
One, two.
One dollar equals one tier.
Two of them together.
Okay.
Double thick.
So these go over this.
Okay.
Around there.
Good.
Yeah, it's still there.
Try pulling the reverse lever of the rubber band.
Snaps it back.
It's a retrofixer.
Want to see the internal guts?
Oh, yeah.
It's good.
Try pulling this pull cord, too.
It should snap back as well.
Fifty bucks.
From Visual Warlock.
Jerma, I found your Jerma Rumble videos on YouTube and instantly became a fan.
You're one of the genuinely funny people on Twitch.
And I want to say thanks for making me laugh every time on stream.
Thank you, Visual Warlock.
Thank you, the power of the rubber bands.
I'm glad you found them and I'm glad you like them.
They're a lot of love when it's at those videos.
So I hold a really deep place in my heart.
So thank you.
Glad you enjoy them.
The gadgets are complete.
Cry incoming.
All right.
Almost done with the car.
Main base is time.
Get the fuck out of here.
J and I.
I, we need the middle pieces here.
Incoming cry.
I'll give all my bits if he cries.
Why do you want me to cry?
Oh, when is he gonna cry?
I'm not going to cry.
I know it's getting late.
10, 11, 12.
It's almost 1 a.m. Eastern.
I'm sorry it's getting late.
Let's try to get this done quick.
Give me the next two hours.
No cry, no topless, no dick.
Fails bad man.
By the way, that is a thousand dollars from Deuce the Gamer.
Thousand bucks.
A thousand.
Not a hundred.
Not a five hundred.
A thousand.
One thousand fucking dollars.
Fucking grand.
A grand.
Deuce the Gamer says,
Here's a few more to round it out.
Thanks for everything.
You're my expensive.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding me?
A thousand fucking dollars.
A thousand.
Deuce the Gamer, thank you so much, man.
Rounding out his one thousand fucking dollars.
Jesus.
A hundred thousand fucking bits, man.
I've never seen that before.
He already left the chat?
Jesus Christ.
I've never seen yellow before.
For a hundred thousand fucking bits in one day.
A thousand fucking dollars.
You up, you paid,
you alone paid for the fucking green screen stream, dude.
Honestly, God, that's not even a joke.
That's gold.
Deuce, that's...
Do you think you can buy them?
Buy like a bed for a thousand dollars.
That's like a car payment.
You can buy like so many things at a thousand dollars.
You can buy like a Vive.
That's so much money.
Deuce the Gamer, I'm not sure that
your amount will ever be fucking surpassed in one day.
MultiTrip just gave fifty bucks.
Yeah, Jeremy, you're funny.
Funny looking.
As long as it makes me happy, dude.
I'm fucking glad to take your fifty fucking dollars.
Jesus.
Thank you, MultiTrip.
Waiting for the cry.
I'm not gonna...
I'm just...
I'm just happy and kind of floored.
There's people in this world that deem this stream worth a thousand dollars.
I'm speeding off into the fucking sunset.
I'm gonna fold this down.
In.
He's challenging his audience to beat a thousand dollars.
No, God, that's so much money.
I'm not challenging anybody.
Show them.
Show them how cool you are.
Come on, harder.
Do it.
It's done.
This goes in the front here, right in the front door.
Right?
Of course.
Now we can flip the piece over,
make sure the lock doesn't fall out of the slot when you do.
I did.
As this piece folds together, I fall asleep on stream.
God, I'm gonna probably die.
So this needs to go up here.
I can still hear that car.
Yeah, me too.
I can still hear the car too.
I don't know.
I don't know what he's doing.
He's just like speeding around.
I'm a psycho.
What do you have to be?
Okay.
Does it match?
One piece from sheet.
I got it.
Throw it all up.
If everyone donates 50 bits, we can surpass the record.
My Lord.
I'm impressed.
Yes, I am.
I'm in Pacific Standard Time.
All right.
So this comes across here, here, that, there.
Should be good to go.
Lay the triangle flat once it's connected.
And then bring this up.
Fold it down.
Fold this down.
And in.
Inside.
Looks good.
The other piece.
Sorry.
I feel like even 50 bits.
You guys are too much for me, man.
I gave mine really early.
I think I'm going to go make like a tuna fucking sandwich.
Like a tuna tortilla.
Let's get those bits.
You know what?
Tuna what?
I didn't fold it.
That's okay.
So this goes in here.
Just like that.
Ah, you fucking idiot.
Uh, Amnestic OW gave 20 subs.
Oh, we got another one.
Amnestic OW.
Amnestic Overwatch.
Amnestic OWO.
Made me 20 fucking community subs.
Jesus.
Criminic.
Turn it around.
Thank you, Amnestic.
For your huge fucking contribution.
My God.
How many more for new emotes?
Um, oh my God.
Five, four, three, two.
There were like 500 subs.
Five tonight.
Just tonight.
My God.
What the fuck?
I'm going to get a tuna sandwich, man.
I'm going to go eat some tuna fish.
Kyra Toby just gave a hundred dollars.
Kyra Toby has given two hundred dollars tonight.
How high can we go?
That's not up to me.
I thank you for the fucking hundred bucks.
I'm going to go get a tuna sandwich.
I'll be right back.
Thank you for the fucking hundred bucks, Kyra Toby.
I need some tuna fish.
Oh my God.
20 subs from Amnestic and a hundred dollars.
I don't know what to do because I eat tuna fish.
I'll see you guys in five minutes.
Not even.
All right.
I'm good.
Okay.
He was crying.
I can't.
How did the tears in your sandwich taste?
Moisture.
That's a tortilla.
Yeah, it is.
It's a corn tortilla because I'm trying not to eat bread
because every time I eat bread for some reason, I feel like shit.
I don't know.
The base is complete.
Okay.
That's it.
Last four pieces from I.
Turning into an old fucking man.
I am.
You're right.
Okay.
Seven fucking hours.
Holy shit.
Your dad's gluten intolerant.
He clipped all wheat and grain.
He feels great.
Yeah.
I mean, that's kind of the idea.
Seeing how I feel every time I eat bread.
It just I feel like shit.
I don't know why I haven't been able to figure it out.
Where is that?
Christ.
Where the fuck is that?
All right.
Oh, you're triple spotting the gas and stickers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So over here, the big one.
You ate that like a child.
Right here.
All the way around.
Beautiful.
Looks good.
Same thing with the more than once, apparently.
No cry.
No topless.
I ain't getting topless.
I'll tell you that you already.
Oh, my goodness.
A wizard just gave a hundred fucking dollars here.
Hundred fucking bucks from a wizard.
Jerma, you congratulations on being the best streamer on Twitch
and building such a fantastic fan base.
You demonstrated exceptional creativity and individuality
in an environment that demands mediocrity and mold fitting creators.
I consider you a pioneer of new era of comedy and entertainment.
Here's a dollar for every time you maybe cry laughing
or help improve a bad day week or month.
Thank you.
A wizard.
Master of comedies channel is a different channel,
but I will gladly take his reign.
Thank you so much.
That means a fucking lot.
Thank you.
For the one hundred dollars.
I wonder if I'm gonna have to do this to all four of them.
Somebody give a thousand dollars?
Yeah, they did.
Yeah, they gave a thousand fucking dollars earlier.
Yes, they did.
Oh, boy, it was a fucking insane amount of money.
Cry so I can leave.
I'm gonna cry.
I got a little choked.
But I cry.
You almost did.
I got a little choked.
I didn't cry.
Cry so I can croak.
Fuck.
What are you talking?
Cry so I can croak.
I forgot to sleep last night, so it's late.
It's one plus in the morning.
Easter night, I understand.
Have a great night.
Thanks for sticking around as long as you did.
Don't need this with a fucking cat.
Yeah.
All right.
Attach the...
These long tabs should feed by...
Okay.
Like this.
Okay, get the fuck away from me.
Pull the tabs up.
Little circles in the way.
They're staying there for good.
This is where the...
I'm gonna puke.
This is where the switch goes.
Okay.
Okay, good.
At least we'll see him puke.
That was a joke also.
I'm not going to puke.
Although I did just eat...
I did just drink like half a fucking box of wine
and eat tuna fish.
So...
All bets are off at this point.
Okay.
That is a...
That is such a puke combo.
You're right.
That is the ultimate puke combo.
Oh, I drank a bunch of wine.
Hey, and a tuna fish in the fridge.
Let me eat as much as I possibly can.
Good.
One, two, three, four, five.
Looking good.
What? Eat ice cream?
Why would I eat ice cream?
All right, we're done.
We are almost done.
How did I make this?
Something fell off.
In.
These two side tabs...
The bottom should be sticking on.
Are they gonna look okay?
Yeah.
The whole thing over.
Like this.
And it falls down.
And stick the side tabs into here.
Shit.
Okay, that's in.
That's in too.
So it goes all the way in, right?
And then it comes around the sides
and goes into the holes, okay?
Got it.
And then like that.
The Toy-Con car's body is complete.
The f...
This is it.
This is the end.
We made it.
We did it.
Boys and girls.
Looks good.
All right.
Bring the wheel in.
Lower from above.
Okay.
Get it.
Correct.
Line up R and L.
That's correct.
Right here.
Nav it in, right?
Okay, that's up all the way.
I'm so good at this.
Looks good.
Add the Joy-Con.
Get the key.
We're done.
It's done.
Done.
Well, I made a baby car wheel.
This goes like this straight in.
What an emotional moment.
Done.
I can do that too.
It works.
Next up, let's prepare the pedal.
I got that right here.
All right.
You can see, right?
It's already in.
Size 8.
I'd recommend using the TV for your first outing in the car.
Are you ready to play?
I'm...
It's done.
I did it.
50 bucks from Golden Cricket.
I was bludgeoning the beef stick earlier and I heard you choked up a bit.
I didn't...
So here you go.
Did you talk...
Wait.
What are you talking about?
All right.
I got my pedal.
It's right here.
Oh, I'm fucking ready.
Put the key in.
Thank you Golden Cricket for your 50 bucks.
Let's go.
Key is in.
I'm ready to fucking drive a car.
This is what you came here for.
Head to the nearby fuel station and fill your tank.
Gas station.
Here it comes.
Open world adventure game.
How do you...
I don't have a brake.
I don't have brake.
There's no brake.
Hold on the reverse lever.
What's the reverse lever?
This?
Oh, shit.
One of the side levers you can use the hose to fuel up.
Got it.
Make the game huge.
Wait, you can't see the wheel.
There.
Fill the tank up.
Get rid of face cam.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Now what?
Build a car wash.
Where do you build a car wash?
Complete all the missions.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Get on the road.
Hey, so we made it to the road here.
Let's get up here.
Can I help you?
What are you doing?
Are you going to say something or what?
Can anybody even see me in here?
No, I got my camera set up perfectly.
What the fuck was that?
Hey, breath of the wild.
You can go to the hole in one, bro.
All right, so where do I go from here?
What does this do?
Should I go inside?
Very generous traction.
Where do I go?
All right, we're going to go this way.
There's so much latency.
Make the game bigger.
What do you want to do?
There you go.
There.
Are we having fun?
Are we having fun yet?
All right, let's go this way.
Let's explore the open world.
Okay.
Desert area 0 of 8.
This is kind of fun.
Pull the lever.
Tornado.
Tornado, pub champ.
Pub champ.
That's so delayed.
Find the flag.
Drive up the pyramid.
You got it.
Just don't want to fucking gas.
Hold the cord.
Give me the flag.
I win.
You got to move.
Okay, that was fun.
Go in the pyramid.
Inside.
There it is.
Oh, I broke it.
Did I break it?
No, it's fine.
Get in the pyramid, please.
Oh, there's a fucking boulder in the way.
Holy shit.
I just got a treasure chest.
We're an official treasure hunter now.
So where do I go from here?
Why has it stopped going so fast?
Okay.
Gas.
We did it.
I've been holding the wheelie for at least 60 seconds.
Oh, dice.
Try to roll die until it adds up to 10.
That's 6, 12.
That's not right.
That's not correct.
Ay, yi, yi.
Gas.
I need another...
Jesus Christ.
What is it?
6, 5, 6, 7.
6, 5, I need a 3.
3, please.
Come on.
6, 7.
A 10 for ever?
A 10 for style?
Chop down five palm trees. Let's give it a go. One. I wish there was a weight. What?
Climb the snowy mountain? You got it. Let's go. Listen to that. Listen to that.
Let's get up there, come on. Come on, get up there. Break it. Give me the flag.
Get the flag in the mountain area. There's one more thing up here. What is it?
How many lilies do I have? What's this? Oh, there's a little place to go.
Oh my god. Smash it. I'm not gonna smash it. The pedal is giving me some resistance now though.
Did I fuck it up? I think it's okay. It didn't do anything. Does it know that I don't have a foot on it?
What? Apparently. Alright, as fast as I fucking can go downhill, go.
Dropping on two wheels. Turn signal. Oh, you're dead.
I'm almost there. This looks kind of fun, not gonna lie. Actually, it's kind of fun. Out of fuel.
Oh. There's now something called car. Introducing the car.
Hey Jeremy. Have you tried?
This thing is really nice looking though. He's skipping the lower. Yes, I am.
Take a test. Oh, it's like 2 a.m. Eastern. Jesus.
There's still like 24, 2,500 people still here. Thanks for staying up with me, guys.
We get it. We made it. I'm here Mr. Receiving. Tell me a little bullshit, please.
Now break it. I can't move. How do I like, how do I go back? Get this fucking key out of here.
First of all, I got the key. We're not going anywhere.
Change vehicle. The submarine and the plane. I didn't make those yet though, dude.
I don't have the submarine. It's like four more hours from now.
I can't, are they talking? Because I can't hear them.
DLC. All right. Bye. Oh, we don't have the submarine at all.
60 to 120 minutes. Four hours. I don't think I can make it.
Yeah. It's like, it's been eight hours. I need to get more food.
I knew he was a liar. Get some sleep. Yeah, I think it's time for bed.
I'm going to wind down. I will finish the labo. Probably never.
Oh, be careful. No wine on the table. Oh, that's good.
I'm going to put this on my shelf back here. Got it.
Don't, I'm not going to, this is, this is like actually nice.
This is a very nice looking piece of equipment. I'm not going to break it.
Plus you can use this as Mario Kart. I will school so many noobs.
I'm going to use this as Mario Kart 8. Anyways, that's it.
There was an absurd amount of support tonight. Thank you everybody.
Let's get this turned on. Let's move this out of the way.
Oh, move the pedal, move the car, move this shit out of the way.
You guys are un fucking believable.
When the credits roll, there's going to be hundreds of fucking names.
I'll never be able to keep up. I'm breaking things as I move.
Come on, man. Okay. Let's do the bits.
Let's go back before here. Back to, oh, why the, this is fucked up.
Well, my bit readings are screwed up. I need that website because this shit is fucked up.
No, never mind. I got it. I got it.
So let's go back here to quite a while ago.
This is seven hours ago now. Damn. That's a long fucking time ago.
Thank you too. By the way, if you take it off, I know it's late.
See you soon. I will see you guys on tomorrow, Sunday, Monday.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Tuesday, we will talk more about the green screen.
There's a lot to talk about.
I will give the poll on Tuesday because that's pretty much what a majority of the stream will be discussed on.
So let's get this labo shit out of here and let's go with an outro. There we go.
So, uh, seven hours ago, we had tons of gifted subs and we also had bits from, let me move this out of the way so I can get closer here.
Decozerski for the one dollar. Chat cast a dud. All of the money is fake. Thank you.
Pocket Pauling gave an absolute fucking shitload of money.
They gave so much fucking money tonight. I can't even comprehend.
Rentacat gave five dollars. They said sorry. I'm not sure why you're apologizing, but thank you, Rentacat.
Derek, thank you. DerekX3 for the five dollars. Sorry. I don't know why people are apologizing.
Matters of Darkness, thanks for the one dollar and your huge amount of community subs.
And I'm here too. Thank you.
Manboy, thanks for the one dollar earlier. You should stream labo more, huh? Sorry.
Thank you.
Limicios, thanks for the five dollars. No message, just cheers. Thank you so much for the five bucks.
Peanut Chan, thanks for three dollars. I don't know why I bought these bits, but I'll add them to the pile.
You're fucking amazing. Thank you.
It means a lot.
Germo Meme Man gave one dollar. Shout out to SimpleFlips.
Okay. Shout out to that person. Thank you.
Awesome Alec, thanks for the one dollar and one cent. Put seven hundred dollars on red for me.
Thank you. Maybe I will. No, I won't.
Abserviday, thank you Abserviday for the money.
If you don't let this pocket-palling person name your first child by now, I don't know what to think.
I hope you name it Greg.
Spegar, thank you Spegar for the two bucks.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you Spegar for the two bucks.
Germo cries on stream. Let me say, I didn't cry.
And I'm so glad we finally get to see it on stream.
You know what I mean? Fucking Minecraft is so...
It's a revolutionary game.
Ayayay.
Minecraft, what a revolutionary video game.
Fucking Minecraft.
Oh my...
Oh god.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Captain Magic for the five dollars. Thanks Captain Magic.
Thanks honestly for all the laughs over the years. Here's to many more.
Hope so. Thanks a lot man.
Mad 47, thanks for the one dollar Mad.
Y'all are so kind and accepting to everything. I love it so much. Keep going man. Cheers.
I think this is a pretty great community.
I think we're pretty open and accepting to anyone.
Anyone. So. At least I think that way.
We can be a little fucking goofy. We can talk a little shit. But you know.
It's only good fun. But thank you Mad 47.
Thank you to Silker. SilkerGN for the one dollar.
Hey Germo95, would you join my Minecraft server on the Switch?
I made the game by the way.
I don't play Minecraft. It's a revolutionary game but I don't play it. Thank you.
PugNinja thanks for the one dollar. Love you Germo. Keep up the good.
I said goofs. I said goofs.
Keep up the goofs. I will try.
Thank you PugNinja for the one dollar.
David Cage official Twitch. Got a feeling that's not the real official David Cage on Twitch.
But thank you David Cage for the one dollar and fifteen cents regardless.
Hey Germo missed you while you were gone. Ever plan on playing Fallout 76 or maybe RimWorld?
Any who have a nice night.
Fallout 76 I might play. Just to fuck around for a little while.
I can't imagine I'll put that much time into Fallout 76 but maybe. We'll see.
And RimWorld maybe I'll ask Italics for some info. On some fun things to do.
Fallout 76 is trash. Yeah but it's alright.
Rick and Morty already played it.
Thank you Carrot7 for the one dollar.
I'm a university student so I don't have much time to spare but there's not a chance that I'm going to miss out on the money train.
Keep being you Germo. You're an inspiration.
Thank you all as well for inspiring me.
Thank you for the inspiration as well.
Much love to you. Thank you for the one dollar.
Thank you Jake Sunshine for the one dollar.
Germo is one of the only tubers I've been able to watch for years that hasn't said something racist.
Why would I do that? What the fuck would I do that for?
Thank you Jake Sunshine. Thanks for the one dollar.
Thank you Ixion Games for the dollar 80 turning 25. I need to hear that.
Talking about being 33. It's an age. You get older.
You'll figure it out. But thank you Ixion Games for the two dollars nearly.
Cal Darby thanks for the one dollar. I tried stretching and accidentally broke my mum's neck.
We've read that one already but that got me already.
Thank you Zan Man for the one dollar.
My 20th birthday is on the 12th and it would mean the world to me if you wished me a happy birthday.
I've been watching your stuff for years and I wish I could afford to give you more.
Happy birthday Zan Man. 1998. Have a great one on the 12th.
All of us here wish you the best. Have a great one. Thank you.
MandragoraRoot thanks for the one dollar.
It's really cool that you can be the single most funny person on the internet but be super real.
Thanks for being the one, the only, German 985.
I only know how to be one person. I don't know how to be anybody else. Thank you.
Funniest person ever confirmed by the way.
I'm not sure that that's the case but I'm glad you have fun.
Darkstar, 700,000 games thanks for the one dollar Darkstar.
It's funny you should mention getting a haircut. I've recently visited my mother and she and I were going back and forth.
She said my hair was too long and I was saying I like the length my hair is at.
Dot dot dot dot.
And then my mother looked at something off to the distance behind me.
Remember I'm facing her and she's looking towards me and she opens her mouth slowly and says oh my god.
I look behind me and there's this 25 foot spider on the wall.
Thank you Cal Darby for the one dollar. Fail RP you're ruining my immersion.
Sorry about that dude. Sorry about that fucking bro.
Ritter Rittington thanks for the one dollar.
While I'm procrastinating on school work that's weeks due by watching your stream.
I just wanted to say that you're a fantastically funny guy and deserve all the damn money coming your way.
Have a dollar you scruffy hobo. Thank you.
Thank you Ritter.
That means a lot.
Thank you Free iPod for the ten dollars. We touched upon it already but thank you.
Thank you Voyeuristic Vol for the five dollars.
Some may call me a no life nerd who's never sexually done stuff.
Jim Davis Garfield before in his entire life.
What? But as long as I can watch your streams I feel like I can tolerate this state of affairs all the best.
What are you talking about? What happened?
Thank you.
Thank you Paradox Potato for the two dollars.
If you think you can drive well you can teach Forsen how to drive.
I don't really give lessons but good luck to you Forsen.
Hopefully you can figure it out too. It's tough.
Digit Guy thanks for the two bucks.
Coffee Cheetos Chicken. Thank you.
Werewed thanks for the one dollar Werewed.
About a half a year ago I started...
About a half a year ago I started writing Lego Island in chat every stream.
I watched and brainwashed the community to make you play this masterpiece of a game.
In the end it didn't work out but thanks for trying.
The journey was fun but I will now go into Lego Island retirement.
Thank you Werewed Forty for the two dollars total here.
What about Lego Island Two?
I'm going to get a whole of a Gameboy Advance maybe.
Tom thank you Tom Sup for the one dollar.
This stream is making my day. Thank you streamer. Thank you.
Enraged Grandpa thanks for the ten bucks. No message.
Thank you.
And Dachshund thanks for one dollar and Dachshund.
I'm sorry I said you took three hours when it was actually two.
I was watching another stream before so I forgot.
Please take my money as an apology.
Apology accepted. Apology accepted.
Thank you.
Enraged Grandpa thanks for the five dollars Enraged Grandpa.
Don't spend it all in one place honey.
I won't.
I'll spend two dollars on a coffee, two dollars on a sandwich and one dollar on the casino.
On the one cent slots.
Thank you so much man.
Thank you Slavic God Memes for the ten bucks.
My mother just walked in who knew nothing about Twitch.
And I had to explain to her that I was watching a 33 year old guy playing with a children's toy while drinking wine.
Thank you for the ten bucks and hopefully you talked to her about online media.
Just say online media.
What are you watching in there Dave?
I'm watching an online media guy.
Oh okay I get it.
Thank you.
Thank you Sad Vega for the one dollar.
They just say Vohio.
Thank you so much.
Clueless Sniper thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma I'm not an oil tycoon like some of the people donating tonight.
I feel the need to kick some bits towards the money stream.
You're an amazing entertaining person and you deserve every cent you get.
Much love.
That means a lot.
One dollar or a hundred means a lot that you would even think about it in the first place.
So thank you so much.
Thank you Dr. Clay for the one dollar.
You say everyone called you an idiot last stream but here is what actually happened.
You're all idiots.
No I'm not saying that.
I'm saying what somebody said.
I was saying what somebody said.
I was quoting what somebody else said.
See?
Gentlemen.
Okay.
I'm glad you left the whole clip.
But thank you.
Thank you Dr. Clay.
Rent a cat thanks for the one dollar.
Sorry again.
Don't be sorry.
Minkcar2001 thanks for the ten dollars.
Hey Jerma I'm also drunk on wine.
Just want to say thank you for all the good times.
I hope these bits find you well.
I will put them to good use.
I will try.
Thank you so much for the ten dollars and for being here and for watching.
Thank you.
Honeychain thanks for the one dollar.
I drank an entire bottle of wine and puked all over my friend's porch.
Then he powerbombed me through the sink.
We already came to the conclusion that WTF mate.
You know what I mean?
What the heck was that?
Thank you Bet3 for your two bucks here.
Give Otto my regards.
I will.
Bet3 again gave three dollars.
FrankerZ FrankerZ.
So five dollars total.
Yes I've got a great dog.
Peter thank you P7R for the five dollars.
FrankerZ I'm having a good time.
I'm glad you had a great time and thanks for the five bucks.
Have a great one.
End Pudding thanks for the one dollar.
These bits are for Otto.
I'll give him a nice bone.
Thank you.
Chubby Funster thanks for the one dollar.
Coming in with one buck here.
Hey Jermbo thanks for always being so entertaining and so lovely.
You truly are an amazing person.
Raise love.
Would you mind flexing on Cam?
We need to see those muscles man.
No worries though if you don't want to.
Thank you.
It's time for Slime.
Thanks for the two bucks time for Slime.
I too was inspired to crack some wine during this stream and I'm already a mess.
I have no idea how you're still as composed as you are.
Bravo.
I thought the red chair was your ass.
No it's...
Thank you time for Slime.
Appreciate it.
Hope you had fun.
Thank you DadHunters for the twenty dollars.
And they say hydrate.
Alright.
I just did it.
Thank you DadHunters for the twenty bucks.
Twenty dollars from DadHunters.
Thank you.
Cosmic Moses thanks for the one dollar.
Jermbo the smell does in fact exist.
My dog smells like Fritos in old books.
But I wouldn't consider it a savory smell.
Come on buddy we're taking you to rehab.
You guys know it's a savory...
Whatever.
David Cage thanks for the one dollar.
Why didn't you tell us Otto was ten?
Jermbo he's going to die.
Thanks.
Make me love a dog who would die.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Otto was like seven.
What?
Otto was seven years old.
He's not ten.
Where did you get that info from?
I didn't say that.
Come on man.
Come on.
That's fake.
Thank you Darkstar again for the one dollar.
Jermbo versus Critical.
Jermbo versus...
Everyone wants to see this happen.
He's a good dude.
Joel's a great guy.
Critical's a great guy.
Give them nothing but the best.
Thank you.
Darkstar thank you for that one dollar.
E-Dragon thanks for the 250.
I really think you should start seeing a therapist.
These drunk fits of rage are really concerning.
And I don't think Otto should have to put up with them.
Otto's downstairs with Kim.
What are you talking about?
Thank you so much though.
Darkstar again for the one dollar.
Whoa check out these crazy streamer house antics and pranks.
I didn't fucking prank anybody.
I walked in his room.
Please.
Hey.
Alright.
Thank you Apepperoni for the one dollar.
This stream was a mess and I don't regret at all supporting it.
Jermamoon.
I had a lot of fun.
This was a ton of fun.
What a great fun time I had.
I hope you guys had fun too.
Thank you Mandragoroot for the one dollar.
Please make a Jupiter shirt.
Jupiter will be on the shirt that is being sold around Christmastime this year.
Along with the Glooman shirt.
Which will make a return.
Look for that somewhere in December.
Thank you Bet3 again for the ten dollars.
I'm thinking about getting some pet rats.
What are some good old.
What are some good names for two rats?
Wrinkle and Dinkle.
There you go.
Those are the two rat names.
Thank you so much for the ten bucks.
It's time for slime.
Thanks for one dollar.
I take it back.
You might be on my level now.
Hey asshole.
What's with the planets?
What?
Shane2567.
Hey asshole.
What's with the planets?
I don't know.
Asshole.
Why am I an asshole?
Sy and TF2.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Here are some bits.
I know it's all you want.
Jesus.
I'm sorry.
Please no.
Bet.
Get out of here.
No I'm just kidding.
Welcome dude.
Thank you so much.
Son of Jenova for the one dollar.
This is a nice frame of your yes.
This looks like an FMV fucking video game screen grab from like 1996.
Thank you son of Jenova.
Cuckoo G1.
Thanks for the one buck.
No that's ten.
That is ten dollars from Cuckoo.
They just say rip cheer one thousand.
Thank you so much for ten bucks.
Thank you the mad god 47 for the five dollars.
Hey German any chance for another directors commentary stream over your old videos I mean.
Rumble live would be cool.
Rat two.
Thanks.
Either way.
Eat some bread.
Well we'll be doing that in a few weeks after the green screen stream.
So it should be fun.
Thank you mad god for the five dollars.
Sieg's corner for the one dollar.
No message.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Also thank you butter derp for the 15 bucks.
Derma heart.
Thank you so much butter derp.
Roy on Nick Roy Roy on Oink.
That is not your name.
Rovo Rovo on Oink.
Robin Oink.
Not Roy on Oink.
Revan Oink.
Thank you for the ten dollars.
Hey German I've been watching your stream and YouTube for a while.
Figured I might as well join in on the meme.
Wishing them the best and always stayed true to being a down to earth dude.
Thank you.
Revan Oink for your ten dollars.
Appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
And I'm just me.
Can't be anybody else.
Thank you shirt for the four dollars.
Shirt one one three four bucks.
Honestly German has made my life ten times better and has gotten me through tough times.
He deserves the best.
I think you deserve the best as well.
Take care of yourself.
Much love to you.
Thank you so much for four dollars.
Maisy kit.
Thanks for one dollar.
I just think it's cool that people can get paid to do what they love like struggling with cardboard.
Thanks dude.
Thank you Bruinstar for the one dollar.
Loved your stuff from the beginning.
Glad to see you're finally getting recognition.
And you can thank all the people that decided to watch.
You know recognition means people are here.
Thank them because they're here.
So thank you.
All of you.
Tiny cactus thanks for the two dollars and fifty cents.
Yeah the twenty five dollars I spent took me less than two hours to earn.
I mean it's not too bad right.
Thank you tiny cactus.
Take a look at the bit leaderboards.
It's fucking crazy.
That truly is insane.
Look at that.
A thousand three hundred two hundred.
A hundred hundred hundred hundred.
Un-fucking-believable.
Thank you so much everybody.
He almost cried.
He got me close.
Thank you Novi for the two dollars and ten cents.
Last of my bits you earned them.
Thank you.
Thanks for even considering.
Thank you so much Novi.
Matters of Darkness gave a bunch of community subs.
What is this?
Hello everybody.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Jerma.
I'm going to start doing gameplay commentaries.
Some of you people might already know me from playing in servers.
But some of you probably don't.
This is my introduction to you guys.
I'm going to just do Team Fortress commentaries.
But I'm going to do other stuff.
Most notably I'll do Team Fortress stuff.
Because I love the game.
And it's my absolute favorite game in the world right now.
It has been...
What is that?
That's my first video?
What does that part mean?
You might know me from servers.
Like you might know me from a server.
Who the fuck was that?
Who the hell was I talking to?
That's not my video.
I didn't make the...
Did I actually say that in this video?
I didn't do this.
This is not me.
Get it off.
Hello everybody.
Introduce myself.
Right here.
My name is Jerma.
I'm going to start doing gameplay commentaries.
Some people might already know me from playing in servers.
What?
Some of you probably don't.
And this is my introduction to you guys.
What are you talking about?
I'm not just going to do Team Fortress commentaries.
I'm going to do other stuff.
Hello everybody.
Who would know me from servers?
My name is Jerma.
I'm going to start doing gameplay commentaries.
Some people might already know me from playing in servers.
Some of you probably don't.
And this is my introduction to you guys.
I'm not just going to do Team Fortress commentaries.
I'm going to do other stuff.
I'm going to be able to do the Labos drunk on stream.
But most notably I'll do Team Fortress stuff.
Because I love the game.
It's my absolute favorite game.
In the world right now.
It has been for a while.
I've been playing Team Fortress since beta.
How good was I?
And before that I played Team Fortress Classic.
Let's see.
I still have that problem.
Three fucking stabs.
Beautiful.
Letron J.
Idiot.
Getting right to the point.
I agree.
This is a big problem.
Tuber Voice?
This is me just talking.
I didn't bring the Tuber Voice out until like a year or two later.
I don't understand why that happened.
That there was something going on in the video editing process.
Kill that Heavy.
I think that Medic was about to charge an Uber or something.
But he jumps to his death.
And I don't know why I did that to tell you the truth.
He could have just ran backwards.
So I'm still on fire.
Let me pick this health kit up again.
Still on fire.
I'm not sure if it's bugged like I said.
I love Dead Ringer.
I love the Spy.
It's my most played class.
It is.
Next to that I think it's Engineer.
It is?
Still.
It's five years later.
Well that's 2012.
Well that's maybe okay.
This Sniper.
I get him as well with the Revolver.
Which this Revolver is hard to kill people with because you have to shoot them.
I think it's at least three or four times if you have 125 health or 150 health.
Like some of the classes do.
But this Scout, I think he's a Spy.
He thinks I'm a Spy.
We both go, haha.
Now watch this part right here.
I don't understand this part.
And you'll get a laugh out of this.
This is a Spy.
And we both know it.
But he just keeps on walking.
Apparently he didn't care that I bumped into him.
Or that I was a Spy.
I don't even know.
I was wrong.
I'm fucking stupid.
I was like a child.
What an idiot.
I think it was a Bot at first.
I guess there were a couple Bots on both teams but I still think he was a player.
I found out that he wasn't.
So if that was you, shame on you.
And maybe you'll get better by practicing.
So right now I'm just kind of trying to lure somebody out here.
The Soldier, I get him.
And that's what it's all about with the Spy.
Just trying to mess with people's heads.
And as you notice, I walk sideways and I walk backwards a lot.
Because if you walk right at people, as a lot of you know, you're a definite guaranteed Spy.
So I'm trying to pretend like this Scout is my enemy.
And I fool this Spy.
But it doesn't matter because I miss anyways.
And nothing happens from it though.
He didn't really come after me.
I think that's the same Spy who killed his Engineer.
I believe that's...
What was that?
Beep beep beep?
What was beep beep beep?
I think that's the same Spy who killed his Engineer.
Nothing happens from it though.
He didn't really come after me.
I think that's the same Spy who killed his Engineer.
I believe that's the same Spy that when he heard me on Cloak, he didn't really come after me.
He just kind of shot in random directions and that was it.
So I get this Medic and I get the Soldier.
I have ruined their days.
And this is, like I said, the last part of...
Keep in mind, gotta keep in mind, this is seven years ago.
Gold Rush, I started a little late.
The first video I've ever made. Ever.
But it's okay because this is a pretty good run.
And I'm still on fire.
Nice little jumping, little side-stab on that Medic.
And yeah, I had to bring up the Dead Ringer because there's no way I would have survived that at all.
And you were 25.
That doesn't, but whatever.
It doesn't matter how old you are.
Which is the best part about the Dead Ringer because if you had a regular invisibility watch, half of these situations you'd be dead.
I'd say probably more than half.
So I try to tele-frag this Engineer and it doesn't really go so well because he's obviously not in the way.
He actually hits me with his wrench and he doesn't kill me.
I think I was over you. I think he critted me, actually, to tell you the truth.
Somebody wrote, I wasn't even alive seven years ago.
See, right now I'm in no man's land because there's just so many people around and this Heavy knows it, so I'm gonna go down.
And everyone doesn't really hear it, but I just kind of freak out.
There's too many people for me to even really do anything significant.
But hey, I tried and that's when I died.
So look, I'm still on fire.
I can't get over it.
I'm still on fire. I've yet to be put out.
And it wasn't like this when I was playing, by the way.
Only when I saved the video.
So I guess this is some kind of bug with demo files where it does this.
And it really is kind of annoying and hopefully it doesn't do this more often.
If you guys do commentaries, if you guys can give me some tips.
If you guys do?
Hold on, I'm asking for tips.
On how to make commentaries.
Nobody was doing them.
There's like nine people making these.
Where it does this and it really is kind of annoying and hopefully it doesn't do this more often.
If you guys do commentaries, if you guys can give me some tips on what exactly could be going on here.
There was probably seven other Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentators in 2011.
Yeah, but not gonna let it ruin my day.
It actually subsides right here.
I had to cut.
I think something crashed.
But yeah, it's gone now.
Wait, hold on. What do I have to do?
I'm not gonna let it ruin my day.
If you guys can give me some tips.
I cut because it crashed?
What exactly could be going on here, I have no idea.
I'm not gonna let it ruin my day.
It actually subsides right here.
I had to cut.
Why did I cut?
I think something crashed.
That's a lie. What do you mean a cut?
I had to cut.
Where?
Do commentaries if you guys can give me some tips on what exactly could be going on here.
I have no idea.
I'm not gonna let it ruin my day.
It actually subsides right here.
I had to cut.
I think something crashed.
Something crashed?
Yeah, it's gone now.
This is still the same life.
It's still the same life, I guess.
So I take the hit from the heavy, bring out the dead ringer, go back to the little spot here.
This is a great place to go.
If you don't go here, you should go here every time.
Go there every time.
But that other soldier is not gonna have any of that.
If you're using the dead ringer, that's a really good place to go.
Because nobody...
You can see my steam overlay.
Behind all the sound of the deep look of the dead ringer is very silent.
So where are the last 10 seconds?
This person is logging into steam.
We are winning this, and obviously I come out here to demoralize the other team.
And it was a pretty good run.
That was pretty good.
If you did, let me know.
Look at that, look at that.
Who's number one right there?
That's Jerma.
Give me a comment, let me know if you want to see something else.
Or if you guys want to see more.
I plan on doing it at least a little bit to try and, you know, try and get into it.
But thanks for watching, and hopefully you guys enjoyed.
I'll see you later.
That was the first video I've ever made.
See you all in the next video.
I don't even know where we were.
That video sucked.
How many viewers did Jerma get in his first stream?
Um, like Twitch or YouTube?
When I started, I had an established group of people when I first streamed on Twitch.
I think my first ever stream was a birthday stream.
It was like 215 people.
And it was like, holy shit, I have like an audience that's coming over to Twitch!
I think it was like 207 people.
And it was a big deal.
It was.
It was like a birthday stream.
That's still really good.
Yeah, no, it was great.
200 fucking people are a lot of people.
So, 2-3, 400 people, like that's what I was starting with.
That's still a lot of people.
If you put 200 people in a room, you've got a giant party.
So, yeah, no.
It's been great. I love it.
Let's get back to what we were doing.
Now I have more than 5 times that.
I don't look at it that way though.
200, 5,000, 10,400, doesn't matter.
I'm gonna still do the things that I'm gonna do.
But, yeah, whoever linked that, thank you.
We are getting closer to the end here.
Thank you so much to Matters of Darkness, 15 bucks.
Thank you.
Somebody wrote, Jerma's an inspiration.
I don't know if you get inspiration from the stuff that I do and the stuff that you see here.
Good, I'm glad.
I'm glad you can do something from it.
Have fun.
Glad you can make something from it.
Cry, cry, cry, cry.
But for real, thank you for the huge amount of money tonight, dude.
Thank you so much.
Green Templar, thanks for the 4 dollars.
No message, thank you.
Shirt, thanks for the dollar and 10 cents.
Shirt 113.
Manfun, thanks for the one dollar.
Appreciate it.
SaintMP, thanks for the one dollar.
Littlesmoop, thanks for the one dollar.
No messages here, just people kind of throwing money into the pot here and it's very much appreciated.
Thank you, guys.
Butterderp, thanks for the 15 bucks.
Jeremy, I don't leave your stream saying that was fun.
I leave your stream saying no, please don't leave.
We touched upon this earlier.
But again, Butterderp, thank you so much.
I'm glad you can have a good fucking time.
AmnesiaStreamer.
Should have recommended that I cry on the green screen.
I probably will.
Jerma, are you a US citizen?
Yeah, yes.
I think, I think so.
Thank you, though.
Thank you to Koalav3Jance.
KoalavGance.
I'm saying your name so wrong, I'm sorry, but thank you.
Thanks for the bits there, dude.
Thank you, DeuceTheGamer.
Again, we gotta touch upon this.
This is the most amount of money that anyone has ever given me during one stream.
A thousand fucking dollars.
Absolutely fucking insane amount of money.
Thank you.
DeuceTheGamer, that means a lot.
Thank you so much, dude.
That's the most fucking money ever.
Watch your language, I'm sorry.
Thank you Carrot for the five dollars.
There's a stream where we bullied Jerma by throwing money at him until he cried.
Well worth it for the greatest funny man on Twitch.
I know we all appreciate how hard you worked, so please.
To please us, greedy gremlins sitting at home.
Much love.
Thank you, Carrot.
I don't think you guys are greedy at all.
GarfieldTheMondayKillit, there's Garfield.
Thank you, Garfield, for the one dollar.
Ahoy there, landlubbers.
Ahoy in that. Come on, Jerma, burn that fat.
I'm glad you found out I'm interning at Nintendo.
They wanted to use my writing skills for Garfographs in their game.
Unfortunately, the Labo branch of the company was closed down.
I'm emptying out my office as we speak.
Yeah, they gave an office to an intern.
Hey, Jerma, when you lie in bed and think how the stream was possible,
imagine Garfield fishing for trout in Alaska and donating trout bits.
Thank you.
Thank you, Garfield.
Hopefully Nintendo brings you back.
Thank you, WinzRind, for the five dollars.
Hey, Jerma, I have this relevant image.
Okay, why did you send a check for ten thousand dollars to Jerma985?
I like their product.
I wanted them to have a little walking around money.
Here is the image.
Thank you.
Thank you, WinzRind.
Walking around money.
But thanks to the five bucks, dude.
Thank you, Tantyrotenna, for the one dollar.
Sniff update, please.
Sniff update.
What does that mean?
Sniff update?
I don't understand.
Oh, the dog smell.
Yeah, whatever.
Thank you.
Funny and relatable username for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, here's a dollar to fuel your crippling chicken nugget addiction.
We touched upon it earlier, but thank you.
Devakitty, thanks for the one dollar, Devakitty.
Just add this to the money pile, Jerma.
On another note, I've been feeling awful about how long it has taken for me to get HRT.
But one of my last appointments with my clinician is in early December,
and you helped me hold myself from falling apart in the last eight years.
I've had to endure dysphoria, and for that I am sincerely grateful.
So wish me luck in getting myself some tit-tax.
We all love you, Jerma, transgender pride.
Thank you so much, Devakitty.
I will tell you, like I've said this before a thousand times,
be the person that you are the most comfortable being.
Whatever you're the most comfortable being, whoever you are,
much love to you, for real.
Whoever, wherever, whenever.
I've said it before, but I will reiterate it again.
Thank you so much.
Best of luck to you.
And we move on to Tiny.
Thank you, Tiny, 840 for the 10 bucks.
I can't give nearly as much as some people here.
We touched upon this before.
Show my appreciation for what you do for all of us.
Thank you.
Thank you, Tiny.
Thank you for everything.
Dubski, dude, thanks for the one dollar.
Jerma, you are the worst influence on my life.
Holy shit.
This got different.
This got like a little weird.
I thought it was going to be like, oh, thanks.
Nope.
Not this one.
Jerma, you're the worst influence on my life.
Your stream has made me extremely paranoid of people who just want to steal my expensive rifle.
And you convinced me to hijack a train and fill it with corpses.
Worst of all, I said ha ha pee pee poo poo to my own mother.
Arrest this person.
Arrest this streamer.
There's so many like, nice.
Oh, thank you so much.
And then, oh, you're the worst.
Oh, you guys are fucking hilarious.
Thank you, Dubski.
Sorry to hear about that.
ACDC, freak, thanks for the bits.
It's not much, but you're my favorite person on Twitch.
Thank you.
Devakitty, thanks for the one dollar.
Again, thank you, Devakitty.
Oh yeah, I also just finished a marathon-length domination-only game of Civilization V,
so just call me a regular fucking pro gamer.
How long is that?
How long does that take?
That's a long time.
A marathon-length domination-only game.
Is that like, that's actually so long.
How long?
That's a lot.
Maybe like 50 hours?
Holy shit.
At least an hour.
Well, congratulations on that.
Civ 5.
Never played it.
I respect it, though.
Rocketfinger, thanks for the six dollars and 50 cents.
Jerma Hart, no message.
Thank you, but just Jerma Hart.
Right back at you.
Thank you, JupaCross, for the 95 cents.
One dollar, round it up there.
Jerma, we all love you.
You lack in height.
You make up with personality.
You're an inspiration, proving that even short men can get a girlfriend.
And I rounded you 95 cents up to a dollar.
And that's what I said.
And that's what you said.
All right, great.
Should have just rounded it down.
Thanks for the 95 cents.
Appreciate it, JupaCross.
Appreciate that, dude.
Thank you.
And yes, it's true.
It doesn't matter.
Everyone will find somebody.
You are correct.
Thank you, Sticks Renegade, for the two dollars and 76 cents.
Here's your thousand dollars of Zimbabwe dollars.
Thank you, Sticks.
Welcome back.
Much love to you, dude.
Round it down like it's height.
Busy Work, thanks for the three bucks, Busy Work.
Grab that auto, owes you money.
Thanks for the three bucks, Busy Work.
Appreciate that.
Dot Shaft, thanks for the 10 bucks, Dot Shaft.
Just cry so we can go to bed.
It was close.
Almost got me.
But I did start thinking about it.
And it was making me really, really emotional.
But I was good.
I had a couple more glasses of wine, and I was all set.
Thank you, though, Dot Shaft, for the 10, 10 dollars.
Flying Sombrero, thanks for the one dollar.
Everyone has given bits tonight, so here's my contribution.
I'm hoping you do a germa ultimate rumble when the new Smash Brothers comes out.
Thanks for the streams.
You'll always be our favorite tiny man.
Five eight.
I mean, who's counting, right?
Five foot eight.
Five foot eight inches.
Five feet, and then eight inches after five feet.
Five eight.
Five seven, but five eight with shoes on.
Let me correct that.
Thank you.
Thank you, Onyx Blaze, for the three bucks.
Pogchamp, Pogchamp.
Thank you, Pogchamp.
Well, thank you, Onyx Blaze, for your Pogchamps, for the three bucks.
Onyx Blaze again, for the two dollars.
Thanos car.
Some meme, I guess.
Digit Guy, thanks for the one dollar.
I found this in my couch cushions.
Am I cool yet?
Also, chug that.
I believe I did.
Thank you.
For another dollar, Digit Guy, I'm the guy in the car.
I don't know what that means.
I'm the guy in the car.
Thanks.
Sieg's Corner, thanks for the one dollar.
I'm the guy next to the guy in the car.
We both drive.
All right.
Thank you, Sieg's Corner and Digit Guy.
Creepy Ghost Sales, thanks for one dollar.
I need to get in on this.
Oh, the loud car that drove by.
Right, okay.
That makes sense.
Thank you, Creepy Ghost Sales.
Thank you to a ton of people who gave 50 cents.
A bunch of you in a row.
Thank you, all of you.
Swiggity Dank, thanks for the 15 bucks, Swiggity Dank.
Let's get those bits.
Okay.
YouTuber for five years have video from seven years ago.
Well, I haven't updated my biography on Twitch in two years, so that makes sense.
Swiggity Dank, thanks for 15 dollars, dude.
Let's get those bits.
Well, you brought a bunch of them, so thank you.
Shimmy Sham, thanks for two bucks.
I want to see Italics's face.
Sorry, you can't see his face.
He is faceless tonight.
More, a bunch of 50 cents coming in from a ton of people.
Thank you guys so much.
Ton of gifted fucking subs.
Thank you, Trotter, for the one dollar.
Get that bread, my gamer.
And Germanose, wipe German heart.
Your Twitch bio is when you only had five emotes.
Yeah, but those are like the five good ones.
Actually, there's like at least 10 more that I would say are good.
Good ones.
I have like 15 great emotes now.
Thank you, Trotter, though.
The one dollar.
Get that bread.
I won't for now.
Star Wolf Ken.
Thank you, Star Wolf Ken, for the one dollar.
For the one dollar.
Thank you, German heart.
No message.
Thank you.
No comment.
34 gave one dollar.
I suck.
I'm bored when I do that.
Kappa.
You suck on Tootsie Rolls.
Thank you for that.
No comment.
34.
Thank you.
It is Kat.
Thanks for the bits.
Thank you, Star Wolf Ken, for the one dollar.
Is this a streamer who cried on stream?
I didn't.
I did not.
Thank you, FussyFuck, for the one dollar.
Thank you, WinzRyant, for the three bucks.
Your streams are getting me through fall classes while I have a chronic sinus infection,
so you're priceless.
Keep up the good times.
Thank you, WinzRyant, for the three bucks.
Good luck on your fall classes.
Hopefully you get an A- on all of them.
Thank you.
The long egg.
Thanks for one dollar.
Very emotional stream.
I almost cried myself.
Maybe it's from painkillers from my surgery, but you demand.
Hopefully your surgery went well.
Hopefully you're recovering, and hopefully you get stronger every day.
Thank you so much.
The long egg.
He used to play the A- thing before B+.
You got to wish everybody for a B+.
Double 11.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Double D. Double 11.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Dermacraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player.
I said what you wanted me to do.
DivUSP, thanks for the 10 bucks.
I'm running out of ad bits, but fuck it.
Laughing my ass off.
Thank you, DivUSP, for your multiple contributions.
10 bucks.
10 bucks here.
Tons of money over the course of the last at least few months.
Thanks a lot, man.
Zareth, thanks for five dollars, Zareth.
I've been following you for a few years, and you never failed to make my days better.
Thank you for all you've done.
Thank you for the five dollars, and thanks for being here.
Ten dollars out of ads.
That is a lot.
TwoBit, thank you TwoBit for the three bucks.
Jerma, you deserve every bit you get.
I wish I could give more because of every year since I found you on YouTube seven years ago.
Thank you, and here's to many more.
I'm going to go as long as I can.
Thank you, TwoBit for the three bucks.
Truna, thank you Truna for the ten dollars.
Ten bucks from Truna.
Hey dude, I don't really know how Twitch works as I always watch you on YouTube,
but I just wanted to say how much I appreciate what you do.
You make me cry laughing more times than I can count,
and you never fail to cheer me up.
Love you, dude.
Thank you, Truna.
Add yourself to the list of people that have just given such immense support over the years,
and thank you so much for watching on YouTube.
It means a lot.
That's fucking incredible.
Thank you.
I'm glad you enjoy it.
I'm glad you're having fun.
Welcome to Twitch, by the way.
If you're not a Twitch viewer, welcome to Twitch.
No comment.
Thanks for the one dollar, no comment.
One dollar and nine cents.
They say this is just all my money, and well actually it's two dollars and ten cents.
They say I'm gay, and this is all my money.
Pride one ten, or pride two ten, actually.
Thank you so much, no comment.
Thanks for the two bucks.
Appreciate that.
Wish you the best.
Thank you, pop them tarts.
I'd give so much more if I could.
You're generally a nice guy, and you deserve the world.
Maybe a small piece of the world.
Not all of it, though.
It's too much.
Nobody wants that much.
It's too much world.
That's too much world to have, you know what I mean?
Sapping my bin yacht.
Thanks for the 95 cents.
Rounding it up to a dollar.
What we're doing tonight here.
That's what we're doing.
Hey, Jerma, thanks for streaming.
Ever since I found you a while ago through a certain droney, you've brightened up my days.
Here's a hundred bits for every time you've made me laugh and smile.
Here's a hundred bits for every time you've made me laugh.
This is 95.
How many?
So I've only made you smile once.
Oh, not even.
95.
Oh, man.
That's good.
Well, Vinny is a great fucking guy.
So I'm happy you even came over here from Vinny's channel.
He's a fucking fantastic streamer.
And he is a friend.
So it's great, dude.
Thank you to Brand The Mans for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, the work you do here on Twitch is truly amazing, and your streams are worth every penny.
Don't ever doubt yourself of the value of the streams.
We love you.
Thank you, Brand The Man.
Really appreciate that.
Thanks for the kind words.
I am a Ribbit.
Thanks for one dollar.
No message.
Elizabeth.
Thanks for one dollar.
Did you see Vinny talking about how you landed in Vegas?
Yeah.
I was in his dryer.
We talked about his dryer and how, you know, he puts some raw meat in there.
It's in the vod somewhere.
He was good to me for a little while.
I screamed a lot, but he would be like, stop screaming.
And I'd be like, OK, jeez.
It hurts.
You turn the dryer on.
But thank you, Zazasoft, for the one dollar.
I don't have big bits or good joke to contribute.
I'm just looking forward to the future of the stream.
Don't worry about giving me huge amounts of money.
Your viewership is enough.
And I truly mean that.
So thank you, Zazasoft, for the one dollar.
And your body, your eyes here, right?
Like you're sitting there.
You're watching.
That's incredibly important.
It means a lot.
He was worried about the jokes.
Wait, what?
No, no.
Not your body.
No.
I mean like you sitting down.
Hey, Darkstar.
Thanks for the one dollar, Darkstar.
My siblings and I have a tradition of making silly short films every Christmas.
And this year we're planning on making a western.
This may seem random, but what would a good kryptonite for an army of a hundred grizzly bears be?
A steak.
Just like a pound of ground beef.
They would just go after it.
Honey?
No, honey.
That's Winnie the Pooh.
One pound of ground beef, and it'll be a fucking nightmare.
Rat poison?
Holy shit.
Thank you High Fire Spirit for the one dollar.
Neat.
I'm a sub now.
Welcome to the sub team.
We don't really have a team or anything, but welcome.
Regardless.
Where are we at here?
Getting to the end here.
Somebody said, carrot seven.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Shut up and watch.
This is your origin story.
What the hell is this?
I can't click it.
There we go.
Please join a movement of six million Americans to impeach Donald Trump.
This is not my origin story.
This is the most corrupt president.
This is an ad.
Hold on.
Hello, everybody.
My name is Hill Joe Golem.
I'm Jeremy's grandfather.
And today we're going to play Insane Aquarium.
It's the best game you can ever buy.
This is my origin story.
I don't really play.
I just like bumped the keyboard.
Hello, everybody.
My name is your origin story.
Oh, like it.
Here's the link.
This is the fucking first grandpa video.
There you go.
Oh, my God.
My fucking head is in the video.
Hello, everybody.
Let's watch it.
Fine.
Fuck it.
Oh, we need to work together to impeach.
Hey, Jeremy, here's your origin story.
Oh, what in the name of God is this person talking about?
All right.
Let's watch it.
Hello, everybody.
My name is Hill Joe Golem.
I'm Jeremy's grandfather.
And today we're going to play Insane Aquarium.
The deluxe mode.
It's the best game you can ever buy.
And it's loading it right now.
Why are we picking up my first three videos I've ever made?
I don't really play video games.
They hurt my brain.
And I wish this noise.
We got to click here to play.
I play casual games because I'm an idiot.
I'm just.
OK, what am I doing here?
I want to do challenge mode because I know I want a new game.
New fucking game.
OK, let's try take number three because I still can't beat it.
I like to use the crab and I like to use the other crab.
And I like to use the floating crab.
Well, you know, to get the money in the beginning, you know.
OK, so it starts.
You click to feed these little fish face fucks.
And then, you know, they drop the dog shit.
And you click and you get money.
Two frames a second.
And you click again and you get more money.
And then my game is lagging really badly right now.
Click that money right there.
The whole point of this, by the way, folks, is you want to try and get as much money.
You can pay for your daughter's wedding.
At least that's what I pretend it is.
OK, so we got four fishes here.
Do you think people are going to watch it?
And I got my little friend Steve over here.
I think that's his name.
So the whole point is you want to give these guys delicious worm cakes.
And hold on a minute.
I have to diarrhea.
What?
OK.
I'm back from diarrhea.
I got a big fishy in diarrhea.
Oh, fuck.
Somebody fucking died.
And I got an alien.
Oh, this is bad.
You're going to shoot these fucking aliens.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Don't worry, everybody.
I got a fucking diamond.
That means we can buy extra food.
$315.
Are you fucking kidding me?
$318 for food?
Do I lose?
Oh, you got to be shitting me.
Can you hear my dog?
So I'm doing pretty well here.
I got a big fish here.
Like I told you.
Like I told you before, I'm making lots of cash.
I'm going to upgrade my food quality.
Oh, shit.
Got to pick that up.
And the silver ones, too.
Remember, silver's worth something to him.
I don't know what this fucking face is for.
I don't know who the guppy is.
Guppy cruncher.
Oh, God.
Why did you think this was a good idea to upload?
I don't know.
What the fuck?
Just a second.
What is this?
This game is a bunch of bullshit.
Oh, my.
You got it.
Whatever.
You know, I'm returning this game.
I'm going to return this game today.
And oh, hello there, Suzy.
What's your name?
Never seen you.
What was I just saying about?
Oh, yeah.
I think I was saying I was going to play challenge mode.
And I need you to beat tank three, because I didn't beat tank three yet, OK?
I need to pick crab and other crab and this crab.
Do I do it again?
The point of this game is you want to feed these fishes and they collect the dog food.
Do I do the whole video again?
The whole point is you want to try and feed them.
And like I do, you've got to be careful because aliens come up.
What is it?
I'm playing a fucking video game.
I don't care.
You can go to hell.
OK.
I'll be up for dinner in a minute.
Like I was saying, oops, all of your fish have died.
Is that it?
You can hear the microphone.
You can hear the microphone get bumped.
What a shit video.
That was my third video I ever made.
I think I was testing.
Here's the story behind that video.
I was testing to see if fraps.
Remember the not DX story, not OBS.
Fraps could capture a game like that.
So just test.
Anyways, where were we here?
We were.
We reached me and beached.
That fucking, I really thought that's what you linked me.
And I was like, what?
Oh, my God.
That's so fucking funny.
Star killer.
Thank you, star killer, for the $1.
I made this video the night you left and people said to show it to you.
Let's see.
I'll stand in my way.
Here we go.
Let us see.
I'm holding away.
I've got to get it.
Is near.
And so I face hurting.
My friend.
I'll say it clear.
I'll state my case.
It's a lot of money.
Of which I'm certain.
I've lived it's full.
I've traveled each and every highway.
But more.
Much more than this.
I missed that keyboard.
It was a great keyboard.
Too few to mention.
What I had to do.
And saw it through.
Without exception.
Each charted course.
Each careful step.
Belong.
What the fuck was I doing?
This is my.
As they'll show you.
When I beat off.
Kachoo.
Alright this is the video's end here.
Because that was.
Oh I got it.
Hahaha.
That was great.
Thank you Starkiller2010.
For that wonderful video.
Thank you.
Goodbye old house.
Goodbye old Massachusetts.
Welcome to Las Vegas.
Oh is your twitch just frozen?
It shouldn't be.
Give us a link.
Here is the link to that video.
I'm leaving Las Vegas.
That's true.
Thank you to Darkstar for the $1.
I think it's time to put your best baby voice.
And do an AFV style stream for your old YouTube videos.
Not for a while.
Maybe someday.
Butterderp thanks to the $1 for your information.
I wanted to make sure that it was me.
Who recommended you play The Sims 4.
Should I play The Sims? It was me.
Me. Me.
Well thank you Butterderp. That was a lot of fun.
The streams were great.
Tora T. Tora T. Thanks for the $1. They say seems good.
Tora gave an absolute
shitload of community subs.
Thank you so much Tora.
You gave a huge amount.
So thank you.
It was a crazy, crazy, crazy fucking amount.
Thank you. So much.
Dr. Clay thank you for the $1.
Do you think every time you pick up auto you're playing
grab that auto.
Well grab that auto not grab that auto.
Different words. Different scenarios.
Wrong screen bud.
There it is.
Thank you bet3 for the $10.
Thanks for everything Jerma. We all appreciate you so much.
Thank you bet3 for your massive contributions.
Thank you guys.
Deva Kitty thanks for the $1.
I just remembered you made a Nidhogg video
years ago where you played the game
and me and my girlfriend have had a lot of
frantic fun playing the sequel.
So I can very much recommend you play it
with someone like Italics
or indeed in the spirit of
Lethal League reunion with Star.
Me and Star did play Lethal League and
Nidhogg 2 does exist.
It's true. Give it a look.
Thank you. Thank you
Synthesis Pandabot
for the $1. I just remembered you made a Nidhogg
video. Wrong.
Wrong. Hey Jerma
what's going on? It's me Garfield's brother
Habba Dabba Dabba Dabba
at Garfield's brother's killer
just letting you know how cool this stream today was
to love, laugh, and live.
Fuck is happening.
You're a sex god or something.
What? What? What?
Thank you Synthesis Pandabot for the
$1. Thank you
Synthesis Pandabot for the $1 again.
It's me Jerma Guy at Jerma95
I'm here to tell you you'll
shoot your eye out kid.
Sans Undertale. Have a good night
funny man. And I'm the
drunk one. Who is this crazy guy?
Thank you Pandabot.
Double D thanks for the $1. Hey Jerma
I've been watching this stream in the hospital. You've been keeping
me happy during this hard time. Don't worry
I'm fine. Just had a small incident when I tripped
and I fell into my walk-in oven
and got locked in for an undetermined
amount of minutes. Okay.
Thanks for the $2. Oop, misspelled Jerma Heart
in the last bit. Hope that didn't confuse you.
Thanks for the
$2 though dude. Synthesis
Pandabot again for the $1.
I want to hear a secret. I don't
exist. I don't really exist.
Well Synthesis Pandabot
you do exist. Cause somebody
had to write that so it was you. It had
to have been. Who else could it have been?
Synthesis Pandabot
again for a dollar.
They say hey there Delilah. What's
it like in New York City? I'm a thousand miles
away but girl tonight you look so pretty. You
yes you do time square. Can't shine
as bright as you I swear.
Let's hear it say hey Delilah. The song is the whole
song. Okay. Thank you
for the $1. For like the $5 here
Synthesis Pandabot.
I appreciate it. And
at the very end Sidwo
for the $10 Sidwo
Hey Jermbo this is my first time sharing it on
Twitch. Keep up the amazing streams.
Thanks for streaming so late.
I'm a real night owl so I always miss most of your
streams. Always happy to join in the last few minutes
though. As it is a oh
my computer's turning off. Is my computer turning off?
No I'm good.
The front monitor turned off. That was weird.
Anyways happy to join in the last few minutes
though as it is always the most chill.
Thank you so much Sidwo for the
$10 here. And
let's run the credits. That's it
for the bits. Huge amount
there's auto. Huge amount of money tonight
guys. Words cannot even fucking
express and I don't even know how fast this is going to be.
Take a look at this shit.
Take a look at that. Good luck.
Un-fucking-believable.
There had to have been 600 subs
tonight. Vroom, vroom.
Let me take this opportunity to thank
all you guys
one last time.
I will see you on today is
technically let's see it's been
holy shit. It's 3am
pacific. It's time to go right?
Sunday, Monday. I will see you
guys on Tuesday the 13th.
We will vote for a
couple of specific actions for the green screen. The green
screen will be on Thursday. So I will
see you guys again on
Tuesday the 13th.
Auto, what
do you want auto?
He's been out, he's eaten. I think he's just bored.
Big stream delay.
Yeah, hi from the east coast.
I never streamed till
3am, 4am before.
I don't even know how many subs there were.
Let me look at a thing here.
This is just crazy. Yeah.
31,
2, 3.
Yeah, it was somewhere around 500 or 600 subscriptions
tonight. That's
crazy. What time did the
10 hour monster rancher 2 end?
I don't think it was 3 o'clock in the morning.
500 subs
tonight. And then so
much in bits.
Thousands of dollars. Thousands of dollars
tonight. Thousands.
I can't even fucking comprehend it.
That's, thank
you everybody. Words cannot describe
my gratitude so thank you.
Yeah, I guess
I'll buy a Vive, you know.
I'm from Serbia.
Hello, it's 9am. Well, good morning
in Serbia. We do have a couple more
bits that came in. Burgaby with one
dollar. They said I hate you.
I respect your opinion. I'm just
sad that that's what it is.
Thank you.
Double D, thanks for the one dollar. Double D
11. How is chat's day going?
Hopefully pretty good. But I
had a lot of fun tonight. See you guys in
a couple of days. There were your
500 fucking hundred subscriptions.
My god.
Good night. Good luck to you all.
See you Tuesday.
Get some rest. Enjoy the rest
of your weekend. And thank you
Elizabeth for the one dollar and Burgaby for the
one dollar. And Pug Ninja
for the one dollar. Thank you.
Have a great night. See you soon.
Real soon.