What is happening guys, it is Jerma bringing you a complete fucking roll video as a heavy.
I'm using the default minigun, the sandwich, and the gloves are running urgently.
And I left it with a little bit of setup time so I could just say a couple things to you guys.
I want to thank most of the subscribers, I think there's 12 of you now that have subscribed to me in the very beginning of this run I'm doing here.
It really means a lot to me, I thank you guys a lot from the bottom of my heart.
And I'll be doing probably some type of giveaway, some type of subscription giveaway for people or something like that.
Something to show my gratitude and get more people to come to the channel and have a little bit more of an advertising thing.
But it's three seconds left, this is a complete roll.
I'm not going to really give too much gameplay commentary because it's a complete roll, we destroy this team with no regard.
I get ubered right out of the gate, there's a sentry on the right, kill the sentry, kill the engineer.
Kill this guy over here, no actually I don't kill anybody, we get on the cart.
And like I said in a video before, rolling people is stupid, I hate it.
I wish it would never happen, but it does.
This sentry gun is distracted by something over on the left, I end up taking it out very very easily.
Keep moving up here, there's a demo man I think up there.
Get rid of this engineer's equipment because that's just a slap in the face.
Get back on the cart.
We are absolutely rolling to the point.
This scout, I didn't think I was going to kill him, he was running around like a little bunny.
Kill him anyways.
And we are still rolling.
These type of games just annoy me.
Well it's hard to say that when I'm playing cart heavy.
That pyro just disappeared by the way.
He jumped up and sprayed everybody.
And then was launched 100 feet in the air and he was just gone from there.
This spy backstabbed somebody on my team, I kill him.
Still on the cart, we are at the second point.
And this is a big tip for you guys right here.
When you cap this point, watch what I do.
I don't wait for the bridge to come up like everybody does.
You don't have to wait for that bridge to come up.
Just run around the side like I'm doing here.
And you'll get people off guard coming through this house like I get this medic off guard.
I'm not sure I actually kill him, but I get this sentry off guard.
There's pretty much this whole team over here off guard.
I think I'm going to die, I run back, throw my sandwich in the ground.
But the point is, use that little route on the left.
You don't have to wait for the bridge just sitting there waiting like 30 seconds for the bridge to come up.
You don't have to do that.
I get ubered again, come up here, there's another sentry over here.
This makes it four I think for me of kills for me.
Take out the engineer, take out the heavy.
And people start to leave the cart at this point.
Nobody's pushing the cart.
Everyone's kind of just sitting back and as you can see the cart just has one or two people on it.
And I believe I say over Mike, I say something like,
Can we push the cart?
What are we doing? Let's just get it over with.
So we all get on it.
And this is an absolute roll like I said.
It's a very quick gameplay.
But if this happens, if you see this happen in the server,
Please switch to the other team.
If you're number one, number two on the server,
Switch to the other team. Don't be a dick.
Switch to the other team, make it fun for everybody.
There's no reason to do this at all, ever.
But anyways, thank you guys, all the subscribers again.
I appreciate all you guys do. Thank you so much.
I'm out.