Hey, why is everybody still saying late? I don't understand that anymore. I've had a window between
three and four o'clock pacific for like six months. What are you guys talking about? I'm pretty damn
early. You never had a goddamn guy come to your house in a window before?
Um, somebody like a worker coming to your house in a window. No, I'm talking, okay, a guy
comes to your house because you asked him to come there because he's doing a job and he gave you a
window of when he will arrive. There you go. All right, I'm here. I have to kneel down because I
have to, I don't have a chair in here right now because as you probably saw by the title of the
stream and by the latest tweet, we're doing connect. That's right. I have way too many
of these games. It was a mistake to buy this many. Half of these I don't think have seen.
Well, okay, let's put it this way. The one that I'm about to start with, I don't think has seen
total playtime across the entire globe from every purchase, probably more than 16 hours of time that
anyone has ever spent in this game across the whole globe. I can't, I don't know. I don't
understand who would, maybe we are going to account for like 30% of this game's total global playtime.
Hope you're ready. It's not Forza. Why would I, I'm not going to play Forza right now.
Is Forza for connect? Because should I have gotten Forza instead of the biggest loser
weight loss game? I don't, what do you think?
We're talking fucking weight loss today. I'm in my gear. I'm ready to work out.
This stream is going to probably be like fucking two hours because you all know how much stamina I got.
I warmed up before. I did a little bit of like stretches and setups and stuff. I'm ready.
I'm ready for at least play online. You can't play this game online. No camera? Oh there you go.
Absolutely there's a camera. It's going on. Not yet though. It's only been like a minute.
Just waiting. I just did a tweet. I got a cool setup this time. So those of you that watched the
movies one from a few days ago with the Xbox live vision camera. No, no, no, no. Today.
Take a look at this. Today I've got something interesting here. It must have been sad for a
minute there. I got something interesting here. Wireless Bluetooth setup. Wireless Bluetooth setup
from here. No wires. Check that out. No wires. Nothing on me at all.
Let me see. I got a Bluetooth setup over here. I mean it's like in Rome.
It's not like ah get that off. No, no, no. I'm good. It's connected. I had no way to put it.
I was going to get a haircut yesterday but I didn't do it so the hair stays. Wait how does this look?
I really don't want to turn this on because this music is fucking terrible but
it's on. Check this out. Yeah that's right. It's been calibrated I think.
Okay yeah it's been calibrated. Oh I gotta hold on. I gotta flip my because if I go like this.
Yeah I gotta flip. I gotta flip myself because it's pulling me the other way.
Hold on. We're gonna we're gonna mirror this because now there you go. All right so uh put
the fat suit on. I'm not gonna put the fat suit on for this. Guys we don't get time to fuck around.
You understand? I don't have time to fuck around okay? I knew that was gonna fucking happen.
It's all right. They're fine over there. I got 40. We got 40 games for the Kinect. It's gonna take
us like six weeks to do this. I just spit all over you. This was four grand. There's a lie.
Red. I'm stalling. It's time to go. This was not four grand. That's a lie. All right here we go.
You ready? It's time. Is this what you do? No. All right here we go. This is the bit. This is
the worst one to start with but I have to get rid of this one quick. By the way we have a rule here
if you've never been here before. Every single one of these games I have to play for at least
30 minutes. What time is it right now? Seven minutes. Start the timer now. Biggest loser.
Here we go. Wireless Bluetooth setup. I have to like get it like to like calibrate it. Okay.
Enter your weight. Use the up and down arrow to change your weight.
No no no that's not that. Are you ready to have fun and get real results?
I'm ready. This is so difficult. All right I'm like 154. Hey uh take the CD out of the tray.
You don't have to fucking be here. Okay let's go. Imagine being 154 pounds and like getting
this game. Be like you know I've got I gotta drop like 40. Choose a personalized program if
you want a custom fitness program tailored to your body and your personal strengths and weaknesses.
Creating your program will begin to test the gauge of your current fitness.
What'd you do? No no no no I want to do the custom one like the like the Wii Fit one.
Personalized program if we're going to test my current fitness level. Sounds good. 30 minute
hey that's just as much time for me to fucking uninstall the game. Fitness test is going to find
your current fitness level. Just follow Bob Harper as he leads you through a series of exercises.
If it gets too hard for you the test will end and we'll look at your results. Okay good luck.
Thanks for giving me that time. Here we go. Fitness test starting now. I'm going to stretch
my spine out. Here's a quick little technique for those who don't know. If you want to stretch
your spine out go on your tip toes real fast. Okay I elongated my body. Now we're going to do
a short fitness test with you to find out your current fitness level. You can end the test at
any time. Take it away Bob. We'll start with a light warm-up exercise but things will get
progressively harder. Remember that you can stop at any time if things get too difficult.
The test will end automatically if your performance drops below a certain level.
Let's go. All right I can't I gotta I gotta be good.
Arm swings. Move your arms around in big circles in a nice controlled way.
Oh I don't know if I can do this Bob. Try to do controlled movements and you won't put stress
on your joints. All right I burnt one calorie. It's time to end the game. Why am I blue? Let's
move on to some side steps. Oh no not side steps. Make sure you don't make your steps too wide.
Listen Bob I don't know if I can handle this. You might have to call the test early.
Perfect form. I do this shit like lying at fucking like fast food restaurants. I just like
I can do this all day. I'm a fidgety fuck. This is too hard. I'm keeping up. This is too hard.
I'm keeping up. I'm feeling good. Try to keep working even if you have to drop to a lower
intensity until it's time for a break. Oh that was me saying that to Bob. Okay Bob. I know you're
working hard. I can see you. This is too hard. That's exactly what I'm after. This is for like
all ladies. Good job. Keep that rhythm going and just march on the spot. Arms and legs move
alternately. This is a nice and easy way to warm up your entire body. Stay with it.
Try to land your feet softly. Don't stand. If you could move your arms a little more for me
that would be great. All right Bob. I got spinal problems. I can't do this. If you're going a little
slow just keep going and when you feel ready move more arms like the people that walk.
The people that like are on the sidewalk that go like this. Move your legs a little more if you
can. What do you mean knee higher? You guys don't even need the fucking face cam. This exercise will
get that heart rate up. Faster isn't always better. Make sure you're matching your trainer and
concentrate on perfect form. Good job. Keep that rhythm going.
This is actually the last time I get a little winded. I've only burned eight calories. Don't
forget that going too fast will count against you. Fuck that man. I just eat one less bag of potato
chips every day. Just do that. How many calories in a bag of potato chips? You've done the light
warm-up. Are you okay to continue to the first light exercise? It's like 325 calories for one
bag of Lays potato chips. If you just didn't eat the bag of potato chips you wouldn't have to do
this whole exercise. Thinking face. You know what I'm saying? All right let's go. Start the light
station? What the fuck is that? Wood chops.
Don't be thinking about swinging down. Place the arm over your shoulder. Does this shit
work? I don't think this works. Yeah I'm feeling it. That burn means that you are working those
muscles hard. I'm not feeling good at all. I don't feel anything. I would laugh my ass off.
Okay now let's get on there. Get on the ground. Let's do 150 push-ups. You can do it.
Do you got any weights? Go get two 50 pound dumbbells. Hold them over your head and scream.
Hold that form. 30 minutes. That's all the time we have for in this one.
Oh thank god for the cooldown period. Arms up in boxer position and sway from side to side as if
you're ducking and dodging punches. Dip down as you sway and try to keep it nice and rhythmic.
Don't dip too low as you might overextend your knees.
Pick it up. Think how proud you'll be if you get this right. I don't think it would be very
probable. Try to reach the same speed as the trainer to prevent the exercise. Burn major
calories and earn maximum points. Try to duck down lower if you can. So anytime you see like
a fitness exercise video this is great. Do this in your spare time. Go to any of these old
fitness instruction video things and watch like the people in the back. The people that are in
the front row right because they really this is a camera really in front row. I'm like oh look at
that there's that lady. Holy shit look at my face. Hold on. Wait a minute. We're staying at a low
intensity with this exercise. It looks like you're moving from side to side a lot. Try to stay in
one place more. I think it's like a bad enough. I know I'm fucking wrong. To perfect the exercise.
Burn major calories and earn maximum points. A little quicker. You're going a little slow.
Just keep going and when you feel ready you can try to pick it up a bit. Anyways what I was saying
is the people in the back all the way in the back they're always doing it so fucking wrong.
Follow your training movements exactly in order to do well. Even something as simple as like running
in place like this they'll go like this. Oh fuck. I feel like we're 20. I feel like I've burnt like
2000 calories. Work out on us hard. I'm not gonna get over that. I wish I could get a close up.
Why is my nose so big? My nose is not this big. What the fuck? Oh shit.
And back behind again as you drop your hips. What am I? I can't see. What's he doing? To avoid
stress on your lower back. Good. Keep it up. I don't even know what. I'm flapping my arms down
here like a bird? Perfect. That's what I'm talking about. It's talking to me. It's talking to people
behind you. And release. And release. Breathe out as you lift your hips. Faster isn't always better.
Make sure you're matching your trainer. Oh thank god for the cool down. Let's mix things up with
something else now. No I don't want to. I want to get up. My spine. I got a bad spine. Now come back
into a plank position. Okay I can do that. And now let's go side arm. Let's do some hip extensions.
Stretch your left arm out in front of you and at the same time extend your right leg out behind you.
What do you want? What? Now pull your arm and leg back in together keeping your hips level. Now
stretch it back out again. Keep your hips in line with one another. If you're going a little slow
just keep going and when you feel ready you can try to pick it up. I think I need a drink.
I think I need a drink. Let's take a few seconds to rehydrate at the end of the exercise
then we'll continue. Okay. Good job guys let's move to the other side now. I'm drinking soda at the
gym. What kind of dickhead are you holding everybody up? You good man? No not yet. Hey
well there's uh there's like 37 other people in this class. Wait I'm good. I got my drink. Go
class. This thing ain't got shit on the Wii mode. I'll tell you that's why I failed. Turn to the
side for this exercise. So take the other leg out and extend the other arm forward. Come on.
Squeezing into your glutes. I don't want to get on the ground. I don't want to get on the ground.
The ground is dirty. Fucking dust and dirt on there. To succeed follow your trainer's movements
closely. All right. How did we do? Tendon de Rangoon. Tendon de Rangoon. Oh shit what
happened here? My wireless setup got fucked up. All right best exercise the march. Worst exercise
proficiency. Let's see. Hold on I got this got fucked up. I gotta change this.
That's better. Okay you performed really well and reached the moderate level. That was a great start.
All right. 106 points. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off quick. Turn it off.
What are the games do I have? Too many. How is this the biggest loser? This is just like a shitty
workout game. What year were you born? Should I say I'm like fucking like 100? I'm going for it.
I wanted to do the intense workout today. All right let's say I was born in like 1921. Interesting
choice. Nine two one. September 21st carnival stream. Make sure you get some uh make sure you
get there if you want to see some fun. Uh when was I born? I don't know. Fucking March. March 1921.
Well it just stopped like fucking data mining me. This is the biggest loser body analyzer.
Body analyzer. With our revolutionary full body analysis system. Good luck in there. Okay.
You need to remove your. Welcome to the biggest loser body analyzer. To get the best results
from the analyzer you will need to remove your shoes. Why? Clothes fitting clothing will also
help you get more accurate results. When you're ready select continue. Okay please stand in the
outline. Okay with your feet together and your hands away from your sides. Arms up like this.
Turn to your left and raise your arms to max the outline. That's not right. That is inaccurate.
That's inaccurate because of where I'm standing. I'm not fucking five four.
This is from like 2006 guys. The technology didn't exist. Waist hips 31. I mean that's accurate.
Neck 163. Hold on like how big is that? 163 inches? That's like a fucking bullfrog.
That's not correct. Place the tape around your neck and adjust below the. I don't know it's I
whatever you did it I didn't. You changed that fucking height. That's not accurate.
Now it's fucking accurate. It's bullshit and it's because of the way this is pointing.
Video games are stupid. You shouldn't have don't play them anymore. All right I'm ready.
Analyzing tone and strength. Stamina. Fitness. The overall fitness training program will help
you lose weight and improve your fitness and increase your stamina. My focus should be on my
butt or what does that mean? Full body. Choose your own program. Choose your own muscle focus.
No no no. What is the one we need to focus on? It's it. You know it said I had a great ass.
I'm that's not me saying that. That's the game. Right? Yeah. Let's go. Next step of the body
analyzer. How'd that work out for you? Thank you using the biggest blizzard body analyzer.
We can start my work towards your goal. Maybe you can return to the body analyzer any time. All
right. Have it's been 30 minutes? Not yet. You're gonna laugh when I put the next one in.
You're gonna you're gonna hate me. People gonna leave. Hey Tended Dragoon 74 welcome to your
fitness program. Your calendar shows you what you did yesterday. What you'll be doing today
and what you'll be doing tomorrow. The icon under today shows that you have training schedule.
You can log out now and resume at a later date. That's not good. That's not encouraging.
This is supposed to be a fitness program. It's supposed to be a fitness instructor.
You don't say oh hey you could start today. Oh you know you could come back like another day.
Just turn it off. Oh you can log. Just get me to log out now. Yeah I guess I could log out now
and then I'll just put it back in the shelf and I'll never use it again. All right what's the
activity? I got like four minutes. Routine lengths. Choose your personal trainer. Jilly Michaels.
60 fucking plus minutes. I'll be sure to get the fuck out of here soon. If you crave chocolate go
buy some fat-free sugar-free chocolate pudding. Sprinkle a little cocoa powder. I need to get that
real chocolate taste and you've got a great chocolate treat. Never ever give up on the
thought of a thin you. Always have a thin you. I'm just going to tell you what to do and you're
going to do it. When you listen to me and you do what I say we're going to get along just fine.
Knee strikes. Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Turn to one side. Raise your arms and as
you lower them strike upwards with your knee. Then do the same on the other side. Keep your
knee and arm movements nice and controlled. Try not to move your hips too far forwards as you strike.
That's it for this one. Feeling tired yet? Bad. This is too hard. If you keep pushing you're going
to feel so much better about yourself. Coward. Come here fuck coward. I'll show you. That's I
wanted that's not Jillian Michaels. I wanted Jillian Michaels. That's not is that Jillian
Michaels? I don't think it is. Jumping jack. I think I got lied to. I don't think that was
Jillian Michaels. We'll fix that don't worry. Am I red ringing here? All right okay. I feel
like I was lied to in that last one. Coming up next. Now they can't lie to me. Hi I'm Jillian
Michaels and welcome to my fitness adventure. Using the power of connect I'll be following you
every step of the way. I'll be following you everywhere in your house. Each exercise safely
and completely. No cheating. With this new fitness adventure mode I'll be watching the leaderboards
to see who comes out on top. Now let's see if you have what it takes. Connect tuber. It's time.
Jillian Michaels. Stick your right arm straight out and raise it up and down to highlight a menu
button. To make a selection swipe your right hand across your body to lock it in. To exit any menu
use your left hand and swipe across your body. Who cares? Give me a new fitness test and I want
you to redo my height first. I got it. I got it. You can see me just fine. Oh what the fuck. My
sides. All right what a stupid fucking way to navigate a menu. Why would you ever have like.
Let's start by recording a few personal details. Get the fuck out of here. Male age 20 and I'll
look at how youthful I am. I must be so youthful looking. Age 20, 5'9", 140 pounds that's inaccurate.
But I mean come on they got everything else right. I'm gonna change that. BMI 22% body mass
percentage index. I'm gonna keep it at 20. What are you saying? I'm your weight at 6'3". From this menu
you can choose between fitness training, fitness adventure, fitness adventure and options. Fitness
no what about stats? No fitness adventure. Trek into a mysterious temple with Jillian as your guide.
Move as fast as you. Yeah oh yeah we'll do it as well. Here you can check out your prog. No stop
doing that. Use the buttons on the right to cycle through each month to see more details on your
progress. You can also choose to see your progress from the very beginning by choosing all time.
Back. Go back. Okay just I'm using control. Can I control me? Okay we'll do an adventure. Here we go.
I'm ready. This is it. Select an adventure circuit on the right hand side and get ready to trek
deep into the jungle temple. Squat jacks, side lunges, water pumps, back kicks. Which one?
Water pumps do lunge front kicks. Huge kicks. Ball scales. Power jumps. You can preview the exercises
used in this adventure. Choose a warm-up routine before you get started or jump right into the
adventure if you've already warmed up and you're ready to go. No no no we're getting hurt.
We're getting fucking hurt today. Did you warm up? Yeah and I'm gonna go like do some weird
movement like eee. Pinch of nerve. Bonus medallions. When running pick up medallions by sticking your
arms out to the side or above your head. The green medallions are good and will lower your final time.
Watch out for the red medallions. These are bad and will add to your final time. Sure.
Do the little guy down there that has to pick these up? I don't understand what I'm supposed to do.
Lunge front kick. Left leg first. All right let's move it.
Open the door. Get those feet moving and your heart pumping. What if I just pretend to take my foot?
Get around forever. I can't trick it. Get on me now. Keep going. I know you can do this. I'm doing the exercise right.
Get moving. I'm just fucking running. I'm gonna wait around forever. I'm too close. Stay focused.
Very nice. Can't somebody just get a fucking log and run into it.
Know you're tired but don't even think about stopping. Get the fucking door. All right open the door.
Don't quit on me now. Keep going. I know you can do this. Let's move it. I'm gonna take it out of the tray.
But you gotta keep moving. Fuck you Jillian Michaels. Open the door.
What? Leg first. What is that move? What? I know you can move faster than this. Hello? Watch your form.
Don't go too fast. Watch your form. Nice. Get those feet moving and your heart pumping.
Is that working? Let's just walk. All right. It's been five minutes. I feel like it's been 30.
It's been 30 minutes. That was fun. That was fun. It's been 30 minutes. Butt kicks. We're gonna start
with the right leg first. This is easy. This is a Fortnite dance. I can do this one. If you want to
make it to the end, you have to keep moving. It's a Fortnite dance. I can do this one. Very nice.
Don't quit on me now. Keep going. I know you can do it. Don't phone this in every single second of
your exercise time count. Got one. Stay focused. Finish strong. Yup. Quit on me now. Keep going. I
know you can do it. Watch your form. Don't go too fast. Watch your form. Happy birthday surprise.
This is the gif that plays at the bottom right hand corner of a fucking meme video.
Get those feet moving and your heart pumping. Okay. Jelly, I'm done. Jelly, you just drained me.
Stay focused.
I ate a fucking tuna sandwich before this. I'm full of protein. I'm good.
I had to tune a casserole. You got through it. You should be really proud of yourself right now.
What'd I get? I'm covered in water right now. Next level. Now I don't see the fucking leaderboards.
That's number one in the world. 14. Never mind. Back. How do I say back? I'm the 1482nd most
strongest man in the world. I do this one again. All right. That's enough. Wireless mic.
I gotta get it in there by the way. Thanks for reminding me. No, I'm not. Take it out of the
fucking disk. I'm not doing this shit again. Hold on. This is like. Okay. That was fun.
Don't really though. All right. Let's fucking get out of this shit. I'm done with that. No more of
this bullshit. Moving on. This one's a little case. Let me get it out. All right. That's enough of
that. Time to do something different. That was a 47 minute workout. Hey, hey, hey, hey. What the
fuck are you doing? What the hell was that? Secure HDCP link lost? I don't think I can do
this one. Well, fuck. That's annoying. Reboot. Reboot it. All right. I'm just gonna reboot it.
There is a very high chance, guys. I don't know what the exact probability of this happening is,
but this thing might break. I might burn out the 360 over the next like 12 hours of what
for these games. Okay. Here we go. It doesn't say it right here. It only says it when I load up this
next game that is actually probably for the best because nobody's going to want to see this one
because why would you? Is it fair food? Fucking bloodshed. The issue can occur if you confess
there's a home theater tuner of AV switch box between your Xbox. Well, I have to capture it
through a capture card. So maybe some of these. Let's try it one more time. Yeah. The 360 has to
go through a capture card. Otherwise, it can't go to the computer. No, it's not going to work.
Well, for the best. It was a workout DVD. Oh, well. All right. Let's actually move on to
something more than just like training. There we go. I'm fucking looking forward to this one.
All right. Let's hope that doesn't happen on like half of these. Don't touch the back of the CD
with your greasy hands. All right. All right. Come on. Don't do that again. I think we're good.
We are. This is another compilation. The soda dehydrate you. I had to do it because we're in
the shirt. What if I just lifted up my fucking whole shirt and there was a huge Coca-Cola brand
logo tattoo right here? And it was fresh. You could see the irritation on the skin. It was like, ah,
and it was like a little thing across it. I got it like an hour and a half ago. Wait, can't identify?
Tender dragoon recognized. You've been identified as tender dragoon. Confirm. Yes.
I gotta make the face can't figure everything. I shrunk it. There you go. That's better. Memory
unit. Use that one. Use it. Yeah. Use this fucking one, please. Use that one. What was that? I get
like buzzed. No. Just use the same one that you're already using. How many save files does a game
fucking have? All right. This is Motion Sports. It's highly rated. It's on every top 10 Connect
Games list you can find. There are two. There are two of those lists. You are now entering
the world of Motion Sports. Now let's get this puppy calibrated just right. Place your hand
over the top left virtual panel and leave it there for a few seconds. What hand? Left hand? I didn't
hear what he said. Left hand? And now place shoe on hand or pre-record it. Perfect. Now place your
hand over the bottom right panel and again leave it there for a few seconds. Great. You're a
natural. Finally place your hand over the top right panel and once again leave it there. Brilliant.
Now the fun begins. Hold your hand out in front of you and slide to the right. Why? Perfect. Now
we're going to take three photos of you as you would like the world to see you. No pressure now.
Okay. When you're ready to enter the photo shoot, hold your hand out in front of you
and again slide to the right. Ready? Okay. First photo. Throw your hands in the air like you just
don't care unless someone you're attracted to is around. Hold your pose until the camera flashes.
All right. Second photo. Pretend like you just won a million bucks. Hold for the flash.
Great. And now for the last photo. Show me your muscles. Wait for the flash.
Sweet. Magazines will pay gold for these. Great. Now let's play some motion scores.
I don't do fucking anything else but this every time. Horseback riding is the first one we're
doing. I don't care. Beginner course. Beginner course. Is it going to be actually me on the
horse? Oh what a fantastic game this would be. This one's going to be boring. Oh he said boxing.
We're going to do ball. This is motion. I got like two or three other fucking sports. We're
not going to do those another time. I'm looking at that stack over there. It's going to take like
three weeks. This is going to take like 10 streams to do all this. Hey, you know what I'm saying?
Fine. Guide your horse. I didn't even see what that said. Why? Don't say slide to continue.
I didn't even see what it said. Hello all. Today we're thrilled to bring you one of Equestria's
most brilliant performers. Maybe not the most stringent course he'll ever face but also not
one to take for granted. Really wants a great start. The rider failed to make a jump move
and his horse is refusing. How do you do that? Jump. Couldn't handle the simple vertical. It
cannot be taken for granted. Whoa. Hey, Magellan. The course is over here.
It didn't teach me how to play. How do you jump? Do I have to say something?
Horse refuses again. Do I have to jump? Am I controlling the horse too? Clean and solid.
Had that down behind. Jumps the wrong obstacle. He has to get back on course or he is toast.
Got it. Couldn't have been more perfect. Couldn't handle the simple vertical. It cannot be taken
for granted. At this level, horse and rider should not have a problem with the double jump.
That is a bad man. This horse just loves the crowd. Look at him go. Tough moments here today
for the highly respected Percy Wilson. But beware when he comes home to roost.
Holy shit. That's an awful picture. I'm one of the world. I'll take it. I want to go fast.
All right. Well, that one sucks. That one's not fun. At TwitchCon, meet your favorite streamers
like Jerma985. That's like outside of the TwitchCon convention. That flashes like 15 different
people. This is the line to get him. What's going on in the back? I didn't take that one. New game.
And then it'll like flash a little video of me. It'll be like, Jerma985 is here. And it's me like,
like, GTA like crash. All right. We're going to go. Soccer. For all of you, you're a bean football.
I still want my fucking like, I don't know. So I still want like my underwear to fall off. You
know what I mean? Like I'm like secure. I kick a soccer ball and like my fucking pants. Why would
that happen? Oh, let me like play connect sports. But I freak article of lower article of clubbing's
off. Am I wearing like a pants that an underwear that is like 10 sizes too big? All right. Let's
go. Stop. Don't stop red ringing and let's go. Place the ball on the ground in front of you,
bending at your waist. Step back, approach the ball and plant your non-kicking foot.
When the riding around the circle says shoot, kick with the other foot. Where did that ball go?
Okay. I got it. Honestly, what I shouldn't be concerned with is like shit in my pants.
For those who live and breathe the sport of soccer, today we bring you a definitive marvel.
First up in this penalty shootout, the talented prodigy smacks the ball against the upright.
Couldn't punch that last one through and now trying to keep them from going down early.
How do I? Is that supposed to die? The pressure of the fans, the pride of the competitors.
It makes for an electrifying competition. Go left side. I'm going to fake about going to go
right side and left. Can't allow himself to go down too far too early.
I was going, but Josh couldn't stop it.
I'm looking him right in the fucking eyes. I'm looking him right in his eyes.
I went like this and I switched around. I did it with the left foot. I went like this. I went.
You wouldn't fucking expecting that. Down one, two.
She's got to feel a hit in the middle of her stomach right now.
Just a patient looking a little nervous now, knowing how big this kick is.
Just never on the approach there. It could be over in a few seconds if he can't save this.
Great instincts in the same missing here would give his opponent the match sneak it inside.
It's just a good pitch. A nice effort with just a few bumps and bruises along the way,
but you witnessed his natural talent. They got a pretty good me in the air.
I need like a headband. When I go for my first break, I'm going to get like a
bandana or something like a headband. The same picture. Hey, welcome to TwitchCon.
Yeah, we only got this one motherfucker here. That's it.
And we're going to use the same photo. Meet and greets at four o'clock.
Wait, what's in the back? The back one too. What is it?
Welcome to the Narcissist Convention. You should really like this guy.
Now that's like in Vegas. They have all, it's getting like, oh, Donnie and Marie are on the
side of an entire fucking building. Aren't they important? What? Oh, I hope that's on
one of the billboards. That's your kid, Evo. No, no new emotes. No new emotes ever. All right,
that was football, soccer, whatever. Let's do, let's actually do, let's do American football.
Vertical run. I want to like do the quarterback stuff. All right, I have to win. What are you
saying? Unstopped. This is a running one. Okay. Jump and, jump and duck. I have to do this one
well because I want to unlock the other game. I need like a better, cool score. This would be
easy. Hey everybody. We thank you for joining us to watch one of the most spectacular phenoms in
all of football. Lots of barriers he has to try and jump and duck without touching.
All right, wave one. Established a solid platform can now start reaching for those high scores.
Why did it go twice? This is taking it more out of me than any of the other ones. The
Jillian Michaels fucking. A 2.2 kids in corner office in 30 years kind of guy.
All right, I did it. Smoking. Excellent showing with a decisive outcome. Great energy and focus
has him nearing his very best. Wait, I want to see how vertical I got.
I got to turn the fan on. I need some cool air. Lateral run. Okay. Fucking narcissist, man.
Who cares about that? They're not going to show up anywhere. Mugshot. Has it been 30 minutes on
this one? The Amazonian dimple. Professor Tom. No? All right. Well, how much time we got?
It's going to be another 15, 20 minutes. This is boxing. I got to be ready to fucking lay
somebody out. He better play everything. We're going to play everything. Don't you worry.
I have to clean up as we go though, because there's so many discs over here. I will ruin
the room and it'll be, it'll just be a cluttered, uncomfortable hoarder feeling in this room. It
happens sometimes. Perry. Raise your hands in front of your face. Real quick straight punch
to the face of stomach. Throw a semi-circular punch to the head of the body. Do an uppercut.
What was Perry? Raise your hands in front of your face. Your guard can be broken if you keep
Perry without attacking. All right. So you just beat him up. For those who love boxing,
get ready to witness the dream. One of this sport's superior talents, the Amazonian devil,
very quick-handed opponent, loves the jab and really puts punches together well.
Doesn't have true punching power though. Look for the dream to take some of those jabs in order to
get inside and do real punching damage. And here goes dream, trying to end it all. Three knockdown
rule in effect. If it goes to the scorecards, landing a lot of blows and a high percentage
is key. Sucks in a jab and wobbling. Eats the stiff jab. Oh my. Takes a stinging jab.
Halfway through round one. Cleans up on it. Has him hurt and in trouble. That was enough.
Trying to finish him. Heard him earlier with a hard left. Did not dream, not like,
push himself out. Now he's a sitting duck. Dream lighting him up. 10 seconds left in this round.
Oh, wobbles his legs. Dream delivering punishment here. Everybody has a plan
until they get punched in the mouth. I thought it was tactical lockout.
Three times you go down. That's TKO. Incredible conclusion to this fight. Unbelievable.
Wow. Dialing up a winner. A simply stunning performance. Brilliant. Extraordinary. Monumental.
That was spectacular. Not really, it really wasn't at all actually. It was pretty lame.
I'm telling you though, if you give me one of those machines, I will go over like 600,
700, 800 pounds per square inch. One of those punching machines. We already talked about it.
You guys already know this. I will prove that one day on camera, I promise. No, more of this.
I don't even want to take these anymore. Where are they going? They're probably going to like
fucking server somewhere. What do we not do? Hang gliding? They're going straight to my PC?
Mine or yours? What do you mean? All right, we got hang gliding. Leaving the nest.
No, mine. Me. You just probably go to me. I'm out of here. All right, so how do we do this?
I guess I can't leave them. Oh, that's me. I did that. So I don't want to be disturbed while I'm
playing Kinect. Okay, raise your left arm to turn right. These kind of piano hands. So piano hands,
lower arms to nose dive. Lift up. Tilt. Tilt. Like this. Okay, if you were going out of gaining
altitude. All right, I got it. I'm gonna sneeze. I tried to hold it. If you hold it in. Hello,
ladies and gentlemen. Today we bring you one of Gliding's outstanding virtuosos.
Wants to nail a solid landing after getting used to the air's thermal mechanics.
That's very, apparently it's very windy. I'm not sure what he was thinking.
Where am I landing?
Oh, a sad showing from our developing star, but like all others with a great deal of pride,
he'll be back. I'll be back. Back from the dead. I don't like that one. I don't like that one.
I don't like this game. Holy shit. Somebody gave, somebody gave 69 subs.
BilacteryLich just gave 69 community subs. Holy shit. 69. You've done that twice.
BountySuperG, SkiCross. I'm gonna do SkiCross. Thank you so much. That's an insane amount of subs.
And that is, like I said, the second time that you've done that. Thank you, Bilactery.
Congratulations to those who got the fucking community subs. That's a lot. That's hundreds.
What is that? 70. That is a lot of fucking money. Thank you, Bilactery. He already dead. They
already did the 420 thing. Four subs and then 20 subs. That's too many subs. All right. Push
poles on to start. So you just gotta ski. Bend your knees and transfer your weight to the left or
right turn. Right? High at skiing. When your first gauge is full, crouch down to speed up.
Let's go. Go as fast as you can. Hello, everyone. Today we bring you one of the skiing world's most
amazing talents. Blowing out the gates. The race is on. It's underway. Sitting in third place right
now. He's in fourth. What's going on? Why am I going that fast? Slingshots off the altar.
That's some big air. Getting thrown down.
Hey, let's go to the on the field, Mike. Somebody just gave a bunch more subs.
And expect to win. Who gave the subs? Austin Atlantis. Austin Atlantis gave 50 community subs.
Holy shit, guys. 69 and 50. Racers muscling for position. Thank you so much. Light of the gate.
Big mistake there. I have to do something fucking crazy. Ridiculous jump. I should do that the whole
time. That just stays a bowl. Did not finish. A capable appearance from him, but obviously
leaving some room. You see me doing the cry. Great talent. Watch it right there. When I'm leaning
this way, I'm doing the cry. All right. I think I've seen what I want to see in this one. We've got
a lot more. Unless there's something. I want to see the quarterback one. Why do you have to put
these behind a time gate? I want to throw the football. To the back of the box. I want to do
the foot throw in the back of the box. I've got two horror games. I'm tired. I assure you, I'm not.
Yes, I am. Why did I start with the Jillian Michaels shit? I blew all of my energy in the
first 40 minutes of the stream. I knew that was going to happen. I'm going to get a second win.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm going to be fine. Running back quarterback kicker. Hold on.
I want to see what that is. I have to. We're past the 30 minute mark on this now,
but it doesn't matter. I have to. I have to throw quarterback balls. Am I desynced? I shouldn't be.
Let's test it. A bit. By how much? What's happening first? Audio is early. How's this?
Oh my fucking God. Hold on. If I left here, let's just give 250 fucking. How much money have you
given this week? Give us a thousand dollars, dude. Oh my God. 250 bucks and 69 subs.
He's just like fucking dropping money. Thank you. Hey Jerma, I had a really good day today with my
father-in-law and wife. Want to share some bits with you. By the way, that paraglider is fucking
dead. He's not coming back walking. Well, thanks for the huge amount of fucking money.
Thanks for like the more than like 1500 bucks in the last week. That's insanity. Thank you.
All right. Let me get this fixed. That's a lot of fucking money. So sound is early.
So let me go like this. If I do this, does this help at all? Ready? Same? No. What the fuck is
happening? Sound is... All right. Hold on. Ready? Better? Still, it's way too early. What the fuck is
happening? I wonder why. Ready? It's worse. It's way, it's way worse. Wrong direction. Now is it late?
Now it's late. Computers don't ever have one. All right. How about this? What? That's impossible.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is important. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Check this out. Hey, ready? That can't be early. See, this is perfect now. But what I have
to do is see on the screen here. I have to, I have to pull. Why would that, why would, what's,
how did that makes no sense? These are both the same millisecond. All right. Ready? Hold on. Watch
this. This shit, they're both at 650 milliseconds. Why would one be, I don't know. That makes no
sense. That's perfect. Fixed. Good. Good. Fixed. That's exactly what it was before. It was 650, 650.
It was always good. You got baited. Are you fucking kidding me? No, not fixed. Let me, let me, hold
on. I'm gonna, I'll be change game. I was gonna, what was I gonna do? Yeah, hold on. Let's change
game. Oh my God. I haven't done anything for 50 subs. I'm just walking around in a circle.
Hold on. It's time. It's time to move on to the meat and fucking potatoes of this stream. Are you
ready? You, I, that was a spoiler. Don't look at it. Uh, Abe Cashem, Abe Cashem, thank, Abe
Cashem. Thank you for 50 more fucking subs. Holy shit. 50 subs. 50, 50, 70. You guys are fucking
giving so much subs. Thank you. The connect is the path to money. No, there's no way this is out of
sync. It's impossible. The, the audio and the video are both set to 650 milliseconds. Delayed.
There's no way. It's literally technically impossible. Somebody give me a clip. I want
to prove this to the world and myself. Clip that. Let me see it. Right now.
Let me see it right now. Why is nobody clipping that? Oh, by the way, we're playing fucking Harry
Potter. Just in case you were curious. It's literally technically impossible. Somebody give
me a clip. I want to prove this to the world and myself. Clip that. You fucking dickheads.
Shit's perfect shit. It's fine. Uh, thank you. The, the wild, the wild ad, the wild. Thanks for the
wild. Appreciate the fucking 10 subs. I just watched the clip. It's very clearly and happens.
I don't, it's over. It's fine. I got my fucking Bluetooth connection wireless setup. I'm playing
Harry Potter for connect. All right. I got to get in here. Wait, just do it one more time.
Click that right now. What the game? I didn't have the game behind me. I didn't have the game
behind me. Seriously. Somebody click that right now. I didn't have the game behind me.
I'm not clicking on that one. Click. I want the real one. Thank you. All right. I got to get in
here. I can't, I can't tell. I have no idea. I think it's, I think it's fine. I think it's fine.
It's the connect. It's not unwatchable. It's like 0.5 seconds behind. No, it's not. I'm done. I'm
done. I'm done. We're just going. Everything's fine. There's nothing I can do to fix it because
there is no fix. It's the connect. And there's like a little quarter of a second delay.
There's nothing I can do to fix it. It's six 50, six 50. If I change it, it fucks it up. Just
relax. Okay. Select continue to play or signing. Okay. Raise hand. Welcome guest.
Somebody's 50 fucking dollars. Can you give us a good expelliarmus? Oh, I'm going to give
you a good one. And that's another $50 and another fucking. That's your worth thousand dollars now.
101,000 bits from phylactery. Holy shit. You've crossed the $1,000 in the month mark. Thank you.
For real. All right. Navigating menus. To move menus, skipping cinematics. Why would I skip the
cut scenes in a Harry Potter game? That sounds like a mistake. To move menus, to move menus to
the left, to hold your right hand out to the side and swipe to the left. I don't know these bullshit
things. Let's go. New game. For those who enjoy an easier experience. No.
Advanced. For those who enjoy a challenge. Is it just normal? Where's normal mode?
I'm not doing casual. We're going to do advanced. Harry Potter was living. Oh fuck. I'm sorry. I
just ruined it. His awful aunt Petunia and uncle Vernon. When on his 11th birthday, he learned that
he was a wizard and received a letter inviting him to attend Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and
Wizardry. Yeah, I've seen the movie. I don't know that owl's name. I can't see from that far away.
Dear Mr. Potter, we are pleased to inform that you have a place in Hogwarts School of Witchcraft
and Wizardry. Please find and close the list of all necessary books and equipment. Turn begins on
September 21st. Make sure you go to the carnival street. Uh, we await your owl by no later than the
31st of July. Your sincerely Minerva McGonagall, deputy head mistress. Woolly mode? Custom mode.
What is that? What's the difference? Does anybody know the difference?
Is it just, it just plays the movie? Custom mode. What's that? What's changing? Let's go
to Madame Malkin's to get your school robes and customize your character.
This is empty. God, you know what I wish this was? I wish this was a fucking skull crusher IPA from
Stone Cold Steve Austin. Taking a psycho. Move your head until it fills the head template. Sure thing.
We gotta get my robe on. Stand in front of that mirror, please. That's it. Now position yourself
so that your head fits the guide as closely as possible. Excellent. My face is too fucked up.
And we'll take a picture. Five, four, three, two, one. Looking good. Now feel free to try a different
look. Where are my eyes? It's really not you. We can always take another picture.
Retake, retake, retake. I don't like that one. That's it. Now position yourself so that your head
fits the guide as closely as possible. Excellent. Is it because I blinked? And we'll take a picture.
Five, four, three, two, looking good. Now feel free to try a different look. Or if it's really not you,
we can always take another picture. I need one more. That's it. Now position yourself so that
your head fits the guide as closely as possible. Excellent. Just one second and we'll take a picture.
Five, four, three, two, one. Looking good. Now feel free to try a different look. Or if it's
really not you, we can always take another picture.
Try a different look. Oh my god. That one, that one's the best. Go back to that one.
Where is it? There it is. Finished. Good luck.
One of the first things every young midshore wizard must get before going to Hogwarts is a wand.
All right, we're gonna get a, we're gonna get a wand.
Trying a wand. Give a wand a try before moving your wand hand in a quick downward swishing motion.
Okay, ring the bell. Just a minute.
Hey.
Distraction.
You will never get such good results with another wizard's wand. Now let's get you a wand.
Okay, cherry and dragon heart string. Nine inches. I don't like it. Don't want it.
Give me something else. No, I want to find something. Apparently not. That one sucks.
I want holly and phoenix feather. 11 inches. Nice and supple. Yeah. Okay, I might like this one.
Let's try this one. There goes two hundred years of history. We'll find the perfect match here
somewhere. Elm and unicorn hair. 10 inches. Quite whippy. Try it.
I want to pick my wand. I don't want him to tell me which one is mine. Doesn't the wand pick the person?
Tricky customer. The wand picks the person. Not the other way around. Try this one. You and
unicorn hair. Eight and three quarter inches. Powerful wand. Very powerful. This one has a good feel.
Oh bravo. Well, well, well. Curious indeed how these things happen.
The wand chooses the wizard. See, that's what I said. I think we must expect great things from you.
I think that's what I said. I've already seen the movie. The moment first years arrive at Hogwarts,
they are sorted into one of four houses. I'd better get Slytherin. Slytherin, Hufflepuff
or Ravenclaw. I'm gonna be sitting there. I'm gonna be fucking just going Slytherin, Slytherin,
Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin. And the hat's going to be like, Slytherin.
Get sorted or try to influence the hat's decision. See, if you have a strong reference,
say Gryffindor, Slytherin or Ravenclaw to try. Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin,
Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin, Slytherin, now let me think,
Slytherin Slytherin plenty of ambition in this one cunning and resourceful
Slytherin I think Slytherin yes oh he didn't drink all right here we go
advanced difficulty sorting head the sorting head sleeps Fox what do I do
what am I doing am I like petting him what if he bites my hand can I like do anything else I
don't know I don't know the memory pot let's do it new potions class oh yeah
year one no no no no no no no no no no I want to see what else is in the office
sorting head let's just see what happens year one song okay let's try oh you may
not think I'm pretty but don't judge on what you see I'll eat myself if you can
find a smarter hat than me we'll do it sour please do that all right let's go
in the memory box this is advanced difficulty potion class year one here we
go there's nothing it hasn't been anything in here for 25 minutes in you
is that me that looked like my face that was my face in there in your first
potions class with professor snake you will learn how to brew the cure for
boils I've done this before I'm sure that's not my face all first years are
required to take potions class with professor Snape Snape his head of
Slytherin house and seems to particularly dislike Harry Potter oh
shit I skipped it how about your hand over an item to pick it up use the
spoon to stir the cauldron in a circular motion until the potion is in
the color shown in the instructions move an ingredient to the center of the
cauldron to add it move the item away from the cauldron once you have added
enough why am I only using one hand brush ingredients by moving the pestle
in a clockwise or 80 clockwise motion why am I not using my left hand or
anything to put an ingredient down raise your non wand hand all right let's go
you are here to learn the subtle science and exact art of I can teach you how to
bottle fame brew if you're not a bunch of idiots have to teach I could have
done that I could do much better than that in today's class you will attempt
to brew a cure for boils may begin follow the instructions carefully be
sure to stir the contents of your cauldron in the direction good the
potion reaches the color show red don't touch it let go select ingredients by
matching their colors and shapes with all right show you put in the book your
that is correct now until the potion is the required this should be the correct
ingredient some ingredients need crushing how I feel when I try to drive
a manual car I'm just like I don't understand so I don't I don't want to do
this I'm not driving this yellow one horned slugs how is this advanced
difficulty oh I try to cook a hand out of there your potion appears usable
well being I don't want to do this manual shit I don't want to do I don't
want to learn the gear shift this I want a coaster here on my desk is beautiful
congratulations you unlock charms class Dumbledore's office and a cure for
boils first years receive instruction in basic charms and spells from professor
Flitwick today you will learn how to cast the levitating when Guardian
Leviosa I think I can handle when asked say when Guardian Leviosa to make it
your active spell when asked make Wingardium Leviosa your active spell by
holding your arms in its pose oh you all here today we'll start by learning how
to make objects fly you select which spell you're going to cast you can
simply say it for today's class the incantation is Wingardium Leviosa now
you try when Guardian Leviosa I was late show you another way of selecting a
spell I was asleep also use movement to select a spell to select Wingardium
Leviosa put your arms in this position give it a go
you've selected your spells or completing the arm movement you can
start to cast it with a wave of your one like this Wingardium Leviosa you've
successfully cast your first spell now I want you away from all the other people
use Wingardium Leviosa to levitate all three of those I got he fucks up too
many spells we're gonna put him over here
Wingardium Leviosa, Wingardium Leviosa, Wingardium Leviosa, Wingardium Leviosa
splendid job you'll learn many more spells here at Hogwarts each has its own
incantation did fucking like $200 come in like ten minutes ago class
dismissed hold on wait wait wait wait wait look at I didn't you didn't see
that first I don't like this shit recording me man but we had a lot Lando
Bando get $50 holy shit Dermot just want to say thanks for helping me and I'm
sure a lot of other members of the community through hard times
absolutely you've helped me through mental hospital stays and major losses
you've definitely inspired me to work towards things that I actually want to
do in my life also I'm working on an animation for the teacher noise I was
wondering if you could make more student what the fuck background noises for me
absolutely yeah it's quiet this award he's coming in he's coming in here
quiet quite quite you see the new smash brothers character yeah I was fucking so
hard it was the hardest game ever played I couldn't beat I couldn't get that that
level we've got with Gino was really really difficult for me the white kids
don't scream like that wait they'll use that but no seriously Lando Bando thank
you so much that means a lot if anybody gets anything from this channel like
I've said a thousand times it means a lot I hope you fucking like it I hope
you enjoy the content hope you like hanging out here cuz that's I I wouldn't
be here if I wasn't having fun too so thank you for real and then the the
wild out again the wild 50 bucks parter Perry harder and the torturers bone fuck
thank you Jerma sucks for the five dollars no fucking community subs thank
you Jerma sucks five don't know that was way more than five dollars all right
troll battle I'm ready imagine that fucking imagine if I was like a boxer
man you got like one of those let's go when professor Quirrell interrupts dinner
in the Great Hall to announce that there is a troll in the castle realize her
Miami may be in danger and go to the girls toilets to rescue her jump to dodge
the trolls low club swings duck to avoid the trolls high club swings throw
objects by making an underarm or over from throwing motion if the troll
grabbed you swipe your hand upwards to poke him when you want I get his neck
this is a lot of information cast when guiding in the video so with a quick
downward swisher you want on when the aiming rectangle appears move your hand
at your target let's go
oh I don't know oh I'm just not sure I just I don't know what the big troll in
this room I just can't tell what to do I'm not sure let's go let's go let's go
oh boy all right this is you go hold on a second there bitch a troll we can talk
about it you stop that right now
why what oh my goodness
no what's my friends Oh crochet
he's gonna get me it's coming over here
Wow all right now stick this like directly into his eye
what do you just think
Ron you idiot you keep stabbing me in my face
oh that was brutal that was an awful and the chance cause swish and flick hit
the trolls club with wingardium I don't remember the name of the spell it's up
there that's up to the W
Oh
wingardium lvios up he's gonna get hit right in the face by the valor
wingardium lvios up who am I supposed to do this to wingardium lvios up
wingardium lvios up wingardium wingardium wingardium wingardium wingardium
We got him.
We re going to go.
Got it.
Whew!
Quidditch match.
Oh, I'm looking forward to this.
When Professor McGonagall sees Harry catch something in midair while on his broomstick,
she thinks that he could be perfect for the position of Seeker on the Gryffindor Quidditch
team.
You fix your hair a lot.
Prepare to play Harry's first match against Slither.
Because it's unruly, and fucking ugly, and gross, and like, I have to cut it.
gets all of my face in my in my mouth and shit like I'm an irresponsible adult
and I should have cut my hair like three weeks ago so it's Harry versus me I'm on
a lean left or right to steer your broom try to stay as close to the center of
this have the snitch as possible okay when tussling with your opponent throw a
punch or kick they do that in Harry Potter hold your hand over the snitch to
grab it it's okay every single it's all right see guys it's hard to see what I'm
looking at violent there's gonna bloody nose yeah what's the goal where's the
thing I just beat up everybody where is the quidditch where's where is it
five-star I'll take it the sorcerer's stone the sorcerer's stone can produce
the elixir of life which makes the drinker immortal to keep it safe
Dumbledore has hidden the stone in Hogwarts protection when Harry Ron and
Hermione realize Voldemort has discovered the stones location they go to find it
before he can get to it boss fight incoming block incoming keys with your
hands when chasing the door key you hold your hand over it to grab it touch
Voldemort's face with both hands to fight him off what absolutely push
Voldemort's face what are we going to do there must be a thousand keys up there
we're looking for a big old-fashioned one probably rusty like the handle go
hey schnoz you'll find it grab the right key which one is it oh shit three
laughs just let it be the face it'll lock it where's the real one whatever I
got a concept right here just let him hit me look the mosquitoes bite me I don't
care that's the key we meet again see what I must do to survive but it cannot
give me a body of my own there is something that can something that
conveniently enough
get off of me
attempts remaining a hundred you can attempt that a hundred times that seems
a little overkill year one Harry Potter year one year two coming up wait okay
do we actually play through what happening to throw by this Voldemort
Harry recovers from the confrontation in the hospital wing Dumbledore visits him
and tells him that the stone has indeed now what is the year ends with
Gryffindor winning the house cup this definitely didn't come up before the
last movie did I can't see it let's go I'm interested you're too bring it on
I wish I just I wish I had a nice cold skull crusher IPA stone-cold Steve Austin
beer professor Lockhart the defense against the dark arts teacher during
Harry's second year at Hogwarts releases a number of Cornish pixies into his
classroom the students must get them back into their cage the last movie was
2011 this came on 2012 quickly swipe your hand to generate a trail the trail
will hit anything it touches say Hermione or raise your non one hand for
second year is way harder than first year he's got two broken shins mandrake
repotting the second years in professor sprouts her biology class must repot
seedling mandrakes being careful to wear earmuffs cry of the seedlings will knock
out a human for several hours like to block my ears when prompted move your
hands to your ears to put on your earmuffs left or right to move along
the mandrake table am I a mandrake move your hand over an unhappy mandrake to
grab it shake a mandrake to pull it from its pot pull the mandrake over an empty
pot raise your hand to switch to a holding your watering can raise your
other hand to switch to holding slug repellent lower your hand to pour water
of slug repellent sounds easy welcome to greenhouse three second years our
mandrakes are only seedlings but their cry could still knock you out for
several hours please put on your earmuffs for your auditory protection now
we'll start by repotting look out for unhappy mandrakes they are the ones that
have outgrown that's it grasp your mandrake securely and leave it and now
place him down into another I don't know what it is what do I go over this
way how do I move I don't know what to do how do I mean okay put him in okay
now right here yep
watch out for any wilting mandrakes you'll need to water them before they
become who's agitated right here who's that anymore
when their head is down
I only have 16 seconds right here come on I can't go any further over my way my
way blacken out goodness looks like long bottom has been collecting his earmuffs
it's like knocked out Neville let's do it welcome to greenhouse three second
there we go I got it I know mandrakes are only seedlings but their cry I want to
get this knocked out of the park look out for unhappy mandrakes they are the ones
that have outgrown their pot that's it grasp your knife place him down into
another empty pot we're going to the next part right next to it I'm trying to
go quick come on get over here who's the bad guy in the second moving I think I
can trust you with something a little more taxi watch out for any wilting
mandrakes you'll need to water them before they become
this is it don't fuck this up this time this takes too long slow down agitated
agitated right these two right at the end who needs it I live 17 seconds
remaining who needs this there's nobody left there's nobody left it needs water
I swear to God there's nobody who needs water who needs the water I have to pull
them out I thought I was just supposed to water these green house three second
yes our mandrakes are now we'll start by repotting look out for unhappy mandrakes
now that's it grasp your mandrakes now place him down into another empty pot
let's go watch out for any wilting mandrakes you'll need to water them
before they become too agitated give me the can who's crying come here who's
crying who's crying you good oh god I think it's time to give you some
advanced mandrake maintenance no it's around free flesh-eating slugs are
harmful to men be sure to apply repellent at the first signs of an
infestation who is doing this oh they're killing him
where's he you fucking idiot I'm going I'm going I'm going
the expert with Mandrake care like that I'm quite sure we should expect a real
that was really really hard that was not easy I did it I'm ready
dueling club I this is what I bought this game Dumbledore has granted
professor Lockhart permission why I purchased a dueling club to train
students to defend themselves if necessary the first two students
selected to duel are Harry Potter and his nemesis Draco Malfoy not me I thought
about me it's supposed to be me step to the left or right to move yep dueling
club hold both hands in front of you to cast
protogo cast a spell with a quick downward swish of your wand arm when the
aiming reticle appears move your hand and aim at your target okay how a lot of
spells incantation or hold its pose to change your active spell does it lead
out of DaVinci thing what's it called like the wheel man let's go wands at the
ready on the count of three I don't know the control one two three
look my fucking clock what's the one what's the one that kills people what's
the one that there was someone that kills me ah it what's it called what's
it called what's it called the Forbidden One
steeper by a dab of a father a father cap dab what is it a dab of a dab of
cadaver a dab a dab a dab a dab of cadaver I don't know how to walk Hermione
Hermione help Hermione Hermione where's Hermione skew it's me
fire with that shit wands at the ready I'm gonna light about bushes on the
count of three one two three
hold up the shield why don't I block attacks
I don't know what of three one two three
what's he saying Tago for Tago for Tago for Tago for Tago for Tago what is it
where we do this
sucks
My eye
Double knockout that was a double knockout
On the count of three one two three
I
Want to do like the this thing
Harry learns that Ginny Weasley has been taken to the chamber of secrets by the air of Slytherin and
Finds a way to reach the chamber through the pipes of the castle
He arrives to find Tom Riddle a young Lord Voldemort who has appeared from a 50 year old diary
Standing over a weakened Ginny
Harry must fight Riddle and the giant basilisk in the chamber to serve his friend
Dodge
Dodging the basilisks of the last second will cause him to stun himself momentarily
Once he is stunned spike him with your one hand to damage make a sword this one
She's still alive
But only just you see as poor Ginny grows weaker. I grow stronger
Only a base
That was bad
You can see the ah
No, no, no, no, no. Come on. Harry learns that Ginny Weasley has been taken to dodge
Dodge and then slash she's still alive
But only just you see as poor Ginny grows weaker. I grow stronger
Oh
She's still alive
You see as poor Ginny grows weaker I
Grow stronger
Myself inside
What are you doing?
Year three after Harry defeats Tom Riddle by destroying the
Tells him that only a true
Relaxing one after that about sorting hat. I want to do the like laser. That's why I bought this
When does that happen which movie that's this is it it's this one it's the fourth movie
Really?
Ron and I'm returning to Hogwarts castle when scabbers escapes from this
Alright, I'm gonna go
Willow a large black dog grabs Ron and drags him into a passageway in the trees trunk
Harry and Hermione must avoid the trees branches to reach their friend
Beat the game. I actually kind of like jump low swinging branches
Duck high. Okay, duck jump and dodge
Oh, I've got much harder that's for sure
Tree so scary
You missed oh no. Oh shit. I hate this
My wireless out. Oh, I gotta pee so bad. Oh
Shit whoo. Come on. Let's make this quick
I thought I had a camera on over here
Grab her
Steve
Oh
Again
You don't have to do this
Pee pants part
That was no joke. Oh
That's right. It is advanced
Harry and how I do this Ron inside the shrieking shack and encounter Snape
Professor Lupin and Sirius black and animagus who had taken the form of the black dog
If you never seen Harry Potter before
That's
The deaths of Harry's parents they must capture the rat and return it to human form
You are getting every spoiler of all seven movies. So if you're planning on watching them
You came to the wrong string
Okay leaning and turning
leaning
hitting scabbers
Let's get this one done quick
I've waited a long time for this moment
12 years in
Azkaban you see I didn't betray your parents. It was someone else Peter Pettigrew
Right now scabbers
I'll get a first try first shot the sofa
He's quick you need to be quicker
You can't get away Pettigrew
everybody see one
scabbers
Where is he? I didn't do any of that. It's still doing I have to pee thing from last time
I've waited a long time for this moment
All right, we go
Where's he got it nice one James
Oh
I'm looking at a 27 inch screen from across the whole room. I
Don't have like a big projector. I've waited a long time for this moment
12 years in
Azkaban you see I didn't betray your parents. It was somebody else did
Take the fireplace. Come on. I I can't see everything's great
It's making me sick
I think we say I have to stop
Everybody close your eyes till it's done. I'll tell you
He's not getting away this time open your eyes somewhere Pettigrew
That one was impossible
Without the secret technique. You're don't do by that hand. I'm going like this hold the wand
Don't like that. It's not whatever. It's like
That's not a big deal
The battle of the Dementors are a man. We go
After capturing Peter Pettigrew the group leave the shrieking shack
But professor Lupin has forgotten to take his wolfsbane potion and turns into a werewolf
Indian suing mayhem
transforms back into a rat and escapes
Serious chases looping kill the diventers
Okay, move your wand and to control your Patronus move it in front of incoming Dementors to repel them
All right, lean left and right to block the Dementors path
Walk with the blonde walk with my body body block and arm block. Oh shit
So it's got fun
Did you take a portion of my soul
Take my life essence. All right, just just block
I got it. It's gonna get harder and harder
It's like house of the dead. They make it so you can't get the two or three people come to the screen at the same time
Let's get to the player
Are you serious?
One more
Let's go don't take any damage till the last phase
unnecessary damage
All right. This one this one was really hard last time
Let's go
plenty practice
We go on in the harry potter game, I was here I was I was here
Two I got the achievement of about two
Oh, it's a perfect score. That's why
That was year three
That was it that movie sucked what a boring fucking movie
Dumbledore's suggestion harry and hominy he used the time turner to go back and save buck beak
And learn that it was actually harry who defeated the Dementors and saved sirius not harry's father as he'd thought
Year four is the tribe was a tournament. This is when I get to do this thing
That's all I care about that we can move on
To the relaxing game
When harry is mysteriously entered into the tri wizard tournament
He must first obtain a golden egg from the crunches of a hungarian horn tail dragon
From the egg he learns the second task will be in the lake
You breathe underwater recover something that has been left swim
Okay
So you swim half spells at the window lows with a quick swish of your one hand
And dodge the window the window lows by sidestepping. All right, so swim slash sidestep
Uh, this movie's not very good
What do I do?
That's close
Give me the thing. I want to do this like three times. Come on quick
Of course, I gotta do this like three times
Okay
They're getting they're getting more aggressive how far I can do one two three go all the way
Good, why do they keep playing the avengers theme song?
Avengers assemble anything else stellar swimmer one time. Let's go
Third task and then we have to fight
What's his name for the third task of the tri wizard tournament harry must avoid obstacles as he races through a maze
And the other tri wizard champions in an effort to be the first to read
I'm not i'm very bad at mazes jump to dodge the maze's low obstacles and duck and shit
duck jump
So it's gonna be terrible. I don't want to do anymore like jumping
I've been jumping for three hours four hours
I can't see them
I can't see
What are you supposed to do that?
How are you supposed to do that? That was impossible
I just need to get to the thing and then we can go to the relaxing game
I'm trying to cheat it
All right last probably phase here phase three
Hey look, there's a dickhead
All right, that's it. That's it. Come on. That's it
I don't want to do this again. Just concentrate
Stop relax, jeremy
Go
This is a big spoiler come on quick get out of here get out of here leave now quick
Die you had your chance
Unbeknownst to harry and cedric the tri wizard cub is a portkey that takes them to a graveyard where they encounter peter
During the one connection raise and lower your hand
To move your cast up and down
Trying to match the height of voldemort's cast
This is the thing. This is this thing this thing
See, I can't block the killing curse
Spell
I'm sorry voldemort. I just ran through forest like 10 spray guns
This thing whatever
Don't you turn your back on me?
I want you to look at me
Here it comes. I want to see the light leave your eyes
Here we go
Is
I can't do it
Oh my neck
I just like jolted my neck
Ah
You can't block it
Don't you turn your back on me?
I want you to look at me. Let's go. I want to see the light leave your eyes
You've lit me you've leading with the kill thing I ain't fucking around now don't you turn your back on me
I want you to look at me
Oh
Protego protego quick
Protego
This shit is fucking hard, this is hard this is on advanced like kids didn't pick this only I did
I have to beat voldemort. Otherwise, I can't move on
I've got to catch him in like a wrath of fire like sicko move like this way
Five
What am I
Don't you turn your back on
Expelliarmus
New move
What's it called
Immobilize take up
So much get up there start strangling him hurry get over there put your hands where it's not
What's it called immobilize
Immobilize
Stupify
It's not possible it's impossible it's not possible they were never designed to be
The queen
Don't you turn your back on
Protego
Incentive
Better you gotta get to wait till he lands on the ground and then rapid rapid fire
You can live forever take him take him stupify it's bullshit he didn't even cast it
No, come on dad dad my arm how do they hold their arms up for this long do it
How many more years are there sure just do it no i'm not gonna do it
No, that's all I want to do i'm done we move on we're doing the fucking relaxing game
Now i'm i'm moving on to the relaxing game
I'm probably gonna get sued for this one, too, by the way. I don't know what the
But how this is I don't know what this is. I'm not sure if this is legal
This is what i'm trying to say harry's wand and voldemort's connected an effect known as priority incantatum occurred
Giving harry time to summon the portkey and return to hogwarts. Let's see what the level is
Room of requirement
All right, we're gonna uh, all right, let me see what it is
Improving defense against the dark arts skills in the room of no
No, no, we'll go back to it feeling. Yeah, I am feeling tired
Thank you xbox. Let's let's relax. I might go back to this one a little bit
What the hell? All right. Um, this one this is a relaxing one. This is just to chill
This is for us to just hang out. We're not gonna be crazy. This is gonna get me
The mic at my whole channel plank
Open the fucking district
This disc
Uh is very like so hot that I can I I could probably burn my if I lifted up my shirt right now
It went like this. It would it would be like a ring. It would burn my skin
All right, let's relax
Let's relax and get fucking sued
update
Look at my sweaty ass hair
Holy shit
Uh, those are the curious. This is uh, our trip to disneyland
Relax for a little bit. No more fucked up movements
We're just gonna go to disney frontier made this
weird
Interesting. Okay
Uh, this is just we're gonna go to disneyland. We're gonna get some like a corn dog
donald mickey mini goofy and
dog
Pluto
Yes, I want to play his beat choose a sage lot. No
always donald
every time
Where do you guys want to go on first space mountain?
Let's go to epcot. You want to go to epcot out of can we go to epcot?
I think this is just a google street view disneyland. Let's just walk around characters. Love to be greeted with a wave
Even if it's okay
Here it is
disneyland in southern california
Here's my ticket
Ah, all right. Well, I gotta catch it. It's gonna fly right into my hand
Oh smell on the ground
Is that me who's this guy this person of many movies?
This place is a whole new world want to go explore. Yes, you know you do
Say, who are you anyways?
Uh, my name is time. My name's jeremy
So today your pick go over the button just reach out and hover over continue. Got it
Look at our small world of choices want to go right just swipe your right arm
Okay, so we're gonna go right to go left swipe with your left arm simple, right?
Okay
Sounds easy enough great now for the hair
Same deal just swipe with your left or right hand. Oh, and there's a world of color
Just hover on the color button
fabulous
now
Yeah
Stop let's get a good let's get let's get a good uh color there
Oh so many choices. Uh, should we do youtuber here?
No, no, no, no, go back back back back shall we i'm your good call now try a new style
fabulous
What you can't even do like green or orange or blue or yellow or teal or anything
Well, like pink or anything
I like that
All right, let's go
Looks good
Again, wow like the genie break out of your bottle
It's me
Let's move on. So where to first?
You want to go?
Mickey just wave like this
Can I walk?
How are you?
Hey mickey
Mickey mom right to meet you
It's origin. It's original mickey my friends autographs today, but i've been so busy with the toontown mayor election
But I have to get in the camps
Do you think you could ask donald to sign this book for me? I do appreciate it
Let's get a signature from donald. Wow to talk to you
See, this is how we talk around here by walking wave. Hello
wave goodbye
How do I walk?
Hey, I better show you how to get around
Say you're in luck
Anything this shiny's gotta be good after all look at me
To walk forward act like you got no strings raise your arm up like this
Hey, you're a natural move your arm bit right you go right
Fun, huh? Now you're getting it
What talent to stop and look around just scoot your hand all the way left or what?
And be amazed
What you're doing it's like you've been walking all your family
I I kind of didn't catch any of that
Oh hold what I just adore Mickey mouse good
I want to go explore disneyland
Easy slow down. What are you bringing somebody? I colored it to make it easy see
autograph donald
Peanut butter pizza. That's not real. Oh, look at this. This is downtown, uh, disney
Just like a random stray wandering kid
There he is donald
Fetch quest
What oh goodbye donald it was very nice to see you
Okay, how much magic we got guess what that reaches the top
What's going on here when it does all right back to mickey?
There he is
How did he get there so fast? He's a magical character
He's been wanting an autograph collection and I thought it might be nice to help him get started
Do you think you could bring the book to him? Just checking to see if we've lost anybody any viewers?
I mean, I figure like it's at this. I mean, I guess people still here
Ah
For what so long thanks for giving the book to goofy big bits. Holy shit
Thank you. G y h d h f e for the 50 dollars
Jeremy, can you pretend you're playing kingdom hearts and and start fighting people with keyblades?
That's not this is not kingdom hearts. It has no keyblades in it. Like no
Thank you for 50 dollars
All right. Now what are you doing?
I didn't gotta go find goofy. It's like skiing
I like I have to get it going. We gotta get on one ride
Watch out for the car
I want to get on one ride
This is the intermission portion of the screen
Hopefully on a dowsing rod. All right, come on. Just walk
I'm not even taking to the sites
There he is
Howdy sport i'm goofy. I don't believe we've met before sign that for me
Gorge, thanks. Did he look strange to anybody else?
He looks strange. What what makes him look so strange?
That's okay
Take your toy
Hugs are forever
Jesus christ
Holy shit goofy
You gotta slow down
He was like
All right. Give me all right
All right. No more. Let's get out of here
All right. I want an autograph
One goofy autograph
Oh god
My hair my hair started to like mad up
This is really bad
My hair is matting
I have to get like a brush
What are you doing? You're goofy
Goodbye pal. I wonder where i just got 25 000 for that
back to mickey
Can we ride a ride or eat foods or something?
Can I do anything besides just walk around and get autographs from all the characters?
Even kids wouldn't think this was very fun
I want to go on like space mountain. All right. It's my turn my turn
Hey me my turn me
Yes, you can practice taking a picture of me
Take my picture. Okay. Okay. Sure like to hear about
Hey, this is it gotta get it don't panic hand up any hand and take it
I can't reach that
I can't what do we grab it and take it?
This is cruel
Okay. Now point to what you got and hold your hand there until you got it. You got it
Yeah, yeah, yes to take a picture got it. Hey, what's going on guys? Welcome to my youtube video. I'm here
With mickey mouse at the magic kingdom
How do I do the picture?
Did you give me that back you were gonna say?
Now you have something in your right hand. You need to use your left hand to move about see
How do you take the picture
Hold out your arm to take a photo
Can you do this for me because I can't I can't seem to figure it out the fuck did you say okay?
I'll pose and you can take my picture. I'll pose
Sure
What who took that photo I thought I was supposed to do it
With that camera in no time
Well, that's one for the album
You know a few albums to get started with but I know there's more out there
Maybe we can get them from the shops
Come on, you broke ass game
Guess you're a little shy
Just put it away. Hey pal. Could you help me out again?
I'm making a photo album for minnie, but I still need pictures of goofy and donald
Would you mind finding goofy and taking his picture for me just bring them all over here just call them on phone
You have a mickey cell phone. They sell it at fucking walmart. I know you have one
Okay, give me an autograph, too. I'm one more
Gosh, I'd be happy to sign that for you
You know, it's a really really good skill
Those disney actors in that suit with the big oven mitt gloves that can actually
write cursive like that
Oh, okay
He took my pen
I'm getting a lot of personal time with mickey. This kid's been waiting in line for so long
This kid there's a kid sitting there for like 20 minutes when we do all kinds of like dance routines
Like it's like can I please have a turn?
No, you can't
I gotta figure out how to use this camera
Where'd it go?
All right, get goofy's picture
Goofy's picture
Somebody look it up. How do I take a picture with the fucking cell phone? Where are you taking me?
You can ignore the story and go for a ride. I can
Can I go for a ride? All right, let's go for a ride. Fuck. Who cares about taking pictures of goofy and donald and shit
Let's go
I can just go for a ride
Where okay there it is. There it is up there
That's uh, that's the magic castle
Splash fountain we're going to splash fountain
Don't do that again
I'm documenting everything
What ride should I go on splash mountain? No, who cares about anything else with splash mountain?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what take you on want to take a photo?
Did I take it?
Take photo take the picture
This kid this kid's I
There it is. I can't wait
This is all I care about
Is just getting on that splash mountain ride. Nothing else matters
Here's a line. Here's a little magic for you. If you want to skip to the menu, you can just call out xbox
Try it nice and clear now
xbox
fast travel
Splash mountain
I'm already here. All right. How about where's the line to get on this?
I think
Work yet gotta go get the right album first. I saw some in the shops go get one
Oh shut up
All right, get away from beast. It's nice. There is this line
Just cut everybody in line
Will you look at that want to see where it goes
Yeah, that's a there we go. This is a ride
the book the
Is this it?
We actually get to do something. Holy shit
Why am I on drugs?
Turn left lean left right to avoid bumping into things
Is this a ride at actual disneyland?
I still get right space splash mountain
No, this is not a ride
Sorry about that say are you ready to get the slopes?
I'm tight. This wind will blow you
Jesus
Goofy, why don't you take a kid to this dangerous part of the park?
Oh, look out. We're just gonna go to the summit eight-year-old
Fucking destroyed
How I jump over that
I just want to cross for snowball
Too fast too fast too fast too fast
This is long
Oh goofy got goofy got hit by that I saw that but still goofy got destroyed
Be careful goofy don't take your advice
How long is this?
This is longer than any part like ditty con racing mario kart level
It's not okay goofy
When we're done, you're gonna get arrested
Boy, I thought he had the power or go ahead with a big heart
Sir, you're under fucking arrest for endangering a child. It's quiet here. There ain't any
Continue
Return to park
We're not doing that again. I want to ride splash mountain and we're moving on
I'm gonna take a water break and come back. We've got something really really really really really interesting
Oh, it's gonna be a good one
Let me come back. This is gonna be a really good one
This is a nice little relaxing walk around his new land and have some fun and then we get back
I've got a good one for you. I'm gonna go get a the thing for my hair. I'm gonna splash some water into my mouth
But i'm gonna ride space mountain first
Is the whole thing actually here
Will help us find characters attractions shops just about anything we want except secrets, of course
So you got lots of choices where you want to go first?
All right, where's splash mountain where's the entrance to splash mountain
Did I miss it?
I just want to rise splash mountain. That's all I care about. I don't do anything else so many people in this park
It's right there. Yeah, that was the yeti one. Where is it?
It's like right here
What was the line?
Is this the line no, that's not it
I I don't understand this walking thing just like what the hell is this
It's right in front of me
Have to use my legs
Not your wife
Where it's right next to me. Where's the line to splash mountain?
I can't fast travel to splash mountain. I'm already here
Where are my parents?
I'm walking around in a circle around splash mountain
Splash mountain is in the other side of the park
xbox
fast travel
frontier land
Live that's thunder mountain. That's not splash mountain
I want splash mountain
It's right here
Manga s
This is i'm right next to me
I'm gonna wander around until I find the fucking entrance to splash mountain
It's not right there
What the hell is this giant mountain over here then?
Go to the disney website and look at the actual map
Go back xbox
fast travel
frontier land
Go to entrance
That's not even in the game. I'm looking it up. I'm looking up. Where is splash mountain?
Where is splash mountain?
Where's splash mountain?
It's a disney land
That the wealth is embracing the characters it is in
Where is it located?
I know I know. Oh my god. Where is what part of disneyland?
You would think that a google search of where the fuck is splash mountain and disneyland would come up with an answer
It's the first like five responses are it's a ride at disneyland. It's also in tokyo
xbox
fast travel
critter
county
Splash mountain
I've been to disneyland once you think I know where splash mountain is
Some of you are I got a season pass up there every weekend
portless today
Continue. Oh, how big is the door? The door must be uh, five foot ten
So that means he must be down break the door is the door handle is seven or two feet up the ground
Do it do it do it. Here's the handle do it
Do it
I want to go I want to ride splash mountain
All right, let's go
All right, i'm gonna clean as I go
This next one is gonna be fucked
Clean as I go clean as I go
Why is it xbox opening xbox live is opening a bunch of shit in the background?
Okay, I gotta clean as I go. I'm not fucking around to do things because there are so many games here
That I will lose track
And i'm not gonna remember which ones we played. This is like fucking
All right, get rid of this one. I'm never opening that game ever again. I'm gonna give it to probably some fucking nice
Or nephew or whatever
Harry potter. I might actually go back and beat harry potter. Let's put motion sports back in
Okay, that's that
What else do I got here?
This is harry potter
Hold on to that one
That's good to go
the biggest loser
All right. Where's that? Where's that disc? Clean as you go
We're playing like 10 of these today
biggest loser
Clean as you go
Jillian michaels fitness
There it is
You idiot that just went on the fucking vr hits it didn't it? No, it didn't thank god
Okay
now
That leaves us with
After I come back and get some water. I would stick around
Because coming up next is fucking hulk hogan's main event
See you in a minute
All right
What do you say we go? I just gotta slam the big water
Should be good for a little while longer
Let's get it going
Hydra, I just did that's why i'm coming back from uh drinking some water
back on camera
Brushed my hair
see
By panic button studios hulk hogan's main event this game. Oh, by the way sucks. It's like riga. It's got really great reviews
Hold your arm about to navigate the menu swipe towards about to select the menu. Yes
You're not currently signed in with the gamer profile. You're not be able to save game progress and earn achievements
All right create a wrestler
create a wrestler
Let's go body
body shape
thinner
Should I make them thin?
or fat
Can you do fat and thin?
I mean you gotta make a fat guy, right?
All right, a little stronger
Not fatter just as big as you can make
Fatter done good
And let's see
Hulk can I take a picture of my own face?
masher
Chins
I think kind of has to be chins
there's also
Three, uh chins. No, I mean like it has to be chins
Take the facial hair off and that's the dumb thing that I did her for like a week ago
All right, that looks good
How do I get you my ass? All right body hair
Waxed. Yeah, that looks good
hair
bald
No, no, no, no
Trouble stripe trouble
I don't know not very many options
Facial hair none
That's better
It still looks like this facial hair there. What is I said none. Why do I have?
That looks good
I think that's good. I don't want any tattoos. I don't have any
Ear
I can't I have to use my hand
Uh shirt
Let's go up here
Uh, let's go with pants. What do I want with pants?
That's fine
I could put a hat on too. I like my hats
That's all I can do. That's fine. I'll put on links with jesse pinkman
That was good
All right. Here we go game modes great wrestler extra
game modes game mode
career mode
Bring it on hogan
I'll tell you what hokomania is the game now and i'm just going to keep on playing hulk hogan
I could have done a little bit. I could have tried a little harder for hulk hogan there, but no
Okay, dude, you ready? It's all good, man
Seriously, bro, you gotta bring your a game now
You know that contest hulk hogan's running
What about it?
The winner gets a wrestling contract
I shot the big time with the hulkster himself in your corner
Sweet, let's do this. He's about to punch me in the face. He's taking on the competition
backyard
360 pounds and ready for his first match he is
Is that that's my name
It's time to show off some signature moves perform the pose indicated by the icon the fast you fall off the low points
This is like a dance game
What I didn't do anything i'm gonna if this is a dance game i'm gonna laugh so hard
Dude, it's just doing it for me now. Why what's going on?
Your local favorite
That's me that's me cooking the burger that's that's me
Why can't I jump in as me?
Talking two wrestlers trade serious hits for the enjoyment of the bloodthirsty crowd block or dodge your opponent's strikes then unleash your own attacks
Okay
Use your hands to block or lean to evade your opponent's punches and headbutts dodge to dodge a kick jump
After a solid block counter-attack use your head either arm or your legs to attack your opponent
Can use my head
Oh
This game just sucks
Folks cuz it's time for her to sing
at the back of the box
There's chairs. Hold on. I gotta wait for the chairs your opponent is stunned time to show off your slamming skills
Thrust both arms out to grab next raise both arms to lift your helpless victim over your head
Once you've opponent over your head perform the indicated slam move
That was a lame throw
Get him grab him
He grabs opponents
This game is fucking awful. I would rather walk here on disneyland get autographed
His opponent is slammed to the mat
He's a feet of strength
Do it go back to disney get autographed
No, i'm giving it a chance. I gotta get the chair first and then he's firing up
Look every game has to take the 30 minutes. You know, that's the rule. That is a very strict rule
I don't make that rule
I don't make that rule hong kong in the corner with the chair. I thought I had to win
All the way before hong kong cared about me
First soften your opponent up a bit use your arms and legs to elbow leg drop club or sit on him
Reach out with both arms to get a grip then lean left or lean right to subdue
It's just qte's it's just quick time events the game it does
Cover him up will he break free? Oh, he's gonna knock me out. He's gonna keep me in the head like five times
I'm putting this disc
Somehow this way lean this way
Hogan what do you mean by this?
I understand how this is happening wrong
It's been three seconds
Is this a 10 count?
Uh, it's the match i've won the match it's been like 12 seconds
really
Dude that was epic. Thanks, man. You think we can win?
Yeah, we can win son. Think positive. That was epic
I'll take the same damn photos. Don't think
It's been 30 minutes it hasn't it's been like 12
360 pounds and ready for the paid
I'm sorry. No one more chance
That was not a look at me thread the game on screen thread the game on screen
I definitely like my shredder up here
I think you can
Shred the disc on screen
All right, let's go. Let me just beat him quick
No tutorials. No, nothing. Let's go
Dialogue is broken. Anyways, here we go
I can't take that one anymore. That game was terrible
I ain't doing that one shred it shred it shred shred shred shred
I can't
I don't know if I can shred it. What if I can't spread it? What if it's not allowed in my shredder?
Oh fuck I have to play this uh, which one of these do I want to play this is this is where it gets hard
All right
I think it's time to bust it out
I think so
Time to play wipe out
Shred this one, too
I'm just gonna shred like six games at the end of this frame
By the way, it's still got two fucking full horror games
You might be seeing those tomorrow
depends
Wipe out god that whole koken game was just awful
There's no redeeming qualities at all. The harry potter game was actually pretty
Pretty legit
I'm gonna say harry potter anytime anywhere abc
All right, this is an abc show
harry potter
and
When I got scanned that first time in jillian michael
What what if we can play? Oh when I threw for a touch down
Oh
I could win this
I could beat this I would destroy this course
There's no way I would ever accept falling down
If I got on to wipe out I would I would not fall down one time. That is a 100 guarantee
Hold your hands over the button to begin the game. There we go wipe out in the zone
Who is it?
Is it tended ragun?
It's me. You don't know me
It's me
So it is david
david's the uh the console
I don't know who the fuck that is
Who are these people?
No, we're gonna use my avatar
my avatar
hard
I'm not fucking around
Oh, I I can't I have to actually go in order
This would be a good warm-up. All right, i'm feeling it
Why don't you just say something doesn't seem to be about jim henson. What does that do wipe out?
Baby mode. I tried to do hard
You saw that I tried
All right to wipe out it's a little game full of highs
Let's just hope the highs are really high and the lows. It's just more fun for all of us that way
All right, let's see what the qualifiers looking like for arkansas. This is an easy one
It should be a walk in the park for him johnny. This is the doorknob everybody's favorite giant hammer behind every door
You have to run past it and then the wall provides the pocket
Playing on like spider-man the big balls
The bouncy ball along with their loving friend this is first person game or is this like a sidescroller?
It's a muddy muddy playground. How do I traverse this?
We're here with oh
Let's just say contestant number one shall we ready to play jump up
Yay
We're going already
Shit
I didn't know we were going that fast
Or I get it I get I know I got hit
Oh shit, how do I grab these what do I do? Oh they come up they jump they hit you
All right, we're good
All right, i'm good
It's really really fucked up
No
Of course they played that one without the one where I bounced around like a dickhead from five times
Damn it. I don't understand
Dark in here, huh?
So far in the round. This is how things stand. I'm doing fine. I'm winning
Next up the eliminator the eliminator
Oh, but I've seen this before
You gotta just get
Yeah, bad our first runner-up is at the top dab with your avatar. I promise I won't when you're ready to snapshot
That no don't do that. Just let's go
You know the sweeper arm really is one of my screws on kids who didn't even try
I don't even get a chance to continue
shit
The wipeout zone, I don't know. I remember I don't remember this thing
About zone. I like it so much. Oh, I do know what this is. I like what I see before I even see it
Uh blades of fury. I'm a big fan. Welcome to the super mario 64 first bowser level
This is the screwdriver stay on the rotating log or this is the crank shaft all those
Let's see if we can get all fucking eight red coins it says snapshot. Oh, you don't understand here we go
That was horrible shit
All right
Oh, it has to move. All right. Go what mimic the pose?
stop
Go you idiot
I win. I win. I won it. I did it. It's like final jeopardy. I got all the points at the end
number one
$1,000 give me the check the contestants is that the whole game?
That's the whole that's it that's the whole game no, that was easy that was easy
I just I don't what I have to play all three of these
Let's go
Beat this game i'm not gonna beat this game. Ah, holy shit how that happened
Damn it. Oh damn. I can't I can't it's too much energy. You take too much energy to do this
Hurry up
Hurry up and go
What is hard like I gotta start back there again
I'm shredding this too
The
Why are you not running I did it I did it
All right, watch it watch out I can get it ready one two three
This contestant's got the eye of the tiger jump lost and I can't jump my my legs are cement right now
I had a chance to get done
I need like a fucking personal ac unit
But in his defense
I did it
All right. I'm not gonna mess this next one up
I'm ready for this one
This is the one we just had to jump
You just have to jump
That's it
Nothing else
No, i'm not ready
I am not ready
Wait
What what do I have to do?
It's too much to do that it's too much to jump in the fucking place in your room no
I'm gonna have to like you drink a bread bowl
This one is most intense of the whole night this is more intense than the first exercise one
I gotta find a way
To like make it so I like going to jump
Can I get like a pair of shoes and just hold me like this?
Do I have any shoes up here?
I have to have like shoes
Stay right hold on
For being trapped in a video game
It works
That's fucked up the thing's tilted
What am I supposed to do about this shit what a broke ass game
I'm gonna press the button it's time to put in a different one
This one's got much better traction. I've heard i'm of course talking
Anytime anywhere abc about wipeout free
Not wipeout in the zone
Is this the same game?
Just packaged differently
It's not right
It's not
Welcome back to the new season of wipeout last season broke every record we have and look at these graphics. They're so much better
Actually the animated bit not like avatars
Is shock full of devious surprises it appears the contestants are ready to go down there
Let's take a look here. They are a whole new batch of fresh willing victims. We have kids now
It's like disney in the morning 3d animation
Looks like they're off to a good start, but it's abc so make sense. Oh, that was a close one
They say she's never like a pop patrol animator
It might actually be
Hey, here's where it all went all right, what's this a cuter and possibly sweeter side of wipeout?
Yes, that's a no
Our most spectacular season ever welcome to wipe out three
Greetings salutations and hello there children ballsy welcome back to a new season of wipeout
Now with new and improved motion controls this season there are two
There are two what
You cut off what why is it so much better than the last one?
better motion controls better game
Shred this one
We hope you have a wipeout in the zone, but it's not a very good game. This is a new one
We hope you shred wipeout in the zone wave. Hello
Better most controls my ass
It's me. Hello
The same shit happened in the last one
I am signed in what are you talking about?
Man, you great job. They haven't really done anything yet play single player wipeout party
single player
Uh contestant shop
home
Contestants
Pick me
timothy bright, uh
I
Let's do it let's go he's got a red shirt on
So
Hello and welcome to wipeout it's freezing out there johnny you bet it is and you'll be happy to know i'm wearing
faux fur designer boxer
Not really tis the season of deck the balls santa promised to bring me lots of wipeouts this year john
He would have promised you anything to get you off his lap time to go a wassling through our qualifier
When looking at this holiday course skip our contestants are in for one jump when you're ready
Let's see if it is better. Uh, this this seems a little better players off
stop
That is some angry aerosol
So much better
Punishing johnny
It is crunch time. What a cracker. Did you see that rat? I think i'm just tired
i'm tired
It was harry potter that fucking ruined me that check point's in the bank. I want to see this one again
Little boy blue
Legendary what even happened?
of some journal
On purpose
Accessorizing with a brand new ramp
It's for you in the stomach johnny this player is a real belly glutton for punishment
Harry Potter was all the expelliarmus and the book of the medicus and sugar. Why not just do that?
Thanks, they would have missed my whole run don't blink
We get a raid
Thanks tyler for the raid
Like 300 people just came over here from tyler tyler
Tyler tyler mcvicker
Thanks a lot. Welcome
Time for a fortnight dance. That's what I do every time I get a raid
I do a fortnight dance
And at the end of the deck of walls qualifier here the standing as you see we're doing some connect. It's connect weekend here
Pick a robot. Oh, no, that's who's moving on
What what's going on? What?
Why does everybody say that? Why is that? Why was that not funny? I didn't do anything. It might look tacky as a lawn decoration
But his route jump up to start
All right, here we go
I'm gonna try to get this first try ready. Check this out
What does this mean?
What is this trying to tell me to do?
Am I taking a fucking left on a bike? I don't get it. I don't understand
Projectile
Clean up aisle two fifth ring is in our player's hand
technical foul
And off goes our contestant johnny
That is some angry aerosol
I'm right here
That was I had to qualify look at these fucking outfits
Holy shit, you can see back here. They're doing me proud johnny
Let's check out somebody game show after round two object the balls
By the way, one of these game show games was insanely expensive
How why why would a robot be allowed to do this?
Seems unfair
Do you ever look at the bottom left?
Round three you haven't been bumped and pushed this much since black 10 bucks. No, it was 50 over here john
Actually may have been 60 reindeer games. These are not you know what they say. It is this easy. I don't like this one
This one feels like an ipad game and our contestant feels like those runners wipe out runner
Up and get sprayed from head to toe
I thought this I don't feel like there's any danger here one two second ring for you
And the fifth ring is in our player's hand. He's looking sharp with a shiny new ring
first try
Somebody just made a strong case to be number one in the wipeout draft
Perfection that's how you do it playa. You just got your first dollars. Nice
When there is a clown nose
I don't know. What's the what's the wipeout clown nose for?
Our course really put the deck in round three of deck the balls and this is generic rock
It's the way the two announcers
are playing
And they made it all the way to the finals
It seems a little weird that the both the announcers
All right
Coming up next. It's our festive wipeout zone. I can't wait to see our contestants fair on this holiday course partner
It'll stuff their stockings johnny jump up player
I'm right. I haven't moved at all
What oh that didn't lose
I think it's supposed to be parts of
Slow down
technical foul
Oh our player gets punched don't do that on an empty stomach
And the fifth ring is in our player's hand
Oh shit, oh
All right. Whatever. Is that all you got?
This is a checkpoint and keeps their eye on the prize
kids be done
It's time for final jeopardy congratulations you finished the merry wipeout zone
Oh, I won
Give me that check
It's not working. I'm not gonna do it. I want to floss so bad, but i'll turn the camera off to do it
Well, that does it for myself john anderson and vanessa lachey. All right, this one sucks saying good night and big balls
Go back to hard hogwarts
Maybe i'll finish on hogwarts
Two more two more movies, right?
Yeah, this one sucks
There's so many more
I don't even know how i'm gonna play that we're gonna have to have a string of just game shows
Three books four movies. Oh, that's right. There's two final movies. You're right
This is discount splatoon
Yeah, it is
It kind of is step right up it's the main attraction the main menu
All right, let's do another one
There was the wipeouts
Well, the first one was pretty good there. They weren't bad
I could see myself being young and full of energy wanting to play for like 12 hours
I'm gonna give you guys a choice
Okay, but what i'm gonna do for the last one for tonight. We'll be back tomorrow with the same thing
Oh, I forgot there's a bunch over here
I think
We're gonna have to start with this one tomorrow. Yeah, that's we're starting with this one tomorrow. Ah, there's so many good ones
Oh, these ones look good, too
No, I can't like these. I gotta I gotta have like some fucking heavy hitters tomorrow
I gotta have a few heavy hitters tomorrow
how about
No, I can't I can't
I'm gonna give you a choice
Finish harry potter or who wants to be a millionaire? I'm gonna give you a poll
Uh, do I even need a poll? This is like that's a trillion people are saying millionaire
Holy fuck
Uh
It's gonna be a millionaire
It's gonna be who wants to be a millionaire
I mean, i've never seen that many people write the same thing
ever
Do oh do a poll you want me to do a poll just for shits and let me go get some water
All right
Here's a poll i'll be right back last glass of water and then i'm gonna do one or two more and we're out of here
I'll be right back
Yeah, who wants to be a millionaire?
What's going on?
What's going on? What are you doing?
Where's the poll? I don't see
No, who wants to be a millionaire has 70 percent of the vote
Thanks for voting
We'll close it out. We're gonna we're gonna chill
It's been five hours 20 minutes. We'll probably close it out around six
But it depends on how long you know, gotta give at least 30 minutes
Who's the host?
Oh, yeah, uh regis
It might be is it regis felton
Or what's the the who's that lady?
I don't think it's gonna be regis
Why would this be a connect game? I was trying to figure that out
Do you just sit here and sit pretend to sit in the chair?
Should I go get my chair?
Well, this is saying that you don't win any money. It's just a joke
You are not recognized I think the xbox I really do think needs to cool off
This thing is chugging right now
Don't ever play connect for more than five or six hours with no 360
That's probably going to be a like a hot plate mark on my desk
Full voice control. Okay
All right. That's this. This would be fun
Who wants to be a millionaire?
That's me
Who's that? There's no host
This is not how this works. Who wants to be a millionaire?
10 questions to answer in round one
The questions are worth anything from one hundred dollars to ten thousand dollars
But you won't know how much until after you answer each question
What let's see the question categories
And now we'll give them a shuffle
This is stupid. What then what is this knockoff millionaire? You can use the jump the question lifeline two times in this round
You won't win money for the question, but you can stay in the game
You can ask a question by selecting an answer with your hand
You can also answer a question by reading the answer out loud
This is not what I remember
Audience, are you ready? Oh, no, we should go back to harry potter
Oh, I chose wrong. I chose wrong
Famous for the life-saving maneuver named after him henry j heimlich was what type of doctor?
Stomach doctor
God gynecological oncologist is that your final answer
No pediatric orthopedist
Pediatric orthopedist
Is that your final answer?
No, thoracic surgeon
Thoracic surgeon is that your final answer?
Yes
A manner of speaking
Do these slang phrases means to contribute money to a special collection feed the kitty?
the chicken
Ride the pony is that your final answer? Yes
Yes
Answer
You don't uh, it should be the one that was feed
You want a thousand dollars
Hey, where do you see what we got tomorrow?
Do you want to see what?
Yes
I'd like to see what we got going on. This is not happening tonight. This is happening tomorrow. So you
Show up tomorrow if you want to see some fucking family view
10 questions to answer in round one the questions are worth anything from
100 to 10 000, but you won't know how much until after you answer each question
Let's see the question categories
And now we'll give them a shuffle skip intro
Here's the first question culinary humor. Let's try this one featured on a jokey apron
Dijon vu is defined as the feeling that you've had this what before ketchup mustard
maple syrup mustard mustard
salsa
Mustard is that your final answer? Yes
John
All right. Let me try to like win one of these one game. Is that okay? I just want to win one
I'm gonna do that. This is what I would do if I was on the game show, you know
You gotta you gotta like look confident and move around and shit like i'd be like going this shit
Bangle spice aptly features a drawing of what animal on its box penguin
Tiger it's tiger. Is that your final answer? Yes. It's yes
It's a tiger bangle is a tiger
What was with the incredibly difficult question for last time
Well, it's because they jumped the the questions jumped around randomly. I don't like this new format. Here's the third question
Goody dalton brown. It's back global event known as earth hour asks people around the planet to do what?
Food networks give it a look for world peace
Stop eating
Turn off their lights
outside
Turn off your lights
Is that your final answer?
Yes
Walk outside
It's earth time. Let's have question number four. It's not even mimicking my movements
This one's what is how is this even connect this again? I can talk to it uses the slogan eating good in the neighborhood
Eating good in the neighborhood tgi fridays
That's applebees
Then again applebees eating good in the neighborhood is that which one of these is tgi friday's applebees
Is it applebees?
It's applebees. Is that your final? Yes, sir
It is yes
Eating good in the neighborhood with our riblets
Welcome thousand dollars
We're at restaurant. I don't think does that restaurant still exist
I don't I can't remember the last time I ate any food from applebees the best-selling history of the american west is titled bury
My heart where at wounded knee?
promontory point
wounded knee by little bacon
in dodge city
wounded knee at wounded knee
Is that your final answer?
Yes
Cheater
No, I know what that is because of and ninja turtles for turtles in time for the superintendent entertainment system
This is the level where you bought the prehistoric another prehistoric wherever it was
It was bury my shell at wounded knee. It was that this it was something like that
That's why I know what it is
The oldest nfl game in history the 1967 championship ice bowl game was played where lambo field?
cleveland municipal stadium
fenway park
Wrigley field
Is that your final answer? No?
Lambo field is that your final answer?
Yes
He nailed it. He got it. He he got it
He got it
Here's question just a hobby. So am I about to win the bucket to win a million dollars
What where's a million dollars?
Where's a million dollars his hobby a cruciverbalist would flip to what part of a newspaper crossword puzzle
sports box scores
horoscope
stock quotes
Probably horoscope
a cruciverbalist
cruciverbalist
What are you pausing for resume crossword puzzle, is that your final answer?
Yes
Cheating cheating cheating cheat. My chat is over here guys
Cheater cheater cheater cheater. I'm looking over here at at the view count
The view counts over here and like my my other fucking uh streamlabs
By definition a doula provides assistance during which of these events a childbirth permits for ceremony
exorcism doula acupuncture session
What about the modula oblongata?
doula
probably
Childbirth, is that your final answer?
I don't know
Let me think about it
No
i'm gonna say
bar mitzvah
anti-cheat spam
Get that anti-cheat out of here. I want to be able to see what people say about the stream. All right, uh
I would say
If it were up to me
Childbirth is probably what it is. Is that your final answer?
No
exorcism
Is that your final answer? Yes
Yes
Motherfuckers, you fucking made me choose the wrong one
Thanks for playing who wants to be a millionaire
I just like took out my fucking wall
Do you want to play again? Yes, and this time it's gonna be on my own. Yes
I'm gonna stand back here
In fact, i'm gonna you're gonna know i'm not gonna cheat
Once i can't do that
To be a millionaire
I'll just look this way. Are you going to be able to answer in round one?
The question is worth anything from 100. I can hear i've got a wireless setup today
I've got completely wireless until after you answer each question
Let's see the question categories
Skip
And now we'll give them a shuffle
Skip intro
Here's the first question
What is the english?
What the fuck
I can't see you. I can't see you. That makes no sense
Look, i'm over here
Why the fucking are not see me?
Can you see me now?
I'm just trying to relax
Hello
Continue, please
I just walked in the fucking grab the translation of the latin phrase bonafide to tell the truth
in a happy way
in good faith
With strong force
Is that your final answer?
Yes
See
What?
Bonafide like with like you you're going for it
Many games left to play
I will fucking do this
Do you want to play again?
Yes
So who wants to be a millionaire? I'm just gonna fucking meditate back here
You have 10 questions to answer in round one. The questions are worth anything from 100 to 10 000
But you won't know how much until after you answer each question
Let's see the question categories
I can't see the question category. So sorry that's not gonna happen
You can use the jump the question lifeline two times in this round
You won't win any money for the question, but you can stay in the game
You can answer a question by selecting an answer with your hand
I just go skip intro
Here's the first question
I mean, I can't
Is famous for developing a high-end variety of what sunglasses?
drum cymbals
stereo speakers
motor scooter
Repeat the question
Do you want to jump the question? Yes
You use your first lifeline and jump the question
The question was worth five hundred dollars
time for question number two
As its literal title suggests stuck on you stars gregg kinnear and matt damon as an affable pair of what figure skaters?
conjoined twins
stock brokers
catholic priests
Conjoined twins, is that your final answer? Yes
Why could you put that on when I was in the middle of how could you put it on? I kind of turn it off
I tried to turn it off three times
Slash emote only slash emote only off slash emote off
What superhero might have gone by the name homo farious superman
spider-man
iron man
I don't know what a farious is they didn't teach us that in fucking boomer school
farious
Iron man, is that your final answer? Fe is iron. Yes
Fe is iron
Yes, I did it on my own on my own
Fe is iron iron man farious. I did it on my own
You can't call me a cheater
Hey, put your fucking 3d glasses on for this
A 2011 elitist series features what noted tough guys love of pigeon racing hulk hogan
jean-claude van damme
bernard carick
mike tyson
I have no idea
I'm gonna just say take a wild guess i'm gonna turn this boy. So, you know, i'm not cheating
Mike tyson, is that your final answer? Yes
I did it
$10 000
It's question number five
Indie film of 2008 the christian-themed drama fireproof stars one 80s teen star. This is my fire logs
Malcolm jamal warner
Michael j. Fox coming in there i'm coming over there
Get your fucking 3d glasses on for this one
Uh, who is it?
Kirk cameron, is that your final answer?
Yes
This is question number six
The next question is worth one of these amounts
Which of these objects weighs roughly 45.52 carats air force one
Eiffel tower
Plymouth rock hope diamond hope diamond
It's a hope diamond
Hope diamond is that your final answer? No
Air force one is that your final answer? I'm getting lied to no
No
Hope diamond. I had it right the first time. Is that your final answer?
Yes
Three thousand dollars
Here's all right, jim. What are you doing here?
Uh, be careful the very way. Yeah, the thing I know about dogs is there what's going on neighbor?
The classic novel the great gatsby j gatsby often uses what nickname to address others full sport
Captain buddy boy a
Old sport is that your final answer?
I'm trying to see lead on out of the caprio's face
he goes
A lot. He has like the drink and he goes
Yes old sport
No, no, he goes
Little fella. Is that your final answer?
No, hey little fella. Is that your final answer? Yes
Yes
Names left to play. Do you want to play again?
So who wants to be a millionaire?
Who have 10 questions to answer in round one?
The questions are worth anything from one hundred dollars to ten thousand dollars
But you won't know how much until after you answer each question
Okay, let's see the question categories
And now we'll give them a shuffle skip
Skip
Skip intro. Here's the first question
Never eat shredded wheat is a mnemonic for remembering what compass directions?
astrological signs
food groups
blood types
Food groups. Is that your final answer?
Yes
You fucking idiot
Get over here
He was doing he was just stupid yes
He's going off the deep end. Well, why don't I have like this fucking standing honestly? It was something to lean on
10 questions to answer in round one
The questions are worth anything from one hundred dollars to ten thousand dollars
But you won't know how much until after you answer each question
Let's see the question categories
And now give them a shuffle
Excuse me guys
You can use the jump
Times in this round win any money for the question, but you can stay in the game
You can answer a question by selecting an answer with your hand
Skip intro answer. Here's the first question
The misquoted the wall street line
Read is good actually contains what phrase after the first word for lack of a better word
Believe it or not and trust me on this
in all of its forms
Those are all just trump sings
Oh for lack of a better word, believe it or not. That's your final. Trust me on this
No
Greed and trust me on this. It's good
Greed believe it or not. It's good
Greed for lack of a better word
For lack of a better word is no your final answer
No
In all of its forms, is that your final answer?
Yes
That was incorrect. Thanks for playing who wants to be a millionaire?
Do you want to play again?
Yes
To the last round and i'm believing
Wants to be a millionaire
Of 10 questions you have to be careful though. The questions are worth anything from 100 to 10 000
But you won't know how much until after you answer each question
Let's see the question categories
And now we'll give them a shovel skip intro. Here's the first question
Yeah, it's something to lean on actually to be honest
What scientific work begins with the sentence? I have never seen francis crick in a modest mood a brief history of time
coming of age in samoa
the double helix
The interpretation of dreams
I don't know
Oh, sorry time to go home you lost
Uh, i'm gonna say yeah george i'm gonna say
George i'm gonna say uh the double heels is that your final answer?
Yes
That's not what I said george
That one doesn't count
That one doesn't count. Thanks for playing wants to be a millionaire. I wish I had fucking muffets back here
I would just do a whole thing with this
I said, yeah, it's because I said that double helix and then I said yes. I was paying attention
Bala koala gave 50 dollars. You got the i've been dropping hundreds of dollars the last few streams
You have 10 questions to answer in round one bala koala 50 bucks germa
Can we see the mirror on the ceiling you installed to see and cheat off the chat?
That's my phone until after you answer each question
Let's see. Thank you for the 50 dollars though for real. Holy shit
Skip intro i'm gonna get this one the first question. I this is the stupid new format
This is that was dumb dumb format on how I met your mother
What actor provides the voice I didn't watch the show I didn't watch this fucking show bob saget
It was bob saget
Kelsey grammar. It was bob saget. Okay, I know that it's bob saget. I know that final answer. Yes. I know that one
tim allen
Seven dollars time for question number two
a scenic setting
What is the main setting of the bill murray comedy classic meatballs college campus?
army base
restaurant
Submarine
I think that's a submarine
Or army base. Is that your final answer? No, no, no, no, no
No
That's stripes
Summer camp is that your final answer? Yes
That's uncomfortable i'm not doing it here's the third question
See for cheating fiona and funky donkey are both limited edition nail polish shades promoting what 2010 film iron man 2
how to train your dragon
prince of persia
I know this one because that is a shrek. That's a shrek reference. That's shrek forever after
Shrek forever after is I know that your final answer
Yes
fiona dunk dunk donkey
If I had said iron man 2
I wouldn't have even known anything about the answer to you
Let's have question number four. What is the name of the family featured in the long-running comic strip for better or for worse?
I think I know this sanger
montgomery paterson paterson
Is that your final answer? I think it is
That's paterson. Yes
I knew that I said that really quickly without anybody's help
I mean boomer. How am I cheater? I said it. I said it
instantly
Instantly it's question number five
The guy said the question
Instantly I said it for his masterpiece 100 years of what agony?
confusion
solitude solitude
It's solitude solitude. Is that your final answer?
Yes
This is fine art time to lose can you guys hear me can you hear me is worth one of these amounts
I'm kind of got the circulation to my brain by doing this. I just stand up
Black and gray are the only colors present in which of these famous paintings christina's world
the scream
The starry night. It's not either one. It's not the scream and it's not starry night. Is that your final answer?
No
No, it's not it's not the scream because there's oranges and shit. There's like oranges and brown in scream
Is that your final answer?
No
Guernica, is that your final answer?
Yes
9 000
How about the 36 000?
Here's question number seven
Oh, that feels nice. The next question is worth one of these amounts. All right, so this should be easier
Prior to 2010's love and other drugs ann hathaway and jake jullenhall appeared together. I know this
The good honey darko donnie darko
The devil wears product. It's a broke back mom. Is that your final answer?
Yes
I know it's not fucking donnie darko
3000 let's go the whole way
The whole way let's go the whole way. Let's go the whole way
Let's go the whole way
Let's go all the way
What a great quote
That's really funny. It's fish and visitors. Is that your final answer?
Yes
Shoes and cloth. Yeah clouds really stink
I look crazed right now. I gotta get a haircut
Almost I look crazed question number nine. The next question is worth one of these amounts
Several of martha stewart's cats including mozart vivaldi and verity are named after famous what classical composers?
Yeah jazz musicians
Silent film stars. Why would they take this long to do this?
classical composers
This is like answer
Yes
That's weird
Why would they wait this long for that?
Because they're random
Is this supposed to be hard that one wasn't
Here we go. We're all player. I should get this one. It's probably video game related
It's gonna be about world of warcraft subscription numbers
Sarah chalk was dubbed the other becky for her fill-in role on what tv show full house
Beverly hills 90210
rosen
wonder years wonder years
This might be I know it might be a rosen
Skip the question
Do you want to jump the question?
Yes
I think it was the wonder years lifeline and jump the question
Does that mean I win the million dollar?
45 000 that's not bad going on to round two
45 that's not bad. That's a carnival scream
This is round two
You are four questions away from one million dollars
You have one lifeline for this round. Ask the audience
Ask the it's you guys answer the audience thinks is correct
If you give an incorrect answer, you'll leave the game with twenty five thousand dollars
Ready for round two
Yes, then let's finish playing
Millionaire
Which of these classic novels was first published when the author was only 20 years old the scarlet letter
robinson crusoe
the last of the mohegan's
frankenstein
That has to be frankenstein. Is that your final answer?
Yes
Not very much fanfare for a hundred thousand dollars. Thanks dick. Whatever his name is
Which of these stars is not among the few to have won an emmy grammy oscar and tony audrey
mel brooks
marvin hamlisch
julie andrews
Has mel brooks has not won and uh, no, has he a grammy?
Has mel brooks won a grammy?
Ask the audience
Yes
The audience would answer this way
julie andrews
Is that your final answer?
Yes
Yeah, the audience is never wrong
Two hundred thousand dollars. That's almost a carnival stream
Which of these locales is not mentioned in martin luther king jr's famous. I have a dream speech will kill tops of new hampshire
stone mountain of georgia
rockies of colorado
blue ridges of north carolina
New hampshire
For anti-cheat for anti-cheat just going up
I would say either a or b
Is that your final answer?
No, is that your final answer?
No, let's see
Nice
Fuck I almost just actually fell though. I almost actually fell down
I that would have been horrible. I would have taken out everything. I would have destroyed this whole desk
Thank fucking god, I caught myself because I have a fucking gamer skills
Show us both your hands show us both your hands both your hands. I know why I chose both your hands
Show us both your hands
Look, I will just hold on it takes a minute
No
See, did you hear anything drop?
You didn't you didn't hear anything
You would have heard like a dung if I had dropped it
There's nothing to drop. I don't have anything to drop
There's nothing to drop that would be the blue ridges of north carolina. Is that your final answer?
Yes
Siri
TVs the simpsons is set in fictional springfield sly reference to the locale of what 50 sitcom leave it to be
father knows best
Aussie and harriet
Make room for daddy. I think it's
It's not make room
For that one
It's not rick and morty either
What are you talking about? Um
I don't know. I have no idea. It's probably it's probably father knows best
Father knows best. Is that your final answer?
Yes, I don't whatever if I lose I lose who cares
I was about to press the button on the xbox
The games left to play I thought that was 500 000. I feel so unfulfilled
Oh
Do you want to play again?
Yes
To be a millionaire. Oh my pants
No, I don't do this again 10 questions to answer in round one. I'm going to bet anything from 100
That's it scream over, but you won't know how much until that's it answer each question. Yeah, that's it
I want a million dollars. Let's see the question category. That's it
Okay
I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow. We're gonna do tomorrow six six seven hours tomorrow, too
Hey, you can use the jump the question. I'll see you tomorrow two times in this round
You won't win any money for the question 9 pm bedtime. Here's the first question
Better get star wars tomorrow. Oh, I don't know. Do you think he don't have it located in what u.s state?
South carolina
florida new jersey
Why would I do that? That's the one everybody wants to see the most
Shred hogan
I I don't think hold on. Let me let me see if I can shred hogan
But no, why would I do that? Somebody could like play it and enjoy it
So I get if I like donate that game or something somebody might like play it. I don't know. I don't want to like
I don't want to shred a game
That thing's probably pretty rare. These things are not they're rare
Antiques
You're gonna make somebody's life you're gonna make somebody really sad. No, but but if you wanted to play what if you love hogan
I'm not gonna shred a disc. I'll break my shredder
I'll see you guys tomorrow
tomorrow
Believe it or not. Let's get on cam
Tomorrow believe it or not. We're starting early. That's right. We're starting early and i'm going a lot. I'm going fucking all day tomorrow
You hear that open your ears for a second going all day tomorrow
I'm starting tomorrow at sunday. We're gonna do sunday during the day
Probably gonna start around one
one 2 pm
pacific
Is he drunk? No, i'm just
I'm just i've been jumping up and down in the fucking corner of my room for six hours
He's i'm not I
This is the oh I drank a coke
I had one coca cola and like three glasses of water
Uh, so we're gonna start tomorrow probably around one or two pm
And then i've got tomorrow is the real kind of meat and potatoes
We've got star wars. We got those two horror games
I got twister over here probably gonna open with twister tomorrow
I would
If you have time
It's all i'm missing
And there's like 15 other games after that
So I really don't know if i'm gonna get through all of them, but we'll oh and
But here's here's the uh, let's get on cam. Lisa
Uh, so here's what's gonna happen for this week
tomorrow, we're gonna do
more connect
and then
I believe on tuesday or when would tuesday that ancestors game comes out
I'm gonna play the hell out of that
tuesday ancestors comes out and then saturday or some whatever the is terrarium
It's the money's game. We play the monkey the apes
And you have to like level up it and and survive. It's a rogue like
Ancestors eight game
It seems like it's gonna be a lot fun
But i'm willing to put at least one or two streams into it
All right, let's get off cam. I don't like it
It's day's gone part two. I don't know. It seems it looks way more interesting when day's gone was
But that's kind of the games that are on tap for this week
The rest of connect well next week too
steam page says 2020
Uh, I thought no it comes that's for a console
It launches on pc like two or three months before console
weirdly enough
That's one of the only games. I think that's done that in a long time
Why does this have already have a three out of ten?
What?
3.6 out of 10
Oh, it's because it's on the epic store only is it is it only on the epic store?
Do I actually have to download the epic store for this?
Well, I still want to play it though. It looks like people say it's not that good
There's a couple of reviews that say it's not good
Well, i'm still gonna play it
Yeah, it goes to ps4 and xbox one. I think next early next year
Or late this year something like that
I'm just gonna do it. I'm playing it but uh, i'll see you guys tomorrow
We're gonna do the bits
Rewind the clock a little
To six hours and 15 minutes ago
We had
a ton of community subs from phylactery lich
69 subs we had austin atlantis 50 subs phylactery 250 dollars ape kesham
Abe kesham 50 community subs
There was a ton of community. There was a too many to count
There was a lot of money tonight
Thank you all of you
Hundreds and hundreds of dollars and tons of community subs
It means a lot guys. Thanks
we also had
Five dollars from shelby kuhn
Thank you the five dollars
They say hey uncle germ i have my pocket money. Also, what happened to burger boy?
The last i heard of him was when you told that story about him eating the giant muff
Um, he's still he's still kicking around
I mean we live
Across the country from each other at this point. So
it's
We talk from time to time sometimes he's
he has like a family and his own life and
He just kind of does his thing and i've whenever i'm back around massachusetts
You know, i'll probably see him
He's got a video. Yeah, he he did like to make another video
Of him like eating cupcakes or something. All right
Yeah, he's still he's still the same fucking weirdo
So don't worry. Not much has changed at least throughout I guess
It's him like laughing and like stuffing cupcakes it down his throat and like puking it back up
It's not you don't want to watch that video. I don't think
Yeah, he's not he's doing all right. I guess
We don't talk as much as we used to but you know, it's I talked to him from time to time
But thank you for the five dollars shelby
Uh abe cash him. Thanks for the
ten dollars
Why did I donate to a moron and then do the little the the three?
Face thing cat legs face thing
Thank you. Uh abe and thanks for your community substitute. You gave a ton
Look at this. I can't even fucking this like weekly
The bit thing is in is I can't even look at this
This is ridiculous
Holy shit
But thank you for the ten dollars
And your huge amount of community subs as well, sir k9
Thanks for the 250 can't believe you died to tree wheel pinwheels shitty your cousin omega lul
I I liked that game that game was charming
Uh rare pepe body lotion. Thanks for the 15 dollars. They just say germapop 15 bucks. Thank you rare pepe
Thanks for dropping 15 bucks. I'm gonna charge my uh bluetooth and my
Wireless headset. I love this thing
I am so pissed off that I didn't get something like this before think about how many streams you've seen
Where I just have that dumb dickhead
Attached wire to my body
And I never thought just to get a bluetooth trans transmitter
What's wrong with me?
It's been i've been streaming for almost four and a half five years
And I I just two days ago got a bluetooth transmitter
What's wrong with me?
Because emf is bad shut it up. Are you using this?
Don't scare me
But thank you rare pepe. Thank you stephunky chicken for the five dollars
Thanks for all the passion and if we put into your streams
It really shows if you're tired from connect post stream and feel like screening it
I spent the last two weeks working on a video about a joke you made three weeks ago las vegas las vegas
Noir it's funny right when you said that
Look at this
Shit, did I get it?
It just told me to take a break. It said you're you look tired
It just said it on the bottom of the screen
As if you wrote it
Uh, I think I need to talk about a couple other things, too
There's like a bunch of shit that i'm like falling behind on the activity book stream. I'm gonna have to push forward
I haven't had time to really want I want to talk about it in length
So where the that activity book?
Where's waldo stream?
Is gonna go forward another few three four or five days probably into like the first week of september
just because
I really want to let people know what's happening if they want to contribute to it
I have just not had a chance at all to sit down and do it
And phylactery lich just gave another 20 subs adding up to like six or seven
trillion or whatever they are
More subs from phylactery lich 20 more
Your credit card is gonna melt
That should that happens that should happen in rocko's modern life. So, you know, it's real
Uh, thank you phylactery for the how many community subs do you have now?
This reminds me of uh, I remember a while ago. There was somebody that had like two three four five hundred community subs
Thank you
You not only have given that many subs. You've also
You are at a hundred thousand fifths
And we're talking not lifetime. We're talking for the week
That's the week
damn, dude
Thank you for the ridiculous support. I don't know what else to say. That's a lot of money
Hopefully you got a large raise. Yeah
I really hope so
But thank you
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
We also had
Oh, but anyways, uh to talk about the not just the activity stream i'll go
But pretty much the first thing we're gonna do
Not tomorrow because obviously i'm gonna be jumping around like an idiot on connect but on the ancestor stream that tuesday
we're gonna sit down and i'm gonna talk about the activity book and i'm also gonna try to talk about a
Monthly community night where all videos
And all artwork and we're gonna go over that kind of stuff
Once a month and just have like a whole viewing stream
for a community night
Where we just relax we just kick back put on some music
or whatever
And just hang out for a few hours
I'll be doing that once a month because so many people as the channel has gotten a little larger
There's a ton of people now with really really good shit really really high quality videos
original artworks and paintings
There's a lot of people that it would be great to show
And I think there's enough content there where we could get at least a few hours of just hanging out and talking
So it's not just going to be artwork. It'll be video content as well
There's a lot of people that make really good videos really high caliber high quality videos
And I want to show them it'll be kind of like it is right now
The only difference is it won't be a stream over screen
it will be
community contributions
Don't become a react streamer. No, this is once a month. I'm too adhd to like sit and watch videos every day
I wouldn't be able to do it
I would get up and fucking start. I would just start moving or i'd have to move. I can't just sit. I can't do that
Some people can I can't
But that's what you can expect for if you hey, I got a video or have some artwork
We're going to start to
Not show them here
And compile them and actually have them and i'm going to talk about it on tuesday
So for until for further notice
I'm not going to be doing end of stream kind of video artwork stuff. We're going to hold on to them
There's going to be an official
Discord channel that we're going to make
To do that
I will be in that channel. I'll be able to pull stuff from it
So it's not just going to be like not like the creative channel
But a hey, here's like my community contribution that I think would be cool
And I think I put enough time into it and it looks like it's you know, looks great
I think i'm really happy with it, you know when you're like happy with it
And you want it to be shown on stream
the creative channel, I think is good just to be
an open forum for people just to kind of talk and post stuff and talk about art and
creative stuff so
German just like a backpack
Backpack was what is my what do you mean my backpack?
This is a new thing that I don't know
Why did you guys start spamming this?
You have 88. I have 80 hd. Hey, yes, I do
But thank you. Uh, jamie jamie gave like two four six eight ten you gave like ten twenty dollars twelve dollars here
Over the course of a bunch of different bits. So thank you jamie for the bits
No messages just a bunch of two two two two two two two two two in a row
Thank you
Thank you zake for the five dollars. What's up, jeremy? It's 4 30 a.m
In finland that i'm drunk as fuck finally starting college on monday
I fucking love your streams and the dedication you put into this. You're a natural. Love you. Love you. Love you
Cheers from across the pond
drunk bits
Thank you so much zake. Thanks with five dollars
Good luck in college
get
Get good grades, but not too good
But good, you know what i'm saying get good grades
Is tomorrow going to be early tomorrow is going to start around one to two pm pacific
We're going to start a couple hours earlier tomorrow
Just get good grades
You know what i'm saying. Thank you to
apple shift for the five dollars
Five bucks from apple shift
Hey, man, it's me gwen. I just finished all the rumbles. So I wanted to do another drawing for you
That would celebrate them really hope you like it
I've been working on it for about three weeks and I finally finished. Thank you for inspiring me and being the best boy
Here's a link to the 4k version of it. We're going to hold on to it. I'm going to hold it
Because this first community stream is going to happen way sooner than you think
I'm probably going to do this
The first one will probably happen before the carnival stream
tonight
Because I I really do think that once that channel is open in the next week or so
A a lot of people are going to start to submit stuff and it will be very very easy to do one
At some point before that carnival stream happens
And if not before then very very soon right after it. I can't imagine it would take a whole lot of time to get some great stuff
But thank you apple shift. Hold on to it join the discord and put it in that discord. We're going to do this once a month
because the reason one of the reasons why
is
Because it's still the end of the stream right when it's a stream over. Okay. Good night everybody. See you later
most people leave
right
And there's a lot of cool shit that I think people would like to see
That we just put on the screen here that I put on the screen
when it's just kind of the
You know like 40 50 percent of all people have left
And I can imagine a scenario where because think about some of those videos we've watched that were 10 out of 10 hilarious videos
that people have made and
Less than half of the full stream broadcast audience got to see it
If people knew that that stuff was going to be available and that was a a night thing that we did once a month
I think oh my god. I'm just like just my tongue almost just like was eaten
It was just aided
It was like
Uh, I think more people would stick around
That was weird. It was like
I know it's because i'm you know, it's because look
I'm like kneeling on one knee and like going like like hunching over I gotta like get up
But uh, thank you apple ship for the five dollars. Hold on to your art. We're gonna do a full night
Where we go over it. Thank you so much for any artwork that you give I
I very strongly look forward to seeing it. That was a little league coach
Sit in a chair. My chair is out. Not even in this room
I had to move it
But what do you say we move on we've only got a little bit more we've got teapot for the five dollars and ten cents
Hey, german just wanted to apologize for last three when I sent a bit messages
That could have been taken as slightly offensive and didn't realize until afterward
When he stopped reading it out loud and skipped over it
It was my first time donating bits to a streamer. I wasn't trying to be an ass or anything
I hope you'll be able to accept my apology
Love the streams and love participating in chat and try to catch your streams whenever i'm not stuck at work
Um
Yeah, I don't i'm not really don't remember
Exactly what you're referring to but i'll tell you something right now
you've got the
You've got the wherewithal to maybe know maybe something you said was maybe not cool or something and you're accepting it
Figuring it out and you're learning and you're moving forward
That's all right
you know you you're
You've got you've got enough of a mind
maybe to
realize maybe something you said was wrong or stupid or
Bad or i'm not saying that but I don't know what you said, but
You know that takes not only that that takes some guts and it takes, you know a screwed on head. So
stupid
You sound like a dad
No, but that's like true though
Look, it'd be one thing. Okay. Imagine if if tpo imagine if instead it was five dollars and it said hey
Uh, you suck. I hate you pee pee poo poo
um
And then you kept going and you said like some offensive shit and you didn't realize you know
I mean, yeah, this is it's been like probably two days
You've already like gone. There it is. I know what I did was wrong
That can be ironic too. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I know we're talking that's not pee pee poo poo is not offensive
It's not
That's like
Five-year-olds say that and laugh and run away
That's an offensive
Yes, it is
Well, I don't I don't I disagree
Yes, five-year-olds do make pee pee poo poo jokes
I will be facetimed by
relatives that have young children
And sometimes they'll just be being like, you know fresh and they'll lean over and be like it do do head
And then it's like, excuse me and they go
And then they like they run away and it's like, but don't say that
It's that still happens. So come on
Did you wash the shit out of your hair? Now? That's offensive
That offends me
I'm look forward to your apology tomorrow in bits
Tomorrow no teapot. Thanks for the five dollars. Don't worry about it. It's all good
Thanks for the five bucks
Lemon pudding. Thanks for the 250. You just said the best idea for a stream. Please do a puppet show stream
I don't know
I don't know about that
I don't think I could handle it. I don't think I could last
maybe
We'll see i'll think about it
But thank you for the uh for the recommendation
I have to go like this because I can't see the screen
Like this xbox. That's another reason why I don't want to do this for more than like six seven hours
This 360 is is gonna explode
It is I put my hand on this thing
It's it's like an electric blanket
But thank you to
Uh jake sunrise for the five dollars. It is a video
It's called germa the short king. We're gonna hold on to this
Because like I said, it is a video it is uh, artwork creative we're gonna hold on to it
Please when that channel is available
Throw that into that discord. So we got to start compiling them now. We have to start compiling these things
Don't worry. It's an xbox slim. Those don't red ring. They just melt. That's what I that's how is that better? That's way worse
But i'm banned from the discord. Uh, well, I don't know why that happened
But I want to start compiling these now and there's really only one way to do that and that's to start now
But thank you so much jake sunrise for the five bucks
I look forward to seeing this video
Very soon
Thank you
What do you say we put on the credits? This is going to be ridiculous
There were hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of subs tonight
You said my name wrong again
jake sunshine
What did I say?
I didn't say that
Here they come
Here come all the subs all the sunrise. Oh
Shit
Thank you to s10w update for the two dollars and fifty cents. Hey germa
This reminds me of the time my parents got me three games for my birthday hulk hogan connect dragon ball connect and garfield show on the wii
So i'm glad someone else suffers with me. Hope you have dragon ball connect as well. Peace and love
Um, we'll see tomorrow
Garfield for the wii did they think that it was a xbox 360 game?
did
Did your parents just think that every console was the same console that's happened to be before?
Yes, uh-huh
Now you don't have the heart to tell them
Oh, thanks. Thanks garfield. I can't wait. I can't even play this. I can't do anything with this
I'm just gonna put it on under my bed or something
Everything is the same all consoles are the same consoles, especially if they went especially when they went to disc based
Once everything became a disc that got real confusing to all the parents
Looking for my name mine
I
Maybe you'll see it. Somebody said I fucking missed the stream. Hey, we got a vod right there and it's free
You can watch the whole thing. I recommend it. We had a lot of fun playing our connect
There's much more
I would dare say we got through a lot of the shitty ones today
No, what? No, there was like at least three or four. I had some of them had really good moments
Our connect it's ours
Uh, thank you though. Thank you to
Silent serenity for the 250. Hi jerma. Could you stop streaming? I want to catch the vaude. Yeah, I will very shortly here
In less than five to ten minutes
Thank you though for the 250. Thank you gnarly for the 250
So when are you finally gonna man up and play insert game here?
I posted it three times on the recommended channel and you haven't played it yet. You're a bastard
I've just haven't played it. Sorry
He's upset with me
Bilactory lich gave another fifteen dollars and 89 cents and then the great canadian fk club
You all remember great canadian
Speaking of money
That was fucking hundreds of subs before
He's back now. He's still right. They're still wrong
I've seen him around
But thank you the five community subs great canadian
Thank you
Appreciate the five. Thank you so much
And to all the people that got those subs you can now do germa earth
And germa venus the two best emotes on twitch just kidding. It's this one
I can't even do my own. Emote, right? I just amaze. We'll just fucking delete my channel
But thank you to great canadian. First of all
Bilactory lich
Your uncountable amount of money that you've given today and two streams ago
Uh, I just finally got to see a doctor about my adhd and got medication for it
It's changed my life for the better good stream today germa best on twitch in my opinion. Appreciate that opinion
Glad you have fun
And thank you for the ridiculous amounts of money
Speaking of money the tingy just came in with five community subs right back to back five community gifted sub
They're flying around all over the place
In every direction
Do you hear this in your left ear?
Do I have one of those microphones? Tell me which ear this comes in
Hey, what's going on? It's me over here
Hey, what's going on? It's me over here. Does that change your ear?
It's both ears. Yeah, whatever. I don't have one of those cool mics
But thank you both of you for the five gifted subs and thank you if I liked your lich
I used to when I was younger. I did medication for adhd but it messed up my appetite
So I stopped doing it
You know, i'm a smaller frame person. So when I was on medication and it was kind of stunting my appetite
I really
I just I just wasn't good for me
so
When I went off of it, I went back to eating normally again and really haven't taken any medication since
Yeah, i'm broadcasting in mono. I have to
Oh booze in the chat booze here booze in the chat
Playing wow classic
Remember when I was in shape I do but i'm also getting i'm like i'm going to that stage of life where
I got all the things that I have to worry about
Besides getting huge
I don't know. I think it will suck
I don't know. It's a tough one. I'm not even subbed to wow at the moment
Not very many people are I don't think isn't it's not really in a great state. I've heard
I was gonna give it a try. I don't i'm still deliberating on if i'm gonna stream it or not probably not
Maybe eventually, I don't know. I have to i'm it's i'm gonna flip a coin or something
i'm, not sure
Bfa is not good
It's unfortunate
Stream os res. Well, it's rs. What's that?
Hey brent muffins burnt muffins. Thanks for the ten dollars
I love you streams, especially since they calm me down when i'm going through stressful changes in my life
Thank you so much for the ten dollars
I am more than happy to be somebody that you can watch in this community can be somewhere you can hang out
to relax
That's i'm really happy to hear that
Not happy to hear
That you're going through some shit or whenever you are going through some shit. I'm not happy about that, but i'm
Happy that there's a community here people we can all relax and hang out and have a good time
German just like that. All right, i'm gonna ban all four of those words
Germa just
Of every all four of those words are getting put to the ban list
I don't even care. It's my name on who gives a shit
But thanks for the ten bucks burnt muffins
Freudian weapon. Thanks for the 250. Hey germa. I haven't said anything in a while
I just want to say that you're awesome and I love your stuff. Have a good night. Thank you. Freudian weapon
Thanks for sticking up
Staying up
Stick it up. Thanks for sticking up. Thanks for sticking up for me
And that's it
Thanks a lot everybody
I will see you guys tomorrow
Have a great one
See you tomorrow
Have a wonderful wonderful evening
And by the way, hey the true mitchie gave bits at the end here
Can you please pm?
One of the mods and give him your discord name
I saw you pop up and I want I want because I think I have you the name wrong when I try to add you before
I think I may have fucked it up
But thank you
Good night guys. See you tomorrow more connect
If I see you there
I see you there