Hey, what is going on guys? It's Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This time I'm playing as the Engineer with the Strange Wrench, the Strange Pistol, and the Strange Frontier.
Justice, I am a weird bastard today. Strange everything. Break a lot of records in this gameplay.
I actually, let me think, I break my buildings built record, my kills record, and I think that's it.
But I break a couple records in this gameplay, and you're probably wondering, Jerma, these records seem like they're kind of low.
Well, they are kind of low. You've got to remember, when I play Team Fortress, I go all out balls to the wall.
I flip out, I go crazy, I go aggressive. I'm not one of those people that tries to save their own life.
I do really well in Team Fortress 2, but usually it's in spurts of two or three lives in a row.
My one life records are kind of atrocious, so if you're wondering, oh, Jerma, you only killed like 27 people in this gameplay.
I mean, that's really good, but that's not incredible because I'm a freak show and I go and shoot people with a shotgun
when I'm supposed to be at a sentry gun 10 feet behind me.
So this is going to be a couple of tips right here. I'm going to give you guys some dust ball tips, at least some dust ball tips.
Take a look at where the teleporter is right now. You want to stuff that teleporter in the corner as far back as it's going to go
because spam coming around this corner, demo men, soldiers launching all their projectiles.
There's a chance that it's going to blow anything up over here.
So be careful. Make sure the teleporter is all the way back stuffed in the corner.
The sentry and the dispenser, you don't really have to worry about too much because obviously you want the sentry gun to be pointed out,
shooting at people that are walking past it, and the dispenser needs to be in a place where you can get right to it right next to the sentry.
So don't really worry about that. As long as these two are kind of tucked behind the wall here, you should be okay because you're right here to repair it.
I know a lot of people like to go inside the building on the first point on defense. That's fine. I just don't like to deal with all the spam.
I think it's easier to stand out here and not have to worry about all the explosions and all the chaos
because if an Uber comes in, that sentry in the building is probably going to go down. It's just in such close quarters.
You come into the building and right next to you, two feet away from you is the sentry, you're going to get rid of it.
Spy came in and I just barely got every single thing saved, but they capped the first point, and let me tell you guys right now,
don't go down with the ship. I abandon it right here, I run away. Do this if you know you're going to die.
Don't glue yourself to the sentry. Just walk away, get back to your teammates, and get some secure position
because look at how many revenge crits I have right now. I have 20 revenge crits.
If I had stayed there and just kept whacking the sentry to try and stay, no, no, no, I can keep it up, I can do it.
You're not going to do it. I got news for you. It's not going to work. So just abandon the sentry.
If they already have the first point anyways, what's the point of you sticking around anyway? You know what I mean?
Just abandon. Control-alt-delete.
So now I just want to briefly talk about one thing to do with the revenge crits and the engineer in general.
Guys, especially medics. Medic, listen up. This is important.
So an engineer with the revenge crits, I have 19. Up close with one shot, it does 180 damage.
Pretty much you can kill any class in the game besides a soldier or a heavy in one shot.
Maybe two. See, I didn't land all the pellets right there, but I do right there. 180 damage.
That'll kill any class in one hit. It's unbelievable.
Heal your engineers. If you see the glowing bright shotgun, put the heal beam on him and walk around with him.
You will kill like five people guaranteed if he has more than a few shots. And he can land them.
Far too often I'll see engineers standing by their sentry guns with the glowing bright shotgun just doing nothing.
And I feel like if you start to heal those people and tell them over mic,
Hey, how many revenge crits do you have?
Oh, I got 17.
Hey, you want to go kill the whole team right now? It's like, it's a no brainer.
So I just skipped that part right there. That was me building the sentry gun and it took about 30 seconds maybe.
It's nothing happened. I didn't die. It was just really boring. So I didn't want to have you guys have to sit through that.
But killing that sniper right there, people freak out.
I've said this before in other gameplay commentaries that when you get hit by a crit, when you get shot in the stomach by a crit,
whether it's a rocket, whether it's a shotgun, doesn't matter.
You freak out a little bit and you go, Okay, there's crits. I got to run by.
Oh, by the way, one shot kill right there.
But you guys know what I mean, right?
When you see a crit screen, when a medic pops a crit screen on somebody and their weapons are glowing,
you immediately go, Here comes crits. I'm gonna die.
The same thing can be said about somebody that has a frontier justice that's glowing.
Even when I'm not playing engineer, I could be playing soldier or I could be playing spy.
And if I see the glowing shotgun, I go, Oh, shit.
And I either back up or I go for another target.
That's what goes through everybody's mind.
So this is the second sentry that's built to completion now.
Get a few kills. That spy was definitely a dead ringer.
You can always tell when a spy's a dead ringer when you shoot them one time from far away
and it does two damage, but it magically kills them.
So dead ringer spies, I do that too, though. Everybody does that.
Doesn't really matter.
So I got four kills on this sentry and I kind of do something really, really outrageous
and not recommended to most people that are playing engineer because we have this one point.
We only have three minutes to go.
And I destroy this sentry to get the crits.
I'm such a greedy bastard right here. You'll see. Ready?
Oh, this is a good idea. Yeah, let me just destroy the sentry.
But if you're quick enough, you can get a sentry built back to completion pretty quickly,
especially when I have that dispenser right there, a full level three dispenser.
I'm not worried about it at all.
Right now, I'm just curious. I want to try and look around, try and get some more kills.
Soldier right in his face, 180 damage. Remember how I said that before, 180.
Looking around, perusing, seeing if I can get a shot on somebody, get a kill.
I miss a few times, but I get the kill on him anyways from long range crit.
Guys, don't be afraid to do this.
If you're afraid to do this, if you think you need to stand by your sentry at all times
and guard it with your life, I mean, that's true.
But it's not true enough where you can't go have a little bit of fun.
Remember, a spy is going to try and backstab you and take out your sentry and all your buildings.
So what happens if a spy just saps all that stuff right now?
The map is small enough where I'm going to be able to get back to at least one or two of my buildings.
Preferably the dispenser or maybe even the sentry.
It's really not a big deal. If I'm standing here the whole time and I get backstabbed by a spy, it's all gone.
Everything is going to be gone.
So why not utilize your crits and be able to kill some people?
And if the stuff gets sapped, you can just turn around and deal with it.
Now, I would not advise this strategy on a large map like upward or bad water
or any situation where there's a lot of pressure on the point.
If there's a lot of pressure, you really do need to stand back at your sentry and make sure it stays up.
Make sure there's a guard for the team.
But in a situation like this, it's totally okay.
As you saw right there, I let that soldier kill the sentry.
I'm not trolling this team, don't worry. I'm not like a troll or anything like that.
I did that on purpose because I wanted the crits and I was 100% confident that I could get a level 2 up
at least within 10 or 12 seconds, which is what happened.
The sentry is now level 2.
I'm in a different spot right now because we only have one minute left
and they haven't even come close to getting onto the point, not even one time.
So just hanging out, shooting people with the shotgun, chilling out here, trying to get some more kills with the sentry.
Nothing I can really do right now besides kind of hang out with the team.
But in my mind, I've been alive for a long time, about 7 or 8 minutes now.
I haven't died yet. So I'm considering, okay, I have a lot of kills.
I'm trying to break these records. I knew I already broke at least one record.
So I come out here just trying to kill some more people.
I know we only have 30 seconds left for me to keep padding my record.
Spy comes over here and knows he's a dead ringer.
So I turn around when I hit the sentry and I get him right in his face.
Counting down now, 20 seconds left in the game.
We have this in the bag. They're not going to win.
So I want to get some more kills.
Foolishly come around the corner with just the regular shots and the frontier justice.
And I get plowed by that soldier.
So, didn't turn out so well, but I broke a bunch of records.
I thought that was really cool gameplay.
Three seconds left. We win the game.
Thanks everybody so much for watching and so much for supporting the channel.
I really do appreciate it.
I will see you all next time and take care everybody.