Bread and Fred. Bread and Fred. I'm turn your volume down. I'm glad I did because the splash
screen is very loud. Yep. Oh, yeah. Turn your volume down. I'm glad I caught that. It is very
loud. Uh, should I play this with a controller? Jesus. What the fuck? I'm trying to turn it down
and it went up. What just happened? Hold on a second. Why? Hey, I got, I got a limiter on
everything that comes through. Don't worry. I have a limiter on everything that comes through now.
So that was loud, but that wasn't unbelievably loud. Don't worry. I put it on there. All right.
How you feel? Hey, how you doing there? Hey, pal. What's going on there, pal? Hold on. What do you,
what resolution are you playing at? What do you, what do you, what? Hey, what resolution,
what resolution are we playing at? Yes. You can do five. What is 5120 by 2160? What the hell is
that? A projector? 5K resolution. All right. Let me capture this. Hey, there it is. Okay. This game
is Torturous Chat. Uh, it's a co-op platformer where we're tied together. I don't, I haven't
played it. Haven't seen it played, but I know that it is going to require coordination between
me and you to succeed. So it is going to be torture. Okay. So how do we get in a game together?
You click play and then it says multiplayer. Okay. Should I, do you want to host? Do you want me to
host it? Uh, I'll, I'll host again. Make sure there's not like a room code before we, we show it.
My screen is hidden. There's no room code. It's a steam invite. I've sent you the steam invite.
I have. Ooh. All right. Are we good? There's no like, oh, there we go.
Waiting for your partner. Yeah. You got to press space to confirm for some reason. Oh, so okay.
I'm Fred. You're Fred. I'm bread. Is a mod here? Can they change the game to Fred and Fred? Hey,
can that mod come over to my channel and do the same? Don't do that. Okay. So how does it work?
I'm going to plug a controller in for sure. Okay. So I'm the red one and how do you move?
WASD is working for me. It's, it's arrow keys for me. Oh, numpad with your, with your coffee.
I'm using controller. Uh, do you know what a fulcrum is? Yes. Oh, you played Q. Why is WASD not
working? And I, this controller not work either for this game. Everything's fine for me. What the
heck? Um, that's weird. Uh, I guess I'm doing arrow keys. Is it that hard? No, it's not that
difficult. It's fine. Okay. Oh, our ping is at the top. It's funny. So let's just jump and walk.
Is there any other buttons? Not that I've noticed. I don't know what this is. I think this is where
you get your collectibles or something. Oh, we got it. We got to go climb the mountain. How did
you just do that? Do what? You were like holding on because we're always holding on. All right.
Well, get up here. We have to time this by the way. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. This is going
to be torture. How do you, from, from there, can I like pull you up? It doesn't, it does not appear.
So, okay. So what? No, no, no, don't just do that. Are we going to, are we going to have to count
down for every jump? Yes. So that's how it works. Ready? Do you want to go like, go or do you want
it to be like one, two, three? How do you want to do this? Uh, uno, dos, tres. Okay. So you want,
we have to get the same thing. Ready? Uno, dos, tres. On three. Oh, I can swing. Uno, dos, tres.
Uno, dos, tres. Only one of us. Okay. Only one of us should do it. We need something better than
that. I'm telling you. I, I say what we're going to do is now jump and on jump. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. No, cause if you do one, two, three, then you're adding 33% more gameplay time.
Yeah. But if we, if we, if it just simply just is now jump, now jump, see now jump. Can I swing
you up here? Maybe. All right. Just one, two, three. No comedy dog shit. One, two, three. One, two,
three. One, two, three. Oh, it's Charlie. Review some of the key points. The most important one is
swinging. One of you needs to be an anchor. That doesn't even work for me because it's down.
And then you swing. Okay. Okay. Don't fall. Okay. So let's go up here. Let's test that out. So I'm
going to, I'll come over here. One, two, three. So I'm going to anchor and then you go down.
What happens if I do that? So you can swing and get yourself up here. I think at some point,
Oh, if I let go, you need to stand up and then we need to both. We're not getting past like the
first jump. There's no way in this room. Okay. Coffee anchor. All right. Okay. Now we need,
we need to both jump here. All right. One, two, three. One, two, three. Okay. Here's here. You're,
I'm going to anchor. You're going to swing. And then when you're coming back. Okay. Wait, wait,
Hey, I'm going to go for it. Okay. Apparently you need to go more up. One, two, three. One, two,
three. Okay. I'm anchoring now. So you want me, when you go up there, I jump when I'm swinging
like that. All right. You just kind of, I'm going to anchor and you find yourself. I can't,
I can't hear. I've got to move. No, German come down. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We can watch, make this jump without an anchor. We have to practice the anchor. Cause it's going
to be, there's going to be a jump up here. We're going to lose. It's one, two. What are you doing?
Don't kind of like, all right. One, two, three. You have to keep the same timing the whole time.
One, two, three. Yeah. Can you, no, I can kind of like pull you. Oh, you have to make the jump.
Okay. You need to swing more than that. So bad at this. We need to count. You don't just sense me.
We're not like close enough that we can just sense. One, two, three. One, two, three. Anchor.
Go for it. I'll do the jump. Okay. Um, what, what, what? I don't know. What? Just swing. I can't.
Why do my forehead get so much bigger? I don't know. Did we break it that? All right. All right.
All right. No, no, no. So now if you swing, you can, oh, there we go. All right. One, two, three.
One, two, three. Don't just jump without counting. Well, I'm getting anchored. We don't need the,
I got you. Okay. And you can pull me up. Okay. Ready? One, two, three. One, two, three. All right.
You just have to be ready to do the jump. I'm not good at this yet. There you go. All right. Stop.
No, don't, don't freak out because we have to get through the tutorial. Okay. That's our child.
Ready? How do we get up there? I think we have to just jump. Okay. One, two, three. Oh, yeah. All
right. We got it. We're getting there. What a challenge you're undertaking. Enjoy the trip.
They aren't coming back. I don't, that's ominous. I don't know why. Wait, don't just jump. I know
you're like a fast gamer. You like to go really quickly, but we can't do that here. One, two,
three. It's funny. All right. One, two, three. One, two, three. All right. That's wait, wait,
hold on. We need the momentum and the jump. That's a lot. That's a big gap. There's a countdown
button. What is it? I'm going to the options. You are controlling my video game right now. Am I?
Yeah. I don't, I don't have. Don't, dude, are you going to go like change my resolution? I got clap.
We got clap. We got pull the rope with jump grab. I don't think I can do that by the way. Rock,
paper, scissors. Well, this is yours. This is player two. Yeah, but I wait. Now I can do WASD.
That's weird because I, because this is weird. This is weird. This is like a hamachi gameplay.
Like we're on a land, but not really. Uh, so look at your controls. Grab is control. Grab is E for
me. Four is no down. Wait, I think what it's saying now is you this countdown is four, but you wait.
All right. Get out of this menu for a second. I WAC does not work. Okay. Hold on. But can I do
that though? I cannot do a countdown. If I go, I can't even hit escape, dude. I literally have no
control of my own game. You're okay. So this is really weird. Go. Can you go to my setting? Your
countdown is num lock four. What the fuck? Okay. So that's hard to do though. How come I can't just
have the same controls as you? I don't know. Why can't we just say it out loud? All right. Let's
go. Ready? Okay. I think you need to move over. Maybe you want me to anger. No, no, no less
because, because if I swing, then I, what I'm saying is when you're that close, I just end up
standing. I know. But wait, you all right. You ready? That's not going to help me. Okay. Wait,
wait. Let me, let me do the other direction. Let me get that. Okay. Ready? No, no. Are you all right?
Oh shit. I killed him. Okay. Can I, can you hit escape for me? Cause I don't know what, how to
get to my menu. I now go to your menu. Now go to like controls. Now go to me, like Fred player two
select like my tab at the top. I did control, grab objects, save checkpoint, pull rope is shift
countdown is four. That's not what it's going to be. Be like, it's the N four is num lock. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. This is being changed. Uh, this is going to be press game pad. Can it be right
control? Wait, there is a gigantic game pad at the top. Oh, thank God. Oh yes. Okay. Left, right,
jump anchor. Grab his left trigger, left bumper, pull rope is B. All right, let's go. You can,
you can get me out of here now. It didn't, it doesn't, it didn't do anything. Do I have to
select it for you? I don't know. Press left on the D pad. It's weirdly enough. I don't have any
control of any of this. Now I do. Like I can control this now. So if I go to Fred player two,
it says game pad. Yes. Is there like a yes button? Like an accept button? No, I think what chat is
an understanding is when I go into the options, it is changing what your options are. Yeah.
And we're on the internet. This is okay. I select game pad. I have to connect a controller,
but it works for him, but I don't have a controller connected. Okay, but hold on a second.
We can't have the same inputs on keyboard. So this is working for me. I'm using my controller
right now. So if I hit back, back, back, I have no control anymore and it doesn't work. And now I
have no control. I can't do it. I'm just going to use the fucking, wait, nothing works now.
Click that. So we had another backup game. No, this is fun. This is really fun. All right. Should
we restart the game? I don't know if that's going to help. All right. Just get us out of this.
Like this. Can you like jump off or something and pull us down? Exit to main menu. All right. Now,
wait, can you set up your options before we play? Okay. Set up your options before we do anything.
I have access. I can use my controller options, controls, game pad. I'm player two.
This is, it works. It's working right now. This works right now. Okay. Okay. I, I let's just check
it again. I'm going to put them both on the game pad. No, wait, would that fuck up for you? Okay.
If I'm Fred, no idea. I mean, it works right now. All right. So invite me. Yeah. My chat's saying
you can't play on a game pad. You would just have to use different keyboard controls. Okay. Well,
then we're just going to have to do that. I'm fine with, with the arrow keys. You either both
have to be keyboard or both game pad. You can't mix it. So do you have a game pad? I don't know
where it is. Let's just go. We were doing fine. That's bizarre. Okay. Uh, I'm ready for an invite.
You want an invite? I, I sent it and now I can't. I'm so confused. The whole premise of this game
is co-op and it doesn't. Okay. You're bread. I'm Fred. Okay. Are we good? Are we? You can move.
I can move. You know what your grab button is? Cause it looks like grabbing walls is also
grab this control for me. I believe. Okay. Is that the wall? Maybe not. Is it number,
the number pad control that's up there? Hold on. Can you go look at my controls?
Okay. Hold on. Red two. You just do it. It's weird because when I'm looking at Fred two,
it switches the controls for you. No, that's gotta be left control. I can change it for you.
I can do it too. Grab object. I want it to be shift, pull rope, right shift. What on earth?
No, like Z clap two. Um, I'm going to do two here. Three comes up one countdown X interact E. Okay.
I think that should be fine. I get us out of here. Okay. All right. I can grab. We're good. Okay.
We're good. We're good. Ready? Yes. Actually very helpful. Three, two, one. You gotta pull with up
jump. Yeah. There we go. Okay. Wow. Look at that synchronicity. Okay. So you, we can try this again.
Ready? All right. We're going to slingshot over there to the wall. You might have to grab it.
I'm going to try to grab. Hey, you ready? I'm going on the next one. Got it up. Jump, jump. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think we do here. Probably double jump. I think it's showing us arrows up
there. Why? Oh, I just jumped. There we go. Okay. We just, we just wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the heck? That was, that baited us. Trying to teach us something. See, you know, I'm just
going on that. Okay. You ready? I'm ready. Going on the next one. Wow. Can you do anything about this?
Can you like worms your way up there? You're going to, you're dying. You gotta let go. You gotta let
go. This is as far as we get, huh? We made it already. Okay. Ready? I'm going on. Wait,
hold on. I'm going too far. Hey, I'm going on the next one. Up, up. All right. Sorry guys. My bad.
Okay. So, okay. So what, what's the deal here? You, you, it shows us in the picture. So grab,
one of us, do you want to grab it or do you want me to do it? Uh, I'm going to grab. No, you,
why would, I don't know. You freaked me out. You did the one, two, three, go. One, two, three,
go means we go. I don't think I could jump and reach the wall unless we both jumped up. I don't
know why you jumped forward. I saw the one, two, three, and I'm like, I have to go. He's doing it.
I'm going to be very clear. I'm going to be very deliberate. I'm going to give
hand written instructions. I'm going on this one. You can do it for sure. Just get enough momentum.
Brother. Oh brother. You can't, you just gotta stand. You gotta stay up there and you keep doing
your little joke. Pull me up. What do you mean my little joke? We don't even need the timing for
that one. All right. It's actually kind of hard to do this. You ready? So when you get the momentum,
you do the jump. You're not getting a lot of it. You jumped at the wrong time. You're not getting
momentum like I get momentum. You're, you're a dead weight. I had plenty of momentum. You're not,
you're an anchor. Look at, there's not much more momentum I can give you.
You weren't doing that before. You see how you can't get up there unless I jump with you.
So give me a countdown. Let's go. Why are you trying to mess me up? I'm connected to you.
You're the anchor. Yes. Next one. Nice. Okay. All right. So what I'm saying here is we need
to both jump straight up at the same time. Then you grab the wall. I, and then we grab the wall.
Yes. Okay. We're jumping up, not forward. Yes. I know I'm hitting it. We gotta, you gotta,
you gotta let go. Yeah. You gotta get higher. Okay. Look at us. There we go. Look at that.
Look at that. All right. Are we going for the right or are we going up here?
We're going to jump to the right. Got it. Men. Now what? The same thing on this left wall.
You're going to grab the left wall. Yep. And then I'm going to swing up. You're going to grab it.
I just, I just pressed the button. It must've been a lag. It's just a bad program.
Okay. All right. How are you? Are you sweating? I'm, oh, that was fun. What's the next game?
Oh, you're not pulling out. You're not pulling out right now. You're not pulling out right now.
You ready? Okay. This is just Jump King with two people. Yeah. I never even played Jump King.
Don't, you'll, you'll be very upset at yourself for like a week. But we're doing that,
but worse. Um, we're at forty. Three, two, one. All right. Am I anchoring? Yeah. Okay. I'm going
to wait a second here because this is important. We make this. Yeah. Just do that. Ready? Got it.
Great. Achievement up here. Oh, look at that cute little baby. Our baby. Oh, we had together. Oh,
okay. You see what's going on here. Okay. I do, but I don't. You're grabbing. I need to grab.
All right. Or do you want me to grab? No, I'll grab. I'll grab. It better not be a lag.
Can you grab? I'm going to try. Okay. Give me the timer. Okay. Let go. What? Wait,
that makes logical. That does make logical sense. I think you need to, as you're doing it,
you need to grab, you need to grab that side. I need to grab on the other side.
We're not in a bad position. It's just, it's stressful because there's a timer of how long
you can hold on. Wait a second. This is a different route. Okay. If we mess this up,
we have to do everything again. I know. And I know you hate this. You hate more than anything,
like having to do the thing over again, which is why you never play these games up,
up. You always anchor up. I need to anchor. Otherwise we'll fall. No, you pull up and then
I pull, I pull up, I pull, you pull up, you're down. That was a weird, you, that was weird.
What you just did. Hold on. Thank you. Okay. Okay. Now wait a minute. I'm going to grab the
first one and then you're going to swing up to the wall on the other side and grab it.
And then you're going to swing and we're going to swing over there. Yes. You got it.
Oh, I'm good. Ready? A little more, a little more, a little more. More. Okay. Ready? On this one,
on this one. Oh, we had it. Okay. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it.
We got it. We got it. We got it. We can do it. What the fuck? I was anchored. You were anchor.
Okay. I'm going on this one. Okay. All right. Let's go over the plan again. I grabbed the wall
first. You grabbed and I grabbed and then what happened there though? I feel like we did that
pretty well. I think you might've just let go at a weird angle and then we didn't, we didn't
launch up. We kind of launched very true. All right. Why have we got this? I'm going to go
on this one. I don't know. I don't know. It was too late. I like the first one. I feel like the
first one was too early. All right. That one must've been too late. Not enough momentum.
I'm going to go on this one. Good thing I pulled you. All right, buddy. I'm going to go on the next
one. You're doing it too late. Is it? Really though? I thought that one was pretty good.
My momentum's going up, not left by the time you let go. I'm so concerned that it's not going to
be enough. Whatever. I'm going on, not this one. Is it going the wrong way? Okay. Going on this one.
No, it's hard. It's hard. There we go. Okay. I'm just going to go on whenever I can.
Is that enough? Okay. Go one. This one. Oh, yes. Oh, oh, just bring yourself up. Nice job.
High five. High five. High five there. No, don't jump. Don't jump. No, no, no. False, false. Okay.
I was trying to emote. Just give me the finger. Yeah. Rock, paper, scissors. I don't even know
what button that is on mine. Okay. We got to jump up and grab this wall. Wait. Okay. You talk about
the wall, the vertical wall. Yes. Okay. Can we even get it? Yes. Let's do a test to make sure.
We can do it. All right. Who is grabbing? You or me? Oh, you want to do a test? Yeah, we can
absolutely do that. I will grab. You are grabbing. Okay. Ready? Yes. Okay. And you just get up here
or do we need to go from here? I don't know. I think you can get up here. Yeah. Oh. All right.
Stop swinging. Stop swinging for one second. Let's pull on mine. I don't think you can pull
me here. I can. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Now we're jumping left. Oh, yeah. I didn't think we were
going to get up this far. What are you doing? We're going to the top. Good luck, guys. You'll
need it. Is it just going to be a bunch of people that make fun of us? Probably. He said, watch it.
Hold on. He said, watch out. What does this say? You already have that. Chad is here.
That's true. All right. Simple. You almost didn't make that. All right. You want me to anchor?
Yeah, that's big. This is a lot. And we can overshoot this too. So,
GG. I'm going to go. I'm just going to pick a good time. Got it? Oh, GG. What is this hook?
I don't know. You want to try and grab it? Jump up and grab it? Yeah.
It went too far. That's bait. I don't want to get a picture. No one cares.
Oh, yeah. That was bait. Was it? It was all bait. Everything. The whole thing was bait. What do
you mean? Everything. I'm bait. You're bait. Oh, boy. We're falling apart. Hold on. You didn't
anchor. You didn't anchor. You didn't anchor. You didn't anchor. Oh, it's all right. Let's speedrun.
You can help. Speedrun. Nothing's going to go wrong. I don't. Okay. Just pull me up. We can do
it. We got baited. It's fine. Just pull me up. Speedrun. We should not even need to communicate
for these ones. Yeah. We've done them so many times. Can I pull you from here? Fuck. Okay. No
communication right now. Okay. No communication. Silence. I want silence and I want you to fucking
go. Ready? Put both your headphones in if they're not in. I know mine weren't. Ready? We're just
going. Yeah. That's not a jump we can make. Oh, are we still communicating?
Let go. Let go. Okay. Fingers are sweaty. All right. Let's see. This game is like,
hey, play this game with your friend and see like try to this patience. And is it your real friend?
This book is all over me. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no. Let's just do it the right way.
Okay. Why? What did you just say?
I can. Yeah, we're good. Now I'm just going to go like this. Let's see who your true friends are.
We're incapable of jumping unless I do a full 360. I did look at my keyboard. I didn't know
when fucking Z was. Okay. Ready? I'm grabbing. Yes. I can just pull you up. Oh, buddy boy. Oh,
buddy boy. You're you're trying to do something. No, no, no, no, no. You just you went at the wrong
time. Play it back and times minus 10 speed. You're trolling. I'm very concerned about you.
Don't be. I want to win just as much as you do. Truthfully, I don't want to.
I suspect that the cost of winning is too high on the next one. Okay. You grab. Then I grab
going on the next one. That was not fast enough. Jesus Christ. All right. You grab. Nice. Oh,
I had a leg. All right. We need to take this one slow because this is the hard one. This jump is
the hard jump. Do we? Okay. Right here. You think right here? Right in the middle or further up?
You're good. I you need to be going full revolutions like crazy. I'm aware that you
need a full revolution man. There it is. All right. Okay, we can do this one. Can we look down?
Like what is going on here? I don't know. Is that that next jump felt impossible? It did.
Unless we have to swing. We might have to do a big swing jump. Well, let's just get on with this
hook. What is with the hook? There's there's I don't think we can get it though. Okay. Okay.
What do we do? There's no way. Is there no way? But it has to be that's pointing. It's playing
there. Wait, we can save the game. How? I don't know. It's a save states. Some people are saying
save, save, save states, save states. What are you doing? If you get the item, it will give you
save states. You want to just use one here? We already have one. Well, I don't know. I don't
know what they're talking about. How do we use it? I think it was like one of the F keys. Maybe.
Was it a lie? Save checkpoint. Yeah. We use it. I can't do it. So I guess maybe we do have to get
this. All right. What if we just drop down? We're getting one guide over. It's assist options. It's
under assist options. Oh, so it's if you're bad. But I know this is your least favorite game in
the world. You don't like to have to start completely over at zero and do it all over again.
You hate that, don't you? I do. You do? Well, it depends. Look, we're just going to do it right.
Okay. You ready? I'm just going to do it right. Why did you do that? Why would you do that?
You ready? Okay. Yes. All the way. You're gonna have to pull me up. Why don't we do a running
jump on this one? Like run at the same time? Oh, his brain is exploding. Okay. The go,
the three, two, one, go is going to be to start running. And then once you hit the end, just jump.
Okay. All right. Yeah, I get it. I get it. I get it. Okay. Oh, we actually did it. Damn,
that was a good call. You could just let me hang because we got it. We got to do another jump here.
Right. But this is going to be horrible. Or we're all the way back at the beginning.
And notice this is, okay, we're just going to do the full rotation. This is a big jump. Full
rotation. Trying to get it. I'm trying to get it in the right direction. Okay. You got it. You got
it. Nice. Okay, we're good. So now we're at, okay, don't let's not freak out. Get hands off the
keyboard for a second. Wipe your hands. Hands are getting sweaty. Yep. Okay. So I think we have to
go either up or down. I don't know which one is the right one. Oh, it's pointing up. I don't know
what that basket is. Maybe there is like an NPC or something down here. It dangle me. I can't see.
I'm blind. You can't see anything. There's a hoop down there, right? It's like a net. Yeah,
let's go down there. Should we? I feel like this is scary. It'll be easy to get back up. Oh,
it's just a hoop. Okay. What if I throw you in that? Can we like do that? I mean, we could
swing off the top if we want it to put someone in the hoop. But why? I feel like it's the game
is saying, hey, there's a hoop here. You should get dunked in the hoop. Do you want to get dunked
in the hoop? I mean, we could try it. You want to just dangle and I'll let go. Let's jump across
and I'll grab that wall and dangle you into it. Okay. So you're going to have to let go.
That was fun. That was great. Hey, we did it. That's fantastic. Wait, maybe I have to grab it.
How do you do the pull up? For me, it was Z. It's a very specific key you have to have it be.
What is the key for you? Q. All right, let's just go up. It's like that is a signal. Hey,
I'm not going to make the mistake because I know that you'll be like, look at what you did. And
you're so bad at games. Oh, look at you. Now what? We got to slingshot someone at that wall.
I'll grab it. Okay. I'm going to throw you at it. I think we need a full revolution. I got it.
Good. Now you grab that one. We got it. We got to grab the other side. Yep. I need a little bit
slack. Okay. And you're going to have to let go when I'm in the right spot. Nice job. And that's
how we get up here. That's how we get up to 70 fucking two. Don't blow it here. All right.
Ready? You need more room? Okay. Hold on. Swing. For what? I'm telling you. Swing. Swing.
Oh, so a full swing. I can't full swing because there's a wall. We're good. So we didn't drop all
the way down. This is the one we have to run at, right? Yep. You know what? Are you confident in
this? Do you want me to do it? We're going to maintain our roles. We're not. We're not goofing
around. Okay. Good. Roles maintained. Stare. No goofing. Stare. No goofing. Was that a goof?
You goofing right now? Are you seriously goofing when we're about to do the big jumps?
No. Or the big boys? All right. Same deal. I might actually have to grab this though.
I mean, whoever can grab it, grab it. Yeah. You have your mouse on your screen apparently.
Somebody came into my chat to tell me that. Oh no. Is he okay? I need to do CPR. Oh,
twerk it. Twerk it. All right. You want to climb the mountain again? Kind of. Shit. No,
we got to go back. Sorry. I feel like this three, two, one go, finding out that there's a pleasant
beep, beep, beep, beep. It's just like activating, like neurons are firing in your brain,
like unparalleled. So we have to keep going. When you hear the boom, you're like you're just
out ready. I gotta jump. I gotta jump. I gotta jump. It's like the Mario Kart thing. It's like
then you've like fucking eyes, your pupils just go fucking wide. What is it? Like a rat in a
Skinner box? You've been conditioned. I'm grabbing it. Okay. Wait, no, no, no. You can't, on go,
you can't say no way. I know, but I was confident that I could grab you if you jumped. If we
failed and you didn't seem ready. What the fuck? I thought that was good. I'm dragging your ass
up the mountain. I don't even care. Oh, geez. One last real try and then we'll play the other one.
Is this really going to be a three game night? I don't know. Are you down after this? I don't
know. I'm just surprised that. Okay, I'm grabbing. Hey, just in case you didn't know, I'm grabbing.
I have an itchy head. Don't wait. Don't wait. Okay. You're grabbing first, right? I'm grabbing.
That's pressing shift. Sorry. Anytime I play a game like this, do you get like this too?
Where like I'm, I said at this desk, I've probably sat here for hundreds and hundreds,
if not maybe thousands of hours. I right now, I'm so uncomfortable. It's just like,
oh no, everything's wrong. Like where I am seated, how high I am in the chair,
where my fingers are, everything just feels incorrect. I get that in other games.
No. Okay. Okay. That one is actually really hard. What a deluge. What are you doing?
You did the Mario thing where you jump after, jump after landing perfectly. Well,
I pressed up to try and pull you up because that's what I thought it was before.
Okay. We, we botched this twice in a row. What's the problem? You botched this because
you're the one letting go. Yeah. But it's, I feel like it's, this is very precise, very difficult.
I think you really, you really got a running jumpy. I don't know. You just got to do it.
You just got to be good. I'm going to go for it. I'm doing a perfect circle. That was, I mean,
that was good. That was like, I don't know if I could do better than that. I don't know if I
could have done better than that. That was like right there. What the hell? You've done better
than that. No, I didn't. I damn it. What are we doing? What am I doing wrong there? Are you
jumping or are you not? All right. Do you want, do you want to move on to the cat horror game or what?
I will continue to play as you want to play. Let's get up there one more time. And then
do you want to try that? Do you want to try that? It's tricky. This game is addicting though.
Really fun concept. I love the concept. Apparently you can play it in single player and you get like
a rock. That's weird. I'm not exactly sure how that works. Do you want to try these or do you
want me to just keep going for it? Stay in your lane. Yeah, but me staying in my lane didn't work
out the last time. I, you have more experience under your belt. That's true. I don't want to
throw that experience away, but like also you're really kind of trash. No, it's hard. You do it.
And you'll see it's hard. It's, it's like the moment. I'm doing it. You're trash. You're trash.
You are trash. You trash can garbage can. No, get back. You get back in there and you,
we're doing it. You closed it. Okay. We could, we could do it right.
I, it wouldn't be funny if you were, if you just weren't even close.
That's funny. How you doing? Are you, are you, are you good? You still, you still here? No,
sure. We, we can, I'll invite you again. Cool. All right, let's go. What do you like,
what do you like about these kinds of torture CBT games? Cause it, it shows the, it shows your
character. It shows if you're really able to persevere through something very, very difficult.
It takes a lot of patience, which I don't have any of, which is, it's a great challenge for me
because I have zero patience. What? I have zero patience. So it's a good challenge to sit down
and be like, just do it. Okay. You, I want you to do these because you need to get some experience.
I don't want to do it. I want to stay in our lane. Okay. We're going to stay in our lanes.
Okay. Why did we just do that? We could have just jumped normally.
Well, you were getting practice. Oh, I see. I do want you to be a little bit more confident in
these though. I don't need to do a full 360 for these tiny ones. You're right. No fucking,
I don't have patience. I do gardening and clay sculptures. Do you have any plants? No. Why not?
Why do I need plants? That's fun. Wrong way. What happens if now's not a good time to test?
Now's not a good time to test. I don't think it is. Remember this part. Well, that was weird.
I held it. I'm dying. I'm actually going to die. Stop. You're freaking me out. That one's actually
really, really hard. It is. Stop fucking around. Thanks. All right. We're back. Not yet. We're not
back yet. We're almost back. You fucker. You, you got in my head. You were like, you need to go faster
with these ones. Not this one. This one's tough. We're not, it's fine. We're right here. You're
doing those way too late. I know, but it's just, it's a little, just go. I'll get it again. I'll get
it. Okay. It's hard. I promise. It's tricky. Hey, you got the easy job. You just have to dangle.
There you go. There's no encouragement. Do not encourage. Don't encourage me. Okay. Which do you
like more, the game or me suffering? Oh, I need a full revolution for these. You got it. You got it.
We got it. That was a, that's tough one. Oh, wait, hold on. It's sweaty. Oh yeah. My game lagged. It
actually did. I swear to God people saw it. It was like, it actually happened. I swear to God,
it actually happened. It really happened. It's unfortunate. It really did. I wish I was making
it up. I'm not about those checkpoints. Stop and do it. All right. You, you claim to want to try
and then like, you get us in, we get out of a rhythm and then you like anchor yourself on the ground.
I'm, I'm coping. All right. This is the last one we're going to do. And then you want to play the
other game or you take it off. I keep hearing, this is the last one, but I feel like you really
deeply want this. I don't think we're going to beat it. I just want to get up to a hundred.
We're at like 75, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding. All right. Don't do that. Ding, ding,
actually stop doing that. Cause you're like a, you're like 30 milliseconds, like later,
I don't I don't like that. Finally, we can agree you're gonna fucking kill us keeping you on your toes. Uh-huh. You got it
Come on
There it is. All right, we're back. Oh, wow. We're back
Really back. This is this is the wall right here. It's been the wall the whole time
All right, let me let me get ready. So I'm doing it too late or too early
I don't know. I don't know what you're doing. This is to get a failure. Okay. All right. All right
You're not gonna make it. I'm doing it too late too late too late. I'm not gonna make it if you're going the wrong way
And there it is and there oh
We're back 72. This is where we lost last time. This is the one right here. We're gonna get up to a hundred
Stop looking around. I know you mess around. This one's fucked up. It is I need you on your a game
All right
I have to do this one a little later as we get some air because it's higher than us. All right
Here we go. I'm going for it. I need a full revolution bingo. All right, 75. Let's go. Oh
This one might be hard because is it is it a jump from here? No, it's not this is a game ender
This is if we slide down we got to climb all the way back up here again. All right, we're not gonna
That's that's not have the end
People saying save it right now. What button is saved? I gotta go into like cheater mode because it's options
Options has um, it's check do checkpoint checkpoint checkpoint. We bought we got a card didn't we so F is not let me try it
What is it on mine? What's on my friend and
Okay, let's try it ready. Yeah, I don't think it doesn't do anything doesn't do anything either. We talked to the guy
Let's might as well talk. I don't know
Assist mode needs to be turned on. Yes, just mode checkpoints. Ah
And then there's pole rope which was on by default
Infinite jumps who cares anymore? We don't need any of them. That's when I get to a hundred. Okay, so if we go oh, oh
Look at that. Okay, cool. So the plan is we know the plan. I grabbed first. Yes
Okay, and then I'm gonna let you go. You're gonna grab that wall. You gotta let go. You ready? Yes. Yes
All right, here we are we didn't even need the checkpoint look at this 85 we're good
This might be a run-and-jumper. Okay, let's do run. Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me. What?
All right, are you dumping your pants right now or are we playing you know, why we're gamer diapers, I'm just going for it
Fuck yeah, we got the clock. Let's go
Oh
Okay
Now, how do we get back to the checkpoint? I don't know. How do we get to the checkpoint? See em. Oh, I like this game
No, ready now. Let go. Thank you. We're fine. You look so defeated me your character. Oh
All right, let's go same deal. This is a run-and-jumper good idea. What are you doing?
Don't you criticize me when you don't know how hard it is. You gave it one attempt and you were like, yeah
You're not even waiting for the food. All right, you gave this one attempt an alt F forward the game
Fucking weird you didn't even grab anything you didn't either true. It's the quiet moments in life. I agree
You really take in the the snowflakes the beautiful horizon to its wonderful looking. Don't worry. I grabbed it. What's the plan here?
Oh
Perfect timing
This is a jump. This is a jump. This is a jump. Mm-hmm. This is a jump waiting for the countdown
I haven't seen it. This is a jump. Mm-hmm. You grab in a run start. I'll grab a call
This is a jump. Yes, it is run start. No, that's gonna fuck us up. It actually mmm
This might be a swing throw checkpoint. It might be let's just cheat
Let's jump at it and try and grab it if you miss. All right, what do you want?
I don't I mean if we're gonna cheat might as well cheat
Somebody's cheating. Are you ready? I
Got you. I think this is a regular jump to
There we are. Look at that get it out of your system cuz we're about to it's about to get hard
We made it we made it past the first area. We did it or not at a hundred yet. No, we're not
I mean that good call I guess now what oh, we're just like, yeah
Alright, I was about to do it too. No, you weren't cat horror game now
No, I'm going for it. I'm going for it, right? No, I can't start the swinging down here
It kills the momentum and if you drop I can see there's like shit down there. We don't got to do. Okay
All right, that's bad. No, they come back. Okay, let's walk over. I guess I just drop you down there
Oh, wait, we angle you down. Wait, wait, wait
That's a jump up here jump up to the wall. This might need a running start here. Let's go to the other side
We're gonna run across and do a jump up. Oh, yeah, just in case we're gonna be careful. I feel you
Oh, this is gonna be hard. Do you want me to grab?
Yeah, I want you to fucking grab it. Well, I have you played this before
Yeah, I you know, I didn't you did even if I was gonna grab you didn't give me enough time to swing over and grab
I didn't even give me enough to let go. I love it. You flip. I love it
You flipped it on me. You flipped it on me, but you just went for it. You flipped it on me, too
That was uncalled for you could have grabbed
Okay, everything's fine just relax
Wait for wait for me to grab it. You gotta go. Yep on me up or do you you're gonna pull me up?
Are we what's happening here? I'm enjoying this. I really need like rest, you know, I
Did it myself don't worry
Three one, two, three go. I don't do that. I had to
Don't do that
You have to it that's it bill it's built-in timing. All right. All right. All right. All right. We're good
You just gotta go for it. All right built-in timing. We're just doing the built-in timing. It's built in just do a plot
It's a normal platformer right now. Oh, yeah
Okay now wait patience figure out where we're going
This is tricky cuz we have to jump together to that top left. You'll grab it and then we'll swing. No, no, no
No, wait, wait, you don't think so. Yes, you're right. I'm gonna I'm gonna jump in I'm gonna grab it
built-in timing
Good. Okay, that's gonna fall. So built-in timing. Okay. Okay. Good. Oh
Wait, hold on. We don't have to there's no built-in timing right now. There is it's a platform
We need to see what's going on here. We get his go. Just jump up to it. Oh, wait, wait
All right, you're any fucking bill in timing and you didn't even do it, right, sir
I'm gonna enjoy this
Thank you. Thank you for like for taking a second here because I can fucking use it
Built-in timing top left. Wait, wait, wait
Okay, you can't just do that. What are you talking about?
We got a swing and then you we need to run yes built-in timing after you land good good idea
This might be built-in timing built-in timing. I'm not sure
Oh
Get up here get up here get up here get up here we've ducked no, I don't know what to do
Right. I do rap feels the timing build the timing this way. All right, we're fine
We've got it. All right, you grab you always grab first
It didn't grab cuz I was on the ground I expected it to grab
What what kind of fucked up Mario game have you been playing with the built-in timing is that early?
We need to wait for this I think
Oh, I think I I think I think I know what to do. Oh my god
Okay, we I don't know. I don't get it. We need to look at it for a second
I'm kind of wondering if you can grab the side of it. What about just jump and left left. I duck
Okay, we got it like either swing to that platform. I think I think we go left from the middle here built-in timing
Wait, what? What have you done? No
No, I thought we built in time. I thought we built in tits. All right built into what you said
I think we need left. I didn't know what left you meant. Sorry lucky to just pick this up. We're fine
Okay, so we're gonna drop and then go left drop left built in timing pull me up
You grab then we'll swing that was fucked up and you know, it that was weird on you. You did great
What are you? What are you doing? What's happening to you?
What's happening to you? You didn't anchor when I we why did you not anchor?
This is so
How come you jumped weird you're weird
It's all right, it's all right for some stupid reason I thought this is gonna drop to we're fine
See you need to anchor who?
How are we doing this? I don't know we just talk about it. Can we just talk through this? Let's talk
I think we can make the jump from here to there if we do it
And then we built in timing
To the top right. Okay, maybe
Yep. Okay, we're good now stop and let's look at this one, too
We're gonna gotta as the things coming down. We're gonna need to built in timing built in timing building timing. Hold on
That's fucked up. Isn't it? Okay. Okay next one
We're doing next one as soon as we see the next one coming down. We're gonna jump across
All right, but what how far down is it back midway?
What do you want to go midway? Do you want to wait till it's kind of at the bottom?
What do you think I think we have to wait till it's past the bottom?
Because otherwise we'll hit our heads. I'm gonna count it down. All right almost do you get infinite checkpoints?
Stirb wanted to cheat and I was okay
I kept saying man
We should really try to do it like on our own and try to really get the achievement of doing it
But he was like he DM me a few times over here. Just like dude
I'm fucking leaving if you don't let me do this. He's like, I'm gonna make up a story how I have to go
Then I'm just like
Right annoying good job
Man we're on our toes. Okay, this is double coming by
Hold me up to the right
Pull me up. Pull me up. Pull me up. We need to not good timings
These are not we need it cuz automatic timings cuz I your timing on where you would do that jump is different than mine
Yeah commander. Give me the give me the little bit
I don't even know what button that is on mine. I have a different controls. No. No, you don't need to do that
Just like vocally. Okay, I'm gonna go tell me about it. All right ready three two one go
There we are again again again
If we have to go like you stopped, I know but I I was
distracted
Can you get on that?
Let go. Oh nice job. All right, pull me up
Three two one. All right, we gotta go boom. Boom. You ready? One, two, three go
Nope
There we are. Boom. Boom. Then this is another good. This is ready one two go. I wasn't ready
I but I wasn't ready. It's all right. I but that wasn't you got to take quarterback then
You got to be quarterback. Look at these fucking timings. Very good. That's not correct. That was does not it's not correct
Okay, three two one go. Okay. Okay. I understand. I did not understand what you're talking about. So I'm ready to go
All right, just just jump off off here. Okay, we're gonna
Very good. Very good. I think I'm lost
There look at that. Oh my fingers cramping up. Okay. Here's what's gonna happen
Three two one go we jump on those. Okay, and they're gonna fall and then grab you're gonna grab nice
This one looks like it's a jump grab and then I grab wall and then I okay. Hold on
We gotta get this planned out. This is a we jump you grab the left side of wall
I swing around I grab right side of wall you go. I let go we land on built-in timing
We have to built-in timing jump to that right wall and I don't know what the hell's over there
Yep, so you're gonna grab that right most wall. Yep. Okay, right. Let's all the way to the left running start
Yep for this one. Okay. Here we go. Okay good. I'm gonna grab the other side of the wall. Mm-hmm
Okay, here we go
Beautiful. All right. This is where it gets kind of weird. Are we checkpoint Andes?
Yeah, we're look we've already done
Six of them so far all of the tension is gone. Hey, it's we're having fun though
Well, I thought I think we just jump when it's hitting the bottom or no when it's hitting the top maybe yeah
Hey ready, I'm gonna count three tops and then we're gonna jump
Okay, we jump on the fourth top so like one two jump on the third one or jump on the like technically the fourth one
like top top
Top Joe. Okay. Okay. Okay one two three
We're okay
I think it's gonna work. I think I think it's gonna work. Okay
top
top top
Bottom. Yeah, see
This is a built-in timing this is we jump right when we hit the top and then built-in timing to the right, okay
All right
Same deal
We're your top top go. No, keep it the same top top top go
There's no need for three top top top. There is keep it consider. You told me to stay consistent with our roles
Consistency there's an update. There was a patch
Top top go top top go. Okay, you do the count top
Top go
I went look at us
We don't even got a fucking talk about it people that people that come to the stream
Are they don't tell them we're using checkpoints until they have to find out cuz they'll think we're good at the end
So I gotta like I gotta like hold on. Yeah, what's yeah, what's the deal here? We got we gotta hide it. Oh
Hide it. I see what what is that? It's part of the environment. It's a piece of wood
Okay, okay
So I'm gonna jump and grab and then I don't know you jump and grab and then you have to let go when I get
To the point where I can yeah, that's the hold on. Oh, it doesn't break. Oh, okay
Alright don't jump and grab. Okay, this doesn't make sense
You yeah, you need to land what let's grab the I think we could do grab the other side
What we get one of us can get up and land on top. So like yeah
No, I don't think that's a strat just hit a swing around and land on top of this just land on it
But it's gonna break and then you're gonna be dangling below me
All right, what do you want to do? There's a hole the whole area to the right is extra. Um, I think that's actually what we have to do
Or maybe go up. No, maybe go from the top. If can we like throw ourselves up? All right, just give me some I
I don't know how the grab is allowed to work here. Hold on. I don't know
You're driving. Oh, I thought you want to try something. So what what's your plan? I want to try and not fall on it
Oh
Try to grab the other side. That's what I'm saying, but it doesn't let me like swing inward. Mm-hmm. I have an idea
Let me throw you
It might
Everybody we're gonna do our
20 minute everybody closes their eyes and relaxes. Okay, close your eyes
What are you doing? We didn't do check one. All right, whatever. Well, we got it. Okay. I tried to grab it
It's dead it's it has to be you grab the other side
No, no
Pull me up you swing you do this swing. So I'm gonna grab it. Okay, you do a full rotation
That's why we stick to our roles, huh? Oh, it's not as easy as it looks. Oh you tried it one time. I
Didn't I know?
Shut up and get off here. Do you hold left or do you have to go like one do I got it?
Then you hold there then once you've spun around you hold the direction
Okay, I get it. I thought you had I thought I still had to change momentum from different sides
I didn't know you could hold it. Thanks for telling me the controls by the way
Oh, wow, when you're only going one direction, you only hold one direction. We open our eyes. Not yet. It's still relaxing time
Are you ready? Oh my god. Oh, I was thinking okay. Okay
We've just been learning we've been learning the rules of the world. Yes, we have
Okay, you can open your eyes now. Chill. I don't know. I don't know we're good
I think we just have to just whip our just throw ourselves to the left kind of here you hold
We assume our roles we're going for you got it. That was weird. It was weird. I
Think yeah, yeah, it doesn't really give any momentum
I think you have to grab the other side after you get thrown over there. It's gonna be
It actually might not be that hard if you if we do it like I throw you kind of in the air like this
I think here's what I think. Here's what I think. Here's what I think. Here's what I think. Here's what I think
Here's what I think. Here's what I think. Here's what I think when I'm swinging around
Yeah, and I'm slightly above it
You need to let go so you're dropping pulls me down and then I grab the other side and so I'm like here
Kind of rare kind of kind of kind of kind of I don't I feel like this isn't the way to do it and we're gonna
Get like the advanced version of this and we're not gonna be we're just gonna be I don't know what we're gonna be
Hey, I'm gonna do it like shit, there's no way that both way grab both climb and run
There's climbing what I mean climbing. I don't think you can climb you replace stir with penis music
You mean to round out stir with penis music that be wouldn't be able to hear his call out. Just climb just climb
Okay, you hold on you hold it. Whoa. Hold on a minute again. Hey, hold on stay there. Hey, let go
I almost had it. That was close
That was very close. It's not what ready
Let go now. Oh my god. I had it. I just should have jumped the other way
They're eating her then they're gonna eat me. We got ready shit. That's it. I'm the third swing
Do you want to do it? Do you want me to do it? You do it? I'm the grabber. That's one
Do you do the third one you're in the perfect spot?
Mmm, I heard but then I don't get I don't get it. I don't get when you're on there. It's just gonna break
And I'm dangling unless you like perfectly grab the left side without ever standing on it. Just do it swing again. I'm here
Yeah, the left wall has to get grabbed you grab okay one two three
Hell yeah. All right. Hold on. Well, that was weird it bumped me. Yeah, we got it. Nice
All right, you can open your eyes. Okay, there's a wooden horizontal over there
Yeah, I think I just get to that and a built-in timing
The jump was uh
Weird. Oh, man. We should have put a no, we don't need it. I hear you. That's weird one two three
Easy
Honestly, whoa
Honestly, I don't know why people would have trouble with that
Like I don't know why anyone would get here and like not be able to do that first try one two
three
Okay
Keep going
Wow, all you had to do is let go I was freaking out. Can you put down a everybody close their eyes flag?
I don't see anything right now. What um, how high can we jump?
We got to jump up to the right one then to the left one. Can we make that? Yeah, I'm here
Yeah, I don't know about that one. These do I what's over here?
nothing, oh
Where does that go? Oh, let's jump on it. Oh
Jeepers how in tarnation did you get up here? It must have been a tough journey. Am I right kids?
The seal by golly. It ain't mine, but we are closer than two catfish in a skillet
Now her name is Gertrude. How would I know?
This guy's a fucking nobody
That timing is not right. Can you pull me up?
You pull me up. I mean, let's just try it
Yeah, the worst that happens is we fall and we built in timing just back up here to the right
falling down on that one
Like a pro. Okay
Soon as it clicks into the top, we're gonna jump. Yeah, and I'm gonna grab in the right side
What the fuck?
There are no stakes anymore
Matter
You don't don't drop it. Okay, I'm gonna count it down one two three
Close your eyes nice. Oh my accolades my accolades we were a little too underneath
Actually, no grab
No, just call the key to and get us the fuck back up there, please
Accolades, okay. We stand on the right side of this thing. We keep bumping our heads two
Three you gotta let you gotta let me go. No, I don't yeah
That's all that's all you you gotta let me go. All right, this is built-in timing, but we have to be careful
Okay, this is a jump. Yes, I
Get it now, but oh my god, if I put my brain on like a 50 millisecond delay
We are perfectly in sync. Those jumps were like jump. Wait jump
Wait jump and it was perfect. Yeah, that's how I that's how you make sure that you can be together
I'm not in timing is when you land you just jump to the next one because you've already landed. Yes
That's not what that was
Yeah, I know but you're where point five with 50 milliseconds behind any other anyways, okay
No, it's more like it's it's more than 50 you do understand that even you talking through discord is coming through
No, it's more than it's more than 50. It's like a half a second. It's like jump
Okay, confirm. We've both landed have a cognitive. I understand. Okay now jump. It's not like jump land jump land
Yeah, it's it's not that it is not this it is jump boom
I didn't know that you were doing that this whole time when you say like built-in timing these things fall
It's like okay jump, but you have to get like the jump has to land
We have to make sure we've land the jump first, but it only takes that long to know
Yeah, but but here's the thing. I you don't know because that's what you gotta like see it. It'd be like, yes
Okay, we've lined it. Yeah, but you understand that we're doing this together
So we both need to land boom land, but like you have to built-in timing built-in timing
Timing is we we are both landing at the same time already
That's why we don't need to wait for the other person to land because the jump what it's not in timing
Timing is when you land we've done it line the whole time
It's there's no you're okay. You're making it sound like it's like land pause land. No
Let's go back go back to the checkpoint. Okay. Now. Let's do it my way
The moment you land we're just immediately going okay
No, but it's fucked up. It's fucked up because yes, it is. Yes. I am do it go back and do it again ready
Why were you slow that time because I thought we were doing German time. No, no
No, that's not what I said do your time your time. Okay, my time. That's not enough time
That's not enough time because like that's you we synchronized with the three two one go and then after that it's automatic time
Not pause reps, there's no it's not a pause rep. It's a
confirmation
50 milliseconds to make sure we've actually landed
It's it's a confirmation if you jump jump jump jump jump. What if you miss?
What if you know, you're gonna make sure you're in a nice spot
We could if you miss you already missed there's no need to stand still and confirm you've missed
It's good. No, it's a confirmation. Okay, so in the future are we doing pause reps or are we doing like gamer reps?
What the gamer reps to me is a mistake in a game like look in any other scenario?
I would agree with you in a game like this. You have to confer you put something in my eye
What did you do to my eye? All right, you ready? Got him. Got him. Hey. Hey, what the fuck dude? What are you doing?
Are you ready? We're going
germapace
But we we did not even confirm that that was our different your timing of like go go go go
I'm on beats right like
I'm on when you actually land is what your needs to occur. You're like
No, you gotta be on a tempo. It's gonna be like you're not doing a tempo
Say there are it's not a sound thing. It's a visual. I have jumped
I'm like it's as soon as you can jump jump. All right, but here's the jump
All right before you make everybody leave the stream with your with your incessant anger towards me and you're bickering
Have we had a problem this whole time? Yes
Since when I think that problem has come up several times. We've never fallen our jump
That jump was a little bit messed up like here is the first time I noticed it because it's a very clearly these things will
Fall and you need to go across them as quickly as possible German mights who's with me stir Mata
Get in the battlements
Shoot the cannons at the stir Mata. All right, you ready? Can we do this and uh, what happened there?
Mr. Super timing mr. Perfect timing
What is you're just fuck with me now he's fucking with me I was
Pull me up it's slippery. I okay
Automatically did a germapause rep on that one. We didn't have a plan. We didn't have a plan
What do you mean? We we've done this jump sixty times. We didn't we didn't have a plan
Fifty percent of the game is this and why did you just jump right there, sir?
Because I'm having an aneurysm our fall
That was wait that was not us it was
No, that was like our toes got stuck. It's because it's slippery
No, that's not what it was
That was like our toes got stuck on the edge and we didn't jump forward pause. I
Haven't even been doing that. You're just making it seem like I don't know what I'm doing and that's not exactly anything that happened
I think it was very clearly demonstrated exactly what you were doing. I think everyone is seen. We took a poll
the germamite
Warship has I got a 95% they were on my side. I did pull I speaking of 95% critic reviews
Yeah, how about that Diablo 4 season one? How you feeling? You know, let's not you do this is bad
You don't want us to talk about this. We'll be on this like four hours
The second we get on D for it's like it's over
I've read I was reading my chat just get lucky to bring us back over there, please. I can't when I'm dangling
Well, we don't we need to come up with a plan. We got a jump here. Oh, we we it's a jump jump
Jump, it's weird over jump over them. Oh, that's gonna okay. You gotta land on the platform pal. Uh, I
I honestly buster
Hold on a second before you before everybody starts screaming about my accolades. You are the host you are the host
You are the host pal. What do you mean pal?
Now you listen here buster. Okay
Can we just like act like this is a single-player game and just jump over it like the slow-moving thing?
We can jump on it. You know how to jump on this. Yes
What do we go from there? You gotta wait till it gets to the top and jump, right? Oh
Now you listen here buster I was ahead of you. Yeah, where does your loyalty stand? It's important. Are we going?
You listen here buster. What was that about? Got it?
I see you gotta get to the top of the mountain. Let's say we do don't as we need to establish contact with these other villages
That's not gonna be right. That was totally it. It was not you just hit your head on the side
You didn't jump. No, I got my head stuck on the rope. Don't run it back
I don't think we can even make this jump run it back, dude
You you got we gotta get a look at it first
It's it's built-in timing. It's germapause rep built-in timing when it when we lock in left we go
Onto the Metroid block. I feel like I've been doing it like that the whole time
built-in what are you oh
Windy winds slippery very slippery slippery slippery
Just keep going. You see there's like wind up there. Mm-hmm. I'm worried about that. Oh
You should be
Okay, it does like pull us. We have to use the wind. What is this? Oh god
Once it once it kicks in nice
Let's jump loser loser loser. What's in here secret any secrets in here doesn't look like it. Oh
We can put on different costumes. How did you do that? Oh, we can change our BDSM rope. Oh
Pog you got this
Okay, just wait wait wait wait once it ends we go once that's just just anchor and then once that once the next one ends
Um, hold on like I have been like hands been like this on the arrow keys the whole time on my right hand
Okay next also. We didn't really talk about that either
Okay, anchor. We didn't talk about that either
I'm using my right hand to play this game. You're using your left hand. You're used to your left. I'm being used
I got your anchor. Just keep it. I just keep it anchored. Think about that. I am NOT doing WASD because I can't
Just anchor we need upper. Yeah, we're gonna need to do a spin jump. Why am I getting question-marked? Were you here earlier?
Do dude what we need to okay, right? Thank her. I'm I'm
What is this about a left hand that you can't your brain?
Can't go to your fingers in your right arm isn't you aren't you right hands dominant muscle memory is?
You're on you you're using WASD with your left hand. That is what you are used to using when you play a video game
I'm your right hand being on arrow keys is a different muscle memory. Can I give you like a word of advice?
No, can you put your left hand on the arrow keys?
But that's weird because like I'm crossing my body and then but I feel like turn the kid. That's weird
That's weird. Like at that point. I would have to like move my seat. It's weird
I mean people get it some of you get it if you get it you get it if you don't then you dumb
Wow
All right, you ready Wow
Whoa, whoa. I don't know what we're doing. We make that jump
I think we go to the bottom unless you want to try to get the top right?
Let's try top right if we fall we fall. Okay, let me get to where you are first though move the keyboard
I don't have that's like I don't have a room to do that
Right anchor. We're gonna okay as soon as this next win ends. We're gonna do the big jump
Stop fucking pulling me. Well, what are you doing?
I need to get a full rotation so we can jump across. I know but we have to wait till the wind is gone
Yeah, so why do you keep interrupting me because I'm getting the rotations going
Okay, you ready? Don't do it. I'm not going to I'm ready cuz I can go while the winds going for some reason
Okay, here we go. It was climb climb. The chatter said you could climb
Hold it. Hold hold hold. Oh
We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. We're gonna go left left. Just wait. Just wait. Oh back of all he fell off
He's doing
Get up here. No, it's windy
Pull me pull me pull me. Don't go down
Thanks for waiting hon. I see how much compensation I did there. Don't tell me you don't know what I'm doing
What I think we can make that I don't think we I don't go for a run I think, right?
Okay, we got we gotta remember we gotta double jump up the hill. Yes, you've gone. Yep. Oh
You're so greedy I was just you I
Can greedy oh dude, it's been it's been like so much fun. How long we've been playing this game for? Oh, wow, like 16 hours
so greedy
once it ends
I freaked out you freak out sometimes too. We freak out sometimes
Everyone is a little freak out. That's usually you time it. I'm just gonna go back
Just wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, just go back
You you've timed it the last few times
Once the wind ends, I know but you've done like the din din
Thought you were gonna go for it. Greedy. Greedy
Stay you guys having fun. How you guys doing? You guys having fun? Everybody doing good. I actually read my chat. Oh
You're really gonna pull that I don't know what that means
What is this I
We have to jump with the wind. We gotta jump probably probably and then I have to throw you with the wind
That's definitely what this is. Okay. So now I gotta throw you with the wind. Hold on. Let me get in a better spot
Okay, wait for the wind. I'm gonna go when it starts to blow in three two. No
Don't tell me no when I'm confident. Don't tell this guy. No
All right, freeze was what did we do? No, you're so sassy. I
Think that we jump on this platform
Nah
Hold on. Okay, we need to see how long it was gonna stay there for
Why we thought six times? Oh, it's to get one more rotation
I'm not I don't feel comfortable about this
But you don't you want to get it right or do you want to get it wrong and I have people omega low and have a
Thumbnail pull me up. Hey, is your refrigerator running? Yeah, I think so you got me
I have to throw you I gotta throw you to that in the wind
You got to grab it and then we got to go. What the fuck just happened. Are you ready?
One more I
Won this thing moves in the wind. I don't think I'm gonna be able to keep my momentum. Yeah, that kills it
So you're gonna start when we're on our way to the left. I can't like I'm we're not gonna be able to get 360s
But the wind will take us further. Okay, so right now I think it's like that. All right, it's the Lakita up there
Yeah, this is ruining my morning. You both suck. What what's going on?
Wait, what do you mean? Where are you? Where are you? All right ready? I'm like exhausted
I've been pushed to my limit
All right now I'm gonna swing you ready one more
No, okay one more. I gripped it. But why did that happen? I actually gripped it and he just went I hurt
I heard it that does happen sometimes
That's why you need the lucky to look Lakota. I
Grew the yoko
We're gonna instantly go instantly. That would be better as soon as it comes down. Yep
So how we need more momentum on this one? How do we get it? Because if I do it there, it won't work
There we go. Give me one more. Give me one more one more. You got it. My fingers fell off the muscle fucking man
We're good. We landed. Oh my god. Why did we both just not do anything? That's not where we're going, right?
That's not where we're going
Because we we've been
Alright, let me get it two more one more right there
All right
There you go, I can't I can't
We're gonna jump when the wind comes. Yep. Oh
No, no, no. Oh
Let's just walk the other way
But we didn't see what was up there
You were gonna fall off too. You were gonna fall the fuck off you if I didn't fall you're so happy that I felt
It's just gotten worse and you think we'd get better at this shit. Let me just take a look and see what my hand looks like
Oh boy, that's uh
That's not good
What is not good? I did a thing. That's millennial humor, which both Millennials. Okay. Sorry
Next one. Yeah, one wasn't right. Give me two more. Ah
Thank you. All right. All right next win starts. So we're just gonna go go go go go. Mm-hmm. Okay, you got it
Jesus. All right. Now I gotta throw you over there
Jesus, okay
This is further than you thought we'd get right 270. I I thought we I thought we were gonna quit the game like an hour
And a half ago. All right. What's the plan here? Let's jump. Uh, yeah
I can we make I don't know
I think we do the running one
the other side
Nice, uh, and then when the wind starts, we're gonna have to do a jump. Yep
Whoa, I overshot it the first time
Let's jump straight up
Can we make the left one? I gotta wait for the wind
Oops
Are you doing as soon as the wind hits?
You fucked it up. I you didn't jump. I did they didn't but I was pulling you I was pulling you it's like off
Sink it's weird when I fall. It's my fault when you fall. It's weird a full straight run
No, when the wind starts when the wind starts, I just straight up straight up when the wind starts
All right, you grabbing or am I grabbing I think we can make the job grab
Okay, I'll grab these I'll grab it you grab the other one. Okay, let go here. Oh fuck. Yep
Good thing you were a little bit further
All right. What's the plan here? I guess it's that
What
Troll dumb just get us back. What what what?
burger
Sounds good
Double jump does it blow with the wind? I think we got it
We got to do it when it's above our head
No shit, that's weird
What the heck? I got you. I got you baby boo-boo
Can you pull me up? I keep swinging. I don't trust that. No, I'm the swinger
Okay, I'm gonna go right when we oh, no, I think you have to start doing it down here
Yeah, cuz the winds gonna mess it up
It's my hitting my head on the corner is what it is. I'm gonna move to the right a little more. I got it
No
Let me move to the right a little bit more
See if that does it. Mm-hmm. I've got it. Trust trust. Okay
I'm gonna go on this one. Okay. Oh
No, what?
Go jump anchor
anchor in this stanker
That was kind of like a I just I'm piecing together what you just said
Going on this one
We're gonna go gotta go gotta go gotta go gotta go
Okay after the wind. Yeah, we should get a countdown there pink for the clouds purple for the mountains. Uh-huh
I'm starting to visualize it
They're actually like it's hard to climb this and there's so many people up here solo. I don't like that lore
How much further is coming? I wonder come here for a run and jump
Wait, we need the wind and also it seems like if you stand behind this wall, the wind doesn't affect you. Oh
It doesn't
Wait, I didn't I know that was weird start at late. So I decided to call it
Okay, when the wind starts I called it. Yeah
You're for the best. You're not even on the ground. I got it. I got it again. I got it. All right
I thought we may have kept moving not risking it
All right, so you grab and then you want me to grab the other side of the wall? Yeah
Right now mid wind
I'm not you're grabbing right you go you go. Yeah. All right. I'm going to grab the other side
What that was a buggy bug bug that was a bug bug bug that was a bug that was a bug it was a bug
I was a bug. That was that was a bug. That's a bug. I wasn't even holding on to the side. Just go second one. Okay, I
Let's wait for this
Platform go
But do it good. Yeah, but dude, it's the first try. Don't worry Lakitu's bringing us right back. Oh first try
We're up 250 meters this mountain first try. We've never done this before
I was concerned that if I was gonna throw you too far
You fucking dunce. That's not a dunce scenario. That's uh, you
You didn't even anchor. I'm the dunce
You got up there and you stood there
I'm the dunce. I'm the dunce though. You're gonna let go of the wall. You didn't anchor
you dunce
I'm gonna get it. No, you're not
But if you what have you done?
We've done you dunce. Okay, I've got it this one got this one, but it dunce you've done
You fucking
Mm-hmm. We got this fast. This is easy. They're nice. Nice job dunce. I'm gonna let this one go
We jump straight up swing up we swing up we jump up watch that wind nice job watching the wind
Do one go?
Pull me up
Thanks, dude, feel bad. I was gonna say moron, but he didn't deserve it. Wait, we need wind
Are you gonna make that jump without wind you're doing the countdown
That doesn't mean you jump
He's doing the countdown this countdown. This countdown is real. Oh, you don't need it. That was slippery
It sure was buster
We need a much bigger running start
Dunce and duncer
Stay there. All right. Yeah, we need a
Okay, just chill here but and we're gonna double jump. Yeah, wait, no, we're not what are you
I would like wait. I would like the evidence into the courtroom here
Said no, we're not and then got angry when I didn't go we're gonna jump to this one
But then we're gonna stop there because we need to swing. Yes, we're too big. We'll jump. Yes, we do. I got it
What are you doing? Okay
That just fucked us up a little more
Okay, can you get us back up? Where's the key to how do I call them?
Let's just just just just just jump just jump
I
Put the it's all right. Everybody relax everybody relax
Let me we need a full full revolution here for sure. Okay. Oh just don't no. No. No, I'm freaking out
I'm freaking out. Just keep walking left
Okay, we're good. We're gonna we we got to jump up to the left and then
Just be aware. We're gonna have to jump up to the left and then like get a little bit of a run. Yep
So all all the way over. Okay, let's I'll count it. I'll count it down
If we need to count it because we're connected to each other at the hip
God, I wish we weren't or were okay. That was always cuz it was because we're good. That's time
It was in time, right? I did it. It just didn't do it
It's fucking hard. Okay, just just chill just chill. It's gonna blow us off
Walk again stay you can't it blows you off
Bro, it doesn't it doesn't it doesn't it doesn't hey check this out, bro
Look at this. Look at this. Look at this
Look at this. All right one
Hey, can you pull me up do I fell off
Did you do can you pull me up? Oh
Could you uh, give me a little bit of a pull?
Yeah
If we don't do it this time, it's red
Hey, you fell off you fell off because you decided to anchor instead of walking to the right on the ice
Can you say Barney loud for me?
Actually, I'm warning
Barney Barney Barney
Different I think um, we gotta get back up to the top red. This is not even hard. We've done way harder things
Pretty good. Yeah, just wait. We've got the road. We're rushing through this. No, we're not
We're you the wind once it starts do not anchor on ice, but sometimes it gives you an extra little boost. No
No
nice Mike
But you were silent
You were just like
Front
You didn't say anything, but you just said uh, we're gonna get different
Keep going. I'm ready. I'm just calling me a piece of shit
But here is the conundrum you are you are way ahead of me. Do you get it now?
No, because I'm throwing you bro. I'm throwing you I think we could just make this jump to the right
Yeah, when I throw you you are like a full you're a full rope length ahead of me
All right, so we're gonna read a full fully documented plan. I'm sending you the email right now. Okay, what's what's in it?
It's a subject keep going. Just keep walking right don't anchor on ice
Keep going timing keep going. I got it. We're going left. We're going left anchor you anchor. I
Don't we need to do that. Yes. This is bad. This is gonna be horrible. Oh dear. Oh
oh
Botha
With the window we have how much more time do you need but I'm just trying to figure out if it's with the window
I feel like I'm gonna go flying past
Oh bother
Regular job, let's wait for the wind
Uh-huh. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow
Wow
Wow, come on
Come on
That was like a fucking fairy tale which
I've got you in my college ready. All right, we're gonna do
You got this I'm ready. Are you ready?
It's we're doing like the family guy fall down thing
Oh
What's the fucking family are running right once the wind hits? Oh
Right. I don't know. What do we do there? I think we're doing it wrong
We can both jump and grab the wall, ah
But why?
So that's the thing the floor doesn't break when the wind comes when the wind comes now. Well, it'll respawn. Oh
What a smart?
You got it. Just
We got a smart ass over here. You are kind of a no, you're not you're fine
no, I
Know but I just thought of like the grimace birth thing again, and it's like fuck with me
Month-long
What's up? It's I don't even know what to say
Okay, say less. Is this a throw scenario? Yeah, I'm gonna move up a little no actually we're good. No
Right keep walking, right?
Keep walking, right? I am I am. Oh, I don't know what you did. I forgot to give the second instruction
Stop walking, right? Hey, what if I threw him right now? I forgot to give the second instruction stop walking, right? Yeah, I
Okay, so let's like just like pause when we're on the ice because apparently we're doing a lot of germa pause reps
I love how this all comes back to me doing this somehow
but
pause
nice
Smooth
No, no, no, no the winds are Howard Howard Howard. We would have gotten going on Howard Howard Howard
It says three two one go. That's when you go
Give it a second. We don't do well that
Did you shave your eyebrows?
No, I probably need to I probably need to do some cleanup on my eyebrows though. They're probably fucking filthy
One of us to get it. I want to hear I want to hear it. Don't talk. We're gonna do this. Oh
Let go
That's a lot of talking
Okay. Okay. I hate this. I hate this. We're going back. This is totally an optional room. I
Don't think it is. I think it is. I think we're waiting for the wind here to jump left. Okay, you say so
I'm gonna do a trick. Where do we go from? Oh
There's gonna be a tough one. It is
We just wait for the wind and I just do it normally
Like this dance you goober we got an achievement for that. Yeah. Yeah, how do we both miss that?
Call the taxi, whatever it is
Hey me Lords, have you tried waiting for each other to jump you have a dent in your head?
Was that you reading a comment cuz I thought you were responding to that person I was like that
He wouldn't usually go in like that
Thought you meant that was you thought I was talking to you
No, what you read the comment the guy said why don't you try waiting to jump and you were just like hey
You got a dent in your head. I didn't realize it was a back-to-back comment
That's true that sounded so fucked up that was
Okay
The our continuation of the let's play
Okay, ready. Yeah
Trashing he's turning purple. Where's my countdown? Oh
Sensory overload the winds not even here you don't
Sensory over and stop my fault. There's too many noises
Death in your head
Hold on fucking rude. That's so fucking like horrible
Why can't we do this anymore? I think we got a jump a little later. Oh
We're like, we're being very conservative with our jump
Okay, we said how is your hair middle and side parted?
Get it. I don't get it. You got a dent in your head. I don't know maybe
Is it is it? I can't I need to look I got I got it. I got it
Hold hold hold hold here. You stop. Um, stop fucking around
What do you mean stop fucking around? You just fell off twice and you've been around so much. Stop you fucking around
It's I'm the spinner. Yeah, but we need to assess what's going on with this situation ahead of us. There is a
Okay, I get it. You're ready. I've been ready. I wasn't though and it's a team game
It's a team game and I wasn't
I didn't think we were gonna make it. I can't believe you did the tutorial of red dead 2 and just be like this game's dumb
I didn't finish it. I just saved your life
Well, we should have double jumped why we don't just went cuz we're on a fucking time limit
Go go. Oh, this is it. We're almost the end. What are you doing? All right
You'd like the ghost took over the computer for a second. What are you doing? I was wondering if that was affecting you
Huh, I was adjusting my music volume. Oh, I turned it way down already
Three two one go I bumped my head on it
Yeah, gaga Google. Oh you want to go? No. No, you said stay in our lanes, right?
Like do what we know what we're doing with the without it's definitely without or is it is it with or without?
it's with
Wait, it might not be I guess it is. Okay
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, pull me up. Pull me up. I'm a little baby
Yeah, oh
I see you want to put a checkpoint after every jump now because you want to be done with this game that you despise so
much I
Get you. Yep. Holy shit. Okay. Well because look at you
Look at you look in the mirror. You're I wouldn't be able to finish this one you ever
I'm looking in the mirror. What is it something my face? What's what my fucking hair? I have the double part. What's going on?
I think we could practice this game for an eternity and without checkpoints. It would never end. Uh,
I felt the same way by the game only up and it was so hard and then I started watching people do like
15 minutes speed runs of that game and yet that was on you that was I don't know where we're going after that
Tbh, whoa, that was weird. I've been comparing only up to dark and darker and I can see how you would like them both
What what do you mean explain I don't think I should
Yeah, yeah, yeah
What do you mean explain? Sorry, I wasn't paying attention. They're both unfinished streamer bait trash. Okay, it's been in the wrong way
All right, just hold tight on me up. Okay. Now, where we going against the wind when it comes go left
Nice. Okay. Okay
Okay, um, I mean but can I ask you a question? Yeah, and you have to answer honestly
Mm-hmm. Can you name me three games that have come out in the last five years that you genuinely really enjoyed?
Yeah, what what are they?
Without looking up a like Google sheet of the game. I'm trying to look up something else. Did you play bet and brutal? No
Exactly. I rest my case
Drama Oh only up. I love only up. I'm gonna check out the speedruns. Oh and if these die play bet and brutal
No, I played only up for like four hours once
Exactly. I didn't when did I say that only up was the game of the year? I said
I said like like I said named a few games in the last five years that you genuinely enjoyed
In the last five years. Yeah name like three
Do they have to have released in the last five years or can I enjoy them? Yeah, like a game that's come a games
I've come out in the last like let's say three years
That you like really would like wow, I really enjoyed that you got to name me at least three
Elden ring Q remastered risk of rain to
Yep, I don't you can't which light infinite. You told me in private that you didn't like it. Didn't like what or tight I didn't
You're you're weird. Can I tell you why you're weird? Why am I weird?
Cuz you'll like okay, I brought up like pizza tower, right? Yeah, and I was like pizza tower
Oh, you should really try it. I think it's like one of the best games to come out this year
And you played it and you were like don't ever recommend me a game ever again
That's not what I said. I just said I it wasn't for me. I
respect
Pizza tower, but it is not for me. Okay, it may have been more
He was a little dramatic at the time. Well, hey, hey, why we're gonna have this whole conversation when I brought up Diablo 4 season 1
Early, you know, you didn't want to talk then. Oh, it was just a hater
Beloved game but love Diablo for the one of the greatest entries in the Diablo series pull up
Oh, you want to talk about it?
I just got really sick and tired of picking up Saigon's boots over and over and over again
You fucking wish that game would drop Saigon's boots. Yeah
Stir has horrid opinions. I don't think stir is horrid opinions stir and I actually agree on quite a lot chat
You're dying on the hill of only up a game that's getting fucking like destroyed for like
Non-fair use NFT shit in their game. You're dying on the hill of like no only up was good. What do you mean?
It's fun. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. The game was fun. I enjoyed I enjoyed it
But the counterpoint is Ben brutal is the exact same game without all of the shovelware aspects
But you didn't try that and you tried the shovelware
That's all I'm saying nobody died on that hill you're fighting ghosts you're fighting ghosts
You're fighting ghosts. I'm just saying
two very similar games came out in a very similar time frame and
One of them deserves a an ounce of respect and you picked the wrong one
Let me I'll translate for those of you that don't know stir
He fell off the pipes and all dead for it get good
This is the I fell off the pipes and didn't want to go back up
This is drama destroying the environment by supporting. Okay, you ready? Okay, let's go. I
Forgot to press down
Three two. No, wait, I was good. You were watching my stream. I wasn't even on camera next time. It touches down. Yep. Nice
Next time it touches up. We're running, right? Oh
Oh, I quit in favelas
I'm here with you. I'm tied to you. I'm good playing it
What ever happened to next time it goes when it goes we're in the middle of we're in the middle of like a divorce
Level argument right now. So I need a second next time
My fingers left. Oh my
Three, what's all I got like oil on my fingers. What happened? Yeah when you're focusing on pulling me only up
He liked it the next time we touched up
You didn't do it
You were never gonna make that jump and you're counting on me to have made the jump so that you don't look dumb
This kid didn't even make it up pipes and only up it's also about season one. Let's hear about it
I gotta I guess I'm gonna be I you breaking up. Are you on a good cell signal? You breaking up? Yeah name five games
Super Mario 1 Super Mario 2 Super Mario World Super Mario 3 Super Mario 64
Best games of all time. Not even a fucking contention
Competition. Did you beat Super Mario World for SNES? Yes. Thank God actually. Thank God actually
Let's move that flag
Next time it touches down. I got you. I got you. I got you. I made it
Did you see the Mario fingers are just so oily it was funny when I did it and why are we counting now?
You did it. You did it. Are we counting you?
Stir he got that. There's a bird. That sounds like there's a bird in your room
I don't know if I heard what I heard was correct, but be careful out there
I heard a very large bird potentially you all right you there duck. All right, you're gonna comes down crouch
Next time we go up. I'm gonna count it down
My fingers are greasy
You didn't even go on look and look what I'm doing here. Look what I'm doing. I see what you're doing
I certainly see what you're doing. Okay. What's the plan here?
I know and
We come back. Yeah
We need we need one of these two. You can't put them here. Yeah put them on ice. Okay, so we need running start to
Okay
Okay, I like how we both just sit so we're going right pop right pop
After the next wind we're beating this. I thought you were gonna do a countdown
After the next wind
Can you jump could you know you pull me? Hey, you know, you're not doing the pole animation
Sorry, there's no signal in the tunnel. Okay, I guess I'll count it down for you
Nice whoo
All right, what the heck once it gets here? Yeah
Then we can go
Up and then duck and then I have to throw you to the left. I think I think this is a throw
I think this might is it a throw
Why not? Why not? Just why not just go all all out you show me your true power. I think it was a throw
It's 500 we're almost there and then then you can go play Diablo 4 so we all know you're fucking huge
You love that game. Well, apparently apparently I like games now
Apparently I like games now good save actually. I don't know if this gets us anywhere though. I think it kind of does
Well, we're gonna yeah, we're gonna have to jump next wind I think it makes sense to me
Boy, I was going by timing. Why are you guys fighting? Hey, it's good games
only up stir and I
Are very comfortable hanging out. We can just you know rifle off
Yeah, we I think we have a pretty good dynamic. We've known each other for a long time. I think we have a good dynamic
What do you think crap? That's it? Yes. Yeah, we have a great dynamic
We have a great dynamic
We know we know who is who we know who's wearing the fucking shoes in the relationship pants
That why what are you counting down?
What were you counting down? What were you doing? You knew that was a bad countdown
The next jump timed perfectly after the wind ended you knew that was a bad countdown
That was a view that you timed that wrong and you knew it. That's why you quiet
Usually you'd have been like turbo you're stupid it but that time you were dead silent because I thought
We've been doing this for like 14 hours
You ready on the next wind? Can you can you notice the wind occurring then we can just do it same exact thing?
We did last time
three two one go
It wasn't gonna work out that way. Oh
wasn't
No, we didn't do it before. I wasn't gonna work out that way
Bro, take a nap. You look tired. I mean I am but how dare you I think that's cuz we're doing that when the wind comes
I think so
three two one, uh
Zero, I don't think we need the wind for this. I think you're you're you're putting overwind compensation in here
I'm putting overwind. Okay, we're the winds gonna end
I'm gonna count it down and we're gonna definitely just slam right into this wall. Okay, this one's a no-winder
No, we can't there's no way to no-win. Okay, okay
This has to be wind. I'm sorry. I had that wrong. Um
Uh-huh. Can you let go? No
No, it wasn't actually holding it. Oh, what this weird, right? By the way, dude, I'm uh, I'm I'm
I'm sorry that I got that wrong
I'm sorry. I had it wrong. It's so fucking hard to do that
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Like you I can't apologize. I can't do it. Okay, let's go now. I know this is so itchy dude. I'm sorry
How did you get to across your room in one second that was weird
Pull me up so we can fly up there
What do you mean?
Well, you're supposed to be pressing the fly up there button. Okay. Good. Good. Good
Alright, this is it
the final 50 meters
I dare you to read this look another pair of penguins. These guys have to have it
Hey, good day guys
Have you brought it? We well, we got all the way here and realized we didn't bring it
We would have come home as victorious
heroes
But no
They've had to leave the most important thing at home
Are you going to remind me for the rest of our lives?
Yes, I will maybe then you won't forget everything. Do you even remember my name?
So I don't want to read this anymore
wait
Come here
No, shut up. We really I wanted people mad that I skipped it. Shut up
Uh, it looked like a secret in there
I'm sorry for saying shut up. I didn't mean that
All right, this is it wait
Oh, you have okay you have one over there
three
No
All right. I gotta throw you I think
Yep, this is gonna be weird because how are we gonna do this from here?
Do what from here? Like you're gonna have to land and then we have to you have to land right on that snow part on the left
Otherwise, we're not gonna be able to do it
Just like that. Don't worry. I got it
On the left
If you landed on the ice, we would have not been able to do it
You're gonna throw it all the way to the ice. Yes, there is if you were unskilled like i'm not
The wind doesn't affect me up here. Yeah, but I don't want to get blown. Okay
Okay, this this might need like a little bit of a run
that's
You had it wrong
How did I have it wrong? We weren't gonna make that jump
See that I I should have done the timing on that one
You haven't done the time. What have you done?
What have I done? What have you done? You've actually done something very very bad. You've done something. You've done something incredibly bad
What have I done? I don't know what you did, but you've done something bad and now we have to do that
It's all right. It's gonna take us right there. What have you done?
What have I done? I don't know. What have you done? You did something bad. What have I done? What have I done? Okay
It's it's salvageable
I think it's salvageable. It's salvageable. We just gotta
Uh, he he is absolutely floundering right now. He's like falling off stuff
He's in shock. We have to we gotta we gotta
Jeremy I like games. Okay. Sorry. All right. We're good. No, it's fine. We're good
Running against the wind. We're okay
It's okay. It's all right. I'm
Jeremy what have I done?
It's everything's gonna be fine. Don't worry. Everything's gonna be fine. It's gonna be fine. Everything's gonna be all right
Just take a look. It's only four. We were at 450 440. This is not a problem
That's really not a problem. Don't go
We need to hit this perfect
As the as the wind ends, otherwise, we're gonna get caught again
So perfect win ending timing. Okay. Yeah, this is not a problem. We're fine. There's no wind here. I'm the anchor
I got you
Any wrongers win here or 432 we're already back
I'm gonna i'm not gonna blame you on that
again
How about you time one? Let's see. Let's see how good it goes. I don't even know what's
I don't even know what the button is. It was like four on the numpad. I don't know what it is
That's how hard it is. You don't even know the button and i'm getting critiques
Why would both of us do it?
One of us has to take the charge on it. Are you gonna swing?
I am so
Like what but it's like what does he mean? Okay, but if we get to 500 from here
That's we that's the end of the game. We beat it and yeah, we cheated along the way, but who cares
We're good. We're good. We're good. This is this is perfect
Dude, I I tried so hard
We did it again, we're gonna be we're gonna handle this three two one go
Uh
You're rushing a little
Because I know we have the potential to succeed you're rushing just a little okay
No wind ice wait for wind next jump
I said wait. I said wait
I said wait, I said wait, but didn't you say no wind jump then wait? Uh, you did say wait for wind
because if
Because if the wind's going
We're just not meant for each other I admit it we needed to just wait a little longer
Just don't put one of those
Checkpoints down here. You call the shots man. Okay, you ready?
Yeah
I didn't you didn't hear anything and are we waiting after the next one?
Here's what we're gonna do ready
Get up and no no no
Go
What's you know? No, I just I don't know what the button is
Okay, there we go put one of those things down
Uh, you can't can't well, we'll just wait down here
There we go
Oh fuck we might be able to get this uh thing
Nice oh my baby boy with his little goatee and his rock friend
Jeff is going to be my partner for the journey. That's the single player
Oh cool
All right. Here we are. It didn't we're fine. Everything's good. Put one of those down
Mine was the real one 50 meters and we're good
Now i'm gonna throw you just call the taxi
And call a taxi
Okay
And go
Help me up. Okay. There's nothing here. There's no wind here. We're good
Good idea that one's hard to time
We're gonna go a lot earlier
Yeah, i'm saying like we go like now
Yep, it's it's too hard to time with the counter
Yeah, I think it's very obvious one to go. I think we should do it. Let's go for it. Okay when it comes up
Okay, uh ready yes, that's perfect
Holy shit
Just go
One of those. Oh, no
Can you get me? Yeah
Okay. So so what what what what what what what what are we what are we now? No
No, what are we doing after we get on that? Okay, we're going
And then we're going to jump to that little block immediately. Yeah, and I
You have I have to grab and then we'll okay. I think we have to throw from there
That was that was just not it was the time timing was wrong
Yeah, but we still had to go
We still had to we literally had to
We're good. Whoa, the wind the wind. Oh the wind bro
the wind
Okay, hold on
Because we need a no wind situation
We do need no wind
Okay, this one
Sit no, we can't oh
Okay, the no wind and then we immediately go up to the next one. All right. No wind immediate next one
Are you grabbing or am I this one? Are you grabbing?
I'm grabbing whoever can grab can grab. All right, then I need to
Let you go
When let go on this one? No
That was just that was it's hard to do that. Wow that and I I didn't want you to
run out of breath
Holding that's actually tricky. That one's very hard
Okay, we need to wait
Are you grabbing or am I grabbing you're grabbing go?
Again, again, we have to go immediately because when the wind comes back from them
Yeah, yeah, we have to go. We have to go honey. We have to go. I feel you
Not this time because when the next time and we have to immediately go to block
And then I'm grabbing
Yes
Okay, ready one. I have to wait for the wind to end. Yep
Okay this time
nice
And then where am I going from here? All the way left, I guess
How the fuck are you gonna do that hit it? You're hitting the weirdest swings
We need wind you have to let me go
I know but your swings were such shit
censor yourself
Your swings were such bad swings
Are you gonna say say shoot?
instead of that
word
What the okay anybody watching?
This is tough
Are you looking for full revolutions when I get on there?
Don't go
Uh, I mean, yeah, that would help a lot
Okay, because you you were going like upright and then not swinging down
You're like dropping down and ganking on the roof. Keep in mind. That is the fourth time i've ever done that
Bro, you accepted your smurf diagnosis. What?
wait
This next one immediately jump on immediately grab the block
Nope
I think it would that one isn't something that breaks. So maybe I should just land on it and drop a flag
Not a bad idea
Landing on it's hard though
This one we're doing it. We're doing it. We're doing it
All right, you let me you want me to let you go on the top?
Let go
You wanna get above it?
Okay, nice
Can you just pull me up now? Yeah, there's no wind up here, right? Oh, there is there is
All right. Now, what the hell are we doing?
Are we just running and jumping or are you swinging?
I think i'm swinging. Can you swing from down here though?
That's that might be too thick
What do you mean? I mean if I throw you isn't that is it too thick? No, it's all right
Needed a little more oomph
Imagine this without flags. Yeah, I know
It'd be horrible
Okay, here we go. This is tricky because there's not a whole lot of room for me to run
We'll get it. We'll get it eventually
I do have to go kind of up
But I don't know you're you're the master
on the swinger
There it is. Oh shit. Nice drop a flag there when you get a chance
beautiful
I
Wasn't sure if it was gonna stop or not
You hit the bottom of it. Yeah, I mean I hit the bottom of it
I'm just saying in general
You you did that?
Uh, we have to I think we have to run left and then right I think it's like a run left run right
See it again
I don't think you need to oh, oh shit. We have the camera there
Oh, that's fucked up
That's you get that far with no checkpoints. You're like, oh, let's just oh wait. No, you can
um
I don't think i'm a sentient human anymore
We only got like 30 meters to go. How are we doing this? What are we doing?
I don't know, but we're gonna do it
It doesn't make any sense
What do you do? I like throw you
What do you do here?
I think we need to time a second jump to get on top of that ice jump up on the ice. Yeah
Hold on. Okay, we're gonna die. Yeah, and then the other one as soon as it gets to the top top
We gotta jump up
You you know, you know exactly what we're doing
There it is. Oh shit, we gotta and we have to keep moving. Oh, that is gonna be hell on earth
We have to keep flying over it. Keep doing the neck. Do the next jump. Yep
We just have to do just imagine you're playing this by yourself
That's a good attempt. All right, play the game by yourself
Oh
Okay. No, I was I had I had a misunderstanding
Misinterpretation we're gonna go up on ice up on ice over to the right when it gets the right elevator
Sorry good
Oh
Yeah, put flag down. Let's go
We're gonna jump you grab the
right
Oops a daisy
Do I think you misunderstood what we're doing? I kind of did for a second, but we're good
See the block what are you guys doing?
If we get to a new zone, i'm done by the way if it's a new zone and there's like more I can't I cannot
All right ready
Okay, let go
There it is
Flag down
Okay, we gotta wait after the wind ends and time this omega
perfectly
This I don't think we can count this down what's with the spam stop spamming what are you guys doing? Stop stop
Go wait
the moon
Ooh, all right on this top. Yep
All right
There's one I think I gotta swing you
And this might be it
We did it the peak
The peak we did it. Did we actually do it? That's me
Did it we finally did it
Give me the rock. Oh with the we have take the rock with us
Kind of slow with the rock
We need it though. Do I need it? It's for the achievement. How do you pick it up?
I can't it's got it. It's got to be tied to you. Oh, well
We're leaving them. You just want to leave them. Yeah, we actually did it. That's the end. We did it. Nice job
Mail in the letter to santa
No
Oh
I can't believe we beat it
Well, we used the check marks still even with check marks. Sorry. I can't believe I stuck with it. Yeah, you stayed you stayed
And you know, very cool. That's fine. You had fun
I did I'm glad that we beat it. I'm glad that we pulled through and we got to experience this wondrous journey
Together that was a good time
Look, that's us. That's me and that's you and i'm in the front. Yep. I'm in the back
Checking out your butt
That's fun. These are the people that tortured us
Yeah
Is there a post credits funny thing that we have to do or what?
My hair has been like glued to my head over here this whole time
Uh, now I know what people were talking about
Look at how long this is getting
Hillary clinton. No, this is this is more lord
All right. All right. Now we have to do it again, but a little bit faster. Okay
So when we fall mistake first mistake and no counting down
Okay from this point forward we're gonna start here. Okay, and this is uh
We just know that we know what to do. We know the timing. Yes, I can't do this. Sorry. I got bro
Okay, see you later
I was trying to time it with you. Yeah
That's fun. That's it too. I've been a bit
It's free for a while
Mm-hmm. We can play our game some other time because it did look kind of funny. Yeah, we should
We'll play the cat horror game
another time
well
buh-bye
See you later stir. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for playing stir is always a good time. It's always good to have stir around
Yeah, stir say bye to stir and follow stir too stir has his own stream where he streams call of duty
uh
He streams. I don't know why I think that's all you stream. Yeah, if you're a college streamer though
I don't play call of duty. He's lying
Uh, but you guys you guys should follow germa
Did you know that 80% of the people watching right now aren't following hit that follow button?
Don't don't it's too many people here already don't I don't want anymore. No more
Talk about diablo 4
We already did
unfollow
He's gone. Oh, he's gone. I hate when he does that. We didn't even get an opportunity to
Roast him. Well, thanks playing stir. Good to see you. Make sure to follow the channel follow stir's channel stir's got funny stream
Okay, so the plan is tomorrow tomorrow. I'm gonna play some browser games and maybe uh, you know
Maybe we'll just play rip hang too. Are we starting around?
Be like 3 pm pacific i'm gonna do a sunflower update probably browser game. Yeah, well
We'll figure it out tomorrow might not be a long stream
Because I I gotta make sure I get everything ready to go for tuesday the house flipper stream
So we'll see you tomorrow. See you around three pacific. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for watching as always good to see you
I didn't see any of you, but you know, I did read your messages though. Don't forget view finders on the 18th
Oh, hell. Yeah, we'll figure it out tomorrow
The stream on tuesday is starting at one o'clock pacific 1 pm pacific
It's probably gonna be about three hours, maybe three and a half hours for the whole thing, but i'll see you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves
Goodbye
Call your mother call your father, too
Thanks for hanging up. I still can't get over that grimace comment. That's like probably top five
Most unhinged comments i've ever heard but man, was it funny?
Yeah, see you tomorrow. Hey, what do you got a dent in your head?
Oh, man, I had a great time tonight. It was a good dream. I had a lot of fun. He doesn't want to leave
um
No, I do
I do I
Remember i'm a i'm like a i'm like a four to five hour andy i'm like a four to six hour andy
it's not about wanting to leave but
You know
We'll do it again. I'll see you whenever whenever it's time
He has a job now. I do that's going really well
I'm really enjoying the roll it off brand. I have been working I have been
Technically going to work. I think it's great
I think I got a pretty good balance too
And like I said previously sometimes you might not see a stream for a little bit
But I don't think it's gonna be too crazy, but I like it if you enjoyed it's good. Yeah, I do
Still trying to get that healthy balance
any projects to look out for
uh, there is at least a few that
I've been on but obviously I don't want to tell you what they are because
They're in development then you'll have to wait till they get announced, but they seem pretty awesome
You have a job
I do have a real job mom
Spoil everything and get fired. What a terrible use of my time. That would be that would be so stupid
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Take it easy
Goodbye. Take care