Alright, let's get let's get one thing straight before I've seen a lot of pogchamps. I'm seeing a lot of venus's
I'm seeing a lot of before you pogchamp. This ain't even real. This is an uploaded video
I want to make sure you're aware of that before we get started. I have a super
Streamer switch which if there's an internet problem for more than four days a video is uploaded and broadcast as if it was live
I'm currently crying in bed tears are streaming down my face because the internet problem has still not been fixed
So hopefully this little tidbit of content will be worth a little bit for you. Can you hear me crying?
Well, you can because this is recorded
How is everybody?
Alrighty, no, we are live. This is live. This is real, but i'm gonna be really honest with you
I haven't even tweeted this this is a let's see if it can stay on kind of moment here
I don't believe you. I i'll start reading names two two one one one one
Thanks for the comment there six two one one two one three three. Thanks for that comment
It's a good one. This is pre-recorded says
One two two two one one one zero zero. Thank you. Nobody said that now. How you guys doing?
I'm turning into a goblin. I really am
We're gonna relax for a minute here and I i'm not gonna turn the webcam on because I look like shit
You want to see a goblin? Would you like to i'm not sure if i'm like comfortable
This is like this is essentially me turning the webcam on and naked
I haven't i haven't looked in the mirror in like seven hours. I have no idea
I have dog hair all over me
It probably looks like such a psycho
All right. Are you ready?
All right. Fine. Are you ready? Let's see
Let's see. Well, I don't know what I look like. I have no idea
full screen
one
two
Three no, I look okay
Look at this look at like I have so much dog hair all over me. Oh, I know I oh no, I look bad
I look okay
I just look a little a little tired though
um
Not lipstick not this time. See
Um, i'm very tired
It's been a long three days
All right. Now let's get this off because I really am turning into like a fucking goblin
Am I wearing eyeliner?
No
I don't think so unless somebody put it on me
Well, I was like going just like this at the wall
I was like a stone person
No, this is just like i'm just like flush
But i'll give you the long and short of it. We've been dealing with this for three days now
I was up at seven o'clock this morning. I slept for like three hours
I've been trying to be on top of this shit
Get at it get at it
uh
And i've got some we got some
bad news
Bad news, it's not really bad news as much as it's just
I mean, it just
Sucks, but whatever
um
It's kind of like too long
It really is you know, like something's just too long to even talk about it anymore. I've been talking about this for less like
34 hours
so
I'd be tell you okay, you know when to go around at a
family get-together
And it's like let's say there's like 30 or 40 people there
And every single person that you talk to you have to tell the same story to
Hey, so
hey
Johnny
How's your school? You're an engineering student, right? What's that like?
well, um
Yeah, I was an engineering student. I you know, I work on engineering and uh, i'm making a i'm making this new plane
of architecture
And uh, i'm i won a award for it in the in the school paper and oh wow
Good to see you
And you walking away to the next person
Oh, it's you johnny. How it's you it's me aunt etna
You're in school, right? Yeah. Yeah in school. Oh as an engineering student that must be
That must be really interesting
Yeah, what are you gonna do? What are you been doing? Um, well, I uh, yeah, I got an award
I've got an award. I was working on this new plane thing plane. Wow. That's incredible
Tell me more
Uh, I got an award for i'm an engineering student. It's been you know, I the the food though the school food
Oh, it's kind of stinks, right? Right, grandma. Uh, yes
Oh, you're so smart. You're the smartest one and you keep going uncle lou
Hey, how are you johnny? I I mean I heard somebody told me, you know through the night that you're an engineering student
Yes, I am an engineering student. Oh, what's that? You must work on planes
Yeah
Yeah, I work on airplanes lou. Oh, wow. Have you won any awards? I've been doing that for three days
Tell us again
Save it for three days
Yeah, and I actually like
I I like time looped myself too, by the way, this is important because we're just hanging out right on you hearing this
So here's how I time looped myself
so
A person from maintenance was here
this morning, right
and I
There was a bunch of bullshit. It turns out there's like a saturated node, you know, i'm an engineering student
I work on airplanes, you know the blah blah blah, right?
so
He gives me the idea. Hey, you should get a static ip address
that will probably that maybe that'll help you with traffic and
um, you know, I got an award for an award for my airplane design
So I call up
the cox tech support
To try to get a static ip
So the guy on the phone
Is telling me oh, yeah, we're having problems issuing you this static ip
uh, it's
No, I can't talk right now. I don't want to talk about my engineering degree anymore. This is damn again
No
I'm not answering. I'm not talking about my engineering degree anymore
so anyways
static ip
They're telling me that they can't do it. There's a problem. There's like an issue with the static ip
And i'm like, what do you mean? What's an issue? Oh my god, what's happening?
Uh, fuck
I can't answer this on stream. That's not cool
What if they were like quick?
We're detecting router levels of over 400 degrees
Tell me where you what do you what do you do for work at school?
I got engineering. Yeah. Yeah
The router
anyways, uh the
The engineering student that talked no, i'm not doing the webcam. I look like fucking trash
I'm gonna mute the volume for now and keep the music background music's nice
So static ip, right just listen listen
They tell me
There's a problem here with your static ip if the phone rings again, I swear to god
No, it didn't so the static ip
Could not go through and the guy couldn't figure out why so he told me well, hold on a minute here. I
I actually see there's an outage in your area. I was like really
What are you talking?
Yeah, yeah
It looks like uh, this is probably what's going on with the static ip. Oh, you're getting packet loss here
There's somebody's going to be out there to uh fix that
There's an outage and i'm sitting there going
No, that's that's me
I i'm going like a full-on go back in time time loop scenario
Where like I was the one that had the guy come out?
to try to fix the packet loss
And the guy thought it was an outage in the area
But he's talking to the person that like caused the guy to come down. So I I didn't even say anything
I was like, oh wow
Yeah, that's interesting. Yeah, I think there's something wrong with the line
Yeah, I mean
Got an award
For that so as it stands right now, we're switching to a static ip and it's maybe gonna help
but the super duper long
sad story is
It's not gonna fix the problem because we have like a saturated node and it's gonna take them
Uh, this is not a joke. I'm not kidding. This is real
It's gonna take them
10 years to fix it
It's gonna take 10 years
Yeah, well, you know, we're working all this stuff and uh
The plan is to have it all done in 10 years to like replace all the nodes and stuff and i'm like wow 10 years
At least my children will have good internet
No, no, no the static ip might work
In fact, we haven't dropped any frames so far. It's just all over the place
There's nothing I can do about it. So the real end of the story to move on and we're gonna play garden flipper
If you were curious
is vegas has done a lot of development in the last year like before
Um before we got here it they've dialed it up to a thousand fiber is now starting to become
Oh my god. Why did I just say it?
Why did I just say that
I don't know what happened man. All I all I picture is like, okay, you know like the cartoon
like in the in the cartoon with a guy like if somebody has like like
Like the charcoal all over their face and their hair is out like this and they're like like kind of dirty
All I picture is like that guy like with like frayed out air and like the loony tunes like
I don't know man. I I pressed a couple of wrong buttons
400 degrees
See in 10 years
No, but it also might have been like all the water all the rain that vegas has had but to we'll put a cap on this
Fiber is coming out here
It's coming everywhere. There's a ton of new development and even if it means that I have to move
Like down the street
That's not a problem. That's not a big deal and you do what you got to do
Just move down the street to get fiber
That is a very real possibility if we keep having problems, right? Let's
Look, I am not going to be the one to tell you just move
but moving
Right down the street to get fiber or to make sure that it's there on like some of these newer developments
So where there's there's like hundreds of them. They pop up everywhere
All over the whole entire like las vegas valley everywhere and that the guy told me
All these huge new developments that they're going all over the place here in vegas
They're all gonna have fiber laid out there and i'm like, oh, all right. Well, maybe i'll look
vas vegas i'm sorry i've i've been sleepless
How long have i've been live?
uh 14 minutes exactly
Just get elon muska's internet
muskas
Elon musk's elon musk get elon muska's internet
But I can't let it bother me. I'm not gonna you know life's too short
to
Get bad
I'm just like it's just i'll i'm just i'm just fucking hanging out. You know what I mean?
So
Here we go
Uh, what we're gonna do today is we're gonna see how long we can be live for
we're gonna get the static ip change over tomorrow, hopefully that helps and
They are going to monitor us
And just make sure that nothing really major happens, but you know, whatever like you can't
Life's too short life's too short to pay premium internet prices for internet that will be installed in 10 years. What's going on?
What's going on?
No, no. Oh, you guys are like scared. Okay. I might be like overtired. You guys just scared the shit out of me
I thought that was like somebody in my room
What's happening? What did I say?
I'm sitting here going
This is somebody like gonna like strangle me behind me. Why would that happen?
Uh, oh monga ish
But we're just gonna chill we're gonna hang out
Uh, we'll see how long we can go. Um, this might not be a very long stream. I'm sorry
but you know, sometimes
it's
What is it? Let's go through the stages
anger
denial and then
Super saiyan and then
uh out of mana then
uh superimpose no, uh, whatever it is
impose
Imposition on somebody and then denial again and then you accept your fate
I think we're pretty much somewhere in the acceptance stage denial too is real
But this is garden flipper. Uh, don't pay no attention to the house
Oh, hold on a second here
Look in the lower left corner
Hey Jeremy, it's me
I'm calling you from my home office
The degrees went so much higher than I originally anticipated
I was trying to fix it
And then I did like a 1980s home alone style movie thing
Or I grab the two ends of the wires and connect them and then it is explosion
Sorry, i'll get back to you. This house sucks. But who cares? We're doing gardens today. Oh, there's the laptop
I had to put it on a cool surface
It's been a long time since we've been in this game
crack outs
We're gonna learn how to play garden flipper a bit of gravel and a couple of bushes
Hello, I work at home in my dentist's office
I can deal with all kinds of teeth cavities but not with the holes
And weeds in my garden
Please lay some gravel on the front part of my yard to get rid of these also
Could you plant something on there to make it look better? This is a stay a stay at home dentist
That you work at your your home is the dentist
That's kind of weird
Planting is now available
Oh, uh a murderer
For now when you're able to design a garden look for plants in gap
Uh
Look for plants in garden category in the shop. Okay plants in garden category
You unlock the garden hose
Congratulations, you've unlocked the new tool using a garden hose will be able to water flowers fill water tanks and wash dirt outside the house
So we can power wash get
garden hose
That's kind of
Oh nice
Can I open his house and spray in?
What was I doing?
Ruining all of his furniture
Ah, that's what I thought
Okay. So he wanted me to pick his weeds
I got five hundred and thirty nine thousand dollars
Why did I just retire? I don't have to do this
I got half a million dollars
Okay, remove weeds
He's gonna retire
Okay, scatter the surface single colored gravel and then plant a
Confurious shrub
So the weeds that have the little flowers on them
Why why did somebody just say whoosh?
Whoosh
Did I miss a joke?
What's the joke?
Oh, I got a skill point
New gardener skill available click the hot key to upgrade the gardener skill. Okay. So what we got
faster planting
Faster digging with a shovel 100 faster unfolding grass from the roll
Grass comes from the ground
Large 2019 trimmer
shovel
Bushi and then coming soon
High grass visible on the mini map. So we got gardener scents visible moles on the mini map
The streamer has never been to home depot before
All right. Let's get let's get this one
No this one
Yeah, high grass visible on the mini map so we can see what we're dealing with here
I'm gonna make this dentist's office look
beautiful
Okay, so
Remove weeds 71 percent. Yeah, that's perfect the plant shrubs scatter the single colored gravel
Can I lift this up?
I need gravel
single colored gravel
Oh
What color do we want? Uh large rocks?
medium rocks
Or little rocks
At the serial this is rice. It's not rice
I'm gonna plant like a quaker oat
Rice cake in your lung. Okay, let's buy how many buy many
Oh, what the fuck
No, no, no, no. No, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. This is wrong. Do I have any other tools?
Scatter. No, I have to scatter this surface. But how do I this looks terrible. How do I get rid of this?
Sell the grass
I don't think I can sell the grass
Do I have like a trimmer?
P on grass that's not gonna work
That's gonna make it worse
Because I got all the weeds
What do you mean he actually tried?
Of course, i'm gonna try
I'm just gonna do it. Look what a dumb job. This is
Okay, i'm gonna just scatter it around
Is that what you want me to do?
Wait, what?
I really am just putting rice cakes in his weeds
Scatter the surface single colored gravel
Oh
I want to cut this is fucking me up man. I want to like cut this uh
You know what? You didn't do it like this. You put like a tarp down underneath
Okay
I'm gonna be completely honest with you all here
I'm gonna be totally honest with you. Is it scatter the surface or cover the surface?
Like cover the whole surface scatter the surface
Wouldn't why wouldn't it just be cover the surface with the gravel because that's what i'm doing
It's do two tone. No, I don't care. I'm not getting paid for two tone
Two tone not yet. I was just learning
I missed a spot. I'm not getting paid to get every spot
All right. This is why is it at zero percent?
Fuck
Is that why people were saying whoosh?
I like the way this looks though reminds me of the sea
Amos getting like sea vibes here
Like bottom of the ocean like that's like a wallpaper at the bottom of the ocean
I probably should have done square use the scroll wheel. Thank you
Appreciate the help. Okay. What does it want? That's one two colored gravel
I'm just doing this one. We already have it equipped
I'm just like waiting for someone to scream from outside of this house
Like from in the house
Lazy, this is just the tutorial mission
Okay, and then we gotta plant that shrub there. This is one tone right single colored gravel
single colored gravel
and
This is the which one was this like how big would you yeah, that's the same one
I will never hire you
Well, i'll never hire you
Two can play that game
All right
income
1,388 bucks
I'm just doing this for fun, you know
We're gonna half a million in the bank. I'm just here for fun
Imagine like you the guy comes out. Hey, uh
This looks fucking terrible. Look at all this weed still. Yeah, you just drop in the same color
Yeah, i'm uh, i'm just doing it for fun. Well get the fuck out of here
Can you recommend me somebody that actually cares?
Uh, yeah, probably have a good day haven't you ever seen one punch man
No
I don't watch anime
He slams the door. All right. Uh, what was it? What was it a shrub?
Shrub does it matter which one?
Does it just call them just any shrub?
any uh
any one of these
Uh confucius shrubs pick a nice one. What about the little ones?
No, these are these are christmas trees
This is just a fake christmas tree that somebody didn't unfold yet
That one's all right
Right in the middle got it
Garden plants need to be planted interact with them to do so
Oh fuck
What do I do with the dirt?
How far do I have to dig into the ground?
The hole is now dug. All right
Now you can put the plant in the hole
Oh
Eat dirt eat dirt eat dirt. I'll do it
Okay, let's plant it here
What's going on?
Wait, do I already have it equipped or something?
Is it not enough room? Hold on. Oh, it's like it was behind the gate. Okay. I'm like wait what
Why would I do I do this with my hands? You're gonna get sick
All right. There we go. Cool. Do it again. That looks nice
This is fun same one over here right there. Let's dig. All right, let's just put it back in
All right, let's put it in. Let's do it with our hands
Why don't you just like kick it in there with your shoes?
So this is not this order's not compliant. I know i'm gonna finish the order
We'll do this one right in the right in front right here
Same thing with this one right here
Let's plant them wash the car. What the hell are you talking about? Spray the car with your hose
Yeah, that's like that's a car wash that I can't wait to turn the hose sideways spray it gently and like
Lick it like a dog and then like make a joke about like
That's how you get sick
Yeah, let me get some air in these tires. All right, so that's it. All right
$2,524 I want to complete it back to my dump build a walmart
Um, I don't think I can do that. I got a new negotiation skill, didn't I?
So this is i'm picking up where I left off it was why is my house such a piece of crap?
Didn't I have a better house?
What's going on here? I thought I had like a huge best buy house owned one sold
I I sold them all holy shit. This is almost a garden, but wait not yet
Hold on now a house in a thicket old house with a bunker uncle's bunker
Oh, yeah, we definitely did some of these look at this place garden after house construction. This place is run down
That's the home alone movie house
All right. Well, look I got money. So
Oh, yeah, we did we did these we've done them. See look
I've done them. Well, let me just do it. Let me learn the tools
You need to remove the bushes
Hey there. I have a bit of a problem
I tried to deal with weeds in my garden and got some kind of herbicide to get rid of them
Luckily just to test it out. I used it on a couple of them and quickly realized it is extremely effective
It destroyed the weeds as well as my bushes
I'm really glad it didn't spray it all over my yard. But unfortunately, I did it right in front of
I don't know why I thought it was gonna see my kids
Like I sprayed my kids. I was like wait what?
I did it right in front of the entrance
Now the plants in that area are dried up and look pathetic
Please wipe them out and fill that spot with some fresh grass
Oh, and if you could mow my lawn as well, that'd be fantastic
All right. It sounds like a plan. We're gonna get the lawn mower
You've unlocked a new tool from now on you'll be able to cut grass using a garden brush cutter
Really? All right. These are dead
Remove object so get rid of the shrub
Use the turf roll to spread the grass in the area mow the lawn. Well, let's
Brush cutter
Oh shit
No, you can't
Oh, all right. So you do just have to cut the lawn
Oh, i'm not doing this. Well, i'm doing this like crap. Am I spraying the oh
No, that's just the clippings
That's not how that works
It's close enough
Okay, so the lawn still needs to be over here
I have no idea what i'm doing. I'm not a pretty i'm not a good landscaper. I'm really good at breaking things
Okay, use the turf roll to spread the grass in the area remove all the shrubs
Remove
Confucius shrub spherical shape. Well, where are they?
How do I get rid of them?
Can I sell these?
I guess not just remove right? Yeah
Okay, so then plant the grass here
turf roller
turf roll
Uh, just buy it. How do I use this?
press to
pay in place
rotate item
What? Wait, is that it?
Is it gonna work?
Should it be rolling?
How do I roll it?
How do I roll wait, hold on i'm picking it up. What what?
This is pressed to place
This is rotate
Wait, what?
No, don't cut and finish. Wait, god damn it
Okay, when I placed it here before I didn't get this opportunity. Okay use
spread
There we go
How far does it go?
Oh, that's so terrible looking
This is like two layers, whatever. They're not gonna know
buy many
Okay, that goes all the way
And then this is gonna go like this
No one can even see it back here
What if I just don't put it under there?
All right, here we go. What I can't it's because this is in the way. They're not even gonna fucking know
Yeah, fuck them. What do they care? They're not gonna even know
Just leave the rolls
This is my first job
As a landscaper
I can't even get them
So we're gonna go this way
45 is it are they gonna get mad at me?
Fuck you. Do it yourself. No, I didn't say fuck you
I said
I don't care
That's it. There's a difference
Is that that looks like it's not even correct
Look at that. God damn it
This uneasy work is giving me a headache
You're you're you're fine
Well, okay what just because there's like an inch of space you have a headache now
What?
No, you can't i'm just learning the tools
Yes
I'm at 95. Look i'll just do it. It's fine. Check it out. Check this out. Ready?
Because this looks like it's on the lip right here
But I don't think it is
You see what i'm talking about?
See that shouldn't shouldn't that be covering it?
Okay, that's fine
See look at see
What the hell?
See look at that
This is this too hard landscaping is too hard
How many I have to like pull the fence up to get this under here. That's not part of the job
It's fine. This one's done
Yeah, no, this is we're good
mow the lawn
mow their lawn
I have to mow the neighbor's lawn. Look at that. I'm not doing that
Yeah, me and ted have an agreement
My son used to do it
But he really didn't give a shit
He just well, uh, by the way, i'm projecting here. This is me i'm describing
So when I used to get like asked to mow the lawn
My father would say go mow the lawn give it come on help out try to jump up in the yard
I'd be like, okay fine
And I'd go out there and we had a pretty big yard
And what I would do
Is I would start in the middle. No, no, no, I would end in the middle. I would end in that
I would just do a giant circle
right
So I would start like on the edges and I would go like this around in a huge circle
And then I would line the tires up
With the where the you know the end of where I end so I made like a giant spiral
So the next pass would be like this
And then like this and then like this
Like this until you got in the middle. That's how you mow a lawn. No, it's not
You're supposed to go like straight up
And then straight down lining up the tires. So you so you get a straight line
The background the background the backyard used was a giant spiral and my father was pissed
and then there was a part of the yard where so the dogs went out and
There was a little section of the yard that they would go to and there was like a rock out there
And they peed on it and they like kind of shit out there
And I would always avoid it because I didn't want to like run over dog shit
I would like avoid because I didn't want to like go out there and like
Clean it up and then mow the lawn and my father would always be like what you missed the dog pen
Oh, yeah, I do but it's okay
I'll get i'll get it later and he'd be like, oh my fucking shot
Okay, is this done 48 percent. What am I missing?
Is it taking in the equation the whole thing over here?
I can't sell the grill. That's too bad. Look in the mini map
Yeah, it's all this shit
But I can't get rid of this
Does this count as they don't want me to get rid of this? I don't want to okay
All right, let's at least do this. Can I get a bigger roll of tape?
I can't make this bigger
Big roll. Thank you. Jesus. No, wait a minute. This is too big
Waste
And throw the rest in the trash
Shit, it looks like but that's correct though. Look at see
That that decay if I click right now doesn't that look correct?
Look at where it's lining up at the edges
See that that's this like right in the corner there, right?
It's from the bottom of the roll. So like this
Start from the fence
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
stay
No, they'll figure it out. Watch this be watch this be the phone call. That is
Mr albertson we're going to be shutting your internet out for about 30 minutes to do the static ip change
If you could do me a favor and just not use your internet stay far away from it
Well, you'll find out in a second here. What a waste. I know but don't worry
We're gonna go down and then i'm gonna cut that
It's all right. Just get tweezers and you pick that up
This is done. I'm learning still i'm just learning
Let's get the even um, let me see what the smaller one looks like
Look, here we go. This is a perfect little roll tape
Why I mean it's
I need to like move their fence
Hey, I can't I can't sell their fence and I can't move it. So like I can't do that
I i'm sorry that you you're not gonna let me move your shit
I can't wait till I get a real lawnmower. I can't wait to show you guys
I'm gonna cut the lawn like I used to
And we can compare the two ways
You're not gonna let me uproot your whole fence
No, I just need to move it
Well, why did they decide to do this? How you can't do it like this?
It actually looks kind of good
Up the game audio
How is it that's probably a little better take a dip in the pool
Uh, that's unfortunate. It's it's called out. I can't
It's a glass pool
Internet what do you guys think is the next step of the internet?
gardeners
Gardener jesus. Oh, no, no, no that okay. Never mind. I was like, what does that mean?
100 wireless. I don't want that
Any other like fucking boomers in this chat like actually scared of like 7g
I'm gonna start growing horns
Imagine not wanting horns and like the telecom companies will all spin it. You know what I mean?
There'll be like a hearing
Well, you know the thing is everyone has started to grow two extra eyes
But now you can see twice as good
I see that as a plus
Okay, this is what's the other percentage here right here?
97 90. All right. There it is 100 complete. I didn't have to do anything else
Oh, yeah, the the senator from new york would like to ask a question
Yeah, uh, so we've got four eyes now, but two of them throw up blood
Every six hours. Well, I think that's just progress, you know
We're done. That's a cool straw man
Wait, what if you had eyes that had blood coming out of them?
There were extra eyes because of 7g wireless technology. I don't think that's a straw man. I think that's a real man
Yeah, good to be home
This is dirty
What the hell is a straw man?
Ah, well welcome to the world of politic
That's just fucking god. I my heart hurts
Fuck come on. Oh my god. That was horrible. I did not
uh
Jesus christ
How do I stop that?
Can I was it it was never that loud before
Wow
Why is it getting louder? Wait, I need to try something cover your ears
Mute the stream for a second. I'm gonna do I need to see is this gonna is it going down cover?
I'm serious, please. This is a warning with an audio warning like it might lower it because that was definitely way louder
Okay, you ready? Just i'm giving you a pure warning in five seconds. Here it comes one
two
three
Four
I don't know what to do. I can never knock a wall down
I can never do anything with the walls
the master
Yeah, but if the master turns everything down
like
Oh, what were you saying again? What were you saying?
Oh my god
Okay. Well
Keep a mental note. Uh, I cannot use the hammer
And if I do I need to turn the source audio down all the way disable sound
That's unfortunate that's unfortunate that sounds like a uh, that sounds like a bug to me
It's a known bug reset the game that I have to is it saved
I have it saved right by by progress
What about my progress?
Uh, oh guys, I don't think I I think I may have lost my progress
Turn the in-game sound down in volume mixer and then it
Is that gonna do it?
Let's try it
We're on the worst timeline. Why the worst timeline?
Is it getting louder?
I don't know man. I think I might have to type into my computer
Out on steam
I got it already
Okay, let's test it last attempt and then i'm not using this device. No, ain't no
I need everybody to do me a big favor though
Like for real when there is an opportunity for me that I need to use this
I need to you guys have to spam chat
just write
Hammer sound or something. I'll forget
And I will fill somebody watching this stream's pants with shit because of that
No, I know now and I know I know I know I know but what about the other sounds let me make sure hold on
No, that's fine. What about this one? What about the paint sounds the tiling sounds?
How loud is this?
That's fine. It's just the hammer. Okay next garden, uh tool
playground and barbecue
Substrats for liquors instead of flowers
What about the barbecue my daughter grows so fast
And she is so curious about the world around her
I would love to prepare a play corner for her in the garden
It seems to me that a swing a sandpit and a rocker will be just right
Once you get started with the garden, maybe you can also plant some shrubs for me as my wife bought them for me
That'd be really nice
We've already enlarged the terrace
But now there's so much space and not much to fill it with
uh
A brugola would be useful here also a grill and a table for the whole family
Big enough to fit all of us even the grandparents when they visit us
Oh, and would you remove all these nettles too?
Those are the worst. I don't want my sweetie to get some burns from them
Okay, the the first two sentences and the last two sentences removed from this email. I'm doing a service
I'm doing a job. Tell me what you want me to do this this
I don't I don't need to I don't need this info this right here. Oh, they were big bits earlier
Holy shit. I was too busy talking about cocks
Uh, we had 50 bucks 5 000 bits from reinville. Hopefully you're still here. Thank you reinville for the 5 000 bits 50 dollars
They say hey germa
I'm a magic the gathering artist and your streams have kept me company during long hours of painting
Really appreciate the positive space and all the goofs keep up the funny shit and know you're appreciated ps popsicle. Germa is a
Better piece of art than i've ever created
That's fucking awesome
Wow
magic the gathering artist
Yeah, i'm sure a ton of people in the chat would love to know some of the cards that you've worked on or done
That's that's really really cool
But thank you for the 50 dollars and i'm absolutely happy to keep you company while you're working on that cool shit
But thank you so much for the 50 bucks and let us know what you uh, what you're working on. That's cool
That's really really cool
All right, so
You've ruined his painting with that loud sound
Yeah, he's like
They're like working on the whatever it is like really detailed work and they hear this
Smash. Oh fucking they like move their hand and go like a big smear on it. Oh shit. I'm sorry
I would feel so bad
control z
Yeah, but what if but what if it was like a big oil painting? Is that how it works?
I need a better tool than this
This thing sucks
Can I like back up one of those log grinders?
And then no, but I would need to pull it up by hand. I mean, I want just like I need a blonde mo
Use your skill points. Do I have any new skill points?
I'll get it. Hey, let's all I have to do is start talking about it. All right
Large 2019 trimmer. That's the one I want
That's it, right? Ooh
That's a much bigger radius
Take down those weeds
Ain't ain't no corn growing on those
Because it kind of looks like corn stalks
Somebody whatever speaking of which I I would long corn
I would long maze. I don't think I would put that in a short sale
I feel like it's gonna really boom here some
All right. So now we got uh, there's still weeds over here
I'm not planting those yet. Look at all this crap
All right. Let me see the mini map
That is just I need to plant
Where's the rest of this?
Uh, it's over here. Look at all. I missed all this. What a terrible gardener
Have you has this person ever been out here before?
How long have you lived here?
Those are just gonna grow back. I know you got to get in there and rip up the roots
By hand that'll spread that poison shit on them
Get in there and rip them up get the roots
Okay, there's still weeds. Where are these last weeds?
Well, let's plant this
I would say to rip them up with your teeth
um
No, i'm talking about no tools
Like this get out of the hands. That's good plant this one
Just use tools. You're a wuss
Don't ever call me that again
Please only use the sledgehammer. Well, I know what
Hammer sound I didn't do it
Wuss streamer yells at his fans
don't ever
Say that I i'm a wuss. That's not a very nice thing to say to somebody especially to somebody that's doing no sedation
colonoscopy
My wuss he's bragging about his colonoscopy
That just makes you look stupid no
That's the hardest flex of
Yeah, i'm gonna prove to you guys that i'm not a wuss by doing no fucking sedation colonoscopy
And yeah, then what are you gonna say then?
Uh, we would say that's unnecessary and just take the like sedation
Yeah, i'm not a wuss
That you're I know you're not but why you don't have to prove that
That's coming up soon, by the way fucking colonoscopy
bullshit
god dammit
too much information
I think most of the stream knows about my
my my internal health
That's all right
All right. I think this is good assemble wooden child swing
Cut those bushes you wuss
Where are these other weeds?
I can't trim them
All right. We need we need the swing sets going right here
swing
wooden child swing
Try to sell him the plastic one
All right. Let's see what we want. We want like a chrome finish
uh
frame handles
Yeah, we want like a chrome
Ugly ugly you you ugly. It's not your swing set
You don't have to swing on this
Dude if it were me though, I would put
I would put like something right here going up
Kind of like the head the like the hedges back here
So you could like jump you could jump out of the swing set over into the pool
I'll add a pool for free. That's fine
That was it. Oh, that was easy. Can I use it? Can I test it?
Okay
place sandbox
I need two of these
These are huge
No, don't ever get one this big
This is too many
Put it right in the back door. So they have to like climb through sand to go outside
That's not that big. This is really big. Okay, we're good
Too many sandboxes sandbox joke. I have a half a million dollars. I can make a joke like this
Guys, I can do like the stupid youtube prank
I got like 500 fucking thousand dollars in my account
We're just gonna set up like two cameras like one here one in the bushes over there
We're gonna hide back here behind the bushes and then we're gonna watch them come out out the back
And we're gonna like laugh hysterically when they like I don't what's happening here
God damn it
Damn it and they're gonna turn around and go back inside
I can make that fucking joke. I got the money
rooster spring rider
What is that?
Rooster spring rider. Oh, it's one of these
It's one of those like mcdonald's toys
This is a very you get what I mean mcdonald's. This is a mcdonald. This is from mcdonald's
Old mcdonald's play places used to have this shit
all yellow
No, that's ugly
That's all right
Your mcdonald's had to throw up corner
What is what is that? What is a throw up corner?
And then we need a cherry tree
How big does it have to be?
It can be small right? Yeah, i'm gonna put the cherry tree back here
Why do kids always throw up in there? Um, I don't think that's hard to decipher that
You eat a bunch of mcdonald's
And then you run around in a play place and slide down a bunch of slides
And get lost in like a ball pit
You that's not hard
If you eat like a mcdonald's cheeseburger if I ate a mcdonald's cheeseburger or three of them or whatever and then slid down
A slide I throw up when I get off
That looks good
Lost in a ball pit how
You guys never went
Did you guys ever do ball pits? How old are some of you guys?
Because if you were old enough to do the ball pit
At mcdonald's
You never did the thing where you dig you dig dig dig your whole body
To a point where you are underneath all of the balls
And you just like lie there for some reason
And pretend like you don't exist anymore and then like the somebody like jumps in
And crushes you
What do you mean? No one does that what you know how many times i've like bruised my shoulder and arm and leg
Because I got hulk hogan leg drop from some random kid that didn't know I was underneath them all
Still weeds somewhere. I'm looking at the mini-map. I don't see any other weeds. Do you see any other weeds?
These aren't weeds
No, those aren't weeds
Got them. There's more somewhere. There's one more this one little turd weed
You were recently in a ball pit
No, I just remember what it was like to be in a ball pit
You guys didn't have like throw the ball pit balls at each other when you were younger
That was original paintballing
That was like that was like nine your eight-year-old paintballing
And you leveled up to go paintballing
You would just like get in a corner and just have a never-ending plastic snowball fight. You guys didn't do that
All right, so I need to place
two times
Why does it say 11?
You want them on here?
Which one is it pergola moco pergola moco?
Oh shit this day. Oh, yeah, they want this thing
Chrome finish
I hate these. Why do you want one of these?
It's not my house. Like so why do I care?
How do you put this here without it being ugly?
Their back patio is not big enough to have this here
Well, might as well just
Whatever
Put it right in front of the door
Yeah, but what if it rains?
And it gets all up in there
Oh, you don't put uh, I thought don't you drape something on this?
Wait, they want 10 of these. Hold on. Do you how many of these do you want?
I'm confused. Hold on. Why do you want so many of these? Do you want more?
Where am I supposed to put these?
You're gonna have to put them on the roof
What?
No, no
It changed. Yeah, but see oh fuck. All right good grill
This one, right?
Oh, I see that I get it. I see you want to have a little grill patio. Ah, nice
Let's burn the siding off of their house
No, that's mean
Nice little grill right here would do
table
Grazy
All right. So I didn't this is gonna be over here
You know what have this be back? No
Right here. Damn it. No, I hate these things. Why do you want one of these?
I couldn't advise against that
Why?
Okay. Now I need six chairs
How do you have six chairs here?
Why would you have this many?
Wait one two
One, two, three, four five six. You don't need this many
How many people do you have in your family that are coming out here?
What? Huh?
You want more? This table is not big enough to have this many chairs
Wait
Wait this did you not want this?
You like got this online and you just you thought it was gonna be three times bigger then you want a couch eclipse a couch
Oh
Why do you want this?
All right, let's do grandma style. That's fine with me
Now this is here we go grandma
Perfect. I think we're good. No, not 100% though. What am I missing? Use the rooster
That looks all right
With like the grandma sleep pod which i'm gonna put down here
So something's going on over here that I missed weeds maybe
In the front of the house. It says I got everything done. How am I not at 100%? It's the three on the map
Oh, damn. Okay two sofa
Sami sofa
Sofa sam what is that?
It's not comfortable at all. Well, it's gonna make grandma
Now we need how many of these?
You want more than one of those? You don't have a big enough house for this
And then a table you don't have a big enough house. You can't have all this stuff
Got it. This person's fucked if it rains. That's what i'm saying. I felt like I was gonna put something up here
I thought we were gonna dread. That's why I was curious of why I had somebody
You know numbers. I thought we were gonna go
Uh tarp or something
That looks pretty good
cool
Seven thousand dollars
Soggy table soggy chairs. That's right. This looks like shit, but it's not who cares
I got lots of money. I just don't spend it
I'm gonna be one of those people that just has a million dollars, but doesn't ever buy anything
You just have it you open up like your bank account and just look at it and go cool
All right. What was this one? Hi there mommy left for a few months
When she returns, I will tell her that the flowers unfortunately rotted
Because I watered them too often
In the meantime, you have to cut them out and plant my favorite plants quinces wine grapes, etc
You can leave the flowers that are at the front of the house
So that won't that she won't notice anything when she returns all her flowers in the backyard have to disappear
That's my spot
Hope you can do that. Can't you see ya?
What the fuck is going on here?
What kind of willy wonka chocolate room kind of shit is this?
uh
Don't get involved in this
Wait, what would what leave the ones at the front, right?
This is a nice garden. No, I don't know. No, I don't like this. This gives me anxiety
And this is like anxiety here. I don't like this. I don't it just does so I don't something about it. I don't like it
Too much just give me one giant cactus and that's it. I don't want all this other stuff
I feel like they're all looking at me
They're all like alive and shit
I'm sorry. Okay. I mean they are alive
No, just I want one huge cactus
and then a big aloe vera plant and
Maybe like a couple other cactuses. So how many anyone weeds?
Yeah, there's still weeds everywhere
more weeds back here
Eating cactus
That shit will keep you alive man weeds weeds weeds weeds weeds. This is a nice table
Those don't even look like weeds. Those look like nice flowers
Okay, almost done with that
The hunt for weeds, you know
Right here. Is there a weed scanner? I don't have the skill point. Well, i'll get back to it. All right
So I need to plant two cornice
remove weeds and then plant
Okay, I need a a chan chan la mai
cornice
mastis cornice
So how many you want a few of these right two of these
Why do you want these fucking huge trees?
Can these go over here? Yeah
No cherry tree you want to put this over here
What are you? What are you dumb?
What are you dumb you dumb
What are you?
Okay, and then three channel them it is
How big are these
These are ugly too. Why would you remove your mother's nice plants?
I swear fucking zoomers man. I want to put this like back here
Not enough space. I'm moving this shit. There's gonna be enough space, but who cares it is a tutorial
It is just a tutorial. It is just a tutorial. It's weird to say that
It's like too many t's in that sentence
It's just a tutorial
How many how many of these three?
I'll go back here
Now these kind of need to be together. Don't they?
Yeah, this looks dumb if they're not together
Okay, and then
That's three then three ribs
ribs r i b e s
You know three of these wait. There was a color change there
species
Uh, let's do
Let's do the red
These are gonna go in the front. Why are you saying spi?
why
Come on, I can fit one more here
right
Here somewhere. Come on
eyes
All right plant
He said the thing
Yeah, I say the thing all the time
I think i've said the word spi more in the last two months than I have in the last five years
He said it again
Just pull surprises these days
Let's plant this
You have to say it with the voice
No, I don't have to do that
No, I don't gotta do it
You can do it. You try it
I don't like the way this looks
Three then I get to plant these over here
Let's just do the big tree
First to get it out of the way
It's gonna take forever to dig. Isn't it?
How long does it take to dig a hole this big?
I don't think i've ever dug a hole like this before every time i've ever tried to dig a hole
I always get into that. Oh, yeah, i'm gonna dig a hole
You get like a not even a foot down and it's impossible
You just can't do it anymore
You like hit you hit like obsidian. It's like
You can't go
I don't know why it's weird. It's like it hardens up
Rocks and shit. Yeah, I don't know how do people dig holes without a
actual
Device to do it
I'm you guys are strong. I'm kind of a wuss
This chat is so easy to manipulate. It's crazy
I didn't say that somebody did it. I didn't say I didn't say that
Somebody said that and i'm just reading it
I said it
soil
Just say pog and we will all spam pog
Yeah, but I mean this goes both ways
because
If somebody puts a fish on the end of their comment, i'm going to read it out loud
remember
So this works both ways
We tested that theory a while ago
All right, there's still weeds over here that looks all right
ooh
Well, it's no this is bad bad placement. Just cut that one down
All right. These are the weeds
Come on weeds
Oh, there's looking how much more of this shit there is. I gotta fill the pool up
I remember having an above ground pool
And this is what you did
You had to just put the hose in there and just let it run. It took like three weeks
Now these pools come assembled and they come with water in them
A company comes to the big truck and just dumps it in there
It takes like 20 hours. Yes spread over like five days. You can't water that in a row like that
That's like that's not allowed
So you do like a couple gallons a day and it took like like two or three months
Found the weeds
Yeah, because if there was like a water ban
The water police would show up
At that point just take a bath
Are you putting
Why does it take so long? Are you putting it through a brita filter first?
There's some sick fuck that does that
You know it I don't even have to fucking pretend. That's not real
There's some like weirdo that has like purified water in their pool
They like filter it first and then they put it in the pool
In case they get thirsty. Yeah, you can just go under water and just go
It's actually kind of fucking cool
That's not that's actually pretty cool
If I've had like a fucking hundred billion dollars
I'd have a purified brita pool
and every month
I would have another pool behind it
And then we just get a giant brita filter and then filter the water every few months and dump it into the other pool
And then have that one cleaned. I think that's good with weeds
Well, wait, I just like I just cut those down
But those doesn't worry. Those are nice
Oops
All right. Now we have to do plant 10 Bacchus
Yeah, get these out of here
10 Bacchus plants
This is gonna take a million years
10 of these
three
I don't think I ever did any work like this before. Can I get some pogchamps in the chat, please for that?
Never. No, I have I have such soft
unused hands
I'm the kind of person that if I pick up a bunch of sand in my hands
I might start to bleed
They're just unused
Now we're gonna do this in waves here
You need to use them much like i'm not gonna read that one, but like all right
Settle down
Just all right. Let's just go for it
See some of you guys that have like fucking unwashed hands
You'll know
You know how long this takes to do
This should take doing this would take like three weeks
You could fill a pool in that time
Somebody just wrote
What are you talking about?
I love it
Local old man has no concept of time. Yes, I do
I was actually gonna buy a watch
And no, i'm not talking about i'm gonna do rolex. No, no, i'm gonna get like a walmart fucking like 1999 watch
An apple watch
No, i'm not gonna get an apple wash. I would wash my hands in the bathroom and I would it would break
I would seriously I would I would just forget it was on and I would wash my hands
And it would get the water would get all over it
Yeah, you have to just get one of those really really just
cheapo ones
That would happen for any other watch
yeah, I know, but there's a difference between a like
$600 watch and a
$15 watch that if you break it you just go
Ah, oh well
Instead of go. Oh, no
No
Get some water is it you could get water resistant, right? But that's too much to think about
I'm just gonna get the time tattooed on my like stomach so I can look down and like know what time it is
It's probably easier that way
I'm gonna get them all in one go here
That's how how cheap is the tattoo?
Yeah, but that okay that I make it I make that joke, but somebody somewhere has that so they can
at the bar
you know when it's like
10-28 p.m
They can lift up their fucking shirt and go 10-28 p.m
And everyone goes like what the fuck
Everyone's mouth curls into like that. Oh
and then he like
shotguns a beer
Somebody out there has that
And it's like digital clock format too. So it's even more like oh fuck off. You know what I mean?
That's literally me
That's like an interesting idea though backtracking
I can hear it. I can feel the backtrack coming out
Okay, so that's done
Nice, you didn't hear what I just said. I was like, that's like a cool idea though
Because somebody just said that I have that and then I got like scared. I was like, I hope he's not mad
Oh faster planting faster digging
Yeah faster planting I got two
Let's get the better shovel
What's the shovel look like? I want to see it. All right medium pear tree
Cherry tree
so medium
cherry tree
Need two of these
Oh, let's let's go over here
Let's put the fruit together
You know right in the back there
And the other side over here
That's not bad placement
That looks I think that looks okay
I've never played it
not once
But I was gonna make like a okay now start dota auto chess and like have them fought. I don't know
Somebody might be able to come up with something from there
They had to be over here. That's unfortunate
Oh, well, I got plenty of money
Forcing chat to make your jokes for you
I I never said I was making it. I was just like
Thinking about it. It's a good shovel
These cherry trees aren't gonna get me sun
Yeah, they are why do the cherry trees look like palm trees?
Uh, yeah, they kind of do you're right
Mod that guy
Fucking mod that guy right now
He's right
All right medium pear tree
Oh, this is cool
I'm just kidding. It's not going over there everyone's but I just saw so many people
Like grab their monitors with both hands and rip it into their face and scream
Uh, let's put it right here. It's fine
All right. We still need more the lawn two medium plum trees are gonna go one two
medium plum tree
medium
Medium
Where is it?
medium
Plum tree, what the hell?
Medium plum tree
All right, let's do it this is the most boring garden placement
What do you mean? I think it looks good
Okay, it is just kind of tree tree tree tree tree tree
It's on the edges. You're right. This is kind of a boring placement. I told you i'm not very good at this though
I'm pretty good at smashing stuff with a hammer
If you need a guy to take down a wall with a sludge hammer with anger
Just leave it to me. I'll take care of that
If you want loud sounds I can make those
With my mouth did I get the job?
Okay, so that's still weeds
Why does it sound like static?
I don't know
I have absolutely
Idea. No, that's not how it works
It doesn't just stop
I seriously
everybody would just
It gets to a point when that the
Power of the devices that you power in your house
So if you have two sockets
Use the
Don't put anything in there. Did you guys get that nice?
All right. Now let's like fucking stomp
With like big boots on. All right. So we good
No, I still need to move weeds
Pool weeds not cool
Where are they?
It's getting dark out. This task is taking me all day to complete lawn
All right, I got the lawn mode still weed somewhere
Hmm. Anybody see weeds?
Ah, no, it doesn't not weeds
Where are these weeds could be flowers though. I can't tell I don't see any
Don't ignore us
What do you want about?
This whole job was two thousand dollars. What a piece of crap
99 percent
Oh
Just like cox's uptime in quotes
That's actually what they say
All right. Um
I got a lot of bugs in my house
No, i'm leaving it like that. Oh, yeah that we destroy these walls
No, I like this stuff. I'm keeping it. All right, there might be time too. I think we know what we're doing here
one little thing to come
Complete my part of heaven. I guess this is what is there any other tools that I have not figured out?
Buy the home alone house. Well, not yet. Hold on. I need to make sure there's any tools that I can use
Why is the music so the music's not scary?
Why is the music scary? What are you talking about?
I should be back home by the end of the week
I just need some rest when I get back and I think that the mess in my garden might make me nervous
See
You I don't even have this garden and it's fucking already making this person like nervous and have anxiety
I feel the same way. I want to hire your company again to put my garden or to own
Please take care of the lawn. It hasn't been mowed for ages
Dear
All right. Okay. Hold on. Can I go in your house?
You want to let me go in the house?
What if I need to use the bathroom?
So I just pee on the bushes?
All right, let's get this out
All right. I'm gonna do this very efficiently
Because I gotta mow the whole lawn
What am I gonna get for this?
like
20 bucks because that's okay when I used to door to door be a lawnmower salesman
I would mow lawns when I was younger and you got 20 dollars to do the person's entire yard
How was it worth it? Let's see
Okay. So this is what I was paid for
Was I getting the advantage taken of me yeah, there you go son. There's a 20 dollar bill
Thanks for the back breaking fucking four and a half hours of work
That's 20 dollars. So you can take that to the arcade
Yeah, I can take it to the arcade. Yeah, you can take it to the thank you by the arcade buddy. Mr
stewarts
Is the name that i'm being given on the stream for ten person?
Joe
This is not doing it. I know why are you mowing along with a weed whacker because I can't I don't have a lawnmower
This thing sucks
You're using a corner edger to mow an entire one
Imagine looking out the window and seeing this sorry ass guy out here just mowing with an edger
I don't have access to a lawnmower
Coming soon. I don't think there is a lawnmower. It's not in the game yet
Oh god and flipper. Am I going to e3 this year? I I don't know
Didn't everybody back out of e3?
Like everybody backed out of that one dude's birthday party
You passed out invitations to everybody and like one of the cool kids isn't going
So then all of a sudden you get like ah, I mean, I can't go. I'm sick
And then you end up with just like the your two or three close friends that go
And you rented out the whole laser tag arena. It was gonna be really cool
You have this vision in your mind
Of two teams of like 15 people on each team
Not the laser tag again
That just kind of reminds me. Does anybody else do this?
where
So you've like a trip or something that you've like wanted to do or planned for a long time
You have all these like ideas of how it's gonna go
Like it would like a water park or like disney world or something
And you go you have you think about like weeks in advance like all this shit that you're gonna do
And how much fucking fun it's going to be and how amazing you're gonna try that and you're gonna try that that
This restaurant seems cool. We'll try that one and then you get there and you do like two things and you're like, this is this stupid
this sucks
Or like, uh, this is
It's like okay, I guess
And you've spent weeks before man. I go like we're gonna try this is gonna be so awesome
And you have the thing you're like, oh this is
Yeah, that's all right
The most fun just kind of happens when you just don't even you accidentally have it
it's like you go to the disney world and
Instead of the ride that you wanted to ride and getting off it and being like that was fun
No, no, there's like a clown in the street. That's like juggling and you love it and you're like, this is fucking great
That's the best thing i've ever seen in my entire life
It's those moments. That's why I don't have a schedule and I and I don't stream that much
He's gonna tie it back into streams
You know
That makes sense doesn't it? It just makes sense to me. This amusement park sucks
You know when you get a game
And you're really excited for the dlc because it's like gardening and wow i'm so excited for this
I'm writing down all these things I want to do
And how much fun it's gonna be to plant and garden wow planting cherry trees and then you start mowing a lawn
and
kind of realize
Stop sputter walking. What are you what is sputter walking?
I feel like is that is that sputter walking like
Because I have to because look it doesn't look look look look look look look look look look watch ready
It doesn't get it all you see look behind me
There's like I I have to sputter walk
Because it doesn't get it all
Stop sputter walking
Ah
See look
See look at
Look, I have to do it again second pass
I wanted to get it all in one pass. What do you mean? He doesn't know
No, it doesn't look. Are you looking?
Look look. Are you looking?
Look at it. It just did it
Look, are you looking?
See
Look, it's not done
right here
See look at that
Fuck you i'm wrong. Am I wrong?
Because it looks like it's not cutting them all down
Fuck i'm wrong
I thought I was not cutting all them down
God damn it. I hate being wrong. I know i'm not wrong. I'm not wrong. Fuck. I hate I can't be wrong
No, I can't be wrong about anything
Uh, no, it's actually um, uh, somehow you're wrong
And i'm gonna explain with insane
Jumping through hoops to figure out a way that you're wrong and i'm right
Because I can't be wrong. That's not possible. No way
That's never i've never been wrong in my life
I mean that's maybe one time. Well, I like
I paid for something
And it was like a dollar 80 and I gave the guy
Like 220 and like I fucked off. I mean that's like everybody does that though. I was right. I was right
I'm right. I'm right. Look at how right I am. Do you see?
Watch this ready
Look at how right I was told you guys i've only been i've only been one one once in my life five
I didn't miss
What if you can't miss?
sputter streamer
No, i'm not. Look at how clean this looks this only took
375 dollars worth of money. Look at the minimap you missed we'll determine that at a later date
God i'm so glad that I won that argument
Oh
Feels great
hydrate idiot
See now we're just having a normal discussion and you have to bring this mean behavior in like, oh, come on
See what i'm talking about like this. I had them right too
uh
Come on
I'll take a break here in a minute. Just just relax. We're fine. It's like arguing with your mom
There's so many of these I just
Can we just use fire instead?
Can I like I think I might have been wrong
Maybe it's possible but you know
I think so though
I mean I was the lead in my school play. How would I ever be fucking wrong about anything?
But one time I threw
a pass
A 40 yard pass
How the fuck could I ever be wrong?
I did I mean I did that once
I got it all I did it wait. I didn't get this part. There's one little strip here
All right. That's good
That's good. Look at that
420 bucks, let's give me a second. Okay
Ah, okay, this is like this
I'm running out of space. No, not always riot always right always
Always right
Oh imagine coming here to this house. Yeah, this is
always
Right
You spent that much time writing that but you didn't mow your whole lawn
I feel like this is the kind of person that would have like 40 bumper stickers
right
So, okay. I was partially wrong
You want to know why?
Here's why you were partially wrong because if i'm putting that's how i'm gonna spin it check this out ready
If i'm putting straight down
Like this. Yes, it gets it all but if I have it up a little it's not cutting and I didn't know that
I I thought it had it didn't matter what the angle was
So you were partially wrong and I was always right
All right. I think it's time to buy a house. I think I know I know what I know what to do
Browser. I got to look at all the money I have
Let's do a little fixer upper
for purchase
Look at this one
Seventy four thousand dollars dude. I
I pissed away 74 grand in my sleep
Let's try it
We can let's look at this. This is a nice little fixer upper
Home alone house now, we can't go right to a thousand miles per hour. I mean don't buy
No, i'm buying this
No, i'm not going to a million miles per hour
Take a part in the garden contest to increase the house value. You may take part in the garden contest
Press enter and select type you want to rate your garden
I don't know what any of these mean
Submit garden for contest
What? American garden crop english
Modern garden. All right, i'm gonna go for the modern garden
It's very often treated as another room with com yeah, but i'm gonna make like a little barbecue or something
Oh, that's it's right now
Okay plant selection five stars equipment five stars lay out three
uncleaned garden one percent home increased by
Hey, let's put this up for a garden contest
You see what I really did with the cans
I was really going
Oh my god
All right. Let's get started. Let's get started. I'm fucking happy. Let's go
There's nothing what do you mean? Nothing to dig
Oh shit, you have to get every little piece
Take a mental note of what this looks like
Because it'll be probably
um
I'm trying to think this is how it'll be like at least
32 to 35 percent better
When i'm done take a mental note of what you see right here. I put away the tool
Screenshot that and then that
And this and then screenshot this
Get a screenshot of this too because I want you to compile. This is like a big collage screenshot that
Get a close-up of that one screenshot right now
Get a screen grab of that
Screenshot of like right here screen. Grab that one there
Keep up with me this right here and facing this way long ways. Hope you got them all
Is this poop like elephant poop?
That scared me so much I didn't know that there were fucking animals that came out of it
He was coming to fight me. Did you see he was like trying to bite me in the legs?
I yeah
What a wuss
Trying to prove that i'm not a wuss
These cans
I I okay. Look, I can't I can't imagine
If you this is like your bedroom right here, right or like right here
Can you imagine just throwing cans of soda out your open window?
What are you doing?
The just don't you have a trash can just you open the windows open and you're just like
Throw it out the window
If I ever threw a can on the ground
It would cause me physical pain
Not only be not only
because
Of the ability to scrape the dna off of the mouth part
I'm not you know, fuck that
Not only being able to cotton swab the top of that and fucking get me
But that it's it's rude and bad and you think i'm making that up. Oh look at question marks
What the fuck is this weirdo streamer talking about? There was somebody
That
Found like gum all over the ground and shit and picked up random stuff
And did dna testing on it and made people out of it. They like went and got gum
And like tested it and made what they think the person looked like
I swear to god, this is real
They did like a police sketch of these of what the people looked like
That is true. Yes, it is
No, i'm not having an episode. This is what do you mean? What about having an episode?
No, no, no
You know, i'm not saying like they made a human out of like finding gum in the trash
i'm saying that somebody did like a scientific research thing where they took
samples from like stuff in the trash
and gum
That was chewed up underneath like seats and shit and they did a dna like genetic code of what that person may look like
What if you're on there? What if that's you?
That's so interesting
That cloning experience. I remember reading about that like years ago
I didn't say what clone? No, I didn't say cloning. I said that there's like that like that's research
We already know what you look like. No, you don't you didn't go like find gum
That's an episode of black mirrors. No, no, this is like actual scientific research
Hold on stay right there
Nobody move. Yeah, it's for real
Just this shit is science guys. It's the pre-recorded joke
Sight your source
I think the american institute of uh collegiate scientific discovery
Yes, I know that sounds like a shell company for like a bit of money like launder money
mla format
The article and or researcher. All right, do I hold let me see if I can find this
I remember this was so fascinating
I got it
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. It's from the smithsonian
Are you gonna are you gonna not say that the smithsonian does like something interesting?
Yeah, like from cigarette butts
And they can make map out of face. This is me smithsonian smithsonian mag
Azine so this is this from the smithsonian.com
All you have to do. I'm not gonna like break the smithsonian website
If you want to figure out for yourself, you just have to type in pulling dna from gum what they look like
Into google and you'll find it
Thanks
Always wrong though, right? What does it say in my front line?
What does it say in my front line?
This is actual research
It's the god damn smithsonian
Use it as a retort for everything
Always right. How do we even get to like the smithsonian like research?
I work for the smithsonian. Thanks for giving us the shout out. Yeah, it's fucking great
Absolutely
Really interesting really cool research for real like it's really cool shit
Wait, didn't I start by saying that I was terrified of that? No, i'm not that was it's cool shit. What?
But imagine if you like saw your face
I do actually think it's pretty cool though for real. Well bullshit. I'd rather not see my face
Well, of course, of course we shout out science on this channel. It's very interesting stuff
I don't leave hair. Yes, you do
What are you talking about? You know, you you know, you shed like 150 hairs a day. What do you mean?
If you have a head of hair
You shed 150 hairs a day
Your hair is everywhere
Um i'm sputter walking again
There's a space x launch tonight. That's nice
All right. I'm i'm kind of just like talking I need to like focus
That's a free haircut every single day. That's true
How do they know it's my hair nerd?
Well, if science ever gets to a point where they can genetically take your entire code from that hair
They'll be able to know
That yeah, you ordered four big macs last night. You were in line
At that mcdonald's and you got four big macs
You can't hide that anymore
They'll have like some big mac juice saliva and you
Like that
dripped out onto the ground
And they'll be able to tell the quantity of big macs that you ate because of the like enzymes in your saliva
Give it like another 500 years
Did they get me?
Uh-oh, we were all right for a little while. I think we're good quantity of big macs
How many big macs do you eat? Well, it depends
It I mean it depends on how hungry I am. What's the scenario my
as I haven't been like
Streaming or whatever. Oh, no, my stream is sputter walking
Yeah, it was kind of inevitable because they didn't do anything
And i'm I was told that maybe as of we'd have a static ip later today
Oh, I think it's actually to zero
Holy shit, that was bad
Hold on. Let me send a text
Am I good?
I'm supposed to i'm supposed to text somebody when it's like really bad
Hold on. Give me a second
Give me one second
I would call this bad. I would call this
Not good
Hmm, is it worth I I feel like I got my hand on like the emergency line and I feel like I
I don't want to pick it up and be like help me, please
And they're like there's nothing there. Oh
Yeah, I don't want to be like the
The boy who crawled uh cried frames do we got a raid?
Oh shit, we do have a raid. Hello everybody. Hopefully we stay connected to the internet
uh, that's from uh
robaz
robaz robaz
Now I know I know who robaz is but thank you so much
That that's you. That's an old that's an old youtuber
the king of um
king of the castle no king of uh, what the
He's an old youtube
Robaz has been around for a long time, but thank you. Welcome everybody. Hopefully we stay on connected
Why am I not cutting this? Ah, yes the castle, uh, but yeah, we're playing house flipper currently fighting the internet
Hopefully you had a good stream robaz
Thank you so much for the raid
What were you streaming? What were you doing? He beat getting over it. Are you serious?
That's impossible
Wow, congratulations. That's insane
All right, I think it's time to say I gotta say I got I gotta like pick up the emergency phone line here
I'm going for the emergency phone line
Wish me luck. Let's see. Hold on
I didn't know how long this stream was gonna be and I hope we can actually keep it going for like at least a little
while longer
All right. I got my I got my hand on the button. I have a text written out and i'm ready to like press the button
I sent it. I sent it. I pressed it. It's been done
Let's see. Let's see if anything happens
I just got a text message
Well, hey, come on, give me a hand here
No, i'll be right back. I'm calling. I got i'm going for it. I'm gonna i'm no text is not fast enough
I gotta do it now
I'll be right back. I'm calling i'll be right back
Uh, that would happen wouldn't it? Oh god damn it
No
Uh, so I i've tried to call
Let me try to catch it call me when something happens
The phone is off
It goes right to voice bill
And they didn't get the text either because it doesn't say delivered their phone is off
No, it's not they're not closed. This is a direct line to somebody. This is this is somebody's like phone number
No, this is the opportunity
No
Charge your phone. What?
They called you no no, but that no no that wasn't them
No, they didn't that wasn't them
I i recognize that that was a different number
I have this person in my phone as like the cox guy and that's not who it was
Oh, well, it's okay
Uh, let's do
Let's do this
And faster digging
But after all I just wanted to make sure I clearly state uh everyone that came over from
Uh robaz's channel
Uh, I kind of was in the middle of this bullshit. So
Thank you again for coming out and again. Thanks for the raid
I really appreciate it
Just want to make sure I got that out
Because I didn't know if we were dropping or not in the middle of me talking about it
I'm saying i've got i've got an accent. I can't help it
I don't think this is any of the stream
No, we're good. It's all right. We'll be fine
Just everyone uh
Everybody just at the same time close your eyes and just think about how just think good thoughts here
The good thoughts aren't working here, but if we all use our like brain power
We can use our own 5g 6g network to be able to fix this. Does everybody think like give
Me better internet right now and like now our brains have electromagnetic, uh currents to them
We're gonna make our own like 7g network into this house
There's so much dead grass
I think it worked
Okay now like like a thousand of you just dedicate yourselves to to doing the brain power thing
And we should be fine. I need to get these weeds
No
Uh, you don't have to do that. I'm kidding. I think it passed
Yeah, I think we're fine
You guys did it
You guys you guys did it you actually did it
I'm, so proud of you guys
Maybe maybe he got the text hopefully I didn't I hope he wasn't eating like a pizza or something
Because if you're eating pizza that your hands
You can't really do anything. You're like a greasy hands and you can't really help and he's probably eating a pizza
And I didn't want to like bother him
If you had like a deep dish pizza, would you want someone to like text you?
No, you put your phone on silent until you're done
And you're gonna eat the whole fucking thing. That's fine. Don't tell that and then people are gonna be like
You ate a whole pizza. Don't worry. Don't listen to them
That's okay
It's not healthy. I know look at all this grass
I'm gonna shape this place up though. Just you wait
I want that lawnmower though
Can I not get the lawnmower?
I wish jerma would text me
No, you don't want me to text you
It'd be a bunch of nonsense
All right this house
Do the weeds grow back after a certain amount of time?
I feel like they probably do
Come on get in there right in the middle. I'll get it later
All right
So far so good
Looking pretty damn good
Oh
A little bit on the edge here. I'll get it. I can't get it
No, I cannot get that
Yes, I can
Gotta get the roots or the weeds will never go away
I don't think this game is going that deep
The house is a piece of crap though
So many weeds and so much grass
With the yeah, you know the house has to be renovated too
All right. What if I just do the part again if I just do the part that people see
Who cares, right?
No one's gonna look in this bush and see there's grass in there
Who's gonna do that?
That's being lazy. Yeah, but
You don't have to do it all
Come on get it almost done
He's being a lazy boy all this crap. That's what it is. It's crap
Look at all this crap
um
Get this chunk out of here
Replace it with some cactuses
I want some light
You're gonna make a house with a dad in the bushes
I have to play the brain. I'm not gonna play the brain power song
No
No brain power
I don't want to overdo it because you'll overload it
Can it be daylight, please?
So I can get on with this project
Need more power. I need to zoom in here with my seat. There we go
Let's open the door and see what we got working with in the inside
I need lights
ugly
Revolting what's with the rooms in this house?
Like give me some light
Uh, it doesn't matter
Oh just put i'm gonna replace him, but let's just buy a bunch
Can I put these outside?
I need the light out here temporarily
How do I turn these on I need the lights on the outside
All right. Here we go
What?
Why?
That doesn't control that how is it possible? Well, that's annoying. I forgot I had a flashlight. Thank you for the tip
No one's gonna see that. All right. What about I gotta clean this house up
I'm gonna be rolling out the uh, green carpet here
Make sure I got enough. You don't get this all just get rid of all of it
Yeah, fuck that get out of here
Put it in myself
This looks like left for dead. It kind of does
You are right
Give me that last little thing there. Come on
This game is seriously such you could become such a perfectionist
How is he still mowing the fucking lawn?
Because i'm doing it with a weed whacker
It would take this long
All right a wild
animal
At this edge
Ah, all right. Nice
I hope you had those screenshots from before ready
Because i'm gonna need them
Well, not yet, but in like probably like an hour
You mowing the lawn with a weed whacker at 3 a.m
Yeah, i'm probably on something really strong
I'm not sure what though
Watch out for the mole
I have to work in the morning. Why are you doing this?
Just just just 20 minutes, man. I got this
Hey, do you care if I play some music?
Anybody care if I play music?
Play some music
One of these
We need a clean slate because I want to get all I can put my own stuff in here. There we go
Oh, by the way, I forgot to say this the uh, the the one of the cocks maintenance like technician people
They told me that the reason why we're having problems is because of the kids playing call of duty
I'm not making that up
I swear to god
It's those kids playing call of duty
Oh
All right
You're one of those kids
I'm playing ultra call of duty. I'm playing call of duty
on like 30 xboxes
Nobody even plays black ops anymore. It's those damn video games clogging up the toilet
Hey, okay
You in there?
Yeah
What are you doing there for so long?
Nothing just I have to go to the bathroom
Get off a fucking call of duty
Come on
We gotta go to church mom said it's my turn to play
All right, but let's just let's just say that is the case, right? That's like let's say that's the truth
And that's really what's happening
What the fuck are you supposed to do?
What?
Too many video games too many internet connections too many
All right
Cock said it's my turn to use the internet
Don't queue our spier right now
All right
I think we are clean
Uh time to become like an irl streamer carrying on one of those like ghostbusters internet backpacks
Where's the broccoli video?
I got a big bigger fish to fry at this point
Okay, so we're good. Let's take take care of the uh, although outside is good
I'm gonna do a line. I don't even know what I want to do
We're gonna replace this grass. First of all, that's really important
That sounded like the weed wacker, but I can assure you it wasn't
My brother used to work at our local isp with nodes specifically
And he told me a while ago that 99% of the time they overload the nodes in higher resonance real areas
Most ips just oh, yeah. No, it's ridiculous
They don't they they don't give a fuck
See what they they just load as many customers on as many packages as they can
Until you have like thousands of people on one node
And then it doesn't work as good anymore
But here's the real awful part about this, right? I'm gonna give you the real reality. Don't use that
Um, most people do not use the internet
like this
right
most households do not have
A connection that needs to be constantly stable
like six thousand up
For three four five six seven eight hours, right?
So they can get away with all this dog shit because for the most part most people don't even know it's happening
The only reason why we know in this area that this is happening is because like i'm streaming right now. So it
You you you you're not gonna be like to convince very many people like hey, let me go door to door
Hey, we're gonna replace that node
What are you talking about? My internet's fine. I go
Fuck
Okay. Well have have a good night
What the fuck is a node?
turf
Big roll. We want a big roll. Let's get this laid out. Yeah, there are other companies out here
There's like I think like three different isps, but they all are the they run on like the same infrastructure
Let's get this out here
Am I do I got that in the right place?
I hope so
Build a labo node. Yeah
but that's why it's it's it's almost like
It's really difficult to even explain even to a technician. This is somebody who like whose job it is
To know like the ins and outs of a network and internet, right and they do they do it's not like they don't
but
Wait, you you you tube what?
What are you talking about? What are you doing? I think it looks fine. It's like, yeah
But I don't think you don't I don't think you understand. Wait, so you're watching youtube videos? No
No
What's youtube? No, it's my tubes. Hey that one was perfect
Shit, this one's not perfect. Cut it up. Get out of here. Just say i'm famous
What that's not gonna do anything
Hey, well, so it's it says here that this is this node is uh, kind of overloaded
And we're really trying to put out maybe oh fuck I did but look
Whatever
Yeah, but I i'm i'm famous
Okay, that's uh, that's fine. We're not replacing that node
Okay, who you are? I'm just gonna keep this going
look at this
and then there's the other option right of
maybe like you
Need to rent like an office
And like go to the office to stream
But those are expensive
Those are really expensive
How much was this?
Was that just five grand?
No, it wasn't was it?
Shit, I did this one wrong too. Sorry
but I
Should I really have to go to get like a stable connection? Should I really have to go to like an office complex?
That shouldn't be a thing
It's too many customers and not enough nodes to service all of them. Well
and like I said previously
Not very many people give a shit
as long as you know as long as like netflix works and they can like
You know play their game or whatever and they can check their emails most people just
Not gonna be that's not a big deal to anybody but sadly it is um
It is like this kind of everywhere
I've heard stories from other streamers and other people that have like do this, you know streaming and youtube and stuff
And they're like, oh, yeah my provider sucks
Like why do we all say that you know, it seems like that happens very frequently
Consistent upload is important to like one percent of all people. Yeah, that's what I mean
Is this lined up right?
Yeah, we're good. It's lined up right
It's gonna take them 10 years to replace nodes
What they should be doing is replacing nodes that people are having issues with on a priority because 90 people don't notice
Yeah, but that's where you run into like total just company like bureaucracy
They have like a blueprint of where they're going
And if nothing else matters
It's just company bureaucracy
That's all it is
Hey, this node is kind of like might need some work might need to be replaced or split
No, that's not that's no, that's that one's like in 2024
Invisible line shit
I'll get the little piece of tape and do that after i'll do it right now. I'll do it right now. I got it
I got I got the line. I'll do it
No, no, no, no, it's uh
No, it's turf turf not tape not turd. No, not a turd
turf
This is so pathetic
This is a turd
Oh man
anyways, uh
The worst part about it is that there are people that are on the ground
Whether they're technicians or supervisors that that will tell you
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, this is like bad or like yeah, they're not gonna replace this. It's not gonna happen
It's like there's like four different companies that are talking to each other that are like different branches of the set is weird
It's just really odd
Let's get a big one here big roll
No visible lines this time
Uh
All right, let's get these rolled out
Fuck I thought I
It's all right. What's my end game here?
to roll out grass
and then put
um a flower bed and a swing set
Come on, don't hit the side. Don't hit the side. Don't hit the tree. Don't hit the tree. Don't hit the tree. Don't ah
And here's another thing. That's kind of sad
Even with fiber you can still have something called a noise floor
People can just dump junk into the network
Sometimes it doesn't matter if you even if you have like a thousand a thousand which is that's what's available
Will you have fiber a lot of times?
This guy told me a story of how somebody had like a halogen light bulb
That was
And like fucking up the network years ago
Somebody he also told me about somebody that something as simple as a a modem not being screwed in tight enough
Can pump noise into the node and it's like a what what?
It's almost seems like why how how why is that even possible? Why would that even be a thing that could happen?
Electrical and veterans. Yeah. No, that's real. Apparently that's real
Halogen bulbs are really bad for interference. Yeah, I don't that's what I mean
so when you have like thousands and thousands of thousands of customers and one guy
like
has an aquarium in his living room and turns on a bulb or something and
Buzzes out the node. What do you do? What the hell are you supposed to do? Is that gonna hit better not?
For fiber any light getting into the cable can basically destroy the whole line. Yeah, it's fucking bonkers
but you essentially you roll any any
Internet that you have especially in north america you you're kind of just rolling the dice
So if you're gonna get a connection that's not gonna have any
really any major
interference problems
And then, you know, sometimes you just get unlucky like like I have
and even in two different parts of the whole country you have like interference and kind of
bad node issues
No, no, i'm not gonna do i'm not gonna hit anything with a hammer. I promise
No
No, please
Cut this tree down just uproot it and move it over there
And we've had the conversation before it's like, oh just move to here. Just just move to here
Yeah, I I I like it here, you know, I I like I wanted to live here. I wanted to move here
This is like where I wanted to live
Are you overlapping the terse? Is that wasting money?
Uh, yes, uh probably is definitely
I would say a hundred percent it is because vegas is a is that a line?
That's that's a visible line right here, isn't it?
Uh vegas is a 24-hour city
so
you know you
Up late at night or you're doing something you can go get food. You can go do something you can
You know something as simple as
Just getting like something to eat at 12 1 2 o'clock in the morning
Is it just the texture?
Vegas doesn't turn off. It's literally 20 everything is open 24 hours
so it's
It's great
especially
Um if you're a person that's like a up late at night all the time
There's tons of shit to do tons of shit to see it's great
Well, yeah, not everything not everything but most things that you want are open
Turn vegas. Oh, actually I asked
I asked that you said turn vegas on and off again. I asked that question to the guy this morning. I said
Can you just like reboot the node?
And he's like, I can't do that. We would turn off like a thousand like customers. No, that's not gonna happen
And i'm just like I can
You can't just restart it and to see if it helps who's gonna notice
Yeah, like your episode of doctor who is gonna freeze for 10 seconds like who cares
That person's not gonna know just try it
turn off
Vegas just flip the switch on and off once
What was I doing?
Turf I want to turf right? Yeah
Let's lay these out
This one right here
And then right here
It's almost like I need to have them overlap a little bit just so I don't get a line
I'm gonna do this one first. Remember I have to do it in this order
Okay, let's do that fucking tree
Vegas is down for scheduled maintenance
Am I no, no, I'm not leaving vegas. No
But fiber is like being built up here all over the place
There's a lot of new shit a lot of new developments that weren't here
But why do I like vegas? I just like the
It's mainly just the 24-hour atmosphere
Because you know, you guys know sometimes i'll be streaming and sometimes the streams will go to
10 11 12
a.m pacific
And I remember I hadn't like eaten anything really all day. I hadn't really done anything all day. So that's like my time
Offstream to like even go get food go to the grocery store. You know that that's
You know if I if I go to sleep at like two three four o'clock in the morning
It's just stuff is available. All right, that looks good
No, I mean we make food at home all the time
Have you seen the plates of food that I that I have from kim does great but making food
I make food too. I've got a great recipe
Sell the trees, uh, I don't think I can these are just permanent fixtures
Turn your flashlight off
It's got a I got a recipe or two
um
Okay, hold on a minute here. I'm gonna give you a countdown
It's gonna be really loud. Just make sure you know
one
Up if you don't know if you came to the stream or later
This is louder than anything in the whole game and I can't turn it down
so
Uh turn your volume down a lot because it's gonna blow out your microphone
one
two
three
I you can't take them down. Never mind. I did that. I might as well water the damn thing
All right, big roll
Let's go right here
But so the but so for instance the internet has stabilized, right?
It's we're fine. We've been fine for like probably 20 30 minutes straight here. It's just so
It's like impossible to like find and fix
It's the saddest truth there is
Peek your mic. Maybe that'll fix it
Because those of you that remember back in october
When we first moved in here, they didn't even work. It was all fucked up tons and tons of problems
It was it was awful couldn't be used
And that is a scenario where they fixed it and there was a big big problem that they fixed
It's not like that anymore
Just kind of just randomly throughout the day just
I'm fine. I'm good. Hey, what's going on? What are you using the internet? It's me the internet. I'm fine
That scared my cat. Oh, I'm so sorry to that little kitty
What's gas name?
sprinkles
george
Pretty cool cat name
Was that in the same person?
Uh, how many how many more of these this is not even real grass
I'm just coming to the realization here. This shouldn't even real
I'm laying out a football field
This is not even actually grass
What it is
This is not astroturf
It's topsoil
They sell this shit at like the home depot by the roll. Is this how you make grass?
Yes, I mean, yeah only if you want it quickly
No, this is not the real thing
you plant seeds in the ground and water it and
No, this is like
This is not real grass
You still using seeds. Yeah, that's the natural way
There's a line there
Come on. Oh
That felt so good. Did you see how good that felt? I got it. I got it
I mean, I missed it, but I got it. I'm good
But this is bothering me though. Why can I not remove these that's bothering me?
Can I take the little tape the roll of tape and do it?
Shit, come on really
It is a bother
I wasted it
I mean maybe a little bit. Can you put the maybe chips around the trees?
I'll try that
How much is this actually costing a lot of money what I for oh, no, that's not that much money
Missed
Wait, wait, wait, I'll do it this way
I didn't really miss
Didn't really hit it either though
Stream stream later in the day try to stay away from the prime time
it's it's just it's tough it really is because
I if you stick it if I let's say I started it like
seven eight nine o'clock pacific time, that's so
Unbearably late for so many people
And then on the same thing if you stream at you know, six o'clock in the morning seven o'clock in the morning pacific
It's just screwing it up for half the other. It's it's kind of it's difficult to try to figure out that right spot
But I I don't I can't really stream
at
Like fucking eight o'clock in the morning. I can't
I don't think I don't have the energy to do it
I don't I can't like get into whatever i'm talking fucking I I don't like wake up really
It takes me like two hours to sort of get up to like really wake up
and i'm at my
Highest energy levels at like this time right now
My whole life it's been like that ever since I was like 16
And I can't change it
I've tried a million times
But all through college it was I was peak hours for my brain
is between like one and
Five pm really is like where i'm at my highest energy. God damn it. I keep fucking this up
But I can't even tell who cares
You were born a 16 year old
No, i'm just saying like I I have
Even if I get up in the morning for weeks
I'm still a slug
I think i'm one of those like
I mean, I don't really abide by like the
energy fields and stuff
but
Is there like a do you just can you get like power from the moon?
Will you roll past the tree?
Can you be like a moon person and not like a sun person?
Okay, why is this not working?
This is gonna drive me crazy
Oh my god, why?
I I can't get this
Nope, i'll put flowers there. That's okay. Yeah, i'll put a flower there. It'll be fine. Oh, look at this
Ah nice. Oh, I like this
Very cool. Very excellent. I think
Yeah, I would say that's excellent
I mean, I know i'm patting myself on the back there, but I think that's kind of excellent
No, I need the big one
but
Internet, I mean, we're just having a conversation here
Apparently having a static ip
will
Help apparently
I got a line here on the left
And it's weird
Because I don't know if anybody knows anything about networking in here. Maybe you do
So I need someone to explain this to me
If you if you do then just chime in this is open forum chime in
The guy on the ground
Like the guy in the truck
The dude that does all the networking shit
Told me that having a static ip
actually somehow
makes your
traffic
Like a higher priority in the node
is
Doubt I would that's what I was told that it was possible that I could help
Doubt it static if he does nothing but I mean, but this is somebody that is
Am I gonna what's going on here? Is it stuck on the tree? Did I pay for this? No
I have a business package. So it all support is
There it's possible to have their qos set differently depending on address assignment
It's possible that because from what he was explaining to me
is
Because it's static
The cox just has rip
And it never changes and they know exactly where it is and exactly the dns. It doesn't change at all ever
You'd be saying it to calm me down
I wasn't like a raving lunatic when this person came
All right, calm down, sir. Let me tell you it got just easy. I'm not like a maniac
but so that's what the guy and and this was the person who was responsible for
like maintenance and monitoring all these networks
And then the guy on the phone like just the tech support guy said no, that's not true
So which one is it?
It's like they have like five different scripts for different scenarios. Like which what's the real what can somebody just tell me the truth?
Can somebody please help me?
We already yeah. No, we we've been on the business package. Ah, damn it. I missed it. No, I didn't I no I got it
We've been on business business this whole time
But it's almost like I don't know who to trust
It's like I have a telltale choice
Who's the one that i'm gonna like go with?
Me we're almost I almost have a legitimate yard here
Dude, like all these isps are so all over the place. It's so fucked. I remember when I first called
To like set up a business package and I said does business have priority
over residential
Yeah
Uh, okay. Cool. That's pretty cool
And then like three days later I was told no, that's not true who told you that
Who the fuck is running shit over there? Like what's going on?
it's just like we have like
12,000 employees and
All of them are not on the same page ever. What the fuck
He's going out. He's getting into another episode. No, no, no, i'm fine. I'm fine. I'm good
Wait, i'm gonna do this because it's cost effective
Static ip is an address for you specifically doesn't give you priority
But it does give them a direct point to know it's you rather than the guy down the street because when wait
That was a that was a one guy statement
Because when you connect to the internet the isp gives you a different ip every time you connect imagine having a street address
That changes every time you mail a letter as opposed to a fixed number so they know it's you
Well, let's see if it does anything
Do I have to water the grass?
Can I get these both?
I'm thinking one go. Let's try it
I'm gonna try it. I hope I get it
All right, let's try it again if I don't get it this time
I swear to god i'm fucking canceling my wow subscription
Ah, it's cancelled. Fuck it. I don't want to play it anymore
No, don't don't do it
Is classic wow going to be a separate subscription than regular? Wow?
Does anybody have any idea is it gonna be two different games or is it just gonna be two different clients?
How's it gonna work?
Oh, okay. That's cool
All right, we're almost done with the yard
Uh, i'm just putting plants around these i'm done with this shit. I ain't doing that anymore one more here
Like one more right here and then we're covering this with bushes
Ah, it's always so misleading to me. Come on
I got the money. It's all right
All right one last one. It's I this is too addicting to just do this shit
That's it
Nice. All right, let's get in there
All right. I don't care about the front here. I'll put like a welcome mat or something
Oh, there's so much more to do
Look at how much more there is to do
There's so many more things to do
Uh
I think I could get him
Let's try this i'm gonna try to just plan it out
Look, it's can't be it's not gonna be perfect
I wonder if that's lined up right? Who knows?
It doesn't have to be perfect. Just get it right
Okay, what's the furthest one this one? No, this one
Wait, what turf drive?
What do you mean turf driveway?
Well, look at this like grasses here. Ah
I have to do these though. Yeah, I can gravel over it. It'll be fine. Hey you turf them where the driveway goes mate
Just turf. Yeah, i'm gonna turf the inside
I'm gonna have a grass house
It's better than it's cheaper than carpet here come the ants
All right. I don't I i'm I need to do. Yeah, the driveway is this but there needs to be you know
What I can just I can i'll fix it in post
Yeah, i'll fix it in post
Don't worry about any of this shit
Get rid of all this i'll fix it in post
That's all except for this one and maybe this one and this no i'll fix this in post production
All right. How's the house look?
All right. Um
Okay, here it comes here. I I don't want this. I don't want this wall here
That's like is it the garage?
Here we go
You ready?
three
two
One it's gonna be loud turn your volume down if you haven't already loud just keep your volume down
Keep your volume down. I'm serious. Don't turn it up
This is as serious as i'm going to be
Why are you doing this to the garage?
It's really important that you see this in a minute
I have a vision that the noise doesn't happen when you do it too much in succession. It doesn't have to random
sick
Frank I can't hear you. Okay, I can you can probably hear me now
Okay, you can hold on let me just take a look at what I did here, okay
All right
There's blood everywhere
Let's clean this up a little bit
All right. I'm not i'm you can turn the volume back up a little bit. I'm not loud anymore
I've got a great idea. There's some trash to remove. I just opened the door for the first time. Will you relax?
A person with like 30 people in their family. You can't even fit everybody in the same picture
I've ruined my painting. Why did you do this?
Just control z like everyone else was you just yelling
Got some bugs over there
Was it what's it back? Don't you get like a vacuum cleaner?
So you can't sell the bugs, okay, that's good
Got some the glass
All right. So we got a little house here
Hold on. Let me think
I have an idea what's over here
What the fuck is this? Why are there like two why the three garages?
All right. So these are the garages. Okay
One two three
Clean up these first so we can get make sure we get a three car garage in here
How's this dirt looking pretty dirty
Okay, so one two three
What that actually do it I can clean from back here
You actually can
But I can't go inside with this
Can I clean the window? Let's clean the window here clean. Come on
E
Oh, it's what other side what I shave get that soap scum off
Just like just brush the window's teeth. Okay, good. Everything's clean in here
So that's that then all right
too many doors
What is this the kitchen?
What is this? What is this the bathroom? Then what the fuck is this?
Wait, does this house have a bathroom?
a bathroom into a bathroom
Why?
This is a fun house. I'm so confused. I need to look at it from the outside
All right. So
I hate this place
I oh all the doors open it up. I hate it
Because I don't even understand what like the
What is this fucking layout? This opens up to a hallway. Why is this door even here? This is pointless
For what?
What is this room the laundry machine?
It's a prize
What do you privacy?
Well, you don't you're gonna like peer over here and like oh, what are they doing down there? They have a door to close. Look
What what do you mean privacy privacy for what for the hall?
Hey, hold on
Oh, they almost shot me
No, in fact, what's on this side?
Now we gotta keep this the way it is. All right, I gotta clean this up lower your volume in five seconds. Thank you
Volume drop it one two door. What is this?
What I need to build
Build what the hell?
loud
It's gonna be loud
Can't break this. Oh fuck. I can't can I not fill it?
That's annoying I can't fill this hole because I can't get rid of this
No, i'm not too short because I can't break it
See
There has to be a door there. Apparently I can't reach it. Well, it's fine. Whatever
I'll put i'll put it like a fake door here
Okay, big professional hammer. That would have been pretty cool
All right store. Um, just like a door
Whatever it's i'll just put it back. That's fine. Okay
I'm not gonna use it. This is the front door here clean the windows
Just make it a window
I don't think you can put windows in
How much money do I have this house sucks? It really does
um
Volume give me some warning here
Volume turn it down
I'm gonna do all my demolition with the volume turned down for all you guys. Okay, keep your volume down
Oh
This house sucks
It's not a claustrophobic house i've ever been in
Okay, so
So this is the bedroom anymore walls that need to come down
bathroom bathroom
kitchen kitchen
No
that
entry
kitchen
bathroom bathroom
bedroom
All right. Okay. I got it. No need to tear anything else down
We're gonna start in the bathroom
Close close
Here we go
Okay
so
We're gonna do tile
wall tile
Wait, what ceramic? Oh, let's do
blue
No floor. Here we go blue rectangles
Ooh
I can have a 3d room
What's going on here? I just tried to put them down put them down. All right
That's pretty good for the ants. I hold on this looks like i'm standing on a roof
This is a roof. This is not a floor
I like no clipped on top of the roof and i'm looking down
Come on get them all get over here. Come on. This thing's gonna overheat all vacuum cleaners are like mini guns
If you use them for too long, they'll just they'll overheat and turn off
All right, they're gone
Oh, this is the outside again. God damn it. It's gonna do all the windows
For goodness sake heavy weapons cleaner
Something like that. All right, that's good
All right now call the insurance company
Let's do all the windows
You guys want me to do the home alone house. Do you understand?
That's like a 20 hour stream project to do that. I will do that tomorrow
All right looks good
Weather permitting we'll do that tomorrow. You know, the weather is the internet here, by the way
Good one. I know
That was a scary laugh. I'm sorry
But am I really sharp?
And the whole stream i'm gonna talk like this
Gonna be called bozo's cleaning job
I'm really thinking about doing like a character
I mean like what's all of this?
Should I do a character tomorrow?
I feel like people would come to the stream and not want to hang out because of this guy's doing a character
Yeah, I got it assembled. What the hell is there a light switch on me? Why that light? Oh, no, I did this
I did this too
Derma raptor house builder. I don't think that would go over very well
That wouldn't go over. Well
I'm certain of it
All right anymore windows to clean. This one is clean up top
inside
Where is this? There it is
There's another outlet switch that's fucked up over here. Uh, I know
Cover your ears
I'm gonna do a running start just so you get prepared for it. Okay another piece up here
There
All right, that's it. That's it for remodeling. I think I don't think i'm gonna have to take any more walls down
Blood on the wall. I got it. It actually was up there anymore up on the roof or anything
There's something right up here. Come on
Where is it?
Must be inside that room
I got it. I think that's all clean. Just wait till you get the garden
You're really gonna get the whole thing here. All right. So what was I doing bathroom?
Bathroom 3d tiles. Can I do a 3d wall?
walls
wall tiles
ceramic tiles classic brown
ceramic tiles two shades of green
only two
Oh
It's actually kind of cool
This is the 3d room. No, we'll do the white ones
Actually, I think I want white on the let me go back
walls wall tile
3d white
Oh, dude crest 3d white it's a bathroom. We'll do the 3d white see how that looks
I don't mind it. I mean it kind of looks like a candy house
too dark
Now this is
Like scary horror room
Yeah
No, no, I gotta no
No, we're gonna do 3d white on the ground
Doesn't this look like like the asylum?
Uh
This is inside of an asylum or something. No, I need to
Like it's like a horror movie horror game. I gotta get rid of the paint the walls paint them
slender
Or is it a public bathroom?
at the beach
What about glaciers snowy glacier?
That's not it's all right national park bathroom this music is banging
That's pretty good
It is a dentist office isn't it?
It's not bad
It's not that bad. It's fine. Looks good
I do need a light a lamp in here or something or I keep doing this shit
I'll just get a fluorescent up here. I need another one
Okay, I need an accent wall, uh, let me get let me look and see what it looks like
Okay
I don't like it. It's I I feel I feel scared in here. This is not like I don't feel comfortable in here
I feel really uncomfortable in this room
It's actually causing me real like anxiety. It is i'm not comfortable right now
I gotta take i gotta do something with this now
I feel really bad right now
Quick get it on there
I it's something about this room. It's the room that's doing it. I don't understand
Anybody else like feels horrible right now
Rust calm down calm down
He's having a nightmare
I'm having a nightmare
It's like p it's pt
That's what it is
It's this shit. It's like
Local radio says that he was under the influence and then he found his way over into the barber shop
And he said they saw the police were notified later that evening
He saw himself with the revolver in his head
And it was that's what's happening. I hate this
loud
Ready my pt in this house. I'm sorry guys. I feel a little bit better
Damn it. Why does it have to be that loud? I don't understand. It doesn't
No
Shit
It's okay. It's okay. I didn't break anything
I did break something
What a waste of pain. Look at my balance didn't even make a dent
I'm sorry loud again three two
Terrible still
I almost need to I don't know what I need to do
It's like the way that these doors are set up it's the doors too
It's these doors. It's like the brown door
They need to be different
It's just like i'm walking through no cover this up
I need lights on the ceiling
That's definitely what it is lamps
sconce
ceiling lamp cube
Oh, I like the brass by many of them
I don't know what's going on. I gotta get out of this room too many doors. It's just too many doors
I think it's where the window is
This house is cursed
Okay, i'm i'm setting one down. It's the lighting
Okay, I just need to paint the walls like blue
And then I can and we find
walls
a biscuit no
Tile it a nice
Ceramic blue
Oh, okay. Yeah, look at this. I like it. I like it. Give me
Yeah, this is nice. This will make me feel better
It really will
The fuck do I use this? All right, I started to feel better a little bit
Somebody said this is a fast food bathroom
Yeah, this is like a long john silvers bathroom
Anything is better than
Pt tiling
No, no, I don't like it. What's wrong with me right now
Pt I just saw pt tile
Package pt the room's too narrow. I can't add windows. I can only have one window here
I'm just gonna do paint. I'm gonna do
um
Spring I feel like this will spring grass. This is the one. This is absolutely the one
I think i'll be able to fucking relax after this one
Let's test it
Yeah, okay. I already feel a little bit better
This is a clown house
Okay, I feel great
Green, I think green is just me. It's just me
Yeah, I feel fantastic right now
This has got to go though. I hate that
You're turfing the room
That's all right
That's better for me
It's the bottom say the ground is fucking me up
It's 3d
I need some rugs
Let me see one of these maybe
Just rectangles. Let's see
Look at that much better. Oh much better
Okay
It was the floors on the tile
It was the tile. Yeah, the floor tiles would just
They were fucking up my brain
Okay, uh, this has to be dealt with though. So I apologize, but you're gonna be loud again one
two
Three this is the only thing I hit right?
All here
All right, get the paint did I delete the paint?
Which one was it?
Ceramic green
Which one this one? All right
I mean it is
This is a this is a nickelodeon sprite room
But it's okay
This is like a slime room. I'm okay with the nickelodeon room
All right. Looks good
Yeah, i'll keep the ecto cooler room
Yeah, I said ecto cooler. I know
He's making nickelodeon studios. Well, not quite
Okay, so
You can't do it
You can't roll it in the house
Sorry guys
I tried I did make an attempt and what about I wanted to do the garden first
But I need to be daytime. This needs to be paved
Pave this
Is it like pavement?
paved
gravel
surfaces
All right
small
Small grain
I need to be square
square
Small grain
Just make it a straight. That's what i'm doing
Not straight
I I have to paint it i'm trying hold on
What did that just go?
Actually terrible. I I have to paint it
That's straight. That's fine. That's straight
Actually terrible it's not perfect. It's rock
Rock is not perfect. That looks all right
And then check this out ready
Let's go into outdoor survival. No
Garden here we go decorations furniture services other
plants
I need like some bushes
broadly spreading bush
That's not bad
Oh, I like that
a dwarf shrub
How tall is this?
No, that looks dumb decorations
Dog house wait, this is all going way too far stone quarter circle shaped flower bed
ooh
Why is this so tiny what?
I thought this is a big lamp post
That is tiny
surfaces
wood cuttings
ooh
Uh, hold on bark
wood cuttings
I need it to be circle
Why is it here we go check this out. It's gonna be nice
Told you I was gonna fix this
Um, I really
I can't
I can't why can I not do that?
That's a bit of worse
I I like the wood chips though
Wood chip. No
I'll go back here
It's got to cover with rocks
No, I can't make it like a stove. Ooh, but I can do this
That doesn't look right
Yes, he's gonna trip on it
I need to put grass down there. God damn it. All right. Hold on plants
How about one of these?
How does it that might be okay?
Ready?
You let me know
I'm not a good direct decorator. I'm really not plants
bushes a handful bushes
salvia
um
Oh
This might be okay
All right. Okay. Hold on a minute here
What if I do like one here?
And then one here
All right, and then there's like another one back here like two or three back here
I don't hate this
They're not that tall guys. Relax
Somehow it's even worse. They're not what are we talking about?
pubes
This is fine
That's all right. And then i'm gonna put like a little flower bed here
flower bed here
Flower bed like a couple of flowers
Why is everybody all crazy right now?
You can hold your review until after
It's too close to the driveway for fancy decorations. Not necessarily
pubes
Oh my god
I can't even man
I can't even
That looks fine. It looks good
and then maybe we could do like
Just one or two little things here one or two little things here and then like maybe a little bed up this way
It's uneven
It's fine
We're gonna do some to jt's
Erectica
All right
Somebody's gave 100 bucks for all luck gave
100 dollars
Thank you, bro. Look
for the
10,000 bits
That's a shitload of money
Thank you
and you say
Laughing my fucking ass off. Imagine if kim found out you were playing a clean the house video game instead of cleaning your house
Lol, this is fine
This is not a i'm no, this is gardening right now
But thank you for the hundred dollars. That's a lot of fucking money
We need some other flowers in here too. Let's do some um
Anemone
Here's what we're gonna do ready check this out
Let's see that don't think I know what i'm doing
He's not doing it right. He's not doing it. He's not doing he's not doing it right. He's not doing it right
Check this shit out. I'm about to blow your mind. I'm gonna change everything. Don't worry
And then let's go with I want some white
Ooh, I like these too. No
No, no, I want white. Those are kind of like those are like those are
I don't like it. I actually don't like it. I want white. I want like little white flowers
Here we go. Let me see how these look how we're getting somewhere. We're getting somewhere here
Come on get in and then guess what goes right in the middle
Can you guess
That no, I gotta get rid of we're gonna do this. No, what am I doing?
I don't know. I don't I have no idea what i'm doing
Yeah, I do. Um
I need like the like one or I need like a tree
some taller ones
I think that's a good idea
The tall ones but we're gonna do off it. We're gonna do one in the other
So watch this one ready
So now in the middle here
Shit
I can move them
So we're gonna go white
purple
Is that too far? Let me see how far that is. No, that's not bad. No, i'm gonna keep the way it was
The leaves don't match. I'm gonna keep the way it was keep the way it was just i'm i'm digging too much about it
Get them nice and tight
The garden looks really old
How does a garden look old?
A garden looks old
All right, that's okay. And then i'm gonna put one more thing behind here
This is um
What goes with purple and white
a light green
yellow
What about this?
Chrysanthemum
Oh, that looks nice. Ooh
This looks nice. Let's see what it looks like over here
No
Maybe the front no
It needs to be a little bit bigger
Gotta be bigger than that
strawberry flower fold
Powerade this is not big enough. Wait, i'm gonna do this plants. Maybe we should put the yellow. No chrysanthemum full
How big is that?
This is big, right?
No, fuck. This is tiny
Well, I have to put this over there gardening's too hard
Gardening's too hard. I think it just it's gardening's too hard
I just need to do that's just too time consuming. Why would anybody do this?
Normally wouldn't over come the parking pathway
But what if they might because they wanted to look decent on their pull-up rows belong on farms not flowers
It's a look, okay. Look at the house looks like shit. That's why i'm having problems here
The house looks terrible. I need to paint the outside of the house. All right, what the hell is this thing called again?
I think i'm gonna do carrots pumpkins
It's the purple one. Where is it?
What was it called?
It's not this one right here. Is it?
Is it animo? Is this one? I think it is this one. Yeah, it is
Okay. Now I got the I got the base here
No, good. No
Okay
Then we just do double it up
I'm done
I'm i'm done after that
I'm gonna go fucking hit up the wall with a hammer some more
Where the hell is it? Can I sort by color?
I guess not where that's doll. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
It's called like doll something
Where the where is it?
Hey
Hey, what was that sound?
Okay, almost done
I don't need it
Oh, look at that. Looks nice
That's cute
This is overloaded here
Too overloaded in the front
You were right. You guys were absolutely correct on that
And we're gonna do let's do um
Yeah, too overloaded. That's better
Okay. Now
What the hell was I doing over here making rocks?
this
There's so much room
um
Okay recreation
This is about i'm just gonna make a carnival back here
Why is this tiny?
Who is gonna use this?
How tall are these kids?
You gotta have the gnome goalies. Okay that yeah, I will I will hold on
hammock
sandbox
What I actually can make like an actual?
All right. Well, hold on. Where's this gonna go? Right here. It's good
recreation
grill projector
Rooster rider
outdoor cinema screen tire swing
a pizza oven
Why is there a pizza oven?
A whole gym. Ah
I gotta have a gym
All right kids. We're replacing your get rid of this stuff. You don't want this
Dad's upgrading you
Yeah, you gotta have the yellow slide. That's very important
Blue slide. That's a lot of bullshit
I'm not gonna have a blue slide in my
That's what you say. You know what I mean?
We're gonna go default
lightning yellow
I want to be able to say when you spin around
It's gonna let's make an obstacle course
You gotta like slide underneath the kids that are all spinning around really fast
That's too dangerous. Ah move back over. All right. We got a little play area
Put some trees in here
I need a
pizza oven back here, too
No, I don't not yet fire pit
Can I put a pizza oven in the house?
Okay, here's the kitchen. I want a pizza oven
Why can't I not have a pizza oven in my kitchen?
Um, really pizza ovens don't go inside. Yes, they do
I'm not gonna have somebody telling me I can't have a pizza oven in my house
Gotta take this down loud incoming
There comes a loud noise. I apologize
I can't close this
I have to have to put doors here
Whatever no, he's not gonna
Slide down. No, that would not be good
Okay
Uh, where can I put this?
I'm gonna make like a little path. Okay, there's gonna be a back patio
Right here
Well pizza oven will come in a later day
I'm gonna be a rich dick
I'm gonna be the guy with the with the you know, if you're the guy with the pizza oven
on the back patio
I mean
You you're kind of a dick
I
I mean you're you're a dick. I
Definitely want one of these
But can't you just see going over somebody's house that has a pizza oven on their porch?
You're probably gonna be like
Is this guy a dick? He might be I feel like that's like a like the potential that you might be a dick
Pizza ovens are dope. I know I want one
I definitely want one on my back porch, but I feel like somebody would think I was a dick
I feel like that's like a
Can I do this?
Can I have the kid's house be inside the house?
You open the door and you go into the kid's house. I guess I can have it in here
This could be like a little playroom. No, not I think everything's about the kids. I'm a dick
I have like three pizza ovens on my back porch
I would gladly be a dick if and then I have a pizza oven
I know i'm just fucking around. Don't worry. I'm really i'm just making I am a dick because
I'm just trying to have the funnest house
I got pizza oven. I got an entire
county fair in the backyard
To charge people to come over
Recreation anything else?
Well now I know i'm a dick
Are you serious?
Who puts this outside? Why would you put this outside?
Well, I need to put the gravel down here
um
sand
Hey what stop doing that every time I go in the house it takes it off
I don't want this tree here. That's the problem. There's a tree in the middle
Oh
No one puts gravel on their porch
I'm just trying to block it out to see
Well, how do oh fuck right? I don't I can do this
shit
I didn't I didn't realize it. All right sports surface
Am I no, I actually have to place them one by one
No, I don't do I really?
Is there a bigger one?
Yeah, there is okay
I don't think I said that would be horrible
Okay, I gotta fix this. I'm
Oh crap god damn it. I need the logs. I need the long ones
How are you supposed to do this?
Or whatever I can it's fine
This is gonna be such pain in the ass
Just make a whole new house
No, I can't make an entirely new house
Dick
Does it really have to be a tree here that I can't remove?
I can chop the tree
How do I do that?
This house is giving me
With a weed whacker
All right. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Wait, this is just the whole thing is messing me up
I need walls. I need to paint this house
biscuit gravy
Okay
It the outside of the wall is gonna be biscuit
Let's see. Let's make I want to make sure I like it because this is it looks terrible
What's even worse? No, it's gonna be
all this stuff
walls
wall panels
wooden house
Brick i'm not doing brick
creamy caramel
no
This one may be
smooth pastel pink
I'm not doing 3d tile
Ew, this is ew
Should I do the waves?
It's gonna I think it's probably gonna be there's a brick
Let's see how bad this looks
Let's just see how bad it looks. Hold on. That's not
Another hundred bucks
No good
We'll do the light brick
uh
walrus boy
Gave a hundred dollars. Thanks for the 10,000 bits walrus boy
Thank you
That's a lot of fucking money
$100
And they say I was a sub for a while but had to cancel my deva card due to fraud charges
And so I was not able to resub again until now
Please take this and consider it back pay for all the times
I wanted to show my support by being subscribed if I wasn't able to
And for the literally years of laughs, you've given me. Thank you. I'm sorry to hear about the card problems, but thank you so much
Means a lot. I really appreciate that. That's a lot of money to ever give anybody
And I am shocked and floored that you'd want to give it to me
So, thank you
Uh, hopefully your card situation is done and looks good
Kind of like the outside of this house looks pretty good. But thank you
How do I panel up here?
um
How do I get that?
Nice. This is a nice
brick oven house
My house just is a pizza oven
It's fine. It's fine
Sooner or later, we'll have a good house
So earlier in the stream
You probably noticed I was
I was very high energy
I'm very low energy right now for the last like probably hour
I hit the wall
So if you don't know I didn't sleep very much last night
I only slept for about three hours. I was up at like seven o'clock in the morning
And I hit my second wind and turned the stream on it was like a psycho for three hours
And now i'm just like
Ah, I don't hate the outside here on the bright side. The internet has stabilized. Yeah, it's been pretty good
Take what we can get right
Go to bed. No, not yet
I think I can finish this house
All right question
Um, should I do the home alone house tomorrow? I ain't doing anything. I should maybe i'll do well
Like isn't there like a horror movie house
I feel like if we're gonna do house flipper I may as well dedicate like a couple of streams to it
That's right beep
Scream at me
This actually is just a pizza
I should just block this off and have these be three different pizza ovens
My house is just a giant pizza oven
And I live in it over here. That's just stupid enough for me to want to do it
I'm not making the pt house. I'll fucking throw up
Is there enough?
Is there two more?
Come on. Hey, look at that. Oh, are you shitting me right now guys?
Can I put like wood chips in here and have like a wood oven?
There's a wood stove
Oh, come on. I can't
Just make yeah, I can make like a like a pizza parlor. That's a good idea
So what can I do for this?
Personally close this up. I need three
I don't have enough. Can I seriously not build more one at a time? I thought I could
Isn't it q or something?
We're like w e r where what is it t q?
No, there we go. I thought I already did this
There we go. There. Okay. There it is
All right. This one's gonna be coal
For like extra crispy pizzas
This would give me wood fire coal fire
and then
um
I don't know microwave
How else does half of the restaurants make their pizzas and is the parlor the garden doesn't even matter
This is like the okay. Uh, this is the way you come in
Brick oven
Yeah, the whole thing's a pizza oven and then the coal look I can do coal and let's just block this out in my brain here
Yeah, you just like fucking frisbee the pizza into there. You can have like 10 of them at a time
Let's see. All right. We got ceramic charcoal
This could be charcoal
Need shelves and racks for the pizza
Yeah
ceramic
This looks like charcoal. It's got to be just like
Brown black or something
That looks all right
Let's try this
That looks terrible
This is shit
This is a shit idea
Okay the back floor
This looks like wood wood fire
Fire
Rug a rug fired oven. Okay, looks good
and then this needs to be like
black
Just need
Not blue
It just needs to be black
They don't black carpets
A pizza rug
Yeah, but that's for the main hallway
Can I just paint the ground black?
Imagine that
Imagine painting your ground black doing some weird shit in there. I don't think I can paint the ground
I mean they could do the charcoal to be the sides
The apartment has black floors. That's interesting
I mean, I guess maybe like entryways
Oh, that's fine. We need like heat lamps, too
I'm gonna air it out
All right. So let me see
So the wooden paneling is to go in here
Maybe we can get actual wood paneling
wall panels
Wood
Here we go. Yeah, that's perfect
Is the same thing? No
Do they even have pizzas?
I wish I could do this faster. It's a pizza hut taco bell combo
Why did you say that?
You just said the magic
like 14 words
Pizza hut and taco bell combo 9. Fuck
Wait pizza hut and taco bell combo. Those are syllables. Those aren't words
You could tell i'm fucking tired
Fucking tired
I counted syllables as if they were words
but you said
You said pizza hut and taco bell
You said the combination of things that make me hungry
I've entered sleeping mode. Yeah, I have um, I am
I might have to call it soon. Unfortunately
I'm just glad I was able to stream for at least a while
And this is relaxing and fun. This is like helping me go to bed
How do people do 24-hour streams? I can barely stay awake for 24 hours
Wooden box room. What am I doing?
What am I making a pizza house? What is it? What are we doing? What are we doing right now?
Making three giant pizza ovens
Why?
Why am I doing this?
I feel like if I walked in this room, it'd be like
I want to is it weird that I want to sprint around in a circle in this room
I want to fucking run around. I know this is basketball court now
I want to just fuck it looks like so waxed and slippery and shiny
I want to just start here and sprint and stop and turn and sprint so it goes
That's so badly want to do that
Whatever gets you off. Well, yeah, that's fine
Have you guys ever seen like a freshly waxed basketball court?
Oh, it's something to behold
it's just like when the uh
So when the when the when the gazebo goes over the ice
And it's brand new ice freshly shaved down freshly like coated
The zip. Yeah, the zamboni, whatever
I always want every time anytime that the the I can't say zamboni. That's a gazebo
So anytime the zamboni goes across
Same scenario. I want to get a running start
like wet slippery just
zambonied ice
Start outside the rink and run as fast as I okay. So let's say that's the rink starts right there, right?
I want to run as fast as I humanly possibly can jump dive face first slide across the whole rink
Did you just make like a golden knights dis?
Why the golden knights did a fantastic fucking job
I feel like I could play like goalie for a minute. I think I could like stop a slap shot. I really do
If I ever got like the balls
imagine if I like contacted
Like the glow like the golden knights organization
And I just had a star player like try to score a goal on me
I feel like I feel like I might die
I don't know why i'm picturing this weird like adam sandler movie scenario
Well, like I get the puck right in the visor right in the between the eyes
I'm not doing all those up there
I can't
That's so small
Do them do them do them. All right. All right. All right. I'm doing i'm doing i'm doing i'm doing them. I'm doing them
Finish painting the other room. I will don't worry. I will
Don't worry. I'm gonna come back tomorrow. I'm gonna be rested. We're gonna have a static ip
And there's gonna be no drop frames
And what are the like fucking wizard of oz bullshit made up scenarios?
Am I gonna come up with here that i'm not gonna be real?
I wonder
I can't paint all the ceiling
I'm gonna leave that there. No, i'm not I can't handle that
Karate
Get that looks good
That's a nice wooden room. Ah, fuck. No, it's not done
This room is just bizarrely weird. I just feel like I need to I feel like I come in here
And like sit in the corner and need to be quiet in here
Uh, this is like a weird. I don't know why this reminds me
I don't know. I feel like I need to be like quiet in this room and i'm being like punished
It's like the wooden room. You just have to go in here and be quiet in there. There's a window though. So
rats
Grass coming up
in
My damn it. I can't make the ceiling wood
I can't make the ceiling wood. It doesn't work
Okay. What was this one gonna be?
charcoal
Go to sleep. I'm good. I'm good. Don't worry. I'm gonna wrap it up here in a few minutes
I'm going for about five hours
I'm very tired
But I had a lot of fun. It's fun to come back. Why did I just what the fuck am I doing?
I'm typing in from reddit
It's like
Our reddit. Why is my this is my browser
I got what what? Oh, wow. That'd be great if I had this much fucking money in like firefox
All right, i'm going that's it. That's not it's time
That's so fucking ridiculous
I'm really not even that tired
Yeah, it's time. That's time to call it
I'm because I was looking I was like r
R slow wait, wait, how come my why is it not popping up? Well, I guess i'll just go to the front page
Let me see this clip. What a joke. I'm going for about five hours. I'm very tired
Wrapper
W-r-a-p-p-e-r is what I first typed for about five hours
I'm very tired
Wrapper
What do you mean? What do you mean wrapper?
What?
Wrapper and then uh
Oh, I was talking about wrapping it up
All right. Good. I i'm getting out of here
oh
That's so like embarrassing but whatever I feel like i'm like anesthesia and i'm waking up and saying weird stuff
You guys like recording me on your phone. You're gonna post me to fucking facebook
uh
Anywho, yeah, that's five hours. I haven't had didn't have much sleep. I'm just glad I was able to stream
20,000 dropped frames in five hours
We were stable for a while though
Thank you again everybody for putting up with this
Uh, it can be very frustrating. It's very frustrating for me
But it's something that i'm actively trying to fix
Hopefully it's not too much of a
Pain in the ass for you to watch
But I do appreciate it and I really do
Much love to you
Uh, we don't have I don't think we're very yeah, we don't have very many
Uh bits or anything because so we can do that would be fine
We'll do some more house flipper tomorrow
Starting at the normal time. Hopefully we have a good string of like five hours of stability six seven hours, maybe we'll see
and then let's take a look at the calendar like just
If I can even stream
I hate that I have to do this again, but
Uh, so today's thursday friday. We'll do house flipper
And because i've not been streaming for the last
You know three days in a row here
I'll try just to go four days in a row
You know what I mean? I've
It's we've been off for three days if I can
If it's possible if the internet will let me
So thursday friday saturday sunday
and then
One two, when is my colonoscopy because i'm gonna have to take a couple days off for that
So then we'll do like one two three
I'll take like two or three days off here
We'll figure it out. We'll figure it out, but i'm gonna have to take a day or two off for the colonoscopy. So
the colonoscopy
But anyway, uh, we'll see you guys tomorrow
We will give it a try
Thank you. Uh robaz again for the the raid and the host and everything
Came in here a couple hours ago while we were in the middle of the internet bullshit. So
Sorry, you had to see that
But let us transition out of here
See you all tomorrow
We should have the static ip tomorrow, which maybe it'll help. I don't know willing to try anything
but
a thank you a special thank you to let's go back into the bits
we had a
mermaid
mermaid's slam for the five dolls feels bad to make a joke about your failed goals my failed goals what
What did I do? What were the goals?
Uh, what were my goals?
Thank you for the five dollars though. Uh, thank you also to
kaylor meme amoto for the three dollars
You should move to canada and come have a good hockey team and good internet
Oh, and it'll suit you really well since most of our pizza places have walk-in ovens
I'm really tired. Have I just been talking about pizza since the beginning of the stream?
Was I I don't even remember
Okay
Am I weird am I being weird?
Am I am I a weirdo?
If you have to ask that question
You probably already have the answer
Uh, thanks for the three dollars though
Uh, thank you am
ambix for the 250
This is a whole thing in german. I think
hello my
damon
This is your episode von germa craft
The siri in dear your minecraft
This were episode. Oh, it's okay. Okay. I see what's going on
It's just the first minute of again
Thank you for the uh german translated germa craft
Thank you for the 250 as well freudian weapon. Thanks for 250. He lives
I didn't think you'd be streaming tonight. Thanks for the surprise neither did I but thankfully we could get something in
And have some fun because I had fun
It was fun learning how to cut grass with a weed whacker
Talked a little bit of shit had a little bit of fun
Hopefully you enjoyed it. Thank you for the 250
Uh, thank you halo soft boy for the 260. I don't think that's a straw man. I think that's a real man
Something I said earlier and then they're laughing about it
rapper
Reddit. Oh my god
Autopilot man just on autopilot dr fudge. Thanks for the 15 dollars
Germa, I can't hear the hammer turn it up. I did at some point there. I really actually did
Am I ever gonna get new brb end stream overlays? Yes, blordow is currently working on them right now
in a week or two
Depending on how long it takes them to make it. We're going to have 10 to 12 new songs
for background
When we do the wind down and a wind down animated screen
Something to play in the background. That's not the stream over so there'll be
A large playlist of songs that he has created
For the wind down specifically so there'll be two portions of the end of the stream this one
Which will not have this stream over
It'll be more thought out, you know
And then we'll transition to this one when it's actually time to leave
We have some ideas. He's got a couple of great ideas for
Stuff that happens in the background and the scene and we've been talking back and forth
It's probably going to be pretty great. Don't get rid of the screen songs. You no, no, no
That's going to be added to a circulation
so the intro and outro songs will stay the same but
If I want to I can pump in one of the new ones in random places
I can have two or three lined up. I can change it once in a while
It's just adding not subtracting. So don't worry
So don't worry. It should be fun. Blordow makes
amazing music
He's one of the best when it comes to making
He makes like really great
just chill
relaxing
music
He's got great talent when it comes to making
Like listen to this just listen. This is just like a this is just beautiful
He's got great ambient talent
So there'll be uh, essentially what we talked about is I was like I want a lot more of this
so
We're gonna get more of these low-key ambient tracks
That he is very much known for so
But thank you to dr fudge for the 15 dollars. Really appreciate that
Thank you. Uh three dollars from Leroy. Thank you Leroy
Hey germa, good luck with the colonoscopy. I'm 26 and had to have one of those last year
For my ongoing stomach problems
I really appreciate that you talk openly and without shame
About this kind of stuff makes me feel like less of a weird gross goblin
Anyway, I wish you the best. Hope you get a chance to check out some fire sign theater stuff in the future
yeah, i've
i've been a pretty much an open book when it comes to
illnesses and stuff
I feel like it's
it's just
I have this shit. I have this problem. I have these things that I have to do. I've had it for pretty much over a decade now
So it's like what I like to pretend it doesn't exist
I just want to make sure
That everything is good
Because I have not been
really evaluated
since like
2014 2013
Maybe a little bit later. Maybe 2015 to the point when I have my last real
Evaluation at a sigmoid
Oscopy, which is not the same as a colonoscopy. It's the same thing
But they don't go as far into your intestinal tract. They just kind of go up
Into like the lower half of your colon. They don't go all the way in so yes
You can say they need to go deeper. They do. Yes, they do
And i'm i'm doing i've had kind of some issues recently over the last six months
I don't know if they're related to the colitis and all these other
IBD issues, but I don't know. I just I it was a good idea
He said let's just do it just do the whole thing and let's be certain certain, right?
So, oh that that's happening next week. The prep is the worst. Yeah, that's why i'm gonna have to take
I'm probably gonna have to take like two or three days off
Because you can't eat
A full 24 hours before the procedure you cannot eat food
So I won't really be
I won't have any energy. I'll be tired. I'll be kind of irritable probably
So I don't think I can stream a day before the day of and maybe even the day after depending on how the drugs
Um, I did say I wasn't gonna do any drugs going straight up. No sedation, but depending on the practice
You actually might from my understanding is they might not offer that
I just don't like the idea of going under. I really don't if it's it freaks me out
You should be okay the day after
Yeah, we'll see
I'm definitely gonna do at least the day before and the day of obviously I won't be able to do anything the day of
but
Anesthesia just freaks me out. I've had it done once
I just don't like it. I just don't like the idea. I don't like the whole process
So I already talked to them. I said I either don't want sedation or I want it
Light enough where like very light so
Hopefully I can you know, they actually adhere to that
Yeah, yeah, you know, it's it's a it's a conscious sedation, right?
I've had tons of operations and I just enjoy it now
Yeah, it's I guess something you just kind of will would get used to
but I I think i'm just kind of
Weirdo and I always like to have this weird scenario in my brain
Where it's like
Okay, like here we go
All right. It's time for you to go under. All right, here it comes
Oh here you're gonna feel a little a little pinch in your arm
Okay, and now you're going down. Here we go. All right. We'll see you soon. Have a nice sleep
There's a fire in the building fire and i'm just like there's a fire
I can't do anything
uh, you know what I mean like
Like if fire alarm goes off and you're just like
Was somebody gonna pick you up
You shouldn't overthink things like that. I know but you don't have like
It's the same person that told you that i'm scared of like them finding dna on my bubblegum
Oh, he would maybe some of you guys weren't here earlier
The doctor screamed in my face one time right before I went under what the fuck
What no, that's so bad. That's not really did that really happen?
The last time I was under conscious sedation. I was
I got my wisdom teeth up
And it was really fucked up
It was fucking weird, man
I was lying in the chair and I remember just like
Hearing the same sound
Go and don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't he was playing music on a radio and it was just
I could hear a loop of the last thing that was said it was just like
And it ended and then we we we we we we we did
It was just that I could hear it over and over again
And then I said out loud
Do people say funny things on this and the dentist said stop talking
And then I started laughing and then I that's all I remember
I had my wisdom teeth. Yeah
I hate that. I hate it
I know some people are really into the whole
Oh, man. Yeah, you get a psychedelic man. Like the walls are breathing
No, no, no, no, I want the walls to stay firm and and not collapse and I want them to not breathe at all
I love just sinking down like when I love that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Are we getting kicked off? No, we're good. The walls got him
I'm very I like I need to be very very close to reality
Otherwise, I feel like i've just I would lose my mind
There's a difference between a hallucinogenics and sedation. I know I know i'm but i'm just saying
I don't I would probably hate it
Just because when I get put on a drug
I I like don't want to be on it. So i'm sitting there while I hear like the same sound play 10 times
and like the walls start to move around and I start to put my head back and i'm just like
I I want to go out of here. I want to go home
That's why i'm like, I don't want sedation and they're like you're fucking stupid
But we'll see don't play yourself like that sedation isn't a bad thing. No, I know I know
Just get sedated to deal with the sedation
I'm not nervous about going under but i'm nervous about the idea of being in that loopy state
All the videos out there are people getting their wisdom teeth removed and worry what I might say
Yeah, I don't know man like I might wake up and start saying passwords, you know, like I don't fucking know
I would be the worst person to be on a truth serum. I would just say I would just tell you everything
You'll just save reddit
Reddit
Reddit I want to go to reddit
And I feel like if you sit around and you here's the thing
If i'm sitting there and i'm on those drugs and i'm going to tell myself over and over again
Don't say anything. Don't say anything fucking stupid. Don't say anything crazy. Just be normal. You can do it
You could do this. You can be normal. I feel like the outside perspective is like
I'm not saying anything normal and i'm being insane. I'm not going to start streaming
No, i'm going to be under close supervision
Nope, no cameras are allowed
I ain't having anybody fill me
After i'm coming up
Mm-hmm. I i'm not gonna happen. They're gonna get all my passwords
That would be gold
record
But let's keep going
I've said my piece
But yes, it is is happening next week
Prime opportunity to bump my stocks
Uh, thank you to big buddy. Thank you big buddy for the 10 bucks
Germa flips houses on stream germa old
Flipping houses is kind of like a boomer activity, isn't it?
No, there are some like millennials and zoomers that are into that
They're just not doing it on tv on four different networks
Thank you zach the sloth for the five dollars
Hey germa, i'm sitting outside watching you stream and enjoying the warm weather
When you first made that loud sound with the hammer
I shit my pants and shouted by phone on the pavement, but don't worry. It wasn't your stream's fault. It was my
ass fault
Yeah, I mean it was
Thank you to sticks renegade for the two dollars and 55 cents. Did somebody say 40 bumper stickers?
Yeah, this is yeah, but just everywhere
Bumper stick is the thing he's like about bumper stickers, right?
Bumper stickers, you know, I got one two three
four
At some point they kind of just look like cars zits
I have a hundred
a hundred
Wait, do you did you do you mow? Uh words in the grass?
What is it? What's all is that like a is it are these pokmon?
Is this is this pokmon characters?
pokmon
You got hold on you got your shit like blurred out, right?
Making sure you have like this shit
Never pronounce it that way but pokmon
pokmon
Uh, but this is their car
I i'm gonna i'm gonna see what I recognize on here
I don't think I recognize is that is it five nights at freddy's character?
Is that the fox from five nights at freddy's on the on the top, right?
This sands is on there
Uh
What is the what's the one?
What's the one all the way to the bottom, right?
Is it like a lightning bolt?
You can honestly you can tell a lot about somebody who has car stickers
How do you get those off?
If you peel those off does paint come with it?
You don't
What if you want to sell that car?
I hope they really like five nights at freddy's
What are you selling that car for?
Oh, is it freddy? I love five nights at freddy's
freddy
fred
Somebody will know what that is. Uh, but that's that's a lot of stickers
That's a lot
I want to see your lawn, but thank you for the
Thank you for the
Illinois hog call there you go
Nice job. I'd key your car to be honest. Hey settle down
Hey settle down
Jesus
Uh sticks renegade, thank you. Thank you. Sergel butt for the 250
Jeremiah i've been listening to your stream for about three hours while I was
smithing
Some tools just want to let you know that there is a part of a blacksmithing anvil called a hearty hole
I thought you should know that
Is there?
Look at the people we got in this chat
We have like way to magic the gathering artist a blacksmith
Every five nights at freddy's character on a bumper sticker on somebody's bumper
Some interesting people here and then the rest of doctors and scientists. Yeah, we've already gone over that
But thank you sergel butt
Hopefully made something cool
One true roadie. Thanks for the 10 bucks
Love you jeremy finally sub since i'm financially stable. Thank you for nearly
A decade of great content
Thank you for nearly a decade
of watching
because without you
Watching this stuff. I wouldn't be here
So, thank you and especially thank you the 10 dollars
Really appreciate that. They never said they watched for that long. What?
They said thank you for nearly a decade of content
What do you mean? They didn't tell me how long
They said a decade that's 10 years
Thank you the yellowest for the three dollars and 50 cents. Hey, hey
I'll have to catch the vaude for this one, but I can already tell it's gonna be great here. Take some cash
Just for being you
I'll gladly take it
Thank you so much for giving it to me. Thanks for the 350
Hope you like the vaude. I was pretty tired
Silver flame. Thanks for the 250. Hey germo surveys gave me bits again. Anyways, I met a girl and we hit it off
Our conversation went to streamers
She made a comment about lady streamers. I mentioned how you sometimes don't wear clothes and stream in a bathrobe
Anyway, moral of the story is that she was actually interested in me rambling about you, which is cool
I think she's a keeper. Well, that's all smooches. Enjoy the money. You silly willy
well
What you told her about me is factually correct statements
I do stream
Without clothes on I don't have a camera on but I do sit here
As just me as the day I was born. No, I don't that's a lie
I don't sit here naked. How would I do that?
There's other people that like live in this house
That's kind of weird. No, I don't do that
You fucking imagine how much of a weird motherfucker you have to be
To when I broadcast I just broadcast
Naked
No, I I always i'm pretty much shirtless every moment of the day unless i'm
Driving around somewhere we could go somewhere
Hey after what was that? He's like, hey, we gotta go do it as a joke
uh, but glad to hear that you're
Might be having a potential
uh getting a new
Friendship into a maybe a relationship. I don't know whatever you're doing here
Uh, wish you both luck. Hopefully you guys, uh
Talk about more street if I talk about me some more, you know
I'm a topic of conversation talk about me
But thank you
Uh, thank you too
Uh raslik corgon for the five dolls
Hey jerma, i'm thinking about jumping into the world of streaming even if I get just 10 viewers think it'll be a blast
Any advice you're willing to share?
You are you're already on the right track
Do it because you want to do it because you think it'll be fun
You already got the right, uh mindset so
Give it a try
You got step one
Take sure no
The thing is people ask me advice for streaming
but
I don't know what the fuck i'm doing
At all
I don't even know how to turn the stream on sometimes
We know
No, but in all honestly it
There's no real
There's no real blanket advice that's possible to give
Just because of the nature of the platform it's it's a bunch think about what the platform is right twitch.tv or any streaming platform even youtube
You can add this together
You have
A bunch of people who are all streaming right right now. There's a bunch of oh, well, can you hear me?
Or did we lose?
I think we're good
uh, what I was saying is you have a bunch of people that are doing this sort of thing at the same time
and
trying to
Maneuver your way around and find some kind of audience or some people that would be fun to hang around with or
Some people that you want to stream to
You kind of have to make your own brand right make your own
Um way that you know how
Because there are a lot of ways to do it
You know, are you really good at something like a video game? Are you like top?
10 percentile in a particular game. That's a that's worth watching. Can you do something really fast? That's worth watching
Can you make like jokes do people think that you're funny and that's worth watching right?
There's a lot of avenues that you can go down to start a stream
So what might be right for you or right? What what might be right for me?
Um might not be the same for anybody else because I really don't have a way to
Here's what you need to do step one step two step three because I I don't know. I really don't know
Just try to do something and try to do something that you're good at
And see what happens did this internet kill the stream? No, we were we were teetering around for a little bit
It was still okay
People shouldn't go into something with the brand in mind. No, no, but that's not what I mean by that is
You just kind of have to do whatever you want to do
Most of the people that started doing this just did it because they felt like doing it one day
And it was just I want to make a video. I'm just gonna make it and i'm gonna put it up
Did anybody watch my first five videos no
My first 10 videos, maybe a few
I just kept doing it because I just was having a great time
I was just having a lot of fun
Making a video
And in the initial stages it was it was almost to see if I could even do it in the first place
We all watched germa craft. Yeah, but that was
That was like 50 videos in I knew what I was doing at that point. I had everything figured out
But I wish you the best of luck I
I wish there was more advice I could give
But I don't really have any
If i'm completely honest
Germa craft was the pinnacle. I disagree, but that's okay
You've seen me in the servers
What's the best video you think you ever made? I mean that's kind of
That's very skewed
I made a germa rumble live action was just that's probably the best video and it's like the last video I ever made
Maybe castle griffin steed just like put a lot of time into them
Thought they were a lot of fun to make
I have a lot of videos that I remember very very fondly
What video embarrasses you to think about?
every modern warfare 3 video
I actually uploaded a video that was a 14 and 7
Kill confirmed gameplay and I thought that that was a good I thought that was it at the time
That was okay to upload for me. It was like yeah, this is this is good. I'm gonna I'll upload that
14 and 7 kill confirmed and I thought it was yeah
But this is listen. This is back before let me i'm gonna go off on a little thing here. This is back before
Esports was really took off
And people were really good and all like the best players were coming out and and and being
Noticed and and good gameplay really good gameplay was something that was sought after at that point
This is like 2011 2012
I used to make
Tip videos on how to play the scout
The heart defended your iphone game video saying that you were genuine casual
Yeah, playing iphone games in bed is not the same of
You know what I mean?
but yeah
Being really good at a video game
Really started to take off like just about five years ago
All the esports teams started to really form and started to make teams started to compete
Money real big money started to get involved in competitions
That was like 2012 2013 is when that really started
but
It's an interesting space. We're in it was way earlier than that
Yeah, but
I mean, I don't know because think about like even like youtube
2010 2011
That was like the call of duty youtubers were just starting to really be popular and
Esports hadn't really
Taken off that much online entertainment for video games hadn't really
It was just starting to happen
back in like 2008
2007 2008 2009 you would get your channel deleted if you uploaded video game
footage
Like straight up your channel is terminated
back in like 2000 before like 2010
Somewhere in like the 2005 2006 2007 when they really started to introduce all that stuff
Yeah, they i'm like
I think there was specific cases of people uploading gta 4 footage
And just it just been instantly removed
Yeah, this is but you couldn't even upload videos longer than 10 minutes. Yeah, it was crazy
2010 is the year that online video game media really was starting to take off
Yeah, you used to have to get approved for 15 minute videos
Video responses. Oh, yeah
Yeah
You might think that that's a long time ago. That's not that long ago that really I mean like 2010 2011
That's less than 10 years ago
I mean, it's not like it was like 20 years ago or something. It was really like eight-ish plus years ago almost
You had so much hair back then. I actually had a lot less hair because I had it short
I cut my hair really short
10 years is still a good bit. Yeah, it is
But in this last 10 years, we've seen such a monumental surge
in attention to like the gaming communities the gaming world
I remember when
smite
Had that 2.6 million dollar tournament and i remember being like, holy fuck man. That's
insanity
That's crazy
There was a big dota one four or five years ago. What was the one was like 10 million bucks or something like that 10
8 million
That's when it was really like holy shit
You mean I can I can be I can make millions of dollars doing this
Yeah, when was the first international?
That'll probably give you a good indicator. I remember reading that article of the first international
Yeah, 2011 2010
The international has a price pool of 20 million dollars. Yeah, that's
It's an insane amount of money
Yeah, it's weird 18. It was not an 1800. Remember the gaming at the olympics video you called it
Yeah, people told me I was wrong
Jeremy in quotes always write 9 8 5
I'm gonna i'm gonna shave that into the back of my head
You really did have such a galaxy brain prediction though
Yeah, too bad back in like 2010 2011 2012. I was doing galaxy brain gaming
Community predictions and not like buying bitcoin
Too bad. I didn't have that kind of galaxy brain intuition, huh?
It's always good. It always goes back to crypto
All right, let's uh, we'll move on though
Good talk though. Good good talk. Very good talk. Thank you, too
Uh lobotomized teddy bear for the two dollars and 75 cents
Jerma i'm an intern at the smithsonian. One of my jobs is web maintenance
If you could not possibly crash our site, that would be great
Also do an irl gardening stream. It'd be
more embarrassing
Than me trying to do it in the digital world
I don't think I would be able to do that
I would rather do the get slapshotted by a professional hockey player in goalie equipment
then
Do a gardening stream
But thank you for the 275. Uh, we also had 250 from
Shalashaksha
I fuck up your name every time and i'm really sorry. I have my hardest finals tomorrow. Could you wish me luck?
Good luck
Hopefully you do well on your finals. Hopefully you get some good grades
And then you relax because you earned it, you know, you've earned it. Good luck
Uh velemi gave 50 dollars while we were in the middle of that conversation a little while ago. Thank you velemi
5,000 bits 50 bucks
Thank you for the large large amount of money
Don't forget to chug a few mountain dew throwbacks before the operation
Yeah, I forgot about that. I have like streamer amnesia
No, I can't do it. I I think I can only have jello
And chicken broth for a day and a half
God, that's gonna suck
Yeah, you can't have anything red
I'm one of those people where I lose my mind if I can't eat
I am going to eat
I don't know. Maybe I should just eat
Should I just drink like a banana peanut butter smoothie the day before that like a
4,000 calorie banana
Sludge peanut butter smoothie like the day before I can't eat anything
Should I do that? Maybe that'll like keep me full
Think of the shit. Jeremy, did you eat anything a day or two ago?
Uh, why?
Just did you?
Yeah, I had a 4,000 calorie two full jar of peanut butter smoothie
Oh, well, that's why I can't see anything
It's still going through
He'll find it in there
How do you make a smoothie out of peanut butter? It's a great ingredient
Just swap it in there
just go
Pull it out and into the blender. Thank you for the uh, 50 dollars over lemme much appreciated
Silent serenity. Thanks for the 250 the last time I had anesthesia. I asked my orthodontist if he drove the lambo outside
And then I started rambling about the ass man seinfeld episode
You know what i'm gonna do
I swear to god because you always like pull out something fucking that you just did or you just saw
It's like whatever whatever's like right in your memory at that moment. I'm gonna watch
the day before
24 hours straight of just
Nature documentaries
so
Uh, did you know that the giraffe can reach heights of 29 feet tall? I'm not gonna say anything embarrassing. I'll have knowledge
I think that's a good idea
Turtle sex is gonna come up fuck fuck
Don't say no that's in here now. That's in my brain now. That's in here now
Me saying that and being embarrassed about it is now locked up here in a door
What have you done?
No
I saw turtles having sex. Oh, this is bad
I'm gonna just watch i'm gonna get something else in there
I'll watch like all of like the teenage mutant ninja turtles the whole thing
I'll watch every movie all the whole cartooners. I'm gonna get the whole thing in there
So i'll just say like, yeah, you know, uh, if I know an episode, uh, 2000
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no i'm talking about just like why did I treat i'm tired
i'm talking about
Your mind just combined them. Oh god
This is bad
We talk we talk so much shit. We say so much dumb fucked up stuff. Sometimes just out of nowhere
One of them is gonna pop up
uh
Mr. Otto need to go aside. All right, fine. There's go shade
Uh, let's get the credits rolling
And i'm gonna take auto out. I'll see you guys tomorrow. I still have a couple more bits, but let's run the credits
Thank you everybody
for subscribing
and supporting
this
Broken ass stream the last week straight
I really appreciate it
Hopefully we have a cleaner
internet tomorrow
dropped
only two percent
today
That's okay
That's okay. That's like doable
That's streamable. It's all right double that up and it would be a problem
Otto's yeah, he's just sneezing auto sneezes him when he gets excited
He just starts going
He's just staring at me. Yes. I'm talking about you
Yes, are you gonna sneeze?
Are you gonna sneeze?
Are you gonna sneeze? I'm gonna sneeze anymore
Hey, he did he did ha ha I knew you were gonna sneeze. He's gonna do it again
What are you doing?
Show him. Hey, i'll just show him for a second. Otto
Otto
Can I show him? Hey
Why are you looking so far? Why are you having so much fun?
Why are you having so much fun?
Why are you having so much fun? Let's turn the camera on
And I will point you in his general direction
What why is your dog having so much fun?
Hey
Hey, hey. Hey, what are you doing?
Were you napping in here?
Yes
Look at that tail ready
Hey
What are you doing?
Uh, he's he's my special boy
But thank you everybody for your subscriptions. I'll see you tomorrow. Hopefully we have at least able to start and stream tomorrow
If not, then i'm gonna try whenever I can i'm gonna try to do this is
Fit him wherever it's possible
However, it's possible
Keep an eye on the sus
If something changes last minute, it'll be updated tomorrow
A lot of subs tonight. Thank you guys
And let's finish up the bits. We only have a couple more
Uh, Vilemi gave five dollars again on top of the fifty dollars
Uh, no message on here, but thank you for the fifty five dollars Vilemi. It's a lot of money
Thank you
And then finally, uh
Hugh or hwag. Thanks for the ten dollars a few minutes ago
Thanks for the ten bucks
They say hey jerma, I recently used you as one of my influences for my senior legacy project at school
I put the blood in the box clip in my video presentation and no one left
Well to to think that that video is funny. You have to under I guess you have to like understand
the like loot box craze
that
Streamers and youtubers were really pushing and showing and it was kind of a craze for a year or two
You kind of had to be there, right?
Time to get a new identity
You're just gonna be the blood box guy. Oh, no
Don't worry, like show them like a cool video. Is there a video wherever it like was cool?
Have I made a video where I've ever been cool?
Well, he was like, holy shit. That was fucking that was cool man. What he said
Lifting the weights. Yeah. Oh, absolutely. Show them the chip. No, but why would you do that? That'd be weird
Hey, look at this guy lifting weights on camera. Why would you show people that?
That'd be weird to show if we're just out of context
It's cool though
I've actually thought about this a lot before I don't believe there's any video of jerma's I could show to a friend
Me either
So we can both agree on that
It's cool
All right guys, I will try again tomorrow. We'll see you soon
Thank you for watching
Hope you had a good time. I did
And keep an eye on the sus I will give you an update tomorrow morning tomorrow afternoon again like I did today
I'm gonna get some sleep. I'm gonna get some food. Hopefully it's a pepperoni pizza
It will be a pepperoni pizza because that's probably what i'm gonna order
Have a great night
Take care. See you real soon
Bye. Bye