Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Hitman Absolution!
This game came out literally last night, and I am giddy as a horse on a track.
I don't even know what the context of that actually means, but I cannot wait to play this game.
I've been waiting for this game for so long, and it's finally here.
So, what do you say we start this? Let's play, baby.
Doing it right from scratch. I've never played one second of this game, so this is completely blind, and let's go.
Listen to me. I need you to be...
Alright, so, I think I have completed the tutorial so far.
The lady was just like talking in my ear, so I was like, you know what? We're like gonna just skip right through this.
So, what I've learned so far is how to essentially play the game, and that's good!
So, I'm gonna try... Oh, he's talking.
Accessing mansion. Approaching target.
Alright. So, ask climb down.
I'm doing some... What'd you... I thought I fell.
Oh, boy.
Move on. I gotta see if anyone's in here.
Nope. Move past window. Go!
Move past window again. Go!
This is some James Bond crap here.
Jump up there, baby.
But, yes, I have to kill my old contractor.
So, let's see. Oh, boy.
This place is heavily guarded.
Uh, can I, like, shoot this guy in his face?
Oh, nope. I'm good. I'm good.
Yeah, get out of my... I'm trying to sneak around here.
Yeah, get out of my face. Get out of the window, man.
Why did I do that?
That means I gotta kill this guy now.
Damn it. Alright, we did it.
Yeah, I'll change it.
I gotta put my weapon away.
I gotta drag this guy out of the way.
Come here. I'm gonna hide you behind here.
That was kind of unnecessary, but, you know, whatever.
Can I throw him out the window?
Oh, I think I can dump this guy out the freaking window.
Oh, man. See you later, buddy.
Oh, no. Oh, I gotta do it to this guy, too.
Wait, any guards?
Oh, yeah, holding down control lets you do something called instinct,
which lets you blend in and see kind of through walls.
So, let's dump this guy now, too.
Hey, your friends out there, you wanna go see them?
No, I don't wanna do this. No, please.
Alright, let's be careful here. No, I don't see anybody.
Here's the exit right here. Open.
Okay, can I open the fridge?
Disable security system. Where is it?
Okay, security system's over there.
Gotta disable it so I can kill my target,
Diana Stevenson, whatever her name is.
Evidence.
Perfect. Yeah, my meter on the bottom right,
if you don't know what it is,
instinct, that depletes the more I hold down control.
So, wait, what is this, disguise? Is this a new disguise?
Can I put this on? Oh, I already have that one on.
If you don't know what hitman disguising is,
when you kill people or you knock them out,
you can take their clothing and blend in with places that you belong.
So, it's very, very interesting.
Beyond this door, the rating system will be turned on.
It will monitor your play style and reward your progress.
Ooh, okay.
You can see it in the top left corner.
As always, how you handle your assignment is entirely up to you.
Mmm, good luck. Alright, here we go.
Get key card from head of security.
Look at all those guys.
Whoa, that guy's right there.
That guy's path is up there.
Alright, what is this pot?
Do I, like, have to...
I don't know, I'm scared.
Let's go, man. Get out of this room. I want to poison you.
Ooh.
Oh, God, he's coming over here.
Alright, I'm killing this guy.
Get out of here!
Alright, alright.
I was only asking. Christ.
Don't have a heart attack.
I say, go guard a gate or shoot at some beer can.
The heat should dissolve any hint of foreign substance.
So, wait, I gotta poison this stuff?
Oh, his knife just disappeared. Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, playing ring around the rosie with the chef.
Oh, boy. Ring around the rosie. Oh, boy.
Oh, no.
I killed the chef.
Get over here. Get over here. Come here.
Come here, you fat bastard.
I'm gonna put you in the freezer.
Oh, I'm gonna take his clothes.
I'm gonna be like Chef 47. Here we go.
Is it gonna look so stupid?
Oh, nice.
Oh.
Alright, let's see.
What about my world famous fish dish?
I'm good.
Except for the big pool of blood over here.
I think I'm doing alright right now.
Anything else I can grab over here?
No, I don't have any visible guns.
Let's go through here.
Looking for the head of security is over there.
There he is.
Gotta get his key card.
I'm disguised as the chef.
Wait.
Choice coffee.
Do I gotta poison the coffee?
Fire poker.
Oh, I wanna pick up this fire poker.
Oh, what's upstairs?
Let's go upstairs.
I gotta find poison or something.
Trespassing? What?
Oh, damn.
Oh, hi. Hello there, sir.
Yes, I know. I'm going back downstairs.
Don't worry. I'm just gonna
go downstairs for a second here.
Don't worry about the MasterChef.
Oh, don't you worry about a thing.
Shh. Quiet. Quiet.
Yes. Yes.
Now come with me.
I'll take this disguise from you.
And then I'm gonna dump your ass
into here.
Okay. I need to find a solution.
I could just go guns blazing, but I don't
wanna really do that. I do that way too often
in games. Sleeping pills.
Ooh. Ooh, sleeping pills.
Bang. You know it.
Activate checkpoint. Hell yeah.
Can I take a dump?
No. Alright, so I got these
sleeping pills. I'm gonna put the sleeping pills in the drink.
The guy's gonna fall asleep, and I'm gonna take his money,
his wallet, and the keycard.
Statue bust.
Take the statue.
I don't wanna use this right now.
In fact, I gotta let go of this.
Let's head back downstairs.
This door requires a keycard.
What? Oh, no.
Did that guy have one on him?
Oh, damn it.
That asshole down over here has
a keycard, I think.
Hey, where did I dump your body?
Oh, in here. Excuse me, sir, do you have a card?
No, I don't wanna get in with this guy.
This is weird.
No, I don't wanna do that.
Oh, crap.
How am I gonna get to? Oh, no, no, no.
I can go downstairs. I actually came from down here.
What am I doing here?
I gotta let go of this stupid statue.
Alright, good.
I wanna holster that.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Alright, where's your coffee?
Oh, jeez, I'm bumping into stuff.
Hey, how's your coffee, sir?
Let me just, uh, can I talk to you
about, um, maybe a raise?
Maybe some type of situation
where you and I can discuss my money?
Maybe that would be a good thing.
Turn around, turn around, turn around.
Oh, turn around. Don't worry.
Don't worry about a thing. Don't worry about a thing.
Come drink your coffee. Hey.
Don't drink your damn coffee.
Get his uniform and weapon and send the son of a bitch packing.
What?
I will make sure he spends the rest of his career as a night watchman
at a midwestern corn silo.
I'm gonna just smash this guy, I think.
Let's see.
Is he gonna drink his coffee again? Please go back to your coffee.
There he goes.
That's right. Go drink the coffee.
Coffee is good.
Oh, you don't even know?
I'm just like, no, nothing. Just, uh, itching my nose here.
Don't worry about anything.
How's that coffee?
I bet you it's good.
Where are you going?
Stay sharp, men.
I have urgent business with gate security.
Is he gonna go, like, diarrhea? I hope so.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make sure he gets out okay, fellas.
Don't mind me. I'm just gonna follow him over here.
Oh, wait.
Just did.
How are you guys doing?
Hello there, men. How are you?
I'm a fellow recruit. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay.
Oh, boy. That guy is...
That guy's not liking this at all.
Oh, I'm out of instinct. I can't, like, fool him.
Let me just read a book.
Oh, nice. It worked.
All right. Give me your stuff.
Give me the key card. Give me your pistol.
All right.
All right. Good, good, good. I got the key card.
All right. We're doing good here.
Why did I do that?
That was completely unnecessary.
I just, like, lost points because of that.
God damn it. Why am I such a freak?
I could've, like...
Oh, well. Let's just go.
Why do I have to kill that guy?
What the... Oh!
Now you tell me that.
Oh, by the way, if you do really well and don't kill everybody,
you get more moves.
Thanks for letting me know.
I could've used that advice, like, 30 seconds ago
before I shot that guy in his face.
Entrance located.
All right. Now what?
Closing in on target.
Done 47. Diana brought this on herself.
Oh, she's right there.
She betrayed us, the agency, the code,
everything we stand for.
She is too dangerous to be left alive.
Think about that.
When you pull the trigger.
So, do I gotta... Oh, I'm gonna see some
inner conflict here, guys. Do I kill her
or do I not kill her?
She's right through this door. Should I just open the door?
I guess so.
Oh, boy!
Censored!
This is where we censor
a bunch of stuff.
Hello, Diana. Glad to see you're
taking a shower.
Fully closed, by the way.
Oh, and he does it.
Killed her.
Wait a minute. Get to Victoria.
What is going on here?
Oh, does it?
That's good to know.
Why do I... My guns are just out.
Dude, sun's out, guns out, huh?
Okay, let's go.
I think I'm gonna have to go in like a blaze
of glory here, guys.
I don't think they want me to be stealthy here.
Can he?
Really?
Hold control for instinct.
Press Q to activate point shooting.
Wait, what?
Place a tag?
Oh, dear
goodness.
Oh!
This is some Fallout 3
garbage right here.
Dude, that was...
That was sick!
I should have just done that to the whole
room down here.
Oh, wow, that was cool.
That was really cool.
I just killed four dudes in one shot.
That was really cool. I just killed four dudes in one second.
Hell freaking yeah.
Oh, so this is like
the daughter or something? I have no idea.
Don't worry, you can come with me.
I will protect you. I'm 47.
Good to meet you.
Sonny in here.
His mouth just moved and he didn't talk.
What was that?
She's dead.
Gonna bring you to somewhere safe.
Bitch.
Alright.
Reduce recoil when firing weapons.
Not too bad.
I mean, I got spotted once.
I killed a civilian apparently.
I killed three dudes.
Well, it made me kill three guys, didn't it?
Complete objective. Body hidden.
Evidence removed. Silent kill.
Head shot. I did okay.
I mean, not fantastic, but
for a blind run.
Cool, cool, cool. Alright, well
I guess that concludes episode one
of this quasi
playthrough of Hitman Absolution.
Stay tuned for episode two when
me and this weird girl go
solve crimes together. I don't even know.
But I'll see you guys all soon. Stay tuned for next episode
and take care, everybody.