Hello, my constituents. Welcome to Favour the King. It is I,
Gerber985, your king, your ruler. And I just have one thing to say, bonjour. Can we get a
bunch of bonjours in the chat, please? Look at the fireworks. What a glorious day it is for
favouring your king. Those of you that don't know how this is going to work,
uh, this one's actually gonna work. Last time we did this, it was a little bit of a problem.
This server is fucking clean. Yes, it's not, it is not the other one. It is not the F word.
Somebody just threw me an emerald. People throwing me jewels? I don't want to get rid of this.
Of course you would send jewels to your king. What am I speaking of?
What are you getting? The snowballs. There's no snow on this map. How many people are in here?
10,000? Is it 8,000 people in this game right now? Something like that. But we have some events to
do. We have a lot of things to do today. I ain't just going to run around and let you shoot me
with arrows. Not like last time. Wait, there is snow. Oh, there is. Yeah, there is. There's snow
here. You're right. Like that. I don't know. That's not enough snow to make snowballs.
There's 10,000 people here. There's not enough 10,000. There's not 10,000 people worth of
snowballs over there. Anyways, the first thing we're going to do is it's going to be a fucking
shit show. You can guarantee yourself that. By the way, welcome to Minecon, right? It's Minecraft
Day. Didn't mean to do that at all, actually. That was just an actual coincidence. I had no
fucking idea that today was like Minecraft Day. Remember, we were supposed to do this like two,
three weeks ago. This got... Is that your dog? Otto? He was like, let me in. All right, the first
thing we're going to do, we're going to kick this off. This is going to be a mess. The first thing
that I need to tell you is if you get in this game, you have 10 lives. Once you die 10 times,
you're out and you have to re-queue. So try not to die. It's going to be kind of hard.
During the course of the next few hours, you're going to see plenty of death. Not from each other
either. We'll see. It's a lag. Here comes the lag for so many people in the same spot. Holy shit.
It's handling it though. It's actually handling it. Everybody said, nice stream, idiot. It's client
lag. It's because the game was never supposed to allow you to have 5 million people in the same
spot. But anyway, nice fucking stream. Honk, honk. All right. Anyways, the first thing we're going to
do, let's get the first thing started. Everybody in the server... By the way, if you want to play,
it's Jermaf.tk in the Minecraft client. You got to have Java. Java client, not the Windows client,
not the Switch client. Got to be the Java client. And once you do that, you'll be put into a queue.
When somebody dies in this server in this game, they'll be knocked out. You'll take their place.
So let's get started. You get 10 lives. I wish you all well. The first thing we're going to do
is build. What the fuck was that? I didn't do that. I didn't do that. I mean, I can do that.
I have this thing. I'm going to get a good look at this. What version? 1.8.8 through 1.16. You
can join any of those. Who's driving the ice cream truck in the background? I can do that.
Can I? I think my stick of lightning is broken. I can no longer cast lightning. Lightning just
strikes randomly in the fucking server. All right. So the first thing we're going to do,
we're going to build. Everyone's going to get blocks in their inventory.
You're only going to get 10 blocks. You all have to make a statue of your king.
If you place a block, it's there forever. You cannot have them be destroyed. They cannot be
picked back up. You want to build me a statue. Forget about the lightning.
Why is it the flag of Italy? That's like the Aquafresh logo. What are you talking about?
Italy. All right. Are we ready? Are we ready to start? Are we confirmed that we're ready to
begin the build process where you have to build me a statue? Work together.
Please, your king. Please. For the love of God. Minecraft sucks. Don't say that on Minecraft day.
You guys ready? I'm going to fly away for a second. Here comes the build. Here's the thing.
If you guys make anything that's phallic shaped, it's getting deleted. I'll just delete it. I'll
just delete it. Are you supposed to build with all the client lag? I don't know. Good luck.
Why is this pre-recorded? It's not. I'm right here, dude. It looks like mafia graphics.
Yeah. From my perspective, it's going to be lagging, but not from other perspectives. Don't
worry. This is like 10 FPS. Yeah, it is because we're capturing it through something else. But
my perspective doesn't matter. We're going to switch. Don't worry. Don't worry. Am I hosting
the server? No. Wait, what? I am not hosting the server. Am I like garage? Everything is lagging.
Well, don't worry. Once we do the actual events and we let the server rest, it's going to be fine.
Did I get a better computer? Oh, this is running over the course of,
I think there's like 10 servers. I think there's like 15 servers this is running on right now.
Grab a Scott burger? Yes. I haven't had it yet, but what is it? Lettuce, tomato,
ketchup, mustard, mushrooms, onions, ketchup, mustard, and bacon. Something like that.
I see a five. My five is not the problem. It's running at two frames per second. Oh, that's
weird. All right. We have a solution. We have a solution. Hey, look at me. Welcome to technical
difficulties. We're going to, we have to restart the server and it'll be fixed when we restart it.
We have to cut the player count by like a hundred people. All right, let's go. Turn it off. Put us
on the BRB screen. We'll be right back. Hey, last time we started the stream two hours late,
I was here on time at 301 with technical difficulties. Just cut it. We'll be back in
10 seconds. I was two and a half hours late last FTK. It's only been 15 minutes. Everybody
chill in your seats and relax. We'll be back in 10 minutes. Hey dude, is it your VPN? No,
no, that was a joke. Hi. Hi everybody. Hey, how's everybody doing? It's me, laggy. Somebody said,
and I will give you this. I'll give you credit. Somebody said, bod watchers skip 30 minutes. Yeah.
All right. You sure you get it. You get that one. I hadn't even been 30 minutes yet though.
Okay. So I think we are ready to start. Keep in mind the first person view for me or inventory
purposes is going to be, it's a lower frame rate. Everything else should not be. Yes. You know what?
Just skip 10 minutes. If you get involved right now, just go 10 minutes from now. You'll look,
you'll see it. You'll be happy. You should have listened to that one guy like 25 minutes ago. He
was right. All right. Everybody's going to get blocks placed in their inventory and you are going
to be looking at it. It says, look at how clean this is. You're in a windows destruction. Everybody
has blocks in the inventory. I want a statue. I want a statue built of me. Place those blocks.
They do not come up when you place them. So don't fuck it up. Here. Look, I'll get you started.
Oh shit. I can't. Can I put, can I pick that back up? Look, I'll start it.
Watch out for the flowers. They can't be, the flowers can't be removed. All right. Go. You only
get 10. Why would you go straight up, dude? The stream is in 1080p. Nice 2008 YouTube video.
This just looks like a level in like Super Mario sunshine. This is not a statue. This is,
why does this guy have dirt? Unregistered hyper cam. This is not a statue. You guys got it all
wrong. What? Whoa. That's actually pretty sick. Wow. That's actually kind of good.
Uh, this is supposed to be a statue of me, not what it feels like to step on a Lego
water. I just spit, I spit fucking water everywhere right there. I spit out so much.
You're a pause to buffer. What? What do you mean pause? How's that? Is that, is that better? Oh
shit. Be careful. You can die. You can die. You can die. I can hear the CPU fans from here.
Yeah. It's all what you're seeing is, is what happens when hundreds of people are in the same
spot. It's all client side lag that it will even out once we do the next couple of events. Don't
worry. Such dog shit. People are just writing fuck. I don't know. Let me, let me, let me,
I gotta be honest with you. I don't know why I want so badly to be have like a collaborative
statue build. This is the kind of shit that those little weird guys used to make in Fraggle Rock.
This is not even like a statue. Oh, I want to build a statue. That's never going to fucking
happen with like hundreds of people in the same place ever. This is absolutely dream fixed.
Oh, we got a POG moment here. It's fixed. Look at that. All right. Keep going.
Everybody said, Hey, dog shit stream. Hey, whatever. What would it say? We're good. We're
good. We're good. Look at this. We're good. Hey, I told you it was going to take 30 minutes. I told
you everybody, everybody. Why is somebody started fire? This is not going to work. The build section
is going to be stupid. Like it was always going to be stupid. Somebody started. I'm just trying
to burn it down now. Wait, actually are you making arms? Oh shit. You actually are making arms.
How do we stop them? Well, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that. I did. It's burning.
I don't know. Okay. In my dreams last night, I was lying there going like, oh man, they're
going to build when people work together, like Twitch plays Pokemon, Twitch plays the carnival
make a statue. Yeah. And I could see the arms being built in the head and the face.
They're probably going to do like a funny like face. No, this is just a series of lines up and
down and I keep striking it with lightning. That's too wishful thinking. Yeah. Expectation versus
reality. Like you, I'm going to, I'm going to cut, I'm going to call this in about two minutes.
I'm going to move on to event number two out of like 30. Oh, I got to change. How do I turn
clouds off? All right. Clouds off. All right. So let me get a good view of this. Nice. Yeah,
just good. Very good. It's just that this is not what I thought. Well, this is not what I saw in
my dream. Can somebody please build like, hold on. We, somebody's got, we got something going on up
here. Good statue of just cobblestone. This is, this is a randomly generated structure.
Like Google AI from 1998 made this and it was astonishing back in the late 90s. Like,
holy shit. Did you see what Google AI 2000 just did? I want everyone to be very aware of something.
This is the warmup. This is the warmup. The first two little events here are a very small warmup
just to get the server running and everything's gone. You ain't seen nothing yet. Don't be
fucking worried. Yeah. All right. I think, I think it's time to call the statue here. I mean,
this is, this look, this is terrible. Don't you feel like you're going to drop a coin in
the top of this thing and it's going to be a cool display to see where it goes. And then you get the
gumball at the end. I mean, that's kind of cool. I guess I don't know what people are getting lava.
Where are people getting lava and water? How does somebody already have lava? Server's been
off for like five seconds. Wait, somebody wrote the word ass when he said cock. All right. I have
to turn off the chat for me. I got to turn that off. Where does it turn it off? It's just a bucket.
All right. What's, what does it say? This is on fire. This is pretty cool. Not a statue,
but it's just pain. Okay. I see. So far so good. Dude, you're standing in there.
I even hurt people with my stick of absolute lightning.
All right. That's pretty good. You guys want to move on to the second, second event.
You've made it a great, a great thing here. Oh, it's done. It's done. It's over. It's done.
This statue is done. Otto smile. I guess the kind of is like a face down here. It's one of those
like Mario mushrooms up there. All right. I would like everybody to follow me. Thank you
for participating in the build event. Why do I think I could go through the fucking front door?
Thanks for participating in the build event, everybody. That was really fun. We're going to
move on now to the second event here, which is going to be a POG event. You can follow me,
everybody. Everyone in the server, please. We're going to go over to the Coliseum and we're going
to start the tournament. It's going to be a tournament between people in here heading over
to the Coliseum. It's a POGChamp event. You're free to say POGChamp if you want to. Follow me
to the Coliseum. Otto, you want to go inside? He's like, let me in, let me out, let me in,
let me out. Take a look at this. Who are going to enter one at a time, you will fight to the death.
Those of you that remain will be tiered based on how many people you've killed. And don't even
try to go down here because you can't. You can. You can't. You cannot. There you go. Don't even
try. You can't. I really wonder how this is going to play out. I don't think this is going to play
the way that we think it is. So two enter. Wait, people can just jump up? You can't go in though.
Good luck. It's just a glass ceiling. No, the tournament's not just everybody go in here and
just start killing each other. That's not the tournament. He's training. Wait, somebody's dead.
Wait, what? No, it's the tournament. Don't kill each other. Why are people on fire? This is the
tournament. If you die 10 times, by the way, you're fucking out of here. I need to make that very
clear. If you type slash duel, you are going to be queued up to be participating down there. It looks
like we got somebody already there. Who's there? I can't even see their name. I'm going to queue up
and fight this guy. Is he fighting anybody? Is somebody else even down there? Dick Daschle
Richard versus who? Wait, why are we all flying blocks? Who is he fighting? There's no one. Oh,
wait, here we go. Yep. Okay. Okay. Okay. Here we go. Let's go. Come on. Dick Daschle Richard
versus 847. I don't know. That's not what the fuck that number is. Are they fighting? All right.
You guys got to fight. Fight to the death. Let's go. I guess what if they just don't fight?
This guy has a sword. Well, why did you queue up for the duel if you didn't have anything to
fight with? I think he's going to win. Does this guy have armor too? Why does this guy have armor?
Who's he fighting at? Why is he swinging at us? He thought he was going to be supplied. Oh,
wait, there's people spawning. Where did this guy come from? Can't join. Can't join. Well,
the server's probably full right now. No one can connect to the server. It's probably because
it's full, right? Why are we all ghosts? Wait, hold on. Peter Griffin just saved the stream
because he showed up. People being kicked? Why are we all like floating around as ghosts? Hold
on. I'll tell him I should go outside. One sec. Come here. No, wait, the server's down.
Connection lost. Oh shit. The whole thing is down. Wait, is it actual next duel? This is the most
interesting thing I've ever seen. Why is everybody's heads just floating around as ghosts? I don't
remember seeing this before. This is insane. It's just spectator mode. Oh, okay. Oh, I'm getting
something in my ear. All right, so there's too many people in spectator mode, which is crashing
the whole client. All right, let's just move on to the main event. No more stalling. Let's move on
to the main event. Let's do the main event. The main event is going to take like three hours,
and none of this shit will happen in the main event. I just wanted to give some padding.
There was supposed to be a little tournament, but there's 50 trillion people here.
Worse than Bugleberry. Yeah, it's all right. Yeah, it is. It's worse. That's fine. We wanted to fight.
Hello. Hi. Welcome back. Okay, if a stream is the worst stream of 2020, guaranteed,
we can remove it from the list, right? Like everything else is an honorable mention at this
point, right? Like this could just sit as like the worst stream of 2020. And then, you know,
we can vote on another one. That's fair, right? That's fair. That's fair, right?
No, we all agree. All right, I agree. We all agree. So what's the point of having to vote for it?
It's already stamped it. Throw it up. All right, here we go. We are going to move on.
We're going to try to do the actual main event of this stream. Oh, no. It's dead.
I'm going to put in Rattatouille quick. Should I open up the Rattatouille level?
I just, I can't. I'm not even streaming. Did you believe that? Emergency Rattatouille stream
incoming. Imagine, imagine the FTK stream becomes emergency Rattatouille stream.
Holy shit. That might be the most ridiculous thing ever. All right, we're going to try this again.
There's so much cool shit in this. There's so much. It's so much cool shit in this. You have
no idea, guys. We just wait. You got to see it. All right, we just have to see it. It's fucking
awesome. All right, we just got to get there. Do another Diablo 2 playthrough. Okay. Yeah,
maybe. All right, I'm in. Are we, are we good to go? Are we good to try? Go play Genshin Impact.
I don't even know what that is, but maybe. No, don't. You just said two words back to back.
I don't even know what they were. You said Genshin and then Impact. Please do, please do. I don't
even know what it is. It's a gotcha game. I don't know what it is. I don't know. Does somebody have
this up? Does that, does your skin say stream sucks? Oh, no. Germa sucks. Okay. All right. Hey,
we're going to try to do this. We're going to try to start this. Everybody pretend to be excited.
Everybody pretend to be floored by this coming up. All right. You ready? We're going to act.
This is acting class 101. Whoa, what the hell? Whoa, there's a dragon. Quick to the battlements.
Get yourselves a bow and arrow and some kind of, we're being attacked. The tournament has been
interrupted by a dragon. Hurry to the armaments. My inventory is full of dog shit. I don't want
any of this stuff. I need a bow and arrow. Oh, you can. We have to, we have to defeat this dragon.
Quickly to your king. Why do I have apples in my fucking. Apples and shit. Throwing snowballs.
This is the Argent tournament. Wow. Reference. Shut up. This is a lot of time.
All right, let's go. I got my bow and arrow. I need arrows. I need to actually need an arrow.
You only need one arrow. It's a magical bow.
Kill him. Excellent work. Excellent work. Watch out for the boss. Oh, shoot. He's killed like five
people. All right, we did it. Victory. The dragon has gone into hiding. Would you look at that? What
a surprise that would have been if it happened in the middle of a fucking tournament. Holy shit,
a lot of people died. Look at all this stuff on the ground. Jesus Christ. All right, here we go.
Wait, let's, let's go back to the town. What do you say? You guys think, let's go, let's go back.
Let's go back to the town. Let's get, let's, let's get this shit figured out.
That dragon just attacked the town. Tournamental. Oh, I sense something strange. I don't know about
any of you guys, but I, I sense something strange happening in the air. Real tragedy. What? All right,
let's head back. Anybody else sense something? Especially potentially somebody on the production
staff might sense where direction I should be heading. I don't know where it is. Where is it?
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where's the thing that I have to touch?
My dream. I was like sleeping going, oh wow. The dragon attacks and there's a statue and wow.
Hey, where's this thing that I have to touch guy on production staff? Help me. That didn't happen in
my dream last night for this game. Where, where actually is it though? This is okay. Okay. When
you're like a little kid and you, in your mind, you have this elaborate thing play out the way
that you're talking the way. Whoa, wait, hold on. What's that? Hey fellas, fellas, I found it.
Hey fellas, I found it. What's this over here? There's a cave system over here. Look out. The
dragon escaped. Come back to the Coliseum and check it out. Something happened here. Why is
everybody listening to me? The only person over here. I'm just playing it alone. Is anybody
listening? Oh, oh, oh my chest. That's so sad, but funny at the same time. No one's listening to me.
Oh, we are here for Steve. I see people. I see people. Wait, I gotta go in. I want experiences
too. I want to see this. I'm on fire. Why am I in fire? How do I put myself out? I'm on fire.
All right, boys. I'm on fire. All right, everybody quick into the, into the portal.
Okay. What I was going to say is you know, when you're like a little kid and you inside of your
head, when you're like 10, 11, 12 years old and you just see and hear this elaborate thing that
you're making up, like you have a dragon flying by in your head and you're fighting with a sword
outside. It's like recess or whatever. And it's like real life out there. That's how I felt it
was going to be. But like in reality, when like the teachers look out the window to recess, they
see like two like little shits just like moving around in circles, going like dragon. Look out
for the dragon. But in their head, it's like a fucking movie. That's how I felt today.
Anyways, welcome. Uh, we're in some kind of dungeon right now. I think we need to
find our way out of this fucking dungeon. We need to go find the king's sword.
I can't even, we're on an RP right now. Find the king's sword at recess. Everybody in.
You got to get it one at a time. Not too many people go in the hot tub. Be careful. You can
die in here. This actually is dangerous in here. Be careful. We got to make our way and find the
king's sword. Careful. Careful. What the hell? What, what the hell is that? All right. There's
like a super creeper over here. Kill it. It's like Harry Potter. It's the creeper king.
Oh shit. Fuck that. Is this the new update? No, no, it's not. No, it's not. This is Minecraft
1.8.9. Someone feed in the pool. Kill this thing. Wait, can we hurt this thing? He's kind of just
looking at people. It's going to explode. The pool is closed. No, the pool is open. You just
got to go in it. Oh no, I see what's happening. People are killing each other. This guy has a
weapon. Don't fight each other. Fight the creeper king. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're supposed to be working together. Did anybody even hurt him? Is he just an NPC for fun? I think
he's invincible. Do we need to do anything in particular? Do we need to like dump like water
on him or something? People are trying to leave. I think we have to kill this thing. How do we kill
it? Oh shit, he's on fire. Wait, wait, wait. Shoot him with arrows. He's not even trying to hurt
anybody. I think I just headshot somebody and killed them. Well, what was that? Where the
explosion? I can't even tell if we're hurting him. This guy just lives here. We're just like
fucking up his whole house. I think there's explosions too. Oh, I think we have to hit the
bottom part. Hit the bottom part? Where is he? He kind of blends in with people that have diamond
armor on. Wait, there's two of them. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There are two of these guys?
What? This guy's bigger. Oh shit. Oh my God. I'm going to die. Oh fuck. All right. I'm going
this way. Who's like a friend or foe? Shit. I'm sorry. What that was? I literally just headshot
somebody and killed him. How much health does he have? RDM. There's so many arrows everywhere too.
This is fucking ridiculous. No one snowballs at him. That's not going to work. Is he dead?
I'm going to die in a second. I'm dead. Oh shit. Why do I have 10 lives? I'm supposed to have a
thousand. Oh my fucking God. This stuff all over the floor. I don't even know what I picked up.
What happened? I'm naked. Do I still? Oh shit. Is he spawned? No, I don't. Nine lives. That's not
I'm flying around. Shit. Someone has my lightning stick. Oh fuck they do. Somebody has the stick.
That's why. That's what lightning strikes are. Somebody took it. All right. I died.
I can put, I can turn on God mode, but I don't think I need it. How much? Hey,
how much health mods? Somebody said somebody has this sound way up. How do we kill this guy?
Why is there an Enderman in here? Does anybody have a weapon I can borrow? Why don't I have a
fucking weapon? Do it louder please. Is there, is there audio to turn down? There we go. Do we
know how much health this guy has? I feel like we're playing Destiny. Destiny 3. Shit. I died
again. I'm killing this motherfucker right now. How do I do it? I'm in God mode. Let's kill this
motherfucker. I'm going to hit him up. Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill. I can't PvP here.
No phase. I can't, I can't even hurt him. Fix the Q. Is the Q server fucked up? Yes it is.
Uh, they're saying the Q server is fucked up. Game server's all right. You can TP to people? You
can. All right. How do we instantly kill this guy? How do we kill this thing? We're just like
bullying this fucking creeper. German, just swallow your pride and play Ratatouille.
Look, it works. We're in. Well, I'm staying. How did everybody get all this diamond armor?
All right. Let's move. He's dead. He's been killed. We got to go through this through here.
I'd kill all. Where's the next room? Oh, it's all the way back here. Am I looking the right way?
I actually can't believe this many people are in here right now. So all the way to the back wall
here. Oh, here we go. All right. Follow me in next room. We're going to find that sword.
Wait, easy, easy. Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow. Don't go so fast.
I can't see anything. There's too many people. It's a giant maze. There's too many people in here.
There's too many. I'm fucking claustrophobic right now. I actually kind of like it. You can't
break it. We've got to, somebody's got to find the exit. It's a maze. All right. Split up, split up.
Don't all go the same way. We have to split up. Is there a fucking, is there an enderman in here too?
All right. Split up, split up. We've got to find the exit. Does somebody have an enderman skin?
All right. Good. Progress, progress, progress. I see name plates everywhere. Good. Spread out,
spread as far out as you can. That way? No? Let's go this way. Why am I seeing omega lulls right now?
Why is everybody laughing? I see omega lull, omega lull, omega lull, omega lull.
Really? You put a maze in here? You're insane. I think there's like a couple. Good luck. Yeah,
it's not nothing. This is some fucking hard shit here. All right. We have to be getting close to
the end. I hear the enderman. I feel like we're making really good progress. Ice cream Hong Kong.
Yeah. All right. I've watched Beetlejuice too. It was a funny movie. Oh, wait. There's a bottleneck
here. One at a time. Progress towards what? Towards, we get towards the exit. We're going
to go through the dungeon. How far, how, how much progress have we made? Anybody on production want
to tell me? Curious, I wonder. Black Friday POV. Get in there. I got to get a new Wii.
How, how far are we? Oh, we're, we're good. We're, we're halfway, like almost halfway there.
Oh, I told you splitting up was a good idea. Oh, I, I just turned around. I got turned around.
Wait, am I going the wrong way? Oh shit. Wait, where? I was going the right way,
but then I got turned around. I have no idea. Oh, stop whispering me that shit. All right.
Time to ban that person. Q server limits 400 right now. Could be a lot more than that.
Is this the wrong way? Oh shit. Hold on. Guys, we're going the wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong,
wrong, wrong, wrong. Turn around. Yeah. If you're not in the maze, by the way, guys,
if you're not in this current room, if you, if you type slash die, you're going to lose a life,
but you will end up at the beginning of the maze. So if you're all the way back and like,
oh shit, I can't fucking go anywhere. You do slash die. You will end up at the beginning
of the maze. Shit. All right. I got to pay attention. Am I going with this? People are
walking forward backwards. Oh fuck. Is anybody, is anybody close? Once somebody beats it, we all
win. This way, this way, this way. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Go, go, go, go, go. I'm so close.
Keep going. Yeah. Yeah. Shit. I thought the turn, I'm turning chat off like fucking Wally. All
right. I got to turn this off. Somebody said that. Why did I read that shit? God damn it.
All right. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Turn around. I feel like we're just ants.
Isn't this how ants work? One ant picks the direction and lays down like ant fluid and
all the other ants follow the ant fluid. Who's the lead ant right now? Somebody has to be lead ant.
All right. Why don't you take over lead ant? It's not going to be me. Somebody take over. I'm going
to bless one of you. All right. I can't see. How about, all right. Scales. Scales 7744.
Wow. That's the new lead ant. Everybody follow him. He's got like a green t-shirt and jeans on.
Follow a guy with the green shirt on. You know where you're going? Is somebody there?
Did somebody do it? Oh, they, somebody got, somebody got really close and then they,
they turned around and got fucked up. Shit. Oh my God. All right. This way.
I don't even know if I'm going the right direction or not. I think we just want to circle.
Oh my God. Okay. Over here and then right. Yep. Right here. Okay. And then, and then this way
and then left. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Follow Tingy. Tingy's got it. Tingy's got it.
Welcome to, by the way, welcome to Minecraft day, everybody. Didn't know that was today.
Minecon 2020. Oh no. I just got, I just got word in my ear, guys, that we are going the 100%
wrong direction. We turned around and went the wrong way. We're running backwards now.
Uh, not going the right way at all. Back this way. All right. I'm going to give this 10 more
minutes, five more minutes before I start taking balls down. Holy shit. That guy's huge. What
happened to the one guy that was almost done? See, is he still getting close? Is everybody just
hopelessly lost? This is just a way to keep us busy. Somebody said career ending stream.
Oh, whatever. That was a good run. Sir, you are fired. That's all right. It was pretty good.
It was pretty fun. He's talking about me. All right. I'm taking balls down. I'm taking balls
down. I want to go to the next room. I want to go, I don't want to do this anymore. I want to go to
the next room. How do I do this? Too hard. I don't know where we're going. Nobody knows where they're
going. Okay. So I'm just going to start taking walls down. I don't have a pickaxe. What? I need
a pickaxe. Somebody give me a pickaxe. I can't break walls. Can I actually not cheat? Oh shit.
All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Hopefully I'm facing the
right direction. Oh shit. I fell through the world. Oh no. Please tell me you can see this.
I'm killing everybody. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No. No. I'm sorry. I tried. I tried. I killed like 10
people. 20 people at least just died. All right. Don't look at the ground and hit the ground.
All right. Wait. I made it to the end of the maze. I made it to the end of the maze guys.
I did it. Pog. Look. Oh shit. Hold on. I gotta change this. All right. Come on in. Look where I
am. Hey. I made it to the end of the maze guys. Is anybody even close? Nobody's even remotely
close. Why is somebody on top? All right. If you hit slash die, you're going to come to me.
Put it on easy mode. Yeah. I kind of did, didn't I? What's the next room? There's a bear in here.
All right. Careful. Careful. Careful. Careful. This is a jumping map. The queue thinks that
there's four. Well, there is only 400 people in the server. How the queue system works is it pulls
you in when somebody else here dies. You'll be in the queue until somebody here is gone. At least
that's how it's kind of supposed to work. Oh, there goes somebody. Okay. Okay. This is a jump
map. Be careful. Let us out. There's only two. Oh, the server. Okay. Right. The server thinks
there's 400 people. I see. I see what you're saying. So the server, the queue server still
thinks there's 400 people. So it's booting people because it thinks there's supposed to be 400 in
here, but there's only 250 from the kind of extreme thing we had to do at the very beginning
of this room. All right. Let me turn this off. How are you guys even making these jumps in the
first place? I can't even see to make the first jump. Nobody's already doing very well. How can
you even see this first jump? Hold on. People are falling, but not dying. You can climb back up.
Okay. This guy is seriously, he's beating the whole thing. How are you this good at this?
Half of us can't even get past the first jump. Are you fucking kidding me? Did this guy beat it
already? Wow. Look at this guy go. Did you just beat it? He's going to sit here and taunt us.
Hold on. Let me, let me, let me, I want to get a good view of this. How do I do that? I'm actually
really surprised that he was able to do that. He's the real king. Yeah. Well, no, I'm the real king,
but he can be the one that's on camera because he's doing something interesting instead of just
falling off the same first jump. You can tell where the bottleneck is because where every single
person is here. There's a major bottleneck at this jump here. It's just inside people's heads.
All right. You got to jump to get a good view. I'm afraid if I walk forward, I'm going to die.
Okay. I'm good. He could just sit here and taunt us. What's that? What's that command to make it so
you can't see anybody but you? Oh, that didn't work. Slash hide. Oh, one word. Oh shit. This is
way easier. I can actually see what the hell I'm doing. Oh, this is awesome. This is cool.
Just cut away from me. Cut away from me. Cut away from me. Cut away from me. I don't want
anyone to see anything that I'm doing. Fucking give me a break. I can't. How do you get that
first one there? People are making pretty good progress though. I got it. I got it. I'm good.
Got it. Are they throwing shit at me? All right. I'm good here. There's a lava portion. How many
people are at the lava portion? Oh, fuck. It's okay. It's all right. I'm good. No. What happened?
He didn't make it in the water. He didn't make it. I'm trying to win. I don't even know. I can't
see what you guys are looking at. I'm going to try to jump. Am I going the... I don't know
if I'm going the right way. This looks right. Oh shit. How do I jump on this? What? Oh, he fell.
He fell at the cactus. No. Really? That's too bad. I don't understand this jump here. I kind
of want to turn... Okay. I'm going to turn my shit back on because I can't tell what to do here.
Hide all, right? So how do you jump around this? Oh, you have to go down. Oh shit. Okay. What? No,
you don't? Well, you have to grab the ladder. Shit. Okay. I wasn't paying attention to that.
Oh my fucking God. Whatever. These are all the rejects down here. Oh, damn it. He didn't sprint.
Oh, somebody said they just got banned. Well, what did you do? Is there any... He's going to
the end? Is there any way we can make the server queue system be actually 250 and not 400? Because
what's happening is it's getting to... Someone's going to be being allowed to be let in, but it's
immediately booting them because the server thinks that there's supposed to be 400 slots.
I don't know if they can look into that somehow. Did it? You actually did it.
Who did it? Which one? They deserve a gold helmet for that. Isn't LNV... LNV-42. Where are you?
You... This is what you get for completing the mission. LNV-42. Yeah, are they...
TP me to LNV-42. Oh, they're right behind me. Oh, there you are. Here, take this gold helmet. You
deserve it. You get it? Nice job. Congratulations. You completed the jumping map. Somebody has two
lives left. Well, be careful. All right, let's keep going. Let's continue. Follow me. Is this a
maze? Wait, is this just a long... Remember, if you have lives remaining, hit slash die and you will
start at the beginning. This is a maze again. Yeah, this is a maze. This one looks easier,
though. Take that, though. All right. I mean, why wouldn't I? Don't open. Why not? I do hide all
again. Yeah, those of you that can... You guys listening for the server side of stuff, can
somebody look into the whole queue thing because I think people are actually getting just booted
just by being brought in. Okay, cool. I don't want to hide all players, though, because then I can't
cheat and follow somebody. Redstone? Everybody... Why is everybody saying, holy shit? This is an
algorithm maze? Is everybody saying this is going to take hours? No, the other one took like 10
minutes for someone to get to the end. Pressure plates, too. I don't know. What do they do?
I see name tags. Shit, we were already here. This is wrong. I remember this is the diamond.
That's where I got the diamond. Shit. This way? Everyone wants to get TP to the end of the parkour
course, say in chat. Well, if you want to... Wait, why can I see you? Wait, did I beat it? Oh, no.
Shit, this is the beginning of the level. This is the very beginning of the game. I went all the way
in the back. I went all the way back. Okay, I'll get it. Here we go. If you do slash die, you will
appear right at the beginning of the maze. This way. There's the diamond. I'm going to make some
Hansel and Gretel shit here, okay? Yes, I can. Nope, this way. This is going to last six hours.
No, it won't. I have the magic of the fucking staff. I can just break through a wall if I want.
Okay, yeah, they're working on the queue thing right now. That's what they're telling me.
Yeah, people can still come in, but there's just a problem with the actual number. It's running into
itself, essentially. They're trying to figure it out. Stop cheating. I'm just collecting samples.
All right. How did I go the wrong way? Here, come this way. I know I just fucking cheated,
but it's all right. Well, how did you guys do that? That's kind of unfair. That's unfair.
And I even blocked it too, so they can't go that way. I'm just checking on how people are doing,
and I don't have to beat this. I just have to check on people. Oh, fuck, you got in. It's all
right. All right, let me see where people are. Nice. That's a pretty cool costume, dude. All right.
Hey, how close are we? How far away from the end are we at this stage now? We are absolutely nowhere
near the end of this maze. Not even close. All right. Well, what if I do this? All right,
somebody might actually beat it, he said. Wait, do people... Am I the only one that can do this?
I got banned, and the reason listed was A. A, well, cut it out. I'm just a helper. I'm just helping.
Somebody is apparently close to the end, or at least close enough. I kind of want to see. I want
to look over here. Can I see? I want to see where everybody is. I have no idea where the hell I'm
supposed to be going right now. Is that a Snorlax? That's a Snorlax costume. Hey, guys, I found
another way. That person has a Minecon cape? Yeah, this is today. Why are we doing this? It's a
Minecraft day. Can I be TP to the maze, please? Type slash die. You will be at the very beginning.
Hey, what about if I had to take this one? It's a Minecraft Minecon 2013 shirt. That's the rare
one. I feel like I'm making this harder. Did somebody beat it? Who beat it? Hold on. What was
it? GM3? Oh my fucking God. There are people that are really are right at the end. You're so close.
Oh, wow. You guys are so close. You're almost there. It's right here. Oh, you did it. Somebody
actually did it. A lot of you did it. Holy shit. Almost all of you did it. Where was I? What the
hell was I doing? How far was I? How far away was I? I was like three quarters. This is a cool
looking level. They're TPing to you. Oh, sit on. All right, what's in here? Oh, we got a boss battle.
All the servers or queue servers are down. Yeah, I think that they're coming down because I think
they're trying to apply a fix to make it so people can get in. Oh, this motherfucker has a health bar.
Get him. What's his name? The Ender Knight? If you hit slash die, you'll get teleported into this room,
everybody. This is unfair. This dude is, he can't even move. We keep going into these people's
really cool looking houses. Oh, wait, fuck. Look at this stuff. There's like little bugs all over
the ground. Did we just cheese him? No, he still has health. Stun lock penetration. So he's shitting
out these little bugs. Do these bugs hurt? It's just everywhere. I can't even kill them fast enough.
Get him. Yeah, get him. Oh, all right. Did the Ender Knight just win with a walk off grand slam
in the world series? I don't even know where he is. Everybody's swarming this guy. I'm just
waiting for a Gatorade jump to be dumped on his head. Just kill him. Don't even let him do
anything. Just don't even let him move. Is anybody even dead? I don't think he's hurt anybody.
I don't think he can. I think he's been stun locked the whole time. Don't you die if an Enderman
looks at you for like five seconds. He can't even look at anybody. He needs more ram. He's
going to be dead air in a second. Need more wham? Wham? Oh, okay. I know what you're doing.
How did everybody get diamond armor just quickly? Is there armaments that they could get into?
Somebody said, sorry, but I'm officially lost in the maze. Yeah, man. I feel you. I feel you, dude.
I know. If you want to give up a life, you can do slash die and get in here. I know, man. It's
fucking rough. Are you in the first maze? If you're in the first maze, I know, man. It's hard. It's
really hard. We kill him. I think we killed him. Hello? Wait, what? Oh, he's dead. We got it.
All right. Let's go. Nice. We got it. Look at this. Look at that dragon. That's a pretty sick
dragon. Wait until maze three. Well, we'll see. All right. Coming up next, we have what I think
is it another jump map? Oh, god damn it. I fell already. All right. I actually want to do this one
right. This looks fun. This looks fun. I want to do this right. You only get 10 lives. Keep that in
mind. Be careful. Oh shit. Are we going to get a jump maze? That'd be really funny actually.
Anyone else getting, I'm not going to say that. This is a mine cough, mine, uh, guy, mine con
stream. I almost said conference. Fucking god damn it. All right. Whatever. Let's go. I'm
going to play mine con day stream. Not mine conference day. Rear ending blunder.
What? How did you beat it already? What the fuck? Look at this guy. Oh my god. No way.
There's a couple of people that are doing really well. I, this is not a paid actor. I prompt now,
cut to my camera. This is us normal people. Okay. Some of you are not even jumping. You're just
walking off and dying. I just kind of like watching. This is, oh, they can't see the edge.
Yeah. I guess that's true. What the fuck is that? Wait, is that, I thought that was in the wall.
Wait, that's not, that's a person. Paid actors. No. So many people. So people have, this is first
jump of the stair with the ladder. People have a lot of problem with, I'd get down there to it
myself, but you know, I, you know, it's kind of fun to see what people do. You have four. Yeah.
If you've got, try to hold on to those lives. They're precious. If I go down here, it's really
interesting to see. This group right here is really, really doing pretty well. I think they're
working together. I think they're playing together. Oh, that guy tried to just flex so hard and he
dropped. That was a huge flex that guy was trying to do. He was going like world one, one Mario
strat. You just don't stop moving. Somebody's shooting an arrow at me. It's not going to work,
man. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to try. I want to try now. Do some shout casting. Okay.
Yeah, sure. Welcome to the entrance of the dungeon here. We have quite a few players.
We've got, uh, Ko Hagen here, Ko, Ko seven, Ko Hagen here, uh, taking a look over the
edge of the world here, like a few of his fellow players. We also have, uh, him and his team there.
There's a, there's two, 16 teams of 25 people at the same time.
Palm seal making a big jump board gets to there. I'm not sure what happened next. He looks like
he's stuffed underneath all the players. Really, really bad spot to be him. And you can't see,
hopefully he has his hide slash all, uh, activated. We've got El Qwerty, Qwerty keyboard up here. Nice
jump onto the tire. Nice jump onto the tires. Can he make it all the way up around? He can go over
the top. Here comes one of the hardest jumps of the entire event. Can he got it? El Qwerty
showing us how to do it. Falling down into the pool. This is the tough part and he makes it too.
We're following Qwerty here, folks doing an excellent job. Now he's got this. He gots the
double ladder jump to make now crouching. Make sure to fall off by the, if you don't play Minecraft,
if you crouch, you don't fall off. He's using that to his advantage. Oh, Qwerty pretty gone.
Oh, we have the court jester. That guy is naked. Oh, he's naked. There are people that aren't even
trying. They're shooting with arrows. Come on. Come on. Super Daza. Super Daza. That was a couple
of really good jumps in a row. Let's see it. Line it up. Oh, he got it. Got it. Dude, no.
Hey, come on. Quit hogging the little steak here, man. Is this person just naked? No. This looks
like the hard one because you have to balance on this and then jump to here. That person has a plus
two germacraft joke. I'm going for it. I want to be one of the people here. This is what it's like.
How do you grab a ladder? This whole W, right? A. Oh, I just showed you I was cheating. What is A?
Why are people being banned for A? I don't know. I have no idea. What does A mean? What a jump that
was. Oh, I had some lag there. Having a little bit of lag. I'm okay. Game's kind of laggy. It's
probably the server issues. There's a server problem sometimes. All right, I'm on. Yeah, I think
don't know what A means. Because we had to quickly just turn off the server and make it 250 instead
of 400, something got messed up and they're trying to figure it out. I will tell you this.
This server is just going to be on after this is over. This stream essentially is a gigantic
advertisement for the fact that this is going to stay turned on for 24-7 and it's going to just
kind of turn into like a Minecraft server. There's a giant advertisement for it. You're going to be
able to play through this whenever you want. Sellout. It's not a sellout. It's the server
that's my name. Are we going to do a fire festival stream? I don't want to play your damn maze.
Stay. I can do the maze. Ego maniac sellout. That's so funny. All right, this is a hard one.
Let's fucking watch out for the wind. There's Mario wind. If you fall off the edge, watch out
for the wind. See? What a recovery. I want to try this jump here with nobody here. Let me turn it
off. That doesn't work. Yeah. Remember if you're stuck somewhere, if you're in an old game,
I slash die. Fuck, I actually made it. This is a fire festival stream. Yeah, that's all right.
At least it works. An hour ago, I didn't think it was even going to work. It's actually kind of cool.
It's actually fun. Can you pause the stream? Can you pause the stream? I need to eat my
pasta. Just go. It's all right. You're not going to miss much. I'm still going to be falling on
the same jump every time. He hates his viewers. What? No, I can't. These people that have beat it.
That's over 50%. I think we can go to the next arena. Yeah, that's a lot of people. That's enough
to keep going. Pause it. Pause it. I've actually seen shit. Final Fantasy 6? 8? How do we keep
going? 7. Right, right, right. How come I can't see anything? I said the one's in between. Yeah,
yeah. How come I can't hide at all? All right, what is this one? King's Armory is this way.
Oh, this is where we've got the diamond shit. Nice. I got to put this all on. What am I stuck
in? Cement? What's this one? It's a big springboard. This barrow all over the ground.
Do you have a health bar too? Mr. Slime Boss. What about the raid loot? Is there any raid loot?
I think there might be something falling out of them. This is some good book reading music.
He just destroyed that guy. That guy was nothing. This area is really cool looking.
That looks awesome. All right, on to the next one. Let's go. Where's the next room? Down here.
Here we go. Boys and girls, it looks like it's going to be time for a maze. Oh, no, no, no,
no. Never mind. Oh, this room is actually really, really cool. How are you all the way up there
already? I don't understand. From the OST back up? Not too loud though. Man of three voices,
man of three mini games. Get out of here. That was pretty good. That was pretty good. That was
really funny. But ban that person for an hour. I just got in my ear with it working on this stuff
on the other side and just said, are you just shooting into the crowd? And I didn't realize
that. Yeah, I'm just shooting into the fucking crowd. So who this is, it's ice blocks. Oh,
fuck that. I ain't going to be able to do that one. Oh, nice try. Yeah. You can barely even see the
blocks. Someone will get it. The cycle of life. Man of three voices, man of three mini games.
I nominate that for a moment. Melon Boy. Oh, wait, no, that was what you're supposed to do.
Was it? Some of the guys that were part corn really well. This looks tricky for them. And
green tea sips. He's killing people. Oh, well, at some point somebody got my lightning stick
and just started casting it at random people. I don't even know where that is now. I have no
idea where it is. All right. Four or five people have made it here. Here are the saviors of this
level. Green tea sips has committed a get rid of them. What does any of this have to do with the
king? Well, it had something to do with it, but everything kind of broke multiple times. So we
just skipped all the we skipped all the lore just to get into the video game. It was significant
lore here. Oh, shit. They're almost here. Once you go all the way around, then you just go.
Here you go. That sucks. Wow. That sucks. Yeah, that's so funny. Look at how many people are
just waiting at the bottom waiting for someone to beat it. These guys are just hanging out.
This might as well just be mine con. Everybody's in diamond armor has diamond swords just walking
around. There are people that are really trying to there's a significant amount of people that
are attempting the first part and some of them are just kind of like walking into each other
and walking around. This person trying to fuck it up for everybody else. Are you the guy that's
from Boston that beat Dark Souls three on stream? I hope not. I am sorry to say mental anguish from
the queue. I wish there was something I could do about it, but I cannot do anything about it.
All I can hope is that maybe they can figure out what's the problem is. I am just I am just
participating. I am just participating with you all. Apparently there are thousands and
thousands of people that are like trying to do it and that's that's fine that that should work.
But the problem is is when we changed it from 400 to 250 it fucked up all the stuff in the
server. So they're trying to figure it out. A true king would have freed us by now. I can't.
I'm king in name only. Understand? What's what's that movie? Isn't there like what's the
movie about a guy that's not like this? That's not a real guy. He's like he's not the real
fuck the king. He's the useless king. Worst king puppet king. This is why you should do practice
streams. We did many of them just don't know Shrek 40 incoming. The discord is absolutely
mauled right now. I don't even want to go over there. It's like going home with a bad report
card. I don't want to go in there. I'm going to go to my friend Dave's house for like an hour.
Hey son are you coming home to show your report card? Yeah yeah um yeah I will.
Dave do you have this exact black ink that matches the report card so I can change
this uh this this to a B? I I was gonna put a line through the D. We need to make it a perfect B.
Somebody making progress. Did he do it? He did it! New king. No he gets an item. He gets the golden
boots of the golden boots of Ratatouille stream incoming. Keep those on. No nice work. Let's go!
I actually know what one of the mazes is and if everyone's gonna fucking flip out I everyone's
gonna lose their minds. In fact if we should probably just skip it because people are gonna
get very very mad at me for having it. They're gonna be very upset with me. I'm gonna get screamed
at. Shoot into the peasants. How am I listening to you? So many arrows here. All right are we
moving on to the next one? Flab with a guy that makes poops go. Let's go. I do that. That's me.
Is this the entrance? Can we knock it through this? Oh there we go. Oh yeah. Dude mace free Pog. Mace
free Pog. Pog mace. Pog mace found it. This is so fake. I'm gonna just find the entrance. I'm gonna
find the exit real quick. How many more rooms are there? I think there's only like like what five
more rooms or something. You're my I am sad. Okay let's go. Get in here. By the way this is a three
level maze. There's staircases between each maze. This is three tier. This is a three tiered cake
maze. This is the hard one and don't worry if nobody figures it out in the next 30 to 60 seconds
I'm cutting through the bottom of the cake and I'm gonna pop out like a fucking birthday party.
You're just torturing his fans. I keep like laughing too much today. I'm gonna be in pain.
Just like torture people. It's so funny. It's just you guys have just roasted me right now and it's
fucking hilarious dude. This is considered cruel and unusual punishment. Wait how people are actually
getting up top? They shouldn't be able to do that right? You can get up. This is a great view though.
This is what a scientist feels like when he looks down. When he's like the mouse and the cheese and
shit. Outplayed. Where's the staircase? Would you ever make a goo to cheese review? Yeah I'll do it
right now. That's all right. We are about rats in a maze. Actually did this yeah being just an
observer is much better. I can just see people progress. Maze experiment. This is a Stanford
I just puked. Stanford maze experiment. Somebody already got to it. Somebody made it up to the
next tier already. This one even that this one's not that bad. Oh he's trying to see where the
staircase is. I have like god mode. I can't even see where it is. Ah okay I gotta settle down.
The like cruel torture of your viewers. Like forcing you to do a bunch of gigantic mazes and
shit like that. It's just torturing everybody. When do you release the creepers? Yeah I feel
like I should be the AI director. Why are there holes in the ground? Oh my god that's evil.
Shit that's fucking evil because then you have to do the whole thing in the bottom again.
Oh my goodness that's evil. Is this Star Wars music? I don't think so. I think it's copyright
free. Oh there it is over here. So there's one there's another layer up top. So somebody
got somebody's already at the top. This did not take as long as it. Why is this one taking so
few amount of time? But the other ones were so much harder. Oh right because you could peek.
Oh right right right right right. Guys I promise you there's only one more maze and it's the worst
one. And this it is going to be it's going to be horrendous. I've seen it already. There's only one
more maze. So it's um it's absurd. You guys are going to lose your mind. It gets it's going to be
worse. Yes way worse. You don't even know. Way worse. Way more difficult. Oh there's no cheating
on level three. We're losing consciousness. So realm of the mad king. Yeah oh shit I have my
lightning again. Oh I'm sorry I didn't mean to do that to you. You're my favorite mukbang streamer.
Thanks man. Somebody said I rescheduled my SATs for this shit. Dude oh man did you?
Did you? Did you? You've rescheduled your SATs? You gotta take those man. Those
that's important knowledge you have to. It's stuck in a maze. Dude I've rescheduled my fucking dude.
I've rescheduled my SATs. I lost my Saturday. Stop. All right I'm climbing out. I'm climbing
out. I'm climbing out. I'm climbing out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm climbing out. I'm gonna get out of
here and I'm gonna find the exit and I'm gonna win. Oh shit you can't go through bedrock. Not
even god can go through bedrock. Shit. You're on your honeymoon right now? Well dude close the
laptop. Like slam it down right now. Don't get caught watching this stream. Oh shit ow.
All right I'm using god powers. Where's the exit? Cruel punishment. It's so cruel.
Somebody oh no that's okay that's like the AI director. There ain't nobody even up here.
Discord is crying. Oh shit I found the exit. What do you mean they made it? What?
How the fuck did you two do this? There's no way. There's no way you two did this. How did you do
this? It's like if you uh that seems impossible. Bring them all over here. It's time for jump. I'm
gonna die. No I can't die. I have god mode on. I forgot. No wait what? Oh shit did I just break
the whole thing? I think I might have broken everything. Jumping pog let's go. I missed my
son's birthday for this. Well you should be a better father instead of skipping your son's
birthday to watch a Minecraft stream. You should play Minecraft with your son. All right if you do
slash die you will tp to the beginning of this final parkour map. Sick. Sick. Sick. I missed my
prostate exam for this. Well reschedule it and go back. I got two lives left now thanks.
Well don't worry we're nearing the end of the dungeon. You missed your heart surgery for this?
Well rip. Sorry. This is the prostate exam. You motherfucker. People are actually doing
really well on these though. I missed nothing for this. You're all I have. Hey well thanks for
sticking around man. Thanks for watching our minecon coverage. What else are they adding to
Minecraft? What can you add to Minecraft? Cave update. Is that cool? What does that do? Adding
swearing to Minecraft. Be weird. Everyone going into the queue is immediately being kicked. Yeah
I know. I know. It's all fucked up. It's all fucked up. This is literally what people have
been waiting for for a long time. What does it make the actual okay when you dig down in Minecraft
and you get the cave they change how that works? Do they make that cooler and better? Because
that's like kind of huge. If that's more fun it already was kind of fun. Releasing next year.
Caves have better generation and unique biomes. Holy shit. That sounds fucking interesting.
I miss playing Mario Kart with my girlfriend's husband for this.
Somebody beating it almost again? Nobody's getting close. You're almost there man.
Why did you read that? Wow. Wait wait this is just the big jump. This is the big jump. You
got to get this. Got it. You did it. Wait is that not it? Oh that's not it. Oh shit there's more.
This person's really good. Oh no. Oh that was close. Damn it. What's left after that? Just a
little bit more right? Check link. Check link. Let me see. What's the link? Let me see. Unknown
Pog. What? Unknown Pog? Wait. Unban for $40? Wait what is this? That's not here. That's not this
stream. That's not this stream. It is? No it can't be. There's no there's no you don't just pay and
get unbanned to this server. It's global? Well I that's not me. I didn't say it. I didn't tell you
to do that. I don't I didn't say buy a $40 unban. I didn't say that. Yeah I've just been piped into
my ear. It is not for this server. It was your suggestion. It was not my suggestion. Hey now
you're putting words in my mouth and you're taking them out of something else that never existed in
the first place. Greed. No I didn't. I'm just trying to get people's money. He's scheming with
Senator Dave State again. Zombie eater gave a hundred dollars they said hey I got banned
here's a hundred dollars please unban me. God damn it. His eyes are bulging with imagined riches.
He should have just opened it in OnlyFans. Oh fuck. Fuck. We have a finisher almost here.
They're almost at the very end. What do they have two four more jumps? You can do it to get us to a
you can do it you're almost there man come on you can do it. He's deflecting so he can scam us.
Not if like Psycho Streamer tortures his viewers for hours.
Remember I would watch your OnlyFans. I'm not gonna have an OnlyFans. Why the hell would I have an
OnlyFans? What do you want? Oh thank you. We have a winner. Fermet spy crab excellent work. You won
yourself a piece of golden armor from me the king. Where are you man? Let's get you front row so the
stream can see you. Where are they? Okay where are you man? Okay there you are here you go you've
got golden apples from the king. Remember this is gonna say was given to you by German 985 so hold
on to it forever. Oh I just gave them to like all of you. It was stolen. Did you get any? Did you get
any? Show me a gold apple make sure that you got one. He didn't get any. Well how about a pair of
This is gold. This has gold on it. There yeah see this is gold. There's a gold tip on there.
Illegal. Oh you guys are gonna love this one. You guys are gonna love this one. You guys are gonna
love this one. It's a maze. Yeah it's mirrors. Some of them have empty spaces. It's impossible.
This shit's impossible. Good luck. Let the torture commence. Ow. He rips off the prize winner. No I'm
I'll give him. Oh don't worry. I didn't know. I tried to give it to him. I think this is the end.
I think there's one more room after this. I've had a nightmare like this. Yeah I have too. End of
career voice. No my career is just fine. I think it has killed somebody accidentally. This sick
fuck is making his viewers relive his nightmares. All I've been doing is like laughing this whole
stream. I've been laughing at like just the roast job. Every time I look over a chat there's like a
new like top of our roast me comment. He's a redditor. Yeah you all you all redditors too.
Everybody here's a redditor. So I'm just gonna I'm gonna take a look. See where everybody is.
Not bad. All right. All right. For all the things that we're talking about some of you guys are
really good at this shit. Some of you guys actually are very good at doing this. Like look the people
over here. These guys are just on a mission. Redditing. You're ruining the immersion. Well I
want you I'm having you see that image is just. Can you pull that image up on stream?
That's funny to me. The image that they're spamming in the chat. Is it possible to get that shown on
the stream? He knows what it is. Would you be upset if a cow fell through your ceiling?
Yeah that would be horrible. That would be a terrible thing to have happen. What are you
talking about? If a cow fell through the ceiling right now that would be a disaster.
All right we got somebody's close. Don't look up. Where's the closest person? I think I would die.
Yeah you mean you would. If a cow landed through the ceiling on top of you. You're sitting at your
chair. You're dead. You're going to instantly die. It's gonna break every bone in your body.
Aren't cows like 700 pounds? A cow is like a thousand pounds. That's like half a car dropping
on your head. They did it. See you guys are actually good at this. Some of you guys can
actually do this shit really really well. 1400 pounds. That's a car man. That's a small car.
That's one of those gerbil cars. Is it called the key of gerbil? What's the song name? I actually
don't know. Congratulations to those of you that went through. Clueless sniper. Nice job.
All right let's move on to the next encounter. We're about to enter the one of the final rooms.
Serious Sam. Fuck I want to play Serious Sam too. Yeah we can go. Where is the actual end?
Okay I still can't. I'm flying around. I can't find the end. I have no idea where the end is
and I can fly through a building. Oh there we go. All right here's here we go. Time for
this is the final boss. The two yetis. Oh fuck these guys actually look like they're attacking.
Yeah this is actually dangerous I think. I think people are going to die here.
What the fuck was that? All right I'm turning off my god mode. I want to get in. I thought that was
in the game and I just freaked out. Another raid boss. This is the last raid boss. Did this share
health? Cod zombies. Why is somebody just jumping in my camera? Get out of here.
I have a diamond sword don't I? Somewhere. Where the hell is it? Focus one at a time.
We're splitting our damage up. Kill one at a time. I need a weapon. Where the fuck is the
healer? Let's see if I have any. Yeah we go. Oh shit. Wait what happened? I just had it.
It turned into a bow. Oh there we go. All right I got my I got my I got my weapon back.
This really is just recess. This is what I would feel like. This is what recess is like.
I get it now. I know what it's like to be a teacher. This is just outdoor recess.
Just replace the bows with little balls or nerf balls. No tanks all dps. I can't even hurt this
guy like this. One chat walking around beating everybody up. Where is the bad guy? All dps.
One of them has two hearts down. What the hell kind of school did Jeremy go to? No I'm not I'm
just I'm not saying it's like an all-out brawl outside. Kids like throwing rocks at each other
and biting each other and punch all of them while punching each other. Yeah that would be really
kind of a fucked up place to be. You're right. The amount of people just looking and waiting and
watching is so funny. Bones? Brawl? All right how much health does he have left? He's not even
rendering on my screen. Anybody else feel like that some of these clips can be taken to make it
seem like your Minecraft clan is really fucking cool? You'll take some of these with the music
in the background and look at this. This is like clan chaos. Don't fuck with us. We're clan carnage.
We don't fuck around at all. We're just really really really just not intimidating at all.
Clan cringe? Okay I'm gonna start lightning this fucking guy. I'm gonna I'm taking 10 health bars
down right now. Where is he? This dude only has two hearts and they would be really close to the
microphone. Sign up on our website clancarnage.com if you think you have what it takes. Wait I can type
what? This is not gonna kill. If I type slash does that kill everybody if I do slash kill?
Can I get confirmed what that does? What happens if I do slash kill?
Yeah yeah it would be a wordpress or vlog spot. That's true. Clan carnage accepting applications
now. Only kill mobs? All right can I can I can I can I get a manual kill on this guy?
How come I can't even see him? Why am I still in my own game? I feel like I'm not even here.
Yeah why is my lightning stick not killing anything? He's gone invisible. Oh it works on
players only okay. Remember you never existed. Oh did I get him? Did I actually hit him with
something? Clan carnage. Oh shit what did we kill it? Did we win? Fist of the sword. Whoa!
Oh my god people are dying. People are dying! What do we do? What do we do? What's going on?
Did somebody put like a kill block here? How do I move them? Is he dead? Oh they're being
tele-frag. 500 people on one block is gonna tele-frag if it happens. Dude I can't even see.
I'm just getting colors. It looks like the beginning of the stream. It looks like the
structure that they made. That work? Stuck on a block with somebody. Yeah one of these blocks
dumb. I'm at times 10 speed right now. All right I have this dragon sword. Am I gonna go kill this
dragon? All right guys it's time for the end. It's time for the end of recess. Hopefully the
bell doesn't ring before we go pretend to kill the dragon. All of a sudden it's gonna be like
about to kill the dragon. Come on in you little bastards. No we're not done with the dragon.
You had the fucking dragon. Yeah oh I died. Now get the fucking class. Uh okay. Dragon coming?
The dragon. Oh whoa oh boy we got extra time at recess. The principal came out. Hey kids
it's me the principal. I know that you guys wanted to play some more outside and frankly
I need another 20 minutes in my office. Recess has been extended by 10 minutes. Go have fun with
you and slay whatever dragon you want. That's right remember me and tell your parents to vote
for me. I'm running for selectman too next year. Don't tell them that principal Danny Davidson
only even have an extra 15 minutes at recess. Yeah by the way I'm getting rid of taxes in this
whole county. Tell them that too. I can't see. There's two dragons. Holy shit. Kill him kill him
kill him. They're fighting each other. They're fighting each other. It's two dragons.
They're killing each other. Where did this one come from?
Now get off me. One of the cafeteria ladies jumped on me. You can't give them extra time outside.
They need to learn. Get off. Now kids don't worry I'll take care of this. Oh shit he's throwing
trees at me. You idiot. Get back in class and remember it's mystery meat today.
Get her. No get away from me. You little shit kid. Have some more sloppy jokes.
I made an extra sloppy for you.
Oh I know how you kids like a sloppy.
We got her. We got him. We did it. We killed the dragon. Hey and let me get off here and say
let it be known that kids now rule the school. No more nap times. No more math homework.
We run the school. Recess all day and french fries only for lunch.
Kids come on in. It's time for recess to be over. It's me principal Davidson.
Just a regular person. Not anything weird going on. I'm just normal. Oh what the heck.
Okay yeah it's gone. I've got to go. I've got to go into school now.
For the kindergarten. This structure is perfect for the kindergarten by the way.
This is just kindergarten scream. This was just this was keep. Oh we went to we went
to kindergarten school. This was just the plot of Billy Madison. Here go build something with
these blocks like a bunch of you. Just I'm not going to fucking pay attention. Just go do it.
Hey look I made a really really hard maze that none of you kids are going to be able to do.
Gonna buy me like an hour. Walk around for a little bit. Here here's some like foam swords.
Pretend somebody's a skeleton king. This is what you this is what you built. This is this is what
would be built in a kindergarten class. How is that the plot for Billy Madison? It isn't. I don't
know. It's close. Kindergarten stream. This is so. How long did I think this was ever gonna work?
Like honest to god. Turn pvp on by the way and give me that skyrim music. The stream was just
a daycare. Recess versus reality. Should it that should be the title of this of this stream.
Recess versus reality. We got pvp on. Change title. I missed my son's birth list. Hey Nintendo
Wii music you know what that means. That means wait for the 2.4 gigahertz connection which is
like actually ends up being on the Wii like like 400k down. Download and update for your system or
to download a game that you know is like 40 megabytes and it's taking like 45 minutes and
then they decide you get Mario starts to walk by and hit coins with his head and when he gets
to the second box with the coins in it that means you're at 50 percent downloaded and then when you
get to about 75 percent downloaded he spams the last coin box until you turn the fucking volume
down on your tv. Can't just have a bar there that says 10 20 30 percent. I'm acting like this is
happening now. That's not currently happening right now. Pvp on. That guy's gone. Wait is he?
Murderer? Murderer? What the fuck? What? You ever visit your kingdom? Yeah you know what let's take
a look around. See what people built last time. I fucking killed people. All right what did you make?
This guy person has a fort up here. Oh no what I just did okay what I just did is the equivalent
of like the dad or like the principal or like the other teacher coming out and seeing oh look
they're doing a little they're doing a little session where they're pretending to slay the
dragon and they're using sticks and pretending they're wands. See in those kids heads they have
their own headcanon how those wands work. If I walk out here with a wand in my hand as like
just principal Dave and I start waving it around going like blast blast blast power move power move
power move power move power move power move it's like no no you can't do that that's not how it
works it's a three second charge three second charge oh you mean like this
no get out of here oh I zapped you no I zapped you oh no you didn't you missed I zapped you
I'm just ruining their time this is pvp on and then you you go full you go full throttle Harry
Potter mode you say like oh I zapped you oh I zapped you and you died no I didn't I did what
no I didn't I'm still alive I'm still praying no I said no I zapped you you have no life left
no that's talking about no you you lost all your hp no I didn't no I didn't I have dad shield
mom let's go let's go dude I got the fucking dragon sword you don't want to mess with the
guy with the dragon sword dude you think you're gonna get away with that you're just gonna take
loot all of it no who got it go look at the fireman church all right cool let me just
there see it didn't really even kill anybody it's still the worst item in Binding of Isaac
all right where's the fireman church damn oh man no fuck that you guys may be the most
the most dangerous slide at an amusement park this is a big water slide this thing would be
insane nobody said pog diamond sword I'll take care of this let's count fucked up all right
where is it where's the where's the church of fireman build a pyramid over here oh shit all
right here we go the church of fireman German's gonna unban me 200 1200 dollars no you're not
getting unbanned Irma finished black and white too the flower given to fireman made by his wife
flower girl the workbench used by fireman during the great yep okay what's with the fake somebody
shaking tin foil thunder come on the workbench used by fireman during the great yeah rat war
okay nice it took you like three hours to do that by the way make sure that everyone's aware of
that for about three hours and now with what's over here is there more to the church of fireman
where's the where's the rest of the tour over here here let me get a good oh I see I see you
all right I'm going to the church oh god bro this shit is stupid okay leave your generous
donations in the box oh sure uh it's oh how can I I'm trying to put something in there
we can't all fit in here at the same time guys stop putting blocks down you fucking it all up
I'm gonna start casting lightning if you don't get it I'm gonna get out of here
everybody help me out help me out of this help me out of this help me out help me out help me up
help me out of here all right so who's the who's this is fucking creepy
dad if you see this turbo one so yeah this is this it's just fireman just standing here
what happened in there
wait what did you say I just yeah I'm sorry I'm sorry did I fireman was a statue he wasn't a person
that was not actual fireman standing there that would be like weird I was a statue of fireman
actually a psycho no get this can I I'm removing get this sign out of here
give me this yes it was no it wasn't I couldn't I couldn't control my wand
don't you guys know wands in this universe they're just like symbiotes in spiderman
they have like a mind of their own and they talk to you what are you guys making over here
actual child all right and what are they anything else you want to show me
you got anything to show me oh a golden apple thanks I was waiting I was waiting for it see
see I got it again it's delicious all right I'm I want to take this opportunity I want to build
something come with me wait you guys can't fly are you idiots there's a rat head where's the rat
head oh shit that's actually that's pretty good uh yeah TP me to the rat pog look at this look at
these builds come see your statue all right the from the from the I already seen it all right
look at that rat pog yeah cool what do you got in here you've been collecting why do you have so
many oak leaves this is a house or is this just a structure this is pretty cool I want to get a
better view it's beautiful dude we should do like Minecraft competitions or I come around I go
that's a seven that's an eight that's a seven that's a six six point five uh maybe that'll
probably never happen all right where's this uh the statue of me is this your doing this is
your doing did yes or no Super Mario Brothers 35 for the Nintendo Switch is male what are you
talking about oh we're gonna sign here I made it all right where's this other where's the actual
statue of me do we have a coordinate for it what is this over here that was the statue but that
was a rat statue how's it going on down here oh you got a little hidden stash back here huh
oops I killed that person hidden stash oh boy oh you can't keep me in the dark I hit the guy in
the back of the head but you don't think I ever played Minecraft before guys I'll get the hell
out of this who's down here with me hey why are you in here with me dig dig wait are they trying
to drown me this is how the king dies this is for all the mazes you twisted fuck I said the mazes
were gonna be fun I thought we were all gonna laugh about it okay no you know I let me out let
me out oh it's gonna get real ugly here in a second you know look what I have equipped
it's gonna be real ugly you better let me out of here it's gonna get ugly I tried to warn you I
gave you a warning yeah watch out yeah whoa get away from the hole yeah why don't you come down
here why don't you guys come down here and get me come get me come on come on in I'm gonna be
safe man wait how'd you get in here oh do I have god mode on good I got out I got out I got out
hey look who got out I'm gonna come here monkey ass come to 690 7 7 you see that this is cute
this is really cute really cute little Minecraft is such a fun game we got I can I unban that
person we put that can we put that can we bring that person back I didn't I was I don't know why
I did that can we bring that person back there's like a look at the log of the last person that
I killed can you bring them back this is like a cute thing they were doing too and I just like
struck him with lightning and pushed him off the edge of a cliff holy shit this is something
I can't show on stream get that off camera dude get that off get that off I don't think you can
I mean that's I don't know it's like a guy with a clown in his dick what do you I don't get I don't
think this is supposed to be like minecon friendly wait you have to say you have to click mature
audience when you click the stream right all right can we can we take can we take off his uh
oh come on dude come on man come on man it just sums up this whole stream this
absolute fucking nonsense okay anybody got anything else that we can all see
uh go read the signs at the church okay that sounds wait there is actually it's like a little
store here how's this place this looks kind of cool a machine gun was shooting what the
fuck was that I just heard a machine gun firing at us what the fuck what was that no it's not
this person that was like shooting what am I hearing what am I hearing oh it's this somebody's
opening a door idiot trap idiot trap idiot trap oh shit it did work I didn't I thought it was
gonna kill you I thought it was gonna spin and be like a blender oh what's this nothing new rat dens
okay the rat king's lair oh shit watch out watch out watch out with that watch out for that watch
out for that watch out for that it's the rat king damn yeah give him some gold is he eating the gold
bars what do you got in the back room lieutenant rat den I think I killed I killed somebody I think
I can't right click I think okay oh shit look at this what do you got in here I'm just rat king
hmm take some of that maybe no why not why yes yes yes I'm taking it all right hit me with that
don't forget who has don't forget who has the fucking cigarette of death I do it's this one
what you got back here this is pretty sick turn off pvp please I'm dying so much I'm sorry man
that was a plea please all right what else we got I'm stuck in the coliseum how do I wait are you
still somebody still in a maze can somebody check is somebody still doing the maze that's not real
right is somebody actually still in there poor kid but he's in maze one no no there's nobody in maze
one guys he's like he's like 50 feet into maze one and it's like five miles long hey but guess
what he's having a ton of fun he doesn't even know he doesn't even care maze one to this person
guys that's that's a lot of content all right this is called my house all right well whose house
please read the signs of the church I'll read the signs of the church I will this is your house
oh that's chest of the cheeto that turn can I want to see your face that's pretty sick dude
person spit on me all right um l mushroom what does it say I'm gonna go read the signs of the
church pretty cool house though man pretty sick house supposed to be windy today be careful that's
a pretty big building though goons are ruining the house wouldn't be my goons I'm gonna come to the
pea shop that's that's fine it's okay don't worry nice nice work though good job oh dog doghouse
look at this one holy shit this is awesome Jeremy is tall no one typed that yes they did whoever
made this sign it's in here that's a rat this is so cool all right this is cool I'm gonna sneeze
but I cannot mute my microphone that's the worst sound I've ever made oh that was
horrible he was faking it no I was okay let me I'm gonna I'm gonna tell you what happened there
that was fucking nuts so I started to see yeah I don't like people looking at me I gotta go
somewhere else so when I started to sneeze I felt it coming and then sometimes if you make
noise and you just act weird it you can make it not happen I can't mute the microphone I have no
way to mute myself it's I so I have no button to press because I'm not technically streaming
through my computer so I can't I turn this way and it stopped happening and then I like as a
joke like made another noise like oh it's okay it's not gonna happen and then I made another one
after that a real noise and then I sneezed and it hurt I don't know what happened there that was
fucking bizarre all right let's go to a village when are you gonna stop recording this pre-recorded
video for the stream and I don't whatever I don't know what you're trying to say hello hey welcome
to the village you just blew up your septum no okay we are building a peaceful mountaintop village
join us donation feel free to take and give build something this is so cool I want to do
this next time all right this is cool you got donation yeah I'm gonna I'm giving you hey shh
you're getting the fucking king's golden boots I'm telling anybody that that's for you discord
seven nine seven four dude I that's a I don't know why you just did that you just you just
you're gonna have to change accounts now you're gonna get like a million messages
right you're gonna get like 5 000 messages a second for the next like three days I I'm just
saying a dense wall of trees would help keep the village hidden immuno mine shaft hey but if you
contact him con if you want to be part of the village then that's what you should be good don't
fucking contact him for any other reason I'm getting out the stick of lightning don't fucking
make me use it what's that playstation place place like cooper wait is this the other way
is it nightwing but I didn't see the rest of this village what's in this house what you got
apples I'm stuck out of bounds his cronies have destroyed everything aren't you all cronies I
don't have like a group of people that are like yeah yeah and go mess the place up while you're
at it go mess them up aren't we all cronies in here this is a cool house though I like the design
on this one statue of king germa oh nice somebody in there all right moose man what do you got
sword you got an apple moss stone look good change the music please for the love of god
oh okay can we change the music to like uh I don't know the song I wasn't ready for that
is dead no it's not
play Gaston all right teleport me to another funny thing uh the answer is no here I'll answer you
does it take that long to break how do I do an n it's kind of an f it's a really sad
okay and oh oh no wait no I gotta say I gotta answer this person's question on the screen
okay no well on what platform would you like me to play it on
god and answer me sure okay whatever platform it is okay whatever you have to help tell me
you shower with socks on why would you do that it would get all get all mushy and gross
all right so this is a pet store mad this is a pet store apparently oh shit so this is so this
is just a duck you get for a pet oh do I get to take how do I take the duck how do I pay you
right here here's one diamond cube how do I pick up the duck that's not is he lay eggs all right
how do I pick him up how do I make him friends oh is he following me now all right let me out
of the gate he's falling he likes me now all right we're friends let me let me out you're
gonna follow me well let's go you just you got scammed laughing my ass off hey that's not your
duck that's supposed to be mine for rent 22 20 a month free pet that's not free if it's 22
dollars a month right click with a stick are you kidding me that's really what you have to do
I mean I that's a stick but it's not the right one anybody have a stick what the fuck is going
on here are you trying to be calling me like yes I'm this is like Zeus and his son Thor talking
to each other why did I that was weird way to say that Zeus and his son Thor what am I right
am I doing correct like grammar all right let's go cool pet shop time to go to uh what I've been
told is a maze okay we'll do the maze okay not bad not bad oh that you got me on that one
tricked me on trick me twice that's it I won it's a pretty good maze what does this say the king
the king oh there's another low system over here cock shed what is that I don't get it well there's
there's a chicken up there maybe that's a good little home what kind of dumb chest is this oh
dude parkour event oh sick almost fuck oh fuck read all the side yeah I need to go back to the
church and read the signs of the church there's that church of fireman again oppie oppies what
are you streaming right now you have to be yes okay what is this ho ho representation
the blacksmith okay all right what can you make me here I'm gonna give you a wooden
axe and I'd like you to turn that into a a wearable what was that I want you put it make
it into a wearable axe to hit freeze down thanks with buttons when do we fertilize the king
so here's the deal but oh wait wait I gotta check on the uh what what what what platform
was that sly cooper did I get my answer did I get my question answered is it over here somewhere
yeah I need to see the church and I need to see what platform they want me to play sly cooper on
play unia what do you live in this sign does a guy live in a billboard play neptunia this is
where I live my house billboard oh hey look thanks you went up so high for this too what's
this little beehive wait that's it that's that's that's it lucky you don't take somebody else's
rabbits for that's cursed there you go I should show feet there it is all right let's go back to
the church I do want to read in front of the church the signs there now you guys have a
coordinates and can if somebody tp me to the front of that church oh it says penis right
lucky what is this you get the this is a fucking securo house this is the level you made the level
from securo the first level with the spear guy you even have like the tutorial and everything
this holy shit dude nice job oh it's crowsky we're doing too good of a job what I do all right so go
to the front of this of the church again it has been changed quite a bit yeah hello germs can't
believe germy craft is real can she stream petition inside it's gonna have eight signatures
boo crew round two you gotta be this tall to enter no one is that tall so we get all none of us can
go in does it say play the age of mythology ost put it on who who a flower given to fireman
slime guy germa please finish salmon max season three nope i'm just gonna sit on the toilet and
go that lemon gang praise the fire through the germa fireman and the flames we carry on
germa play rock band drums you might talk about my immersion being broken
this fireman church bit welcome to the church of the everlasting fireman through this way germa
fireman the flames will carry germa played rock band drums germa germa praise me
for
my fireman as a memorial to his late son inferno lad 1996 2014 may he rest in peace
do not touch punishable by death even for germa is that what's going on right now well yeah get
excuse me what get this you don't know what's allowed back here so what else what else is back
here is this way this is a tomb all right you're gonna you're gonna desecrate the grave with
toontown when do you guys remember vh1's pop-up videos it was a tv show and it would play a music
video and it would be like it'd be like like michael jackson would be dancing on the and it'd
be like michael jackson was born and it would give you like random info and facts about like
the set about like who the who is the musician or whatever this is just pop-up video the stream
i just keep getting but when hey hey hey germa when are you gonna play garfield card
germa small you know it's really funny i think i think it's time to hire somebody
to like do a pop-up video on a video that i that gets uploaded to like the second channel
just have them be fucking horrible we'll do pop-up video on some upload coming up in the next
whatever what's this what's the deal with sterner's sign i was saying it's i don't think it's even
i'm glad it's being blocked i think it's just nonsense i pee i forgot they forgot about where
they peed or something whatever all right let's go up that's it wait secret this is a really bad
this is a really bad house don't give me that i'm just saying is that rude no it was bad like
it's it let me put it this way incomplete it's a little incomplete i didn't mean to say bad it's
just not done toxic you're a psycho no i didn't mean bad in that way i meant bad like as in
like man it's bad because you don't this you don't have enough stone to put up
i wish you had more stone to use throne room an amazing stream i i you are really cool dude we
actually love mazes we were joking best maze stream of 2020 this is made by farmers guild
play garfield card thanks for uh all right read these hey thanks guys i think my favorite part
about the stream is like guy with the piston dick i mean that was probably my favorite part
i literally put it in your hands what is this read these read i'm here i'm reading read these
jesus christ yep i feel like i'm in a nightmare and weren't these the same ones this is the throne
room guards kill him yeah so it's a mutiny then just like the emperor just like this wrong line
i thought that was an enderman it is actually isn't it all right i think uh i think it's time
to to can this i think it's time to can this this is oh fly cooper answer yeah i don't where is it
i'll answer it end of career stream no it no it wasn't all right where's the answer there it is
okay on let's see look at this guy on where is it auto why did he remove it we're just desperately
looking for it set it down there no it was up high wasn't it wait what was that it's by the
peaceful village play lego island i mean that's pretty creative considering you did it on an
island later okay all right so above church on cobblestone best joke of the whole stream
above church on cobblestone best joke of whole stream what i you what is it what's what is it
that's cobblestone right here take the sword oh shit thanks all right pick this up press q
too many times okay well here's this answer it's a somebody said it's over here there it is place
sly cooper on e p2 this you didn't even answer who did somebody make this and then leave the server
on pc oh okay yeah sure i mean i might as well pc all right yeah i'll play sly cooper on pc i mean
i'm gonna answer your question man all right i am we're gonna actually we spent a lot of time
just after doing all the random minigames i'm surprised we spent this much time just doing
this this has been fun too play age of mythology on pc that's not a bad idea yeah it is i'm just
seeing if i missed anything over here murdered uh please do not kill me there's nobody here what
are you hiding yeah what's what are you hiding i even though secret base death okay well that's
his shitter dude far cry one germa we've been waiting for years all right all right i'll play
far cry one uh on monday how's that sound you just got ultimate one guide you got ultimate one guide
right there i'm gonna play far cry one on monday there you go play on ps2 wait what this was
changed go to the santa house it says ps2 please come see my auto statue all right i think that's
it we had to skip all the lore in the beginning of the stream and it was very hard but it was
still fun so here's what's gonna happen now this was just a gigantic advertisement stream for this
fuck the king what the uh we're out of space here this server is going to stay on for at least a
little while you'll be able to do pretty much what you want you can play through the mini games if
you want again you can just have a little server here hang out chill arm please please come to the
farmer's guild one more time all right one more time at the farmer's guild yeah so the server is
gonna be the server is gonna be off the next probably couple of hours because they're gonna
like reconfigure a few things i guess but it will be on you can just play on it i just immediately
thought this was a dick and i didn't even this is like a space invader thing is it 40 dollars no
it's not 40 dollars it's not gonna if you get banned from the server you can't pay 40 dollars
to come back i know that for a fact i've been told that for a fact no that's not here that's not what
is this and we'll probably like it might be fun just to have just like a place just like a server
kind of add to this just for fun it's 50 now no all right where was that farm it's the last
thing i want to see before we get out of here thanks for watching though guys i mean the it's
still sort of experimental a lot of this stuff but it was still fun regardless it was still chaotic
save the coliseum what do you mean save the coliseum what's wrong with the coliseum
remember get that guy out of the maze i feel so bad for that person what do you mean save the
coliseum oh save the guy from the coliseum okay i will where is he i think he disconnected help
wait they're saying help where are you what was that don't forget the signs of the farmer's guild
we invested okay yeah yeah all right where's the farmer's guild we'll call it there save the guy
he's gonna be fine help help i'm stuck in the maze tp to me help okay come to the throne room
please i am in the throne room i can't get out of the maze okay come see this you stupid hold
i hold on a second where's the farmer's guild i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm clean i'm just trying to end
the stream cleanly where where is the farmer's guild i heard my throne now and then i just started
right clicking you can't say that shit to me all right here we are at the farmer's guild thank you
all right read these i tried really hard please you're not helping please bro please jeremy we
tried really hard on this jeremy was here he's coming back come here why can't you guys just
type to each other you just killed one of your friends it didn't work you killed yeah you one
of your somebody's dead that was the farmer's guild like accountant i'm all right i'm fine
well there goes another one oh i put a block okay well um i'm gone that was fun i got
teleported somewhere that's gonna be it that'll be it the server is gonna stay on in a couple of
hours that same link by the way that you see germa f dot tk it's a minecraft server go enjoy it
go play through the dungeon if you want maybe you can tell me what your best time is i know i'll be
keeping track or just walk around and just have fun hang out and build something fun what we'll
put this this might be actually kind of fun to check in on this place every like now and then
just for like an hour or two how did you bring it back two hour queue why is it on fire you guys
flooded the place see what you think come to the throne tp to the throne room for a selfie all right
i'm going to the throne room for a selfie everybody get to the throne room for a tp everybody to the
throne room for a selfie tp throne yeah throne room selfie i just heard it short photo yeah photo
time everybody get in all right everybody get in here let me get like up in the front and let me
crunch down and go like p sign up let me know hey let me know when you're gonna take the photo
all right ready get everybody in here okay take that photo take a selfie selfie cheese selfie
selfie say ftk dude ftk yeah say it that was just rude why is that happening again hey you stupid
motherfucker come here all right where's where's this i want to i want yeah where are you cody cody
where are you oh no i'm still okay let's go where are you cody i want i want to talk to cody all right
yeah i'm here we got is it gonna be another chance for fans to play with you in a game
probably but i mean i'll be popping in on this server every now and then oh look it's cody 090
909 you want to fight okay i'll use a wooden sword and i'll still beat you oh he's ducking
because he said fuck you behind him all right cody sure yeah i'll hey all right i'll let you
get the first hit right here throw the first punch you throw the first punch throw the first
punch you throw the first punch now you do it bro yeah hit me bro what are you gonna do bro
yeah right you're not gonna throw a punch bro no hit me bro hit me hit me come on man all right
whatever fuck you dude how to rotate sign in minecraft pvp is off pvp is off yeah that don't
mean you can't die from lightning okay you passed your test you passed your test of can you withstand
my lightning abilities you can withstand the power therefore you get the power my leash oh
that guy got it it's raining hell power you just gave it how would you give it back you get one
chance man remember where the fuck are you dude i'm everywhere and anywhere man you have to see
this oh my god it's not clickbait all right fine general arse what would you like to show me tp me
to general arse right now if what they have is not something incredible that's not clickbait
i'm banning him from the twitch chat too let's go kill me okay what do you got general arse let's
take a look i'm ready to be wowed please play toy stories 2 for playstation 1 it's great and has
good music please play it please ban this person in the chat they're now banned from the channel
right at least at least 20 minutes we got anything else to show me is this supposed to shoes for the
king i don't get it for the king oh is it is it a double middle finger that's pretty clever actually
he got banned from minecraft auto behind church or die please it's worth the auto statue behind
church tp me to mobile it's pretty good skin there's a rival thrown behind farmer's guild
come fight me this guy just doesn't want to stop playing minecraft this is actually really
interesting and he said general arse got banned in twitch chat for 30 minutes well you told me
it wasn't clickbait and that ban or if not if clickbait please super paper mario for the nintendo
we you know what i guess this is your chance for me to say no i'm sorry no i'll play sly cooper
all right i'll play sly cooper on the playstation 2 all right ttp me to uh ttp me too yeah here we go
let's get some music all right what is what's here what was here super paper mario is this
shit i'm sure it's all right it's a jump party i don't know i want to see no no i don't want
to do that either there's no music for this please go to the sour tower wait a minute i
what am i stupid oh i was about to get to it too play minecraft pog welcome feel free to rest
and enjoy the stay all right this kind of looks at what my inventory looks like in this game
okay so what's up here what is it what's what's in here this is your house got a good view hey
nice house pretty good house here right in the mountain sorry remember you lied to me you broke
my heart you never tp'd to me all right tp how do i do it tp to mobu tp mobu is that your name
i got that wrong clash tp to mobu doing this right i had a whole bit where i named a sword
germa's penis but you dropped it i'm sorry dude no that's a that's not accurate but okay say say
that again so i can just so i can make sure i'm getting this correct there are there are three
people who are actually still in the first maze that's not accurate it can't be i just got tp'd
in here there are three here what germa you are breaking my heart mobu i'm trying tpa your name
player name tpa instead of tp and then just mo be there here you are all right listen to me
not this dork do not listen to this creature play to blob for the wee nah germa do you smoke
weed from mob no toy story is two for pc nah you wouldn't your mom thanks no play time splitters
please that's what might happen all right mobile what was the deal here i was gonna give you the
god powers i think that's what it was something like that i don't know i don't remember hey this
motherfucker right here has it and he's freaking out he's sitting there going oh fuck oh fuck oh
fuck he gave it to me accidentally i gotta put it away put it away put it away don't i don't want
anyone to see that i just had that in my hand i'm just chilling man just saying you know i knew it
i knew i told you see i told you i told you we caught him fight his fight response wait why is
this star wars music playing why is this star wars music listen to me okay what's this say
you can wag the tail auto it's so
is this auto or is this is this a meatball with a switch on it oh it has a face okay
this is so cute now i wait oh uh where wait who has it oh shit my powers are gone i can't do my
powers well you know what i was gonna do the church of the fold of the fireman's holy library
on the first day the fireman made the biaz and the humans the biaz diverged from the human race
after 10 000 years the fireman is embodied by the avatar who is ultra powerful the king germa has
faked his credentials as the avatar yeah okay we're getting we're getting the story as it comes
come on i guys if you ever want to get out of this room you've got to follow the clues
oh are they oh i get it they got us in here so they could drop grenades on us
i see let me take a look hey can can you uh deposit of uh some tmt into my inventory
i got something real wild i want to try actual grief actual griefing guys i don't even know how
to use tnt i'm gonna do a tnt test over here how do you use tnt just have to touch it right
paying attention okay all right who's uh you stink well now now you gotta jump good luck
i didn't want to keep no didn't want oops i'm sorry that guy didn't do anything wrong
it was a uh it was a casualty that happened for no reason how does that get through how does that
get through how does i'm how does that get through i mean tp me to that guy but like how does that
even get through am i the only person that didn't that saw what that person said oh i'm i'm shaking
and you didn't see that nobody did oh okay somebody in chat said something fucking crazy
you tp me to that guy though i feel like he's so herma give what herma give me a stack of tnt
mine carts well i can't read it and some rails all right dude all right can i get can i get a
stack of tnt a stack of rails and a stack of uh something out whatever he needs all right come
over here shaking your order is finished at the blacksmith it's so there's too many things going
on okay here you go no hey stop this guy bad guy this guy's a bad guy this guy's a bad guy this
guy's a bad guy this guy's a bad guy that guy's a bad guy here you go who wanted it this guy
really had 10 letters right all right 10 letters here take that mine a mine cart with tnt i hope
i'm giving this the right person okay did you get it i thought we were gonna end the stream an hour
ago yeah i think i've been having fun though this is like fun to do this they're communicating
stack of tnt iron for mine carts okay yep i can i get it wait i did not give you a stack of tnt
some somebody has a secret says a secret murderer that has a cnt and a stack 64 of them mine carts
don't stack oh gonna be a blast all right if someone's shooting you with arrows remember
i got free content for you hold on all right so what is this i was gonna blow that up what are
you doing what are you no no no no no no no why would you just jump okay well i do i i did
why did he just do that he thought he was caught and that i was gonna kill him i wasn't even gonna
kill him he just was like god i guess i'll take it i guess i'll jump i just was asking him what he
was doing it was a very basic question i mean clearly i'm gonna build this over and dump lava
on people and kill them but you didn't even get halfway through man i didn't even catch you
committing the crime so what are you making i got freaked this is just hurting people
this is just killing people there goes somebody they can't stack them no zebra hey it's your
best friend cody all right wait i'm gonna find who was it was what was it gonna go somewhere all
right we actually do have to close up soon blasphemous bullshit all right let me see who
was it tp begging bend your fucking throne room please come see my statue all right let's go to
sweet buns it's so good i love this i love it it's perfect it's unbelievable there's bite marks on
my couch throne room needs help okay your king is coming uh you give me an anvil so i can make the
germa's penis i you're gonna reach out to somebody else fun fun ill chan i think i got your name
wrong what happened in the throne room but there's one guy up here shooting arrows this is what i
have to come back here for is this person think that this person claiming the throne is that what
they're saying i don't know is that what this person's saying no what are you doing on the
throne what are you doing sitting on the throne is that a place for somebody to be that's not the
king that just i think they deserve that's a pretty good question smite me please all right i'm only
doing a few more of these and then i'm done what was the one that had free content pun pun or fun
was it pun pun what ill chan that fun pun let's do tab to auto complete knock knock where sorry
mario princess is in another castle nothing in here well that was pretty good joke everyone you
broke my heart i made something for you no all right i'm i'm doing three more tps and that's it
tp andy no no that's a tp denny i was like people call me tp andy now but where are we oh this is
where i want to go you guys did a great job coming all the way up here and like hitting people with
arrows from this far up but you didn't expect that god was going to come up here and see what
you were doing so i mean i'm going to give you a choice a hand for the wand i will give you
50 dollars if you tp to me okay what's his name fabby ray tp fabby ray i did i did i just did
hey i'm right here where's the money where's the money where's the money where's the money
where's the money oh you're supposed to kill him dude how am i going to get 50 dollars now
what do you what do you want now i feel bad for saying what do you want you're my favorite
streamer man keep up the funnies makes me very happy every time you stream also please play
pajama sam on pc thanks for the 10 subs uh chef lazarus what about your house what's your shop
i can give credit like credit card due to hard times the shop is out of stock come back when it's
i'm a little richer see what you can get for those everything has a price miss the throne room miss
the throne room miss the throne room miss the throne room miss the throne room miss the throne
room all right i'm coming and this is the final tp no two more all right if you've read this you
oh chat 100 subs no i don't news and copter sour tower reach the top if you dare speaking
of subs thanks yes is online for five you made your own like mini game reach the top i'll try
dude this is pretty good this is pretty good parkour maze chicken prison only bad chicks go here
oh i don't want to be here tp for the battle of a lifetime i'm just changing channels on minecraft
tv that's what i'm doing first viewing platform great for viewing you got a big fucking tree in
the way and your neighbor has this antenna almost touching your house yeah this is a great view on
like your pretty on your page on zilla you just go like this and you zoom way the fucking and you
crop that right there and then you blow it up and you upscale it that if you see this spam sour
towers oh shit there's more damn look at this this is beautiful third viewing platform fuck you
oh that's not that's pretty good that's actually what's that over there i'll be back oh never
mind mr windmill if you made it this far leave something in the box oh cool this is somewhat
like a cool thing here how about one of these don't tell anybody i gave this to you this j
doesn't stand for germa my name also starts with a j well now it starts with i because there can
only be one of me secret viewing platform not so great for viewing that's pretty good view
it's up here too many people okay guys guys guys guys guys if you act like a diablo 2
server i am not going to join your tp if you come into my fucking game that i have with like
my brother and his friend and you spammed your diablo 2 item website i'm gonna want to take the
chat off bungee jumping platform no bungee rope wait don't do it then rip kit fisto he'll be
missed yeah play noita is the game recommendation master kit fisto is dead oh he's very much alive
he's dead he's absolutely going to die yeah he's gone that was pretty cool you know and all these
segments no not today no no maybe one okay just one that's it all right fine are you ready are
you ready let me join the diablo 2 virus one what's his name like me please there it is me
what's who is it thing t thing t what's her name tp for battle of a lifetime government love
what's your name i can't even see the name wait you're fucking kidding me you have why
do you have that name wait you own the name germa 985 get out of here you want me to get serious
what can identity theft on stream wait hold on this this person just did this person just like
i don't even rat tatooie waiting room yo germa wins marvel i don't even know what that means
i shat myself send help very cool please drink a baja blast on stream
germa do an irl stream i'm so friggin torched right now all right dude cool i mean you didn't
even what what did you do over here you made just a bunch of signs hoping that i would find them
there's no interesting house here or anything did you you made this you're my message for the king
i i'm so into this like changing channels on minecraft thing what you got sick house apparently
past streamers show theater riot people are spamming dude come to me i have a great game
recommendation that's not what this is it's not like oh i'm gonna be teleporting around looking
for game recommendation okay shit what's his name what's the game paper of mario for the nintendo
oh we germa but it really was just a game recommendation absolute psycho in the throne
all right i'm not gonna kill you i'm not gonna kill you i'm just gonna push you off
i'm not gonna kill you i'm just gonna push you off if you survive you survive
all right you lived please i'm crying i'm i've heard germa please i'm crying spamming works
okay let's see let's see if we're gonna ban this person from chat no it doesn't because
i don't know everyone started doing it i don't even know who you are you're not the only person
spamming tp for farmers guild throne room you got it worst castle 2020 i mean i don't i don't think
it's the worst castle i've ever seen panic room okay yeah uh panic now i wouldn't want to be in
here don't you know uh everyone that thought that was a good idea playing survival and left for dead
you all go in the bathroom once the tank shows up you all die seems like a good idea good stream
ger me must thank you that was the original meta for left for dead because nobody understood
never scored jumped from here at the end of stream saint moped is die you just jumped off
what the fuck this dude just literally just jumped off of the castle why why did you do that
why did you do wrong person throne room so wait that person lied he forgot defend your throne room
i'm coming hold on tp dick dastardly richard all right i'm here oh oh yeah nice okay cool i'm
gonna swing swing swing swing go ahead oh you go you will what's that what's that sword made out of
boy pond yeah boy pound you kill him and i swear oh now you're in deep trouble and stay out how
many people died we got rid of them still wrong person you haven't helped the people stuck in the
maze i'm so addicted to this i'm sorry okay are we going late i just want to like let me ask
everybody over here are we like going late here should i like end this i'm addicted to doing this
okay not easy being the king tp to me sure kid an idiot i'm gonna let you live you get to live
if you with your bare hands get us out of here if i see a tool i thought we were like 5 000 feet
below the other surface okay yeah you're good i thought we were like two miles down near bedrock
okay let me see to me to me you keep confusing the fuck out of me help auto help the auto statue
is burning who am i tp-ing to keep farmers get from them i'm dying okay hey we'll do that one
to the farmer high council nice skin for the high farmer lando brando yeah you were a little
premature and he died from it a little premature a little premature yeah you tried and then you're
your engineer over there uh it's okay i'm invincible this is what you wanted so bad
yeah well now king false king by the way get on in there you're going to be killed by your own
contraption oh you know what who did that come to my house come to my house all right only a few
more i'm a tp please you never answered my question uh no but super paper mario i'm not
gonna play it yet be to me tp to me for the hell what do you just do you abandoned me in the maze
you know that's how you hide that that's how that's how that gets hidden how did you guys get here
this guy made a portal to the nether so he could trap me here well it worked and then he jumped
into the lava and died tp to dave cap okay incredible marble for ios comes out october 8th
i solo developed it i have no marketing budget i am sorry thank you i think you'll like it though
it's pretty fun okay sure you're gonna get this opportunity i want a series of signs that are you
explaining the game how it works how many players what we can expect when we play i'll be back in
five minutes i wanted you to play pajama sam not paper mario come to me or i unsub dude okay you're
gonna start holding that over my head now tp to me tp tp already oh man i can't even read it
i need to store emergency i can't even read this this is going too fast this is shark tank it really
is minecraft shark tank i'm ready to be good okay i'm just going to pick one of these out i have no
idea who tp already i can't even see i gotta get a first or second word uh i came this little
chat down i have no idea how to do this i can't read any of this how's your junior i think wait
what diving board emergency emergency whoa what holy shit that's awesome wow now that was fun
that was really i was worth the teleport yeah thanks for that that was worth the teleport
that's pretty sick all right what do you got go sit on the throne you sobbing this is me crying
i'm so sad jerem i'm crying right now why psycho streamer throne fuck you jerem you abandoned me
for a man you abandoned me in a maze for four hours i almost died i was eating dirt and sucking
water out of moss and grass you could have did slash die all right fine i'll sit on it i'm
sitting on it how do i sit on it is there a way to sit do you forget where the switch is you know
you're not gonna drop me in lava i think you're surprised i'm still here where'd you go oh it's
the penis guy's house okay yeah i should have killed him all right tp what time is it right now
i'm only doing this for another 15 10 minutes tops grant me this one wish okay i didn't expect you
to come but can you give me creative i want to fly yeah give lon 0005 creative yeah one minute
and then take it off there my tp i made you i don't know who that is but okay let's see free
stuff very fun come to me or i'm gonna unsub there's a lot of people that are going to do
that apparently i'm gonna go back to germa 985 or no apparently we're going to germa's son
your father germa loves you he wasn't done he was setting it up he wasn't done he wasn't done with
his joke oh i'm so sorry we have into the wrong germa once upon a time there was a man named
jeremy he's but a humble e-clown playing video games on twitch one day jeremy decided to torture
his viewers he created hundreds of mazes and forced his viewers to traverse through them
it took them years of pain and suffering play lego racers make this tp i'm praying all right
all right i'm gonna i'm gonna start to get bored of this in a minute i'm getting bored
i want something i need something good boar i'm getting bored tp me i'm paying my bills to you
all right come on let's go dave cap all right dave what do you got all right here we go let's
find out okay this sounds like super monkey ball too play that instead have you ever had a marble
work or marble run toy as a kid you will recognize incredible incredible marble you have marbles
roll down plastic slides and earn money for building cool marble slides you spend the money
to build more and better slides and you upgrade them to earn more not your time not time for your
ad to earn more it's single player free to play no pop-up ads you can pre-order now at you can't
click that in credit marvel dot com ios october 8th android pc coming later this year the game
defies physics and it's just fun to watch you'll love it chat read homestuck it's great i don't
think this is you anymore give us a wink please in credit marble that's right guys all the
germamites check out in credit marble on october 8th on the ios store and android and pc coming
later this year if you've had fun when you were with a kid when you had fun when you were a kid
playing marbles and making plastic slides was where's the last one we're going to for my tp
please what's the bills guys no i'm paying i'm paying you my bills i gotta go to that person
can we pull that person out of it that is i can't see who's the one that's saying please i pay my
bills to you tp to me i can't read it i'm gonna pull out a letter here i saw this all right what
do you got young pal penis bernie sanders play roblox bernie sanders women's shopping bernie sand
is this supposed to be bernie sanders disclaimer not actual size oh it is supposed to be bernie
sanders okay tp already there's tears tp already tears tears tears tears tears i can't read your
name man i'm sorry i'm trying these tp tears i can't even read it man there's so many names
okay like you know the matrix when they show like the weird matrix
particle effects that's what i'm seeing when i'm looking at the names so retro
hold on what does it say what is this oh you guys went to the skybox oh i see very very cool i like
the skins too guys the statue of me the person to jump off i didn't even see it on camera look at me
tp look at me tp x e e all right click nobody talk in the chat i'm crying um you're gonna have
to cry i'm sorry pink boo i'm having so much fun doing this it's the giant rat oh cool hold on
really cool great job good build poggers rat pog yeah it's pretty fog actually is really good
yeah it is it is pretty good oh we got to see the other side of the puppet where your hand goes
all right to the campsite swift my mother doesn't like how much you talk about your ass monkey s
monkey s you i don't even you do i didn't write this one but fair why not he is dummy thick also
end stream and play darts in real life silver okay this has to end i have to stop doing this
why is it so addicting joke behind germ germa ftk stream okay what about it i don't get it
am i sitting on something oh it's a toilet i see it's a toilet yeah you get two i hit a mod with
that that was supposed to be you all right i am literally doing three more of these and then
that's it we're out of here i see campsite okay last minecraft stream you killed me and let my
friend live we never forgot and i hate you for it i clipped it and we re-watch it all the time
start clipping now where's your friend where's your friend they're gonna stay alive i want to
find them where's your friend i want you to remember this too is that your friend right there
germa germa germa germa well let's look at this house this is actually kind of oh i like this
house i shouldn't have killed that person jesus what the hell what is in here this is awesome
nobody touch this no no no this is like wheat farm don't eat this leave this alone this is
his like this is his farm replace that is a pretender on the throne killing us all right
i'm gonna go to s90 we do not open dude this person has an entire underground house sex room
whatever anal demons okay well i'm we've got to get out of here we got to get out of this one
we got to get out of this one this one is it this one's a t.o.s uh okay this is we're getting to
t.o.s potential sign this house is fucked what even what even is this what even is this for
this is scary what's this like scary thing up here see that what's the scary thing
it's a dungeon it's a sex place groundhog day tim allen jeremy jeremy germa what's up
dp to me and i'll make my firstborn and name my firstborn map after you okay all right was
it was it mitch mitchell all right mitchell what do you got germa i've been a fan of yours
since 2012 try freedom force on steam i think you'll love it it's a superhero rp let's get
let's just get get it over with omega lull in chat one of the default costumes look like a b.a.
this is i'm changing channels in minecraft but i break every tv we got what do you got on the
first day germa paid twenty dollars for a potato server on the second day germa built the server
using a gtx 570 none of this is true on the third day germa shat his pants and became king that
could be my paypal is in my okay germa poo pants you're gonna link your hold on a minute
you're gonna link your paypal yeah all right okay here's my game that's going on the app store
hey like germa's farted germa's stupid but like linking your paypal come on man come on dude you
can't he wants me to you want me to kill you too i'm not gonna do it i'm gonna let you live
with the fact that you wanted you know what i hope you get at least fifty dollars that's the last
one i'm gonna do here we go tp please please i'll give you a 10 000 subs a nice that would be fun
wouldn't it i want to be the guy born to be the one guy please i can't even read man i'm sorry i
have to pull them out randomly i see cat at girl this is my lava hot tub sorry i don't have anything
interesting just wanted to take the time to say you have brought me genuine happiness and you
should be proud play trials in tainted space it's all right it's the temperature's pretty good
i know i would say this is kind of like medium to hot why don't you come in and try it it's not bad
yeah come on come on let's have let's sit in the hot tub and hang out what was this person's name
you should try out botnik it's an ai that generates scripts articles books reviews
that even just created a choose your own adventure book created by the ai
okay so this is a church craft any bread here cool this is not a small home but it'll be a compact
one humble house to peasant crairy play ace attorney funny man solve crime god bless our
gracious king thanks for hosting this it was fun i wouldn't call this a church as much as i call
this your house bread here have some tulips and hey i'm telling you right now you don't want to
get rid of this put this on this is literally the golden chest plate like the super enchanted one
put it on make sure nobody takes that from you i'm too church this wasn't church love your streams
man saw two baby also play meet the robinsons i've been watching since your team fortress keep up
the good work this is donation messages these are just like bit messages don't forget to leave a
donation on your way out saw two baby play meet the robinsons this is just recommended bit messages
please take your seat all right i am the priest you have to pay attention to me please fireman
says trans rights okay jerma sucks breakfast in america by super tramp jerma get your duck i
didn't mean to scam poopy what i'm supposed to hang out in here wasn't it supposed to church
there's the there's the bills guy found him this person says he's paying all of his bills to me so
let's see what he wants look in here okay open block of iron block of iron chain boots well the
sniper has a gift all right hold on what what are you just giving this to me is this for me oh well
i mean like i appreciate the gesture but iron kind of looking for blue in here not necessarily
iron or anything it's all yours yeah i mean it's it's cool it's all right if they were if they were
blue like they were diamond or let me know i'd be like pog i'd be like pog champ this is still like
fun this is cool though i'll take one ungrateful i'm just kidding i'm gonna take them all and i'm
gonna shower my peasants with it whatever the guy with the 64 dynamite by the way this is actually
a ridiculous amount of iron don't you need like 50 iron to do this is chainmail better than oh
it goes on top no it doesn't okay getting to the we're actually getting to the actual end all right
clueless sniper what he got like corona trigger probably at some point these flowers are for you
flower the king flower the king these flowers are for me okay cool thanks sniper nest snipers
only what's in the sniper nest play tf2 on pc it's a fun class-based shooter with tons of
maps and game modes did i mention it's free sounds like a kind of cool game karma all right
come on dude my store is dying here we go where this is it this is the end this go this shop
red is free germa play runescape i can't even carry that stuff man here you want some iron
take some of this iron so what do you do here all right demon i'll take pity you had ended
and furfer demon and furfer that's it that's pretty good piss shop this my base i made with
my new friend sorokio he had to leave before the stream started but i wanted to give him a
shout out here all right nice who are you for halloween flash what's down here wrong person
that was a wrong person what was the person the most last person's name wait why is there a 984
now sufan okay a rare green crystal it's my blacksmith order kill him who am i killing
kill him is somebody behind here somebody said kill him jim i told me to kill this guy i don't
know why please come all right pink goat play minecraft ost right so we've waited waiting
room yo germa wins mar i was already here yeah you yeah you weren't here when we went to this
we've already been here we found this accidentally you're breaking my heart you said you tp i did say
that all right what do you got you're breaking my heart i am here oh it's thanos okay what do
you need what do you want to show me all are welcome okay replace the trees please i'd be
down no way partner holy pillar of germa play donkey kong country too speaker's podium afk
playing league but you deserve this you let that guy in your house gamer all hail our true king
the sunflower germa hups poo classic this pretty sick house what's this e in recess i swear to god
the recess stream cool zone four i didn't finish it yet my blacksmithing order all right all right
there was um somebody reminded me there was somebody uh s90 something s90 something no game
request fuck you let me out let's fucking go let me out me in four days i how did you get over here
soofan okay how did you even get through this this is a hacker let's fucking go all right well
i'll get you out no you don't know fucking leave them leave them all right soofan i mean he's
trapped over there that's like whatever hey what do you got s90 55 we yep i'll get it after this
germa what is it about jump off this everybody said you're gonna go to s90 i will so what is
this for oh i need my pickaxe it's the blacksmith right i gave the pickaxe all right is my order
done holy shit nice and i'll give you a block of iron and a block of iron and a block of iron
for that awesome hell yeah let's get a selfie all right what do you got s90 i'm here the second
half of the stream is better than the first half lul sorry to the people that worked on it there
were just too many people chat if you see this can we get some germa tvs on the real though germa
you're my all-time greatest of all time the streamer just keep being cool made by twitch.tv
s95 we that's twitch.tv slash s905 we they are a dota 2 player and they dabble in minecraft from
time to time they also uh do irl content they uh go bowling and irl and stuff and they have a great
time it's pretty good just gave you a launch pad just gave you a launch pad go play dota 2 after
the stream is over please no game requests from me it's pretty yeah i mean it was fun it was an
experiment germa just please we want to see you what i didn't forget anybody right you're making
pixel art holy shit what oh man no that's i know that's okay that's awesome that's actually really
really well done other side that's so good it's almost done too no not micro what hey hey what's
up all right well hi hi germa by the way you should play rain world again it was fun thank you for
bringing joy to the world hey thanks balder back to the throne room all right here we go we're
gonna close it out here we're gonna tp to the throne room what's going on in here am i gonna
just start spamming right trigger again what's it going what do you want me to do and what's
happening in the throne room why do you hate me end the stream right now i'll okay i'll do one final
tp we're gonna go we're gonna go to viking get a selfie there we go selfie time can i get a tp
yeah we're gonna do it we're gonna go to viking now and sprite dude get your hair ready everybody
say cheese ready three two one see i'm not gonna do the thing that everyone thinks i'm gonna do
what's up all right you got it cool now we're gonna go to uh i forgot their names already
all right i forgot their names already i don't know viking all right all right what's up last
sign please don't read homestuck please i didn't plan on it the pog cabin it's not finished yet
all right true thanks for being so god damn funny entertaining my friends only watch streamers who
would never do this and they don't get why you're funny not sub but thanks been watching since tf2
your test tips tf2 video helped way back in high school through college germawalk germawalk thanks
man what you're saying is you're the only person out of your whole friend group that thinks i'm
funny yeah uh how many how many people are we talking how many like out of how many of people
10 20 because that would be 10 percent which is not very good margins seven that's still not very
good hey at least i got you though right at least i got you interesting art here come take a look
let's just uh look out the window gaze out the horizon we say look all the way out there
and okay whatever this guy has a question okay what's up dude dude's got a question what is it
what's the question you ever just think about where your hands are and what they're doing
they just sit there monkey ass all right what was the last one there was one more sorry i lied about
the 50 dollars i just knew you were greedy and we're gonna tp you come read my all right this
is it this is the true final one hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa craft
the series where i play minecraft this is going to be a single player let's play when i say let's play
i say that term pretty loosely because i'm an idiot in this game you're going to see lots of
fails you can see lots of triumphs at least i'm hoping so so grab yourself a nice hot cup of
coffee a cup of cocoa i got apple cider right here freshly brewed let me take a sip that's good cider
also uh love you germa make us genuinely happy now time to disconnect you thought you could hide
you thought you could hide all right i'll see you guys on monday for far cry one i did say that
thanks for participating everybody the server staying on this has been a giant ad for the
server it's not turning off they're going to close it for a few hours and change a few things they're
going to bring it back the server is just going to be online this is just a minecraft server it's
just a server so you can play on it this was a giant ad for this server we got about one guy
i did he hates sprite dude oh shit what are you guys doing i think i caught them in the
middle of something hey that's my stream you want to help all right i don't know what we're doing
but i guess i'm gonna help yeah we can end it here let me let me just uh yeah so uh i'm talking i'm
talking to i'm not talking to chat right now i'm talking to somebody else so when this turns off
in what like a few hours maybe will it be able to be joined again yeah so in a couple of hours
this is gonna turn back on and it's just gonna be available i'll probably check back in with the
server just to see what you guys have done sort of similar to what we just did right now because
that was fun that was actually really fun just going around seeing the weird shit people made
so i'll see you guys again on monday i'm gonna play far cry one i guess for some reason on stream
or your own time i don't know yeah on stream i would assume i'm gonna play it on stream i'll
have a backup in case i don't want to play it anymore raid raw is raw streaming right now
is ross actually live right now yes yes yes all right let's uh let's let's raid ross we played
with ross in the phasmophobia stream and they are what are they doing this is late night among us
i feel like i probably would really like this game i but i do will i i would probably hate it i would
like it in theory uh but yeah let's uh go show ross some love that we actually we played with them
and it was a lot of fun so uh um let me because i'm i need to be logged in my twitch let me see if i
can do this before you killed before you guys kill the stream because i am not streaming right
now guys weirdly enough we're doing this is a remote thing because we have people working cameras
and stuff so it's gonna be impossible so let me do this great is that gonna work it should yeah
all right thanks for watching everybody we'll see you that was me on the computer that was me
i grew a beard it's shared hallucination it was something it was there was a real fucking
that was a real something