Hey, what's up? Uh, dropping some frames here right in the beginning.
That's not a good sign. Stable now, I guess. Uh-oh. No, how you guys doing? What are we doing? Today,
we're gonna be doing something that's not the Nintendo vibe. I'm sorry. The vibe has not come
in completely yet. It'll all be here tomorrow, according to amazon.org, because I bought some
extra stuff. Uh, my room is not really... I can't just have the default vibe set up.
I had to get... fuck, we're dropping frames again. I had to get those stands, because
this room is not really... I can't really mount those things anywhere,
so I'm gonna have two stands that are in the corners pointing down, and they're not here.
On the ceiling? No, no. They're two, like, tripod stands that I have to screw those... um,
what are they called? The trackers? Not the trackers. They're like the little squares.
They're like boxes. I don't know what HTC calls them. Lighthouses, okay. Yeah.
But I'm excited. I'm excited to, like, VR my room for real, because the PSVR was fun,
but it was very... it was very limited. I had to, like, be sitting down. I had,
like, that small cord. I did have a lot of fun with PSVR, but I'm excited to kind of graduate
to the big boy machine, like, the vibe. The vibe looks better, it's more comfortable,
and it's more versatile, so I'm looking forward to it. So here's the plan. I got a new
schedule here for you. If we can stream today... I don't know why I'm dropping so many frames.
Let me make sure, like, nothing weird is going on here. I'm like, I got nothing going on.
Just kind of happens. But the plan is today... remember that species evolution game I was
talking about, like, a few days ago? Where you have to, like, make spore creatures, and they
eat each other, and mates, and they evolve? It looks really fun. It's called Species
Artificial Intelligence Real Evolution, I think. Oh, the second channel finally got to the
Boston to Vegas arc. Yes, it did. They're on a different timeline. Is this the game with the
annoying stock splash sound effect? No, no, no, no, no. This is not a... this is a PC game.
It's on Steam. There's just no... it's not a category on Twitch, so I can't... I can't even
change the category, because it's not on, like, the Twitch's directory or whatever. But we have a
kind of a different problem here, and that is... I guess it's one of those days where I'm going
to drop 10% of every frame. It's been, what, five minutes? That's why I'm kind of just sitting
here. I'm, like, waiting to see if this corrects itself. But... so I... let me get...
I gotta give you some information here. So the Vive did not come completely yet. I'm still
waiting on it. I am going to do the Vive stuff on Valentine's Day. So from Valentine's Day,
which is Thursday. So today is Tuesday. Yeah, so Thursday, Friday, Saturday is going to be the
Vive stuff, because tomorrow is my anniversary with Kim for two years. So we're going to go
have some fun. We're going to go do something. And so Valentine's Day, we're kind of doing,
like, a dual Valentine's Day thing here, where it's anniversary and Valentine's Day,
but it's not... not yet. That's where I'm going to be tomorrow. And I'm trying to
just swallow my anger right now. Like, as deeply into my stomach as I can.
I am, like, eating this anger. I am eating it. It's like it's a monster that keeps coming
out of my mouth and I keep chewing and swallowing back down. He's getting really angry at his
fucking anniversary. No. Just let it all out. No, it's not worth turning the stream off.
Try getting two ISPs at once. Somebody, like, pissed on the box or something, wherever it is.
How do you beat orphan across? There's a point where he goes
and you have to run away because he's going to make the whole place electricity.
Don't attack him when he does that. A lot of people just go in for the kill when he does
that and the whole place becomes electrified. You don't want to do that. That's how you get
yourself killed. All right, I'm going to attempt. I'm going to attempt here to open up the game.
But yes. Hey, look, there it is. Nothing tomorrow. Anniversary with my girlfriend.
And then we're going to do Thursday, Friday, Saturday with the Vive.
And then next week, I've got a PS3 game that I'm incredibly excited for.
It's a Safari game where you take pictures of animals. That's the whole game. It's not
Pokemon Snap. It's a PS3. It's called Africa with a K. I'm excited for it. But this game,
in particular, this is called Species Artificial Life Real Filler for Vive.
Is it what this one's called? No, no, no. I kid. This is going to be fun. This is going
to be cool. So how this works, I've kind of done a very basic look at this game.
You get a randomly generated seed, randomly generated world, and you have to essentially
watch and take care of and watch over slugs. These slugs then evolve over the course of
the game into anything. They mate with each other, they eat each other, and they can turn
into fucking anything. If you've seen the trailer of this game, I recommend you do,
because it looks wild. Yeah, that's how I feel right now. Yeah, that is the germ of Pluto
right there. That's how I feel right now with the internet being a piece of shit. That
actually does look like it. They could smell how they could just, I'm telling you, the
computers can hear this shit. But world style, we're going to just kind of do whatever
the defaults are for now. We might go a little deeper, but it's kind of been on the radar for
a little while since it came. It's an early access game, which I don't really like to play
early access games, especially on stream, because they could be void of content. There
could be like nothing here. That's why I don't really like to do them, but it looked
interesting enough where we could have a little bit of fun and it's freaking out.
It is, it is, it is. Why does my screen look like it's melting? It shouldn't. So I'm
going to have to save frequently. We're going to save frequently and get this gone.
Fucking internet, man. This is just like Happy Gilmore situation where like Bob Barker,
I'm just like, oh, why is the screen all red? Is it? Oh, actually I got to make a text
here. Hold on. Let me just text. I got to, let me text. I got to text somebody.
I'm going to give somebody a warning here. Texting in 2019. Now I'm, I'm giving,
I'm giving italics a warning because I think he was potentially starting his stream
in like a little bit here and it's like, well, I don't know. Be careful with that.
Texting and streaming. Yep. Sometimes. But all right, let's go. Let's just try. I can't sit
here and cry over spilt. Uh, I almost just said something that I would have regretted.
Uh, you could probably fill that in. I'm good. I think I'm getting better at that.
I'm getting better at that. Don't cry over spilled milk. Right. But I was going to say
cocks. Don't I've been, I've been getting very good at that. Just has to happen enough
times. All right. All right. So far I like it. Pretty good default. Oh God. This is a
little too loud. Didn't I turn the music down? I can't adjust it now. All right. So there we
go. There we go. So it starts out like this. We've got, all right. Okay. That's, that's
manageable. So new world. It's the same one we were just on. To me, this is not evolution
music. I'll be honest. This is like going down the tunnel in a third person driving crime game.
That is not Grand Theft Auto. All right. So I got controls to get time acceleration,
which is one, two, three. This is what I got to work with here. So everything starts off as
a slug. As you can see that everybody has like a Sims meter. So this is health,
this is food and this is stamina. Let's take a look and see where we want to go.
I think everybody starts off with the same thing and I get to choose kind of who mates with who.
The music just kind of abruptly stopped. That was a little odd, but okay. I think we're good.
That was really jarring. All right. So take a look. We got species. I can do, I think I can
like look at, there we go. Number of creatures, survival, not, I don't know. Age 60. How are they
aging this fast? I have it on like the, okay, there we go. Health capacity. Age out of 90. Why
do, how long do they live? It's cold blooded. 28 optimal temperature. What temperature is it
outside right now? Gluttony. Angry. He's about to die. Feed him quick. This is, I can feed
him. Food. All right. So food's going good. No, don't kill. When, when do they mate?
All right. Get these tutorials off the screen. There they are. What happens at 90? Do they
all just die? Physiology. Okay. This is just a few of the values defining physical structure.
So this shows how long the creature is before it dies. How tall it is, the volume, the mass,
the head scale. Good. We got a save point. Let's see overview. 62. They're very sleepy.
Anybody else like alive over here? I don't want to play with those guys. They're going to
die. What about these ones? Starving. Oh God. Okay. These are, these are,
I got to feed them. There we go. All right. So we're going to deal with these over here.
How do I make like food bins? Oh, you just can do it. How many times can I do this? How,
how many times can I do this? Okay. Cause this is their hunger meter and they know this is
stamina meter. Uh, 10 community subs just came in from whiff, whiff, sigh. Thank you.
Whiff, whiff, sigh. 10 community subs. Oh, whoa, this one's got bigger. This one got
bigger. What? How did this one get bigger? Oh, they, look, we have, okay, okay, okay.
But this is good. This is good. Forget about everybody else in the whole planet.
Sniff. Oh, hold on. They're multiplying. Omnivore. They eat grass. So what happens
when they run out of grass? Potato slugs. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I think we have,
no, they're just multiplying. Energy. Okay. So stamina, draining its stamina somehow.
I think they're just impregnating themselves. Yeah. They're like a single celled organism.
Genetics. A, C, G, T, T, T, G, T, T, T, G, G, G, G, G, T, T, T, T, T. I don't know what that
means. Uh, that's a placeholder. Okay. Okay. A more thorough explanation of the genetic
system will be implemented later today. It's a placeholder. Creature energy, health,
food, stamina. That sounds good. It's just a hash. It's everybody's password.
What happens when they come over to this species over here? Wait, they're all, they're
all the same species, right? This one dying. We have to focus on like just the big ones,
I think. All right. Hold on. Genetic engineering. Oops. Uh, well, I killed that one.
Why would you have feed next to kill? Genetic engineering, draw bones, animation, skin type,
secondary saturation. All right, hold on. What about like a brain? This one's going
to have a brain. Gluttony. Oh, I can change how they, how they feel. Aggression.
Hold on. Head, neck length, neck, neck length. Oh no. All right. Let's not get too carried
away yet. We need to have, this has to be natural. No, I can't make them like a tether
ball. Not yet. Um, just five. That's fine. It's got to be natural. Head scale. You can
do anything you want, huh? But I need them to evolve into each other. So head type.
Ooh, I can add. All right. Definitely have to have the underbite. That's pretty,
I like the underbite. Yeah. Underbite. No, that, that doesn't look right. We have to
start easy. I don't want it just to go crazy. Okay. Number of features. Number of facial
features. Face. Uh-oh. Uh, what about, what if I drop this back down to where it was?
All right. Face. Feature type one. A horn. Texture. Size. Okay. We're gonna, there'll
be a horn. All right. The next thing I'm gonna, I'm gonna make Spider-Man, I think.
No, stop. Just do it normal. Do it regular. Not yet. It's been like 20 minutes.
There they go. He's got eyes. Just keep, we're going to do slug and slug. Okay.
Tail. Um, give him a tail too. Give him like a little, like sausage casing for a tail.
That's all right. It's like a little snake thing. I'm gonna make the neck a little
thicker too. Size. Maybe a little bigger. Okay. Limbs. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to, we're going to go make another person over here and we're going to give them
arms. Uh, this is going to be called, gonna think of a good initial creature name. It's like
Slagonius, uh, Slagonius hornopolis. Whatever. Who gives a shit? This is our first creature.
The game crashed.
God damn it. When did it save? I had a creature made too. That sucks.
Where was it? It was too OP. No, it was this guy right here. All right, I can do it again.
Did it save it? There it is. Right there. We're good. Crashed again. Shit. God damn it.
Really? Is it too cursed? No, it can't be. Try it on somebody else. Export creature.
Slagonius hornopolis. Generate. Did it work? Is this, did it turn in? I don't see this. No,
this is, this is not it. That's not it, right? Are you going to evolve into that?
I don't, so I over writ. All right, hold on a second. Let's fucking do this one more time.
I overwrote it. All right. Well, let's, let's try this again. This has so much potential
if it worked. You understand? This is like, there's so many options. There's so much to do.
If I didn't crash the game five times in 10 minutes. All right, let's go with that. Let's
see if I can get it to work. That looks good. I'll give it a tail too. And a long tail. There
we go. All right. Generate. Slagonius hornopolis. It doesn't matter if it doesn't have a horn.
How about this one? Crashed again. Fuck. Hold on. Let me try something else here.
I'm going to like go to like a different version. I had like the new like update
and I'm going to just try to do it without that update. Let's try it again. Just do something
easy. Just make it like a fucking tube sock for all I care. Generate. Shlomo char. Who cares?
All right. It worked, right? Which one was it? It was this one right here, right?
I can't tell. Did it do anything? Oxygen. Needing, it needs oxygen. Are there too
many people? There's too many bugs. Speed up the time. All right, which one was it? It was
this one right here, right? Let me look at the genetics. Overview. Swim stamina. Why is it dying?
Why is this thing dying? What the fuck was that? Why did that just happen? Did you just kill it?
They were eating each other. You just killed my creation. When you got a creature selected,
you can see their state over there. People are just dying. What?
What? Genetics. Physiology. This is just like how hard and long it is. Energy. This is how
hungry it is. Species of a creature. Energy. I read these already. Creature genetics. This
is a base for it. Premium specimen is like the original list one here.
Gene editor. Design creatures by specifying their genetic values.
Synthetic genomes can be exported and used as target genomes in the nursery.
Okay, hold on. Where's the nursery? Nursery, nursery, nursery, nursery. All right. Welcome
to the nursery. Here you can experiment with artificial selection pressures. Drop in a creature
or two and then design or import a target genome with the gene editor. The nursery will
encourage creatures similar to the target to breed while humanely killing off the rest.
Drag a creature in here. Capture a creature with a move tool. Okay. Why are they on fire?
Why are they all burning? What? That's not the music you should be playing.
There are too many of them. We have to just find the one that's going to survive.
All right. It's definitely not these ones. Is everybody dead? No. There's a whole thriving
colony over here of burning insects. Drop the temperature? Cool it down. Why are they just
burning? Delicious meat. They've been burnt apparently. All right. I need to at least make
one monster. So here's the nursery. So, okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Where's the healthiest
one? All right. You look pretty healthy. Come here. Get over here. Welcome to the nursery.
Here you can experiment with the artificial light. Yeah, I know. I'm trying to grab
somebody. Okay. No, I don't want, I want the one underneath you. The one that's on fire.
It's too hot. All right. You look good. Come here. In nursery. All right. We'll get a drone
coming over here. I need another one. How are you doing? You're almost dead, but we'll,
we'll keep you alive a little longer. No, no. Stop breeding in the nursery.
Wait a minute. Where the fuck did you come from? How did you get that mouth?
What the fuck? Why? Why are they exploding? Why can they not live in here?
What? It's too hot. I made that mouth. Oh my God. Okay. Nursery. Applied radiation.
Edit target. Okay. Let's just go for, let's go for a long neck again.
I can't even see what it looks like, but whatever. Generate it. Everyone exploded.
And there's no sounds of the drones smashing into everybody. Is it still too hot?
Why do you want it at negative two? Now it's too cold and now it's too hot. I need land fertility.
Increase the fertility of the land. They need more. They've been eating too much.
We need oxygen. I told you we're looking into the petri dish. So we need more fertile land.
Increase water fertility. Look, we're just going to raise the water level. No, no, no,
lower the water level. That'll kill everybody. Okay. We'll, we'll do more land fertility.
They eat it as soon as it gets here. It's just overpopulation. I, I don't have any more.
All right. How do I get it? How do I do like a plague? They're breeding too fast.
And this is just one section of the island. All right. What about these? Look at these guys.
These guys look okay. Let's manually feed these guys. I'm going to get this. I'm going to
figure this out. Chode diagram. Rover. Allow you to drive rovers. Okay. Rovers. Add a rover.
All right. This is the fucking what I'm looking for here. Feed. Feed creatures with high stats
and big size. The fuck is this? Oh, no, no, no, no. High stats. Size. Drive. Go.
Okay. Let's make like fucking four of them. No. Kill population when there's a, when total
creatures are higher than 200. We got to start to mitigate some of this statistic. Okay. When
there's two, drive that around. Go. Feed the creatures with low hunger. Right. So somebody's
feeding them to keep them alive. And one of them is killing them when there's too many.
This is very counterproductive, I think. Feed for stomach high, stomach low. Stamina diet.
Reach mass. Armor. Insulation. HP. Energy. Energy low. Right. That's what we're looking
for. I got the wrong game listed because this game is not on Twitch.
I cannot make this game a selectable game in the, in the directory. So it's diagonal with closest
damn thing I could. All right. Low energy. Go. What the fuck? Hold on. I have to drive this
thing? It's already dead. How do you feed? I have to, why wouldn't I just use my mouse?
Don't damage them. They're very expensive. All right. Well, get me out of this.
Let them do it on their own. Okay. So we've got a lot of issues. Okay. Yeah, they don't
have to do it. They're good. They're good. They're good. They're good. See the killing and
come on. I need to see that from a different angle. Details and stats. How do I get out of
the fucking rover? I got to get out of the rover. Diagram nursery rovers ecosystem mode.
Okay. There we go. Species selection mode. Creature selection mode. How do I get the
fuck out of the rover? Toggle indirect. Okay. Toggle camera mode. What the fuck?
All right. We're good. Showing thoughts. All right. So now I got a rover blasting around,
feeding and killing. How are we doing over here? This, this thing is murdering everybody.
This doesn't seem correct. Maybe I should just put this one on. No. Okay. I need to put this
one on feed because this one is killing them before they even have a chance. No. Stop that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. How do I control you? Stop. Which one is killing?
No. Feed. When creature count. No, no, no, no. Feed trees with low energy. Feed trees.
Do it. All right. They're not going to be killing them anymore. I need to, I want to make
something. How are you doing? This one looks healthy. What about in the nursery? Well,
wait a minute. We got, we got a mutation here. This one's bigger. This one's really big.
Why the fuck did it just die? Keep this one alive. How's it doing? Fatigue needs sleep.
How you doing on temperature? Build a fence. Place a climate control. This can be used to heat,
cool. All right. Fuck this. What's wrong with that fence? I need to keep one person alive.
Okay. And a climate control device. Temperature. Target value of zero. In here. Create it.
All right. Now, fertility. Target value of, um, I don't know. That's fine. Does
a guy get an ecosystem in here? Now it's time for a germ or rumble. No, it's time for like a,
I need one person to live so I can turn them into, how are we ever going to make Spider-Man?
That's never going to happen. This much pollution. Uh, three fertility. They're both
fertility. Do I have to like change that? Are they both fertility now? Look at all this
fucking pollution. Look. Okay. This. Look at it. Look at it. We got like a, we got
like a cookie monster here. All right. Feed them. Feed them. How do I feed? Get off. Out.
Out. Come here. All right. You're, you're in the fence. Good. We have two cookie monsters.
Why are you dead? Why did you just eat him? The baby just ate the adult. The baby just ate
the fucking adult. And now I got to keep these guys alive. More fertility. Why are you eating
each other? I don't understand. Okay. Now let's go to genetic engineering. You eat him
and I'm fucking going to throw you in the river. Don't even look at me like that. Did
you just look? Do you know what you were doing? Needs oxygen. How do I increase the
oxygen? Artificially inseminate the selected creature with save DNA from another creature.
You got it. Don't crash. We're going with long neck? No, the one with the legs.
Target number to import. Ready? Did it work? I don't think it worked. Let's do times two
speed. It's got legs. A species has split into two species. This happens naturally. Wait.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. A species has split into two species. This happens
naturally when there are no longer any members of either population that can breed with
members of the other. One of your wild species encompasses a lot of biodiversity. Being part
of the same species doesn't necessarily mean two creatures are capable of breeding.
Rather, it means that they are connected by a chain creature that can. When creatures at
either end of the chain are genetically incompatible, the species is known as a
ring species. Okay. Well, I didn't do that though. I gave him legs and I gave him a
tail instead. I need to increase the fertility here. The dying target value of. Oh my God.
We used to. Why are you doing this? Uh, 10. What? No. What? Temperature? No. Of 10. Fertility.
That's good. Whatever. What? I'm so confused. Let him out. Let him out. Okay. Okay. We got
a first mutation. Well, what's going on over here? No one has evolved. They just got green.
That's all that happened. It's because they've been eating too much grass.
What a mutation. This is the equivalent of when you eat too many carrots.
It's just a bunch of fucking mouse turds. All right. How do I go from mouse turd to Spider-Man?
No. Okay. I'm going to release them. You ready? They're free. Go. Keep an eye on this one.
This one's got legs. This one's got legs. Feed this one. He's cold. They're cold. They're
cold. They're a little cold. I'm going to sneeze. I fucking couldn't get it. Whatever.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Oh, this one's got a neck. Okay. We're starting
to get necks. A species has lost. A species has been lost forever. Extinction is a fact of
life. In the long term, only a very small percentage of species will survive. Even for
those lucky few, survival is often a phyric victory. The chances that their descendants will
even resemble them are slim at best. What species was eradicated?
We need to keep the ones alive that are... Not the... Okay. The ones that are eating each
other. Here's a good leg curve with the frog right here. Damn it. That's why you need to
keep them in a pen because you can't control what's going on. I need an overview here. Hold
on. Give me like a... Give me like a fucking... That's a chart. Head scale. Genetics. No.
Species. What about over here? Yeah, these are all part of the same species. What are
they doing over here? Are they developing into something else? No. Because I haven't been
fucking with them over there. All right. Where the hell? Where am I? I have no idea.
What the fuck was I? Can I like a quick go to this person? Here it is. All right.
What about the nursery? I need to have like fucking... What we got? We got a new color
scheme here? Oh, all right. All right. Genetic engineering. Let's... I need to make something.
We got the watermelon creature. Let's go with... Let's go with torso. Hold on. Torso.
Chest height. I need to start making people with legs. Otherwise, they're going to keep
going like this forever. Okay. The head has to be higher. Where do we go? We're going to
make like a praying mantis. The head needs to change. Give it a neck. Hold on. Let's get
the claws, stingers. Limb step size. That's how big it is. Limb 11. Okay. Limb type. Let's see.
Oh, shit. Okay. Hold on. Here we go. There we go. I'm going to name this one the boxer.
Length. No, no, no. Wrong, wrong, wrong. It's this one. Too much. Too much. Too much.
I'm making a silent hill monster. We need some like shoes. I don't know which one this is.
Oh, God. Okay. Limb tip. Here we go. It needs to have shoes. Barbecue shoes? Limb tip. I need
to make a different... Limb tip. Oops. Oh, yeah. For sure. I got to get rid of the...
This looks awful. Limb... What's it? Limb 21? Limb 21's got to go. That's better. All
right. So this is going to be called... We just need to... We got to throw some weird shit in
here. We got to get this going. Generate. This one's going to be called... Okay. Where
is my shoes of rocket? Right here, right? So we're in the nursery. So let's go to the nursery.
And we're going to apply this. Select target. Target is shoes of rocket. Import. Okay. There
it is. Let's see if it happens. Apply radiation. Apply like fucking three times radiation.
Okay. That's good. Is it dead? Is that one dead? That one's dead. Is it? Are these... Okay. Why
are they just exploding? Where's my Sims meter? They're suffocating. Get some oxygen in here.
How do I get oxygen inside of here? What the fuck are the rovers even doing?
Where's my rovers? Feed creatures with high size. Feed... It's all feed. They're feeding them.
They're not killing them. Not supposed to be. Feed the trees. How do I get more trees? Wait
a minute. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Freeze time. Nursery. Got it. Right there. Get the radiation down. Target is selected.
Go for it. You need to survive. This one's coming out. Come on. What the fuck? What is happening?
Why do you keep blowing up into... They come out and explode. I didn't give them explosion. Okay.
They got feet though. They do have feet. Need oxygen. How the fuck do I get oxygen in here?
How do I get more trees in here? All right. I'm getting you out of here. Need more
fertility. You guys all right? Everybody like... No, he's just dying.
They keep coming out and they keep fucking instantly dying. Cold bask in sun. Walk to
location. Feed the trees. Look at all these trees have maximum energy. There's like plenty
of trees in here. Look at all the energy they have. Max energy. Max energy. Max energy. All
right. I'm getting you out of here. Time to get to the real world. Oxygen. Oxygen. We need more
fertility. It's too cold. He's drowning himself in water. No. Stop drowning. Why are you
drowning yourself? Get out of there. No. Why? What are you doing? Why are you doing that?
He wants out of the simulation. I took him out. Instantly just instantly goes into the water
to die. Oxygen. Seeking oxygen. What am I missing here? Hold on. Genetics. Energy.
Excess pregnancy. Okay. Diet is an omnivore. Luke warm blooded. Optimal temperature
is 24. It's aerobic. Okay. I've yet to have a meaningful evolution except for I just
they're just that's why they explode when they have babies. Is that what it is? Are they
having are they getting too pregnant? I'm just gonna ultra fast forward. Uh oh. Sorry about
that lag. It's apologizing for the lag. It's very CPU intensive. Do we have anybody else
that's like mutating correctly? I need to put a species cap. I think it was his own
the default. Like okay should I make like a new world and all right here's what we're
gonna do. This is gonna take like 40 in-game days to get what I want. There are just
two yeah there are too many rabid shits. This thing doesn't even have a head. Oh yeah
it does. Set okay hold on somebody's gotta set all the mutation settings in the world
creation menu to maximum if you want actual results. Oh okay. Well that was a fun interesting
like how does this game work. Let's try it again. Number of creatures. Uh let's go with like a
a hundred? Fifty. What's the maximum that I should have? Fifty? Okay mutation rate. What is
the maximum? This mutation rate is high enough to completely obscure the effects of natural
selection. Offspring may not resemble the parents at all. Three. God damn it. It's like
being at the gas station. A high mutation result in a lot of genetic drift. Okay breeding
range. The maximum genetic distance a creature can be from another creature while still allowing
them to mate. Put this a little higher then right? Like 40? 50? Automatic population control is on.
Okay anyone can just mate with anyone right? Tree growth rate. Yeah we want I want more of
these fucking things. Forest density. A little bit more density. Temperature sensitivity. Fertility
sensitivity. Speed multiplier. This is fine. Damaging rate is one. Temperature loss.
I think these are fine. So we got much better temperature noise map. Temperature average.
Fertility average. Should I make this higher? Yeah I got like way more vegetation and shit.
Lower the creature cap even more to what like 20? 25? What if they die?
You're making an ice world? Max efficiency. I think this is okay. Oh okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait I see what you're saying. Creature cap is at 3200. Yeah that's a lot. How about like 100?
200? 3200. How many starting creatures are on the map? Let's go with like 10
and let's have like 500 are allowed. World size that's fine. Get 10 starting creatures.
I'm ready to get my shit together. This looks good all right. Turn off the tutorial messages.
I don't think I need them anymore. Max fertility. 350. Starting creatures.
We have a choice here. Predator and prey. Aquatic. Random. Or blank. So is it going to be
random shit? Oh my god. I mean do I really want to work with random? Not yet. Not yet.
Let me just try doing it with like me really trying. That's gonna make fucking all kinds
of fucked up characters. We'll do that later. I need to try to make my own creature. So what
was the last thing? Breeding range. Lower it a little bit to like what 20? God damn it.
Whatever. 1999 is what you pay in like the steam store for 80 percent of all the games
anyways. All right let's go. You ready? Higher mutation. We'll get there gradually.
Here we go. So where are this 10? Here they are. Already they're like already already
dying in the ocean. I got three. Where are the other ones? Did they spawn in a random place?
Fuck them. Who cares? We're gonna these we'll have here we go. Seeking oxygen.
Well get out of the fucking water then. You can feed them all like that. Where are the
other ones? Is there? All right found one. Get over here. Okay we got sleeping. It's a little
too hot. Wants to go swimming. Wants to go swimming. Oh they're getting bigger. What
about the ones over here? All of you get like in the same spot. There's too many of you already.
They're already breeding in extreme levels. Temperature up a little. Where are they going?
All right so let's try. Let's get some of you. That's because the fertility rate.
They're just going to overpopulate this immediately.
Okay just let them do whatever they're gonna do. Seeking oxygen. Seeking oxygen. Seeking oxygen.
They've already ruined the earth here. It's just a virus. All right get in here.
Let's make some stuff happen in here. At least the truth. All right no no this is
just ridiculous. Hold on. I gotta do this one more time. New world. Fertility rate. Oh my
god. I picked that slug up. Put it in the den and 15 babies came out. Wait this is fertility of the
the land isn't it? Variation. Let's keep it at one. This is vegetation. Breeding range.
Ecosystem modifiers. World size. Creature detail. 0.05 will not work. Mutation rate
up. Oh they can make it so they have to be sexual to reproduce. So they're reproducing
just on their own. Okay so they're self reproducing. So now we have 10. They have to mate
to do anything at all. This is going to keep the numbers low. We brought the fertility down.
Tree efficiency can stay on. Mutation rate is good. All right let's try it again. Good luck.
They have to have sex. I'm looking for one. I have 10 here. I should just have two. Where are
they? Okay they're... this one's eating. All right that's good. What are they? What's wrong
with you? Armornus? Armornus. What does armornus mean? Cold basking in the sun.
Okay the tropical rainforest. Looking for others. There are others but where are they?
Okay. How are you guys doing over here? Okay. Somebody already had sex. No don't do that.
Okay so you exploded and out came. No no don't just...
Well you are having a lot of children over here. Much more than over here.
All right let's try to make something happen. We could just watch.
No let's get somebody. Come here. You. Get inside of the nursery. Wherever the hell it is.
Come here. Get over here. You. Genetic engineering. I'm gonna make something. We're
gonna have to be a target. Make it bigger. Like maybe like a three. Five maybe. Let's make
it a different color. That didn't really work. Okay what about? No that's not doing anything.
Whoa. Okay we're gonna have like a caterpillar. Caterpillar fuzz. That looks good.
Optimal temperature. Just like fucking one. Torso. Chest height. All right now I'm gonna get...
I'm gonna make something. I'm gonna make stingray. Or a broom. No I'm not...
That doesn't look right. Stomach. I gotta make it wider. It's disgusting. Well it's not done.
It's grotesque. Well it's part of the evolutionary process. Length of pregnancy.
That's fine. Litter size. That's fine. Positive values are carnivores. It's gonna eat things.
Torso rotation. Oh yeah that's what I'm talking about. Okay hip height. Stomach width. Limbs.
All right I gotta change those. Looks good. Limb ending type. What's the thing from Half
Life? I'm gonna make those things from the greetings to you and what the guys that do
magic powers. The Vortigaunts. Yeah I'm gonna make the Half Life to like magic power monsters.
Okay this would be a little thicker. Triceps are a little bigger. Biceps are a little bigger.
All right Lim 11. Let's go. Why is Lim 11? It's a weird name for it.
I changed my mind. I'm gonna make General Grievous now. Which one was more grievous?
28. No. That looks no. It's like an elephant. The first one I had was pretty grievous.
That's kind of grievous. Make it a little longer. Okay it's gonna be more upright though.
Rotation. Where's the rotation there? Torso right. Torso rotation. Oops okay.
Uh that's this is the legs now. Yeah this is the forest giant boss.
Check this out. Watch this. Oh no never mind. Shit. How do I get back to? I need to rotate
these. I need to rotate these. Please stop. Burn the computer. Just wait. Hold on. Holy fuck
that looks horrible. Oh all right I like that. That's not bad. Neck. Has a neck. Neck length.
Where's this neck? You guys see a neck here? Uh oh this is the limbs. Oh it's fucking with me.
I clicked on neck. Neck. Okay there we go. Neck length has neck. I think it's just one. Yeah
okay I need to make the thickness of the neck bigger. Stop making it do that.
Okay neck slope. Are you guys gonna hate this? It's just one of those snakes. The
fireworks snakes. All right bring it down. Even more. Even more. Even more. Okay so it's
like that. Good. It uses his neck as another limb. Looks good. Head. Head scale. You can just make
a giant ball. Head type. I feel like there are actual bugs and shit in the world that look like
this. That one's horrifying. Look at the eyes. That's eyes and mouth. Yep. Pretty great dead
space character you got here. Brain. Uh let's see. Sex drive. Climate sensitivity. No you find
empathy. Reduces the chance. Yeah like give it some empathy here. Risk taking. High risk,
high reward food sources. Okay laziness. Aggression. No it's not a coward. It's not
that aggressive. It's not that lazy. It's not that gluttonous. Okay number of features. Facial
features. We got a couple here right? Let's go two. Feature one. Which one is it though?
Feature. What is it looking at here? Feature size. Feature type two. I think it's just not
big enough. Holy shit. Okay it's got a giant hat on. Okay well it's wearing a shell on its head.
Make it very aggressive and very lazy. Why is it all these weird shells? It's got a birthday
hat on. All right it's gonna wear a birthday hat. Okay. Face. That's good. I think this
is a good a good start. It'll mutate into something else. Generate. Did it work? I can't
tell. That's never gonna successfully exist. Did it not do anything? I don't get it. We're in the
nursery right? There it is. Okay so it's going from here. It's trying. It's looking like it's
trying. It's gonna make this like weird crab birthday monster. Okay go back. So the question
is. I need to. No get out of here. Can I like feed? All right hold on we got another
mutation going on. The drones are killing the ones that are not genetically similar.
That seems kind of unfair. I just want the crab birthday monster to come up. All right.
No. It's just killing them if it's not correct. It's just browsing. All right I'm gonna
turn off the royalty-free YouTube tutorial music. I don't. That's not my decision.
Like come on. Somebody grow. All right well you keep doing that. Well I go check out the
other people in the wild here. How are they doing? Is anybody even alive? Okay. How are we
doing? We have a couple of changes it looks like. They've started to change color and
have little tails and little legs. The population's getting too high. All right.
Can I please get like a mutation going? Nuke the island. Come on. Somebody evolve.
Sleep. Seeking oxygen. Eating. Corpse. Premium species has gone extinct.
Has gone extinct. Have they gone extinct? Premium egesium has gone extinct.
Lucarius specimen has mutated. Oh the drone's killing the ones that are mutating. Let me
just take that. I don't have any. I don't think they are. I think they're like controlling
the population. Evolve. Dammit. Evolve. One of you will evolve. I have a better idea.
Evolve. Rude. What do you mean rude? What the fuck? Web of life. Where the fuck are these people?
What? How did you guys do all this without me? Hold on a minute. These they're like progressing.
They got hands. They got mouths. They have weird little eyes. Feed them. Feed them all.
So hold on. So I can see where it's gonna go. What about these weird ones? What's this one?
Oh shit. They are. They're just like skating around. Oh no. It wants to go swimming. It's
gonna die. Well it's extinct. Don't feed them. So where does that web end up? Go down here.
We've got major species partially player owned. Minor species. All right. You're still going.
My controlled environment's not doing well. Cold. All right. Let's kick up the temperature.
That's so cool though. What the fuck is that? Where is that? All right. Right there.
It's rapidly exhausted. It's a hairy arm. Let's think from all real monsters.
Apply radiation. Oh god. Okay. What the hell? All right. I'm gonna do radiation. Times like
2.3. This is dopey fuck. Look at how much fun this one's having. They swim upside down.
I love this one. I hope this one never dies. Where are you going? It wants to walk to location
over here. To like hang out by the tree. And now it wants to go swimming again. Looks like a
tongue. Yeah it does. All right. Hold on. We got more species shit going on. Look. Look at
this one. Look at this one. You just gotta let it happen. Right? Oh god. This is extinct.
This is. Okay. Like the brown rabbit turd is now extinct. So that's kind of good.
Here we are. Any others? Yep. We got plenty over here. Well that one's coming up. So how
am I going to introduce mine into the world? My stupid tripod monster. Have you still not
evolved yet? You asshole. Hurry up and evolve. All right. We need to make it a little warmer.
Turn off the drones. I can't. I don't have any like that are here.
Unless I can like turn them off in the nursery. I think they just do their thing, right?
Increase radiation. These ones are not. Why? Come on. How come they get like cool ones and I
don't get cool ones. Oh shit. They're burning. They're burning. They're burning. They're burning.
They're burning. They're burning. Oh fuck. The whole place is burning. This one just evolved.
This is involved into like a like a crusty booger. It's. Turn it down. Temperature down.
Down. Down. No. Stop it. Down. Oh for the love of god. I'm fucking torching everybody.
It was fine. Well this stupid dumb ones in the nursery were like it's cold. So I literally
started killing everyone on earth to appease like six people in the nursery. All right. We're
down to 20. Everyone's fine now. 40 degrees Celsius. 104 degrees Fahrenheit. Yeah. I know.
But I was appeasing. You know what? Why don't I just fucking put you in here? Here. Give me
the cow. God damn it. Speed this up. Go on. No. What the fuck are you doing? I hate this
thing. And now it's extinct. And we still haven't evolved at all. This control group
doesn't have any water. How? Should I like put a fertility box in here? Or like an oxygen box?
These guys haven't done anything. They're killing the ones that are not mutations.
Get a drone to kill the drones. I have to raise the radiation in the nursery again.
Oh god. Is that going to be bad? Come on. Give me the fun music.
Get them out of the nursery. All right. I'm gonna take like I'm gonna take this one
and put it out of the nursery. This is the control group over here.
Right here. Come on out. All right. This is the control group. It's been radiated.
This is like patient zero right here. Uh oh. Are we gonna infect everybody? No. You just
died in the water. Well a couple of kids just went out into the open. Oh boy. Here it
begins. They they come they're gonna infect everybody now. There they are. How many more
generations need to pass? There's so many texts. Yeah somebody's blowing my phone up right now.
We got some weird looking motherfuckers right now because look it. That's what the target was
right? With the long uh arms in the front. What about over here? How's the nursery doing?
You still haven't got it. Not ready yet. I wonder if they're gonna start walking upright.
That's what I'm waiting for. The nursery is killing all mutations. Wait why is it doing
that? Fuck it. Let's introduce more. Get in there. Good luck. The nursery preserves a species.
All right well okay but if isn't this what it's supposed to be making?
Ten creatures in nursery. Edit the target right? The target is this.
Isn't that the point? It's the purity zone. Nursery. This is not the nursery here.
It will only spare the mutations. Just blast them. Well I brought I dropped some over here.
I think we're gonna start to see some interesting things now. They're starting to get legs.
Do they fight? They're starting to turn to crabs.
This one's doing like the stand like a handstand. Nice hand standing dog. Well
there we go. We're gonna follow this one. Herbivore starving. Holy shit what's going on
over here? Is that where I am? Are these are they have friends? Yeah it's an unpeeled
potato. Hunger. Browsing. It's just browsing around. This one's fucked up too. Hot desert.
How you doing? How much oxygen? Well stop doing that. Get out of there. What's wrong with you?
Why would you bury your head in the water for no reason? I need oxygen. I might as well put
my head in the water. I want to see what comes out of this one. It's just basking in the
sun. Oh hold on. I don't know if he peed on him or if this is him basking in the sun.
I'm not entirely sure. Look at this guy. Hunger. Scanning. He's gonna eat this one.
They're gonna get so fucked up. I do. This is my favorite. What's this one called? Primarius
anemurk. Oh no not as interesting as this guy. They're eating from the same tree. I'm gonna
pull out here in a second. Bring him to a new island so he can take it over. Yeah that's a
good idea. All right uh but how do you produce? Pause it here. I need to see this.
This is primarius anemurk. Statistics. Physiology. Hold on. Averages. It's an herbivore.
Does it need to have sex to survive though? Well I think we got we already got that.
We got all right. These two. No we're gonna get it. We have to bring two together.
Age 2000 out of 70. Okay well it's a capable warm-blooded optimal temperature.
Optimal internal temperature. Hairy. It's a decent it's a decent animal.
Okay let's go. Litter size one. We're gonna get you to a secluded place.
You can just you can keep living your life for a minute but who do we combine them with?
I need to be the okay you need to I need to be able to pay attention to you. Come with me.
I need to secure the secluded part. This is pretty secluded.
Down here. Make sure you're fed. Just bask in the sun for a little bit. All right you're
down there. Now who the hell do we combine you with? They're all binding of Isaac faces.
It's like I just walked into the secret room. This one's kind of cool.
I wish I could get a good look. Are you that green? Look at how green this is.
Is this the mate? I think it's green. Yeah green boy. Come with me. Where the
fuck did I put him? Over here right? Right here. All right you two you ready? Now play nice.
You're doing good. A little bit uncomfortable but it's okay. Now you go over here. Stop
resting. Come here. Come over and like enjoy this person that's on the island with you.
They'll figure it out. It's not the same species so it's too cold for them.
All right come on. Scanning. This is eating. They aren't the same species. They won't reproduce.
Well fuck. What about one of these weirdos? Okay so this is Primarius
Anemic. This is an Anemic. Taurorus Anemic. I need to okay so that was that was that was a
Primaurus. So this one could can can be blended. So I need a Primaurus. This one's fucked up.
All right what about you? Content. Basking in the sun. Don't breathe this. What do you mean
don't breathe this? Come here. Okay you guys are the same species and you should be good
friends. Going to take a swim in the water.