Hello? Can anybody hear me? Hello? What's up? Who is this? Who's this? You called me. Oh, okay. Yeah.
Yeah, yes, my number is one number off of your number. Okay, cool. That's really great. Um,
that makes me happy. Okay, please never call me again. Goodbye. Great. That was fun. It's
seven o'clock in the fucking morning. You guys never heard of that? I know it's not. I was doing
a bit. I was doing a routine. There was a big spotlight on me and I had the mic in my hand
and the house lights are down. Spotlight, bang. I go into my bit, my performance. No clapping.
Don't, no clapping. House lights come down. Bang, spotlight. Here we go. I'm going. Oh,
let's clap. I can't. We're not clapping. No, he's just going. Okay. See what I mean? Let's go.
All right. Get it back on. Get it back on. I'm not ready yet. You can clap.
You can clap. So today we're going to do Mario RPG again. We're going to do Terraria
tonight, but Star and I could not sync up good. We had our days mixed up, apparently. I thought
we were doing it Monday. Apparently we had that wrong, I guess. I thought I thought I said Monday,
but whatever. It's all right. It's all good. So we're going to do that probably a different day
or Terraria is kind of just cursed. So it seems like every time something happens,
like Star's computer breaks like three weeks ago and then two weeks ago, my internet like doesn't
work at all. And then we mix our days up this time. Let's just pretend we beat the moon boss.
There he is. Is he here? I thought it was a different day. No, it's fine. It don't matter.
I mean, I did, I mean, I, you know, I did clearly if you scroll up in the PMs,
I did clearly say Monday. And if you scroll up in those PMs,
he's fucking so mad. No, it's all good. Terraria is just like a relaxing, fun game to play. Anyways,
here comes another year long joke. Release the email. It's all good. But so what we're going to
do is just because we couldn't, I wanted to start around like 334. So I didn't want to have another
scenario where it's like, oh, let's set a 30 minute, 40 minute setup time because Terraria
multiplayer fucking doesn't work half the time. But we love Star. We do. But we also love Super
Mario as well. We'll do something someday. Maybe tomorrow. No, not tomorrow. Maybe like
next weekend. No, we should start. No, we should actually do. We should just get to the end
of Terraria and just turn the stream on and have the last base game boss have one HP left.
And then just be like, like fucking screaming and stuff that we did it. And then just move
on to our own game and then end the streams. Oh God. Anyways, I'm going to pick up what we
left off yesterday on Super Mario RPG legend of the seven stars. I got voices.
The throat is voiced. My throat is lubricated. It's well rested. He's starting his tuber voice.
That's how you know it's ready to start the let's play continuation. We have five of them.
And they're distinct. I'll prove it to you. Oh, that's four. Hold on. This one. This one. This one.
This one. And this one. There you go. You got five distinct voices. Told you.
All right. So we left off. We got the princess. Princess join the party.
We now have to go unravel the mysteries of, uh, I don't know. I've played this game a thousand
times. I don't fucking remember what happens next. All right. We go through to marry more.
We go to booster's pass. First of all, because something happened here last time. You can't do
the Malo voice because you don't use Malo. Yes, I can. I didn't say five distinct currently on
camera voices. I just said just five distinct voices. Oops. I fell down. We want Malo. Well,
Malo is not in the, you know what, for the first time ever, I may replace genome. It's possible.
I don't know. I haven't decided yet. Here we go. Come on. Let's bring out a sixth. Golly,
you're that famous Mario. Nope. Golly, you're that famous Mario guy. If I beat you,
they'll make me sniff at number four. If I'm lucky. Here we go. You ain't going to be sniffed at
number four. You're going to be sniffed at number six feet under. Well, now they'll make me take
the training course over again. Slow down. Okay. Flower tab. Broad coin. Kero Kero Cola. Got it.
I got the secret. I got the secret. Oh, Mario just fell off the base of the earth. All right,
let's go. I think there's something else you can do here. There's something else on booster's
path that I don't want to miss. It is like a training course, but is it over here? Where is
it? This is that way, but I can't keep going that way. I forget where it is. You have to
scale a mountain. Let me check that over here one more time. I think, let me follow up the other
side. Like this. Nope. Hey Jerm, I was watching your last stream. Could you maybe cut back on
the ha ha entertainer joke? Please laugh. Jokes, please. Then you what? Ha ha entertainer jokes?
Laugh, please laugh jokes? What the fuck does that mean? I don't even know what that means.
The laugh, please laugh jokes. I don't know what the fuck that means. All right. What was
the last thing I just did? Let me try to remember. We got the princess. Oh, we got to talk to the
frog fusions. Okay. Oh, let me check from frog coins. May I help you? Uh, no. Where's the frog
coin guy? Welcome to the frog coin emporium. I got 15 frog coins. I'm not going to use any of these
because you can get accessories later that are really, really good. Hold on. Let's see if
Todofsky has anything. My favorite song is the Bolville Miner's song. Oh, me do so. I have a
picture. This is my phone. I'm going to get the next layer of card. Me do so do re la ti do.
All right, let's get that up. Where is it? Remind chat of September. What is that? What the hell is
September? I think I have to take a photo of this. Me do so do. Whatever that is. To me,
this is the me do so do re la ti do is more important. Hold on. Me do so do re la ti do.
When are you ever going to do an experimental no talking stream?
A hundred of you would watch that. I'm not going to do that. All right. Me do so do re la ti do.
Got it? And then I have the image there. Let's do it. Okay, September. It's half off of all subs.
Really? Oh, all right. Okay. What do you mean half off? How does it make sense? What the
fuck was that? What the hell is that? My phone just like did a different noise. It's never done
this noise. All right. No, that's good. All right. So you want a music lesson from me? No, I don't.
All right. I got it. Oh no, I'm supposed to keep my phone open. Did my phone overheat because I had
the image on for too long? This is the third year it's happened. How do you not know this?
I don't know because it's only like one month out of a year three times. This only happened three
times. Look. Me do so do re la ti do is more important. Please laugh at that. All right.
Do re mi. This is the last one. Okay. Me do which is right in the middle.
Me do so. So it's do do ti la so fa do re la so that's do ti la so fa do ti la do do ti
do. All right. This is it. What do you think, Todofsky? I did a pretty good job. I think.
Hey man, did you have a mental breakdown? A long time ago you said you'd only play this on stream
if you had a mental breakdown. Did I actually say that? I got a tenner card. Wait, why did I
say that? I said I would only play this game if I had a mental breakdown on stream? Well,
yeah, you can count Simpsons hit and run. That makes sense. Yeah, nothing wrong with that.
All right. I got my card. We have the next level of stolen music from this guy.
All right. Mario tennis counts. No, I'm okay with that. A tenner card holder, huh? What'll it be?
Oh, we get mega elixirs now. The whole party recovers 150. That's a lot of money.
All right. Let's go talk to Frogfuture so I'm ready for one of my distinct voices.
I have the latest news, children. A large star has been sighted on Star Hill. In other news,
the sky is fucking blue. Why are you coming to me? Sorry, Grandpa. Here we go. Star Hill.
This place is cool. I get a lot of claymation vibes from this place. To marry more and then
talk to the flower and the flower, if you talk to the flower, a gate will open. This one is to Star
Hill. Here we go. I still haven't figured out how I want him to sound. I have to figure it out now
because we're getting to the top of the roller coaster here. This is Star Hill. No. Watch out
for the lizard behind you. Behind you. This is Star Hill. No, that sounds terrible. This is Star
Hill. No, this is Star Hill. No, this is Star Hill. No, this, this, this, this, this is Star Hill.
Wishes which were transformed at the Star Road fall from here, but some wishes that haven't
been granted yet are falling because Smitty destroyed the Star Road. I have to do the anime
voice. What else am I supposed to do? I'm combining them all for that character. You're
getting all five in that character alone. Oh, it's Otto. No, I don't want to hurt Otto. Just these
things. Migraine. I think Migraine is an instant kill. Just do text to speech. That's, all right,
why do we have to, that did one damage and I didn't even block it. That's not very nice. These little
guys though, I do want to attack because I think they give you stuff. They drop stuff.
Say the same thing twice. I think I actually kind of like this Virginia. Yeah, I'm going to stick
with this one. No, don't let them run. Don't let them get away. These guys drop items. 30 bucks.
That's what I'm talking about. Go all the way around, touch this one.
What about the little star? Look at that emote. That is such a cute little emote, isn't it?
If I could just get that melody. If you could just get the melody.
The hunger. Oh, for some food. Not creepy. What do stars eat? I want to be evolved class Baker.
Have you figured it out yet? Have you figured it out yet, class?
I want to be the best treasure hunter in the world. Yes, these are wishes from the people down below.
Did it really take? Come on. Figured it out. I got it. I want to be the best treasure. Who's the
best? Who is that? I'm not even sure who that's supposed to be. I wonder what character that is.
The hunger. That's probably, that's, uh, Valom. What's my wish? Um, I can't tell you because then
it won't come true. Where's this other stupid flower? Please let Malo find his way home.
Why, this wish is, wait, wait, this wish is, it's from my mom and dad. They're wishing for me to come
home. This is not the time to be crying. They're waiting for me to come home. Come on, Mario. We've
got a busy schedule. I'll make you eat dust if you don't hurry. What? Is that what he said? What did
he say? Did I say that wrong? Is dust like dirt? Like berry? I'm going to make you eat dust. Who's
this one? Wish I could run faster. I hope I become famous. It's mine. Shh, don't tell anybody. So
the one problem with Mario, this is the only issue that most people have with this game, is this is
just a free star. You don't have to do anything. This is kind of the padding. This is the filler
episode of this game. It is a cool stage though. Yeah, it is. Hey, look at that. Only three more
to go. And one could say this is the end of the, yeah, the merry more arc. You've come a long way,
but your journey is not over. There are three more star pieces. We're good. I want to be a great
plumber like my brother Mario. Luigi, I'm sorry, but you'll never be as good as me. You'll always
be second best. I'm just being realistic. You know, come on. Luigi, how many games have you had?
One, two. I've had like 38. You need to have 36 more games under your belt before you're going
to be able to fix his toilets like I can. What's going on here? Apologize. I'm sorry, Luigi. There.
That's a family guy joke? How is that a family guy joke? I'm just a customer. Don't tell me
you want supplies. I know. Wait, I made fun of Luigi, therefore I was a family guy joke?
No, I didn't know how the rules were. I'm sorry. All right, bad mush poisons an enemy,
a Muku cookie, Fright Bomb, Fire Bomb, and Ice Bomb. These are really good, but they're way too
expensive. Ice Bomb is crazy. I think it does like over two or three hundred damage. I don't know
what this does. You owe us a Peter. No, I don't. At all, actually. So thank you very much. In the
middle of the ocean is a pirate ship. You'll find, I mean, there's a pirate lives there. His name
is Jonathan Jones. He isn't very nice. A star has fallen into the sea. The pirate, probably.
I mean, that man, Jonathan Jones, probably has it. He's nasty. This is the inn. You may stay for free.
Thanks. Okay. I'm scared. Check your money. You may stay for free. Outpass. Okay. Wait,
this one already. It's like a cat. Kavir, you're collecting stars, right? Only three more to go.
If you want to enter the ocean, jump into the whirlpools. You will find the village elder
in his house. He is the most respected person here. I'm spinning. I'm spinning. Finally, it took you
long enough. I am the elder of this village. I got to my exalted station in life by
pleasing my superiors, which is something I do well. A star has fallen into the ocean. I need it
for a certain purpose. You must find it for me. You'll find the star in Jonathan Jones' territory.
Don't worry. You can beat him. At least I think you can. Hurry and bring back the star.
Hello there. You're Mario, right? You remember me? We met at Tadpole Pond, but I'm still at Tadpole.
I've graduated from Frogfusious's school, and now I'm searching for the meaning of life.
It's been so quiet around here. It's almost eerie. Is something going on? It probably doesn't
concern me. Well, if you got any frog coins, I've got some neat items to sell you. There we go.
Doubles experience when equipped, doubles the coins you win in battle, and cuts FP use in half
during a fight. This also is you can use this to start a fight over or allows you to always run
away from a battle. This one is awesome. This one is probably this is the probably best ring in the
game, but it's 50 frog coins. Realistically, I could probably get one of these. I definitely
don't want to do this, though. Go farm the Midas River. I could, but I don't think I'm gonna do
that. It's a cool character, though. Be careful up here, by the way. Do you have like a stick or
something? Can I give you like a symbol? These people here are dangerous. Look at them. Oops.
I think I can get in there eventually. All right, I think I'm good. I have the latest equipment. What
do I have for items? I have too many honey syrups. All right, I'm gonna use these as well. All
right, I gotta do some, I gotta, I gotta, I have to get rid of this shit. I need some mushrooms.
How many mushrooms do I have? I need more stuff. Hold on. I'm gonna have to go to the town and get
some stuff because these guys won't sell me shit. I do have so much stuff, but I just need to get
rid of it. No, who sells you? No, who sells? You sell. Bad mushroom? No, I have to go to a different
town. There was a Super Mario manga for a bit. Was there really? That seems weird. All right,
let's get some stuff. Uh, Wart Club, we already have everything that's the best. I need some mid
mushrooms, though. And I'm gonna sell, I have to sell them. They're taking up so much stupid space.
Honey syrups are just dog shit now. I could get, I could, look at how much you could get for that.
Bucky Jewel, I know I could use that and I could, uh, I had to. These, these are, oh shit, panic
buttons. I still have a Yoshi cookie. All right, I'm gonna get another, I'm gonna get a maple syrup.
Yeah, two maple syrups. That sounds good to me. Whatever happens happens. I should be fine. Let's
go to the sea. This is time to go find the star that's apparently down here. Oh, there he is.
It's been a while since people came around here. Oh fuck, look at all this. I don't have any money.
Super hammer, pearly gloves, handgun I already have. Oh no, how much can I get if I take off?
Hold on. All right, if I, if I get rid of the happy shirt, get rid of the happy cape, keep the
amulet. The work pants are always good. What if I get rid of the jump shoes? All right, I'm gonna
sell those two and see if I can afford any of them. I'll be able to come back and afford it later.
Happy shirt, happy cape, buy sailor shirt, sailor cape. All right, we can get Mario's shirt.
I'm not gonna have to come back for Gino's shirt. The ship sank into the briny sea because a giant
squid attacked it. Some people went in to survey it, but they never came back. Weird. Sailor shirt.
All right, you'll be fine. Giant octopus. Never came back. I'll come back. This is,
I believe there is a star right here, so I've got to be ready for this.
More, more, more, more, more. Oh, Mario's level nine. You know what to do. This is in your hands.
Please click on the screen where you'd like me to put the points in. Have fun with it. Power,
power, power, power, power. Okay, I think that's all I need to see. Power it is. 55 to 57 and then
27 to 28 defense. What am I gonna do? We got another one. Gino. Gino got a good HP increase.
Yeah, very good. Pretty much crossed the board, everything. Choose wisely. A continuous speedrun
the next day is against the rules. All right, guys, that's it for tonight. I'll see you tomorrow
where I pick up at 42 minutes and 12 seconds. That's funny. All right, uh, we're going with
Magic. 40, 41, 24, 25. Anybody else? Wow, I think the whole, uh, the whole entire group leveled up,
I believe. Malo's creeping up on Gino, but look at his HP. It's terrible. He'll get one hit killed
and half the encounters late game. Potentially a decent choice. I do love the dancing flowers,
though. What's the actual meta for this game? I have no idea. Not a single group. Guys, I just
press buttons. I don't know what they do. I'm actually surprised I've been able to do this with
my eyes closed for this long. Toadstool has reached level 10. Look at that magic. Gino, Toadstool,
and Malo, I believe, have the highest damage for Magic. Why am I not playing Classic? Wow,
I have Warf- I have Warf- I have reference, not Warference. I have reference Warcraft every stream.
Because I- I don't know. I'm not playing it. Maybe I will. Guys, you never go
to the new attraction the day it opens. I don't want to wait in line for four hours
to ride the new Galaxy's Edge ride. I'm gonna go when everybody doesn't give a shit anymore,
and I can stay in the hotel for fucking three nights for the same price as one night right now.
Thank you for voting. 45 and 31. You're gonna stay in the hotel when it's not cool anymore.
Yeah, it's- what do you mean it's not cool anymore? It's cool to like me, my two sons,
my wife, and our gran- and my grandfather. Well, I don't care. I don't give a shit how- how cool
it is. It's cool to us. Found the secret room, by the way. I- hold on. Important. I'm about to get
destroyed. I do. Oh no no no no no no no no no what did I do? What did I do? What did I do?
No shit. No I got baited. I got baited. I wasn't supposed to do this. No. And I just saved it
right here. It's the only save I have. Did I get- how much money did I make? Not enough. Thank you,
drop by again. All right, I'm- that wasn't as bad as I thought it was gonna be. In fact, that was
not a big deal at all. I just overreacted. I reacted harder for you, okay? That was a lot of
reactions. The reason why I did that is because over here, there is one of these things that-
never mind. I had it incorrect. I was wrong, and I will stand by my correction that I did- I thought
it was a different part of the game. It was just some free stuff, and that's it. But I want to get
up there. Oh, I get there. I know you can like get sucked up there somehow. I didn't want to do that
either. Yes I did. I want to come up. Got a max mushroom. Let's get rid of one of our honey syrups
because these things are stupid. Should I fight it? Hold on. I think there's stuff over here.
Isn't there something here? I always thought there was something over here. This- I- I remember this
part. This part sucks because you can only breathe- you can only be underwater for 30 seconds before
you start to drown. So you have to keep- there's like oxygen pockets and shit.
I'm just kidding. There's a page from the travelogue. Let's take a look. It looks boring.
Here's the thing. I know the password already. I've known the password for 15 years. So there's a
password. I don't even need to know any of these things. We've managed to trap the giant squid in
the treasure cellar. The treasure will sink with the ship, but so it goes. There's a big password
you have to figure out. I already know what it is. So I'm sorry to all the people that are like
waiting for me to deduce this password. It took me a while to figure this out when I was 12,
but ever since then it's been burned in my brain. I don't need to do anything else. I'm more- well
we'll just- we'll just- I'll just pretend, right? We'll do- I'm gonna do like a YouTube let's play
here. What are you done for? A giant squid's got a hold of us. The ship's going down fast.
No, I gotta save that one. I gotta save that voice for the actual pirate.
The door to the cellar is locked with a password consisting of six letters. In order to proceed,
you'll have to decipher the password using the six hints. By the way, the password is pearls.
I win. Oh fuck, this must be a YouTube let's play. Sorry guys. Uncover the secret of the six hints,
of course, since they're provided by different people. That'd be pretty tough to solve. Maybe
even impossible. Mm-hmm, little secret. He's bad at tubing. I don't think he can be good at tubing.
You just lie down on it and jump into the snow and then you scream and just pray. Okay, um,
let's go. They're scared. Willy wisp. 40 fucking damage. See, Malo would be dead.
He would really only take one of those and then be gone. Damn, he was dead. This guy sucks.
Ooh, Bowser level 10. Pretty good increases all around. Oh, Gino doesn't have any armor on. Oh yeah,
that's right. Oh right, you're right. You are right. Completely correct on that. Gino is not wearing
armor. Um, I have to go back and buy the sailor cape. Thank you for reminding me, but I can't
afford it yet. Who gives the most money? Wow, 76% of you guys. Really? That's, I mean, yeah, I guess.
He is really strong. There's a problem here though. Um, two of the people in this current party,
you're only giving power to. Mario and Bowser have not great HP and not good magic damage or defense.
Only Gino does. So, and Gino is not wearing armor. You guys might have screwed this all up. I'm just
saying. Here we go. Coins. How much money do I have now? 136. I need like 200, 300.
Ah, let's just get this over with. Didn't kill them. How? Shit. Come on. How are you doing less
damage than Gino? This motherfucker is naked. Here's a Gino again. Bye. He's dead. He has one health.
He'll be fine. Look, 110 damage. These guys have a lot of armor too. Once again, that's fine. Run
away. I'm looking for about 200 coins. That's three. That's not 200. Shit. Oh, shit. Oh, okay.
I gotta actually stop fucking around. Got it. No. Oh, don't do it again. Not on Mario. No.
Mario sucks. Laughing my ass off. No, Mario did this very good. Done. Good. Once again,
I'll take Lucky because that might be coins and you guys will pick. I promise.
16 damage on a block. What the hell are you talking about? What the fuck just happened?
He's got no armor. He doesn't have any fucking clothes on. Oh, everything's fine. Don't run.
100. There we go. Okay. So we've got six coins. Chance to double your coins. Let's do it. You're
ready? Give it all you got. Follow it. Okay. Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me.
Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me. Why am I not using the scan line filters? Because they make
me throw up. That's a pretty big amount. That's a 47% think it's over here. I really hope the
14% of you that clicked on G-Node actually that you didn't know where it was because that's a lot
of percentages. So here we go. Let's do it. You guys say the left and you are correct.
That is 12 coins. 15 EXP. No, I wanted to get away so I could heal. Okay. This is bad.
This is really bad. Give me a chance. Gino has no fucking armor on. Okay. Basu, you have to stay
alive. Run. Actually run away. You got away. Good. Oh my shit. That was fucking lucky. Okay.
All right. Now let's go back and get Gino's outfit. It's going to be 300 something damage.
No. These guys take a lot of damage. But they obviously are very hard to kill. Time that wrong.
No, I forgot. You have to kill them with magic. I remember now.
I remember. Yep. They only die from magic. Go on Mario. Go ahead. Gino sucks.
No, he doesn't have any. He's not wearing any armor. That's why he's not very good.
Okay. Let's go back to the merchant and let's get what we need to get.
This is who you guys want in Smash. Yes. And I turned my head slightly over my shoulder a little
and my face is bright red. Yes. Like I am embarrassed that he's being he's doing not doing so well.
Okay. Sailor cape. I have the sailor shirt. I now want the hurly gloves. This is for Bowser.
I already got the handgun. Super hammer is the super hammer. Hurly gloves are better.
Are they than the chomp? I don't remember. I think they are. We'll find out. Hurly gloves. Oh yeah.
They are sailor cape. Finally Gino won't die instantly. Okay. So I'm going to sell the chomp
and I'm going to get the how much is this? 107. You guys are going to love the hurly gloves.
Oh nice. Is the super hammer as good as the masher or worse? I don't remember.
I'm going to find out. Damn it. It is worse than the masher. Okay. All right. Now I'm going to
pick me ups. Get another one. Get another one. Sell items. In fact, you know what? No, no, no,
take it. Take it. Use the flower jar like for the love of God. What are you? That stupid, stupid
idiot. Jeremy, what are you? Dumb person. I need to use this during a boss fight. If I use this
during a boss fight, it guarantees a luck. It guarantees one of those, uh, the three eggs of
Yoshi. It's going to be a lot on the line. So if I use this at a boss fight, I hope you guys are
ready to really truly try and pick the right one. That leaves me room to do a couple more mid mushrooms.
I have to trust you guys. I do. Let's do two more mid mushrooms. I'm going to pick Gino.
All right. I can leave. No, I can't leave. I just know I can. I didn't ban anybody. I just sucked
up all their messages in a vacuum cleaner. They're still here. All right. Check this out.
Want something funny? I love freaking out my new guests with that one. Those of you guys that are
new to the stream, ah, you probably were like, what the fuck? Man, this stream is awesome.
I love freaking out new guests. Actually. Okay. Lucky. There it is. I'm going to do this one.
Is that what we are? We're guests. Could be. I wasn't prepared for it. Okay. That can kill
you. Is that the variety? And now he throws out the little, the action figure. 19 and eight,
double the coins. I can handle this one. I'll get this one, but I do need to heal.
Oh, I don't need to do it to Bowser. He'll be fine. Bowser can handle it. Okay. So let's go.
Everybody has their gear. I got there. All this stuff that they need.
Damn it. I tried to jump the whole thing. I need this though, because otherwise I'm going to get
slammed dunked on. This is going to be interesting. What happens here?
Yeah. Aren't you glad that Mario has no magic defense? Cause he's almost dead.
Are you guys glad you clicked on power? 12 times? 10 times? That was the plan.
How did I miss everybody? Oh, come on. Go to the back. If we didn't click health once,
you'd have the strength to do this. I'm good. I'm lucky. Do the spee voice. I don't remember how.
Experience. This is important. I have no idea. Help me. This is for like 30 EXP. That's pretty
good. One versus 100. All right. So, uh, how do I get this one? Like that. Memo left by Magellan.
There's an S in the word. I can skip this whole thing by the way. I already, I know.
I know though. I know the whole thing. That's not cheating. Okay. If you study for your math test
and you know the math problems, are you cheating on your math test? I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Second try. I am going to do this for the flower tabs though.
It is found on the bed of the ocean and it has an S. It is a Pearls.
Now let's just, you know, let's level up a little. It's going to be a tough fight.
Those are the most dangerous. Probably the Grim Reaper. Not messing around.
Fuck. And I wish I had a Lucky right here. That was, that's pretty good actually.
All right. I want the flower tabs. This is a three-dimensional maze.
Press X if you give up. I'm just feeling on the walls.
What? No, go back over here. Over that. Up on this. Come out this door. I can't, I don't know
how to do it. I can't move anywhere. I got nowhere to go. Am I even up a level? I'm stuck. I think
I'm actually stuck up here. I'm pressing up, down. I'm trying to move. Am I there? Where am I?
I can get like up here somewhere. Okay. I can't go up left. I can go left,
but that brings me all the way down here. Can I go right from here? Okay. Can I go up from here?
Can I go down from here? Can I go left from here? Can I go up from here? Can I go,
can I go down from here? Okay. Up. Left. Right. Jump. Okay. Right. Up. Jump. Right. Jump.
Down. Jump. Right. Jump. Down. Jump. Right. Jump. Down. Jump. Right. Jump. Up. Jump.
Left. Jump. Up. Jump. Down. Right. Up. There's like something blocking me here.
Okay. Oh, fuck. Up. Fuck am I? Come on, Mario. Get over here. Ooh. Ooh. All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for viewing. There's two vowels. This is royal syrup. I will
place a honey syrup. I'm out. Got it. Can't jump down. That's fine. Oh, there's the uh,
this is the guy that sells stuff. Hey, it's good to see you. If only I had known that. I forgot
that you were here. I want. I got pretty much everything I need. I'll give you a hint. The
password has something to do with the sea. Even if you don't get through all six of the obstacles,
you would try to deduce your way through. Good luck. Can I jump over you? I think I can. No,
I can't. Just fight him. Uh, let's do. This is actually kind of a big fight. Come on, Mario.
Got them all. Boom. Boom. Yes. That was a big hit. Lucky. You can't stay awake. I can help. This
is only for that person. So everybody else mute. I'm gonna give you three seconds. I just have a
chalkboard back here and I just scraped. Okay. Tell everybody they can unmute. Yeah, you can
unmute. All right. Pick. No, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. Not yet. Can you do that but
louder? No. It's as loud as you're ever gonna get. That was just enough of a weird sound to
have somebody go, what the fuck was that? All right. Now pick please. Super lame. Going for power
again. He's screaming. I'm just sitting here going like, I don't, I wouldn't want to miss that, to
be honest. I just blow up my vocal cords screaming as loud as I can. I can't do that. If I were to
do that, if I were to scream as loud as I fucking can, I would have to stop screaming. It would be
over. I would sound like this for the rest of the entire day and it would hurt. I don't know how
people scream because they're angry. I guess that's true. Wait a minute. Are you guys actually
clicking on HP? I'm very interested in this. Okay. Thank you. 89. Mallow didn't even have to do
anything in these level. Mallow learns shocker. Super. End of career. End of career voice.
Playing Sekiro. What? Hold on. I need to hear this. This is important. I need to know what the fuck
this is. End of career? What did I do? I just want to hear it. Um, I don't know. I can't think of
anybody. Mark Simpson. Homer. No, that's going to fix it. Homer. Holy shit. It's Joan Rivers.
Oh, Joan Rivers. Absolutely. It's unbelievable. Oh darling, you look so beautiful right now on
the runway. Let me tell you something about just how I forgot about the fuck. I forgot. Fuck it.
Let's go. I can't fix it. I think I have this voice forever. I have this voice forever. I fucked
it up. I coughed too much and now it's over. I actually have this voice forever. This is it.
My career is over. Oh my God. My career is over. I have to turn it to Larry the cable guy. Oh no.
Hold on. I'll be back. I actually remember this because I remember I started doing like Bernie
Sanders and Larry David and shit. That was crazy though. Damn. Good thing I recovered.
What did you guys pick? You picked this one. Crazy. Haha. Damn. It's a good thing that you...
No, I don't smoke. I don't smoke. Quit spreading rumors about me. 49. Does he have the highest?
He might. Fuck. Oh, it's a bunch of coins. Damn it. Okay. Crystal. And how do you have
that clip just ready to go? Daryl slaps himself. That is the worst clip ever. That's seriously the
worst clip that's ever been recorded on this stream. It has to be. It has to be. How do you
slap yourself? I... very carefully. Bone gutted. What the fuck? All right. Peach is level 11.
She will have the highest magic attack of the whole group, I believe. And she learns sleepy time.
Give me something to work with here. We're gonna have to make a pretty
major decision soon as to what we want to make our final party look like.
Is it gonna be Peach, Mario, and Bowser? Is it gonna be Peach, Mario, and Mallow? Is it gonna be
Geno, Mario, and Mallow? Is it gonna be Geno, Toadstool, and Bowser? Come on. I can see something
with the extension not installed and you're not clicking. This is... we're at 43, 42. Come on.
Thank you. I'm so sorry. All right. It's gonna be HP. Thank you for voting. Three, two, one.
But that actually helps a lot. All right. Now do I have enough money to pay for something?
Let's see. Let me see. We got six. Pick me up seven maple syrups. That's a lot of maple
syrups I probably don't need. Okay. Just chop up. I want the stuff that's in here. There's a screw
that's getting really loose on my chair. And I could probably really easily screw it in.
And I think it's one of those scenarios where it's a very major, like, construction part of
this chair. And if it goes, the whole chair might just break underneath me. I'll be fine.
Floating coins? It's a load-bearing screw. I can farm coins here though, can't I?
No. Ah. No. What the fuck? No. What? I'm actually mad about this. How am I not touching this one?
What the hell are you doing? I thought I was gonna turn to something else.
You guys realize I never did these because I knew it was pearls. Why is that so hard? No,
but I thought I had to keep up with it. I never did that one. Half of these I didn't do because
I knew it was pearls. So I didn't do them. I've never walked in these fucking rooms.
That's the first time I've ever been in that room. I knew someone was gonna say it. I was
waiting for someone to say sans. Every time this character pops up, I look over the chat and I
don't see it. And I'm like, really? No one has said it yet. I knew it was gonna happen. I was
waiting. Okay, those are the really big fans of Undertale and Sans. If Sans was in Smash Brothers,
Sans from Undertale was in Smash Brothers, but he was $150. Would you buy it? I'd be tempted.
He's not in a pass. He's $149. Finally crossed 100 HP with some character. That's good.
Nothing is too much for Sans. Would you pay that much for Gino in Smash? No, I would not. Now
there is my public persona where I say no and there's my private in the dark in my bedroom
when nobody can see what I'm doing. And I've got my credit card and I'm punching in the numbers
and make sure nobody's around. And then I have Gino. You know, is that? And then who's gonna even
know? I'll just always disconnect my switch from online. You guys pick the up. All right. Boom. I
think I have to jump on them. I'm telling you, I've never been in these rooms. I've never been
inside of these rooms in 20 years. I think I have to move it? Yep. Ah, mushroom and it's worthless.
At last, two consonants are side by side. At least two consonants are side by side. Oh,
that's a stumper. Save it. And what? What? Oh, do I do this puzzle?
Maybe I can do it from high up. Oh, it's not working.
Mario's password is motes. The R comes before the one. Just like Portal. Yeah. All right. It's
Pearls. Those of you guys that is your first time watching. Letter number one is P.
Letter number two is E. A. R. L. S. The password is pearls.
Good job. I'll let you through. If you can get past me, then we believe first, that is.
Secret octopus battle. Whack. Oh, that hurts. Damn. Bob, so you do a ton of damage.
Am I playing? I'm playing on an SNES. I'm playing on an SNES classic. The little mini thing.
And if memory serves me correct, after this, there is. This is the part of the controversy that
Nintendo had to face was that character's gone. And a lot of the reviewers were really upset
about it. They're like, wait, what happened to my character? They never explained it.
Bowser's just gone. He's just dead. I don't know if people got upset about it and didn't
make me stop playing here. Same joke for you. I mean, come on. I have to make every time I
have to make that joke. I have to. It's not old material if it was less than 24 hours ago.
This is not my, like, comedy special from 2006. This was 12 hours ago. All right, I gotta heal.
Let's heal Gino. All right, I like to go right for the legs. So we're gonna go left leg and then
right leg and then face because these things are annoying. They do like 10 damage every hit.
I'm not a fan of it, so I want to get rid of them. Let's, in fact, let's do super flame. 96.
How we doing? Venom drool. Didn't really do much now, did it? Okay, let's get another...
No, no, no, no. I need to save these. Let's do a Gino beam. Remember when you did that stand-up
set for Comedy Central in 2005? That was great. Yeah, and remember I made that joke about how...
fuck. Remember I made that funny joke about how Super Mario RPG when Bowser gets thrown up in
the air? How much controversy. Imagine going on stage and saying that, like, telling that.
No one ever had any idea what you're talking about. Do I use to pick me up here or do I just
do this without Mario? Throwing undead Mario, yeah. 132. Pretty good. Shit, I didn't get that.
You know what? Just boost Bowser. Drain beam on all of them. Mario, your defense is so bad
against magic. Can I replace Mario? No, no, no. That's it. I'm free. Mario might be dead here
again. I'm doing it without Mario. He's not... he's just... he's starting into, like, some...
he's a liability at this point. Got it. I'm so glad I did not use that pick-me-up because I'm
gonna need it. 100 coins, 34 experience. That's pretty good. All right, let's heal up. Everybody
is all right. Oh, everybody is. Hello? Right, go in here. Should I attack one of these? How close
is everybody leveling up? 70, 170. All right, we're gonna... we're pretty much there. Another
two or three battles should do it. Never mind. I'm gonna climb up here. Why did I show those stats?
They're terrible. They're not terrible. They're fine. They're just fine. I don't like this.
I didn't know that... that you just did so many fake outs. I don't even know which one of those is
real. Holy shit, that's a lot of damage. Once again. Damn it. Mario. Mario. Mario, your defense is so
bad. I should just do a two-person team at this point. 20 experience. All right, on this next
level up, we really got to figure this out. Mario is starting to become extreme weight. In fact,
I'm gonna do this now because Mario's just not good at all. How about more power? I gotta get
him a better item. The masher is good, but almost there. Another, like, two fights or so should do
it. Oh, come on. Really? What are you doing back here? Once again. 57 damage. Why do I feel like
there's something wrong with his character? Look at how much Bowser's gonna do right here. To the
mouse. 150? What's wrong with Mario? Is he all right? Ow, my face. All right, here comes the
opportunity. It's a lot of coins. What the fuck? Which one's me? I don't know which one I am.
Easy as fight of the night right here. Is the Spider-Man pointing at Spider-Man?
Fuck, I fell off. There's something in here. I think there is something in here, actually.
All right, which one am I? Karo-Karo-Kola. All right, I'm jumping out of the fucking map of
the game. I'm going to, like, the developer. That's all, folks. Karo-Karo-Kola is amazing,
though. Not Mario. Whatever. All right, don't. This is bad, potentially. Not quite. I'm not
gonna use it. I can do it. We can do this together. The only threat is this thing back here.
I'm gonna heal up with Mallow, and I'll be good to go. Actually, I'll heal from the level up.
That's about to happen. There we go. Mario has reached level 11. Magic defense increases to 23.
That's better. Gino Whirl. There it is. Gino Whirl can do 999 damage, if you do it right.
This is closer, but... Hold on. Hold on. All right. That's it. That's it.
Thank you. That's it. 52 magic attack. And there's Mallow. Magic is so strong sometimes,
but he's so weak. His defense is 30. And when your HP is that low and your defense is that low,
you just get hit by one thing and you immediately need to eat a whole mushroom. Not good. Right
flower gang. Right flower. Wait, I gotta get over there. All right, everyone's been healed.
Except for Bowser, right? No. Bowser's still... Ah! Oh, okay. I actually have to take one of these,
so otherwise I'm gonna be in deep shit. But I have to do the magic. Oops. Bowser, come on.
Mario did something. A little bit. Ah! That's so annoying. Because now I have to... Let's just do...
No, Gino Whirl is 8. Gino Beam on dry bones. New weapon. New weapon. Need a new weapon for
Mario. Bad. I need to accessorize as well. Give Mario the amulet. Yeah. He's gonna have such a
terrible power though. Then what about, what about, what about Gino? Come on! I'm trying to get rid
of the two in the back there and now I have to Gino Beam this dry bones. Irritating. I have to
do something here. Like, we have to get rid of... Bump somebody. This is gonna kill it, right? Yeah.
I mean, come on. Shit. That's not good. Uh, Mario's dead. And Bowser. This is cutting it close. This
is cutting way too close. This is a really, really stupid idea. In fact, it's so dumb, in fact,
that I, I have, I have to heal. I'm gonna heal Bowser. See? This is the no healer team. Yeah,
this is straight offense. This is offense to the max. Nice throw. Pure water. I could sell that
for a lot. All right. Now there's something back here. Something back here. Nope. Nothing back
here. Nothing back there. All right. I just had to check. Full health. Let's see. Oh, it's, this is
where it is. Okay. You got it. I got him. All right. This is another mimic. Ow. Gino Waro. Let's go,
baby. Damn it. I didn't get it. It's right after it hits, right? It's like right after it goes off
screen or is it right when he winks to the camera? Holy shit. That was a lot of damage.
That was so much. Let's get it. Ah. Oh my God. I just, I destroyed this thing. I love the little
itchy goombas. They like the little, like itchies. Ow. 22 fucking damage, Mario. Are you for real?
Are we sure that Mario has armor on? I didn't take Mario's armor off, right?
100 coins, 17 experience and got a safety badge. Very cool. Let's actually, let's do some
reorganizing here. Safety badge. Prevents mute and poison attacks. The amulet on Mario
is not as good as the amulet on, actually the amulet on Gino is also bad. 125 wakeup pin.
No. Jump shoes. Jump shoes are better than the amulet? How the fuck is that possible?
No. I am really, really stupid. I read it backwards for no reason. All right. Safety badge
is better than the, yeah. That prevents mute and poison. What does this next? I think that's
better because now Mario's got 74, 45, 62, 45. So Gino now is going to be pretty, pretty shitty.
It's all right though. I think we're good. Let's take mushroom. Max mushroom. I need some
mushrooms. I have all these like caro caro colas. Too much maple syrup. Pick me up, pick me up.
Mushroom, mid mushroom, mid mushroom, max mushroom, max mushroom. Jupiter storm coming in.
Whatever. No, no, no, no, no. All right, here we go. It's what? Why is this back? Oh.
Go to the door. Was there, was there a door here? Is it a door? Holy shit. It's a frog coin.
We're going to jump immediately. Nope. Jump one, two. Oh, you idiot. Wait, I can,
I gotta run. I don't want to fight this. No, I'll just fight it. No, I want to run. Good. All right.
Frog coin down there. I wonder if I can go in a little whirlpool or something.
There's a lot of frog coins down here. Three. Keep your eye on those. I'm going to check this
out later. Oh, it's Christmas morning. Wow. Nice. When's the carnival stream? September 21st.
Anything else up here? No, the door, right? No. Yeah. Now we're underwater. See you in 19 days.
That's true. I will be here in 19 days. I'm running away. Ow. Coward. I'm telling my mom on you.
Indecisive today. I feel like all of Toadstools have been completely split.
At least 20 to 30 percent on each one. I wonder why that is. 75. Aye yai yai. I think they have
a hundred health. Mr. Kipper. 36. What is that bullshit? You want to bring, you want to bring,
you want to bring Peach out? Who do I replace? 75, 97. So I do the original, the original Nintendo
Dream Team. Bowser's too good. Bowser's the best of the three so far. I'll do it for a little bit.
Uh, hold on. Does she have any weapons? She has slap glove, polka dress, and she's about to have
a wake-up pin. Now get the thing off of, uh, Gino. What does Gino have for a safety badge, right?
Get Mario out of here? I would. I can't. 62 wake-up pin jumpshoes. All right, let's, let's,
let's see what, let's see what she can do. Point to point. All the stuff is outdated.
Oh shit, that's right. Uh oh. What's going on here? Who are you? What are you looking for? A star?
I'll let you see stars. Anyway, you're out of luck. You see, whenever falls into the sea becomes
Johnny's property. Got that, matey? Oh, and one last thing. Read my lips. We ain't letting you
through. Read my lips. No new taxes. Therapy. Group hug. Sleepy time. It didn't do anything.
Oh, oh my chest. Oh, 210. You guys want me to replace Bowser?
That's a great, that's a great attack. Whack, whack, whack. Terma sucks. Terma sucks. What the
hell is this? Bowser at level 12. Breached 100 attack. Magic attack and magic defense is so bad,
though. Terrible. Just awful. I have to put Gino back in because she doesn't have any of her armor
or any new weapon or anything, so we're gonna do it after this. She's a healer. Okay, all right.
No, I'll stick with it. Power. More power. More power. 105. Are you stronger than you look?
Better warm me up her dick. Come on, mates. All right, where's the intruder? I don't see him.
Did he get away? There he is. Get him, boys. Here, this is on us. Oh, what the, how dare you dodge
the barrel? Are you guys all right? Are you guys okay? Hey, how'd you get up here so fast? Well,
your luck has run out. We don't take kindly to strangers here. That's a lot. Okay, this is a lot.
Poison gas time. Oh, that's pretty good. Are they poison? Oh, they are poison. Eight damage a tick.
That's not good. Let's do it again. I wonder if I'll do it. There, nice. I think I can kill them
all with just regular attacks now. Dealing 70 damage is pretty good regardless of no magic.
Yeah, that is really good. You're pretty tough, mate. All right, I'll let you through to the
Johnny's place. You're pretty tough. You're pretty tough. Yeah, so you're the Mario. Yeah,
not much to look at. Well, this store fell into my sea, so it's mine. If you want it,
you'll have to fight for it. Here's a boss fight. I probably could have done that a little,
a little more of the promotion in there. Got them all except the one over here. All right,
I'm thinking a super jump on Johnny. 58, 70. Whoa, that's really, really fucking good.
That's, all right Bowser, you've solidified yourself as the best character.
Now, the strategy here is you want to get rid of the minions, but you want to leave a minion,
because if you don't, oh, and guys, I just got a lucky. You know what that means? I'm going to be
relying on you to double whatever happens here. This is going to be a huge deal. I do not want to
kill Lucky again. Double. I'm going to heal myself. It's a pretty good heal. That's so good.
It's almost worth doing the poison gas and killing this thing again. 102. Yeah, tough. I wonder,
can I put him to sleep? I wonder if I can mess him up. Yeah, it takes less damage now.
Hmm, we're good. Putting a status, you're doing a status effect on a boss in an RPG.
Well, he said, I know, right. It's a bad idea. They're all immune. That was terrible. Don't
kill him. It's a shiny. Well, that's just too bad. If it truly was a shiny, he'd have sprinkles
flying around him. Let's try 26. Come on. Stop it. Who does he heal? Try to top off somebody.
Let's just group hug. Good. Well, Peach is actually pretty damn good. See you later. See
you later, Tony. All right, guys, double your coins. We'll lose them all. I probably should
have given you just a second. I didn't even give you guys a second. People might not have even
looking at the monitor. Oops, I'm sorry. Oh, no, this is bad. I don't know which one. It could be
any one of these then. I don't know why I did that. I'm sorry. I just, I don't know.
Is it the middle one? Holy shit, you guys did it. I can't fucking believe it. Nice. And Malos
leveled up. Well, thank you, Benedict Cumberbatch, for being right. They said I was right. Good.
Thank you. Thanks for the help. Okay, more magic. I should just honestly replace. I mean,
no, I can't do that. Okay, I'm, I'm impressed. Mighty. You've earned the star.
Think of it as a souvenir of our fight. Funnily enough, Johnny's voice was voted the worst voice
of the whole playthrough by a majority of Jerma985 subscribers. When interviewed about it, Jerma
very clearly said, I just wanted to do Mad Eye Moody again. And it was an excuse to do it.
End quote. He must have really wanted that star. Now go on and get out of here before I change my
mind. Johnny's our main man. He even fights in his sleep. We'd follow him anywhere. Hop on the
trampoline in the next room. It'll take you outside. Go on now. Give it a try. Okay. Thanks, guys.
Hmm. 50 bucks. Oh, shit. Mr. Purple, thanks for the $50. 5000 bits, they say. When are you pursuing
a career in voice acting? Never. Right now, actually. You found the star. Well done.
My dear Johnny, end here. You are so gullible. Don't you know who I am? I'm Yardage,
a member of Smithy's gang. Chalked. It's no wonder my impersonation of an ordinary person was
flawless. Your search for the stars has worried Smithy. So if I take the star back to him,
I'll earn a brownie points. This is the way to get ahead. It's futile to try and fight me,
just hand it off nice and easy. And to think I got the star without even soiling my pants.
I'm such a genius, it scares me sometimes. No wonder I'm so important. All right, everyone,
listen up. We're returning to the castle. All right, should be here about now. Wait, come back.
I didn't mean to give it to you. I can't get a free night. It's locked. Hey, someone's in there.
Blade's late. What's taking him so long? We need to get out of here. I gotta get out of here.
This is just great. Mario got up with us. Only one thing we can do now, and although we may
be a little rusty, we'll have to swim for it. Not so fast there. That star is a gift to me,
mate. Mario, you spineless dogs have no code of honor. We'll make you a walk the plank.
Joy! Maybe we should have leave the Mario the pleasure of wrapping things up here.
Eh. I guess we'll take our disguises off now. Group formation! No rest. Three bosses in a row.
No rest. Oh, fuck. This actually is bad. This is actually a hard fight, and he does a lot of damage,
as you'll see in a second. Oh, yeah, this is bad. I'm gonna lose. When was the last time I saved
the game? Okay. Oh, good. Good. Yeah, you're right. Right. Oh, boy, this is bad. Okay. Bowser,
it's off, too. Oof. What, super jump, maybe? No. Mario, you are not very good. Are you good,
Jerma? You're forgetting things that happened seconds ago. You're telling me that, that...
Okay, he must have a high magic damage blocker. Can't eat a group hug right now, or everyone
dies. Good. Uh, if Peach was not part of this party, I would lose. So, good party swap before
this encounter. Which one's the real Yardavich? That's not the real Yardavich. This is the real
Yardavich. Yep. I have plenty of FP. Good thing I blocked that. Nice block, Peach. Come back
together again. Uh, I need to keep Peach alive, so we're just gonna keep the heal up. Yeah.
I'm all right. I'm gonna just heal Mario. Thank you. All right, they're back together again.
Three. I need another group hug. This would have been hell without Peach. I would have used every
poke. Somebody would have just had been on total item duty, and that actually, that also may have
killed Peach as well. Oh, not good. Um, I actually, I'm gonna just, I was gonna use a mushroom on
Peach, but no. Should be all right. No, she won't. All right, she would have been fine.
Ow. God damn it. Stop targeting Peach. Well, I guess you're doing the right thing. Just defend
with Peach. Yeah, that's not a, no, no, I don't even have to. Counter's over. I win. That could
have been way worse. Mario has reached level 12. Almost 100 health on Mario. Uh, let's get,
my click maps is currently disconnected. What? Uh, that's weird. All right, go for it. 31 to 30.
Oh, it's a fight. It's a chat fight. Who's gonna prevail? The thing that we click on every single
time or something new. By the way, that is 30. That is over 30%. That's 34%, guys, because Mario,
they're overlapping. Pride flowers at 20%. Uh oh. Oh no, it's, oh, it's bullshit because there's 10,000
clicks. Sorry, guys. I didn't have the thing where you can't click a thousand times.
Choose wisely. Oh my God. How about just pick one? Wow. It's time to close it in 10,
nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero. Fuck. Nice work, everybody.
Try again. This is flower. Oh, right. Flower. Oh, you know, actually kind of, I like, I like the
whole like right flower. Everyone click right flower because that, that's just a place for
people who's vote. They, you know, we got like a nice clean, like 60% of our audience here voting
here. We've distracted the, the people that are just messing around. So this is a really good
thing to do, I think. It doesn't really matter, could still magic. 57, 35. Got it. Smithy is now
in the hurries for the star pieces. What horrible surprises might he have in store for Mario?
It's the last chance I'm going to be able to have. I'm not going to be able to do that anymore. So
nope. To Mario. To Mario. No one knew it must have been a breeze knocking out Yardovich.
Ah, by the way, my pirates say they saw a huge axe flying across the sky.
Hey, it's probably one of the Smithy's nasty friends. Go get him, pal. Well, my girls have
hailed on me. So I'll be heading back down now. Drop him. I couldn't read the rest. It was shitty
handwriting. Here we go. Let's get in here. Hey, everybody. I've come to rescue you. Thank you so
much. I've had enough cramped dirty old places like this. Hey, fellow, you got outside of a blind
piece. It was mighty unpleasant in here. Thanks for helping us. Thank you. Yeah, thanks. Be sure
to stop by our shop. Well, thank you for freeing us. I've got to get back to work now but stop by
at the end. See you there. Hey, Mario. Thank you for saving our little town of Seaside.
You exposed the fake townspeople and gave up your star to save us. Please take this with our thanks.
Got a flower box. This townspeople all sound like fucking goofy. Five distinct voices.
Count them. Weapon and armor. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes. Yes. I got 999
Geno World coins. Yes. Okay, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. This is important. This is an overwhelming
amount of cool items, equipable items. Let's go with... This is a Mario weapon. This is the
Trooper Shell. I think this is better. This is the Parasol. This is for Toadstool. We want that.
Double Punch for Geno. Yep. Ribbit stick for Mallow. Okay. Please come in and browse. I'm running an
armor shop. Here we go. Sailor shirt. Sailor pants. Sailor cape. Nautica dress. Get... No.
We're about to go... No. We're gonna go to a new town. Nope. All right, I'll get one. Trooper Shell.
Masher is currently at 132. Oh, but I'm sick of looking at this shit. It's different.
It's the same damn thing. It's different though. It's... I don't want to see that same animation.
Get that thing out of here. Parasol. 96. That's much better. Double Punch is for Geno. Better than
the handgun. Double Punch. 125. Without an accessory. Holy shit, Geno. Ribbit stick. 100.
Better than symbols. Of course it is. Polka dress. Nautica dress. Much better. All right. So now we've
got... That's all right. I'm gonna stick with Peach for a little while. Let's sell this stuff.
Symbols. Masher. Handgun. Slap glove. Polka dress. Good. I got a lot of money. All right. Now,
let's go up here. Mario, if it's a star that you're looking for, I may be able to help you.
At the far side of Land's End is a town made up of reformed monsters. A mouse came by the other day,
and I overheard him boasting about a star of theirs. I don't know exactly where this town
is located, but if you follow the road, you'll get there. Good to see you again. Do you have a
chance to accumulate many frown coins? Yeah, I got plenty. No, that's what I wanted. Dumb. I need
one more. Hi, Mario. We've got a lot of health foods at our store. You gotta treat your body right.
This is a terrible store. Where are the mid mushrooms? I thought I could have a mid mushroom.
Hey, hey, hey. I'm the mushroom boy. Did you know that hidden amongst the regular mushrooms
are some special ones? Unreal, huh? I'll give you items in return for those special mushrooms,
but you've got to taste them to find out what kind they are. So I'll take a nibble first. I'm
hoping for a special mushroom, but even if it isn't, at least I'll get a meal out of it.
You have any mushrooms? Far out. Munch, munch, munch. That was just a regular mushroom. Thanks
for the snack. Is this the way for this guy to just get free food? I don't remember you.
Accessories. Oh, hello there. You were so brave to rescue us, and I'm so thankful. But listen,
maybe it's time you thought a little more about what you wear.
Accessorizing is a big business these days. Say anything you like here.
Antidote is pretty good. I already have fearless. True form Zoom shoes. You don't really...
Pitch shifted goofy is actually a pretty good voice. What do you mean pitch shifted goofy?
Pitched up or pitched down? It's pitched down? No, it's not. Five stars. All right, on our way.
Let's continue. I've got my items to land's end. Can you do the Trump voice for a character,
please? Yeah, sure. The next character that shows up will be Trump. Jumped it.
I want to get up there. Oh, how do I get this? Oh, look out. I sound like an alternate universe
Ray Romano. I 100% do not sound like Ray Romano. I don't... I don't know where you're getting that
from. What? We're talking... We're thinking of the same person, right? We're thinking of...
We're thinking of Ray Romano, right? Well, you know, it's me, Ray Romano. That's who you think...
You think I sound like that? Right now? You think I sound like Ray Romano? This guy's a no joke.
Pitch is dead. All right, I need to stop paying attention to the fact that like somebody thinks
I sound like Ray Romano because everyone's going to die here. Like Mario's about to die.
Bowser's about to be dead. They're both asleep. This is the first death incoming. Not quite.
You idiot. I want to go down because I want to check out this over here. There's some things I
think that are possible. Oh, I need this. I thought that was something. I'm just wrong all the time.
Ow. I do like the parasol. You just open it on him. I guess there's no... There's no way to get at it.
This is bad. Again, very bad. I need Peach to do group hug or I lose. Don't kill Peach.
Miss. I'm not going to revive. Why would I do that? Peach does not have a very good
physical power right now, unfortunately. Although someone's going to level up soon.
Get up. I'm trying to dodge so bad. I don't want to fight these guys. I don't... I need to get
a lick to an HP station. Save. Let's check it out. Wait a minute. Hold on. Oh. Uh-huh.
This is the obstacle course. I remember this. And there's our friendly friend up there.
I'm happy for this. Not a secret. Not a secret. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I'm just going to
revive them. I got plenty of these things. I just did a bunch of bosses in a row. What am I going to
use these for? Oh, sleep sauce. All right. Here's a game you can play right now in your room.
Try... Say sleep sauce with as much syllabus as you can. Sleep suss. Oh, sleep suss. It's pretty
funny. That's right. You've run. There we go. Peach level 13. Did you learn any new moves?
Come back. That is the revive. Nice. What am I supposed to say about this? Thank you for voting.
58. Oh, come on. I actually do need... No, I don't. Come back. Oh my god. I'm really,
really impatient. I tried to get away from the fucking bee. Stop fucking this up. All right.
So here this is... Welcome to the sky bridge. It's a big tourist attraction here. Yeah.
You want to challenge it? Sure. I'll need five coins. Wait, am I getting minus two
because it's not... I didn't do Trump. This guy already existed in the universe. You can't do that.
This guy already had a voice. He existed in the universe. I'm trying to say the next new character.
It was the Yahoo. No, was it? I thought that was pretty good. You can cross the sky bridge in one
of three ways. However, if you fall at any time, you lose. On the normal course, you'll make it
across just by jumping. You'll get five coins for that. On the special course, the blocks will fall
if your time runs out. You'll get eight coins there. On the expert course, the blocks will fall and
the jumps are harder. You'll get a frog coin. On all the courses, you'll have to jump and avoid
the bullet guides. Which course do you want? Normal first. We're going to go one, two, three.
All right. I got my investment back. Yahoo. You want to double your winnings. Get double the coins
you make it across in the same course in one attempt. The course is harder and if you fall,
you won't get any coins. Still want to try? Yeah, let's do it again. Thank you. You want to double
your winnings. Get double the coins. You make it across in the same course in one attempt.
Yeah, that was great. Here you go. 20 coins. I want to do it again. I want to do the harder one.
Okay, let's challenge it. I'll need five coins. Let's do special. Thank you.
Want to double your winnings. Get double the coins. You make it across the same course in one
attempt. The course is harder. If you fall, you're going to lose your coins. Let's try it again.
The audio is half a second behind the video. Why does this keep happening?
No, I need to pay attention. I swear to god this happens. Like half the time. It's either that or
I'm being lied to half the time. I panicked. Sorry. Let's do it again. I'll get it this time.
And then I'm going for the frog coins. I'm going for three frog coins next.
Give me my frog coin. Two frog coins.
Oh, what the fuck? That's so infuriating. That's so annoying. I had it too. Do it again. Come on.
I know I can do this. Three points. No, that's four coins. All right, let's go.
This is the one. Let's go. This is four frog coins. I need these. Thanks a lot. I'll take it all.
Four frog coins.
Ah, haven't been here in a while. I've been busy traveling around.
Where are you headed? Is it Monstro Town by any chance? Yeah. Okay, listen up. Look for the
world where the ant pops up and proceed after it. Keep following it and you'll find your way around
underground. Once there, Monstro Town's just around the corner. I'll see you there.
I forgot and I get the end. I remembered. Oh shit. I think I poison gassed this.
I need how much? 2159. That's all right. Let's do a super flame.
That's not good. 130. There it is. What is it called? About a what? 104 fucking damage. 52.
Um, just keep the hills up. I can take a maple syrup if I need to. Damn it. Uh oh.
Staticky is not that bad. 30 exp and a Bowser level up. 120, 109. Not bad. Hey, what is that?
Hey chat, who's bored? Let's talk. I have a discussion. Talk. Talk to each other. Communicate
with each other. You should be talking to each other. What was over here? Look, I'll give you a
discussion, okay? Over easy, over medium, over hard. Why would you choose any of those? Which
one do you prefer? Now, I need a syrup. Me, I prefer over medium and the reason why I do I like
over medium is because I don't, when a yolk gets really runny, it just kind of gets all over the
place. You bite into it and it turns into water on your plate. It's just, you don't, it's kind of,
I don't like it. Over medium gives a soft yolk, but still it's like almost like a gel. But it's
hot and it's able to be spread on stuff. You can put it on your toast. You can dip stuff in it.
Over hard is just too much. Too solid. Poison gas. Only one person got hit by that. I don't believe
it. I refuse to believe it. I forgot the ants were annoying. They do a ton of damage and they're hard
to kill. Once again. Ow. Pick me up. Let's do this while we're here. Good. I don't even remember
which one it was because I had to go to the menu. God. Shit. They just spun around like crazy.
Oh, another one of these. Come here. Get over here. Come here. Patrick. Patrick, help me.
It's supposed to be a jellyfish. That's like half of your guy's favorite fucking show.
It's not mine. It's a pre-30 experience every time. Come on. I gotta hit them all with this.
Finally. They should die from the poison. At least I hope they do. It's not enough.
Somebody else is gonna level up here. Going in. What the hell was that? I really wish I had,
I might switch Malabar for Bowser for this part because I really want to get like 100 damage on
each one. I think that'll kill them, right? It's 90. 30. No, I think they have 150 each. Sneak us
through to Monstro Town. Hey, look. Mario's level 13. Look at that magic defense. That's the worst
out of everybody and that I have in the whole game. Fly far. Do the right thing here. Come on.
Well, I may as well just press power every time, I think. Can I ask a question? This is a very
serious question. Is it because the POW symbol is the coolest looking? Is that why? HP is for babies
because I want you to suffer. Well, we've got a pretty interesting combination here.
Five seconds. I'm bringing Malo in. Malo for, Malo for Bowser for, just for now. Why'd you do that?
Really? That's so irritating. All right, let's see if we can get a couple of kills here. I don't have
enough for Shocker, but how much will Thunderbolt do? Not a lot. I could do it again.
Did Shocker hit more than one person? I don't remember. Big froggy stick. Too bad it sucks.
Somebody else. There we go. Gino. Gino's kind of balanced. Magic defense is not great, but that's
just the nature of the character. Am I gonna play Earthbound? I don't think so. I'm not sure I would
do Earthbound. Jerma will let you choose one for a Sans impression. I don't, it's fine. You can pick
only one point. Come on. Stop baiting me. Stop it. Hello again. Isn't this just incredible? It really
does look like the edge of the world, doesn't it? It's too spooky for me. I'm too scared. I don't
want to do it. I'm heading back to Monstro Town. It's safe. See ya. This comes into play later.
Now this time I'm gonna do Maple Syrup because I want to do Shocker on one of you. What's the
timing on this? I don't know if I got it. I mean, I kind of, you can kind of just drop the Gatorade
symbol on him. So I don't know when I'm supposed to do that. Watch, ready? All right, it's not really
the Gatorade symbol. I thought it looked like it for a second. It's not. It's not even close.
Let's read a mind. I want to see what the ants are thinking. Do as you like. Okay. Pick me up.
And another level up. No. Oh, I think that's a star down there. I'm super excited. Here we go.
Oh, I got them all. Yeah. 14. Why would I do a Sans impression? There's no reason to do that.
Sans. Do Sans. Sans. Please. Please. Please. What? Why does everybody want the Sans voice today?
I've never seen that. Even when I was playing Undertale, people didn't say do the Sans voice.
Do the Sans voice. Maybe if you're good. And you guys actually picked the HP. Smart. Let's see if
you continue to be smart. Yeah, you have to be good for the rest of the stream. And then maybe
I'll do it at the end. Yeah. Hey, Santa comes on December 24th, not January 2nd. I've been good
for one day. No, you got to be good all year before he figures it out. You're looking for a star? I'll
sell you one for 400 coins. Hold on. Let me see. No, no, no, no, no, no. Come back. No, no, no. Wait.
Did I fuck that up? He's back, right? Yeah. I got, I got plenty of money. I got a ton of money. He's
still there, right? He's there, right? Oh, fuck me. Come on. Really? I'm going to leave and come back.
How long ago is that safe? I don't remember how long ago that was. Is it right here? It was right
here, right? It's literally right here. It was minutes ago. Okay. Thank you. All right. We're
finally go. All right. I remember what you guys picked. You guys, it was uh, Peach was HP. I
remember Bowser was power. Here we go. 400 coins. Looking for a star. Yes. Thank you for the star
and thank you for the like two levels. Let's go. What the hell? Why did I just freeze? I need to
get them all. I have to kill the thing. All right. Ultra jump has been learned.
Hey, you happy? Let's go. Like he was so pumped up. Let's go. Yo, let's go. Oh, yeah, dude. Fucking
hype. Oh, wait, hold on a second. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I get to pick one now.
Excuse me. You know, blast caution confused monster himself. He just tried to hit himself
in the face. I'm sorry. I want you to like to go home and go to bed. 70 fucking three.
Malo, you fucking toad wannabe. Hey, Malo, you're a fucking toad hat with legs.
You have to plus two it now. I'm gonna pee. I'll be right back. Dude, let's go. Let's go, dude.
Dude, let's fucking go, dude. I was testing you guys. I had to see if I did like a
laugh out loud like boomer joke. Ha ha. And then I ended it with the sands. I did. I needed to see
what was going to happen. My hypothesis was correct. By the way, let's fucking go, dude.
Valom temple. For 100 coins, this shortcut will get you back to the surface. Okay. Should I take
that? I think. Where does it go? To the surface. But is it still available? I'm going to see if
it's still available. Like, can I? I'm good. What are you guys saying? Vinny is a big Chrono
Trigger fan and he loves Earthknot. Yeah, well, I love peanut butter and jelly sandwiches.
My brother loves peanut butter and jelly sandwiches, but I cannot fucking believe I
can buy another star. Okay, what I was gonna say, so I can come back later. What I was saying is I
love peanut butter and jelly. My brother loves peanut butter and jelly, but my brother hates
mozzarella sticks and I love mozzarella sticks. No, wait, hold on. That's different. I love
peanut butter and fluff. My brother hates peanut butter and fluff. Just because you like peanut
butter doesn't mean you'd like peanut butter. Like the peanut butter is like this just because
you like sandwiches. You know, relax. It's in there somewhere. You'll find it. Do you want your
fortune told? It'll cost 50 coins. Oh shit. Oh, what do I do? Hold on. Let's go. Let's go.
I can't even do it.
That's so funny to me. The three faces on the wall,
hit them in any order and you'll receive your fortune.
All right, I'm gonna say middle, middle, left, right. You want to, no, we're not voting on this
shit. It's easy. Fine. Oh, I don't know why that's doing it for me. Like a guaranteed minus two
moment and I can just instantly switch it around. Even if it's a bad sans and it doesn't matter.
I just say the word eight, eight, eight. I just say eight and it's over. I win. You guys are
programmed to like that. Okay, let's go. Isn't this what I just said I was gonna do? I can't
do middle again, so we're going right. If you proceed through the pipe next door, you'll have
plenty of good things to look forward to. Isn't there a treasure room here if you do it right?
I just thought there was. Snowy. Let's do snowy. Holy shit, that's cool. Very cute.
You think they're putting fishes and Doritos in your comments? They're gonna make me read them?
No. That's a lot of coins. Double the coins. Okay, guys, I'll get this one.
I'm just gonna fucking guess. I don't care. Got them all back. Don't worry.
Nice. I haven't, by the way, I have enough frog coins to get the experience one, which is probably
the best one to get. The yellow tile will get you to the next room. Your fortune determines which
room you'll arrive at. If you're lucky, you'll run into Baylum and Monstro Town will be just beyond
him. I'm so hungry. Wish I had some days. If you're lucky. Get it. Oh, well, I don't have Bowser.
I don't have Bowser. I don't think I can reveal this thing. Can I? Psychopath. I have a secret.
You have a secret. I don't think I can do this. I have to run. It's the gas. There's no way I can
reveal this. Unless... than to bolt. Let's try something. Let's just... let's just not go.
No. No, there it is. And just beyond Baylum will be Monstro Town. That was almost... uh-oh.
Bowser's coming back for the Baylum fight. All right, so I need to put some Scarecrow
repellent on. All right, uh, let's just... let's do this now. Let's get Mallow out of here
for Bowser. Let's make sure somebody has a true form pin on. Mutant Poison. I don't have a true
form. Who has the true form pin? Do you know? Let's give the true form pin to the person
that needs it the most. The person that needs to be able to stay alive and heal everybody.
Wait. You look so tasty. I think I'll have just a snack.
Mm-hmm. Just keep it going. I'll never forget a taste. In fact, I can clone someone
after just one slurp. Take a look. You all look so delicious. Well, how do you taste?
Tastes peachy. There we are. No, I ain't gonna do it again.
You all look so delicious. But how do you taste? See, the developers... there's a lot of controversy
on when this happened. I didn't even do it. Come on, give me some slack. I ironically did it. I
ironically did it. All right, I need to stop farming minus two. So this is going to be the
lowest rated string of the year. They all sleep? Holy fuck, that was a lot. How do you taste?
Always get rid of the clone first. How are we doing on health? Snap out of it. Somebody... okay,
uh, we're fine. I have an able juice. I might as well just use it
because I need you. Let's just do group hug. Do the ultra jump again. 240. God, keep eating
peach. That's fine. How is it gonna kill peach in one hit? Do it again, Mario. You know what to do.
One, two, three, six, seven, fifteen. No, not again. I'm starving. Time to go home for dinner.
Goodbye, boys and girls. What am I... what is going on here? Trash loot. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, hey. Hello again. That pipe is a shortcut to my house. Beautiful house. Monstro Town.
I'll see you there. Monstro Town. I love Monstro Town. It's great.
Weapon and armor shop. Just a minute. I'll be there in a second. Oh, my.
Goomba, what are you doing here? Well, Bowser, it's been ages, hasn't it?
Sorry about going haywire on you. I ran away because I was scared to fight Smitty.
A lot has happened since then, but look how far I've come. I'm managing this store now. And look,
here are my little ones. Come on, show your manners and greet Uncle Bowser. Although I can't
fight for you, I still have some items we could use. Maybe you'd fight it in your heart to forgive
me if I could help you get equipped. Don't worry. I'm not angry with you. I've got new troops now,
and we're going to reclaim my castle. You can go on with your life here. I wish you the best.
Well, I really appreciate that. What can I get you? Oh, you know what I'm getting here.
Spiked Link Courage Shell. 155. Let's go. Courage Shell is... Magic Defense Down. What is it here?
53. That's just... that's just not very good, but I kind of...
How does Mario have 100 and fucking 50? No. He's 144 attack. Why does he suck?
Give the amulet to Bowser. No, don't do that. I need some more of these. How many do I have?
I have a lot of pick-me-ups. I'm never going to buy any more of these again.
Okay. Nice to see you. Goodbye. Feel free to rest here. The Three Musty Fears. I remember this.
Nice to meet you. I'm Grieper. I'm the Big Boo. And I'm Dry Bones. We are the Three Musty Fears.
He's sleeping. Boy, he sure is. Check those bubbles coming out of his nose.
Maybe he can still hear us while he's asleep. Hey, you. We want to play around and find the
flag. Right. We'll each hide a flag somewhere around the world. Find all three flags,
and you'll get an awesome prize. We'll go and hide the flag. See you when we get back. Dumbledore.
I looked over and saw Dumbledore. I just... it was one comment that said Dumbledore,
and I fucking lost my mind. They'll be back. Our first year students. They will show us
very wonderful things. I'm back. I hid my flag behind a wooden flower. I know what that is.
I'm home. My flag's under a green bed. I'm back. You'll never guess my spot. It's between
O and an A. Ladies and gentlemen, the first flag is behind the wooden rose in Rosedown. The second
flag is on Yoshi's Island between the O and the A of Goll, and the green bed, if you believe it
or not, happens to be Super Mario's own green bed in his house. Did you know? Our flags are
invisible, so search very carefully when you think you've found the spot, Harry. Don't forget what we
told you. Go. Time it. Time right now. Start the time. No, wait. Start the time when I... wait.
I'm not... why am I going this way? I'm going the wrong way. Hold on. Don't start that timer yet.
Hold on. Where's the door? It's this door right here. Go. Reaper flag. Big Boo flag.
What is that? It's not his name? His name's not Reaper? Dry Bones flag. All the flags got.
Call it when I get back in the bed. And... time. Good job. You found all three flags. Hey, you're
not half bad. You did pretty well. We had a great time, too. Thanks for playing our game. In fact,
we just got off lunch and you did it. Not even. We were on our way to lunch and my phone buzzed.
Who fucking helped you? The grand prize giveaway. Don't forget what we told you. What did I get?
I got a great item bad smell. Where is it? Oh, there it is. Ghost medal. Raise his defense
while attacking. Yup, yup, yup. Yup, yup, yup. Yup, yup. Yup. Yup. It's been sealed.
So the super jump is your specialty, right? Those multiple jumps of yours are pretty amazing.
I heard that your record for consecutive jumps stands at 12. How do you do it? Jump
more than 30 times in a row and I'll give you a prize. You're a terrible. Rumor has it that you
You're a quiet and accomplished jumper.
I may be out-jumped, but you're totally out-pumped.
A strong, silent type, eh?
Don't you dig these vibes?
It's really weird sometimes I hear the guy next door.
He's always mumbling about a crystal in evil.
Isn't a crystal some kind of shiny rock or something?
I know I've seen those somewhere.
Oh my, a traveler from afar.
Welcome to Monstro Town, where many of our kind mingle.
I'm the landlady, you monster, I'm a,
a star, you say?
Oh, you're here to see our star.
She's upstairs.
So feel free to go and take a look for yourself.
Sometimes if you jump in the right places,
a treasure box will pop out of thin air.
Anything like this ever happen to you?
These treasure boxes are known as surprise boxes
because they appear out of nowhere.
They didn't get found of all, but there are still 32 left.
I've been all around the world, almost every country,
but the strangest person I met
is this old geezer in Rosedown.
He's really weird, but definitely worth meeting.
That's the song, that's the Todofsky song.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, somebody screenshot that, okay.
So what do you think?
Our star is adorable.
She's so talented too.
Folks come to see her from afar.
Geez, starbees?
Oh, starpiece, I'm not familiar with it.
So you came all the way out here to search for a starpiece.
Must be really important.
This is the last place on the land.
If you can't find it here, then the only place left is up.
What?
So you wanna go up there?
Oh, you're an open book.
Okay, here's what you need to do.
There's a secret passage to the sky had been valid,
but first you must scale the cliff beyond the desert
to get there.
Since you're such a nice guy,
I clearly introduce you to someone that can help you.
Sky troopers, I need you.
What was our flying time, troops?
8.52 seconds, Sergeant.
Sky troopers reporting for duty.
Ask me anything.
We are 0.52 seconds late.
I hold myself personally accountable for the delay, ma'am.
Still as rigid as ever about your rules and regulations.
No need to bother with the protocol around me, Sergeant.
I've got a favor to ask of you.
Yes, ma'am.
Anything we can do for a civilian.
This fellow here really wants to,
really wants to get to Bean Valley.
Could you help him scale the cliff?
Understood, ma'am.
The orders are get mustache over the cliff.
We will succeed.
We will now deploy ourselves to the cliff it lands in.
Troopers, keep a tight formation.
We have liftoff.
They're odd, but trustworthy.
Good luck with your search.
Hope you find your star.
No, no, react harder.
React harder.
Turn him off.
No, it's not down yet.
Don't you dig these vibes.
Is it down?
Another little tip for you.
That's how you get the key.
Got the temple key.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
I did.
I have it.
I do.
What the fuck am I doing?
Okay.
Now I'm going to go up here
to meet the best character in the game.
Not this guy.
Who is it?
Sorry, but the Sensei's not in.
Oh my God.
Ha ha, oh my God.
Jagger?
Bowser, I haven't seen you for so long.
I've been studying here at the Dojo
under the Sensei jinx because,
to tell you the truth,
I knew I couldn't beat Smitty.
That's why I'm here now.
Someday I'm going to return and make you proud.
Don't worry about me.
I've got two new troopers now
and we're going to take back my castle.
You stick to your guns.
Train like there's no tomorrow.
My Sensei's out right now, but he'll be back shortly.
In the meantime, will you accept a challenge from me?
Sure.
Okay, great.
Nice.
You know that I'm not going to make it easy for you though,
right?
Bang, bang, bang.
Oh, that hurts my eyes.
Every time I attack with Bowser now.
Oh, no, that sucks.
Terror punch.
Dead.
I found the solution.
Every time it goes,
just close your eyes,
just hard blink and you won't see it.
So just go blink, blink, blink,
and you won't see at all.
That's what I'm going to do.
Yikes.
I guess that was to be expected.
Mario, you're a top-notch fighter.
You did well for your inexperience, Jago.
Sensei, have you been here all along?
Hmm.
You felt my ki, didn't you?
Not bad for a novice.
No.
Your fighting style isn't as foolproof as you think.
I'll accept a challenge any day.
You wish to challenge me?
All right, let's see what you're capable of.
All right, here's the strategy.
Ready?
Block now.
Yep.
That does a lot of damage.
You have to block right when you can hit the ground.
Got it.
All right, ready?
So blink, blink, blink.
Triple kick.
Block.
I remember these timings.
They were really annoying to get used to.
Shit does so much damage though.
I have to keep using it.
I'm sorry.
Actual real, like no jokes at all.
Like if you're sensitive to flashes of light and stuff,
like that's going to happen for a while.
So seriously though, like take care of yourself, right?
Battle her up.
Oh shit.
I need her.
Six.
Again.
You don't get to go twice.
That's not fair.
Group hug.
Woo hoo.
Simply amazing.
I guess I underestimated you.
You packed quite a punch,
but don't let it go to your head
because I had let you have that round.
Let's have a rematch.
This becomes very, very, very hard.
All right, you asked for it and no crying if you get hurt.
Quick silver.
He missed.
Good block.
And even if that would have been a one hit kill.
You see, you see what I'm up against here?
That was a gamer Jupiter?
What the heck are you talking about?
Oh my fucking God.
I looked at, let me re-chat and take a hundred damage.
Yeah, I'm a little under level for this part.
I still might be able to do it though.
There's a third phase that you actually need to be
like at least level 15 to 20 to do it.
Cause he will just kill you.
Zero.
Well, well.
Just perfect block every time.
I mean, that's true, but you still take damage.
And yeah, he has a move that instantly kills somebody.
That move quick silver, I believe is a guaranteed kill.
Or it brings you down to one.
You can see me through a telescope.
Well, I hope you're enjoying fucking space.
I missed it.
Didn't even need to do that, but I did it anyways.
All right, here we go, phase two.
I'm gonna do like 10 damage to him now.
Fuck man, that is actually bothering me.
Blocked it.
I really am trying to time the blinks and it's working,
but I might have to get rid of Bowser for a little while.
You know what I'm saying?
We're gonna have to use him as parts.
31.
Miss.
64 damage.
What the fuck?
That really angers me.
That really makes me upset about that.
Oh, this simply amazing.
I simply just can't believe.
Still haven't had enough.
It isn't often that I have someone this competitive to spar with.
All right.
This match will be the one that counts.
Since I'm placing my reputation on the line.
I'll go for it.
I need a better team though.
Sorry Bowser, you gotta go.
Like I just can't look at that anymore.
I need a, no, no, no, no.
I can't, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready.
I'll be back.
Where the hell am I going?
Lands in.
I'm gonna go back.
Oh wait, just, I need a few more levels.
I need a few more levels.
And I did say I was gonna remove Bowser.
And I did.
I'm pretty smart.
Now go to the equip section.
We need the work pants and the ghost medal from you Bowser.
Thanks.
We've got the double punch on.
Work pants and the ghost medal.
Out there.
Do I need a break?
Um, I'm good.
I'm good guys.
I ate a piece of salmon earlier.
I could literally,
I could literally lift up a car right now.
There's gotta be, I don't remember.
Caution, confused monster.
The yellow one.
Don't hit me.
What does it mean?
What does it mean no balls?
What are we talking about?
What's going on with you guys?
That was an incredible room.
I don't want to fight that.
Get out of the way.
I hate this.
Ah.
Gino Blast.
Here we go.
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is why Gino is best character in the game.
Toaster learns mute.
And he still has one more move for Gino Flash.
Gino Blast, Gino World, Gino Boost.
We're talking about standard B, side B, down B, up B,
final smash.
Get on it, Nintendo.
He's made for that game.
That's the only reason why he made this long ago.
67.
More frog coins?
Can I accumulate more frog coins?
Yeah, let's double it up.
Double it up.
Four more frog coins.
You can farm frog coins here.
That'd be pretty sick.
Four frog coins.
Here we go.
Let's climb the mountain.
Which way is it again?
Over this way.
I think it is.
Over this way, I think.
There it is.
Okay.
Ten Hut.
All troops in positions.
Mario, your mission is to scale the cliff
by jumping shell to shell.
Don't give up.
Sure and steady does it.
Try it again.
It's timed, by the way.
That's why I'm doing this.
I can't get on that one.
I know I can.
I know you can skip one.
Maybe you can't.
Oh my God.
That's a pretty good time.
Mission accomplished.
Last time, 13.9 seconds.
Let me do 12 seconds.
Shit.
Ah, that was close.
Again.
That could have been probably 10 seconds.
I'm hitting the shell over there.
Get out of here.
I don't care.
I got the frog coin.
Who gives a shit?
Let's go.
Ooh.
That's gonna be good.
Distinguishing work, soldier.
Here's the next best thing.
A Troopa pin.
Got it.
Grants Troopa confidence.
Sure does.
But what does that mean?
What does that mean?
Beanvale.
It's 20 speed, is it?
What is the speed stat even for?
Missing when somebody misses you?
You hate this song.
Why?
This is a great song.
Wait.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Time for a nap.
Aim sucks.
Am I actually seeing game sucks?
I don't believe it.
No, you're not actually doing that.
That this is, this is the Michael Jordan of video games.
What, really?
Crusher.
So overrated.
You're actually talking about one of the best NBA players
to ever live.
Overrated.
I'd be more invested if you did playthroughs of Paper Mario.
This is, this is, this is, this is Paper Mario.
The only difference is it's like real game
that came out before Paper Mario.
You are playing Paper Mario's father.
Paper Mario's dad.
Everything that Paper Mario learned from dad,
he learned from his dad.
In fact, some would argue that dad was a little quicker.
Fighting over what is better.
They're all on the same team.
You're on the same team.
Otter Fiend, thanks for the five community subs, Otter.
Dropping five subs here, thank you.
Appreciate it.
Five community subs.
I remember something about this.
This is important.
Something important here.
With either the, something here.
Something here, there's something here.
It's very important for something.
The seed, something.
There's an item that I need to pick up here.
I just forget what it is.
And it's the most important thing in the whole game.
That is a 200 fucking name.
Damn it.
I can't ever get that again.
It's in one of these.
I can't screw this up.
Mods to the rescue, what was going on?
Everybody just chill.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Now I'm not gonna do the Sans voice.
I'm sorry, but I'm not doing the Sans voice anymore
because of this.
I saw some, we apparently had an issue in the chat room
here and I told you guys to behave.
Punish us all.
All right, is this the, this is it, this is it.
All right, something happens here.
That's what happens here.
Shouldn't have known.
That's a lot of damage.
Are we on health?
We're okay.
Mute.
What is that?
What can I do with that?
Mute.
Will this work?
420, Jesus.
Mute that motherfucker right now.
There it is.
Ooh, that's it.
Group hug time.
Mario's a god now.
Yeah, Mario's a god now.
150, goodbye.
150 coins and you got a nothing.
You got nothing.
There's something, frog coin, there's something in here.
I think this is some, there's a secret in here.
I know there's something going on in this one.
That's not it.
Maybe I'll see it soon.
Free Wonka bar?
You can't get Wonka bars anymore.
I don't know why they ever decided that that was a good idea.
Cause they're awesome.
Yeah, some company bought them up and liquidated them.
All right, here's Mario.
Pretty good.
What do you guys think?
Why even do it?
Gino's attack is actually getting really, really good.
50% clicking on the right flower.
Nice.
Power on Gino.
All right.
I'm so happy that 31% of you clicked the flower
cause that's a good choice.
Let's go.
100%, you're morphing together.
This is it, this is it, this is it.
What do I do?
Okay, so you do something, that's the golden,
that's the golden, that's the golden thing.
I found it.
Now I forget what you do with this.
I think, you don't kill it.
What do you do to this?
This is the casino.
I forget what you do.
Uh oh, forget to kill these.
I think you do.
Whatever, I think you do.
And they drop something.
Hold on, I forget.
I actually am cheating right now, but that's fine.
I know, I know how you do it now.
I know how you do it.
I gotta go back to Booster's Tower.
Yeah, I remember this part.
I'm gonna, you guys are gonna laugh at me for this.
I'm gonna fuck this up a million times.
Remember, it's this one up here.
Oh, you idiot.
Hello.
Once again, nope, attack up.
They're vote kicking me.
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
I can't get kicked out of my own stream.
This is my stream.
What did that do?
Did I not get it?
All right, it is time.
Let's just attack you.
Vote kick, vote kick, vote kick.
Last time I was vote kicked from a server,
I think it was when Grandpa played CSGO jailbreak.
I think this is the last time it's ever happened.
I made everybody sing, and I didn't like how they sung.
So I just dropped everybody.
Pay attention, pay attention, everybody watch.
Look, if you're looking on a different monitor,
look right now.
War, it's a free day, free day.
I remember that.
Free day.
Nice work, guys.
I can always count on you.
I'm probably at 999 coins.
Nope, almost.
Oh, time to grow.
You know what?
What do you say we put on a table throw?
I'm so hungry.
I wish I had a carbo cookie.
La dee da.
It's shower time.
There there, my pretties.
Hi ho dee da.
I'm gonna take it down.
That broom made my desk vibrate.
La dee da.
It's recycled water.
There there, my pretties.
Hi ho dee da.
It's you bliss.
No, I want an able juice, and I want a geno blast.
Come on.
Oh that, you guys are like,
oh wow, I like that character.
That sounds like really creepy.
Yeah, that's what the character's supposed to be.
The fucking creepy ass motherfucker.
I'm doing my job right.
Triple.
La dee da.
Oh, I added some nutrients to this one.
Whoopsie.
Oh, there there, my pretties.
Grow up big and strong.
Hi ho dee da.
Better?
You like that better?
Okay.
That was bad Mario, come on.
I haven't been paying attention to anybody's health.
I probably should be.
Who has health?
Oh no.
First death incoming.
I have able juice, right?
Yeah, we're gonna do able juice here.
I have one more, don't I?
I do.
Okay, give this to princess Toadstool
and Toadstool has to do group hug
and then group hug and then geno.
Come on Toadstool, do something.
Don't do the Mario.
Do it to Mario.
That's fine too.
Okay, can Toadstool get a turn?
That would be nice.
Come back.
For a second I thought it didn't work.
Like is that possible?
All right.
Bring him back again.
When do I time this?
Right when at the end or when it comes out?
Am I gonna play battle for Bikini Bottom remastered?
Well, after I lose in Mario RPG
for the first time in 15 years.
Next game.
That's no, that's not how this works.
Oh, I get to do the voice again.
This is the guy that died to Piranha Plant.
Yeah, it's a tough fight.
They change it into all kinds of shrooms.
I would have Bowser here, but Bowser hurts my eyes.
So I can't have Bowser here right now.
When is Piranha Plant gonna get on Smash?
Um, did you pre-order the game?
I've got great news for you.
If you didn't pre-order the game, then I'm sorry,
but I have some pretty decent news if you did.
Give me turn.
Gino has like 40 speed right now.
I'm just fucking shocked.
You can buy the plant?
I'm not, I promise you, I did not know that.
I thought you had to pre-order that.
I didn't know you had to buy it.
I wasn't aware of that.
I stand corrected.
Lock.
No.
Oh, miss.
Oh, no.
I have to get shroom defense.
I'm gonna die again.
I have to get like shroom.
I gotta go back to town and get anti-shroom.
Somebody might live.
No, not anymore.
That's gonna be a triple kill right here.
Nope, it's not.
Somebody get out.
It's been like four turns.
He's out?
No.
Get out.
He did it again.
All right, I'm just gonna give Peach the shroom for him.
Okay, I missed Mario, but that don't matter.
Mario's, okay, Mario, he's out, he's out, okay, okay, okay.
Good, I'm glad you did some Mario
because he's not gonna revive him.
This is important, I'm going for it.
I have to, good.
I have a chance here.
Now we do a, I'm gonna heal up Mario.
I got it unlocked now.
As long as he doesn't do the mushroom thing again.
Because then Peach can come out and do a group heal.
Hey, look at that, group hug, let's go.
All is good.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Fuck off.
Everybody three times in a row.
Oh, come on, that is actual stupid bullshit.
Peach is gonna die.
Usually he's going for Peach every time.
Okay, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
I have to keep Peach alive.
She's all right, she's pretty much near full health.
Okay, now I'm gonna do, we're gonna do this again.
Mario's out, game over.
He can't have that much health, let's do it again.
We're going in a circle.
Okay, I've had enough, goodbye.
Oh, look what you did.
Smilax has been whacked.
Oh, I'm gonna get it.
Queen Valentina told me to keep everyone out of Nimbus land.
What should I do?
I know how to run away.
I dropped something.
What's this?
It's a seed.
Picked up a seed.
There's the seed, I found it, and boing.
And yes, you don't need to tell me.
I know where the, I know where the other insane thing is.
I know where it is.
Wow, did you see that?
It's a magical beanstalk.
Big, huge, all the way up into the sky.
It's the biggest beanstalk I've ever seen.
Hit the block once more and you'll get on it.
I promise.
Sorry, the mouse had the blue dialogue,
so I'm just kind of keeping with the cannon here.
I need, okay, I'm all right with health.
How to climb the vines.
The vines are positioned from the bottom
to the left to the top of the right.
When you jump, you will be able to disengage yourself
in the vine, Nimbus Department of Transportation.
And it goes like that, it goes, doot, doot, doot, doot.
I wanna see what that one is.
I'm curious about that one.
Really?
All right, guys, fine.
I love this area because it has the cool background.
Oh yeah, the fat Koopa.
If you let them launch, I think they kill everybody.
Oh shit.
All right, let's keep moving.
Flower tab.
Coins, I'm gonna get all these.
I was gonna say, does this thing not exist?
Ooh, caught it right at the end
and this one's on the other side.
Oh, you idiot.
How do I get this one?
Because you have to come on it from a different angle.
Can't come in from the front, can I?
Those clouds.
This is just you guys in chat right now.
I'm trying to come around the edge, but I can't grab.
Look at the shadow.
No, I know it's on this.
It's on the front, right?
Can I just, no.
Because if I can't jump and get it,
I'm on the other side and it's in front of me
and I can't get to the front.
Oh, oh my God.
This is gonna drive me fucking crazy.
Holy shit.
Okay, let's go right here.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
It's finicky.
I have to get them.
They're so easy, but they're not.
What plane are they on?
This forward plane right here.
Okay, got it.
Good.
Here we are.
This is a very good song, by the way.
All right, everybody, listen up.
Shut.
Shut up.
King Nimbus's condition is growing worse.
This means we'll be losing our magnificent ruler.
But it just so happens that I have found the missing prince.
Prince Melo, that is.
Prince Melo?
Please, sir, prince.
Get over here.
Well, well.
It seems that our little prince
has a mild case of stage fright.
Excuse me.
Where it's gonna happen.
I don't, wait.
Make it snappy.
You can't get through.
Just look at you, tubby.
Introducing Prince Melo.
Look at that, Prince Melo.
My, you've filled out a bit, Prince Melo.
You're looking fit, prince.
Yes, what is it, dear?
What?
You're asking me to?
Gracious.
You're serious, aren't you?
Why, I don't know what to say.
Dear me, I've made my decision.
At the request of prince, of the prince,
I agree to become his queen.
Here it comes.
Queen Valentina, oh, it just makes me shiver.
Fucking do it.
Well, that's that.
Back to your business, everyone.
Hurry it up, William.
It's been a while since we've heard him.
Can you believe it?
What a coincidence.
There's a prince with the same name as me.
Don't we have anything better to do than hang around here?
Come on, let's go and find the rest of the star pieces.
Say, you have that, I'm looking for something,
look in your eyes.
What can I do for you?
Mega glove, war fan, and cannon, sticky glove,
fuzzy shirt, fuzzy cape, fuzzy dress.
All right, this is gonna take it.
I have a lot of stuff in here.
Okay, wait.
Pearly gloves are for mega gloves.
These are kind of jokey.
War fan for princess Peach.
Hand cannon for Gino.
Sticky glove for Mello.
Now we have courage, should we just keep that on?
No, just sell it.
Fuzzy shirt, fuzzy shirt, fuzzy cape is better than...
80 versus what?
71, that's pretty bad.
I think work pants have kind of outgrown them.
I think it's not worth keeping them on because of the defense.
I also should give the ghost medal to somebody here.
What does the ghost medal do?
Raises defense while attacking, what does that even mean?
Okay, so we have, we'll keep all the accessories.
Fuzzy dress, put that on.
Sailor cape, these can all, I can sell all of this.
Ribbit stick, double punch is not good.
Hurly gloves, not as good, right?
No.
Yeah, trust this can be sold.
Trooper shell, parasol, hurly gloves,
double stick, ribbit stick.
Sailor shirt, sailor cape, not a good dress.
I'm gonna hold on to the work pants just in case.
Rest of the stuff, jump shoes,
I'm just kind of keeping them for no reason.
Okay, let's buy.
How many, I have no more mid mushrooms.
Five pick me ups.
I probably should get a couple of these.
You know what, I feel like I haven't had
a flower box in a while.
Here we go, a flower jar, finally, okay.
Hmm, get rid of this mushroom.
Use the flower box right now.
Still want these pure waters, I can sell the pure water,
what do I care?
It's worth a lot.
Rock candy is really good.
Still have the seed, I'm not getting rid of that.
This looks all right, maybe a couple more maple syrups.
Five of them, all right, I'm ready.
I used to work for King Nimbus,
but all of a sudden one day,
Valentina told me I was fired.
I just don't get it.
He needs help, he's sick.
We used to be able to walk through the castle freely,
but I guess we shouldn't disturb the king now.
Have you seen the volcano?
Not yet.
Ooh, the volcano's to the east.
Sure wish I could take a dip in the springs.
I'm watching that volcano over there, what?
Star pieces, huh, never heard of them.
Why did Prince Malo make Valentina his queen?
I guess it's because she found him.
You know about the royal bus?
What's the royal bus?
It's a regal vehicle used only by the king.
It's parked now due to the fact that he's ill.
I'm going, before we do this, I'll be right back.
Hot springs are up ahead,
but only royalty can bathe in there,
and you don't look so royal.
I wanna go give the seed to the elder guy.
I think it's over here, right?
Where is the elder?
Up here.
See this pot over here?
This is the elder of the town.
Oh, it's the gardener.
Hi, I'm the gardener.
See that huge planter?
I spent many years seeking the legendary seed
and fertilizer to fill it with,
but I've had no luck.
If only I could find them.
Oh, incredible, I can't believe it.
It's a legendary seed.
I've been reading about it in the average garden text.
These are so rare.
Can you even begin to comprehend what a huge discovery this is?
I spent my whole life.
Hey, I haven't finished yet.
Well, that's my story.
Will you give me that seed?
I finally have it.
This is extraordinary.
He has the seed, I need to bring the fertilizer.
I need to get the fertilizer.
Something special might happen.
Now, I'm going to go fight Jinx again.
Those of you who remember who Jinx is,
he's the guy back here in monster town.
We're doing a cleanup loose ends here.
I wonder if I can beat him.
I also have the temple key, which I haven't used.
All right, let me save it first.
Where is there a save point in here?
Isn't there someone in here somewhere?
I also didn't do the 30 jumps either.
Who the hell is the save point here?
I'll be fine.
Hole, hole, hole, hole, hole.
I don't remember.
You don't actually die though, if you lose to Jinx.
You want a challenge?
Let's go.
Here we go.
Let's see if I can beat him.
Ooh, I don't think so.
Quick, run away.
Run.
Just get up, just get up.
How disappointing, running during the middle of a match.
Come back when you've leveled up sufficiently
and we'll try again.
Instant death.
Mario instant death.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's what happens when chat chooses levels up.
I want to go back to the temple.
I have a temple key.
I'm fairly certain I can do something in here.
I go up here, I have to get my fortune again.
Where is it?
I'm not accepting visitors, it's past my bedtime.
Okay, there we go.
There he is.
That key you have there looks pretty tasty.
You can have the key.
It's poison.
Absolute jackpot.
Royal syrup.
Max mushroom.
Fire bomb.
No, it's the worst, probably picked me up.
Or mushroom maybe, yeah.
And then one, two, three, four flower tabs.
Now, I think it's time that I try to do the casino.
We have to go back to Booster's Tower.
Wait, what am I doing?
I just leave, can't I?
No.
I just want to go in there.
Just keep and smell the cards.
I have to go win a other casino game.
A shitload of times, I think, if I remember this
from what I Googled.
Back to Booster's Tower.
All right, we have to make it back up to the top
to go to the secret casino.
And then it includes that chain chomp.
Come on, I'm telling you, I'm way higher than these guys.
I can run.
Jeremy.
Look, just get her.
Just.
Am I gonna fight the secret boss?
Yes.
I will defeat, probably first try,
the hardest secret, almost impossible boss in the game.
In fact, I probably guarantee it.
Because I'm going to have certain items
that will make me very, very strong.
There he is.
I'm really, really sorry about before.
Here, I'll make it up to ya.
Yeehaw.
Are you having fun yet?
Hee hee.
Ah, that was just practice.
This time for real.
Yep, do it.
Guess which hand the yellow ball is in.
If you can, watch carefully.
Which hand is it in?
Very good, it's a prize.
You want to play?
I do.
Which hand is the yellow ball in?
Again.
The wilt shroom.
Ooh, doesn't that, this is for the weirdo, right?
The weirdo wants one of these.
What's cheaper, pick me up or mid-mushroom?
Want to play?
There we go.
Left again.
Wilt shroom, more wilt shrooms.
I don't think I want more than one of these.
It's wilted.
Let's go.
Right, another wilt shroom.
I have to do it again.
Left hand.
Another wilted shroom.
Want to play again?
I do.
Right, rotten mush.
Right, mid-mushroom.
Hey, cool, throw it away.
Left hand.
More rotten mush.
I don't want it, because I already have one.
What's the text on this?
Ew, it's rotten.
Again, what the fuck is happening?
I have to do this.
Come on, how many more do I need to do?
Like two, three?
Left, moldy mush.
All right, right hand.
Congratulations, you deserve this.
You got a bright card.
All right, throw away, pick me up.
I'll let you get into my brother's casino.
Wherever that is.
Member's card for the casino.
Come on, let's go save it.
Now we go back to Bean Valley.
Can I do anything else up here?
Trying to remember if there's anything else to do
in the booster tower.
Oh, come on, this is still active?
Get out of here.
It's nonsense.
Oops.
Oh yeah, they have new weapons.
Let's get the big hamburger gloves.
Oh my God, I just don't want.
Just do it, I don't care.
I don't even want to do any more attacks.
Mari.
Do you want to play a casino?
Just play the new NBA game.
It has an actual slot machine for real money.
You know what, just do it.
Wait, why does an NBA game have slot machines in it?
I didn't even touch it.
That doesn't make any sense.
I want to win my next bribe and fall from the sky.
Well, that wasn't worth coming all the way up here.
How dry his mouth must be.
Pretty dry.
So let's get to the casino.
Now I have to go back to Bean Valley.
Oh my God.
I just, I can't even run away.
Oof, I like that.
That's got a good sound to it.
Okay.
Let's go back to Bean Valley.
Go in there and do the thing we need to do
go in the secret casino.
I'm excited.
Bean Valley.
Pretty good dodges right there.
It doesn't sound very excited.
Well, I can assure you, I am very excited.
Did Jerma play Mario 64?
That's all I did when I was younger.
It's the only game I played.
What about this one up here?
Let's go, dude.
Let's go.
Would I ever try to speed run this game?
No, I never tried to speed run any game,
let alone this one.
I told you this joke before,
I was actually gonna try to memorize the first 12,
probably five to 10 minutes, maybe 10 minutes total
of the Dark Souls one speed run.
I was gonna try and learn the first
at least few minutes of the Dark Souls one speed run
and just do it on stream
and just pretend like I was gonna actually do it.
Here we go.
Great guys casino.
It's inside of somebody's house.
It's a really, really high and plain site here, huh?
Great guy.
Please enjoy yourself.
Hello, Mario.
I run this casino.
Feel free to enjoy yourself.
Business is slow.
Hey Mario, wanna play look the other way with me?
Ready and look the other,
hit left or right on the control pad.
Wait, gotcha, I win.
What a shitty casino.
Let's do it again.
Look the other way.
Got it.
Oh, you didn't get caught.
I lost this round.
You can have this.
Multi mush and guess what we have to do.
Look the other way.
You can have this.
A mushroom.
Ooh.
I'm not gonna say he's gonna go right.
That's what he wants me to think.
Yep.
Rotten mush.
He's gone left a few times.
He's gonna go left.
Damn it.
God damn it.
Same way.
What?
You did three times to the right?
Oh my God.
He's playing me like a film.
What the fuck?
Oh my God.
This is almost statistically not possible.
I did it.
That's unfucking believable.
When do I get the item?
I know you didn't do this a bunch of times
like the other one.
Oh, why?
I win.
I have to win a hundred times?
No, I don't.
You have to win up 100 fucking times?
Welcome to the great guy casino.
Wanna play the slot machine?
Absolutely.
How do I use that?
How do I do it?
Costs 10 coins per game.
Hit it once to start the game.
Each consecutive hit will freeze one of the pictures.
Match all three and you might win a frog coin.
Mushroom, star, star, star, star, star, star, star, star.
Star, star, star, star, star.
Oh, you have to jump when you see.
So now it's, there's no way I can do this one.
This is it.
It's rigged.
So I have to jump when I see the star, right?
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump.
Oh my fucking God.
It's rigged.
See, okay.
I thought I timed that pretty well.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
I did it.
I'll do one more.
Welcome to Blackjack.
Let's play around, let's go.
I don't know, I know how to play Blackjack.
Don't even tell me.
Two cards.
Your first two card, your first card.
What is it Mario?
You got a 10.
Okay, his second card.
Six, is he gonna get a 16?
I will draw one card.
Draw or stay.
Well, what do you have?
I can't see what the dealer has for the first,
I can't see?
What if you have, what?
I will draw a card.
I have 26.
I broke 21, you won.
Here's your frog coin.
Let's go, I'm gonna get a hundred fucking frog coins.
I have to just take his word for it.
All right, seven, two.
I would like to draw.
I got a seven.
I'll play with this hand.
Draw or stay Mario.
16 again.
Well, I don't know what he has.
How am I supposed to know?
You hit on 16 if you're showing like an eight or a nine,
seven, eight, nine, 10.
I don't know what he has.
All right, I win.
Just kidding.
I'll take a frog coin.
This is the shittiest blackjack ever.
I thought I had 15 for some dumb reason.
All right, I got a two.
I think I should, I'll draw please.
16 again, against who has any idea.
I'm gonna stay, of course you do.
17, I have to stay on 17.
I don't know what your cards are.
I don't even like this game.
Where's my frog coin back?
Stay on 17 or more?
That's true.
But if I could see his card,
if he had a 10 facing up,
then you pretty much assume you're gonna lose again.
That gives him a chance to win.
Give me another 10.
Thank you, split.
All right, am I back to positive again?
Seven.
I am at plus one.
All right, give me another card and make it a 10,
make it 21, see you later.
Three, that's great.
Fantastic.
I'll stay.
I have 24, I have plus two, here's your frog coin.
All right, plus two, right?
Where's my frog coin?
46, I was at 50 frog coins.
Oh, I can't just use it for free.
I'm actually in my plus two.
I'm good.
I want to go look at, I think I want to go,
I think I want to get the XP ring.
It's a big purchase.
Oh, also the Turovsky.
Doubles experience when equipped.
That's so, that's amazing.
Coins is not a big deal,
but I will just stomp on everything late game
and it'll just be like, let's go.
Or I cut FP in half.
Yeah, I also have to do the fireworks and get the stone.
I'm going for the XP boost.
It's done, it's too late.
Who's going to wear it?
Probably Toadstool.
All right, that's done.
I'm going to need to have a ton of boosted up levels
for the real final boss of the game.
I need to go get fireworks.
Now wait, fireworks gives you the stone.
Stone then is you.
Okay, so where do I get the fireworks?
I think it's from mole town, right?
Who's selling fireworks?
Oh, there's mushroom guy too.
A mystery egg, I have no idea what it does.
It sort of grows on you, huh?
It's yours for 200 coins, I'll take it.
You can't get inside Bruce's tower really easily.
You need a strong person.
What can I get?
Who's selling fireworks?
You're a hero, Mario.
If it weren't for you,
Dinah would still be inside that mountain.
Oh, I wish I had a card about cookie.
Go to my pretend store.
Would you like a shiny stone?
Yes.
I have you bring me a fireworks
as you get your shiny stone.
Who's selling fireworks?
You?
Pa fixed the roof up.
He's singing mobile blues
and putting in a hard day's work.
Who's selling fireworks?
Oh, I think it's you.
You like fireworks
and working on my very own invention right now.
I've only got the sparkles down, but I ain't giving up.
Want to buy one for 500 coins.
Well, don't think I'm going to the casino
for like fucking 30 minutes.
I can sell some shit.
I mean, that's the easiest way
to keep myself out of the casino.
I don't think I need it for anything.
I, yeah, there's still an item.
I'm not gonna beat,
I'm not going to do that a hundred times.
Damn, that's a lot of money.
I'm keeping these moldy mushrooms
for the guy, the mushroom dude.
What the hell am I gonna,
should I just sell a Carol, Carol, Cola?
I mean, it's a full recovery.
That's not a good idea.
Remember, this is just like Resident Evil 2.
I'm going to hold onto these Carol, Carol, Colas
until the credits roll.
I will never use them.
I can, I can get that money.
It's over.
$500.
Thank you.
Fireworks for the shiny stone.
And then you guys are going to get a sneak peek
for those of you who have never seen it before.
Welcome to my pretend store.
Would you like a shiny stone?
Yes.
You'll trade your fireworks?
Thank you.
Please come again.
Shiny stone.
I got it.
Let's go see.
I'm going to save the game
so you can see what's happening here,
but you don't even need to, it's cool.
It's all cool.
Here we go.
A sneak peek preview of the hardest boss in the game.
Giving fireworks to little kids.
I didn't even think about that.
All right, here we go.
You ready?
It's been sealed.
Look, the shiny stone is reacting.
The seal has been broken.
Greetings.
I am Kuulix, dark knight of thunder.
I have crossed into this dimension
to fight for the dark mage,
but this world is uninhabitable for me and my kind.
I must return to my own world before I go though.
I would like to challenge your strongest knight.
Will you accept my challenge?
Will you enter combat against me?
Sure, what can go wrong?
Unguard.
I am matter.
I am anti-matter.
I can see your past and I can see your future.
I consume time and I will consume you.
That hurts.
Goodbye, Jano.
Mario's dead here, too.
Goodbye.
That was a one hit kill from pretty much full health.
And that peach is still alive.
No.
Dead.
I didn't beat him first try as promised.
No, no, but that's not, that wasn't a real first try.
I wanted you to see the character.
That didn't count, I wanted you to see it.
That's a sneak peek.
No, I just walked in there with no armor on
and just took my helmet off and said,
shoot a bolt of lightning at my face.
I'll be back.
I didn't even try to fight.
Cause that's not even the party I would go in with.
That is, but yes, that's the hardest boss in the game.
Even the actual true final encounter
to get the credits to roll is,
that is probably 10 times harder than that.
Like that fight right there.
Let's head back here.
So that leaves us with, let me see,
we got a Nimbus land, what do we got left?
Let me get a look at the whole map.
I think I can, how do I get out?
I don't know, get back up.
Isn't it like a L and R?
How do I get like a full view?
I don't know there's a way to do it.
Up, down, left, how do I get out of this?
I want to see what's left.
Oh, there we go.
All right, so we have, from here,
we've gone through all this.
We're currently about right here in Nimbus land.
Nimbus land, we've probably got,
we've probably got about,
yeah, like probably like another four or five hours,
I would say.
So what I'm going to do,
I think that's probably going to be it for tonight.
No, I want to clean up a couple other things,
but that's it for like game progression.
I'm going to clean up a couple of the other
small little things that I want to do.
We're about 10 p.m. Pacific,
we're getting about 1 a.m. Eastern.
Did Phylactery Lich just get 49 more subs?
You madman.
You've lost your mind.
Another 50 subs from Phylactery Lich.
Holy shit.
Thank you so much Phylactery
in your insane contributions.
This over here is the most,
probably most fun of the whole game.
There is this interesting,
there's an interesting puzzle mechanic in here,
where you pick a series of rooms and a series of doors,
and it's very, very odd,
very interesting, cool things to do.
Just this part in here is probably about an hour or two.
This is probably about two hours,
maybe like an hour and a half, two hours,
and then like probably two hours here, two and a half.
So I think I'd want to do this on another stream,
but I'm not done yet,
because I'm going to go do the Game Boy thing.
And that's all right.
And then Kool-X as well, which that might take a while.
I might die a few times depending on how I approach it.
Where's the little, where's the game kid?
Merrymore?
Rosetown, where's the little kid?
Merrymore, right?
No, it's all the way in the beginning.
And the mushroom guy, that's right.
I got to go back to mushroom guy.
Where is he? In the corner over here?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right, yes, I'm done.
You want this for 500 coins.
Suit yourself.
God damn it, I need to sell more stuff.
I need 500 coins.
About to do it.
Quickest way you can get money.
Safety badge is 250, but it's really,
the ghost medal is really useful too.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm selling the card.
It's gone.
Say goodbye to the card.
I'm not going to that casino anymore.
Ah, I can't do it.
I just need to go make some cash.
Who cares?
I'm selling.
Like, I'm not going to use these.
I'm not, I know it because I've got peach.
I'm back.
I'll take it, 500 coins.
Want me to teach you?
Yes.
High score if you hit the shells with the stars
fired from the beetle.
If you get hit, recover by firing consecutively.
Just do it.
Select game on the menu and you can play beetle mania,
but please be sure not to cheat with the turbo type controller.
I'll try.
What happened?
Why am I getting hit by it?
What's going on?
Oh, the red stars are hitting me.
You want to hit them when they're highest.
Am I actually going to do this to 5,000 points?
I should just wait.
Wait till there's a bunch on the screen.
Start a chain reaction.
I got to beat this kid's high score.
I have to.
All right, you got to get the combo.
Oh, my screen just, I guess lagged.
Holy shit, I just got so many.
How many points did I just get?
What just happened?
I think I broke the game.
I just got 146,000 points.
Can I, now can I like turn it over to the kid
and be like, I did this in 10 minutes.
You've been here for weeks, kid.
I'm going to stay in the corner.
Oh shit.
Nice.
I got to get as many on the screen as I can.
No, no, no, no.
Damn it.
Okay, how many presses does it take?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Okay, seven.
Let's just test that theory.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay.
Three, four, five, six, seven.
Why did that not work?
How did I get so many multipliers last time?
I have no idea how I did that.
I'm not sure there's an amount of things
that can be on the screen.
All right, here we go.
Let me try it again.
Last try.
I mean, I can't really beat 146,000.
More.
More on the screen.
Shit.
This music's driving me crazy.
Come on.
All right, that was 12,000.
What's that?
I didn't even see that.
What's a heart do?
Oh, what?
Come on.
That wasn't anything.
String, string, string.
String.
Oh, I ran out.
Last, last, last, last one.
What the fuck?
I don't think I'll just,
the length of this time have anything to do with it.
You gotta get lucky with the chain.
We need a bunch on this.
So you need to get a shitload on the screen without firing.
More, more, more, more, more, more.
One, two.
I kinda did it.
Okay.
More.
All right, that's it.
Oh.
All right, not bad.
Why are they here?
Did they run into each other?
Close.
We're getting there.
All right, I'm starting to run out.
I'm running out of juice here.
Oh.
Come on.
No.
67,000.
What are you gonna give me?
Oh, I'm obsessed with this.
You gotta maximize the beginning.
So it's seven presses.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
No, it's six.
Now it's seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Come on.
Why is 146,000 not enough?
Cause it's not 150,000.
That's a huge problem for my brain.
No, it needs to be clean.
It needs to be clean.
This is the actual final try.
Changes based on who's in the middle of the party.
I just read that.
That's pretty damn cool.
Come on.
Good one.
What?
How did that not get anything?
Do it.
Try shooting the corners.
Oh baby.
That was fucking pretty good.
I'm running out of steam.
This is the one.
Give me the heart.
Oh.
No, I got it.
I get it.
I actually get it.
I get it now.
You gotta try to spread it up all the way from the corner.
Thank you.
Come on.
Dammit.
Switch the background.
Hold on.
Not yet.
Oh, it's never gonna happen again.
All right.
I need some more to fill up.
That's it.
Oh, you mother.
What?
How could you not hit something?
It's impossible.
Statistically, you gotta run into somebody.
Do it.
You assholes.
I have to start over.
All right.
I'll change the background.
Actually easier to see this.
Come on.
That was a lot.
It's so hard to breach.
It's not fair.
Just don't shoot.
Well, it's almost impossible not to
because every button shoots
and the only way you don't die.
So when I get hit, right,
I have to tap shoot to spawn.
And every time I get hit,
I have to tap it one more time.
So one, two, three, four, five, six, right?
Don't hit it again.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
And eventually you kind of just can't.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
You've got to be.
You're gonna be kidding me.
This is so dramatic.
Is this the one?
Oh, don't.
This is more difficult than a casino.
Yes, it is.
Shit.
It's possible.
You can't dodge it.
It's impossible.
Good start.
Just need two more big ones.
I'm pressing this shit so fast.
You have no idea.
I'm the fucking master.
Let's get to a goddamn million.
250, 250, get over there.
I can get it.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Give me the heart.
I did it.
I got you a fucking million.
I got you a million.
Two million.
My arm hurts so much.
No.
That's a two million fucking books.
Give me two million.
Give me 10 million.
Oh.
He's gone insane.
I lost my mind.
We're gonna have two million points.
It's not gonna end.
I've reached the point of like no return
where it's impossible for me to lose
and I'm gonna get like a hundred million points.
No, that's not a good strategy.
You gotta get them when they're bouncing around.
Like that.
I'm doing this in front of the high score kid.
I'm just cackling.
He got 5,000 points.
Get on my level, you little bastard.
All right, five million
and I've ripped the fucking ethernet code out of my computer.
I have to stop.
You know what I'm saying?
Like at some point you gotta just call it a day.
Holy shit.
It's 999.
It can't even go any higher.
That was max combo right there.
And I thought 5,000 was hard.
Once you get to this point,
it's just impossible to lose.
Five million, that's it.
I think five million is a number that is just perfect.
You know what I'm saying?
It's a perfect number.
Get exactly five million.
That's impossible.
Actually, it might not be.
No, that is actually possible.
I'm gonna go for it.
Good idea.
Why is it slowing down?
Am I just getting slow?
Am I getting tired?
I can't tell.
I didn't chain these over 99999.
Five million, exactly.
Five million points.
3.8 million, almost there.
This all wasn't for nothing, I promise.
Get to four, come on.
I just love that.
I like the sound that it makes.
I'm a bug to a light bulb.
All right, here we go.
I gotta be careful here.
Five, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero.
Easy.
Don't do too good.
That's pretty damn good.
How much is one?
I have to start shooting them, right?
Let's see, it's like 70.
I can do it.
I almost blew it there.
Holy fuck, okay.
It's still going.
4.8, we're almost there.
It's almost time.
Okay, 4.8.
I gotta start to shoot them on my own now.
No, not yet.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I understand if you have to leave.
If you wanna leave, I get it.
I really do.
I get it.
Trust me, I do.
But I'm going for 10 million.
Keep away from my internet cord.
I wanna see if it goes to 10 million.
It might not even go to 10 million.
It might break at 999,999,000.
We're fine.
I'm gonna do it very good.
There we go, it's gonna be like six million right there.
Five and a half million.
What if I do five, five, five, five, five?
I'm gonna go five, five, five, five, five, five, five.
What the fuck happened?
I like blacked out.
Okay, I like kind of blacked out there.
I like, my brain just, I turned off.
Five, 55 million.
5.5.
All right, one more.
I'm kidding.
That's 10.
That's five and a half million, come on.
See you around, kid.
I'm gonna teach you.
Trust me, kid, I already know.
I don't get anything from doing the high score?
No, well.
Well, that's it.
You ruined his life.
No, I didn't.
There are plenty of games.
He's probably way better than me at Fortnite.
I guarantee it.
He still has the Game Boy.
Yeah, I handed it back to him.
I was like, take it, egg-o-kid.
Try to beat that.
And it's just the both handles
are just covered in greasy fingerprints.
His screen just has fingerprints all over it.
Potato chip fucking hands all over his A button.
His B button is smushed in
and you have to mirror over it
and press down hard to even have it register.
I'll see you later.
That's the end of the stream.
Well, not technically the complete end,
but the end of this portion.
I do have to take my headphone out
because that's all I can,
I can't hear any of the sounds besides that now.
Oh, next up is Terraria now.
So I'll see you guys, what's today?
I'll see you guys probably on Thursday.
Thursday, we'll go again.
End of the stream, beatbox.
I don't think I can.
Time for the Terraria.
No Jerma all week.
Hey, it's Monday.
Today's Monday and Thursday is still this week
and Friday is still this week, too.
But I'll see you guys on Thursday.
I'll see you guys on Thursday.
And Friday is still this week, too.
But I love these Mario RPG streams.
They are just fun to relax and just play a game
I know everything about.
Well, like 90% of everything.
Thanks for sticking around, guys.
We will complete Mario RPG on the next stream.
But because it's probably only gonna be
another three or four hours,
I'm gonna do something else, too.
We might open with something
or we might open with this and close with something else
because it's not gonna be more,
because this is, the game's only about 15 to 18 plus.
So it's only about three or four more hours left.
Unless, yeah, unless Kool-X is an insanely hard thing
that I can't do, which I think I should be able to.
So this is Thursday,
the same time around three to four o'clock Pacific.
We will be doing potentially two things on Thursday,
finishing this up and something else.
Thank you for joining me.
See you guys later.
Have a good next couple of days.
Let's rewind back to earlier this evening.
We had some subs and some bits and all that stuff.
Sergelbutt gave 250.
They say, please clap.
I did.
Thank you, whole of one zombie for the 250.
My team understands the German mug pitched to you
wasn't up to scratch.
Here's at It's a Bitcrap.
We pride ourselves on groundbreaking designs.
We hope this new batch suits your requirements.
Look forward to working with you.
Out of my ass.
No one would buy this.
I was like, you know, I thought about a while back.
I was gonna do the German old emote as an iPhone case,
but then I realized no one would buy it.
And I know that people will say, no, I would.
That would be so funny.
I would open up like my Teespring account.
It'd be like 11 purchases over like five weeks.
So I was like, yeah,
maybe it's not worth like the cost to do it.
I'm not sure what the top one is.
That's a wallet down there.
Those are sneakers.
But what is the top one?
Is it a t-shirt?
Just a really, really shitty t-shirt.
It's not even the right way.
That's a tie?
Oh, I thought the guy,
I thought it was an open shirt with a white t-shirt.
And that was at the bottom.
Like that gross old man's stomach fanny pack.
I was like, why that t-shirt sucks?
Thank you though for this.
I will not be using any of them.
Did I save the game?
I did, right?
Let me make sure I did.
But thank you, Whole of One Zombie, appreciate it.
And power down.
Also, thank you to SirK9 for the $5.
Hey Jerma, it's Kevin's mom again.
I don't appreciate you trying to censor me
from your audience about how you caused
serious injuries to my son.
It's gotten worse.
And now all he does is he sings and plays
and dances to the Han Solo song from Star Wars.
I hope you're happy.
Kevin, listen to your mother.
Listen to your mother, Kevin.
I know you're watching.
Listen to your mother, see?
I helped.
Thank you to Allie, Allie Titian with the $10, Allie.
$10 and 15 cents.
Thank you, appreciate it.
No message, just thousand bits.
Thank you.
Thank you Drumajor, or Drumage Door, for the $2.50.
I had a dream a couple days ago
in which I was making music
and you were commentating to it
with the LOL epic YouTuber style
that made me remember what the heck happened to that.
I'm gonna make my own music stream
as we're looking forward to it.
The carnival stream happened.
I had to pick something to focus on.
And I thought that that was more interesting to me
at the time.
What happened to your book?
You know, I've gone over what happened to my book
like probably a thousand times.
I ripped it in half, I put it in a shredder.
I wrote like 17 pages.
I copy and pasted just random parts of the book
into the chat like two years ago.
I wasn't cut out for it.
I'm not cut out for it.
I'm writing a thesis.
I'm at 130 pages.
I couldn't even get to like 16.
But I also was making,
I was trying to like do way more elaborate stuff
with Choose Your Own Adventure stuff.
Writing a Choose Your Own Adventure book,
you have to write like 15 books.
That's the amount of data that's inside of one of these.
And I got overwhelmed and I was like,
this is probably not gonna work.
I wish I could.
But that is what happened to the music stream
that got eaten both financially
and kind of mentally by the carnival stream.
All things off stream that I would be potentially working on
is carnival stream until the 22nd of September essentially.
And then I'll be kind of wanting to do something else.
But hope that answers your question.
Thank you Nukable for the $10.
Hey Jerem, long time viewer, first time donator.
I've been watching since your TF2 days.
Jerma Hart, PS, please play Metal Gear Solid 3.
That's a great game.
In fact, I would probably put it up there
with in the top two, I think.
I think that's probably one of the best ones.
May even be the best one.
But thank you Nukable for the 10 bucks.
Glad you stuck around.
But I have no immediate plans to play any Metal Gear stuff.
But thank you.
Thank you Blue Crew for the $5.
Hi Jerma, I just turned 22 today.
Happy birthday, first of all.
And I want to share the celebration
with one of my favorite people on the internet.
Been watching since your grandpa Call of Duty videos
and you've helped me through some tough times.
Was wondering if you'd be interested in streaming
one of my favorite games, Lisa.
Cool Earthbound inspired indie game.
Anyways, thanks for everything, man.
Thank you for the $5.
I have actually touched upon Lisa before.
I have said I'm not going to play it on stream.
Unfortunately, I will not be playing Lisa on stream.
Play Celeste.
I did play Celeste.
I beat Celeste on stream.
That wasn't that long ago.
That was only like, what, four or five months ago?
I've done that.
It was fun.
It was a really good game.
But happy birthday.
Happy 22nd birthday.
Have a good one.
Eat cake if you like it.
If you don't like cake, substitute that for ice cream.
That's what I do.
Who wants cake?
We got cake here.
And I'm like, can I, can I just ice cream?
And you get that fucking squinting stare.
Like, really?
No, that's okay.
Thank you.
Thank you though.
Happy birthday.
Thank you Apple shit for the 250.
Hey man, do you listen to Taylor Swift?
She's my fave.
And she just put out a new album.
So I've got to ask, have a great day.
Let me try to come up with one song from Taylor Swift
that I could reliably say is Taylor Swift's song.
Let me try it.
Hold on.
She wears sneaker.
I wear sneakers.
I'm in the bleachers.
Right?
Is that one?
That's Taylor Swift, right?
I don't know the name of that song.
All I know is that that is Taylor Swift singing that song.
And you, and you, and you belong with me.
Eee.
I had to just decide if I was going to be able
to hit her or not and I could.
I don't, I'm glad you like Taylor Swift.
That's the only song I've ever heard on the radio.
I don't even listen to the radio.
Guys, I silently sit in the car.
Does anybody else do that?
I don't listen to music or anything.
I just sit there quietly in the car and just drive.
Does that make me a psycho?
But I need to be, no, I can't.
It's the sounds of the road and the tires
and the vibrating of the dashboard and stuff.
Guys, I make my own and I talk to myself in the car.
How would I ever be able to play music
when I'm having incredibly detailed conversations
out loud with myself?
He's Patrick Bateman.
No, no, people, everybody does that.
You even pull up at a red light and you look over
at the car next to you and this,
and somebody is just talking away.
Just their mouth is moving up and down and all kinds of,
they're like really distinctively,
and there's nobody in the car.
And then you understand there's no music,
so they're not lip syncing or singing along with anything.
And they don't, there's no call.
They're not on the phone.
No, they're not.
They're not on a cell phone.
They're looking straight,
they don't have their hands are both on the wheel.
No, no audio coming out of that car.
No hands-free phone.
Why are you staring at this person?
It's free phone calls.
Well, good.
I'm glad you all think that.
I'm glad that's all what you guys have in your brain
whenever you see anybody doing that.
Because when you pull up next to me,
I'm not on the phone,
but that means everybody thinks I am.
So that's good.
I'm glad.
That makes me really happy in knowing that people
will just be like, oh, that guy's on the telephone.
No, I'm not.
You don't do it while walking down the street.
No, because the car,
an automobile is a completely enclosed space.
It's like, it's almost like your own,
it's like being in the bathroom.
It's like your own personal little bathroom space.
Nobody's there.
If you're, if it's nobody in there,
you can, you can talk, you can just relax.
You drive, you obviously pay attention to the road,
but it's like your own little space.
You're enclosed.
No, you don't go to the bathroom in your car.
It's the only place where you can truly scream.
This person gets it.
You get it.
In the car is the only place where you can scream.
You can be like, woohoo!
And it's just, it's fine.
It's just you.
If I do that here, I'm gonna wake somebody up.
Just do that on your Twitch streams.
You do that in the bathroom.
No, I don't do that in the bathroom.
The car is the safest place to make weird noises.
Yeah, you can just be in the car and be like,
boop, boop, boop, boop, ooo, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Ain't anybody ever gonna fucking know you did that.
I just did that right now.
I bet you Kim heard what I just did.
She's, I mean, after the stream's over,
she's probably gonna come up and be like,
why'd you make those weird noises?
And I'm gonna be like, god, wish I was in my fucking car.
What kind of car does Jeremy Albertson drive?
We already went over this.
You guys are gonna have to guess.
You'll never get it.
It's so cool.
No, it's not a 2009.
Yeah, it is.
Did I talk about this already?
Did you guys already get it?
Did I already?
Oh, yeah, you guys already got it, nevermind.
The mystery is solved.
Nevermind.
But, enough of that, we'll move on.
Thank you to Gnarly for the 250.
Today I learned that some of the voices
from Undertale characters are sampled sound clips
from other media.
Flowey's voices are from Ronald McDonald
and Sans is Patrick from Sponged Bob.
Hold on, wait, Flowey's voice is Ronald McDonald?
What clip of Ronald McDonald sounds like that?
That's insane.
Flowey.
That game was really fun.
That game was really just interesting to play.
Hold on, I wanna listen to this.
Sans voice is sample of Patrick going,
maybe it's the way you're dressed,
but the A part is trimmed out and looped.
Oh shit, huh?
The way you're dressed, maybe it, maybe, maybe, maybe.
Wow, interesting, that's cool.
That's, yeah, that's cool.
Did they have the Flowey one?
What's the Ronald McDonald one?
If anyone's got that one, I'm interested in that one too.
This one.
If this is a gnome, this stream's a gnome.
Just make sure where I go,
so you're, maybe you're aware of that.
So you guys really, really, really
are having a good time here.
There's a Rick Roll link and there's a gnome link.
Thanks, thanks to this person that saved the stream.
I'm here.
It packs the right, let's see.
And try shake.
What in the name of, what the fuck?
Make good use of that.
Ah, here they are.
Triple thick McDonald shakes.
Well, they're empty.
You sure can get a lot in these bags, can't you?
You always make good use of that.
Ah, here they are.
Oh.
Damn.
I did that last stream.
It's pretty weird.
But thank you to Gunther.
Thank you Gunther Riddle for the 250.
What is Yardovich's favorite flavor of gum?
Blueberry, I don't know.
Thank you though.
Thank you Gnarly for the 250.
These RPG streams are fun.
Hope you do more in the future.
Preferably Bowser's Inside Story.
But I think we're driven,
we've driven that point home already.
I guess that is the one that everybody likes the most, huh?
But thank you Gnarly.
I thank you Gunther for the 250
and it's the second part of the
what is Yardovich's favorite flavor of gum?
And the answer is Spear?
Spearmint?
Spearmint.
Because of the spear?
That's pretty good.
Thank you BitSlave for the five dollars.
Hey Jeremy, a few streams ago I told you about
how I was stuck in the base, in this base.
You said you hoped I got orders soon
and the very next day I was given orders
to out process.
I'll be attending Survival Evasion,
Resistance, and Escape training.
Well, I'm glad you got actual orders
but you were talking about that.
So I wonder how intensive that is.
Survival Evasion, Resistance, Escape.
Well, good luck with it, whatever it is.
And then they say,
by the way, will you please play League of Legends?
No.
Somebody could knock on this back door here
with like a briefcase full of like 50 grand in it.
And all I had to do was play League of Legends
and understand the whole game
and understand all the champions
and play at a level that I was at least competent
in knowing how to do everything.
I would slowly close the door
and come back and sit up.
I wouldn't do it.
That would take me, you know,
if I had to put in like a hundred hours
to like know everything about every champion,
I wouldn't do it.
I wouldn't do that for fucking 50 grand.
That sounds like, that sounds really, really,
really like entitled.
I wouldn't play a game for 50 grand.
I have no interest at all.
But I don't know, here's another thing though.
I have no interest in like farming either.
If somebody was like,
hey, I'll give you 50 grand
if you'd learn how to plant all these carrots
and corn and shit and like learn to milk cows
and run my farm.
I'm gonna be like, dude, I don't wanna do that.
I don't even know, I don't know,
where am I gonna start?
It would take as long to learn
every recommended perfect meta build
for every champion.
It would take the same amount of time
to learn how to run a farm.
That would be, that would be,
I could probably learn how to run a farm
in three to 500 hours.
I could probably learn how to,
I could, you know, think about like class.
If somebody would teach me how to plant every crop,
it would probably be about 500 hours
of me knowing how to do it.
Would I be any good at it?
No, still takes an extensive amount of knowledge
and skill to be able to run a farm.
It takes, you know, become an outdoor IRL farmer.
I don't think I'm good.
Every crop.
Farming is way more useful.
You know what, now that I think about it,
I would take that,
I would take 50 grand to go be a farmer
because that's, yeah, that is incredibly useful.
I would tell the guy trying to offer me 50 grand
to play League of Legends,
I'd be like, can you just go make a farm?
Pay somebody to make a farm.
Go grow some almonds somewhere.
What is the cutoff for the magazine submissions?
And okay, so let me, I gotta go over this.
This is very, actually really important.
There is no cutoff yet.
There is no cutoff for those submissions at the moment
because I need to place that somewhere.
So there is not a cutoff yet that's not tomorrow.
Because remember I told you last week
that I was gonna have to move it again
because of all this other stuff.
So that is not accurate.
We're just gonna keep those submissions open for now
until I can get a real date.
Somebody said, wait, when is this?
We don't have a date yet.
It was going to be,
the submissions deadline is gonna be tomorrow,
but it's just gonna be open for a little bit.
So take your time.
It's not gonna be closing on like tomorrow
or the next day or something.
This, it'll probably end up closing at some point
like next week and we'll do it like the week after.
It's gonna happen before the carnival stream,
but I kind of haven't been able to focus on it.
What am I talking about?
I'm talking about the activity book stream.
In the discord right now,
there are a series of channels under activity book,
dot to dot, where's Waldo, brain teasers, jokes and the like.
What you can do is you can go there
and submit a community themed image
in one of those categories.
I'm gonna compile a bunch of them to have about,
five to 10, maybe 10 plus dot to dots,
where's Waldo images and we're going to do
a community themed activity book on stream.
I'm gonna do it on stream.
There'll be coloring book pages
that are gonna be in there.
It's just gonna be a neat little thing that we're gonna do.
How am I gonna be picking the ones to use on the stream?
We are going to just kind of pick by our discretion.
So we're gonna try to find the ones that are,
obviously they could, let's say we do 10 to 20 dot to dots
or like 10 to 20, where's Waldo images
and where's Waldo by the way, if you don't know,
it's where you have an incredibly detailed potential image
where you have to hide me in it and I have to find it.
So that's still up in the air.
Just if you're working on something for it,
if you wanna have something for it,
I will have a real actual hard day here soon.
I just have not been able to put any real time into it.
He does scream in the car.
Yeah, like this one time we were going out
and I was so excited.
We got to a red light and I waited for the summer
to pull up next to me and I was like,
Yabba Dabba Doo, he's screaming in the bathroom.
I do not scream in the bathroom, okay?
Unless it's a Yabba Dabba Doo scenario.
Anyway, we're gonna move on.
Thank you to BBBBBBB Bird for the five dollars.
Hey German, much love from Australia.
Unfortunately, the Sans voice is,
right, thanks for the five dollars, appreciate it.
Yabba Dabba Doo scenario equals pee pants moment.
Lots of pee pants moments.
You've been live for seven hours.
You should have consumed six gallons of water by now.
Did you do it?
Hey, Demons V, thanks for the three bucks.
I like Mario RPG out of two.
I think they're very, very good games.
This one is a very good game, singular.
Just don't drink it from the Berkey.
That device is actually pretty good.
I really don't want to have to say this again.
It's not bad.
This next one is Noodle is bad at gaming for three dollars.
Thank you, Noodle.
And they say, I made a funny meme.
What do you mean you made a funny meme, what's that?
It's a me as Sans, do you eat ass?
It's a second long, just click it.
Show us how it would look if we saw you screaming in the car.
No, I'm not doing it.
Smelly boy, thanks to the 250.
Here, here, just the first minute,
you don't have to play this whole,
you don't have to play this on stream.
This is the best Trump impression I've ever heard.
I really can't stand your Stephen Colbert Trump.
My Trump is not Stephen Colbert Trump.
His boy better than that.
Trying to make some middle of the tiny.
He says, he says, hey, it's me, Donald.
I'm just trying to listen and let me tell you something.
I was, I was trying to find.
That, that's the same.
I heard the same thing.
In fact, I said it at the same time
and it was in both of my ears and I heard the same voice.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hey, been loving Mario RPG,
you should play more comfy games like this.
I probably will.
No, Stephen Colbert, Stephen Colbert Trump is like this.
He goes like this.
It's me, Stephen Colbert doing the Stephen Colbert Trump.
I'm sorry, mine's a lot more nuanced than that.
My Trump is a little like this.
He said, I, hey, hold on.
Don't, I don't put my hands in the air
and wave them around like this.
Well, you can't see.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on, we're gonna put this to rest right now.
Oh, that's a good Trump.
That's a good Trump.
And his eyes are rolling back in his head.
What is it?
That's a good Trump.
That's not Trump.
Hold on.
If you think that's even close to what I did.
Get to the part with the rapping and the music.
Get to the part with the rap.
Get to the part with the rapping and the music, okay?
I don't have time to do this.
I can't believe this thing won a Tony.
No, I can't believe this thing won a Tony.
That's unbelievable, not even close.
Your Stephen Colbert doing a Trump impression
is better than the actual impression.
No, it's not.
No way.
My fucking ego.
Shit, that was 20 damage.
It's all right.
God damn it.
Let me tell you, believe me.
Hey, I never claimed to be an impressionist.
I just claimed to be incredibly gifted
at doing other people's voices.
Oh, fuck.
Have I seen the tongs?
I don't know what the tongs are.
That's a good question.
I will come down and help you look in a minute.
If I liked your lich also gave an insane amount of subs,
let's go ahead and put them on screen.
Cause I mean, it was 49 gifted subs.
They're gonna fly by.
Here they are.
Thank you everybody for the subs.
Thanks for new subs, old subs, community subs.
If you stuck with this channel for the last four years
or if you just found the channel literally last night.
Thank you.
Have a great next couple of days.
See you guys on Thursday.
We have two more bits to go through.
Much love to all of you.
Thank you.
Gondor Lane, thanks for the 250.
Have you heard of Limbo of the Lost?
It's a really horrible point and click
that's infamous for using stolen assets from a dozen games.
Yet it has its charm of being so bad, it's good.
It's free to download because it's also been abandoned,
but it still has the reputation of the worst point
and click game that has ever existed.
Please play it.
You'll do us all a good favor.
Maybe.
I do wanna do another FMV night
because there's at least a handful of FMV games
that I have not played that I would like to play.
So you will absolutely see me play a bunch of FMV games,
although I don't know if that's also an FMV game.
I do wanna play Ripper.
That should be fun.
Also at the very end, thank you to Flugboy for the $5.
Hey, hope you're doing well.
Jeremy was waiting to ask you, wanted to ask you something.
Now I know you like newer shit like the Gorillaz,
but you like any old school music
like The Beatles, Deep Purple Prince, et cetera.
Yeah, I do.
But I kinda just, I don't have any Beatles albums,
but if The Beatles are on the radio,
when I'm not fucking talking and doing a monologue in the car,
if The Beatles are on somewhere, I'll point up and go,
oh, The Beatles are on here.
Guys, I get most of my music media consumption
from the inside of a grocery store
or whatever is playing in the mall.
And if you're walking around
and you're buying some jeans at Old Navy
and you hear like fucking Prince on the radio,
you look up and you go, oh, all right, Prince, nice.
And then I go back to buying jeans.
But I mean, I like music,
I just don't really listen to a lot of music.
Jeremy is confirmed an NPC.
I'm not an, what do you mean NPC?
I'm a playable character, all right?
What do you mean, what does that mean, true?
True, he's an NPC.
Why, because I walk around the mall
and go into Old Navy and buy jeans
because I don't listen to The Beatles?
That makes me like a non-playable character?
Guess what, guys?
When I play GTA, I turn the damn radio off.
I'm driving around as like Franklin in that car
or as Jared, what's his name?
The other guy, Michael, and I turn it off.
What's his name?
Trevor, Trevor, did I say Jared?
And that might be because I don't wanna get
my channel copyright striked,
but it's also because I'm the playable character
and I don't wanna hear it.
But no, I do not really listen to that much music.
I listen to it when it's available,
but I don't listen to it kind of on purpose.
I'll be like in a club or a bar,
that's the lie, this doesn't happen.
It only happens when for some, I don't go to clubs.
But if I was there, I would hear the music in the club.
I can't even tell, I don't even remember
the last time I walked into a club.
It has to have been when I was like, I don't know, like 22?
I have not walked inside of a club
in probably 10 fucking years.
I don't even know what they play in clubs anymore.
The guy with the marshmallow head, right?
And they play Fortnite music.
That's what I heard.
All right, I'm leaving.
I'm actually seething.
I'm kidding, it's a joke.
I'll see you guys on Thursday.
Bye, good night, goodbye.
See you Thursday.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a good night.