Hey, what is going on everybody? It's Jerma here again with another gameplay commentary.
This time we're playing as the Spy on Payload Badwater.
One of the more popular maps in the game. I've done a couple of commentaries on here, one or two.
Playing as the Spy as you see here with the Dead Ringer, the Big Erner,
and the new Diamondback, the new Spy Revolver.
I don't do anything with it. I don't even know why I had it equipped, to be honest.
So don't expect me to go on some kind of tangent with three or four or five crits.
I don't even get one crit in the gun one time.
I kill a couple people with it though, so don't be too too concerned about it.
And if you have not heard, tonight is the night that I do my live stream, my first ever live stream.
Don't be too mad because I'm not going to play Team Fortress 2 the entire time.
I'm going to play Team Fortress 2 for a while, but my plan guys is to play Deus Ex.
I haven't even loaded the game Deus Ex, so I have to install it.
So once that's installed, once it's all ready to go,
I want to stream that because I hear it is an unbelievably fun game.
There's a lot of choices in that game too,
so I'm sure you guys can help me pick the things when you're in the stream tonight.
So be online at like 9 o'clock tonight Eastern Time.
I'm not sure what that is for anybody else's time zones,
but try and be on 9 o'clock Eastern Time. Should be a fun time.
And oh my goodness, it's already been a minute and a half and I haven't killed one person.
Let's change that right now. Medic Demoman coming up here towards the point.
They already capped it, it's okay, but I get one, two, and I turn around and this medic is kind of alone.
I thought he was going to kill me, but no, I pump him full of lead.
So I bagged the triple right there, which is a good thing,
because now they do not have a medic right here.
And I'm going to give you some spy tips right now, guys.
A lot of people see these as unorthodox or as not super elite or not pro,
but I have found them to work great.
I'm going to give you a number one thing to do when you're playing as a dead ringer spy.
If it doesn't work for you, I'm sorry, it's not going to work for everybody,
but it works for me and it works for other people I've told it to,
and hopefully you can use it too.
So here it is, the secret to playing spy from Jerma, walk backwards.
See what I'm doing right here? I am just facing forward at my teammates
and walking straight back and nobody gives a crap to spy check me.
So I can go on a little tangent and kill three or four people,
and then take the... once you kill one or two people,
guys, this is something you have to remember.
Once you kill one or two people and there's not a third or a fourth right in your reach,
have the dead ringer out ready to go because you're going to get killed.
The dead ringer is an escape tool. It's not meant to be an invisibility watch.
See how I pulled it out right after killing one person? Don't freak out.
See how I let that guy take a swing at me? I just kind of stood there.
They know you're a dead ringer, but it's okay because it doesn't matter
because they're not going to find you. The only person that's going to find you is a pyro.
That's it. Nobody else can find you unless, of course,
you're standing completely still and a heavy is unloading on you.
I don't understand why that heavy, speaking of heavies, he didn't do anything about it.
Dead ringer's out, killed one person, nobody noticed me, apparently,
and now let's turn and walk with the team. Hey, I'm on your team.
No, see? Look what just happened. I walked backwards and that soldier was
completely oblivious and now I go on a tangent here and I get three kills in a row.
That is the spy tip of the decade for you.
Disguise as somebody on the enemy team and walk backwards.
Now, obviously, this is a strategy that is only able to be used with a dead ringer.
Don't do this with the invisibility watch because there's a chance that somebody could
just stray fire and kill you. That's why the dead ringer has to be out
when you're backwards and look at this. This whole room, they all want me dead and
I actually get one kill with that revolver. I thought that was pretty funny.
You have to probably imagine they were on the mic all screaming about me at the same time
and the whole team was pretty much in that room which I can imagine because I was alive
for about four minutes right there just killing a bunch of people out of their spawn over and over
and over again. Coming around this corner right here, I just want to get the dead ringer activated.
I don't really care about walking backwards at this point. There's a lot of people there
so I figured one of them would have probably spy checked me. I want to just get up here in this
corner. This is a great place to hang out as a spy. Get this heavy. I believe it's a domination.
It is, but who cares? Just trying to get someone to hit me. Come on, somebody hit me. There we go.
Coming around back up these stairs, a great place and we're going to do it all over again.
Spy is all about routine. You just got to get in the flow. You just got to get a feel for the class
because you kind of do the same thing over and over again. You rinse and repeat,
get hit with the dead ringer, come right around, exact same route, do the same exact thing,
get hit again, pull the dead ringer out, pull it around, go the same exact way,
jump across the stairs, do it again. People eventually will start to really get really
pissed off and really start to look for you and that's what you want. You want to cause chaos
because the longer they're looking for you, the longer they're not going to be capping the point
or not going to be going for the objective because remember guys, everything in this game is timed.
There's a time limit on every map so if you can take seconds off that clock by having important
classes come after you, looking around for you, always being afraid of you, you did your job and
your team is probably going to win the game because those last 10 seconds, even if it's 10-20 seconds,
overtime and everything like that is incredibly important so you could just screw the whole team
over. So I get this demo man with an ice stab, come up here and watch this stair stab fail.
I couldn't believe this. I was so pissed about this. What was wrong with that? My knife went
up and everything. The animation went up. I had it. It should have registered. It just didn't work.
Whatever. I've never done a stair stab before really so I was so upset about that.
Less than 40 seconds left here now. Coming around the corner. Kritzkrieg demo right here doesn't
really do too much so kill the medic. He had low health anyway so it's not a big deal. Hanging out
here, nobody saw me apparently. Nobody cared to look at me when I was disguising again.
Back stab is heavy. Go for the medic but it doesn't matter. I miss. Just trying to get behind
everybody and now we're at the point where there's less than 15 seconds left. I run into
another heavy right here and watch this guy. This is weird. What are you doing? Now you realize
I'm trying to kill you? What are you doing? So we end up winning this match. They get overtime but
it doesn't matter. Get a couple more people right here right before the match ends. Maybe one. I
think it's two. No, it is one. Thank you all so much for watching. I really appreciate everybody
that checks out my videos. Come to my live stream tonight guys. 9 p.m. Eastern Standard
Time in the United States. Check your local listings and find out what time that is for you.
Hope to see you all there. Should be a great time. Take care everybody. See you soon.