What is going on guys? Jerma here with a V-Log.
Quick little update. I just want to let you guys know what's going on with the channel.
I want to keep you guys in the loop. So a lot of you guys have probably noticed by now there are
ads on the videos. There are pre-roll ads and stuff like that. And that's because as of right now,
I am a machinima partner. And it's unbelievable to me guys. I really can't believe it.
And I got nobody to thank but all the people that support the channel.
You guys did this. I mean yeah, I make the content but you guys watch and you guys are always
supporting and you guys are always so helpful. You guys are always so awesome. Thank you all so
much. All my subscribers. You guys are fantastic. Unbelievable. And I also got to thank the guys
over at Respawn at the Respawn app. You guys are just as awesome because if it's not for you guys,
maybe I wouldn't even be seen. You know, maybe something like that would have happened. But
all the guys, all the employees at Machinima, I'm not going to let you down. I can promise you that.
And I'm going to start to take this channel a lot more seriously. I'm going to be making content at
the absolute best amount I can make it. The highest amount of quality I can put into it.
And I'm going to continue doing that. And hopefully you guys stick around. Hopefully you guys
are going to keep with me. Stay with the channel for a long time to come. So thank you all so much
everybody. You don't know what it means to me. The second announcement is I have an official
Team Fortress 2 server. The link or whatever, it'll be right there. It's dedicated 24-7 in Chicago.
That's there for you guys. If you guys ever want to play on it, just go play. It's open to the
public. Anyone can play on it. With the only exception that on the weekends or every couple
weekends I'm going to be doing an open lobby. So that information will be available if you are on
the Respawn app. So I highly suggest guys go to the Respawn app and be active there. Join the
Respawn app. Go check out new videos. It's a great place. It's an unbelievable community.
Please guys if you haven't already go over there and just be part of the community
because it's a great place. So thank you all so much. My brain is like all over the place
the last few days trying to piece together the stuff going on up here. But
thank you so much everybody. And peace, love, and respect. See you all next time.