Hi guys, how are you? Yes, we are very, very early. So early. 2 p.m. Eastern now. 11 a.m. Pacific.
It's very early. You know, I went to bed last night and I thought to myself,
you know, I neglect all the European crowd and I felt really bad about it. I was like, you know
what, I need to really start to do EU streams. That's why I did this today. It has nothing to
do with my dog having a vet appointment in like four and a half hours. Absolutely nothing to do
with that. But no, the truth is, yes, I have to go to the vet with Otto. He's fine, don't worry.
But because the appointment is weirdly in the afternoon, instead of just outright just not
streaming today, because it's three, four, five, I never get back in time to start a stream
because the vet that I go to usually has appointments scheduled out into the afternoon.
So instead of just not streaming today, I was like, you know what, let's just go,
let's just do it in the morning for like three or four hours. And because this stream
is only going to be like three hours, we're going to go on Saturday too. So we're going
to go bang, bang, bang, bang, four days in a row. Would you like to know what we're doing on
Saturday? Take a guess. How would you ever guess? There's like 500 million different things
to do. Hey, what are we doing on Saturday? Can you guess? No, you can't. It was recommended
to me a while ago, and I figured that's a good Saturday night kind of stream, is the
MS-DOS-Archive.org website. I'm going to turn on smart clicks, and we're going to play
a shitload of old MS-DOS games. That's what's going to happen on Saturday night.
I'm looking forward to it. There are, when I looked at it, I think there were 4,337
MS-DOS games. And it doesn't have to be a one time thing. I'm thinking if it's fun enough,
we could do that for like a Saturday night stream for the next couple weeks, you know, DOS night.
Well, I would call it something else. I would definitely call it something else. But today,
because I was fighting with the idea of what can I do in three hours today? I was like,
well, I was going to play Dreams today, but I don't have enough time. I want the move
controllers to really sculpt and shit because I want to really get into that. It's a lot of fun,
but I want to be comfortable doing it. So what I figured is instead of sculpting and making things,
maybe I'll make something small. But as you can see, when I turn this on,
we're just going to surf. I think I'm hovering over the perfect thing to start with.
This is, this stuff wasn't here before. So we'll do another little surf here. I believe it's 30
different dreams, right? Is what you get when you do a general surf. Or we can just pick them up.
I have cookie clicker open right now. This cookie clicker or the original cookie clicker.
So that's important. Maybe we can throw in the auto surf. But yeah, I'm not going to create
anything. I'm not going to spend like six, seven hours making anything today because I
really want to get those move controllers working and I don't have the camera. I was
going to go out late last night and find a Walmart or a Best Buy or a Target or something
that was open. And I did the thing where you can search to see what they have for inventory
and none of them open had the PS camera. So couldn't do that. I guess that would be
Dexter from Dexter's Lab somehow. I feel like we kind of have to open that one.
Yeah, we do. Dexter's Lab. Hope it has theme song. Is there any sounds at all? Take book.
Right, I forgot. I thought that open. Let me tell you something. Never have your secret lab
right behind the book. How would you have it opposite side? Close lab. All right, let's go.
Can I jump? Oh, I can't wait to find. I can do it. Hold on. No, I can't. It's too early.
It's not close. It's okay. That's you know, when they do impression contests,
it's like 40 people come up on stage. Give us your best Dexter's Lab. Dexter. And you
get some really bad ones. I would be one of the guys there. I'd be in the top 20,
you know, you would hear it, you'd go, yeah, yeah, I mean, I'm not embarrassed for you.
I mean, I am. You're doing a Dexter's Lab impression contest. So right off the bat,
I am. But not after that. Not after that. At this time, you don't have any tasks,
but soon here will be a complete list of missions for you. Okay. Yeah, you stream
today. Here's the worst part about this. I feel so bad about this because
first EU stream in a long time. And it's three hours long. Hey, what was your last regular
stream? A seven and a half hours or something like that. What was your last EU stream? Yeah,
two, three, whatever. Do you really give a shit about your EU audience? Yeah, three hours.
See, six months from now when I do this again. Is this robot in Dexter's Lab?
I don't remember the orange Cheeto robot. I haven't seen this show in a long time.
This is really good though. Mark the calendar. November 9th EU stream.
I want to see that. Wait, wait, where's the, um, this makes his mountain creation look
slightly poor. Yeah, I know. But listen, listen to me. We all, we all have the things we're good at,
right? I'm, I'm not, what is that? I'm not good at making stuff like this
at all. And I appreciate that people are. I'm, I'm pretty good at brushing my teeth.
I do a full two minutes. Unlike a lot of you idiots. You don't brush your teeth for a full
two minutes. I do that. I do that very well. Two minutes. That's right. Every time I go to the
dentist. You have really, really nice teeth. I know. Yeah, I do it well. I do. I see you
got the thing that you do. You're, you're a dentist. Highly paid, highly skilled job. See,
I brush teeth good, don't I? We all do the things we do well. And the dentist is like,
please stop talking. I'm trying to, I'm trying to give you a crown. Oh, right. Yeah, yeah, sorry,
sorry about that. This is really cool. Give that one a thumbs up. But yeah, look,
let's compare that with mine. Those of you that weren't here last night. Let me see, let's
see mine. Uh, okay. My creations. All right. Look, I get where you're coming from here.
I get where you're coming from here, but also understand that
somebody has to make the art on the back of the cereal box. There's a place for all of us here.
I don't need my painting hung up in an art gallery, an expensive art gallery. Everyone
comes in and says, oh, this is made up. Unbelievable. Somebody has to draw a two can
sim and put them back there and make the fun puzzles. Doesn't have to be the best art
you've ever seen, but it exists. What's this back here? This is a guy's, well, I fucked
up his eyes. No, don't get me out of here. Don't make me want to fix this. I will want to fix
this. It's a guy with, that's his nose and his nose is sniffing over the mountain. That's his
hand. Oh, I didn't even play it. What am I stupid? I didn't even play it. Look,
it looks good from far away. Yeah, that's what it's supposed to be. It's like drawing
a name on a grain of rice. People have been wondering what's over here. This is the oil
coming out of his head because this is the robot fight over here that I was doing. He's
punching through this guy's head. That's oil. All right. Do you see that one?
Oh, no, no, don't save. Don't save. And then there's this. This is this thing.
This is supposed to be me. This is the way the camera is supposed to be right here.
Yes, it's supposed to be a jaw. I saw people talking about what the fuck is going on here.
It was supposed to be a jaw breaker. It was because it's supposed to be my mouth and
I don't know. My butt legit clenched. Yeah. Oh, don't people like it? Oh, yeah. Maybe I
shouldn't. I got 12 thumbs up on this thing. I didn't do that. And then here's this one.
If you didn't see it, just want to show you. If you didn't see it, this is called Scorpion
Boss. This is the ice cream one. And you'll understand that in a minute. That's the German
ice cream face, which is supposed to be an emo, but I didn't have time to do it.
I cannot get over that. You know, do you guys know that I was laughing in bed last night
at that picture of the person that made the popsicle one? It's too, I did not. That's not
what I was trying to make. It's just so, oh, I did not. That's not what I was doing.
Anyways, there are my three creations. What does this one have? Oh, I didn't make this one
publicly because it's not done. You couldn't make this one more done. So I'll just stay like that.
So compare that with somebody has to make two can't see them, right? Somebody has to art.
It's the best thing about art. I can make anything I want. I think it'd be a piece of
crap if I wanted it to. And I could somehow stand up here and be like, well, um, are you
sure? And I would, you know, put on my big glasses and stare at it and go, well, because
I have some news for you. It doesn't matter because art is completely subjective.
And I start talking like a serial mascot, you know, to, for my inevitable fate.
All right, let's, let's just, um, let's just breeze through some, it's called ball world.
You sound like Krillin from Dragon Ball. World select. Oh, this is the, uh, this is the
menu. World select. Update. Support me. World select. We'll see it soon. Sonic menu.
Are you kidding me? This doesn't surprise me at all. I'm going to turn it down. Um,
this doesn't surprise me at all considering what people were showing me in VR chat.
It's not surprising. People are just so good at doing these things. All right. Well, I
guess, oh, I can, you just go down into the city. All right. That's cool. All right. We're going
to go, of course we're going to go to a green hill zone. LBP pod. LBP. Oh, it's a little big
planet. Okay. There's triangle change in music. Touch pad to hide. Okay. This is really great
too. Somebody just goes, yo, ball world adventure map. Let's go. You have to stay on
this. Is this like that toy at the doctor's office? Oh, no, no, no. This is the actual
overworld. Okay. Let's go. Sky Hills 1-3. This is Sonic level. Sonic, what's this thing?
Sonic, I'm having, Sonic, I'm having a feeling about this place. Um, looks like we've been
here long ago. Anyway, the good new is there are only 40 lost emeralds. But wait, I see
something on my smart teleport radar device. Maybe only the storm. Nevermind. Be careful
out there. Come back to the future platform. I thought that meant like come back to the
future. Come back to the future platform based safe and sound. Got it. Good luck. Time traveler.
What do you think of Sonic the Hedgehog? What's the first thing you think of besides
like speed? How loud the game is. All right. How about now? What do you think of now?
Oh, okay. This is a bad experiment because that's not what I'm okay. Not like, no, no,
no, no, no. All right. Well, what I was gonna say was music. I was gonna say music.
That's the first thing you think of. Then boy, they got a long way to go to fucking
salvage this guy. Imagine that. Oh, hey, what did the Super Mario? What's the first thing
you think of when you think of the word Super Mario Brothers? Porn. Poor feet. Porn. Um,
okay. We're gonna, uh, I don't, I was, I'm surprised. All right. Well, I was gonna say music.
So why wouldn't they just make more? Never mind. I'm gonna move on because that's,
this is not gonna work. Sonic, be careful from here on. There is no way back. You
should have found it at least 35 emeralds. Check them out and go ahead if you're ready.
I only have 26. It's like an E3 conference. You know the guy asked the crowd something.
Imagine like Sonic has an E3 conference and fucking, I don't know, George, whatever his name is,
comes out. Whoever the CEO of Sonic the Hedgehog is or Sega. Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
it's, and joining us now is the head of Sonic Team, George. He comes out,
fucking suit on. All right. Hey, everybody. How are you? Hey, how are you? Yeah, yeah,
thank you. Thank you. So today, but, but, whoa, wait, there was a shark here. Whoa.
That's pretty cool. Anyway, so, uh, ladies and gentlemen, let me ask you something.
Before I get started with my next major announcement. By show of hands, how many of
you got, how many of you guys associate Sonic the Hedgehog with porn or feet?
And like, they, they, they scroll over all the journalists and they're all fucking
putting their hands up? No, that's right. That's right. So what we're announcing here
today. Right. Right. Yeah. Yeah. All right. I don't, I don't have enough emeralds.
Uh, run towards the screen like in Sonic Adventure. I didn't, I didn't play this one.
Oh, I have 31. He's stuck. I, I did, I did. I don't think I ever played that one.
I played it on stream. I don't remember that. Hope I'll make more levels in the future.
Press triangle to change music. Oh, this is the menu for that. Okay.
Okay. This is Ball World. Get a tie. This is cool. Oh, I'm going to fall. This is a little slippery.
It's very slippery. He put extra grease on here. That's fast. By show of hands,
how many of you people associate Ball World with porn and feet? Oh, that's too many. Too
many. Too many. Well, not today. This is actually kind of good. Now this is just,
it really is like a close-up doctor's office toy. Do I have to go around it or just jump?
I think I have to go. I don't think I have enough speed. Now I gotta just.
Oh God. Do I have to go up? In the Sonic menu. Wait, I already did this one. This is the God.
There we go. This is what I wanted. Little big planet, the garden. This reminds me of your iPad
game streams. Well, it's a pretty similar format. You play something for 10. Well,
that's like the appeal, right? The appeal of this game is to just surf around and see what
people have made. It could be anything. It doesn't have to be a game. It could just be artwork.
I just hope that they keep updating those tools and keep making it, you know, intuitive and
creative because we've seen some awesome paintings in this game. The last time we did a
little bit of dream surfing. I know everybody wants to make a game or see a game, but holy
shit, some of those are good. I missed a ball. Now, how many are you? Why is it Dr. Phil? Dr.
Phil comes, all right, Dr. Phil comes out to announce the new Sonic game and he asks that
question and then he psychoanalyzes everybody in the audience. Now, why do you think that?
Why do you, why are you searching for porn in Sonic the Hedgehog? What happened? Oh,
I like this button. You know what I want to make? You know, if I'm going to make a level
ever, I want it to be a bunch of wall jumps. Sonic has a uni eyeball. It's a mega turn off.
All right. Oh, cookie clicker. This is what I came here for. Earn cookies by clicking a
huge cookie. Wait, okay. Upgrade achievements. Cookie clicker. No, you can't use that here.
You cannot use like the porn reference here. Only one cookie per, hold on. I'm limited to
the amount of times I can press X and it's not even registering them all. All right. What about
upgrades? This is actually, somebody made this. How many grandmas? No, I need a better cursor.
Let's go back to it. Get grandmas, get grandmas. I'm getting them. How do I get more
click? Cursor. There we go. 97 cookies. Profound statement. Is this going to be the next three
hours? Look, I don't schedule anything. You know, I don't plan anything. I don't really schedule
anything. So I mean, it's like very possible that this could be, you know, if I'm having
fun. Bold content to stream. I need gold cookie. Can't you click on cookies? Don't
they pop up randomly? What are you doing? What? I don't, this is a recreation of cookie
clicker in dream. This is really well made in the first, and everyone's just mad that
I'm going to be playing it for, all right, fine. This is what you get for the EU stream.
Yeah. The EU friendly stream is me playing a remake of cookie clicker. All right,
I got to get out of here before I stay here all day. I'm going to like
miss my dog's appointment. No, but you don't understand. I have to go. I got 700. Let
me just get one factory. No, let me just, let me get one portal and then I'm out of here.
I'm done. I just want at least one of each. I just want one of each. That's it. Okay. Here
we go. I want five of each. I almost have 2000. Don't worry. Okay. Come on. Almost there.
Make an idle game with like the planets. You know, I've actually thought about something
like that before. I thought about making an idle game and make a bunch of elaborate,
stupid things you can do in it. It's funny you mentioned that because I've been talking
to somebody in particular about making a full-fledged game. One that is, you know,
comes out releases and you can play. And I got a little bit of a hint for you. They're,
they're currently VIP right now. All right. All I wanted was 15 of each and I got what I
wanted 20 of each and I got exactly what I wanted. Make a dating sim. Somebody recommended
that to have, hold on a minute. I was going to say it kind of looks like my face from
back here. That could be me. That looks just like me. It does. Wait, what was this?
I just drowned. Is there a punch? I think I just get chased. I need 30 coins. The
braid is perfect. All pirates must use secret tunnel. Beware of ye beasties. No treasure
hunting allowed. Who is this person behind me? Why are they the, it's a person inside of
a person. That's a person inside of another person. That's not supposed to be one that
looks like a baby holding onto its mother. No guys, that's two people. There's two hats.
Don't tell me this is not the same person. There's two hats. What do you mean we know?
Oh, was I just arguing with myself? Why did I make up this character in my head that told
me this was one person? I don't know. 22. Oh, not yet. Oh boy. I don't know. What's
the mechanic based on? Why is that here? I'm talking to one guy. Say I knew what I was doing.
All right. Is this person still following me? No, they can't get up here. So I need 22. That
ghost is not getting up here, are they? I don't think it's supposed to be up here.
All right. This is the unfinished zone. Guarantee it because that's a non-painted
T-Rex over here. Damn it. Oh, I knew it. I need to go see what that says. That's
developer island. They want to keep me out of there? Don't you know? Do you know what I
used to do in World of Warcraft when I was bored? I would find a corner and I would jump
up to it for hours until I got up the ledge on top of the mountain and ran into the no
player zone. You're gonna keep me out? Doubt it. I would do it for hours. Hours. There
was this one spot in Ironforge in the corner next to, I believe, the mailbox where if you
jumped at the right moment and pixel perfect jumped over and over again, you could get to
the top onto the ceiling and people would be sitting there doing it and they wouldn't be able
to do it. They would be just, you know, five or six people. This is back when they were
like fucking five trillion people that played the damn game and I would just crack my knuckles.
I would log in. I'd be like, all right, let's check the mail out. I got, we got like three or
four people trying to do the jump, huh? Crack my fucking knuckles and I would go do it first try
and everyone would stand there and stop, look up at me while I like did like the wave from
all the way at the top and I would go, I'd get on my huge awesome fucking dragon up there.
Like I get on my awesome mount up there. So people like, oh, amazing the mount too.
And then they would try again and I would try, I wouldn't tell them the secret.
Why would a magician ever reveal their secret? Hey, what does that sign say? I want to go see
the T-Rex, but I can't go stand over there. Can I stand here? No, definitely not, right?
No. All right. Developer Island is, oh, well that's the, is that the, I think that's just
the door. Do not feed anyone to the animals. I don't think he has collision on his head.
Why am I lying? Why would I lie about something so stupid?
It's like that, that's the dumbest thing to lie about. Because you have, what? I'm not a liar.
Stop it T-Rex. Oh, well I just had to walk in. I just skipped that. I like this one. I'm gonna,
I like that one. Yeah, why are you like lying about, I already did this one. Hey dude,
why are you lying about jumping in this specific corner in World of Warcraft? Oh no.
Oh no. Silent Hill.
Damn. All right, so this is, this is not a game this time. We're just watching. Nice. Oh, I love
it. So this is the kind of shit that I would want to do. And I'm, I want to move the, I'm
gonna get like record and camera and shit. Can I just be like the camera guy? Can somebody make
me something cool and give me the assets and I'll just make a video? Can I just like edit the video?
Instead we got the scorpion boss fight. I'm gonna ruin this song for everybody here.
But the Silent Hill theme song is just a slowed down nice Italian restaurant.
This is still going, huh? It reminds me of the Godfather. Yeah, yeah. Cloud Factory.
Another video. Good. This is what I'm talking about. Another thing we can just watch.
Streamer doesn't produce any content. He just consumes it on camera with you.
Look at that. Look at this camera work. I don't have to do anything.
We can just sit here. Look at that log. Nice placement of the log. You ever just have a
weird freak out moment for five seconds? I'm going to give you the weird insane freak out
moment that I just had right now. It was and these feelings are only a tenth of a second
and then they're gone because of my brain goes you're an idiot. What are you talking about?
Stop being a weirdo. When he put his hand out like that and was looking, I just for a tenth
of my brain was just in a splash. It was like you have a VR headset on. Take it off.
Oh no, no. I'm not in VR. It was not even a tenth. This is lies.
This is really good. You're ruining this. Stop it. Everything is a lie.
Dream cheese. That's well beautiful fucking landscape. I'll tell you by dream cheese.
The smokestack. Look at that. I want to go. Can we rewind? I can't even.
Those smokestacks back there. Green Hill test zone. This is another Sonic the Hedgehog.
I can't get the rings. I don't know how to do sonic slope logic so just run into it.
Ha ha ha. Nice. Silent Hill's police station. Oh fuck.
That's very, that's really high quality sculpture.
That's high fidelity sculpturing.
Is there rain out the window?
Compared to where my anything is. Look at that.
All I can make of monsters and fucking like love crafting horrors. I can't do anything else.
Hey you guys laugh and I can't do this but hey don't you think I could do a pretty damn good
job making like the next Dead Space 4 fucking enemies? I think I could. I could pull all kinds
of fucking crazy shit out of my head. You know I am available for consulting work if you want
to be scared. This is really really good. Jerma, Jerma you're unemployable. Oh you know
me so well. Yeah. Yeah you're unemployable. Yeah I know you. What do you know? What do
you know? He struck a chord there. How would you know that? You don't know?
Ethan's house upstairs. Press X to go downstairs. Who's Ethan? He's actually mad. No but you can't
make an assessment on something. Okay let me tell you something. You cannot make an assessment
on somebody's career aspirations or abilities based on them playing Dreams for fucking three
hours. Okay if I handed you a controller and you were Bill Gates, like 25 years ago Bill Gates
and you're like Bill Gates can you like make a sculpture in Dreams? He'd be like I don't
understand what you want me to do here. He'd make a fucking worm. I made a worm there now didn't I?
Yeah you did. You did. You did Bill. Interesting. No no Bill you can't you zoom in you zoom out
you zoomed in. Oh well sorry about that. I thought I the controls are kind of hard.
I put a face on that worm didn't I and it looks bad but you're like oh nice job Bill.
Is Bill Gates unemployable because he can't what Bill Gates is unemployable.
You're right you're just like Bill Gates. Thank you. I love the badge.
That was the voice I was just doing for Bill Gates. This is Bill Gates talking to us.
I need to make all of this shit. They had to do all day to put it in the right place. They put desks there.
Now they didn't have to make every single thing because obviously the game has a clothing
feature. You have to make it once and then you can use it over and over again
and change the color on it too.
Ethan's house downstairs. Is this supposed to be this person's house?
Pokemon? Professor Elm has been waiting for you dear. The only reason why I do that is
because of the backwards hat. I didn't I could not tell if he didn't have the hat on I
wouldn't know this is a Pokemon game. The music I've never played Pokemon is another Sonic.
This is pretty good Sonic. I dare say that this may be the best Sonic we've seen so far.
It might even be the same one. Here's the interrogation. We're going to get a lot of
signs on the hill. What's your name sir? Tom Sanders. How well did you know him? Did he
seem different? Any possible motives? Any possible motives? I can't think of any. Did he seem
different lately? He had been down for a while after losing his job but that was nothing
new. This just came so suddenly. How well did you know him? We go back a long time. And then
he fucking tosses the table over like a Lovecraftian German created horror comes out of his mouth.
I know talent when I see it. Could you tell us about... It's strange though.
It's happening everywhere now doesn't it? All over town? Yeah it's a real head buster I'll
give you that but uh maybe it shouldn't surprise us. Oh yeah? Why's that? It's freaky.
This guy's scary. I have been looking around me lately. The mood is different. People seem
so on edge. So many have ended up on the streets recently. Does this happen in Silent Hill?
Economies going through tough times. Takes more than that to start a riot like this.
There could be more to it than just that. I'm sorry exactly how did you know Henry Sullivan
again? Yeah? Those photos you requested sir. Ah yeah the photos of the crime scene I asked
for. They're in the photo lab. Realistic knocking. We'll talk later Tom. That was not me.
New Bark Town. Another dog game. I can't wait. I love the dog ones. They're the best. Oh no shit.
I made that sound like I didn't think this one was good. I meant like I thought it
was gonna be a dog one. Oh that's pretty nice. This is pretty cool town. So you know
when you play and you just realize you have this moment in your brain where you understand
how everything works now? I do. Remember I was asking about lighting and how do I turn on the
lights? What do I do about the lights and lighting? It's the glow tool. That's it.
You can make anything a light. I thought that you had to stage it. No it's just the
glow tool. That's it. Anything can be a light. Anything can emit light.
You can make light any color and you can aim it. Well what is this? Is this a oh that's a
ra what's it rat? Ratasco? Ratatouille? Ratatouille? Ratatouine? What is it what is
called? Tabasco? That's sauce I've ever made. This is uh I can't even go in here. Look at
how huge I am. Ratabasco? Ratatouille? Ratabasco? Ratasca? Ratacastrobrown? Um what are the rats?
This is really cool. I'm gonna get a thumbs up from me. Tabasco is fucking disgusting. It is
not. Um if you really think Tabasco is disgusting then you and I are no longer good friends.
We're now kind of fun friends not good ones. Wait no remix of silent wait what do you mean
remix? I can hear them calling to me from hell. I used to do that when I was younger. I forget
a word in the sentence and I would put it above and then point an arrow down. I can hear them
calling to me from hell. Forgive me Lisa. There's some monster inside of me. Oh boy
they always write those things. I sent more info on this guy now. You're living in that hotel.
You know the worst thing in the world is what we're describing here. All right what we're
talking about now. I I do this shit on checks and it makes me so self-conscious and I feel
like I hate it. I will write a check to somebody and it'll be like oh who am I writing that to?
Oh you're writing it to B&B Associates LLC or something and it's like oh fuck why do you
have to have such a goddamn long name and I'll write the checkout and I'll get to the end of
the line. I'll have like the S in associates written up and I'll have to do make tiny tiny
little letters and trail it off like it falls off the cliff and don't even get me started if
it's a weird uneven number like four hundred and twenty two dollars and sixty eight cents. It's
just like fuck do I have to write this whole thing out? Can I just just give it to you?
Can't you just make it like four hundred dollars or like two hundred dollars or like
one thousand dollars? Why is it always like ah that's right there. Thirteen hundred forty
four and fifty two cents. I don't want to write that whole thing out. You have to write
the whole thing. No but not even numbers as in like I'm talking about like a like an
easy flat number to write out because you guys have ever written a check before?
No. How many of you guys have ever written a fucking check? This is this is wonderful.
This is really good. I love the coral reef and the little astronaut guy. The little underwater
scuba guy. Balance your checkbook. No you guys I'm asking about writing checks to a group
of probably he's dead to a group of people that probably have never done it before. I forgot
we're in the digital age. Digital zoomer. Only take checks though. I find that hard to believe.
All right so let me give you a scenario. Most of the time still even in the digital zoomer age
if like a plumber comes to your house you gotta pay them how do you pay them?
They don't have like a card swiper. Most of them are just like yeah it'd be a check
cash. All right so but what if the job you're paying for is like hundreds of dollars?
Do you just like withdraw like fucking eight hundred dollars in cash and like bang oh there's
like eight hundreds. Why not? Yeah but then but you can't you can't prove it.
If you pay for a service in cash that money's gone. Receipt. What plumber is going to give
you a receipt? Never happened to me before. Oh this is cool. I give you I know I'm just
fucking around. Actual swinging animations. This is cool. Cell F. Bad plumbers.
Nah to be real though I don't ever carry cash. It's a hazard.
The spider even has the oof. It's a pretty cool spider though. Is that the quest? List
of prisoners. John. Murder. Cell B empty. Cell C. Brigitte theft. Cell E. David murder. Cell F.
Censored. Boris. Conspiracy. Edita. Tax evasion. Cell I. Someone please get rid of that ugly
spider. Charlie. Murder. Kevin. Gambling. Let's go check on Kevin. It's okay. Why would you get
arrested for gambling? Dead for conspiracy. Illegal gambling. Oh okay. Cell block. Who's
in this one? Shift schedule. 6 a.m. 2 p.m. 2 p.m. 10 p.m. 10 p.m. 6 a.m. No please
stop using empty cell L as a storage for your items. Thanks. From the captain.
Well I picked it up. It was a health potion. Sleeping quarters. That's actually scary how that
moves. You and the captain make it happen. Kevin grunt. My crunch berries. I had trouble
sleeping tonight again. Another nightmare about monsters attacking our fort. Kitchen.
Whoop. You gotta start. Yeah you're right. Oh fuck. I fucked up big time. Oh no. What am I
thinking? I'm doing like American humor and American references. That's not gonna work
right now. Fuck. Why are you guys still doing some like EU references and like British and
German Lithuanian humor. What do you guys think is funny? I don't know. I've never even
spoken to you guys before. It's been a long time. This is like going and being like a comedian
and going to like do stand-up and you look out. Where am I doing my next show? Oh we're
getting you on a plane and you're going to Germany. What? Yeah none of your material is
gonna work. Okay um I can figure something out. You really bombed with that NA check joke. I
know right? That's the problem. I thought that was gonna fly over really well. Current
inventory. Bunch of apples. Two healing potions. Someone please order more food immediately.
This captain sounds pretty uh. The EU is like five years more advanced than America.
I don't know if I believe that. Five? Like you're talking to an American right now.
You think I'm gonna stand for that? You think I'm gonna let that just fly and you're
gonna come after and attack my country? A country who every single business you've
gone into in the last at least five years are still running on Dell computers and Windows XP.
You think you're five to ten years ahead of us Americans? Are you out of your mind?
These skeletons are actually really well made. So it's actually kind of funny.
This is a universal humor. This has nothing to do with where you're from.
Right? Let's see. Tell me how this one flies. It's a reference to what we were just talking
about. So I was at the bank and this actually happened. I was setting up some account stuff.
I was squaring away some account details and this is a giant boss room so hold on.
You guys have banks in the EU right? Yeah so I'm already off to a great start as you can see.
Gotta make sure I don't die to the finale but anyways so I was having my
don't die. I'm gonna die. EU uses only Apple Pay. An American company I see. Come on. No!
That's it. I didn't do it. I have done too long. Too long NA. You know too long North
American. What's going on? All right TLDR EU. I went to the bank and they were on a Dell computer
and the computer crashed in the middle of doing my information and the guy was really upset.
He's like I can't believe this is happening man like what the fuck why does this have to
happen? I'm like I don't worry about it and then I just was curious. Okay I did it. So but
I was just curious so I asked him. I said what are you running on that's causing this many problems
and this is the really scary shit that I think about this. Really wrap your mind around this
shit. So this person told me that his browser crashes all the time. He's on Windows XP.
Probably no security updates in a fucking decade and it was an old Dell computer
and I'm just sitting there thinking like this is like banking information. Your browser is
crashing. Your browser is crashing. I almost wanted to be like can you like get out of the
way for a minute and like sit in his chair and fix his computer but if that's the case
and they were they were very very adamant to tell me that this bank was not going to give
them updates and give them new computers and stuff. I'm just sitting there going you take
how do these I mean oh I can't believe it. How did that major breach happen?
I don't know maybe it's because this guy had Bonzi buddy installed on his computer and it
infected the entire fucking network of like eight million customers. What? I couldn't believe it.
Yeah well we here at we here at BankX yeah we we're very take we take security very
seriously. We have an entire team of people that make up like at least four to five probably
a million dollars in salaries. Your salary is very important to your security is very important
to us. Oh yeah? Yeah. Can you give all your branches new computers with updated Windows
security fixes? No no I don't think so. Why? That cost too much money we have
security experts that uh we pay the security experts uh okay I don't know what they do but
they are experts at it. Can you at least give them Windows 7? How much that gonna cost?
I don't know is it worth that or worth like a 10 million customers data breach because of
browser hijacker? I don't get it I never will and the EU crowd fucking loves this shit you know
what it means because like EU I gotta make this jump. Next game no no no way I have to make
this jump. It made this one really hard but it it's honestly it makes no sense.
That was unfinished that's it. Fall damage from spawning in.
Uh factory run let's try this one but no like we take security very seriously.
Can I just call and uh yeah I'm gonna use social engineering to trick one of your customer
service agents. Hi yes uh Bank uh BankX. Hi uh I'd like to make a withdrawal please.
Okay uh who am I speaking to? Jeremy Albertson. Okay uh just for security purposes I want to
make sure that we get this and make sure we know who you are. Uh by the way replace this
with any fucking company any any company that has a feature like this. Uh can you do me a
favor and verify uh your first and last name? Jeremy Albertson. Okay all right just making
sure I'm talking to the right person. What would you like to do today? Take everything.
Okay take everything. Okay let me let me just like turn to my page in my script.
Okay to take everything um I'm gonna need a little bit more verifiable information.
I'm gonna need the last four digits of your phone number.
Oh thank god I know I'm talking to the right person now. Sure through space this is look at
this shit. But it's true though all these companies claim to how well we take security
seriously. No you don't stop shut up. It's bullshit somebody you know people like people
okay if it's possible for somebody to walk into like a target or like a gas station
and literally put like a credit card skimmer in their machine I don't think they're paying
that much attention to it. How did somebody swipe 500 credit cards? Oh there was a skimmer in
this ATM. Whoops how did that get there? Pull it out. This is really cool. This is a full
space station. People tap people's pockets with contactless credit card bridges and
take loads of money to time. I know it's it's it's like scary though you know what I mean? Like I
you gotta be careful under construction. Well let's just let's check this out.
You yeah here's the crazy part about the chip right? A lot of people don't take the chip.
A ton of retailers don't do the chip. This is cool and they even have a thing on the device
that says chip reader not functioning please swipe. What do you mean it's not functioning?
It's broken. What are you talking about? Welcome to through space. For now it's just a dream.
I'm building this environment and doing some experimentation but through space will eventually
evolve to a story-driven sci-fi game. Gradually lore and more detail will be added.
Keep in touch. I could have just pressed the triangle. Chips mean fries for EU. Fuck you're
right. I meant um a credit card um internal chip like computer chip. This is actually really
nice. I like the ground too. Oh now I get it. He's dude he's just slaying this EU audience.
Computer fries. I like this one. Good job. Very good job. You can say Europe Jeremy.
EU is just a treaty. All right well excuse me. Hold on a second. Wait wait wait wait wait
then why do you call it NA? North America is more than one country. So excuse me. This is hard.
Europe is not EU? Wait what are you talking about? What are you talking about?
And NA is a shitload of countries. What are you talking about?
Are people just fucking with me here? Oh I see.
I thought you guys were fucking with me. Did we already see this?
Is it because I said North America and everyone just thinks North America is
America? I forgot EU audience. I did say North America. NA is like three countries. All right
now you're just proving that you don't know. It's it's like 30 or 40 at least. Can I not
go in any of these doors? I get the fuck. This is cool. It's 20 23 what I say 30?
30 like what? So I didn't know I don't have the exact number of countries in North America.
I thought it was like 27. This is this is the first game I've played that has a really
well-made third person swinging animations. Central America is North America. Yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's a it's a hemisphere. This is fantastic. Oh yeah I forgot. Aerial attack,
jump attack. A lot of work went into this. This is really good. Hold this is block,
crouch. This looks like a little prototype. Focus camera and lock on. Wow somebody's gonna make
something awesome. Hold L2 and then back flip. So this is like Zelda game. There's even more.
Sprint, a roll. Oh yeah. Finisher attack after one second sprint.
Sprint dive.
What is this one? This is just okay. So there is a suicide button I guess. Looks like they're
gonna have enemies scattered around. This is really well done. Can I give this a thumbs up
plus? Can I give this more than a thumbs up? Because this is this is obviously somebody that
knows exactly what the fuck they're doing. This is probably a this is a dev. This is a
dev and I put that in huge brackets. Like this is a dev. You can tell. You can just tell they
know exactly what's going on. Like in quotes like dev. Nice job. Pixel plaza.
I don't like this. I don't like this one. This one gives me a headache.
I gotta get out. I can't do that one. Boom balls hub one. Review tubes games presents a very small
percentage of you to make sure that the seizure from blackout comes from a certain life.
We've got a warning for this one but not the last one. That was a a seizure warning at the
bottom but not the last one. Well it's there. I just don't know why. Really really good.
Oh shit. Trench bucket intro scene. Another super quotes dev. I don't mean that as like a
mean annoying way to be like oh yeah a dev quotes right? Cable car? So strange time of the year
to be going up in the mountains isn't it? What are you doing here? None of your business.
Pretend I didn't hear. By they do get deaf young these days don't they? Don't they? He's
trying to goad me into a conversation. Not on my watch. These lips are staying tightly closed
mister. Looks like it's my stop. Ha! I win. If I had the skill to do it I would just take the first
like eight pages that I wrote of the book and make it a game.
Oh it looks like my stuff isn't far away either. Finally who knew a two hour cable
car could take so long. I'm a dev. I can do it. Boom balls pipe drink level one and start.
Press and hold X to explode. Reaction game. Flawless. Galactic geometry dream evolved.
Coming soon. Advanced scoring system. Many update notes. Bug fences. Spawn invincibility
added. Update 04. Spawning patterns. Score chasers be aware that the future updates
the peak. Some of you guys are talking shit about this one. You sure about that?
I can check my pockets in any notes I've made using the touchpad. I can look at my
messages too. Come to think of it didn't someone message me on the cable car?
I want to see if there's fall damage. Mobile phone. Cable car ticket. My one of my one line
of communication with the outside world. Mobile phone. Check my messages on a different page.
Messages from mum. Are you all right? Is your phone out of battery?
Just checking in. Hi sweetie how are you? I just dropped all your flat to say hello
but you won't get the EU crowd loving this one. Just dropped by your flat to say hello but you
weren't in. When I asked old Giuseppi next door he said he hadn't seen you for a few days.
Have you gone on another one of your trips? You don't need to tell me everything you do
but a bit of a heads up would be nice. Please give me a ring soon love mum.
Well then this stream right now. How's your mum? My mum is doing good. This is beautiful.
Perfect. Wonderful. I envy being able to do this. Envy it. The EU is not British.
Oh yeah all right. Ring ring ring ring. Looks like my phone's ringing. It's from
Gregory sweet cheeks. We really need to have a serious talk. I've taken a glance
over your focus group report and I must say I'm not pleased by what I saw. I can see a pattern
emerging in your work. It's not a good one. I'm afraid to say that this is not acceptable
and you will need to step it up a little bit here. You're going to have to put in extra
hours to complete. Unacceptable my behind. He should have seen what I had to work with.
I worked late all of last week to get him more finished and this is what I get.
More overtime at a glance than never this fucking mate. Well whatever. I'm on holiday.
Work can wait. Ring ring. Ring ring. Again. We really need to have a serious talk.
I meant going not gone. LOL. What part of holiday leave does this man not understand?
All right so this is what's happening right now is when I'm trying to do this
in real time you have an accent slider and you're playing back the audio clip of me talking and
you are sliding from like cockney british over to irish back and forth a few times
mid-sentence and australia yeah looks like that should I go in go go in boom falls level two
oh sorry boom crisps level two fucking eu crowds 11 all right all right i'm i've had my fill
i've had my fill with uh with those references and those i'm not doing them
first try come on no short final done too that's a jeremy title holy shit look at that over on the
right look at the eyes and it's the peasant voice what what do you mean peasant voice
i like that fire effect have you looked to see if anyone made anything new today
no not yet i'll do that before the street men's we will check look at this dude just waiting for
the oof i like this one i just saw a resident sleeper in chat no i like this one look at
the rain look at the background the blending that's going on in the background here come on
i don't get it i'll help you understand so the kind of tall mummy guy was britain and
the fire was the eu and they really want to bring them i said i wasn't gonna do it anymore
come on this is my one opportunity in like months look i'm so i haven't been able to
talk about like i haven't been able to say the word brexit is this still a thing i don't know
is it one punch man stage one i eat too much crab and turn into this crab latte
hey you you're since we have them coming i'm gonna let you live
i'm gonna rip his arms off okay what are you looking at a big chin brat if he's caught
hey kid were you messing with a crab monster he was asleep in the park i just drew some
nipples on his chest found you okay losing in one punch man all i have to do is punch him once
it's the title of the show dodge left i just have to do the show's title i did i'm
punching it's not hitting him watch i just punched it's not one punch man is it
it was three punch man it's our i know it's all of one i know it's all of one all right no
all right no naughty bear hello this is just the house set so far i will have more details
and features later possible features co-op multiplayer fights and a version cops and
robbers i played this game on stream for 10 minutes please follow projects be your fan
naughty bear i didn't know there were fans of naughty bear better crouch no auto jump more plant
types detail touch up item interaction and weapons didn't pick up the gift i don't think
i can pick up the gift beachside will be redone this is nice sound test boo that scared
the fuck out of me listen to this it comes out of the controller too oh my god that was
sound test successful yeah this is really well made beach you got some good foliage but let's
uh let's see oh you made sure that you put invisible walls up good for you nice work
because i was about to go look at it on the other side and see your assets that you
accidentally painted over here but you're a good game dev and you may be not able to
no this is nice i mean it looks good this little campfire is cool the logs now you'll
notice a true sculptor at work here because those are the cylinder shape that had been hollowed
out but instead of just doing that painting them brown and maneuvering them and putting them in
the fire do you see the etchings on the lungs they went with the little ball tool and they
sculpted out etchings resident sleepers apparently the apparently the eu audience is
not uh doesn't care about artistically inclined things the the north american audience was
like all over this just want to make sure you're aware of that we were talking about etchings and
and clay and stuff apparently north america was more interested in art and i'm interested
i'm learning a lot today no one cares
eu appreciating art lul what are you talking about this time like the the art was like
invented in the eu in like the 1700s this looks like the best view i'll be getting
i could probably just set my telescope up and wait until the night now if i wanted
not yet i want to look around get that up there durham with that history major isn't working
out right now i don't have a history major this is really really nice okay i'm gonna go i'm
gonna go on a limb here i think this may be the cleanest uh most well-designed open dream
like area let's see look down here it's great what did i study that's none of your business
anytime somebody says that's none of your business when they're talking about what they
studied in school they're embarrassed to tell you what it was frog studies no not biology
no not zoology frog studies i got scammed i have a scam degree somebody scammed me i did
an online fucking personality quiz and then i got my i got my diploma after like two or
three weeks and i thought it was real but thinking about how i could not be real
the dean of students it was signed barack obama i was like holy shit really like i didn't
believe it i was like holy fuck that's crazy okay pick up the phone subject re re re we really
need a serious talk just a quick message to let you know that you will no longer need to put
in those extra hours look at the night sky here karen has been amazing and rewritten the report
from scratch so you don't need to touch it ever again what a star don't forget to thank her
when you get back oh well that's wonderful good for her fantastic i may as well have sat and
stared into space for a week for all the difference it made that big thing up there
another week of my life thrown into the abyss never to be seen again well if that's how it is
just throw the phone oh the star is all lovely tonight aren't they that looks really good
all right she she's one punch man stage two versus super custom this is like spoilers for
the show if you haven't seen uh if you haven't seen uh one punch man we're gonna get every
fight this hasn't changed since before i became a hero i haven't made any impact i'm
not necessarily sad about that but there's something bothering me lately as the days pass
my emotions grow more distant and i guess fear tension joy anger i don't feel them any more at
all no such a time to give you shall be i don't remember this guy's voice i used to feel all
kinds of emotions i'm a custom car machine killer if you think you're getting in my
way i'll put a shine on that face damn it i just get knocked back what do you mean i took
too long i can't this is as fast as i can go if i see r1 one more time i swear
i guess i guess all i had to do is punch him once oh man the grocery store is having a sale
today come on get over here i it's dodge the kick don't tell me what to do don't tell me
what to do i'm gonna dodge the kick immediately after i dodged it just spam r1 no i can't look
if i spam r1 look what he does you have to time it ready like now or now i did it i just
punched him it even made the sound have you tried pressing r1 on the top of your dual shock
love your stuff this is called the car trip what is i'm not doing this
am i controlling this
you just crushed the car with a rock with the band animator that was ridiculous
i like the little wave flick here
inspector gadget yeah inspector gadget okay penny
tell me to stop you're gonna tell me to stop doing that were you enjoying the music i was
i probably should have stopped who are you i'm just a guy who's a hero for fun i knew it
fire looks good though i will tell you does this make one punch man and panty back
we're gonna get the actual song can we get the song how many what else is he doing i think
is he resting i think he's charging up i should be able to get him here i think it took too
long god damn it into the fire he didn't even do the balls that time too by the way listen
to when i press do you see after pressing how long it takes i'll get it i'll get it he's
gonna go down oh my god i almost had it no get there i'm almost there come on i can do it
i just have to one punch that's it do it please don't let him do it he has a kick
he also has a kick how am i supposed to do this yes i punched him in half season two looks so good
oh my god i know i can't wait is it called the desert drive drive oh that was the intro
for this game hold circle to reset and get stuck this has actual car damage
of all the things you've seen today this is absolutely the most impressive
this car that you made in dreams that has actual damage engine too this is awesome
get out of the way don't crush me will it crush the car oh god it will okay get through
yes off-roading this is not really the car you want to take off-road
got that sedan i don't right way i want this song where the where's the song from
look at the engine awesome he doesn't know he doesn't know he doesn't know
happy town look it up look it up wait dreamiverse dash we've already seen this one in fact
i don't i'm unthumbs upping it because you sure i don't want to see it again
this really is just spoilers for the whole show okay good no nudity this is like episode two
yeah let's just show the season's only like 10 episodes long eight episodes long this is
like 20 percent of the whole show flying punch r1 how do i do oh he's gonna clap me
dodge left dodging how do i dodge this how do you dodge them clapping in the air
can i dodge it should i just do flying punch um i think i have to do it right when i land
because i can't so i just gotta go now r1
r1 oh i didn't hit him he keeps like banging on a trash can i got it that was awesome
now we're in the happy town oh i'm gonna use the mario kart show cup the saw blades
i just got that just got me oh dear r1 no it's fine oh unfair no way for me to go through it
unfair please do a reaction video too you got that rocks cue the rocks feel like i'm playing
stuntman bingo prometheus fps demo i think we've already seen this one yeah we have seen this one
it's very good but we've already seen it r2 r1 good times yeah good good times i believe there's
also a look at that we've seen it already i have already i haven't even thumbs it up
well now if i didn't thumbs it up before i mean i'm retroactively adding a thumbs up
i'm telling myself to thumbs is you know what fine smash that fucking button this is called
separate reality watch out the gap in the door it's a separate reality the only means oh man
i think we've cycled yeah we've cycled back to pt i think we've seen them all
let's turn it down it's a little loud i'm just gonna drive straight that's
the developer always puts in like a secret and it's just driving a straight line
oh this is a spooky scary skeleton
i have no this song damn it thank god there's a checkpoint what a good dev come on secret
i don't know why but every time i hear this song i always think that tason day made it
but he didn't yeah tason day the audio is distinct what which one the
game audio that doesn't make this weird that's a nice touch it was like the ghost
it's the game did what did that just start happening it's been happening really i don't
know why it shouldn't yeah we played this one already they're cycling see i already
thumbed that one up all right so hold on you should be hearing when you should be going
right when i scroll over it is it not happening it's good it does yeah so wait i wonder what was
wrong that's weird that's really strange it's always something with the capture device loop
one oh no i know this is i'm just gonna skip it immediately in order to hit it yeah but uh
you know for people that didn't see it the first time somebody made pt but i might as well
to show you the first loop because it's amazing that somebody did this the day of the
crime the father went to the trunk of his car retrieved the rifle and shot his wife as she
was cleaning up the kitchen after lunch when his 10 year old son came to investigate the commotion
the father shot him too his six-year-old daughter had the good sense to hide in the
bathroom but reports suggest he lured her out by telling her it was just a game the girl was
found shot once in the chest from a point blank range should we just go and open that
one to see how elevators seem is that amazing it's just a whole it's a one-to-one recreation of
the whole game oh this is the car game car made by witchcraft story line stored by mcbroden
director pretty good maybe it ain't over what the hell who are you i am evil or something lol
then i'll put an end to you come get me curiosity now we saw this one too but this is cool
remember i had to walk the whole thing that looks like a car you would drive
which one the one with the horns
why would i drive the one with horns yeah we've cycled we've cycled we're getting
repeats because i've seen the new ones but we do have car game car game is best game
hammer panic yep remember this one fight till the end there's the car we have to fight
saw blades hot wait well i have a machine gun now how do i use the machine gun
x can i turn the gun is it doom is it i'm not i just i didn't put this on
is it the doom soundtrack it is isn't it the soundtrack the end everyone's gonna love to shoot
oh jesus i didn't think that was gonna be possible all right well we're going this way
spin around no the car is kind of hard to control did i win oh no i didn't i have to
kill the boss it's 70 health where do you go over there come and get me do they have a gun
too is this kind of unfair got you finish no we don't get to see the conclusion
because auto surf is off wait no i mean hammer panic that's not the last thing i did
is car trip right let it begin credits fight till the end is that it elevator scene happy town
credits no this isn't the elevator yes the elevator no it's not wait a minute you are
the music was not created by me check the credits list to get a hold of some amazing people thanks
for playing no i did all right cool because now that the elevator scene is here right okay
because we did see that when it was in the same car okay cool don't take this game seriously
have fun time on a car trip with your friends most amount of you'll see are not made by me
especially not the car yeah that was great okay let's go back here i leveled up level 16
you like to play but recently you've been dabbling in art that's true you do got that right
mario dreams adding goombas i think we played this one these are the top rated ones i'm
assuming yeah any of these that i didn't see i think we saw most of them this one was really
cool dexter's lab this wait what happened to cookie clicker what was that why did it just
change on me what uh okay cat boy adventure panda adventure interdimensional puppet
pepe's adventure official office disaster added some dialogue and gave him a yorkshire dialect
for laughs shadow man mini golf master follow the light home you cannot dream uh we'll try
we'll see what this is 125 thumbs up what is it hello controller what are you doing why are
you doing this controller what the hell there's an earthquake the whole thing that's like an
earthquake what summit down what is it we own like a mountain oh jesus the the water is
like coming in is it rising oh the water level is going up i didn't even realize that
oh damn now here i'll see if i see out from other side or roof
uh can somebody can somebody translate eu oh fuck they don't know he's dead nothing here
check the other side okay thank you fuck can i go down here i guess i'm going in here
and then go through the door no this is broken this way i don't think i can jump
over from here i can see on the right god so that way you just have to land on here
come on what press r1 this is really difficult to do this the character's speed i think needs
to be toned down all right we're gonna try this again all right at some point you have
to accept that it's not it's not my fault it's not your fault no god just trying
acceleration because to turn around like okay look i have to turn around on this thing i have
to be facing see what i mean i have to shimmy all the way around it's not as easy as it looks
oh my god that wasn't just a platform that i could walk on that one was good it was
it just i it's too hard to get over there on that platform the copy machine do pt
uh yeah after i just might browse a little bit more that's jokes this is just me
i got a neck i got i got a couple more monitors though hot tuna
load document this is every vr game i've ever played speaker i can't grab anything else
get over there try to crash the game okay can i put two things at once
no uh you can't crash the game i don't think i think it's deleting them as they come out
i think there's a limit that's on here yeah two spart that's right thumbs that one up
uh the universe of wonders i skipped pepe quest pepe's adventure we can do this one
jump interact attack and map oh okay i thought it was the little gnome guy
hey you attack jump attack interact map you can see the whole thing interact welcome pepe
hello is it wall jump it kind of is i'm not sure i need it though oh nice bird
can i not punch the bird i can't interact with the bird no punching apparently no he's
picking me up um okay there's a double jump what's this thing oh a wand
every time a door opens he says hello come on i don't have time for this i only have like
another 30 or 40 minutes to stream come on every loading minute is a wasted minute oh wait
the game doesn't think i'm done the game thinks i'm still in the game maybe that's it
you cannot dream this one looks pretty cool we're gonna try it you can not her okay this
hurts my head a little just warning there's a warning on here this is might be a little
wonky so here we go impact august pterodactyls birds berserker what is this
this you cannot die well let me play it a little fine let's up i'll test that out eva series model
i think i'm playing this
little guy on the screen i'm in this one i'm in this picture this is a spoiler for what
what is this a spoiler for what do you mean spoilers 2019 i don't know i did i just that's
that's evangelion oh well i don't know is that like the last sequence or something i don't know
it's 20 year old joe well i can't skip this one that's for sure i can't wait to see these
models look at i can't wait come on get me over here
look at that face look at the sculpting i don't know which side is the side with his face
is it this way or this way it's just a meat cube
what am i supposed to do i think this is it the jaw breakers look really really good bird
uh squifty five community subs from squifty thank you the subs five of them i think i missed
some earlier too i was kind of involved i'm sorry but thank you squifty donut man robotic arm
i feel like i know what this one is already what about down here all right
hold on there's some more we haven't seen no stop doing that i just had new ones we saw
cuphead we saw playstation home why is it doing this here we go don't don't refresh like that
is it gonna do that again it hates me i guess i can only go so far titanic the experience
olympics javelin throw yep run with square launch with x
uh i'm not sure what i did wrong i'm supposed to hold x i think i was supposed to hold it
oh i got destroyed no i don't want to see all the players rewind do it again
shit beat the whole thing throw it out of the stadium i don't need to see the other scores i
went cat simulator sure i win i win i got 100 left swipe right swipe jump and sit
all right get up don't sit stand up isn't it called like catastrophe or something
where you do this
this is cute oh kitty spilled over the vase put the fridge in the fridge it's a strong cat
what's in there milk milk out the impossible quiz all right is this the impossible the
whole thing how do you want to play normal how many holes in a polo that'd be two
i mean two one two one two three four can a match box no but a tin can understand
ko choose the answer out of order finish the lyrics i took my to the square root of onion
is shallot the answer is really big match numbers in cancer horse shallots the answer is
really big no infinity no an elephant right where does the general keep his armies
uh in the bin up his sleveys up his sleveys where was the answer to question two
uh that one if you press this the game will end alternatively click this one to carry on
there you go nice one what follows december 2nd a question mark no it's in can answer i took my
horse shallots of the sleveys this one i'll touch it but this one i don't understand what
falls december 2nd is at the end d 142 dwarves december 3rd no all right it's n which of the
following do you need to build a greenhouse vodka i didn't mean to touch it twice one more try
horse shallots is that elephant give a sleveys no i didn't mean to press it twice last
what do you need to build a greenhouse paint okay what sound does a bell make
which is the largest milky way galaxy mars earth
just the largest milky way galaxy earth how is the earth the biggest
where does the great wall of china start the chinese border hole over there 10 letters in
one two three four five six seven eight nine ten what do germans water their gardens with
ears rain urine literhose 24 minus seven equals um urine i feel like it's not this easy
what is your what is spider-man's favorite food crab sticks fly sandwiches deal or no deal deal
fuck one more try what a tin can ko the answer took my horse shallots an elephant
fly sandwiches deal or no deal seal no seal seal let's play dreams says
press x what no i don't know what the fuck i was supposed to do
what that was different that wasn't part of the original one that was that one didn't count it
wasn't fair that one didn't count didn't count you gotta give me just give me a second hold
what was it didn't know seal seal okay that one sucks what's two plus two for some random
answer 21 obviously fish two plus two fish it's not four what is candy made out of pink clouds
cotton sugar fluff fluff pink clouds cotton candy like okay fat elephant morning joseph
playable diorama uptown bubbles evening walk strike forwards just play the actual
flash game i could do that one day oh how about playground vibes shoot them up basics all right
well here's what i'm gonna pee and i'm gonna come back and we're gonna go for time is it
we can go for like another like 45 minutes give or take so give me just a moment i'm
just gonna pee we'll come back and go for like enough just about another hour see it in
just two seconds hello so i can't i can't search for anything right now for some reason when i
searched for germa last night or yeah nothing's coming up now i wonder why that is hmm i wonder
why dream shaping is it do i have to do this browsing create maybe i have to do it from here
browse all that's what i just did is because i wasn't i was in like the surfing mode
there we go okay here we go so we saw this one oh whose is this germa's house of fun
germa comes home from another day of gambling only to hear the horrific sound of a man
hack-o-boy on twitch if i'm in chat you in chat you in chat all right germa's house of fun
you just took that you took this okay i'm curious to see what this is what okay
let's go reason for that um bring myself to say because it's just going to upset a lot of
people first before i upset a lot of people ridiculous if you're out there somewhere
thinking for 19 hours of being why do you have to tell x's stream no thank you for
subscribing ridiculous 19 hours ago like not not a month two months three months 19 hours
that's more than my attention span i already forgot what i was telling you about but how about
we have a little bit of this
man screaming i can't even go up the stairs the camera keeps changing
thank you for sharing that with me again for a third month in a row
give you the piece up to italics at all it's a long time that's true
hey is this my door hey felix welcome back can you speak up i'm eating chips
just wear headphones no that's his room why do i have drugs and pills everywhere
me directly except when you if you use over the ear headphones and you're eating chips it's
just an objective fact i have two beds with me and kim sleep in different beds
in the cup is significantly louder than chips in your mouth and then cover your ears
and then crunch i mean it's not louder than not covering your ears because i mean what
stream is this of his skull vibrating just why did i turn the lamp on and off
and why am i so small because what has happened in the last two months where uh
who is this is this kim she's not hey she's not going to be happy about that
thank you this is called a germa comes home i think that's it this is by door shame okay
this one germa raptor it's just the sound here is rat movie diner you gotta be kidding me
me this is perfect on the set of the rat movie you can actually walk around oh look at that
look at the giant rats this is awesome the thing is terrifying nice i love it it's an actual
one-to-one real scale every detail is here the best part about this i love the seats the
painted on fleck it looks very accurate whereas the night oh but you want this person to make an
a full night suit of armor in like two days come on this is perfect this is amazing what does
it say dancing is ten dollars yep this is awesome awesome awesome awesome that was tactical robot
the rat movie diner germa rat a couple of these oh it's the rat model itself
nice that's this is pretty damn close this is really really close louis cheese louis cheese
like the little one says that's right you can scale them you can make a bunch of rats
oh louis just it's the chat name i get it okay well thank you louis cheese this is great it's
a perfect rat model let's give that one a thumbs up we also have this is this is germa
raptor remember this one from last night reverse beer belly yeah i got a bigger ass than this
though thumbs that one up and then i think these are the same thing except i think you
can actually possess this one maybe i think that's the same thing it's published two
different ways already thumbs it up well that's what we had this is what we have available
this one is like a full game too is germa worm search for germa nine eight five
uh i don't think that would matter would it would that actually matter it does not nothing
for germa nine eight five but this takes a lot to do shit in this game so i'm people have
already made that even those things you've seen those things take a long time to make
try second germa germa pop yeah i'll get that out i just kind of went to bed and woke up and
started swimming again i don't what i don't think i this stuff to do here this is like the home
screen i didn't do anything here i haven't even added anything but who cares about this though
dream community jam that's cool spring season that's cool add the popsicle to the home screen
wait can i just can i do that do i have anything that any sculptures have been made i think i have
to actually save the sculpture right i don't think i've saved any of those sculptures
no they're not saved entities i cannot do that that's all right you can't add anything not
made by the depths of the home screen that comes later i see this is still early access
technically so let's go back into dream shaping or dream surfing tag here because i want to do
uh pt i want to see like the rest of pt right p t p period t right is it just pt vape life
was that one i kind of want to play vape life captain cat that's cool clap trap survival
dreamers the unbinding silent hills there it is right i mean this is it isn't it maybe it's just
not called pt no this is the sound of four what the fuck oh dude you gotta give somebody a
heart attack with this controller thing yeah this is the room sound no four well you're
my favorite customer johnny thank you hey doggy i hate this radio wow what a story mark
i don't think i can do anything hello i need to get out of here
just use the key to unlock the door i don't know how to pick up the key
whoa wait i think it's it really wants me to do this i recently watched uh the disaster
artist and james franco honest to god sometimes i couldn't tell he did such a good impression
like the movie itself was the movie itself was okay but just like that impression itself was
worth watching it was perfect pick up the what pick up the key to open the door i can't pick
up the key look there is no key pickup yeah that was all right that was fun how about human 1.0
time corruption adventures of captain gorpu yo ho ho collect some booty just trying to learn
the tools yeah look at this i want to see the sculptures do i have to press a button or
something how do i see this i want to see your sculptures how do i see them click them yeah
i can't do anything this actually pretty good those are real actually really good stones and
rocks it's a really good job i mean you did kind of bait me with the whole uh immaculate
carved out statue but these are really well done no this this this has to be here somewhere
anything up or down i don't think i can do anything oh here we go rechat r1 rechat r1
that's really good i wonder how long this took to make this is what i tried to do yeah
mine turned into the you know when a seven-year-old or a six-year-old draws something
and it's that really all over the place not even remotely accurate but they tried and it
looks like they tried this is the adult version and mine is the six-year-old version
this is really good this is actually this is very it's very good functioning pottery wheel huh
edit mode only read description dreams doesn't currently support asset deformation during play
mode you'll need to remix this to create your own pottery you have to remix the scene or the
element not the entire dream okay well how do i do that while in create mode press the play
button on the toolbar enter this enter sculpt mode by scoping into the lump of clay okay
so i have to protect if six save this right because i how can i remix it i didn't didn't
give me an option continue reset you can't remix stuff from the dream surf tab you have
to find it in the dream shaping browser oh okay well that's really cool caps and shanty
eclipse capture the beast tutorial super loose painterly sculpts hard-boiled you can look up
the guy who made pt it's lewis c all right let's look up lewis c lewis well there they are
lewis c creations pt work in progress what is this listen up end bathroom loop watch out
final loop i think we've already seen these i'm pretty sure we've seen them all
but we can just do it yeah we've seen pretty much all these
screens before did him out of order yeah you can sort by most thumbs up
oh we're getting started no no we've already done it okay how funny joke where's sam and max
tomorrow the regular time family was gathered at home on a sunday afternoon the day of the
crime the father went to the trunk of his car retrieved the rifle and shot his wife as
she was cleaning up the kitchen after like i've played pt like three times on screen
yeah we've already done it this game has a little big planet vibes well there's a
reason why you think that it's made by the same people that made a little bit
kind of brutal killing took place while the family was gathered at home honestly
don't touch that dial now yeah we've already seen all these i don't think there's any new
screens let's go back and search for most thumbs up don't you touch the dial all right
uh search for dreams categories uh is there like a most thumbed up sorting and filtering
get rid of that most thumbs up that fps this is all media molecule stuff
curiosity do molecule hug me hammer pin i think it's gonna be all the things we've already seen
am i dropping frames that's not good i might have to send a uh i might have to send another
message and try to get a hold of cox again because this is happening a lot more frequently
now the last two streams in a row have been just randomly just thousands and thousands of
frame drops for like an hour or two straight i'm gonna probably have to send another email
i've seen this one this one was awesome slayer scrolls is great don't forget about auto's
appointment no i know i got i'm good i still got some time i have enough time definitely to
chill for a little bit and do the bits and hang out and talk probably do like one or two more
we did pool that was cool we've done i think most of the highly rated ones i think we've
done them all actually auto is a good boy auto is a good boy yeah we've done all these
what most of recent 15 puzzle what's this 15 puzzle start shuffling in progress
three two one block what is block 14 position i guess it's just yeah it's a slide puzzle where
i have to go up now i need to get them in order yeah this i don't want to do this
it's still cool though it is it's interesting somebody put this together these blocks are all
made oh that's cool invert i can kill the music that's cool it's cause that's thumbs up worthy
it is that's cool sailing at sunset let's look at this one oh yeah let's see it this looks
pretty search for pick ross i wonder though how you do this because this is clearly darker
i don't know i haven't even checked really attempted but is there a video mode or filming
mode where you can play around with these settings or is it just something as simple
as all lights are off and the sun is just one glowing orb there are world tweaks
where you can change the atmosphere there are global post-process effects and lighting okay
okay this is great this is wonderful play the tutorials i did i did i did i did i did i did
i did i did i did there's only one tutorial i didn't do and it was the character creator
he did it he did it he did it press r1 no don't let me ruin this this is great
get out of your dream like the boat yeah they get they gotta patch that thing out if you're
watching one of these things if you're in like the play or hold options to my imp
you just took me out i was in the beach looking over here at this boat that's sinking
and you reminded me that i was in a video game that was really really good bugs hi
we have to play hi my father was a wealthy man spotlight like the stars up here
i like the paint in the kind of the background see i should have just made something like this
i spent so much time making like a bunch of mountains and lakes and i just did one thing
and make an expression as an abstract art instead i spent so i did like five scenes in
one scene samurai do you surrender i do not let's see what that does it's just like this
scene here okay cool anything else down however it's just it's just a nice little
painted scene with the moon and okay abstract designs abducted again in progress
slender find the eight pages i feel like i already did this one is that ice age
oh loud it sounds like this was that was recorded through the microphone what you're
about to see will be a fraction of what's to come pretty alpha footage project epsilon
game two level one level 10 and level 21 okay a dreams production this looks good
pretty good ice sculptures somebody using this just to remake game cube games
games yeah we can't get them to run we can't get these wee games to run in the dolphin emulator
just remake the whole thing in dreams do i have to do something here this is ice age so
what if you record the whole ice age movie on your playstation mic and just remake the whole
movie this is the kind of thing where somebody would remake this whole movie like this the ice
age record it from the phone and this would be one of the bbd's that the guy on the side
of the street is selling in new york city like one of the street vendors in new york is just
like i got ice age here like oh i said okay all right this is really good though
all jokes aside this is very very good this is very well made this is literally the game cube
game no it isn't that's is this the this is how the this is the game cube game holy shit
how big this is 60 bucks for infinite game ripoff if this game takes off just wait till you see
somebody creating these people will do it people will make like the whole godfather movie and
shit you know how people are people do all kinds of like ridiculous shit with games like this and
engines and i gotta get i can't have 23 i gotta get at least 30 come on i need 30
there i need 30 or i won't be there we go 30 done this snow looks really good now how do you do
that is this painted this is is this paint or is this a sculpture that's been
messed with i think it's painted on looks really really good though 30 yo 30 yo boomer what's
that mean i know what it means i know what it means press r1 still don't
this happened in the game cube game god this is probably better than the game cube game
i really like this i'm just trying to look around gets punished for his sin i saved four
going to hell no counter anymore though this is where the progress let me see we'll get first
time all right i gotta i gotta start to get out of here i wanted to go for at least three
hours three four hours before having to leave but like i said previously if you weren't here
at the beginning of the screen i had to scream early and short today so i'm going to add a day
on saturday so we're going to go four days in a row tomorrow is going to be sam and mac
season two probably episode one and two we'll see where we are after that and then on saturday
we're going to do a archive.org ms dos night there is a website with a bunch of old abandoned
vaporware ms dos games and we're going to have some fun on saturday night we're going to play
a bunch of them did what's happening how did i get up here hit the last button holy shit this
is really well made this is like really well made this is a gork ripoff oh there's no
damage that's fine i can run damage has not been implemented yet get to the snow i get it i escaped
the lava into the lake this should be on the popular tab yeah it really should i mean it is
kind of just collect the nuts but there's a lot going on what are we focusing on how do they
make this i don't know with all kinds of logic and levers and pulleys and am i supposed
to be getting these i love this landscape just take any random screenshot from this whole thing
the way the snow is on top and kind of takes over and fluffy on dies is wonderful
i think the camera leaves was i supposed to be jumping on these does the camera leave me behind
i can hear him jumping i missed the auto scroll no but why would the camera be moving
over there no because the camera wouldn't be turning left and right putting me off the
screen we're gonna hit the waterfall we're getting close i know this definitely is supposed to be an
auto scroller let's see what's going on can you see me am i down there that was very very good
it's a work in progress not done all right i gotta get out of here i gotta get ready and
start to move on out rage quit no that was just a regular quit so uh again we're gonna
go four days in a row this week tomorrow sam and max season two starting episode one and two
depending on how we go in there we might start the third episode but we'll see and then saturday
night is going to be old archive ms dos games so thank you for joining me on this little
quick quick little guy stream i did want to go three and a half hours and maybe maybe like
three forty five at least so uh eu crowd i'm happy to at least do this once in a while
so thank you all as always i'll see you guys soon if you don't catch the stream tomorrow or saturday
then maybe i'll see you another time take care guys let's move on to the bits see you soon
hey look there they are this shouldn't take very long because well we've only been going
for about three and a half hours so don't do the archive there's all sorts of weird
shit in there i'll be i'll be careful i'll be careful we're gonna do click smart click
for you to pick the game i'm gonna play and i'm gonna uh i'll now that i know that i'm gonna make
sure that whatever you do what do you feel we're gonna click on them and we're gonna check them
before we do them but a few hours ago we had let's see here torah t gave five community subs
earlier this morning thank you torah t didn't catch you when you did it but thank you
regardless uh cq thanks for the 10 bucks they say wtf i'm not sure why but thank you for
the 10 dollars they said oh it's because of what the time it was i see i see thank you cq cq for
the 10 dollars and yes i started at like 11 30 a.m today c4g thanks for the 250 ironforge parkour
stream when maybe if wild classic comes out and that doesn't they didn't fix that maybe
it's classic so it's there and it's not patched i will show you if it is a thing i can do
but thank you for the 250 after looks atrix thanks for the 250 shout outs
to simple flips simple flips at a game and dreams thank you for the 250 uh the jack thanks
to the 250 don't give shout outs to it's a trap probably should have read that second one
first i i don't i don't know what it is to what it's a trap of i don't know i don't know
that means did i just say something wrong i don't know don't tell them whatever i don't know any
of these things i thought that was a game in dreams anyways uh thanks for the 250 uh thank you
ned for the three dollars if you like dream sculpting you should try a vr sculpting program
like sculptor vr they are quite fun i think the next time i do dreams sculpting will be
with the move controllers feel like it's way better because you actually can move your hand
around it's not tilting around a controller with your wrists i feel like with if i if i
had two hands being able to hold things and sculpt around it i'd probably do a lot better
it feels so good with them yeah i'm looking forward to it but yeah sculptor via maybe i'll
try it there's a few more vr games that have come out to add to the list so why not right
thank you freudian weapon for the 250 can't stick around for tonight's stream but want to
show a little support i hope you have fun thank you for the 250 but with tonight i wonder
where are you i mean we're not here now but tonight if it was if it's like 11 or 12 o'clock
11 30 in the morning but where would be night time somewhere in asia okay tonight yeah australia
or asia it's always interesting to see where people are coming from you know hey marvosh
magali thanks for the 250 the song you wanted there it is this is the video that made it
famous the video that made it famous you got that it's the you got okay this video has 25
million views well that's a thing cool i didn't even know what it was like i'd show it you
know i don't i don't get time i don't get time everybody knows this meme except for me i
except for you you're talking to the ultimate in meme history that i don't know i don't know
any meme history we're both out of touch no we're not you're not out of touch that's not what
it is out of touch would mean that i've never heard this before and i don't like it i don't
i think this is stupid no i'm just that doesn't out of touch means i have a problem with it
out of time yeah mossy out of time is more accurate can't accept these out of touch
you know i probably am i turned 34 this year i who knows what the hell you kids are fucking
listening to these days i don't know i've listened to the rennan stimpy soundtrack
and i watch rugrats on tv that's all i did i don't have any other references
every reference you've ever heard me make was tied to a rennan stimpy episode
i don't have anything else up here what a man child of what i'm i'm don't hey boomer's
got to do what a boomer's got to do so okay if i'm a boomer at 34 what am i at 55 am i still a
boomer i'm not even 34 yet i just always do you guys do the same thing i do this do you guys
say how old you are for the year that it currently is because you don't want to because
you know it's coming like i'm 33 but like i'm turning 34 and it's like fuck that's the i
just say i'm 34 because it's coming it's gonna happen january 1st 2019 i was 34 january 1st
2020 i'm gonna be 35 i just i've never heard anyone say that i guess it's a way to like
cope with how old you're getting it's like how old are you 34 i'm turning i turned 34 this
year 34 but in my mind in my own you know headcanon i'm 33 i know that so it's like ah
you know i'm just preparing for it uh thank you c2k for the bits yeah it's a federal crime to lie
about your age you're hitting yourself you're hurting yourself twice no i'm not i'm preparing
i had a nightmare last night from your worm creation sorry clueless sniper thanks to the
250 no message thank you though and then finally we have uh zack or zakey zack how do you say
your name you've popped up a few times i want to make sure i get it right is it zacky is it
zake zacky it's okay zakay jeremy really enjoyed the stream but you really didn't have to scream
thanks for the 250 appreciate january 2nd birthday don't got no trouble like you boomer yeah i mean
if you had a january 1st january 2nd birthday that's actually really convenient because you
are just the next year you are the next year older imagine having a january 2nd birthday
january 1st birthday hey atrox atrox thanks for the 250 shout outs to the thing that people said i
got told to say and and thanks to the 250 what do you say we run the credits here they come
the subs on this stream today are as follows that guy this one that that one this one that
one i'm gonna say one of the one person's name here everyone's gonna be so jealous you
ready which one am i gonna say who's the lucky one oh i was gonna say it i was gonna say
oh no it'll be okay it's gonna be the one five names from right now one two three four
straight say say surge hunter and then sticks there you go he can't say it right too bad it
didn't land on germa's nuts right all right the next one i'm gonna say is 10 from now ready one
two eight nine mr spoop hey thanks a lot appreciate it i'm surprised at this many subs
for a stream that's less than a few you know three four hours thank you guys for real
i will see you real soon we're gonna be the normal time probably i don't maybe i don't know it
depends on when i go to sleep tonight plan on the normal time but i you may maybe maybe you
might see me like a couple hours early maybe depending on if i just just look like it'll
be a nice surprise for you it's gonna start between three and four pacific but like you
know maybe it might be an hour too early i don't know we'll see what are these names forgot
password to my account i push all the buttons there are a lot of strange names huh i just
got her i thought germa sleeps during the day like a normal streamer
what am i gonna rebuttal that i can't what am i gonna say against that but thank you
for joining me on the short stream i'll see you guys tomorrow for sam and max season two
episode one and then saturday for the ms daw 6 revaganza take care have a great night great
day i know it's not even night this is weird i usually start streaming like now it's weird
have a great rest of your afternoon and evening for some of you see you tomorrow ta ta goodbye