Hey, what's up everybody? What's happening? Welcome to the stream. It's me, Jerma. Nice to see you guys.
How was your day today? How were you doing?
Today we're gonna be playing the L.A. Noire game that we played last night. We're gonna just keep going.
And...
Okay, sorry about that for a second there. Just had something in my throat.
How is everybody doing today? Are you guys ready to play some games?
Okay.
Frame drop. Oh, yeah.
That happened to us last time too, though.
Sometimes it takes a second for us to get really going.
Already dropping frames. Loving the stream, buddy.
Come on, man.
Come on.
I dropped a hundred frames
in the first two minutes.
It has been like
40 hours of streams the last like five days and we've been pretty green.
So look, it's gonna it's gonna hiccup every now and again.
I mean like, come on, man. My title's got a typo.
Uh, oh, yeah, it does.
Nice. Hey, good pickup.
Well, anyways, hi guys.
Uh, we're gonna play L.A. Noire again.
Because that's just kind of what I that's what what we're doing.
We've got a lot of these games that I started and got halfway through.
I'd like to at least attempt to try to finish them.
How could I be a substitute teacher if I can't spell unknown?
Well, here's the thing. It's called, um,
pressing the keys too fast
and
not pressing down hard enough on the end.
Then you graze by it and you keep going. That's where 90% of my problems come from when I'm using the computer.
Is just grazing keys and not pressing down hard enough.
Making excuses to seem smart.
That mean do I need excuses?
Graduated at the bottom of my class.
Barely scraped by high school.
Um, got like a 2.7 GPA in college.
And, uh,
got a degree in communication.
Got a gamer degree in, uh,
blockbuster video.
I think I think I did okay, you know?
I got the boomer degree.
How does communication work?
Communication is film, tv, and radio.
It's you know, like it's mass media is what it is.
Fake gamer certificate.
You're lucky
that I don't permanently instant ban you.
Boomer jokes were never funny. I'm not making them. I'm just responding to them.
Should I stop responding to the boomer jokes?
Should I do that?
Let's get that smooth jasmine, but yes.
All the negative comments. I don't read just negative comments.
I read nice ones too.
Like for instance, uh, smelly boy says found the boomer.
Um, another one, uh,
uh, senpai says change outfit you dirty man.
I,
I can't read them.
I can't,
king crawfil says idiot streamer.
I'm trying to read good one. I don't, I, I can't read them.
They're,
play elf bowling you idiot, you idiot, you eater, you, something about,
I'm not reading that one.
All right, let's go.
I'm gonna pick up right where we left off last night.
And then guys, you know, because I've decided
I'm gonna let's stream. You know what I mean?
We're gonna do spring tomorrow as well
and judging by how far we get here, we're gonna go tomorrow too.
So my plan is to go tomorrow and I'm gonna take Sunday and Monday off
because I really need to prepare for the green screen screen stream because listen ladies and gentlemen boys and girls
We've got a solid date here now.
Thursday the 15th
Is the green screen stream locked in with the studio
Should be a good time
15 so there's gonna be a poll that will show up here on
uh on tomorrow for tomorrow's stream
And it's going to be you're gonna have to vote for your top few favorite
Um meme actions you want me to do because i'm not doing all of them
There's like 15 to 20 options. You're gonna have to narrow it down to like three
So there'll be a poll tomorrow. I will give it to you
Before the stream during the stream and after the stream as well
And before he streams a blank green background for four hours. Oh, but so much work has gone into this
That would be the dumbest thing i've ever done
Timber, please turn the game volume down. My wife can't hear it
Can the game volume down?
I don't understand
So tomorrow is an elf bowling stream. It is not
It would not i'm not going to play the virus fucking cereal box game. Sorry
Lego island you guys it's not just it's not that easy
It's you know, it's not that easy
I have to like do a virtual machine to put like 25 minutes of content
We did see this last night, but might as well just get another view
It's such a bad game
More like 25 streams of fun
Whole of your hot counselor now is not the time to lose your narrow
It would appear that someone has hooked a rose gold wedding ring and matching engagement ring
So you're to get to catch everybody up here
There's been a series of murders wedding rings being carved off of fingers
Naked bodies attacks
deaf
And I gotta put it all together then get out to the railroad depot on santa fe avenue
I'm fortunate found this morning beside like knack two
I'm gonna write to
real yard and pawnbroker
another body
An act two is like
The emperor may soon have to come you guys are mixing like somebody else's joke here
If you get that little shoved up your ass, you know what I mean?
Like that's like that like that's a funny joke is it good but it's that
Like you want me to go up on stage and do like steve martin's whole routine and pretend it was me
I mean like you want to like steal like a comedian's whole routine let's go to the pond bro. Yes
Do a donkey voice no like that's the equivalent
This is the equivalent of like no i'm gonna say it because like I don't want to like make people
I don't want no we're gonna move on from this because I don't want to like have
Hey, he said this out loud every time I have to say to this guy
That's but like okay, whatever. It's not like anything bad. That's like telling that's like no never mind
I'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna keep my hands clean of this one
Um, we'll just leave it this donkey is a very talented funny comedian online content creator
And he does that he has an act two joke
and uh
That's that's really funny. It's his he does it
This is what happens when you kill your own memes
Detectives felps and galloway la pd you have a rose gold wedding and engagement ring david bremner
We're gonna get something. Oh, by the way half the people in this chat are gonna be really disappointed
No, I mean that like I mean the half the people that were here last night
Feel lucky you're getting here. I got it
But we're not not yet
Trust me on this
Need to need to wait
One more day
Because there's something else that I found that is important. What's this mark here maker's mark?
Usually traceable that one came from hartfield's june. That's a whiskey, isn't it? Thanks for the tip
What is happening? Nothing
What is he talking about? Well, if you were here last night at the very end of the stream
We talked about something not bad
Does this mark mean anything?
Almost gives you an idea of the quality
Okay
Hello
What have you got on the guy who brought these in?
It goes by the name of percy b shelley gave an address
15 poland street london that's far away
Can you give us a description of the man who pawned these rings? Not sure
Medium height what if he was like ugly?
Really ugly I think ugliest guy i've ever seen
He just had one of those forgettable faces. We'll be in touch. Mr. Bremner
Okay, I like this desk
Then now this is the kind of desk that I wish that that I had
On the right you gotta you gotta draw to put your stuff
Enough place for three monitors computer can go under here and then a big storage thing. I wish they sold this
I'm, not a big fan of the finish. I would I would actually prefer um a walnut finish
That desk I have is nice
But it's lacking storage
You've got to admit this is looking hot
And he went to pawn a ring
But if you take it along with all of the other indicators real yard hugo moeller was identified by the school's ground keeper
He's our guy witnesses have fingered the wrong guy before he ran for god's sake. What's my game of the year so far?
He always maintained he was uh red dead redemption 2 made it unfair
We have a problem
We could have the local so i'm not gonna you know i'm not gonna include red dead redemption 2 in my list
purpose of games of the year
Because that's just cheating it's not fair
That's like an s tier it's that that always is number one and then we have to find out like what the other ones
Underneath it are all your letters are genuine and the man who may have also killed dear drew moeller
And how do we prove that like if you do a top five?
In like the golden locked slot up above the top five is red dead redemption 2
So
Red redemption 2 is zero
What have you played it?
It's very fun
I still have to play god of war. That's
People are talking about how great that was
Spider-man was really good house flipper
And I try really do mean that completely not joking like i'm not kidding when I say that
Yeah, those of you that think that's a joke. I mean it sounds like a joke, but it's not
Zero is below one
Well, yeah zero, yeah
One zero would not be above one
A way out a way out was a really interesting game that had a really interesting cool finish
But the whole game of a way out was a little
It was a little I don't know the climax of a way out was amazing
I don't know
What else came out this year?
This is so much further away than the objective, but by the way, this is like this
I don't even want to do this anymore. It's too far away
What was better detroit become human or a way out?
uh
uh, I don't know
I mean probably a way out because
a way out was
Something very different
It gets an extra notch
on the belt
for being
All different if detroit become human got rid of the other two storylines and it was just
Connor and hank go on admissions together and it's like a buddy cop game
I would probably think it was
Way better than it was
Don't shoot him. Oh, wow. He shot him. Why did he start running this way?
What
This isn't like a football game, man. You don't have to like
Oh boy. Sorry
All right. Don't kill this guy. I need to apprehend him
Killing this guy is not I I need to apprehend the suspect
No more code fours
I almost shot that guy right there because he had the same clothes on
Why is this guy so much faster?
Okay, here we go
Wait, he's not getting in a car. He's in he's he's in the car. Which car is he in?
It's a stitch up with her lovely tune
I thought he was trying okay
I thought if he followed him for long enough
He was gonna got in the car and was gonna leave and then I saw the gunshots and I
Didn't know which car he was behind and then it was too late by the time he got behind the car
Like you the death sentence was already there. So
He was there for a solid fight. I doesn't I I i'm sorry
But he got behind the car and I was already backing up and I didn't feel like getting out to like pursue him in
Or he probably would have shot me and then I would have seen the lul in the chat a hundred times
You know, I would have got out like how do I arrest him? What's the arrest button? What's the arrest button?
And then he was chopping the head and it would have been like lul like failed fish like idiot guys stump stupid idiot
126 iq I would have seen I've looked over and would have saw it
So I took it into my own hands and he got in the way. So it's just I'll finish
He still saw lul a hundred times
But that was not like and that was not me intentionally trying to receive lul because there's plenty of moments where like you can tell
I'm intentionally trying to get some lul's out of the out of you guys
I would say it's like I'd say it's like like 30 percent is intentional lul moments and the other 70 percent
Is unintentional lul moments
And that was one of those
God damn it. We survived this
It's going to be another thing to just to briefly bring up it and me saying lul and you guys, you know kind of
be
Inceptioning that into your head
As I got back with the analytics and the data behind it and I send certain companies that contact me
Well, how how how funny is your stream? Well, you know, if you take a look at the amount of lul's that happened last night
Uh a lot here forty two forty three hundred lul's
Uh, I can i'm here for you company b company a
Like i'm just i'm gaming analytics right now, you know what i'm saying?
So if any company's ever looking for like a really really really funny guy
I mean i'm i've got to be number one. You're crazy. I'm crazy. It's your fault. Okay guy with the gun behind my back
How am I supposed to trust you? God damn it
Don't shoot her everybody just shoots the person see sir. I think you ought to calm down. Here's kenny mind your own
God damn business. Why is everybody always on my case?
Told you here comes the sprint run away
Watch it
Give it up old man
Where is he?
Where's the where wait? What? Oh, he's right here
Okay. Okay. Okay
I got it. Okay. Did did I kill him?
Come on code two code two car 11k
Code four at alvera street, but i'll need an ambulance shots fired. The suspect is down
Solve that big case
Lul moments
Like isn't twitch will keep their own metrics and eventually when twitch implements like top lol lul moment of the week
I'll be in that compilation and they're like they'll have the chat on the side
Funny man crazy man german on a5 one of our resident top 1000 twitch partners
Did something outrageous
Chasing down an old man in a parking lot
He actually ran him over with the car. It'd be like bob bob saget. What do you mean when he used to do the voiceovers?
on home videos
Somebody that's what you'll start doing voiceovers and like oh my hey, it's me
I'm the old man wink wink add like fucking barking sounds and the funny like baby noises and stuff
I'll be on that compilation because i'll be able to look at the chat and see how many lul's were there
I'll be in the top lul moments of the week
Those of you that don't understand that reference
It's pretty specific and it's pretty old too kids in chat never saw
american
Another one of these
Too young
Hey, I remember i'm old enough to remember when it wasn't abbreviated to afv. It was america's funniest home videos
not america's funniest videos
And bob saget was the host and every single clip he did the same baby voice
And added comedic effect to every single clip and somebody won at the end
I think i'm would it be funny to do that do like a top clips
from twitch
And they're already there, but I just voice over them like bob saget used to do
Oh, yeah, wait that already that did already happen
Yeah, but like ray william johnson didn't do funny baby voices over all the footage
Did he?
Jesus felps
He did
I don't remember him doing that
He pitch shifted his voice up
Oh, yeah, he did do that
Forgot. Yeah, he did like pitch shift his voice happened say things. He did do the bob saget. Holy shit
All right, here we go. This would be the third street crime in a row
You leave no witnesses you stay out of the park
I'm not riding all the way to santa ana and then on the cincinnati with you pissing in my ear
I don't think anyone wants to pee in their ear. I don't have a choice
Stick-up charge is still a stick-up charge and I ain't going back inside
You got stuck that place up with me you're in trouble anything stupid
All right. This one is this one won't be a code for because it's no i'm not shooting anybody
This one is just pursued
Oops
Oh, this is tight tight tight corners here
You gotta get me closer
I think i'm like a little buggy
Clean this asshole off the road
What is this driving?
Is this what it looks like from back behind a different angle me driving?
It is it has to be
see
This is just i'm just watching mario kart ghost footage. Did somebody just come out of the jump out of the car?
Hit him coal spin him out
apprehend the suspect
Oh, they got in a car accident
All right, jeremy, that's enough reckless driving for you
See
They lived car 11k calling kgpl
Code four at the lucas i'm
I had nothing to do with that. I had nothing to do with it
They got enough straight-on head-on collision. I didn't do that
Are you guys certain the code for means they died?
or is code for I mean
Like we got him
What does it mean?
cold come on
Code four means no further assistance. So does it mean they died?
You guys are telling me code four means dead
You gotta code four. You're fucking idiot. What?
Oh, thank god, you can't go through windshields
We both imagine we both fly through the windshield
You can fly through the windshield and red dead. There is no windshield though
I'm getting fucking old
No, seriously, I like them
Look at the body of like a fucking 50 year old man
It turns 30 and like it's just a light switch flip
Am I gonna play hitman 2? Absolutely
I why why does he not have why does he not have a webcam? I don't understand. Why is it a webcam on?
I wonder jim gaffigan voice
Really was I really just like got possessed by jim gaffigan
How do I get down there?
I don't want to drive there
Come on. Come on. It's right there
It's right there
There has to be a way. I can just jump this
It's right here
Clip through the wall and I have to drive. Let's go right right right
Do my best donald trump impression and I will subscribe
And i've done trump like a thousand times
How do I get over there? Am I out of my mind?
Do I have to go through this gate?
Okay, well there we go just give me a break finally, okay made it really hard
You boys ready?
Follow me
We should keep this development
We're all on the same team
chain of command
Skipper will decide who needs to know
Got it skipper
Let's investigate the crime
Do an impression of donkey kong?
Um, well, there's two different donkey kongs
Hard, isn't it? Yeah, I look out for all the rail depots because the donkey kong that could talk the negro
Nelson gaines called it in there is I came down here to make sure him and the other guy jameson stuck around
Jameson found the body something like that guy makes me sick. We'll talk to the coroner keep an eye on both of them
All right, let's investigate. But yeah, there's there's there's when um
What have we got here? It was when he was just a gorilla approximately 40 years of age. Remember he used to go
At least nothing legible
That's all he did trauma to the temple nose and eye regions ligature marks point to the probable cause of death being strangulation
He didn't have any other lines any idea of the time of death from her temperature after midnight would be my guess
Okay midnight
Okay, let's see if we can no you need to go
We just examine
No neck mark
No rope around the neck on uh, this
Particular case here smell very good. There is the usual evacuation smell
But it appears she's been living rough for quite some time
very strong smell of alcohol
The autopsy will tell but I would assume that she was inebriated
Do funny baby voice
No, do funny baby voice. What does that mean?
The ring is gone. Another missing ring
It certainly seems i've been swabbing a lot of bare fingers recently
Can you be more exact about the time of death? He thought about it
I'm trying to figure out what it meant the body was in a one or two hour window
The baby voice is the spi voice. Uh,
No, but it's not though
Anything else I can't do anything else. That's nothing
Where are the markers?
Where's the this is evidence marker?
He's a giant yellow square. Look somebody put down a giant marker for me
Do you Christopher Walken?
well
Okay
Dear uh, Evelyn
I hope that this letter finds you in a better way than when you we lost part
Better words were exchanged you are taking too much liquor
And this is bernie sanders whoops
That's bernie sanders
I don't know why that happened
Uh, but I am not writing to harass
I'm writing to apologize as heartbroken seeing what had become of my little girl
And what she is doing?
to destroy herself
Uh, you are destroying your body and uh, believe me your soul
Wait, I can't do it anymore
No, no, no, Evelyn
Evelyn, let me excuse me. Excuse me. It is harder for me. No, excuse me
Let me excuse me. It's harder for me to watch than you can imagine. Okay, believe me
Yeah, I can't
Can't do it
There you go
Is that guy gonna subscribe?
We could go over to the lot and see what they know about her. No
That's gonna be difficult col
Keystone studio lot closed back in 41
He did it I think I did I get did I get conned here
I don't know what we got. We got matches
With a looks like i'm kind of a dress on it
Come on. Maybe someone had mentioned
You mess with the germa you get the perma
I'll sub if you finish oblivion. I'll dog. I see you in 60 hours
This is a shit for personal items not booze. That's like 20 streams from now
Okay, two large suitcases a small suitcase bed row pillow plain bed sheet
Um a hairbrush bowling pin statuette makeup clothes. Is that it? I think that's it
That's not it
Anybody to talk to
Did I not?
Hold on sing the overwatch song
I don't even know. What are you talking about? I already did that
I I don't I don't know what you mean
It's apparently still evident somewhere
like you're talking about the song that goes like
They're like
That was not ideas detective felps and galloway homicide
Can you tell me exactly what happened the thing that plays before every trailer when I saw this man here?
Lying on top the woman wasn't moving and seemed to be in a bad way
What time was this about 7 30 this morning, sir. Thanks for your help
Have you given patrolman hart your details? It was hard. Thank you. You can go now
So you pick up the phone
Any other evidence?
No good to me
Violin over here
Do I know what tiktok is? Yes, I do. I know what tiktok is
I've seen plenty of memes. I've seen plenty of weird
I what are you thinking? I'm not it's city keeps tossing us dead bodies
We're just running to catch up
I'm in touch with the youth. I know I just told you I know what it is. I don't know anything else
Detective felps la pd homicide john ferdinand jameson. We need you to answer some questions john
If you don't mind, I prefer ferdinand. Don't push your luck knucklehead. What were you doing to the body?
Are you sure you won't be upset?
Try me ferdinand
I was kissing her
Whoa
It's not against the law shut up
Turn out your pockets for this guy's and hey, what's he what do you got in your pockets?
You fucking asshole
Classic carmine. I've seen this lipstick before
Is this yours ferdinand? No
I found it near her purse
I thought she could use some lipstick rusty. He says here he goes again
This guy is fucked
All right. Well
You uh went through her purse. It wasn't like she needed it
I took a look
Fucking peewee herman
Is he posing for pictures?
He's posing for this
Okay, uh
He's that's like a straight on scare money wasn't any to take
I found her lipstick in her matchbook over on the mat
Not much else
Okay, you found the body
Yes, I did
I work here. I was coming off shift and headed home
well
That's not true
Why didn't you report the body jameson? Do you know how this is gonna look to a jury a jury?
I could tell that she was dead a jury. Whoa. What are you talking about? She wasn't here then let me
You're under arrest jameson. We'll see how this plays out
Until then you can think a little on how you'd like to be treated if you were found dead
I'm telling you it's not illegal me and some friends of mine
Jesus
Clyde you get this sack of shit into a cell i'll deal with them later. Sure rusty
All right, call it in
Did I drink?
No
What why why do I have to be drunk if I do something weird?
Phil's bed 12 47
This is
Look, I need an address on levin's liquor. This is a store to the san fe rail yard if possible from starbucks
Just a moment detective
Would be the one at nine three nine south hope street
Thanks for your old man body
All right. So now we gotta go
Ha ha filly voice germa, are you drunk?
Get drunk and do something weird wait you relax. What are you prime scene? Wait?
Isn't that where i'm already here
Do I need to come back here did I miss something hold on
I should do a drawing stream where I draw stuff from bit messages. I'm so bad at drawing
That would be embarrassing
Oh, hold on blood splatter on the carriage
She must have been struck while standing up
All right. Here comes the legend of zelda. You opened up a treasure chest and you got something inside
No, that's it. What else is there we do here?
This is the crime scene
Well, hold on it doesn't appear to be connected
Okay
Once the music stops you're done. Yeah, but what did it mess up on the body?
No
Back to the note
Wait, did I not read this?
Is this something on the other side?
No, it's not here
Read the letter. I didn't I do that already
I I opened it before like I already did that but I didn't like scroll all the way down
There it is
Okay
Locations, let's go to the bat
Set as destination
Dangus
Sorry, I opened it and read it and looked at it slow and I didn't go all the way down to the bottom of the paper
To get the you looked at the clue thing to pop up
Sorry, i'm sorry that we're sending it
Yeah
Yeah right about that people are starving. They can't do that want to sell the food to fund the civil war against the communist
Really?
I guess that's okay then armies can't go through
Oh, what is this even a rock star game?
Did rock star have anything to do with this game because that chain link fence goes down
Armies can't fight that one does
You spend all your money on weapons, but you still have to have the will to fight
unfortunately
The reds will win in china
Rockstar published the game. You know what you're saying?
The people of this country overthrew king you think the chinese will balk at an emperor if they are rock star
Sure, let's do it
I can't turn down a client
I can't turn down a chase guy around
And then shoot him was it dead in the chat. What's up, man?
and remarkably
Calm down not one person was injured really enjoying your game though, man
Deb in the chat. That's crazy, man
What's up, dude?
Hey, what's what's going on kid? What's up, man?
So I got a question for you dude. What's up, dude?
Do uh, what's going on kid? Do you like
How long did it take you to make uh some of the the animations in the game?
Like some of the facial animations like from the last cutscene dude
It took a couple months. Nice kid
No, I can't
Ah son of a god
Can I really not do anything? This is just what a lookout point. What's the purpose of this? So what next?
So this is deb in the chat
First of all, I mean, what's up, dude?
What's going on, man? Happy to have you, man
Uh, what happened to um the part up here?
I think the power's gone to your head felps
Why would you walk back in the path?
Is it up there? Oh, man
This was no there is no joke. I'm just pretending to be like a streamer that has sees a deb in the chat
For a joke. No for pretend. Why don't you come on out jimmy? I'm pretending hurt you not my honey boy
Wait, oh, I remember this one. This is the guy
This is the shotgun guy, okay
That the lady of the house
It's a nice story two old lovebirds just moved in together, but they had a falling out and chased across the yard with a 12 gauge
now
Let's go
Multi-kill godlike
Shut down shut down shut down. How do you do that guy's voice?
No
That's not how it is frog like
How do you make those noises with your mouth well first of all, what's up, dude? What's up kid? Thanks for coming in
um
For will you just shape your throat in the directions? Thanks. But hey, what's up, man? I get the point
That mailbox i'm flying
This is why people randomly hate you
What who hates me?
What who randomly hates me?
I don't I don't know. I I don't want people to hate me
but at the same time
If I want to if i'm gonna say godlike in a frog voice i'm gonna do it
And nothing's going to stop me from doing it. I need to ask you some questions concerning eveline summers, you know
I'm walter metch
eveline summers
What is it now? You knew eveline as well as I wanted to know eveline somebody really hate me because I did a frog voice
For five seconds and drinks. They've had any money. That'd be a really weird reason to hate somebody
Did you ever tell you where she was staying?
I don't think she was living rough. She had that kind of schtunk about yeah
I went to this guy's dream and he did he did like a frog voice. I fucking hate this guy
All right. What are we doing? What's your name?
Grover McCaffrey mind if I ask you some questions. Mr. McCaffrey. I'm just a starving rider detective
What do you want to ask about eveline summers and why she was found beaten and strangled in the rail depot on santa fe?
Okay
I see your point
How well did you know her?
I can't say that I knew her it was more like I was aware of her
What was your last contact with event? Did you see eveline last night? No
I was at home. That's bullshit writing
Maybe not. I mean you're moving around a lot though, but he's not darting his eyes around
Do you want to get dragged into this McCaffrey? Do you want us to get interested in you?
She hung out with this powder puff james tiernan
They haunted the public library together. Oh, well, do you know james tiernan? I know he works some kind of plebeian job
Rawlings bowling alley
Brawling I know that place corner of ninth and grand a lot of cops pull there on tuesday night
Nobody hates me right? Like nobody hates me here. Just making sure do you have a criminal record?
Nothing serious
It was a fucking joke i'm but i'm rebounding the joke
Say I had a joke force filled up. Uh, hold on. What the fuck did you just say?
He's doing a lot of blinking
You want to save me some time or do you want me to look up your file industrial disputes?
strikes
worker's rights
That kind of a regular fifth column
Nice to meet you comrade
So I was gonna do a thing and now thank you for the information to do it mccaffrey
Where I was going to do?
a um
I wonder if there's an extension I could use to do it to kind of be fun
But this would just the reason why I can't is because this would just be the lie detector stream again
But a different version of it
Or I would just put the prompts on the screen and just sit in the right position and have you guys interview me?
But we already like we already did that
Um, let's go. Let's go to the bar. Wait, we already went to the bar. There's something else here
Yeah, did the same camera angle and sound effects but that would take some time to put together but be fun
Did I miss something here?
You're free to speak to the regulars just don't shake them too hard
Go to a casino for a stream and like I I you're not allowed to film in a casino
You'll get a a hand swat down on your hand
I like an idea though. Why don't I just like run my own casino from my house?
you know what I mean
I could like instead of I could try to make some extra money on the side by
Inviting people over to play like blackjack in my this is a will ferrell movie. Never mind
I don't think I can do anything else here
I mean, there's this person here. But again, I think I can talk to thank you a friend of
Summers didn't ask it very cute. You know, who's asking? I know my rights
You don't have any answer the question
Evelyn mooch is for drinks. I don't have any time for that. Was that so hard?
Keep writing me copper
Um
Okay
What's next?
Uh the liquor store. I don't know what i'm missing here, but I don't know what it is. So we're just gonna go
You hate the new wendy's ad. What is the wendy? What is it?
What did you make him a cafri? Let me guess
He'll come a day two close friends sitting at inside eating in the restaurant, but he's out of us here
Which by the way that very never very rarely does that happen?
I don't know what it is with fast food companies where they depict like whole people going in whole families and friends like having
Like getting together and sitting around like a big table and eating donald's
That no one does that
That's first that's the first mistake
whole people
And then their second mistake is people being excited about peeling off
Stickers that give you like 20 cents off of a large soda
Like oh man, yeah, bro. I won and they hold it up and it's like oh me too. I want a nugget
Nobody you ripped it off and you're like, oh, I don't fucking care
You never use it because you throw it in the trash. You never bring it back
What can I do for you? LAPD Phelps and Galloway. We're making inquiries into the murder of Evelyn summers
Evelyn
She's dead. You knew Evelyn summers, mr. Robbins. Yes. I knew Evelyn. I was a good friend of her ex-husband
She kept some of her stuff here. Yeah boardwalk and park place collect them both and you get a jet
Come this way you get a million dollars
They don't even print those, you know
They don't even print
Boardwalk they print park place and park place is so common
Everybody gets park place and then they go. Oh shit, dude. I just need boardwalk and i'm dead
They don't even print boardwalk. It's not even printed
The ceo of mcdonald's like he's gets on a plane to some random town in iowa
And he like slips boardwalk on one of the slips one of the drinks down and into fucking some random place
And the next person in line gets it is one printed
He did something other than drinking her spare time. Oh, she was bowler
The ceo slipped the ceo. She's like goes into a random store with quite some time. It's in a case
That large mcdonald's fucking soda
With the boardwalk on it is in a locked gold case that only the ceo is allowed to touch
and he
In his weird fucking creepy tower throws a dart at the board in the united states
And picks the one place that he's going to go sneak and put like a fake mustache on and drop off the golden case
One summer is what exactly did evelyn work in the pictures?
1938 worked in legal copyrights for music. Okay
You've said too much already
Is the volume below them i'll turn it up for you
picture
Okay, is that it?
Evelyn was reading aristotle
Aristotle metaphysics
The stupid thing about her was
What else is in here and she was borrowing books from grovener mcaffrey
Can I read?
um
Yes, yes, I know how to read. Thank you
She wasn't always such a loner
Okay
Ronald mcdonald hates you because he said all those mean things about mcdonald's
I didn't say anything mean about mcdonald's
What did I say bad about mcdonald's? I was just speaking
candidly in my opinion of
The contest of the monopoly contest
I didn't say it was bad
I I eat mcdonald's mcdonald's is fine. It tastes good big mac number one
I mean, you really can't beat a number one. I don't think
Big macs are awful cut nothing, but
I don't think so
Number two the two single cheeseburgers. I mean, it's hard to argue
It's hard to argue with facts. Okay, the number one from mcdonald's
Is probably the best fast food item
Besides that you're talking about the wendy's crispy chicken sandwich or scares away customers the wendy's crispy chicken sandwich
Or the burger king long chicken sandwich
I mean those are that I think those are tied for first place
Gentlemen, I have a store to run
What are we doing?
We're trying to account for everyone's movements. I think it's big burger king sucks. Okay morning burger king doesn't do anything good anymore
Let's pick up some of our things
Yeah, here's a burger king just goes. Hey, wait, our food sucks really bad
So let's just like dump a bunch of sauce and bacon on every sandwich and that's how that's how they get customers and it
tastes good
I'm surprised burger king's still in business
I look I don't hate burger king. I think it tastes fine. I mean I I ate burger king like two weeks ago and I was like
Oh, this is good
but I mean
You can't and the taco bell is in this here, too
The cheesy godita crunch beats the big mac
In a one-to-one fight, right? But if the big mac has the number two in the corner as a tag team
Nothing else on the whole taco bell menu is worth eating. You know what i'm saying?
So one-on-one fight go to keep cheesy godita crunch will win every time having cops in the store scares away customers
What about kfc?
stuff like that you you check filet you but no no guys guys guys
Like you can't bring in like the higher tiered fast food places
They're in different with different weight classes
Like the the featherweight doesn't fight the heavyweight. You know i'm saying they're in different weight classes
No, kfc is not a higher tier. Check filet is a higher tier
Arby's is a higher tier. I'm not putting kfc in high tier. I'm putting kfc in the in the other in the gentleman
I have a store to run. Arby's is garbage, but it's like it's it's but they have fresh turkey
Okay, there's fresh turkey at Arby's. They don't have that at McDonald's. What was the question? I don't even remember
I don't know what he even said
Can I can I review the information?
F tier kfc is good. You're all idiots
Idiots
You're all idiots
No, i'm not saying that i'm saying what somebody said
No, I was quoting what somebody else said
the gentleman i've
Okay, i'm just gonna pick one. I don't know what he did, but he looks like he's telling the truth
Any idea where the money came from? She didn't mention it, but she did say the booze was a present for a boy
She said they have been fighting and she had to make it up to her
Okay
I don't I don't i kfc is good. What's wrong? Are you in devil close? Mr. Robin?
How many people will be sad? It's not it's not at the same quality and tier of like
uh
What what give me give me some higher tiered like fast food places
You've got um
You've got arby's
I'm not even paying attention anymore. Fuck. Why does this have to happen? I'm gonna lose this case
Fresh turkey
I've only had arby's one time. I've I have no opinion on arby's
What did he say?
I've got the impression that evelyn had been sleeping rough of late. This is why people hate you
Why am I shilling it i'm just i'm not trying to get her back on the straight and narrow
I aren't look i already told you the number one and the number two from mcdonald's to be honest
You have to have a good reason to want to get very difficult to beat on the run
Unless you're a cheese it go do the crunch
I got them both right. Do you know a friend of evelyn's by the name of mcaffrey?
Not personally
This guy just telling the truth, isn't it?
No, he's not
We're struggling for leads robbins. Did she know mcaffrey?
She idolized him
And what I gather the feeling was far from mutual
He seems to have missed eating dog food tier fast food on stream
You could see how it's all bad. It's like evelyn
None of it's like any good mr. Robbins. No problem
I got them all correct. Hey, i'd like to make arrangements for the funeral
You think I could get in touch with evelyn's mother?
Put in a call to the watch commander. What's my favorite brand of chicken nugget?
He'll be trying to reach the next of kin. Well, thanks
I bred my own chicken nuggets and I make them from scratch. Evelyn never hurt anybody not wendy's of the bed wendy's
So we need to go
But I don't have chick-fil-a
At least I don't know if there's any around in las vegas, but in
Massachusetts, I don't think I think there was one chick-fil-a in the entire state of massachusetts. Let's not keep the man away. It wasn't available
Go to the bowling alley
We just like learned that
It's my very new place in vegas to eat
uh
Boy, I could never tell you
Some of the best restaurants i've ever eaten are here
so I
I can't tell you
I mean i
Gordon ramsay steak was probably the best piece of meat i've ever eaten
So I mean is that?
It was it just was I I can't just be like, well, you know
It was the best piece of uh, like red meat I probably ever had
Hello rusty two on your usual lane. I'm detective felts homicide. You must be new
What's your shoe size?
More like shoe things
You got a guy who works here by the name of tiernan. Sure we do
He's a pin setter
Clears the jams works the gutters
Go right in
He'll be hopping around the lanes toward the back
What a great old lady actress, he's a nice boy. Thanks, ma'am
That's what i'm gonna do. Let's go get it
i'm gonna be
When I get to be like 60 70 like 75 years old
I want to be the old man at the desk
in movies and tv shows
All right, but did she say he was like back here?
I just don't know how to dance or have to go like down the lanes. Is it like in the back?
That broad has socks in it for zero
That's it
Do I have to like run down the alley?
He's like where where did she say he just was i'm sorry
All right, we've been talking about fast food. I don't know what the case is anymore
The women don't find you handsome. Does she recommend the specialness?
tiernan la pd
Oh, here we go. At least we got the camera on his face. We know what he looks like
What are you waiting for get after it? We might go faster if we weren't carrying the extra weight
Wow
These are flashy cars to be parked outside of bowling alley the lanes attract a fast-living individual with money to burn
Or a middle-aged individual with the need to feel dark
Keep it steady and i'll try to bust his tires
Hit him clean this asshole off the road
So now I have to hit him because you couldn't do your job. Don't go to sleep on me. Get me back in close
So i'll take care of it
Hit him call spit him out
Another runner at least we've got a suspect. Why do they always run?
I'm sure we've got the wrong person in more than one of these homicides, but they always seem to land
That's not him spinning out that's him just dropping through the park, okay
If this isn't the killer we can at least get him for reckless endangerment
That's unless he runs into a wall and it saves us all the trouble this car is going to explode
Tunnels god damn it. He'll kill himself. All right knocking into the train
I'm okay with it
fucking time
Hands up hands up hands up hands up hands up hands up hands up
Put your hands in the air
Why is he in a train conductor uniform?
He isn't what
That's what he was wearing
So what does that mean? So that's uh, that's the suspect
So now we've got
I don't know why the bar is still on here, but now we have to go to the police station
Is mario wearing a conductor's uniform?
Um, well mario has overalls but not a train conductor's hat
That's what was really
Completing that thing was the train conductor hat
You're gonna kill us
What happened to that lady?
Is that lady alive?
Not with who killed this lady?
Uh, okay. Well, I don't know
interesting
You did no I didn't she fell down
I did not I ran into the medium. I didn't kill anybody
Is somebody gonna tell us what the hell is going on?
Is everybody knows what the heck's happening here?
Hey, maybe you guys don't even tell us what the heck is going on down here captain
Ray and mal have some concerns over the henry and molla cases
Which I don't want aired outside of this room evidence is solid captain. I agree rusty
It's just that corpses keep piling up
copycats
I've been banging the same drum
But the notes and the lipstick messages evlyn summers cartel classic carmine
Each woman same brand same color
Teresa tarrelson didn't have a lipstick message lipstick murderer. Technically. You're right rusty. She didn't have any lipstick
But she did have a message
We found it beneath her dress scraped with a sharp stick. What did it say?
You sure you want to know ray?
As far as we can be sure it said cunt bd
That's one way of looking at it
Looking at what?
Cunt is all about access though. You're married yours is mortgage
Some of us like to pay by installments this guy
Doesn't like to pay at all
Why are you so angry mal?
Because I just had to fire one of my assistants. He was a friend of jameson's god knows what he might have been up to
Captain we have good leads in the summers case, but it's up to you to decide how we proceed
Keep this under your hat for now
Follow up on evlyn summers. I want daily reports
I'm back. All right. I was just in the bathroom. What did I miss? We got our orders back to the summer's case
I'm just scared. I'm just scared and you don't even i'm just kidding
trace address on
The governor's mccaffrey that every day
I'm just looking for a phone. It's apparently here
Where's your phone? Where's the police phone?
operator message for kgpl
Putting you through now felps batch 12 47
I'm gonna get 12 47 tattooed on my back. I need an address for a grodner mccaffrey
Thanks, man
Okay, invest to get the apartment
What happened to the car? There it is. He's already in it
The ogf 658 i'm gonna get that tattooed on my back. Let me pose a question depends
What's it got to do with morals?
Would it bother you to put the wrong person away depends on what on whether anyone except the poor son of a bitch
In the slammer ever found out
There's people there that guy definitely these people all got hit
All of them got run over i'm gonna get germa 985 tattooed on my tongue
Cole come on
So every time I brush my teeth i've reminded him
Who I what my channel is?
Shortcut possible, maybe this is break. You're probably stuck through here
What are you doing? What are you doing? Get out of here get away from me
That's just big enough for the car, isn't it?
Come on. It's like the baby toys. Whatever
Cole can I do it? Let's see
j e r m
A 985 I can do it. I could get germa 985 on my on the front of my knuckles here
Like put if I put them together and it'll say germa 985
I could hold both my hands up like straight like high five
And instead of a high five on my fingers. It's just j e r m a 985
I'm not gonna do that. Why would i'm not going to do that?
Now we're gonna find wait. Hold on. I was gonna look at the list of people
Apparently not
Okay, it was on the other side. Where's mcaffery
mcaffery is an apartment six
apartment six
Six that I it's kind of hard to see it's dark
four
two
one
I don't have to go up. Do I three if I have to go up the stairs, what wouldn't this be like?
11 or like what different floors? No
Level two. All right. Come on, man
What is that?
Doesn't look like anybody's home kick it phelps
Okay
God forbid you need to take the stairs. I'm not complaining about the stairs
I'm just complaining about the fact that
It should be 101 102 103
201 202 203 204
Here's the bottom part of that letter
From the letter we found beside the body
Very least i'd say it ties mcaffery to the scene
Anything else?
Oh, it's also another this is a critical theory
Well, there's
I will say that the criminals have been very very bad at not leaving the bloody clothes
And murder weapon on the ground in their apartment
He said at least put it in the closet
And we have a book. I see carothers argues way out of this one
specifically the tire irons
Who are you guys?
What are you doing in here from the la pd, ma'am? Do you know where we might find mcaffery? I'm his neighbor
Is he in trouble? Look lady we need to find him and in a hurry. Are you gonna give me trouble?
He has a pigeon coop up on the roof
He spends his mornings up there when he's been drinking how do we get up there he drinks with pigeons down the hall and up the stairs
That's kind of drunken in command of a carrier. It's kind of badass actually like surely we can get drunk with pigeons
A citation at least change the outfit again. Why i'm going to be officer felps
So we're gonna go up on we're gonna go up on the roof
That way stupid
Rooms 9 and 10 room 11. No, that's not it. We gotta go up. We are at the top
But what out the window?
No, there's roof access
Running on a hangover mcaffery sit down and we'll talk. Did he think that was gonna work?
I'm gonna throw a bird at you. Nice try don't get down
Go back up
All right. Come here grover
Grover mcaffery you are under arrest
He just got stuck there
You a runner mcaffery stay and fight the good fight
tackle
tackle them
Not yet
Give it up la pd
I mean, I think he knows where you're from at this point felps
You're wearing a police outfit. You've said it three times. Here comes the tackle
tackle
Tackle him. There it is
Can't we talk about this?
What the fuck?
What can't we talk about?
Little thing was
Uh kind of messed up
We need to get downtown and wrap this thing up. It's got to be the captain unless
Terran and set him up. We talk about don't think that asshole jamison could have done it. Do you?
And whoever did it brain just shut up his brain queued up that line
And it was already into his mouth through his vocal cords by the time he was knocked out his name was never on it
If you think the list is exhaustive rusty, who am I to argue listen? Let's just work the case at hand. Shall we?
Then we can sit down for all the puzzle pieces to get right on this side
I ain't scared
Still gonna do it. I'm not scared
I'm not even gonna get off this either
Well, I passed it
Give me a break
It's too focused on driving on the tracks
I was hoping I was hoping it was going down going to the cut scene
But it didn't excuse excuses excuses excuse
All right, we got a lineup. We have a couple of suspect stick with one of these suspects
It's either mcaffrey or tiernan, sir
I think jamison is an aberration
All right
I'll deal with that degraded lunatic myself. He's got some fearful retribution coming turn in as a one
Caffrey isn't two. I want the confession from one of them. All right, let's go
Where we go who we go first
Whatever one of these are strips off me at the grand jury two
Who's in in a room? You've been you're in room two
It's you ready to caffrey questions. You think I have all the answers
People who run from the police usually have something to hide
Touche detective
Let's see where this takes us
Relate to chip with the victim, but wait a minute
I need to see some things here because we have pawned rings rings pawned by suspect
Percy be shelly dark hair medium height and build
Show vagrant lifestyle missing ring good and from marks on victim's skin. The ring was gone
digest after midnight
handbag
movie lot employee id found among victims personal effects
This lipstick in possession of john ferdinand jameson
Torn letter addressed to evelyn pieces found in possession of victim and mcaffrey parking tickets to hand out. This is the one
Okay, so this ties them together
Inscribed this is the mcaffrey found amongst her personal things. This is his book
So, I don't know what she is. She'd never let me borrow a library book. Oh, yeah, I got it right here
With victim bought whiskey for a boy after an argument
And then there's a tie iron. Okay
What is your relationship with you told us you barely knew evelyn summers. She hung around sometimes
I had very little to do it
Well, that's not true
uh
Now the question is
Is it like the book?
You do you have you lent her a book?
Like that's very clearly like your signature and you lent it to her
Or this letter
You'll have to do better than that grovener. We know about you and evelyn. Evelyn was a lush and a boring one at that
You can't link her to me
All right. Well
Which one is more damning though? I mean this this did he write this who wrote this?
I mean the book is
It's clearly
It just has his signature in it
But yeah, I mean that's we know that you thought enough of her to loan out your copy of the metaphysics
I what?
I did no such thing that bitch stole that book from my apartment
The impudent fucking moron and that made you angry angry
I was livid looking up at me with that stupid face of hers begging me to forgive her
Very good
That's one to you detective. This guy's fucking crazy
Ah
We're not like a what?
Okay alibi
What's your alibi? Evelyn died sometime around midnight
Remind me. Where were you?
I was at home
writing
I'm working on a manuscript
Uh, where are you now? You're going to need to do better if you don't want to swing for this
I was having a political meeting in my apartment cheese and crackers for the fifth column
Some of these people will corroborate your story. I won't give up names of party members good
Your funeral
It's either going to be you or tier net opener
Make it stick detective
The party has good lawyers
No, you've got me you got me there touche
Well, let's go talk to the other guy
All right. We need interview room one
Which is it this way?
No guns. Wait, is this an interview room?
No, this is the holding cell
Here's interview room one
Why did you run tiernan?
I was the last one to see ephelin that night. I knew you would think it was me. Oh bloody
All right. This is the bowling alley guy
So hold on relationship with the bowling alley guy
handbag
movie lot
uh
Liquor purchase so liquor purchase
Store owner robbins testifies victim bought whiskey for a boy after an argument, right?
So he's gonna he this is this is the boy, right?
Can you describe your relationship with eveline?
I barely knew everyone
Sounds like half an answer to me tiernan. Were you sleeping with her?
That's none of your business
Aristotle's metaphysics the book that belonged to mcaffrey
Mccaffrey saw her looking at her once and laughed in her face. What's in his front pocket? You're saying eveline stole it
She wanted something of his truth
I mean that's he's staring
Directly
That's truth
Look at his eyes. He is locked in
You don't like mcaffrey. Do you tiernan?
He's full of the common manner team, but he props up a bar like the rest of us
Evelyn thought he was going to be a great novelist
He had nothing but victory offer
Holy shit, that's wrong. He okay. So this guy
He wasn't darting. Okay alibi for you and Evelyn were drinking together last night
And she had no other place to stay. I don't know what happened last night
I don't remember. We got him here because this is the little bit. Yeah, you're
Yeah, i'm, sorry, dude. You're lying tiernan. She bought you booze and you know it you fought and i'm not lying
She got up and left. That was it
well
Sorry, but facts
Stayed other ones
She left but she came back. She bought you a quart of whiskey to make it up to you. She told the liquor store owner
You're in deep trouble, buddy
She said she loved me
She wanted to care for me. Oh
Confession never stopped talking about mcaffrey confession
Mccaffrey was a writer and mcaffrey was a hero mcaffrey cared for the little guy. Did you kill her tiernan confession?
I might as well have confession
Kicked her out. I kicked her. She had nowhere to go in her mouth. What? Okay. Well
Well
Do you own a car tiernan? No, I don't
Have access to a lug wrench
No, we use a lot of them to clear jams in the pin setting machines
No, this is okay. He's lying. But hold on. Wait, wait, wait
That's not that good deck. I don't think I can connect it
Coroner's report says that evelyn was killed with a wrench
I think you did it and then planted the evidence at mcaffrey's apartment for us to find
We went to his apartment
Mcaffrey was up on the roof
Evelyn stole the book
Mccaffrey went crazy when he found out he said he said he would put her out of her misery
He can be very cruel
That was correct. Yeah, that was it from her right hand. That's strange
She always wore it
uh
Big black circular disc with a yd in the middle
It was made from an old typewriter key present from the prop department at her old movie studio 50 percent
We're going to talk to mcaffrey
You need to think about what you've told us tiernan. You're not in the clear
Okay, so
Let's see
I got this gadget with guy putting recording devices in this place
So I have to go to the other room
Sit down. Hey, so did you do it?
I want to ask you another question
access to the tire iron
We found the lug wrench that evelyn was battered with in your apartment and the note from her mother and your blood-stained clothing
We have you cold mcaffrey
You think if I could be bothered to murder evelyn summers, I would be stupid enough to leave the evidence in my apartment
Tiernan testifies to threats of violence against victim made by
gaffrey
so
We got you
I don't believe you grovener. The evidence says that you killed her
You can prove that I wanted to kill evelyn
Tiernan is prepared to testify that you threatened evelyn's life in his presence
Self-preservation
That's understandable
Okay, i'll level with you. This guy's so weird tiernan killed evelyn
He came to me for help. I listened to him and he explained why he did it
Tiernan went to you for help. It's not to come to buy that back. That's how it went down
Back and forth a terrible mistake, but he would be throwing his life away
If he went to the cops I took his things and told him I would dispose of them, but you didn't
Speak to tiernan
Okay, god
Okay, so I now we gotta go back in there and say hey
Uh, he says you did it. Well, he did it. Well, he says you did it. Well, I say he did it
Jesus
Okay
Oops wrong way
Where's the other interview room?
No, no god
You spoken to mcaffrey I can go I hate the
Camera spin third person angle that they stuff in these have these small corridors
Okay, so
Rawlings bowling alley employee and friend. Yeah, okay. Wait, wait. So let me see
Here's this accusation
gaffer testifies to tiernan confessing and asking for help disposing of evidence
So evelyn passed out and you walked out. What happened next? I woke up in the morning
Mary hung over
I thought evelyn would have come back
Okay
Uh well
I know you're lying james. You went out looking for her. Tell me what really happened
I don't know what you're talking about
How can you say I wasn't in that hotel room?
This is a dub
Can't we just hook like something up to your brain and see what your thoughts are?
You wound up in mcaffrey's you were still incredibly drunk. You passed out on his floor
It's time to tell me what really happened
mcaffrey
Woke me up. Wait a minute. Is this for real?
He showed me the log wrench and
the letter and the box
And he said I came in with him last night
He said that I killed Evelyn
But what if he didn't though, did you? Then it was all over the radio
And he would protect me
And I don't know detective for the life of me. I can't remember a goddamn thing
I was angry with her
Really angry I could have done it
Wasn't me
I don't know
I don't know. There's not enough evidence
uh
So the scenario is
other guy
Tiernan Tiernan tells hey, I found all this stuff in your apartment and you killed this girl
And he doesn't remember anything from the night before
But what's
I don't that's too fishy for me
It's weird
He was
Wait here
Uh, is there any?
I don't know if you're I'm the other guy I think
Let me like talk to this guy one more time. I think we bust in there and find the goddamn evidence
Can I talk to you for a second?
Railroad someone else
I'm not saying anything
Uh-oh
I can't I can't talk to this guy
Phone phone phone phone. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. I but
Yes, there's a phone here
Operator give me dispatch
Cole felps batch 12 47
Thank you, I need the jacket on a grovener mcafee
Oh god, oh god. All right. Well, he did it. Thanks. Need a drink. I got the jitters again
Well way to make it real easy for me
James tiernan i'm charging you with the murder. Oh, well wrong guy
Oh my head. Oh, I have an instant headache
Oh
Load how do I load that scene?
I need to reload the cut scene
Oh, he didn't do it. I knew it. I just I went the wrong room and oh I
Whoa, my blood pressure just went up to like a hundred
How do how do I restart that?
That's not the guy I wanted to assume that you both have very good excuses for what happened to my station today
You had a perfectly good candidate for a capital case and some
But quit it quits. That's what was it gonna put me though, man
What's it gonna put me? What's it gonna put me?
Is it gonna be all right?
I you guys all know that's not what I want to do. I just like pressed
I was in the wrong place to press the wrong button
I you know, I solved the mystery
I just gave myself like fucking migraine
I just gotta electrocute it up here
Pretending for no, I swear to god. I just
I mixed up the names
13 if she was a day
Okay, so hold we just we we're just gonna do this again
We knew what I was gonna do. We just gotta skip ready to answer some questions
You think I have all the answers. I don't remember the things I did who run from the police usually have something to hide
to shade
Okay, so let's see where this takes us. It was the book, right?
You told us you barely knew eveline summers. She hung around sometimes
I had very little to do with her
Okay, so this is the book you'll have to do better than that grogner we know about you and eveline
Evelyn was a lush and a boring one at that
You can't link her to me
Oh
God, it gave myself a fucking migraine. We know that you thought enough of her to loan out your copy of the metaphysics
I what?
I did no such thing that bitch stole that book from my apartment
The impudent fucking moron and that made you angry angry
I was livid looking up at me with that string some more water. I have been drinking water
God damn it. Aha
Very good. That's one to you detective
Evelyn died sometime around midnight
Remind me. Where were you?
I was at home
writing
I'm working on a manuscript
Okay, that's uh, that was a lie
You're gonna need to do better if you don't want to swing for this
I was having a political meeting in my apartment cheese and crackers for the fifth column
Some of these people will corroborate your story. I won't give up names party same mistake. I'm not i'm not gonna pretend I
I'm not gonna it's either gonna be you or tiernan grobner
You want to go back and make stick?
I'm I did it wrong party has good lawyers
You want to go back? I just need to correct the mistake that I made. I'm not I don't care about the in between
I'm gonna go cheese and get a perfect score
No, that's not fair. All right telephone
Uh apparent apparently not
Telephone isn't here yet
No, I didn't cheese. I made I made a mistake and I pressed the wrong button
Fucking god
Yeah, the goddamn way nice guy. I felt lousy coloring
Why did you run tiernan? I was the last one to see ephelin that night. Okay, I knew you would think it was me
I really describe your relationship with the same mistakes
It's got to be authentic. I barely knew her bullshit bullshit bullshit bullshit bullshit
Sounds like half an answer to me tiernan. Were you sleeping with her?
That's none of your business
Yep. Yep. Yep. We got that one wrong. I remember aristotle's metaphysics the book that belonged to mcaffrey
mcaffrey saw her looking at her once and laughed in her face. I'm gonna do the same things I did before and stole it
She we're not cheesing a 100 i'm doing the same answers
We either hang this on you or mcaffrey. You better give us something
Mccaffrey's been in trouble with the law before I mean he always makes out with some kind of labor dispute, but
You know, i'm not so sure
Lame streamer. How dare you? How dare you?
You and eveline were drinking together last night and she had no other place to stay. I don't know what happened last night
I don't remember liquor purchase. I've got you. You're lying tiernan. You've been fighting with her you fought
And i'm not lying. She got up and left. That was it trailer moment. By the way, that was in the trailer
She left but she came back
She bought you a quart of whiskey to make it up to you. She told the liquor store owner
You're in deep trouble, buddy
She said she loved me
She wanted to care for me
She would never stop talking about mcaffrey
And mcaffrey was a writer and mcaffrey was a hero mcaffrey cared for the little guy. Did you kill her?
Might as well. I just keep flashing back to my brain kicked her out
She had nowhere to go
access to the murder weapon
Yeah, right. Yeah, right. Yeah, right
Have access to a lug wrench
We use a lot of them to clear jams in the pin setting machines
Corner's report says that evelyn was killed with a wrench
I think you did it and then planted the evidence at mcaffrey's apartment for us to find
We went to his apartment
Mcaffrey was up on the roof
Evelyn stole the book
Mcaffrey went crazy when he found out he said he said he would put her out of her misery
He can be very cruel
Evelyn was missing a ring from her right hand. That's strange
She always wore it
Big black circular disc with a yd in the middle
Present from the prop department at her old movie studio
We're going to talk to mcaffrey
You need to think about what you've told us tiernan. You're not in a clue
That's all I hear that's all I can hear right now. All right, let's go accuse mcaffrey first
We've got an accusation that you did it
Wait back here. I've not said my piece yet
Do I have to do this first?
Why is he telling me what to do?
I can't get up
Why is he commanding me to to stay?
We found the lug wrench that evelyn was battered with in your apartment and the note from her mother and your blood-stained clothing
We have you cold mcaffrey
You think if I could be bothered to murder evelyn summers, I would be stupid enough to leave the evidence in my apartment
I don't believe you grovener. The evidence says that you killed her
You can prove that I wanted to kill evelyn
Yes
Tiernan is prepared to testify that you threatened evelyn's life in his presence
self-preservation
That's understandable. Oh, yeah
Okay, i'll level with you tiernan killed evelyn
He came to me for help
I listened to him and he explained why he did it tiernan went to you for help you expect me to buy that
Well, that's how it went down. That's how it went down
He made a terrible mistake, but he would be throwing his life away if he went to the cops
I took his things and told him I would dispose of them sometimes I mean depends if there's a certain scenario
He'll give it up
Okay. Thank you
Telephone call for mr. Phelps. We've got some information
Operator give me r and i putting you through now
Phelps one two four seven
tattoo
I'm uh, how could I help detective?
I need the jacket on a grovener mcaffrey
Just a moment detective different voice was formerly under surveillance by the red squad convictions for pet to death. Thank you
Okay, uh, so
Put him down with my sap
Is that all we need?
What happened here?
Do I have to do the other guy first here?
I've not said my piece yet. The thing was I was a really nice guy. I felt lousy coloring him
Who what?
You were in the war. Yes, I was
Seeing the things that I saw it changes a man. I came back here determined to change things
All I wanted was
a pen
And an opportunity to speak out you told us before that you had only minor run-ins with the police
You didn't mention petty theft i've never been in trouble for violence. That's the salient point here, isn't it?
You're lying mcaffrey. You have a history of violence towards women
How do you turn a couple parking tickets in a petty theft misdemeanor?
into an assault charge
because
We've got it
I almost just clicked this
I would have been very upset
We know all about you and your dishonorable discharge beating some poor woman near to death in syracuse
You've never been in combat mcaffrey your whole life is a fraud. She was a goddamn peasant whore
Try to steal from my wallet. I could have fought for this country
I could have you beat her because she stole from you because she tried to outsmart you the ignorant audacity of the bitch
What is a man supposed to do?
Sit there and take it
How is a man supposed to call himself a man and eveline summers a poor drunken nobody stole your book
And she got what was coming to her
Oh well, i'll see you
In the slammer mcaffrey i'm charging you with the murder of eveline. That's what was supposed to happen
She was a sad lady who never hurt anyone except herself
I hope god finds a way to forgive you
Wrong guy congratulations boys you bagged the fine catch
Another red to boot go back do it again. He didn't do it. I want you to put this business about a repeat offender out of your mind
This mcaffrey creature shows no remorse and neither will the grand jury
The walk along might a better candidate for an unmarked plot at the prison graveyard. Thanks dad
all right, so
I am going to find out first. That's not bad only
Uh, it's too much damage
No injuries though. All right, so i'm going to uh get a drink
After we get a point to stop there
We have lost most of shaughnessy and dunny squad his gunny is dead first platoon is in worse shape
That medic is the crazy the bravest man alive that we rally with the first they try for the nambus
It's seared to the left to the right. He goes right through a pass with two nambus and inflate
Peanut butter
Smoothie that sounds pretty good
We keep getting those flashbacks
Murders coming up next well done lads you did well with the summer's case
We have a problem the examiner received the new letter today. Do you mind if I take a look ray?
Go right ahead
They've both been rinsed in gasoline like the previous letters so I can't lift the print
Uh, come find me know about this message where I hid myself
Okay looking
Another snippet from the cellar looking in wonder up to heaven while yet the music peeled along
I hid myself within a fountain in the public square
Right lay like the reflex of the moon seen in a wave under green leaves
Waste of paper man. You could have added a little bit more a couple more paragraphs
All right. Uh, let me just
Percy the poetic works of percy
be she shelly
Suffer woes which hope thinks infinite to forgive wrongs darker than death one night
To defy power which seems omnipotent
To love and bear to hope till hope creates
from now
Until my final watch
Because it's time to start the night's watch. I don't remember it
I don't know the I don't know how it goes if the note is from the dalian maniac
He definitely also i'll be back now and I agree i'll see you in a minute. I'm gonna make
If this is the dalian killer and he is responsible for the tarot's and murder not to mention the mallard hang on a moment skipper
Let me finish rusty
We have five birds in hand and not yet the bush
The department will not survive a scandal if we have to let them all go without catching a feint first
Your careers would be over for a start chet
Looking in wonder. Oh fucking I knew this technical support would be true
I hid myself within a fountain in the public square. You like that stuff
What is it supposed to mean?
Forget what it's supposed to what does he want? Where are you going with this call? He's obviously taunting us
He believes he's far more intelligent than we okay, it's some kind of story, right a guy that god hates chains him up
It's an allegory rusty a story with two meanings
Which one of the guys in the room is the guy plant and all that's doing this?
Within a fountain and it's gonna be somebody in the world
Somebody tell me what the fuck is going on the fountain in pershing square
Come on. We have a clue captain
Me
Be careful felps. It's just me his game. You're playing now. It's my game. It's gonna be him
right
All right
I'll see you guys in
t-minus
Two minutes i'm gonna make a smoothie beer back
What are we waiting for?
Hey col let's get moving. What are we waiting for? Hey col let's get moving
What are we waiting for what was going?
Uh, by the way, I made this a little too thick it's kind of like it's like a drinking paint
What are you waiting for?
What what is what is going on?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey col get moving
What am I wait, what do you mean? What are we
Was he just talking the whole time that's fine
Uh, what the hell are we doing i'm getting it's getting harder to
Pay attention
City park, okay. It's the current destination. I was I was so all in the ball last night
Now i'm like thinking about fast food and like bananas and paint
Like i'm lost
This seriously has the same consistency as paint though. This is like drinking paint. Oh jerma
How do you know what would paint taste like because i've drank it a lot
All those cases rusty what have I been telling you all along we've got to get this guy I know
Enough women have died. Yeah, and it's our ass is on the line too felps
You are what the captain said. Okay department is not going to take responsibility for all those bad convictions
Success is a double-edged sword. Let's just get this sick pervert. It's beautiful by the way
By the way, by the way, by the way, you know what? I love I love uh, you know, by the way
I love how I love how x I love how I love hey by the way
It's like how 60 of every sentence I say when I stream starts with I love how by the way
Watch where you're driving you what happened rather you than me felps
Where's the crime scene?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, that's right. That's right. That's right in the fountain. We shall shine
When it's time to dine
my social security number
Is there for you to find?
Elizabeth short. Oh shit, that's mine
Well, what by the way, I love how that would be my like number if it was potential
That was potential
Use your words and make it count. You're all overgrown with trailing odorous plants which curtain out the day
Where next?
Elizabeth short social security card. Jesus christ
German 985 is short. Here's his social security card. I already told the joke that you guys are writing
So, please see if I do it you can't
Hidden vehicle
This is a huge map go get the hidden car
We're in the middle of a mission
Uh, hold on a minute. Let me
square
decipher the second excerpt
What was the can I look at the excerpt again?
Please right
There's a cave all overgrown with trailing odorous plants
Which curtain out the day with leaves and flowers?
And paved with veined emerald in a fountain leaps in the midst with an awakening sound from its curved roof the mountain's frozen
Tears like snow or silver or long diamond spires hang downward raining. Well, I don't know what this is
How the fuck am I supposed to find this
Is it another fountain?
We have to go find another fountain
the cave
There's a treasure in the caves
The station could be a cave
Cave bingo
Why are we running there?
I should take a car
I'm, so proud of myself
I forgot the car out of the car police officer my back in there. Wait, hold on. I gotta wait for harold
Come on harold
Yeah, really him the fuck who killed the dalian leave this
He's leading us
It's his game rusty
You may want someone to catch him, but he's extremely dangerous
It's down if you leave it's me down to the fucking ground clip this fucking would get citation
What a day to be a cop
Have you guys seen felt about his hat on
I haven't
They're gonna be fucking horns under there. Come on
Whoa, this is what you get for not fucking getting out of the way
Could we try not killing the people that pay our salaries?
All right, you well you're very good at this so i'll let you live all right, but looking for the
Thank god, okay
All right. Everybody be quiet for this part. I want total concentration. No text
Can I help you sir?
Detective scale the chandelier. This is very important, sir
How do we get to the top of the chandelier you what have a little faith pal?
We're in a real herd head up to the top floor. There's an access panel and a ladder in the maintenance room
My concentration, I don't know if somehow it's breaking here. I thought I asked for
Complete silence and no talk no text nothing in the chat
Can you guys do it?
I want I wonder if they'll if they could be no messages
Let's do an experiment here. Can there be no messages in this chat for like one straight minute?
Twitch plays don't talk
There's no way
This is absolutely no way
It's impossible
coffee room
fire department
No, see emote only mode is doesn't help because emote only mode is the equipment. It's just screaming
electrical
Private every time I see an emote. I imagine that emote yelling its name like pokemon
police department records
Got it. Oh, hey, let's go. Let's go
I'm going out there rusty
Better you than me
Be careful be a trap. Oh, come on really
I thought I could just keep swinging back and forth
You found my clue good for you
Now it's up to you
Upon my mouth. I do chew
What am I or in a stew? What is this?
It's just a watch
From the temple's high of man's ear and eye of man's ear and eye roofed over sculptures and posey
From the mermaids of the duneshield springs where science bedouins is dead down wings
Oh
Mario hit the chain mario
Swing the chandelier alive
Only got a few more teeth on this chandelier
Well, that's
Two hundred thousand dollars in city damages. That's not going to be on the bill at the end of the level, right?
Let's get out of here
another dahlia clue
No, a yellow gold wristwatch
A molar dame. Yes, and a scrap of the poem
Another location if I can work it out
All right, one two three four five six
from the temple's high of man's ear and eye
roofed over sculpture and posey
From the mermaids of unsealed springs where science bedouins is dead down wings
Man's ear and eye temple high
That's a station could be an ear an ear canal
No, I was just there
the rko theater
That's it. Huh from the temple's high of man's ear and eye
Roofed over sculpture and posey
Looking for a temple
Most miraculous interior. No, we don't give a shit about interior
We're as short as railroad
Top up jti radio reminds you an ounce of prevention saves many an emergency
Jesus felt
Just looking for the word to one word
This guy needs to be taken out of circulation
He takes pleasure in stringing us along for laughing demonstrating how much smarter he is
Why am I not interacting if we survive this it's going to be a miracle i'm trying to decipher like clues
You can enjoy it while it lasts didn't I snap counting some neck like six months ago
Watch it. Will you maybe I drive better if you shut the hell up
Oh
Jesus felps you're terrorizing these poor slobs. You okay?
His name is felps. It's always i've read about him. Yeah, I I just read his license plate as it drove into my face
It's now permanently imprinted into my forehead
Climb the library tower
I'm not hauling myself up there. Go get him tiger. It's slowing me down anyway old timer
I don't even have
No, oh another pigeon
Another pigeon npc
It's gonna be the lady from home alone, too
Horns there they are demon horns a plus commentary. Well, what do you want me to say?
Well climb it up the climb it up here. Okay. Oh what we got here
Looks like another scaffolding another ladder. Let's make climb up this ladder. All right, here we go climb it up the ladder
What's next a jump? Let me just jump this. Okay. I jumped it and let's jump this one two jumps
Stop talking
You see smart ass
All right, um, this is what I get for reading sometimes a step backwards is a step in the right direction
That's what i'm trying to do
Why are you not interactive? All right. All right, that's it
That's it
All right. That's it. Ooh, that was what i'm alive. Okay, so let's go up there. Thank you very much
Yeah, that would hurt. He like rolled on his neck
Have to go all the way to the top
It's a locket
And a letter. Here's the next one. I can't wait for another clue
Round which death laughed sepulchred emblems of dead destruction ruin within ruin
So this is a treasure hunt
Now we're looking for skeletons
We're looking for the word skeleton human that that's what we're looking for our lady of guadalupe ripped from antonia's necklace
Read it out loud in a funny voice
No, no, I understand that this is a boring mission guys, okay
I got it. I get it, but it has to be done
What is it this time the religious medal from the maldenado case the dahlia?
molar maldenado
When this gets out we still have to find the guy rusty another poem
He must have some idea, right?
Come on helps. We're on a roll here. Don't let me down
If only we were just having the fast food conversation now fourth excerpt
Let me read it again and pull out the one word that I need to remember fourth excerpt
round laugh
dead
ruin wreck
population
mortal monster
skeleton statue home
shape gray
Jam hard
Okay, I don't see any of those words
hard jam skeleton
monster
monstrous the brady bunch building
monster hard
All right, he was here
I wasn't here though
spot city site
father settlement no
designed
open cost grand tile marble
room outdoor
Railway. Nope
Where is it?
Uh
What's that?
street crime
down here
Checking the same couple of bills. I'm trying to
None of the words were there
Thank you for listening to kti radio serving california and the west coast come on music
Harold get in here. Come on
Wait, hold on. Wait, is there I did it wrong? Did I just get spoiled? Did somebody just spoil me?
Two years ago you were missing the new
Harold it just got spoiled
Harold i'm i'm sorry, but we've been spoiled. This is kti a member of the american century broadcasting system
Who is harold?
How does this happen in your kitchen?
So then where is it then?
If I did just get spoiled, I don't see it anywhere. That's what I just put
Oh, there's other I didn't even know these
Existed I thought these were vehicles, but apparently they're places
Skeleton. All right. Yeah. Yeah, okay
You're gonna catch hell for this
Banging up innocent men
The newspapers will well i've found that I just I guess I didn't know about our mistakes
So it would be okay to find that landmark yet
I hope you're right. I would have found it be famous
I would have it's me. I'm the killer
So, you know how like some references and some jokes and memes just live forever
Do you think that I made this I did it?
You think it's ever gonna go away ever?
I don't think it will I think it's here forever
I won't let it
No, I wonder who actually is the first person to do it
I wonder if they're here right now, you know, that'd be interesting
If they were here
What are the streamer jokes gonna end what do you mean screamer jokes?
Walmart a landmark
Watch out for me
Come on streamer insert comment or current situation
Just go easy felps
Bad streamer or like streamer does streamer local streamer that kind of stuff streamer reads information
No, I know what you mean. No
I can't walk up this
Why did I just freeze?
Can I walk in this?
I'm not gonna get a game over screen if I walk in here. Am I?
Um, so what's the deal? Uh, I gotta go over where the elephants are
It's tar
Yeah, well that never stopped anybody from jumping in the water in gta
What do you think is tar a weird substance?
What the fuck? Holy shit. I thought that was actually an animal
What am I supposed to be looking at here? I mean, this is definitely a point a location here
Well, there's the
There's the you found it. All right. Well, why did you bring me all the way back here?
These are my best shoes felps. I'll leave you to it
I'm sure i'll do everything. That's fine. Just let me take care of literally every single thing
very funny
Reach the island
whoa
Move quickly between safe platforms
I am moving quick. I can't go that way that quickly. He's dead. He died that fast
How did anybody do why are these boards here who did maintenance here this is all fucked up
Whoa connect the dots
I'd be doing better if you were the one trying to get across this thing straight or right right
Easy to the island steady bag a right
That's at the forefront of my thinking
This is long
right
Right
So what was what's on here that I need?
cigarettes
shoes
One of theresa tarreltson's shoes
Okay, besides this there's eight
From the other opening as many thousands fears
Okay, where to now?
All right sphere crystal sphere crystal music and light
What is it?
What open toed white shoe and another stanza from apollo?
Oh, I really thought that hobo bun. Why couldn't I just get in one of these fashion from the insane aren't the most credible evidence
for us
This thing over it's all part of his power over making us run around all over the city for the
So if we keep this up we can find the guy
How many are there
fifth excerpt
This is the fifth time i've had to do this
Okay from wood opening the wood russian loud and whirlwind harvey sphere
crystal solid lots of sphere
sphere
Sphere. Oh, I didn't even need that first attempt. That's right here. Got it done. I'm really glad it's right here
I hope this is it. So this guy looks out for women in bars. You've had too much to drink
Who are emotionally disturbed need a shoulder to cry on he plies them with booze
Probably offers them a lift home then beats their brains out and strangles
Could be any schmoll hanging out
Breathe just a wooden fence dammit. That's a wooden fence
You're telling me I can't drive through
No, not anyone he displays the bodies leaves us messages for all the violence. It's very controlled behavior
Really good wooden fence
Now what do we have to traverse?
No, don't you fucking dare?
I'm playing resident evil 4 again
On it goes what do you think will reach the end of this thing?
I refuse i'm gonna try to break the game
Reach the center of the maze
Whoa?
Okay
I'm gonna try to reach the center of the maze
You ever been in here gal? I got to do that again. No, I have no intention of going in
I heard that thing's tricky
I'm gonna wait here and have a quiet smoke
think about hidden meetings
It's been a while since i've been able to
To do that
Dolores
Good to see you again
Where is the center of the maze?
Ha ha ha ha ha
Once belonging to selene axeford henry
All right. Here's the big the big climax right here
Well, you found me but not so fast. I admit
Thrones author is another one
No, it couldn't be
Cutscene thank god
See
That was easy. I found selene henry's ring
How far does this thing go?
I was in there for a long time
It took me a long time to get out
All right. What's a good clue again?
Thrones author's judgment seats prisons
Which wretched men were born to see our sword chains
Reason wrong glows ignorance where those monsters
Are buried ghosts of okay?
obelisk
Democratic no
nine beds
No throne
Was it was a throne there?
Egypt no
I'm ready. What's your
sky court cage
123456789 at level 34 fuck
Thrones. Yep. I got it
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it right there?
throne
Oh, I got it. All right. I'm ready to go
Let's do the let's do the the padded one hour long
drive around town and look at
landmark mission
Leading us this trail of evidence
Why vanity?
He wants to see if there's anyone out there smart enough to catch him
He leaves us evidence, but every location is a trap. Why testing us?
Physically and mentally to see whether we are worthy of him the titan guy
Very good. You're thinking about reading some jelly all that egghead stuff
I'm sticking to the funny papers
Jesus philps
What's wrong with you?
uh
Forget drones
Is this the end can this please be the end?
I don't I don't really don't want to do this anymore
it was fun running guys around and jumping on them and shooting and
Finding out if somebody's lying or not. I don't like the treasure hunt read the fucking home mission
Calm down skip the driving
By marking it and making him drive
There's the throne up there there's the throne
No, I don't want to run. Oh, all right. Look at how about like high school story?
So that's what the new title of this is going to be so there's one time in high school
Now I was a pretty uh rough kid. I was a pretty uh wild kid
That's it
Can I jump to that?
What am I doing? I don't know i'm bored
Thanks
Thanks for the help
I can't just
No
No, so from up here
So I need to go down. I just have to go over to where harold is
Oh that worked
Okay
Thanks a lot harold
I appreciate it
That's not his name
It is not
Jesus now look what you did. What am I doing? I'll get you off of there. What's that? Whoa my
Why did this turn into a mario party minigame?
I'm trying to say what he's doing. You've got to make it to the next platform get that thing as close as you can then jump
Finish
What am I doing now scaffolding I mean I have to get over here, right
So I have to jump up to here climb this
Apparently not
Somebody's yelling at me this thing's a ladder
The ladder where's there a ladder do I have to go down? I thought I had to go up
Okay
fighter ring helen summers
All right
E
There it is
No a seventh excerpt placey. Why did this game become so fucking boring? What the hell man?
This game was very interesting and fun
I really don't want to do this again. So the seventh time
It has to do with reading it has to do with
seven times
There it is. Give me the cut scene
I thought the whole thing was gonna come crashing down
It almost did I thought so too. Oh, he murdered Evelyn summers rusty. The last trophy was her ring
What did it say on the piece of the poem? Yes
I would love to say it you sure call but it'll antagonize chat
Seventh excerpt here we go
um two three four five six seven eight nine ten no two three four five
remit anguish that
Delighted stare close thy one lips
Let that thorn wounded brow stream not blood it mingles with thy tears fix fix fix those tortured orbs and
peace and deaths of the sick rose
Shake not that crucifix
So those pale figures play thy now go horrible thy name. I will not speak of that become a curse
I know what it is
You just you said you said the word crucifix. That's all I needed. All right, where is it?
Where is it an angel? Wait, maybe i'm wrong angel
Cry cry. There it is. That's that's the thorn
There it is. That's church. I just needed to find the church
It might seem like crucifix ain't the archaeo theater god's sake belps i'm not trying to justify this
Hear me out
This guy has been successfully slaughtering
Maybe longer the research is weak and then plants evidence so that we always have someone to go at if he hadn't sent the
letters in the poem
Okay, where is he
Where is the bad guy?
Boom doors break open. All right there you found me
He'll never take me alive
He's gonna be praying at the altar
Watch this praying at the altar. He was a religious nut the whole time. Look out
We're from the la pd sir i'm gonna tell you only once to lower your weapon
The la pd you say
Is it really possible you could have found me after all this done the gun shit bird
Last warning this foolish ignoramus could never have found me
It was you wasn't it?
Remember me detective the temp bartender. Yes, you found it. Oh, it was the bartender
What walk in here like lamps
What a reveal
I can't believe it. It was the temporary bartender not like the captain or me or
Where did he go? Where did he go on the tunnel?
He can't let the son of a bitch get away
The house rusty there must be another entrance into the house. He did say it was me though
Into the catacombs
I'm gonna turn the dial. It's a secret
Any secrets?
secrets secret
Any secrets over here secret?
Okay, never mind
uh
Okay
La pd give yourself up
Like i don't know if he's in apparently apparently you are in here somewhere
Come on in even the bedroom. Where the hell is this guy?
Okay, is he just hiding in here?
I mean, there's a door. I couldn't open this door. Could I open this? All right, I can open this one
Wait, jesus
You realize this must have been the place rusty
This is where he did it all
It's fucked up
It's the basis for all his riddles
Prometheus defied the cruel gods this guy's the basest from that. That's what I thought he said. It was the basis
Wow, that is kind of like a basest pose, isn't it?
I'm really gonna need to try this guy or
This is evidence, right?
kind of need to
Look at it
Had a cool experience baby, at least some working knowledge of biology
He's cruel and he's methodical
Anything else
I don't think so
Well, we're going down there kill garrick mason
I'll go so not even back up and keep an eye out above ground and see capture
Kill oh there he is
You're an interesting man
Reinforcements are on the
Why is he holding the gun like that?
Do I get a sense you're looking for personal redemption
He got the hat
All right, just fuck this man
Go put him in the bathtub
Where's the press gap?
I think felps and I should get a medal for this. So this has got to be the case of the year, right?
The case of the century when you think about it you finished
Yes skipper good
Because there won't be any press briefings all accommodations. It was my son
What are you talking about?
We got the werewolf the guy who killed the dahlia killed all the other broads. You've got no one
Mason was a ghost and you at least tell us why captain
Mason is the half brother of one of the most highly elected officials in this country. Oh this is true
Beyond the moon for mere mortals like us rusty
We no more mention of them the senator knows you both half brother
There'll be no mileage and never bringing this up again what's going to happen to the suspects in the cases captain
I won't be a part of that
A bit of missing evidence at the grand jury
Procedural error here a mistake there
They'd all be quietly let go
The da knows how we have to play it. That's it
I'm afraid it is
And I have some news for you folks
No more rooting around in the entrails of cadavers and corpses for you
The head of vice has asked the chief
Reluctant to see you go to the glory boys about go home to that lovely wife
the real
Villain was politics
Apparently the simple art of murder case report 15 out of 15
Who is injured remains open the truth lost to all but a handful of men prepare for reassignment
Reval kid you'll go purple
I'm scared sarge everybody scared kid
Anyone who says he isn't is a damn liar
How many times have you been in combat sarge?
I was with raider battalion on pelaloo my first time was it bad
It's always bad. Will this be bad?
As bad as it gets kid. It's bad. It's always bad
So some of the guys they aren't very friendly sarge
They've lost a lot of their friends in the last couple of days kid
I think if they don't get to know you that they won't have to grieve for you if you get killed
They're wrong. It doesn't work that way. Don't worry. No marine in this company will let you down
Okay
so
What's next?
The black season hollywood police station
Phelps welcome to vice
This is your new partner. Roy earl
Take a seat
Roy request was made to transfer you to add vice
We need a man with your kind of starch on this desk son
We have two dead negros found in an apartment this morning on yucca street
Number sixty three fifty eight. Why is everybody?
Got better things to be doing than wasting our time on two dead junkies. Did I ask your opinion detective?
Two men dead on u.s. Army issue morphine
That makes it an add vice case
Beat it
Yes, sir
Oh, is this my partner? I remember this guy this guy sucks
uh
Lieutenant have some history
You could say that I thought he stepped out of the way and was like that other guy behind him
So you're working with the big boys now col I guess so, right? I thought homicide was the primo assignment
That may be the case
I asked for you personally phelps. I had to pull a few strings to get you over to add vice. How does it feel?
The lieutenant seems to think i'm doing okay
Okay
Don't get humble on me phelps
You're doing great. You're the department pent up boy
War hero and crime fighter. What a combination
I can assure you i'm no war hero detective. Let's rouse some hop heads
investigate the crime scene
When is polar bear golfing car roy? Is it department issue?
Uh never no, this is my sled
You can't be seen slumming it in a nash if you're in vice court
Meanwhile, we got needle freaks kissing do I have another?
outfits
Wreck his car
Look where you're going not gonna say anything about his car police emergency out of the car
That's the cop from the newspapers
You can't do this oh i'm so starstruck
I discovered a landmark
Whoa, whoa easy. Whoa
Phelps is the swimming guy, right?
Uh, yes
Phelps is the swimming guy
What's going on here? We dropped a couple frames
Looks like it detective phelps. I got the call for assistance. Who are the suspects bank robbers?
Same gang that took the citizens national trust and savings last month
He seems pretty happy about it
How long you think you can hold out
Let's move up
Oh, fuck. He's getting it
He's getting a car got him. That's it
That's all of them
Good thing my partner can shoot
That's it
20 out of 40 street crimes complete
nice
I earned a achievement
Johnny on the spot. We still good on frames
Yeah, a little hiccup it's bound to happen
dropping
400 frames in three and a half hours is uh, i'll take it
christ
Crime scene, what are you doing? What did I hit?
I hit a divot in the ground
What are you doing? Please pick the fry shithole for a first date
Okay, here we go. Excuse me officer. Yes
I want to see
uh
No
Carry on. I just want a quick look is all up the stairs. I want to see around the corner last door in the left
The things I wanted to be when I could work. I got friends who work at the examiner
About 50 bucks for an exclusive
Where's the where's the actual crime?
scene
up here
You're coming from a crime scene
Your show now
You said up the stair. I'm just looking around. I'm just looking around
Jesus
What have we got
two stiffs overdosed
Been dead a couple of days government issue morphine. We use the same syrettes in okinawa
Fucking negro junkies can't take supply this pure. You know these guys
I know of them
The younger one's a two-bit horn player by the name of cornell tyree. The other one works in distribution
Started using a little too much of his own product and jack d took exception
He wasn't born that ugly his name's lamont
Tyrone lamont, I don't like this guy's tie. You know who's supplying the drugs
That's easy whoever knocked off the wharves in san pedro
Jack dragnet mickey cohen dopes been all upside down ever since jimmy utley started the long walk at quentin
This guy sucks and he's wearing like
like tampon tie
We are supposed to uphold the law the hell is this tie? Yeah, and we do
But we can't change people
The truth is everyone wants a license to get a little dirty now and then
Our job is to keep it manageable. That's how you see it
Contact lens cases
Can we get on with this today preferably
So we got a wallet
Let's actually do a look at this stuff
Knock you off for combat trauma two of them will stop your heart
Is
Say only the good die young. I hope it was true in your case
Interesting
Do you have anything else?
another wallet
Another day another dollar must have been messy eaters. It's all over the floor
Tyrone lamont, not even 23 years old. You always check the wallets first
A small chance in life is probably better than no chance
So wallet on ground wallet on guy find anything interesting sheet music
I wonder what's the correlation between the love of the needle and love of the music
It's some kind of fruit a bell. It's a slot machine
strange doodle
People are yelling at me who is jj. Why do these two care about his taste in music?
He listens to 275 fm anything else let's find anything interesting looks like it was always going to end this way
Never the same are they now?
Okay, did I pick up this?
He's on the oh it's popcorn black caesar from the joint across the street
It's like something was taped to the bottom of the cup that's really weird looking popcorn it's almost like a
keyed in
Took his jolt and drifted off and I suppose his friend wasn't in any condition to notice that he had stopped breathing
what else
superglue
Street life have no idea morphine
Another special order from the caesar
This one last piece here
No cooking or preparation must have been the easiest fix these two ever had
kitchen bread
Heavy for an empty cup something in this one
Well, they've been getting their fix right over the counter and broad there it is
Food hut eggs the emperor across the street appears to shift a lot of popcorn eggs on the ground shake them down
So that's it
You catch all the good ones phelps
Hey, thanks
Is there nothing else to look at yeah, I think so wasn't it night four minutes ago
Let's go to the food hut
Right. Let's wrap this up before I actually have to work over time instead of just claiming for it
Time moves really fast true inspiration to us all right
Right here. Okay
help you
Detectives phelps and earl la pd we're inquiring into the death pan over the popcorn numbskull before we kick the door in
Uh
You know, I I was actually just
Get that son of a bitch
Come here
Give us the popcorn
I was waiting for it. I knew it was gonna happen, too
I was going too fast. The game was like hey you're doing you're going too fast. Can you just slow down?
Haven't I done this bit like 10 times already?
Yep
Sure have
I lose
Oh i'm pressing circle i'd step different rockstar game this is going to end in tears
What he's on the ground?
What's your name?
More he's all right half an answer is no answer to me asshole
Fleetwood morgan
Keep an eye on him. Roy while I take a look around
Keep very still fleetwood
Don't give me an excuse to shoot you
It's like a creepy smile
Oh wallet I doubt it. He's stamped on the reverse by the issuer
Who's the trumpet?
Here's the plunger
In here
Yeah, it's 6 29. These numbers slips might affect your tone fleetwood. That's a silencer
Here
It's a trumpet silencer
Morphing might not be filling but i'm sure it's satisfying there it is
What else you put in in the uh popcorn here?
Eggs see I told you we needed to look at eggs optimistic cool. Oh
Doesn't tell me anything. Ooh
Somebody's gonna eat all this
Should I turn the stove off?
reverse side of ticket
Okay
Maybe morgan can give us something what I do without you guys jones character about time. We heard what fleetwood here asked to say call
All right, let's see
advice
Get the kid's story. He's a small fry but he could give we're inquiring about the deaths of two men in an apartment
Across the street fleetwood. We want answers
Of course
I'll do my best. Mr. Chad is the second mind
Yeah, I just need to look over here and see like the word and I go
Oh that like I need to find that word that I just saw
You sold the drugs to cornell tyree and tyrone lamont. Oh, I sell
I sell fried steaks in in in black eyed peas
Well, i'm sorry
But you have morphine. We know that you supplied inside of your boxes by no drugs
All I do is my tan hair flipping burgers. Can you prove any different?
I can
I can wait into that. Okay, if that was in the apartment here it is
Flipping burgers and strapping jolts of morphine to the bottom of popcorn cups fleetwood
Now I want the truth
Who supplies the drugs cat by the name of armstrong edwards?
All right brings the stuff around about once a day
I know armstrong. He's a two-bounce strictly small time. Who's he working for fleetwood?
germaine jones
Okay, we got our distributor
We have you for the hop and resisting arrest
Tell us about the numbers if you want our help look the numbers are the white man's tax on poor folk
All right. Now now what else you want to know?
Looking at the ground
We have an address on the slips
We're gonna go down there now and rat you out fleetwood
Tell whoever it is that you rolled over and gave them up. No, no, no, no, no, no
No, look i've been cooperative. Okay now you gotta help me some
Fleetwood i'm gonna speak personally to the judge on your behalf a name fleetwood. He's he's a real slick dude
Wears a hat and swings the cane goes by the name of murder. All right, I ain't got a last name
See you at the station fleetwood
Wait, you're gonna help me, right? Of course kid you helped us out. We always like to repay a favor
Can you see that fleetwood gets a nice cell wallace one with a window and a nice fresh pillow?
Oh
I see phone on map. I have to talk phone
operator message for kgpl
Putting you through now
felps batch 12 47
I need an address on a germaine jones musical booking agency
Just a moment. Thank you
Germaine jones the office is listed as 5528 santa monica boulevard. This is my favorite act voice actress than the whole thing
She sounds so real
That's just i'm just kind of reading that's it who cares
Numbers operation
That's where we're going gambling den and lottery operation work address of merlin auti
Okay, auto
Auto p. Uh, yeah, that's funny. He's right behind me. You can't pull that same bullshit twice
That doesn't work twice
felps
See auto
You will
soon
Show us now. I can't i'm driving this car. Give me a second
All right here and you want to see auto
It's too dark in here. Hold on
Turn it up and it's still too dark
It's you're not gonna be able to see him that well
No, you're not gonna be able to see him. I'll grab him
Hold on
Look, he was just trying to sleep
Now I have to bring him in front of the camera
Cole we got things to do
He's you know, he smells the peanut butter and banana
Dogs go crazy for that shit
Can you hear him sniffing into the microphone?
Hey, what are you doing? Yes
Yes, your breath stinks
All right back to it back to what you're doing
You need a dog
Keep the face cam there at that size while playing. I did that joke already
That was a a joke from
eons ago
All right. Do I have my speaking of camera?
Okay, just making sure I have it off
All right
That's the only reason why I watch
Well, i'm glad you're here watching
Detectives phelps and durel la pd
The name's meryl anody
I run a strictly legitimate bookmakers detective
So that's not an illegal wire service that your colleagues are running and the number slips that i've been picking up all morning
With this address on them have nothing to do with you. I'll pay my kick to the waps and they pay they cut to the la pd
You can't go shaking me down. You're a loudmouth motherfucker. Aren't you?
Anyone ever tell you the criminals are supposed to keep their mouths shut
Stay where you are while we look around
Okay
trying to
What are you doing over there?
Now you know he's like trying to have fun
finishing the end of my smoothie
all right
golf clubs
baseball
incidental
lamp record player
we got a
Boost paper we got telephones
Why so many going took over the wire service from seagull, right?
Slop machine he's held this like the button and pressed to hold a symbol
Oh, hold on. Where is that thing?
cherry bell
win
So we need cherry bell we get cherry in the first slot
Oh, that was one
Cherry cherry hold the cherry, please
Cherry bell
You can't do this on slot machines. You can't hold a symbol forever
And here's all the morphine
This quantity we're looking at a high level trafficking charge. There's a lot in here
And we got tickets
Thanks for the paper trail merlin free morphine. That's what you win. Oh, that's quite a win for a dime merlin
You better start talking. Get after him felts
Chase give it up. Adi
Go after him felps
Okay
Who did that?
What this is a secure area. You all need to leave
How do I stop him
All right, all right relax motherfucker. You got me
He ran into somebody too bad. You couldn't pull off your vanishing act
Make your joke smart guy, but don't damage that. Oh my god. There's a valuable antique
You don't say
Maybe you ought to have a look at this cold
Okay, let's look at look at the what is this a this is a
What is it? What is it? What does it say? What is this?
Duck stir. Oh, he has jose rames in his pocket
Ramos must have forgotten his lucky dollars in no sense
I think that's it. Would you like to calculate the odds on you going to prison for a very long time merlin?
I'm not going nowhere. I've paid my contributions and i'm not getting hustled by you
We're only interested in morphine army surplus morphine. What do you have to say about that? I heard about that
Big robbery on the ship
Ain't my line of work. I prefer something with a sporting outcome
Lie
Okay, merlin behave like a moron the two dead guys. I'm telling the da that you sold them the hop
Are you hearing this?
And clear motherfucker I have chips and i'm not throwing my cards in this easy
Rames seems to owe you a lot of money. We all owe somebody
That's it
Okay, so it has nothing to do with the proceeds of the morphine shipment
It's a gambling debt
The heaps took over the wise service and screwed me now. I just do what i'm told run numbers and ship dope
Jose's no different
He just thinks he's a big man that can run up tabs
You're not the guy we want merlin we're taking you in maybe some time. He wasn't telling the truth before something worthwhile
Fuck you
And fuck you
You'll never put a charge on me
Take this bum in I was just gonna make the joke
Don't be gentle with him. I can't got that
I was just gonna make that joke about how like oh and then it cuts to him in a squad car
I didn't make it because I made it already
I almost wish I said it now
That's unfortunate. I was gonna say it
Mickey cohen runs the dope rack always sonny theme plays
All right, Mickey does what he's told
Benny siegel will take a cover his operation going. I thought jack dragnet was
Dragging is an old-time greaser. He keeps his head down and pays his dues
Word is he's gonna clip bugsy
Who's word?
Does it matter one low life killing another low life makes our job easier?
I'm just gonna go here
I already arrested the guy you can't do anything on maybe
Sounds like me singing
Don't take notes while you drive. That's true. You shouldn't do anything like that
Thank god, we're not in my car
Well, that's because I destroyed your car in front of you and I've burnt it so
I don't know what you mean by that exactly
god damn maniac
Is there a penalty for running people over there's a penalty for doing any damage at all
Bumping into cars hitting anybody you get a monetary penalty
every single fender bender
I thought it was this store. I thought it was that store and we were gonna get a cut scene quite enough. I thought
wrong
You use money. I know I do not believe so at least not at this point not that I can tell
Look at this place
I'm guessing not much talent comes out of this talent agency
Right
Not much, but wait, we're looking for two three eight jones two thirty eight
two four one two three nine two
three eight
Hey
Hey, who let you in?
I did
Your door was unlocked
Jermaine jones don't bother getting up your flunky fleetwood morgan just snitched you out. I wasn't planning to
Now you think you could tell me who the hell you are
LAPD we're croc. We'd like to take a look around
The hell you will motherfucker you carrying a warrant
No, do we need one?
Search the place col
What do you think you're gonna find policeman?
Scott phantom fine radio mfm shortwave am and fm my father has a scott
Do I have like any megahertz here radio station note
275 fm
Let's get the morphine out of here, too
So we got fm
Now we have to tune it. How's volume?
Get it on max
bingo
We got cauliflower. We got no wonder this thing is pencil erasers
Brennan wilt get over here
Take these assholes apart. You heard the boss
More fighting
Is this the best you got these mugs are dope to the eyeballs
Clean them up quick boys. I ain't got time for this
Come on. Come on beat these sons of bitches down
Sit tight asshole
Pretend you're at the parlor getting your nails done
Cole you better search you that stuff in the radio before you brace our friend here
Come on
Money they must be at least 30 in a year. How many starving musicians pay with perfect clean 50s?
Too much for felony possession i'm thinking intent to supply
We also have another
Super glues morphine how those two bum standing guard take their wages
392 your friend fleetwood was also a betting man germaine
What was that mezz removals it must have taken special care delivering this for you
Okay, well would you look at that
Now let's talk
Lamont and tyree are dead at a stretch the da could have you on felony murder for supplying stolen government tyrone and cornella dead
They're on a slab downtown with the amy examining their last meal
popcorn washed down with morphine
You offering me a deal
I have a pet judge who hates blacks
I'll give you 50 years for your two buddies. I know the 30 for stealing from uncle sam. You'll be out by the time you're
And the changes you'll see
I get the message
How much is this gonna cost me?
Okay
Who supplies the morphine? Where is the morphine? I don't know nothing about that
It's in his it's in your it's in your jukebox over there, man
So we make you for all of it. You're the fall guy from mickey cohen
You're the fall guy case. Do you haven't noticed i'm a colored man
Do you see any two boys running around here?
I collect my cut any of the think controls the action
Lenny who
Lenny fenkelstein mickey's dipshit brother-in-law
What is the link between the morphine and the numbers slips? There is no link
You're wasting your time here
His face
His face went like immediately from confident. Oh, he just got sad
You either rat out the next link in the chain or you spend the rest of your life in jail
Are you gonna put that in writing asshole?
What's the score with ram as removals? I brought a radio from there
That's all
These faces
I kind of wanted his watch for a little while
Oh, he's back to being well, no, no, no, he's he was sad there for a second
This is okay. You know those artificial intelligence
robot demonstrations
Where the it's like that mannequin face will go from sad to happy to scared to crying
It's just one of those tech demos
So when we visit ram as removals and tell them that we want a special
Bookcase or wardrobe to hide our dope in
You're going to be copacetic and when we tell them their good friend germaine sent us and said they could do a nice
Deal for the la pd. I could use an act like you too
There's fuck saban and costello on the slide
Hollywood could use another couple of deeply unfunny white bread humps like you very good germaine
You have character
Now cough it up ramez is a good friend of lini the think
You're getting the picture
Take them all in there. We have a deal, right? We're after the morphine. I'll speak to the da on your behalf
You have my word
Okay phone
Phelps batch 12 47
Detective I need an address for ramez removals. That's ramez r-a-m-e-z
Thanks, ma'am
Thanks
No, it's it's the three briefcase boys
They all have the same briefcase
So mickey cohen or jack dragnus stole the army surplus morphine and they are selling it on the streets
They're on their way to the briefcase convention looks that way
Pop once returned customers not corpses. Why haven't they cut the morphine?
Of the american century broadcasting network good question detective
This robbery happened months ago, right?
the beginning of the year
They're selling the morphine suddenly turning up now
Another good question
But where does it get us?
It's like asking questions in the middle of the movie. You just sit tight and keep your yap shut
We'll find out what happens. Okay
We need to follow the evidence
Am I gonna finish this game?
Definitely not tonight
That's for sure
LAPD
We're here to see jose ramez. What's it about routine inquiries, sir? Can you tell us where we can find him?
He was in the delivery truck just went out god damn it
11k calling kgpl
Go ahead 11k
In pursuit of narcotic suspects aboard a gm delivery truck commercial license david charles 457
Well, I thought I had it
What is this lunatic? What the hell are you doing? Hit him colt spin him out
We're not playing around here. Get this clown off the road
Oh, no, here comes the sofa
Here comes the fridge don't do the fridge
Don't do the fridge
That's too bad, I really wish he was gonna throw the fridge step on it, huh just give me a little closer
He's going left onto hollywood get along
Show me your hands
He's going for the sink
No tires
Do I have a dlc? Uh, I do not
Jose ramez you're being arrested on suspicion of supplying illegal drugs resisting arrest and for malicious damage to la pd property. Hey
Hold your horses. I supply furniture not drugs and that thing back there. That was an accident
Some furniture came loose
That's all save it for the da chico. Keep an eye on him. We're gonna take a look around inside
Let's take a look
True size are you going to the slammer?
Is this gonna be a furniture maze?
It is isn't it?
No, i'm so happy to do the furniture maze. Where's that trail of water coming from colt?
There must be a way through the back
What would you do with all this stuff?
Welcome to furniture village where taste comes to die
No, it's not the wardrobe
What a pile of junk
My mother would be in heaven
Well, the water is here
I bet this is the kind of crap you love col 20 years out of fashion
Wait, am I crazy?
That was where the water was leaving people in here. Is there water on the ground over here?
Oh
I fucked it all up. I'm looking at I just came in the
Who lives in a pineapple?
All right, I followed the water what happened water this way water this way
Following water
What happened to the water?
There it is
Is there water over here? There is not this water this way
This is where I ended up before
Time to check jose's books. See where he makes his delivery runs. Try the front desk
So the water just stops right here. So what the hell do I do?
See where he makes his delivery runs. Try the front desk
Time to check jose's books. See where he makes his delivery runs. Try the front desk
Hold on a second. Are you are you telling me that to just go to the very beginning?
Try the front desk
So there was no reason for me to go and follow the water trail to there
Is that what you're saying?
I'm fucking serious
Okay, uh, so I need to find what am I looking for do I have like a
number slip
Say something funny
Well, there's there's the there's the thing everyone's saying is buying so much ice
Nice finger
Well, here's the rest of this
Can you think anywhere else to meet kid? We like to choose our ground. What is that supposed to mean?
It's something wellington said at waterloo the guys who win normally choose where to fight. We're gonna fight kid
The two of you versus my boys here
I love the fight game. I went a few rounds myself
You and your friend
It looks tough, but uh, I don't like your chances. Nah, we don't have to fight. Mr. Cohen
We have you an inflate. What the fuck is that some kind of steak?
It means my men are in cover, but that they can still shoot you
If those were my orders, you would all be dead now. Are you kidding me on purpose? This is a $200 coat
You got some balls. So
I hope you didn't scratch the pain in my new lincoln
These guys are getting out of the dope business. Mr. Cohen. You'll have no more problems from them
The morphine is going to disappear back into the sea. Hang on you're getting hasty
There's a lot of dough on offer here. Thanks for the offer. Mr
Cohen, but we are going to have to politely decline after today. The morphine is no more
This isn't the way we normally do business. I'm aware of that. Mr. Cohen call me mickey
Are you aware of the risk? Huh? I'm giving it to you straight. Mr. Cohen. There will be no more morphine
We made a mistake you would like to back out gracefully if you come after us
We will be forced to come after you. You've been polite up till now
So don't start making money. I don't make threats. Mr. Cohen
I'd like to thank you for your time after this cut scene. I will
Graciously take a look
There's something you should know about jack. Mr. Cohen
He killed six jabs hand to hand with just a bayonet and a k-bar knife
His outfit the six marines killed over a hundred thousand jabs in three months in okinawa and he was in the thick of it
Those japs are little guys, right?
Yes, mr. Cohen
about your size
All right
We're loading. Oh
Okay
newspapers
All right, you know, we need to do anything else here
Any more red dead redemption?
Yes, i'll probably be playing that again after this
This is the second la demar stream
But let me get to the cookie crm gave 50 dollars
Thank you so much for the 50 bucks cookie
And cookie says hey there germa, it's been a rough tough few months for me
So it's nice to come and watch the stream. My crappy time got better
Got the better of me and I kind of acted like a jerk on your last stream in boston
I made a few jokes about how your stream sucks after donating 115 dollars, but I don't think the joke went through well
I've felt awful about it ever since so here's some more money to go with my apology
Even if you feel it's not needed to enjoy a gift to kickstart your gambling addiction
Uh, I don't I don't remember
I don't remember any
Mean comments or anything but thank you for the 50 dollars here cookie
Sorry to hear about your um
That you're having a tough time
Hope it's better now. Hope you're having a better time
You were crying
I was really drinking
I was drinking heavily that stream
but anyways
Uh, thank you so much, dude. Don't worry about it. I don't really know. I don't really remember
But it's all good. All right. Is there anything else I need to do in here?
I clicked on this because somebody said it
Well, an audio is buying a lot of furniture
Stream sucks, by the way
well
That's your opinion. I'm glad you have one
It'd be bad if you didn't
All right. Now follow trail of water. There's a trail of water here
Drink the water
This is useless
I can't see a damn door or ladder
You need to get up onto the floor of water
All right, uh
Phillips, I think it's time for you to join the american ninja warrior crew. Holy shit
buttons
What is this for?
Grab the guy
Can you can I like pick him up?
Crush him crush him
Ah
Wait, did I just block myself and dad's let him in?
I think I have to pick that up again and move it. He's right there. I tried
Block the door again
All right. What do you uh
some kind of shortcut
or
What?
Now block him in
No, i'm not jumping
I'm not i'm not restarting this mission
I think we know where the water's coming from. You're gonna want to see this
Yep
Uh, I think frozen inside. No, i'm not gonna make it and what I was gonna say was a mosquito or like a jurassic park
Fucking fossil whatever
Uh, okay. I'll be damned
Giant jenga. I've played this at a bar before this must be how they transport them
Leave it right there everyone out of the vehicle and put your hands up
There's something in the ice
He's making a run for it. There's something in the ice
Oh
Get him
No, don't lose me in the furniture maze. I'm wide open here fuck
Oh, no
He's dead
I think no he's good
Take them all to hollywood station have the me and tech services go over this place
What will you be hunting polar bear polar golf polar bear ice golf?
Is otty serious is the lappd turning a blind eye to narcotics
Keep your shirt on felps
Drugs are prohibited doesn't mean people don't want to take them
Limiting supply doesn't mean that we have limited demand
I understand that I know that the average joe needs to unwind my plans on the switch
Is this this is orphan switch heroin?
It's important to demonize hop phelps. It looks good in the papers
But when all is said and done, it's just another chemical like booze
A lot of people in high places think we're doing the city a favor by keeping the dope rolling into central avenue
Donnelly certainly believes we need to keep them anesthetized
Better jobs and opportunities would go a lot further
Will you listen to yourself
No
I don't think so
Landmark. Oh, that's right. This is his car
Must have gotten fixed. I missed a turn audit
You're paying for every last scratch
For years
Not much call for ice anymore with all those newfangled refrigerators save it for someone who wants to hear it
How many janitors carry a gap?
Give it up finkelstein your brother-in-law will get you a good lawyer. My brother-in-law hates my guts
Come and get me if you want some daylight for that suit of yours
Well, that's three
I'm trying to just get him really quickly
Damn it
What don't do it again don't do it again throw out the guns
I didn't hit him at all. I didn't hit him in the face. Oh, you had a spark head there
Here easy
Push forward pick up what like my god
What is this like?
I'm gonna say
All dead finkelstein leave the weapon and put your hands up now
Put my hands up it says press x to pick up weapon
But it doesn't actually mean it you have to be standing on the weapon some old friend puts a an ice pick above my ear
No, thanks only one other way out shit heel
Let's have a look around now that we finally got some peace and quiet
I think i've had enough ice for one day
Until the scotch I pour myself as soon as we get out of here
Three guess is what's in the box open her up col. It's gonna be drugs
Yeah, there it is. This stuff has got to be worth at least a hundred grand
So finkelstein robbed the ship
My guess is lenny took it off their hands
This is big
This is going to make the papers felps
As senior investigator i'll do the talking
biggest drug bust ever
Well, well who would have thought that roy earl's hand-picked new partner would have turned out to be such a great case, man
This is a good result felps as far as we can tell lenny
The fink was moving the morphine across the city and as far north as frisco
This makes the feds very happy and it makes mickey cohen look bad
Don't lie to you kid
I like the headlines
I like them a lot
You keep this squad in the papers and we'll get along just fine
I did it case report
Not that great, but not it's very
The death of lenny finkelstein should keep administrative vice in the headlines for now
You know a freddy calhoun
Sure, I know freddy needs money to get out of town
Says he's prepared to blow i'm not looking at it. It's a wild tangent distribution ring
Says he said how much it's gonna cost 50 bucks and the department will front me the 50 you can put in an expense claim
He's over at mike lineman's on hollywood boulevard. See what you can find out
All right. Um I
Unfortunately looking at my phone a couple of times here. I have to make a few phone calls
About important matters
I need to make two phone calls
So I have to go
uh
Don't worry. Everything's fine. It's just about
a couple of
loose ends that need time
so I need to um
I got a skedaddle while it's still
Uh, what time is it? It's still it's still not even midnight. Oh, yeah, I gotta make I have I gotta go
Oh, I gotta go. I gotta get out of here
um
But i'll be live tomorrow
Uh, this should give us just enough time to go through the bits
Just make your calls and come back. Uh, that's that's not gonna happen
i'll probably be on the phone for like 30 or 40 minutes and at that point, uh, it's
12 30 one o'clock in the morning eastern might as well just start again tomorrow
So the plan tomorrow is you'll see
Not the green screen green screen is thursday
but
Uh, i'm gonna do something else tomorrow something that uh should be fun
Not delta rune
Something else something else
A pumpkin carving
Nope
What's the I have to make two phone calls each one is going to last probably
15 to 20 minutes each
Maybe more so that's where the 40 plus minutes comes from
And at that point it's gonna be kind of too late to come back I think to start another stream
Yeah, I guess one of them is my mother. That's correct
You are correct
But uh, thank you for sticking around. I'll see you guys tomorrow
I'm gonna start earlier tomorrow
uh probably around
Like four or five pm eastern so like the typical time that I started yesterday the day before
I had to do some stuff today, which is why I wasn't here till about 6 37 eastern
But i'll see you tomorrow
A earlier for something else
Take care of you leaving. See you tomorrow
And if you're still here
Why don't we go ahead and do this?
Let's go back
to lazy luke
Ten dollars from lazy luke. Thank you so much
No message just ten bucks
Appreciate it, dude
Kesh woof. Thanks for the ten dollars as well. They say love you jerma jerma heart. Thank you
Back to back here ten dollars
Big ten spot here from the two of you. Thank you guys
Ultra levin. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey jerma. Just want to let you know you always brighten my day. Keep being you. Thank you
Appreciate it levin
infinite deodorant. Thanks for the one dollar 1940s
Buick driving geezer simulator
Credits music is too loud. I'll turn it down
Uh, thank you though. Thank you infinite deodorant. Thank you div usp for the three bucks. No message. Thank you div
Uh a pepperoni. Thanks for the one dollar. This used to be a main a stream
Well, that's an old one
That's an old that's that's old
The stardew valley man, I survived germa 985 stream and all I got was this la snore stream
Well, you already survived the stream
So you've survived the stream and you got a stream
But thank you. Thank you to uh
It russa it ross gara. Thanks for the one dollar do thanksgiving stream
With italics and kim like you did with the with your family
I don't even know what the hell we're gonna like even do
I mean like let's eat like turkey sandwiches
But thanks, dude. Thank you ex
skater
Thank you ex skater one for the one dollar and 30 cents. No message. Thank you
Thank you, uh newton my yep. That's how i'm gonna pronounce it. Thank you newton my
lips for three dollars and fifty cents
School lunch hot dog is better than anything from wendy's
school lunch hot dog
What are you talking about school lunch hot dogs tastes like they came out of the microwave
But thank you. Thank you. Uh newton
Thank you also to man boy for the one dollar and they said, uh, they said they I made this
I don't know what that is
Well, I made this
Uh centurion centurion. Thanks for the one dollar. I just watched five ads for these bits. I hope you're happy
I'm happy if anybody decides they're gonna give me money or watch my stream. So
Thanks for watching. Thank you, man
Thank you smelly boy again for the one dollar. Will you be smoking or ingesting illegal substances as part of the green screen stream?
So I have a recommendation
I'm not gonna why would I do drugs in front of a green screen? What how does that do?
I'm just gonna do drugs in front of a green screen. Thank you. Thank you rick t for the one dollar rick tt
No message appreciate it. Thank you
uh
Yeet tweet in d d thanks for the one dollar. They say frank or z
Thank you garfield the monday killer. Thanks for the one dollar garf is dropping in from the rafters
A flying slobberknocker to charlie cheesnip. So what's this odie comes up from the ropes
He's using his tongue twister on him. It's a jim davis tag team
I've never seen anything like it
Folks glue man doesn't look so good garf is relentless
Garf would never be allowed in in like in the rumble. I mean well he he like ever again
I mean garfield would just never be allowed ever again. It's too powerful
How much you want to bet germa stops reading these bits midway through?
He's right you're right you got me
Yeah
That's absolutely what just happened. How much you want to bet that I stop reading them halfway through
And chooses instead to go on a wild tangent about how many garf bits there are. I just want to impress you father
Thank you. Thank you garfield
Uh, you did get me there. That was pretty good
Cookie gave the 50 dollars earlier
Huge. Thank you to cookie crm
Thank you for the astronomical amount of money
It means a lot. Thank you so much
uh actual
dragon tears
Thank you
Hey germa, uh
Life's been dealing me a shit hand lately. I've got hurt and got sent home. My grandpa just died
I just want to say that I finally watched your murder
House video and laughed harder than I have in a long time. Thank you
I'm really sorry to hear about that. That's
That sucks
But if you can get any joy or happiness or take your mind off something
um
happy that you think that
my shit's worth watching and worth putting on that kind of a
A pedestal up there. That's
I don't know what to say. Thank you
Sorry to hear about your loss
And that's it for the bits
Thank you so much everybody as always
uh, sorry for the kind of abrupt stream ending but
um
i'm getting texts here
and it's
I need to make sure I can make these calls because i'm on pacific time and I keep forgetting that
It's not late for me, but it's late for everybody else
uh
And then right at the end it's rugara for the one dollar sims 4 is getting a first person mode
Will you do another one with that another murder stream?
I don't know maybe that probably not though because that was like I can't I don't like going back and doing
stuff that I already did
because
At some point, you know, it was so interesting and so funny to me that going and doing it again is like
And we're doing it again
Remember the thing we did again. I don't know. I feel like i'd like to keep that
preserved
But thank you. We'll see i'll take a look i'll take a look at that, you know in quotes
Uh, thank you. Dr. Clay at the end here for five dollars finally get a chance to join the stream in the beginning this time
With your new schedule. It's a little hard to join the stream live because I tend to be at work when you start
Thanks for the stream today
Yeah, i'll have a more clear schedule probably start after the green screen stream is when i'm gonna really
hunger down here and
Get all that done
I would say but in my opinion the green screen stream
is like the start of
Here we go. Here comes more streams. Here comes like the stream shit these this last week or so
I mean remember i've the internet's been all fucked up and i've been moving and stuff
So these last week or so of streams have just been
Hey, i'm i'm here and i've had a lot of fun red dad has been fucking a ton of fun
La noir has been a lot of fun, too
But i'm still trying to get back into the swing of things and this week has been what that's been
But we'll see how it goes. Thank you though and let's do the credits
The credits are going to roll right now. Thank you everybody for your continued support
You guys are amazing all the subs old subs new subs and I will see you tomorrow
He's been moving for six months
Oh, well, not really i'm here now
He does the credits after the bits. Well
people have subscribed
During the bit sometimes the bit readings can go an hour
sometimes, you know 20 30 40 minutes hour two hours and
You know people subscribe during that so I figured I'd just do it after
Remember when bits were two hours?
uh
Well, also remember another thing to keep in mind is
During my normal stream schedule, it would be you know, four to six hours three times a week
right
I've been streaming every pretty much every single day for
seven to ten hours a day
Why are the credits off to the side a little?
Um, I didn't even know that thanks. That would mean more bits. Well that
Whatever
That's fine. That's not
Streaming longer doesn't necessarily mean more like money from people giving bits
It just just kind of you know, people give money. They give money. That's how I see it
I don't i'm not putting like a a quota of how much money and bits that I have to receive per stream
That's just
You should play more old school games too many triple a titles recently
You mean red dead redemption?
That's the only one
I played lethal league with star and then la noir which came out like seven years ago
That's all i've done since being coming back
You know, it's still triple a
Well, I mean
I I well here's the thing right?
It's kind of like damned if you do damned if you don't so like red dead
I started red dead and I stream red dead four times in a row
and
If I stop playing red dead completely
There's probably a lot of people here that'd be like why won't you do what do you want to go do red dead again?
Why are you leaving red dead?
You know, i'll go play something else and then three days go by go back to red dead
It's trying to do a balance, you know
And plus all these these are all these huge
You know five ten year in the making games like red dead redemption two
Is specifically is more than five ten years in the making
So it's not like a typical I don't really play that many triple a games to begin with
You know like for the most part I kind of just do whatever
but that's one of those titles that I would like to experience and play and have fun with everybody with because it's just
It's it's just the new rock star game that
It's just so there's so much to do and so much to see
But I will see you all tomorrow
Have a fantastic rest of your night. Make sure it didn't miss any bits of the very end here. I did not
So much to do so much to see
Sure, but it's always been it's almost you cannot tie loose ends up at midnight
Yeah, i'm gonna turn to a pumpkin
But i'll see you tomorrow. We're gonna do something different. Don't worry. We're doing something different tomorrow
What is it auto? I'll see you guys bro. Have a good night. Goodbye. Take care