Every journey is a series of choices. The first is to begin the journey.
Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Anti-Chamber.
I don't really know that much about this game because I just downloaded it, just installed it not that long ago.
So all I know about this game is it's weird. It's a weird game, it's got weird mechanics,
and it's like a puzzle art project adventure game with a throw-up experience.
So I don't know what's gonna happen. I don't think I'm gonna let's play this whole game, unless you guys really want to see that.
I'm gonna try and get as far as I can, maybe play for like 15-20 minutes, we'll see.
But anyways, time remaining. Do I only have like an hour and a half to beat this whole game? What the hell does that even mean?
Alright, all my settings are okay. Let's get started here.
No, I do not want to go through the exit. I know you start here, that's all I know.
Here we go, choose your destination. Leap of faith, baby.
So already this game kind of gives me a headache. If it gives you a headache too, I apologize.
Jump! That didn't work. Okay.
This game reminds me... Oh, is that another... Whoa. Whoa!
Look at it, it's like building the floor around me. Can I like jump on that?
What the... What? What the hell did I just even do?
Alright, well apparently I fell through like the second floor. I can't get back up there, let's see. What is this?
Failing to succeed does not mean failing to progress. Gotcha. Let's go.
Let's go down like the secret super 80s hallway. Where's like Janis Joplin?
Girls, just wanna have fun. That's not Janis Joplin.
Some paths are clearer than others. Alright.
Hey, where's like Dilbert? I feel like Dilbert's gonna come out and yell at me. Look at these like comic book graphics.
Alright, red or blue? Do I want to be on defense or offense?
Alright, let's go on offense. Yay!
I don't know what that did. Okay. Hmm, I'm thinking.
A choice may be as simple as going left or going right. That's what I just did.
Alright, let's go on red team. We're gonna go on like Thunder Mountain on defense on red. I'm gonna play the soldier. Here we go.
Oh, this game gives me a headache. What? I already did this.
The choice doesn't matter if the outcome is the same. So it does not matter if I go left or right.
Hold on, I need some Dr. Pepper to help think about what's going on here. I got it, we're going blue.
The stairs up here, though. This game is supposed to teach you to not think regularly.
You're supposed to think outside the box. Can I like jump on these stairs?
You're telling me I can't like jump and like spin around and go down that way. I definitely can.
Jump, spin, freak out. That's not working. Let's just go over here.
Again, is there no more clues? Am I really lost on the first puzzle of this goddamn game?
Can I like move through here? No, I can't.
I can't. It's probably something maybe if I jump like this.
Damn it. Hold on a second. What if I go back?
Ah, there it is. My house is on fire now.
When you return to where you have been, things aren't always as remembered.
How are you supposed to figure that out? How are you supposed to figure this out?
I just like walked over here because I was being a weirdo.
Maybe it's because the stairs are going this way, too?
The stairs let go. Wow, this game is for a way smarter person than me.
I probably won't even get past level one, guys. I'm not going to lie.
Alright, let's go.
I don't think I can do this for that much longer.
Alright, don't touch. Can I crouch?
Alright, apparently I'm supposed to touch that.
Should I hit escape right now to not get like laser beamed?
Oh, if you don't like where you've ended up, try doing something else.
So I ended up back here. Alright.
Alright, I did what it told me to.
Taking the first step can be harder than the rest of the challenge.
That's it? So I shouldn't have even jumped at the beginning? Let's go this way.
What the? What the hell just happened?
Whoa. Where? Where am I right now? Do I go down?
Oh, where am I going? What is happening?
What is happening? I am so lost right now.
Guys, it's not even funny.
I managed to... I'm still going down apparently.
Is this like a teleporter? Come on, let's go.
Whoa, jump. So do I have to jump? Okay, do I jump down from this?
This is really freaking me out. I definitely have to jump straight down.
That is definitely an illusion, alright.
Yeah. Okay, we're back. Up here again.
I gotta jump off. Alright, I get it. I got it. I got it.
Here we go. Ready? Ready? Ready? Come on, let's go.
Now get me off. Yeah. What does this one say?
Dig a little deeper and you may find something new.
Should I go down here? No, we're going to go in this room.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What? Alright, whatever. Let's go.
What appears impossible may have a very simple answer.
Alright, where's your PhD to play this game?
How we perceive a problem can change every time we see it.
F-E-L-I.
F-I-L-I-F-I-F.
Felfief? Look at the Illuminati looking at me.
What is happening? What is this god damn game?
Look at this like trippy freaking...
Am I supposed to solve this puzzle? What is that?
Where is it going? I'm going to follow this down the hall.
Come on, block. Little block. Little purple block.
Tick all the way down.
This is a trippy room. This is an absolutely trippy room.
Can we speed this up here, Block? Let's go.
Alright, hold on, I wanna look at the stuff, hold on.
Wow. Wow.
I'm closing one eye right now, guys.
One eye is closed.
Because this game is hurting my head.
This better be worth it! I better not have to be wasting my time doing this.
Hold on, I wanna see where this ends up.
Oh, it ends up over here- what the hell?
It ends up over here.
I'm saying, I am gonna push this all the way.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Make your way across.
So what can I talk about while this does this for the next six minutes?
Well, we'll talk about the color purple.
So what things are purple?
Um, lollipops can be purple.
The Lakers, the Los Angeles Lakers have purple in their uniform.
Hmm, other things that are purple- a grape?
You can get purple grapes from the grocery store.
They're delicious, they're nice and juicy and cool.
And put them in the freezer, they're even better.
You can have- alright, hold on, we're almost done, we're almost done.
What did this just do?
What?
Where did it go? I just lost it!
When- what?
What is in there?
Hold on, I wanna find my purple block.
This is- this is- what?
Did I honestly just do that for no reason?
Stop looking at me, I.
Oh, I get it.
I gotta look at this while I move backwards.
Oh, figured it out.
A few steps backwards may keep you moving forward.
Oh, whoa.
This is just renamed this game, Acid Trip the Game.
This is just Acid Trip the Game.
It simulates taking a ton of acid.
Window of opportunity can lead to new places if you are willing to take a closer look.
What?
So can I- should I like not look at that?
Or should I look over here?
I'm just gonna go this way.
Hey.
Where am I?
What's happening?
Where's my flashlight?
I don't even know where I'm going.
Apparently, I ended up somewhere.
Look a little harder and you will find a way forward.
What?
I- hold on a second.
This is the thing that was here earlier.
If you said, Jerma, I'll pay you a million dollars to put this where it's supposed to be,
I wouldn't get it.
I would not get the million dollars.
I would have to- I- I'm gonna say it's probably supposed to go right there.
But that's definitely not what's supposed to happen.
What if I pick this up?
Can I pick this up and then leave?
Last time I did this, the whole world changed.
All right, here we go.
It's gonna change.
Look at that.
Wow.
Venturing into the unknown can lead to great rewards.
Yeah, I have like this block.
I don't know what the hell I'm supposed to do with it though.
The end may come before we were ready to get there.
No, I don't want to go out that way.
Yeah, this is the- wait.
Did I just beat the game?
Life isn't about- life isn't about getting to the end.
Oh yeah, I like beat the game.
Except I didn't.
What about this way?
Hey, look at this.
More stuff.
Look into this thing and the world changes, right?
Still holding this blue block.
I want to read that.
Uh, sure.
Why not?
Should I go around the other side and look?
Oh yes, I should.
Hey, hello.
At times we need to view the world from someone else's perspective.
Very true.
Does that mean I can leave now?
It does.
Uh, what?
Venturing into the unknown can lead to great rewards.
Yeah, I already did this.
Was I able to go through somewhere else?
Still holding.
Let's switch this again.
Switch this again.
Was this thing here last time?
Confused.
All right, that was not there this time.
So now let's open it up again.
Let's go through.
I can't go that way.
What if I put that there?
Nope.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Can't see again.
What's that?
What's that thing?
I want to go in there.
Let me in there.
Bastard.
Wait, hold on.
There's another one of these.
No, this is back to this weird room.
Shit.
Damn it.
I need two of these friggin' blocks?
You gotta be kidding me.
Where's the other one?
Where's the other block?
And that is going to wrap up my initial video on Antichamber.
Again, I'm not sure if I'm going to play through this whole thing.
I don't think I'm gonna let's play this whole game.
Just wanted to give you guys my initial reaction to the craziness that is in this game.
Highly recommend this game if you are into the puzzle genre or the physics simulation type genre.
Because this one is a mind bender.
It truly is, as you've seen in this video.
But that's gonna wrap it up, guys.
I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.