This is a one-on-one. I haven't even unlocked like any characters. It doesn't even matter. Does it really matter?
Do I need to unlock characters when you got fuckin' Pac-Man on this list? Gotta make sure I choose my right control setup.
Who's first? Who's first in the For Glory ranked 1v1 Pac-Man vs. the Entire Universe?
Yeah, we get this guy's Robin. Two-stock. Let's do it. I'll show you guys how it's done.
I'll show you how to... I'm gonna be one of the most professional
athletes you've ever seen in this game.
See, all I know is that you gotta have the hydrant down. When the hydrant's down, you can do extra damage.
You can launch it at people
or you can just get hit by everything that he's done so far. That works, too.
You see that? Do you see that hydrant play? You see that hydrant play?
See that? You see that double? Oh my god, you're talking about the best fuckin' Pac-Man in the world.
I don't really have a follow-up to that one.
I gotta like concentrate. I don't want to lose this. This is my first ever ranked match.
You know what I mean? You can't like screw this up. I want to come down. Is that right? 104%. I'm doing good.
I'm doing fine. No, I'm not. That was a mistake. And now she's gonna launch it again at me. No, do not dodge!
Fuck!
I missed! I missed again!
All right, sit up. Fucking sit up and play the goddamn fucking game.
That fire move. What was that? I don't even know these characters yet. I don't know what I'm doing.
There we go. All right, time to shape up.
That was close. That was a hydrant play. This is a hydrant play.
This is a hydrant play. Right here, guys.
Hey, we're gonna play Smash Brothers?
How about we play Jerma gets publicly embarrassed? That works, too. How did you- what is this?
What is this, like, super smoke that you're doing to me?
I'm telling you, comeback of the year right here, guys. You think it's a joke? Oh, come on. What is that move?
It fell off. It's all right. I can recover this. Oh, did you see that recover? Come here! Come here!
How am I still here?
No, what the fuck? Drop it. I know what you're gonna try to do.
Sure, I could have capitalized on that, but I didn't. All right, now I gotta launch it. Now I gotta launch it.
Bang. It's all right. He's a little- he's a little confused. Now I get him with the fruit.
Oh shit! That one was backfired. What? What? Why did that not hit him? That went right through his body.
That was a load of dog shit. It's all right. I can- I can recover from this one.
Dammit, I threw the jello in the wrong direction. I lost. Throw the flu- throw the strawberry at him.
You picked up my strawberry?
You used my own strawberry on me? That's when you turned it on.
Now I'm angry you picked up my strawberry not long ago. Those strawberries took the grow on my farm.
Two months! How long does strawberry take to grow? Like, a week? I don't know.
Ten days? No, that's UPS ground shipping. We're not talking about ground shipping. We're talking about strawberry growth.
There we go. Now that you did that, you really started- you really got me angry with that one. Okay, I'll just come grab you.
Nope, I missed. Oh, I got to win this one. Come on.
Don't do it. Oh, don't do it. Don't do it, you motherfucker! I lost again!
19 ranked games and only two victories.
I have a 10% win rate. Guys, I'm pretty sure that I have better winning percentage
with scratch tickets. I feel like I've played the lottery in one more games than I have in fucking Smash Brothers.
Pac-Man versus Bowser, huh?
All right. I heard you liked balloons. Oh dear. Okay, I gotta be careful. He has like
some dash moves and stuff, I think.
Wait, can he grab you and like drop you off the stage?
Oh, I almost just- I almost just died there. See if I can get him. Got him.
Whoa, can he do that from the trampoline? Shit. I think that's the move I'm thinking of that he has.
Don't even think about it. You know, I get too caught up in dropping that hydra. That's like the pro-
What- I'm sitting here talking. Rude. I was telling a story.
I apologize in advance,
but I gotta be quiet for this one. So enjoy- enjoy the gameplay.
Enjoy the gameplay because that's what's gonna be in the background of this gameplay commentary.
Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here with a gameplay commentary.
Uh, this is post, so I'm not playing the game right now. That's because, you know, you probably could guess.
I suck.
I got a- I got a new costume. You know, it's all about the costume, I think, in my opinion.
If you don't have a good costume on, I mean you might as well. Why did none of us hit that?
Oh, that would have been sick if I just hit it with him. Come here. Jump into it.
Oh, you got hit by the balloon.
Oh, that was a full smash.
Right, we're good. We're good.
Didn't want to do that, but it's all right. It's- it's still kind of worked out. Drop the hammer on him. Turn around.
Smash it into him.
Perfect. Follow up with the up in the air. Up in the air, trampoline.
Double.
Yep, that's exactly what I wanted to have happen. And then,
you're gonna throw the key at him. Oh shit. No, you're not. You're gonna throw the fucking balloon at him again.
It's gonna miss. It's all right. I got a- I got an advantage over this one.
Damn it.
He's at 72%. I should- I should get this. I should be all right. Oh, come on. That's what it is right there.
You can't- you can't recover for this one.
Come on.
Oh, damn it. I missed again.
Oh my god, I'm just grabbing you with my radar. No, he grabbed me. Did I just bounce off his head? I did.
That's fine. I'll just launch you like that. Save it. Save it. Save it. Come on. Let me- let me- he's got 128%.
I should get this. There it is. Come on. I did it. Yes!
This is too stressful.
Is there anything in this game that's like not as stressful as 1v1 for glory mode? Yeah, this is what I'm talking about.
Eight player smash.
Nobody knows what's really going on with their character. It's just a mess.
It doesn't matter who wins or loses in eight player smash.
It just goes in front of the screen. No, but it doesn't matter.
I don't even know where I am. I'm up here on the right. Jigglypuff, you're dead. Eat this.
If I aimed in the right direction, that would be great. There's no competitiveness here.
It's just Diddy Kong
and Mario. Flame Mario, by the way.
Am I gonna win? I have a chance here, guys, to win
against a bunch of brainless computer players.
Okay, it's just down to me. Nope. It's just down to me and Dark Pit. We both have pretty high health. What's going on?
Why am I doing that?
I will beat you. Yeah, get spiked. Yeah, get dumb. I won.
I think that qualifies as if anyone could that's watching could qualify.
Pac-Man eight player smash victory against all cpu players that you've made the easiest difficulty.
It's got to count for something. It's got to count for something, right? I mean, it's got to count for something.
It's got to mean it's got to count for something, right? I mean, it's got a thing, right?
I mean, oh, um thing, right?
Okay. Bye guys.