Oh hello, pardon me just one moment. Good to see you again, all of you. Of course you know who I am, I know who you are.
It's me, B.F. Mugleberry. You're still your favorite person in the world. I am here to show you a few wonderful, magical things.
Three of which, don't want to drop my magical potions, but what is it? What's the matter?
There's too much reverb, like me. I haven't even gotten started yet, just give me one moment.
Oh, just hold on, wait just a second, hold on a minute. Reverb, that's what he said.
Hold the book upside down for God's sake. Reverb, reverb, reverb. Thank you. The smell of diminishing echo.
Take that very quickly. That's one tablespoon of riboflavin. That's good. Is that even correct? I believe it was.
One dash of mouth droppings. A batwing, which I have here somewhere. Batwing, leviton, and of course cave moss.
Cave moss from a cave that I have explored, all these ingredients I've explored, many times over, just like that.
Now this should. I know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know. Everybody relax. Hold on.
With one touch of the head. One, two, three, get it. As they say, bottoms up.
Hello. Can anybody hear me? Can anybody hear what I'm saying? Hello. Yes. Are we fixed? Is it better?
Oh, that is such a breakthrough. That's quite a breakthrough.
The spell of diminishing echo. I have to write that. Make sure it's etched with blood.
Anyways, let me just briefly tell you what we're doing now that you can possibly understand.
As you know, I'm B.F. Bugalberry. I'm here to show you my cauldron of acid, my cauldron of demonic fluid.
And in this we will be creating spells, monsters, creatures of the likes of which you have absolutely
never seen. I can guarantee you that one. I'm your host Bugalberry. Let us begin, shall we?
The first recipe that I would like to create for you is one that I'm sure you're going to be very
interested in. It is a spell, a secret drink that everyone knows the ingredients to. I'll
start with a little bit of nutmeg. Nutmeg flavoring. Oh, no, that's not right. That's
musk of muskrat. Gotta get that one right, Bugalberry. This is it. Make sure I have the label
right. Yes, this is nutmeg. A dash of nutmeg into the cauldron it goes, whisking, filling,
screaming in a way, yearning for its brothers and sisters to join the pot with it.
Next is lemon lime peel. There's a lemon peel here. And we go like this. We go, bam! We go, bam!
Up next, there's two ounces of corn syrup, which I believe this is. We have some flavored corn syrup
there. It is a dash, a dash of caramel coloring. Just this way here. There it is, a dash of caramel
color. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. There we go. And then we stir, stir.
We end up with a beverage that I trust you will put this down. I really want to get into this one
here. What do those witches say? What do those witches say? Double, double, toil and trouble.
We don't actually say that, you know. We don't actually do those things. Why would we say double,
double, toil and trouble? I don't understand. It doesn't make any sense to me.
Oh, there it is. I believe it's ready to test. So, let's see how it comes out.
Looks like it's the right color. Has a good smell. Give it a taste. Just like the real
thing. I bet you can't tell a difference. I bet you couldn't tell a difference.
Let me upload this to YouTube on a science channel. This is technically a science channel now.
I mean, I am creating all kinds of spells and creatures that you will see very soon.
That's the recipe for not hola. Don't want to say the first seed word. Just to help get arrested.
So, coming up next. Oh, if you wondered, ladies and gentlemen, where the characters
that Gerber creates, where they come from. Oh, do I have news for you? He has nothing to do with it.
He commissions me and I create the creatures. I create the characters and I create
many other things that he uses. Don't let him fool you. Don't let him do that. So,
we're going to make some now because that's why I'm here. I'm here to show you the process.
Look, my thinking, how I do things when I create these characters. The first character we're going
to make, we'll see. I want to see if you can guess who they are before they come out. First up,
we're going to use, let me get it right, one walrus whiskey. And it's been dehydrated
many times over. If you don't spit it, it won't work. One can of Pringles. I don't have those.
What can I substitute? One concentrated liquid from a tomb of the 70s. This is it right here.
As you say, this is from 1976. Yeah, 1977. You can tell. This is very, very raw. Very raw.
It's very raw. The 1970s. There we go. A little extra. Then next onto this
is wishful thinking. And the final ingredient is this. Germa's DNA. I collected this for many years
collecting soda cans and scrubbing his toilet many times over. Plenty of Germa's DNA to create.
Let's see who we got here. We need quite a bit of this. Okay. Whoa, whoa, don't be too. Whoa,
hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Oh, it's starting to get windy. It's starting to get
windy. Come on. Rise. Rise. Mustache Germa.
Why do I keep saying that? Let's go. Yeah, go. No, character registration is on your right.
Go that way. No. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. That way. Yes. Oh, he's an idiot. He put very much brain
and power in that. Our next character that we will be creating, this is a popular one. Let's start
the process. I've got to keep this moving. Five percent. Not that one. Not that one.
There it is. Five percent of every children's Halloween costume. Yes. A pinch. A small pinch
of mouse droppings. We'll be using these quite frequently. That was more than a pinch. Hey.
That wasn't part of the recipe. I just wanted to see what that felt like.
It felt pretty good. Strange. Very strange. Anyways, a pinch of purple liquid. This is blue,
but we put red in already. Of course, children's DNA should be used very frequently. As you see it
pilling, bubbling again like it always does. Mesmerizing. Hypnotizing goes. I'm weak of men,
but I am not a weak man. A strong man. And then all we need to do is wait. Stir. And that will
give us. Oh, who do you think will be that character? Arise. Arise. I don't think that's
going to make it that far. I'm not even quite sure a German will be able to use that one.
It's not that different. Kind of. I tried. Maybe he'll make it. And then it is his DNA.
Coming up next. We have a good one. The first on this list is protein powder. Protein powder,
which I have down here somewhere. We can use mouse droppings. Protein powder. This protein
droppings. You just don't know it. A small dash of testosterone. Lots of it. There it is. Lots of
it. A little bit of vitamin D3, which is this one here. Yes, it is vitamin D3. Make sure you take
that by the way. Not enough people get vitamin D in their diet and they don't go into the sun
to get the sunshine. You need more vitamin D. Go get it. It prevents a lot of things. Helps you
with the cold, the blues. Makes you feel good. A little bit of tanning lotion, which I believe I
have some down here. Tanning lotion. Oh yes, yes, yes. There we are. If you didn't know tanning
lotion was made from fig leaves. Don't know how accurate that is, but this is not a science.
A little bit of kosher salt. A little bit of kosher salt. And finally, the DNA. Oh, that was
way too close to my face. Yeah, but please arise. Whatever you have been, whatever you have been,
whatever you will do, arise. Oh, this is a big one. He's a big boy. That's a big boy.
Of course, that's muscle germ. Here's a big guy. Very strong. You know, it probably takes a long
time in the gym unless you know me. Unless you know me and I can make a clone of you.
Then you can just send your clone in to go out in the town and people will think it was you
and you're gonna sit there and just go like this on your computer and nobody will know it was you.
So, the next one. I've been waiting to create this for a few months now at least.
I was told that this was an important character. Let's go ahead and start with the catnip.
Not new very much. Just a little bit of catnip. Kitties love it. Some humans do too.
A pinch of catnip. A small amount of Lynx venom. The most powerful destructive substances on earth.
Just a drop will kill a donkey. Don't ask me why we always use that term. Don't ask me why a donkey
has to be the thing we kill to determine how poisonous something is. Oh, it's enough to kill
a horse. Why are you killing a horse? What's wrong with you? You don't understand. You're killing demons.
Ridiculous. Up next we have, what is next? Can't read any of my glasses. Some water on it. Up next
we have, hair of the bobcat. And finally, oh, Gemma's DNA. I might put something else in here too.
Right now Gemma's DNA. What will we create this time? Arise. Doesn't even need stirring. It's
ready. It's just the chemicals reacting into each other. Come on up, catboy German.
Where am I? I don't need to wink into the spirit. Why? Ow, my head. My brain just hurt.
Where? What the fuck is happening? What? Do I know who you are? This way. Bye-bye. Registration.
Registration. Character registration over there. Talk to Lucy. Talk to Lucy. Lucy, she's waving at
you. Yes, Lucy, thank you. The next character we'll be creating is a silly one. Oh, it's cold,
I think. One, two, three, four, four dehydrated frozen ice cubes. I dropped it because it was
too cold and I got it in. Wow, wowee. That was very, very cold. Too cold. Too cold. A little
bit of kosher salt. The fangs of the ever-living dragon like we used previously. A little diarrhea
potion or whatever it was. And then all it takes is a very simple potion, very simple brew,
a little bit more of, you guessed it. It's getting cold. It's getting chilly in here. Anybody else
feel a breeze? Does anybody else feel a slight breeze? Wow, that was cool. That was cool, man.
Oh, don't do that actually. That was cool. I know some of you do. I see it. I see it right there.
That was a good joke. Thank you. I do them better than the guy that owns this place.
So the final creature we're going to make, you don't even need the book. We're going freestyle on
this one. Rink stuff. Crumping kitty liver. Catnip. Mush of the buscrap. I don't even have a recipe
for this one. Ocean water. The caramel coloring. We are going to get something extraordinary.
Oops. It's all right. It's all right. It was just a catnip. That stuff's pretty cheap.
It's not, it's not this stuff. Don't drop this stuff. I stirred up. What are we going to get?
I want to create my own creature. My own creation. And what is it? What is it? I feel
like I'm playing Monster Rancher. I saw those terminated by strings. They were pretty good.
Whoa. What is it? Oh, dear. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, no. This is horrible. Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, he's, oh, he's coming after me. He's, oh, he's fighting. Okay, I've got to be ready for this.
Hey, I didn't even, I didn't even give him a name. What was his name? I don't even know what he was
doing. Why would he attack me? A fish bastard. I don't even know what I did, but I keep putting
my hands in here and it feels, it burned for a little while the first few minutes of this dream.
You're going to track him down Lucy. He's on the loose. Oh, it hurts, but it doesn't hurt at the
same time. It's very odd. Lucy, I'm going to do something here that might, I don't,
when they were coming out, it looks comfortable. Oh, oh, oh, it hurts a lot. It hurts a lot,
but something about this is, oh, I, something's missing though. I like it, but I feel like I
should be more comfortable. I feel like the atmosphere needs to change. My, my mindset needs
to change. I'm getting this strong, incredible urge to receive donations and subscriptions.
I don't even know what that means. I don't even, I, I, I've only ever streamed with German once,
twice maybe. I feel so good right now. Oh, something about this. I could get used to this.
Hot diggity dog. Lucy, get all this shit out of here. Clear this out. I want, I, I want to
hang out with the chat now. I want to hang out with everybody over here. I want to give them,
yeah, clear this out. I want you to get rid of that stuff. Get rid of it. Thank you. No, no,
go off the back door. Go off the back door. Don't drop any of those. Don't drop any of
those potions. I saw you. You have no idea how hard it took. That was, that's 5,500,000 years
of my life. What do we do? Did somebody say I was muted? Muted? Are we muted? I was just
yelling at the people with my potions. I said, don't drop them. They just picked them up and
walked out of here. They went, they went too fast is what they did. But, uh, this is kind of nice.
What should we do now? I mean, this wheel is here. I wonder if we should use it. Should we use the
wheel? What's on here? We have, if we can get, can we get a closer, closer view of this? But
should we have a reason for this to be on here? Yeah, let's put, put an overlay on. Why don't we
make it fun? Let's make it fun. Oh, this is pretty nice. Five subs for a name on a ball.
Ten subs for your name on my body, which I'm gonna have to take this off eventually. 20 subs
for a dance party. Oh, I bet you want to see that. Oh, it's nice in here. Without the cauldron
bubbling. Why not? Why not? Without the cauldron bubbling, it's actually pretty nice. I really
hope that that fish face guy, hope they catch him. I feel like I have a scratch this big,
right here, right there. Wait, hold on a second. Did you just say that every single thing has been
redeemed? It happened already? It's only, how many subs was it? It happened already? Oh,
this is very liquidy. Very liquidy. Already? I haven't even gotten my cool shirt on yet.
Well, we're gonna have to get their names down.
Apparently, people love me. Well, let's hope we can get all those on the body before we continue.
How do I even put this on? Oh, this is good on the back, too. This feels good.
I haven't even gotten the shirt on. How many? Can you even count?
Wow. My days of potion making should be effectively over. Oh, we got some names. Oh,
there it goes. Community Jake, could you come over here? I don't even have the shirt on. Thank you.
Community Jake. See, I can hire him, too. I can hire him, too. I'll go over these names in just a
second. We should have to spin the wheel four times. I'm just gonna lay it on like this. What the
hell? Oh, we have called me false. Thank you so much for your 10 community subs. Also,
the great Canadian FK Nug. Thank you so much. I really appreciate it. Thank yous to Tippedover.
Wow. That's your name on a ball. I'm gonna say people's names twice. Oh, don't look at that.
Don't look at that. This is not. Don't look at that. Daddy? Oh, no, it's Daddy Big Box.
That's kind of comedic if you think about it. It's pretty comedic. Blind Irene 1. Thank you,
Blind Irene. Poly Hex. Thank you. Wow. I'm gonna put this in again. Let's do this here.
Oh, and we also have the eco leech. Thank you. There's no more of these remaining, by the way.
At this point, we didn't get enough balls to do this with. Throw them in. Good. Good. All right.
All that went in the eye. Fames. Wow. Fames, thank you so much for those 10 community subs.
Who else we have? Cherry Rowlett. Wow. Thank you for those 10 community subs.
Shinomi. Thank you for those 10 community subs. Oh, oh, but I can't.
Oh, it's too much. I can't get up and spin the wheel. Let's do it. That's 8 Bugs. That's 8 Bugs,
my favorite. Oh, I love Bugs. Give me a few Bugs. Did I get them by the way? Are we good?
Oh, this is what I'm talking about. Delicious Bugs. Oh, that's unbelievably delicious. Again.
Oh, that's a random potion. The microphone is wet, apparently. What's in this one? This looks
manna. It's like it's under water. Can you hear? I can hear it. It just sucks. Oh, well.
Oh, shoot. I have to write somebody's name on my face.
How am I going to write that? That's impossible. Let me do it. Please take this. Storms and shadows.
You're going to go right here. Let's see. Oh, geez. It's been quite difficult. I don't. Oh,
that's an E. This is literally not possible. I need an S. The aliens find us one day.
It's over. Wrong way. Storm of what? Storms of... This is so hard. You have no idea.
I'm drawing backwards. Storms of shadow. You get the idea, okay? I still have a bug in my mouth.
I lost it. Where'd it go? I don't even know who that was.
I need to swallow this thing in my mouth, okay? Somebody said damaged?
Swallowed. Just that simple. Oh, Shinobi. Did we get Shinobi already? What did I not get? Oh,
I'm sorry. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Is this 15? A feed line.
Feed line defined. Thank you from a 10 community sub. Do I have to write that on my face?
Oh, okay. Vertix. Thank you. Clavicle. Thank you. And hello, my name is Blank. Thank you.
Let me try to move the... Do you want to come adjust the microphone?
Give me the microphone adjuster. That's my neck. Ow. Ow. Ow. Okay. How does that sound? Is that
better? I sound like Bane. What does that mean? I don't know who that is. Your skin, your neck skin
is peeling. They're saved. Saved. Okay. Thank you. We have some more to read. I need to spin the wheel
a few more times. We did not anticipate this many people were going to actually do this,
so we were not very well prepared. Sentry J Man. Thank you, Sentry J Man. Appreciate it.
Master Mudkips. Thank you. Chef Lazarus. Thank you. And real anime hours. Thank you so much.
So who do I need to put on my body? Where is that marker? Oh. Call me false. Call me false.
Okay. There you are. Call me false. And then Blind Irene. Oh, interesting. Blind Irene
one. And then who? Ego. What's it again? Sorry. My hearing's not as good. Ego Leech. Okay. Ego
Leech. Olly Hex. Olly Hex. Okay. Daddy Big Bugs. Is this what people do? I'm running out of room.
I'm running out of space already. Where do you put it? There we are. Fanes. Okay.
And this is not coming off. This shirt's not coming off. Sorry about that, all of you.
Fanes. Chevrolet. Real anime hours. I'm going to go on the other arm. Why not? What? Real anime
hours. What are people saying? Do it. I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to take this off.
Out of your mind? Have you lost your mind? You already got the scene of the abominable snowman
pretty much naked. That's not enough for you. What was it again? Real anime hours. Real anime
hours. Well, I did my best. I just keep on wrecking. All right. I can't do this anymore.
What was that? Century J-Man. Century J-Man. This thing's running out of ink. Take a look,
everybody. Those are your names on me. He removed the jorts. Okay. All right. That was interesting.
Century J-Man and all of you. I hope nobody heard that. I really hope nobody heard that
because that was awful. That was awful. It was absolutely horrible. Please tell me no one heard
that noise. Nobody did. All right. No more writing on body. I'll do right on face. I'm not writing
on body anymore. You can't do this. I know about potions. I know how things work. I know if you do
this too much, you could get you sick. It'll make you sick. I'm not doing it. What is this? Red
Riolu. We did not anticipate this many. We thought we were going to spin the wheel three times.
We didn't think we were going to spin the wheel like five times. Sedata. Thank you. Red Riolu.
Thank you. What else we have here? Sculptor. Sculptor. What else we have? Forklifter. Wow.
Selling out. Is this what it is? Selling out. Selling out feels pretty good. E-Himbo.
This is the one that I just grabbed. This is quite, quite the image I would say.
Quite the image I would say. We got 100 subs. Oh, God. E-Himbo. Okay. Let's spin the wheel.
It's very hard to keep track of and keep up with it, but we're going to try. Let's see if we can
get something here. That's the question. You see, when we originally envisioned this stream,
I thought maybe, maybe we would have people ask me questions, but when 2,000 people subscribe
at the same time in 15 to 20 minutes, that becomes not possible anymore. What's the question?
Did I fart in the tub?
Does that answer your question? All right. I need to do things. 50 more subs. What's the name?
Freddie Dredd, the musician. I'm just going to use this because it's easier. Oh, you have it
right there. Freddie Dredd, the musician. Very talented young man. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. You're
going to have to go down somewhere on the neck area. Riding backwards and sideways,
mirrored. It should be a special skill. It should be like at the Olympics. Oh, actually,
that makes it a little easier. E. Oh, shit. Fuck. F-R-E. D. How did he do this? How did people do
this? It's not possible. It's not possible to do this. It's impossible. It really is.
Fred. Freddie Dredd. I like your last name, if that is your real name. E. F. Bugleberry is mine.
Stands for Barry Fennard Bugleberry. I do. Okay. Let's see. Freddie Dredd. Good. Very good. H. F.
S. K. A. H. Oh, man. H. F. S. H. F. S. K. A. K. A. F. H. F. H. F. H. This is painful.
J. D. A. I got scammed. Oh, yeah, I'm scammed. Oh, I'm the scammer.
Oh. Did you just say that there was a phone call? Somebody was trying to call? Who's calling?
You said 50 seconds before that. You said there was a phone call. Is that German? Hey, what's up?
Did you make the characters yet? Yes. Did you make the characters? The new characters?
Yes, I made them. Of course I did. That is all you are supposed to be doing.
I can't just hang out. I don't want you sitting around in a tub on the street. All right? I don't
want to die. It's a cauldron. Get out. Get out. You're done. You're done.
I'm not done. It's a cauldron. No, you're done. You're done. Get out of the hot tub.
It's not a hot tub. It's a hot tub. That's what it looks like. Get out.
He's just pissed because he's not getting the money. How much money did you make?
That's right, yeah. Too much. I get some of that money.
No, you don't. I get at least half of that money.
No. No, he doesn't. Not at all. Hang up on him.
Nothing to do with anything. Hang up on him.
This is not what we agreed to. Hang up on him.
Just get out. Thank you, everyone. Thank you, Bugleberry. It was really nice to see you.
Shut up. Hang up on him. Did you hang up? Good. When he calls back, don't answer again.
He can come down here if he has a problem. Oh, I'm making money. Oh, that's what it's about.
He's annoyed that I'm making more money than he is. What a fucking joke. That was not a fart,
I swear to God. That was not a fart. It looked like it, but it wasn't. It kind of did look like
it. It sounded like it, too, if that picked up. Oh, what have we got here? More balls. Let's see
them. Well, he could do this if he really wanted to. Why is it my problem? Is there a lot coming in?
Oh, shit. I cannot read these all. I cannot read these. Freddy Dread gets a ball. He's on my face.
How does he get a ball? He has the whole real estate. Fanches, thank you.
Ghost Pop Live, thank you. Hey, Kip, thank you. Three more in the face. Oh, I think we have two
mics on. Oh, who's got a question? I'm not trying to scam, I promise. Aaron, what is that? What's
Aaron? What's Aaron? What is that? What's Aaron? Why are they saying that? Oh, I think we lost one
of our lights. I think one of our lights got screwed up. Hey, here's a question for you.
Why the fuck are we doing this? How's that one? What is my height, Bugleberry? I'm six foot four.
I'm not German at all. I'm up here and he's down here. I'm not German. Oh, these are the ones that
go on the face. Holy smokes, hold on. What is that one? Question. Any more questions? Oh,
I'm not going to be able to do this. Okay, so we have Vinsmore. Vins. Oh my God. Vinsmoke. Vinsmoke.
Vinsmoke. Metalzalor. Metalzalor. What'd you say? Metalzalor. Hold on. Metalzalor. That's right.
And then Goikki. Goikki, I'll put you up here. By the way, I just want to make this clear. I'll
say it in a second. Goikki. Here you are. Goikki. Excellent work. It just looks like the original.
It looks like old caveman paintings. This is Grug. My name's Grug. After paying for production
and paying for the people that are kind enough to be spending their time here, the remaining
proceeds of this stream will be given to charity. I want to make that very clear. So, I'm going to
be giving this to charity. I'm not going to be taking this. It's time for a dance party. Oh,
dance party. Play the music. Hold on. What the hell is that?
What is this? What the hell? I don't know how that happened. Man, that hurt.
Should we spin the wheel again? Is the water warm? Yeah, it is. It's perfect for me.
Negative 15 degrees Celsius. That's nice and warm for me. Stand up. Oh, no, no, no. I don't stand up.
I will spin the wheel again and hopefully we land on something besides Question. Maybe Question
should have been something we made small. That's my fault. I should not have made Question big.
Figured it would be easy. Let's go. That's foam. Time for a foam party.
Hold on. This looks really, really ridiculous. That's 2,000 subs. I just rolled around for 20
minutes. Who is this? Goo Berry Juice. Well, I dropped the marker in the hot tub. Hopefully,
we can get that out with a little bit of elbow grease. Goo Berry Juice.
Goo Berry Juice. Okay. That was directly into the eye socket. Thank God I'm already dead.
I'm an undead demon. I can handle it. Goo Berry a boat. I think it's time to end the names on
face. We're running out of room and I'm very wet. Goo Berry, we'll get you right here. Goo. Oh,
my God. Goo Berry. This looks like two musical notes. Goo Berry Juice. There you go. Goo Berry
Juice. You don't understand. I'm very wet and this is wet too. This mask. What mask? This mask
is going to be... Why are you saying that? You're talking about my skin. Weird, weird people on this
community. I sweat my arse off making characters for you to enjoy. You know how much I get paid
for it? 40 bucks a character. 40 bucks. Oh, Gerber, don't do that hot tub stream. Don't do
the hot tub thing. It's a cauldron, first of all. What? I would rather give it to charity.
This is what I'm doing. It's Shinoli. I'm going to do Shinoli on the cheek. What on the chin?
Shinoli. Shinoli. Fix the S. What's the other one? Captain Nemo. Captain. Hello, Captain Nemo.
I keep laughing really hard, but this looks like a three-year-old's bedroom wall that he would get
in trouble over. This is just... You got into the crayons. Let's spin the wheel. Oh no, not again.
It got in the eye again. How? How did that happen twice? Spray it in the tub. In the tub. In the tub.
Inside. How did it happen twice? Okay, I might need a small towel. It happened twice. Thank you,
Community Jake. Thank you. Oh, goodness gracious. I can't wait to see the out-of-context Twitter
tonight. Oh, boy. Just throw them in. Let's do another spin. Pinata time. It's time for the
pinata. All right, let's go. Okay, here it comes. The pinata. Oh, I got it. I got it.
All right, take it back. The pinata just broke his neck. That's all I did. He didn't have any candy
in it. That was just awful. His neck just fell down. Get him out of frame. Get him out of frame.
No, I don't want to. I don't want to. Look at him. He's very sad. Hold on. I'll fix him.
I'll fix him. Take it away. Take it away. Spin it again. Why don't we? Another random potion.
Interesting. Oh, what's this one? Yellow. It's like eggs. It smells like eggs.
Tastes like eggs too, but I like that. Oh, you know what I would do with this? I would drizzle
this on top of a piece of toast. Put an avocado on it. Oh, that would be scrumptious. You can take
that from me. You're probably noticing there's a small sliver here. I don't want to burp. Mute
my microphone. Mute my microphone. Did you make that? Did you lie or did you actually mute it?
Good. Good boy. So you're noticing there's a small sliver here. If that hits, it says apocalypse on
it. Oh, and you know what that means? That means we are done here. Oh, look at that. Look at that
nerd neck. I've heard that German has used that term before. Let's try. Get another one. Eat bugs
again. Eat more bugs. Just give me one of the little ones. One of these little guys here.
Okay. Holy shit. These are good. I really actually. Hold on. I'll get it. I'll get it.
I'll fix it. Wait. There we go. These are very creamy. I would just throw them in. You're going
to eat the bugs. You eat the bugs. You will eat the bugs. You will eat the bugs while you're saying
what's worse. Turtle. It's not even a bug. It's a turtle.
Oh no. Everything is sold out. Oh no. Oh, it's all sold out. Why don't we spin the wheel one more
time? Huh? Again, everything's going to charity from my portion. I'm going to be paying the
production staff handsomely. And then all of my portion from this stream is going to charity.
I wonder what's going to happen if we spin the wheel again. What do you think is going to happen?
Falling backwards. Don't end the stream. Let's hang out for five more minutes.
Let's see if I can read some of these names. That's xsparter45. Oh my God, a human. Thank you.
So what I want to do is I want to take a picture of this. I want to get them all out,
take a photo of it. I'll retweet it out. That sounds fun to me. If they'll do that in the next
day or so. I'll ask Jerma if it's okay. PPSlap. Thank you. Oh, tipped over. I think we got that
one already. Somebody said our stream Andy. Our stream Andy. Who's Andy? We did not anticipate
this amount of things happening. We only had enough stuff for like 25 people. I don't know why we
thought that that was going to work. Oh, it's time to spin the wheel. What's it landing on?
Oh shit, it landed on apocalypse. I'll see you all soon. Don't worry. We'll get out of this together.
Thank you. Let me just be really clear before the world ends. This was a fun little joke,
but I hope you enjoyed it. I appreciate you hanging out here, everybody. We'll get a nice
photo of all the subs from today. Oh shit. Get this off camera right now. Get it off camera.
Did we miss anybody up here? He was rigged. Ocean dweller. Ocean dweller. Should we get him up here
too? Let's get him up there. We want to get at least those ones. He said potion dweller.
Ocean dweller. And that's all the fifties. Okay. Ocean dweller. All the people on the arms,
I'll give you a special thanks very soon. I'll write it on my arm another day.
We didn't anticipate this many people. Thank you everybody. Have a great rest of your evening.
We're out of here.