Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This is going to be a live commentary though. It's going to be a live commentary with four
people. Just messing around, having a good time with the guys from Method Gaming, Pwnstar,
MLC Stealth and Enad. Playing as the Soldier and then the Sniper in the next gameplay.
Two pretty good gameplays. I probably could have done normal commentaries on them. So
enjoy everybody. The live commentary will be kicking in right now.
I'm dead. What are you talking about? Oh my God. That's a Spy. That's a Spy. I'm so scared
right now. Get away from me. Is it us three against Enad? No, Pwn. We're on the same
team. What are you talking about? I think you need to... Oh my God. Oh my God. That's
a lot of people. All right. Let's get a quick cap here. Quick cap. Oh, I died. I'm going
for gold here. Jerma rocking it out with 10 points. I don't believe in you. All word
I'm in trade says Pwn. The word of the day is all word. We got anybody coming up this
little hallway here? We do. Oh jeez. Somebody just gave me five crates. Is that you right
there, Enad? No. What the fuck is this? Oh my God. Sure, let's just sit in the corner.
Is that you fucking camping? You little bitch. You were all crotch down, nuts sitting there.
Were you fishing or something? I'm on a pyro. You were like casually sitting there too, man.
Like you had some beef jerky and beer on the side. You were fucking making... That's called
like camping. That wasn't camping. Who camps in Team Fortress 2? I call it strategic waiting.
Strategic waiting. Okay. Hey, what's the rule? Sitting in the same spot for 30 seconds? I
was only there for like four, five. Bullshit. Yeah, it's the same thing like when a fucking
whore calls herself an escort. It's the same damn thing. Oh man. Oh, Optimus Prime's in
here again. Oh, is he on our team? Hopefully Optimus Prime is on our team. He is. Oh, you've
got to hit this. Oh, I will. Oh my God, where'd you go? Where'd that medic go? Oh man, come
on now. Oh damn it. No, they aren't. Not if I have anything to say about it. Do you think
about that one, Burt? No, I didn't. Oh, heavy on point. What's your butthole catch? Oh, you
guys are going to get it. I've almost got it. Oh my God, uber germa. I've almost got it.
Uber germa. No, get away. Too many people. I have nowhere to go. Run. Oh, you guys are
so going to get this. Over time. We can't even get up there. Don't fucking hate. I just
want crates. Oh, we won. Oh, I think we did win. They did. Unless somebody can get on
this. I think that's all she wrote. I'm hiding. I've got my Sandman out. Oh, that's it. Good
to game. All of them. Here we go. I'm a plain sniper. This is going to be the round where
we destroy. At least I hope so. Oh, that guy dropped down right at the right time. What?
Oh, you want to duel me, Optimus? You're going to whoop my butt. I got ubered and I just
walked outside and started swinging my sword in every which direction and didn't kill anyone.
Then I just ran back inside. Oh, God. I'm the worst. Oh my God. I keep on throwing the
Girardi right at somebody's back. That's what I wanted to do. Here we go. Wow, I just got
fucking... This guy said, po, no offense. You should have a ping limit. Offense taken.
I am so rich right now. Oh, that was a nice headshot. That's what I'm talking about. That's
what I'm talking about. Let me say, let's keep it rolling, boys. You denying the duels,
too? No, God. Oh, I got the Gunslinger. I already have that, don't I? It's a good weapon. Any
spies? I'm just throwing the P down. I'm not going to take that chance. Optimus Prime's
hiding somewhere. I can't even see. I literally can't even see. I'm just shooting into people's
backs. I don't even know if I'm hitting anyone. Okay, now I can leave now this way. So we're
doing Battlefield after this, yeah? Yeah, sure. Why not? Well, I'm going to try to.
Oh, boom. It's not going to work because my computer's going to be like... Oh, can I get
that heavy from back here? There it is. Come on, now. I'm going to try that spy stuff.
Damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, Optimus Prime. What is the Envis watch for the spy?
I'm stupid. Oh, no. There he goes. There he goes. Off to the races. He's still alive. Off
to the races. Get him. He's not dead. He is not dead. He's going to get me right in the
back. God damn it. No, I knew it. I knew he was there. I didn't turn around. Oh, don't
even go there. There you go. Nice job, guys. That is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it, and I will see you guys all
next time. Take care, everybody.