God damn it all. Here's a pyro on that point, fellas.
Don't worry, I'll take care of this. I take care of pyros all the time.
I do. Oh, what's this thing?
The new exciting game in TF2.
Watch the saw blades in Sawmill.
You get one point for every person that walks directly into the saw.
There's one point already.
So I'm just going to sit here.
I'm going to sit here and just record this whole round, start to finish.
And we're going to see how many times people die on Sawmill to the blades.
Use the scientific method.
Roll up your sleeves, get out your safety goggles, because watch out.
We're going to see some type of chemical explosion from this experiment.
So get your flask ready.
Get your sodium fluoride ready.
We got a lot to talk about here.
Here we go.
This is the pyro.
Same guy.
Did the same thing.
That's one.
There's one.
Oh, there's two.
He didn't get his second double jump off in time.
This is like the most intense game of TF2 ever.
Just now, red is nearing capture.
Oh, blue scout.
That was like a photo finish right there.
I think that guy got hit by the saw, but he just didn't register.
One of these guys is definitely going to walk into it.
I would be shocked.
Okay, see, I told you.
I wonder if there's a way, like a server mod or something,
where you could have those saws go back and forth like a hundred miles per hour,
because there would be a hell of a lot more deaths if that was the case.
Well, scout, he wants the health pack.
Place your bets.
Didn't even have time to go to Vegas and place my bet.
Here's another skirmish.
When there's like three to four people standing on the point,
that's when you start to get the saw blade action.
Like for instance, I don't know what happened right there.
I'm not entirely sure what was happening.
I think, I think, I don't know.
He just wanted to go see his friends.
They have a sentry on here.
Red, you got to get that sentry off the point.
We need more saw deaths.
It is required.
It is a requirement.
We need more saw blade deaths.
This is not enough.
He just barely caught himself.
He still might walk into it.
It's definitely a high possibility at this point.
Oh, there it is.
There's another one.
See ya.
God, he got launched.
He got launched.
If red can hold this or blue needs to come take it.
Otherwise, wow, that was close.
Blue pyro coming in.
Bye bye.
There's another one.
Have a wonderful trip to saw blade hell.
Life will find a way.
Let's snipe her on it.
No, it's going to be blue team with a victory with I don't know how many saw deaths.
It was at least seven or eight.
I could seriously sit here all day.
I could sit here all day and do this and I probably will cancel all of my appointments
put everybody on hold because I don't really want to talk to them.
I want to watch people walk into saw blades.
That's like the number one.
That was almost that was pretty close.
All right.
And wait, wait till it wait till it comes until it comes back.
Ready?
Three, two, one, go.
It can't even do it.
It couldn't even do it.
It was getting stuck on people.
Yeah.
How are you doing that?
You are a master all dudes pile on top of him.
Somebody trying to get on his head.
Can that work?
Can that actually be a thing?
Can you guys like ride on top of each other's heads?
I love everyone trying to attempt to do this.
This is great.
It's not seem to be working.
Oh, we got to get above the waterfall.
That's key.
If we can get above the waterfall.
Oh, no, oh, no, it's over.
Oh, who toppled Jenga.