Alright, well I literally can't afford to lose all that stuff, so I have to go get it.
Where was that piece of crap? There it was.
Okay, we're good. We're good. No harm, no foul.
I got it. Come on, give me this. Let's get out of here.
This house is a travesty.
First of all, I need to make... I need to make a furnace.
Furnace is done. And I got... okay.
I gotta put the furnace down. Let's get some iron.
I can take this and put it here.
So you make multiple furnaces. That's what I like to do.
Whenever I play this pro game that I'm a pro at.
Let's get multiple furnaces going, burning mad stuff.
I at least want to get this closed off so it's not a completely open area.
There we are. Get me on top.
And I want to make rooms. You know, it's gonna be quite the challenge.
But I'm up for the challenge.
Because this is JermaCraft, baby.
As long as it matches. What is it, three up?
Something like that.
Look at that hole. That's an instant death waiting to happen.
I can't reach down there.
Gotta make the climb. Start putting some torches down.
Those things still brewing?
Alright, castle mode activate.
Do I have any other... I don't have any of the materials, do I?
Alright. Starting to come together a little.
Dun, dun, dun, dun.
Alright. What do I got for iron?
Ow. Six bars.
Seventeen bars of iron.
Get the coal back.
Let's make some armor.
Because I really need it really badly.
Let's go with a helmet.
And I think I got... I want to get a chest piece.
Chest piece is like this, right? Yep.
Chest piece.
I want to make sure I get an iron pick.
Because that's really important right now.
And I want an iron shovel as well.
And... nice.
Alright. I'm looking for diamonds.
You know what I haven't seen anything of yet?
I haven't seen any endermen.
And people were telling me, oh well Jerma, if you see an enderman, don't look at it.
If you look at an enderman right in the face, it just starts attacking you or something.
So you're not supposed to make direct eye contact with them.
Which that's pretty damn terrifying.
If I can think of one very scary thing, it's to... it's like Medusa.
Don't look at him or he'll just murder you.
So they must be passive.
They must be... hello iron.
They must be passive.
Unless you look at them I guess.
They kind of just walk around.
I don't know. That's scary.
How many irons?
Only one.
Oh come on.
You're killing me.
I can't wait for my first enderman experience.
I'm probably going to crap my pants.
So let's get my house built more.
Because I want to make sure I can close this off.
I don't want to have to deal with this anymore.
I need to get a bed too. This is bad.
That's good enough.
So speaking of building houses.
I got a little mini story for you.
I guess while I close this up.
So my sister, my sister used to go.
Well not used to. When she was younger.
She was in some kind of like Peace Corps thing.
Not really Peace Corps.
But she went to the Dominican Republic.
To build houses for the very needy.
And the people that have no houses.
No any shelter really at all.
And she kind of used to go do this.
She used to go to the Dominican.
She'd fly down there.
This is when she was I think in high school.
She was only like 17 or so when she did this.
Which is pretty crazy.
And she used to go build houses for people.
Well I can't really call them houses.
Because obviously if you don't have an architectural degree.
You can't really build a house.
But every time I do this I think about my sister.
Building something like this.
Just making a small hut.
Just a small you know living space.
And it makes me smile.
Because my sister is really cool.
If you saw the latest grandpa video.
You already know who my sister is.
Because she had a cameo.
She was the granddaughter I guess.
In episode 3.
And yeah she's cool.
That story can lead into another story.
I have two siblings.
If those of you who are wondering.
They're both older.
Brother and a sister.
I'm 26.
Which makes us pretty much.
We're all pretty much a year and a half apart.
And it's pretty interesting living a life.
I'm the youngest. I'm the baby.
Say your jokes. Go ahead say your jokes.
But it's good being the baby.
The baby always gets like what he wants.
I need to make legs.
Do I have enough legs?
I don't think I do.
And I'm probably doing it wrong.
No I do. Nice.
So I have a full set of armor on now.
At least not as easy as it was before.
Full set of armor.
Let me know in the comments guys.
If you have a brother or sister or something.
Let me know how things are going with them.
Because if you're not close with your brothers and sisters.
You should be.
You really should be.
Because when all S hits the fan.
When things really go down.
Your family really is the only thing that's really totally there for you.
At all times.
At any given moment.
So if you're having problems with your siblings or something like that.
Just always remember that.
Really important.
So let me know.
I like to hear about that type of stuff.
It interests me.
Trying to make this all level here.
So the roof. I can essentially extend the roof.
By not building anymore.
And kind of just dig down.
With my new beautiful iron shovel.
I need to make a.
I gotta get more wood.
Look at this. They're just kind of floating in space.
I'll move them.
I will move them.
Oh will you stop it already.
How's that look?
Close this off.
I gotta make. Oh my god.
Remember like five minutes ago.
When I said that that was going to happen.
I even said it.
I just scared the crap out of myself.
By doing that.
Okay. Okay. Alright.
Make a little bit of a doorway into this room.
This is going to be the bedroom.
This is going to be the sleeping quarters.
Because that's not going to be cool.
Alright. I gotta fix this room.
A lot of stuff I gotta fix.
But as of right now. See you kind of turn the corner.
Right here.
Clean this up a little right here.
Alright. Awesome.