Yeah, you can just call me on time, Andy. How's my mic? Sound bad? I'm playing around with
settings. I think it sounds fine. That's good. All right. Hello, everybody. How are you? Let me
tweet. Let me tweet first. Tweet has been out. Very good. Thought you were playing hard time.
Yeah, I was. I was until I wasn't. So here's why I'm not playing hard time. M Dickie has
two or three iPad, Android exclusive mobile games. So I'm like, there's a superhero one.
There's one where you pick a superhero and it's M Dickie superhero world. So I was like, you know
what? Why don't we just like do it a day where I just play all the M Dickie iPad games? And then
I was told that there's like three versions of hard time and like one of them is the one to play
or something. So I was like, you know what? Let me I'll figure that out. In the meantime,
this is a highly requested game. Diablo two waiting room. You've got you've got like a month
to wait for that. And I'm not going to stream Diablo two. I don't even know if I'm going to play
Diablo two. Like I don't you know what I mean? Like I have no idea. When's the next Sims stream?
Well, I have all the mods. I just didn't want it to be like dollhouse Sims three. I'm the Sims guy.
Come on back from the dollhouse and check out the Sims three. So like, you know what? Well,
I have a bunch of fucked up mods. We'll play with it some other time. Maybe like next week
or something. So here's how this is going to go. Okay. Today, we're going to play snow runner.
And I heard it's quite a rage game. You better be ready for that one. You drive around in big
trucks and have to deliver stuff. And you have to be careful. The meltdown. I don't know if I don't
it's not possible for a meltdown. I don't have the brain power to do a meltdown right now.
No way. Even if I wanted to get really angry, it would just hit a wall and I'd be like, what the
fuck? I'm just like, so I'm still kind of coming down from the dollhouse. Even though it was like
a week ago, I'm coming off like the high of the dollhouse week. So I figured we'll just
chill today. No more heroes. Three is out too, by the way. So we're going to do that this coming
weekend. I heard it's long too. No more heroes. Three is like 17, 15, 16 hours long. The first
two were like 11 hours, 10 hours. It's a longer game. This game is going to lay waste to your
attention span. Is it? Is it a hard game? LOL. Do you do drugs? I mean, if you count a seed of
medicine, ibuprofen sometimes. No, I'm not high right now. I'm not. Although I've told you this
before, but it is a great excuse. Anytime I do something stupid. Ah, it's, it's because he's
high today. Yep. Yeah, sure. That's why I can't add six and four in less than 10 seconds. Yeah,
I can't do eight plus seven because I just got high today. You know, you guys are right.
So it's a great thing to fall back on for sure. All right, let's go. Did I tweet this? Yeah.
Welcome back. We're going back to normal. We're kind of closing the book on the last week of
insanity onto the next one. There's already plans on the next two larger streams. I'm very excited
and we're just going to do them. If they're fun, then I'm going to try to do them.
There will be more details on those soon. And also I want to make this clear. Grotto beasts
is not just gone. Grotto beast is here. It'll be here. You'll be able to buy it before the end
of the year. We're really hoping that somewhere on Christmas time, like the November, December
space, I want you guys to be able to get your hands on those. And now that all the dollhouse
stuff is done, the months of that, all that work, we're going to focus on some of the smaller
projects that aren't huge, gigantic streams and Grotto beast and the German craft server are the
next kind of coming up in line. So let's play snow runner. Let's just do it. I came on. I hope
not. When is baseball? Baseball is going to be, hopefully if it's not by the end of October of
this year, just whether you can't really play baseball like November, December, it's just not
possible. Let's go to like a dome, but I don't think we're going to go to a dome. If it's not
October, end of October this year, then that's the first thing that'll happen around like the
spring training time, February, March, hopefully of 2022. What is baseball though? Something that
I've wanted to do for over a year that was ready to go a year ago and COVID fucked the whole thing
up. So it's just done and it's ready, but I can't do it. Well, it's not done, but you know what I
mean? All right, snow runner. Am I going to, am I going to fucking hate this game? I don't know.
We're going to find out. Let me turn it up. I'm not going to play it on hard mode. By the way,
I got a 30 90. So, uh, this should look really good. Like only the second or third game I played
on this 30 90. All right, let's go. New campaign plot one. This guy's rich. He has a 30 90. No,
this guy's got a 30 90. Cause he had to pay like a hundred percent ultra premium to make a new
computer. Don't think that like, Oh wow. That's cool. No, I got like scammed. Cause I bought like
50 fucking percent over market price. Like that's not cool. Like that's, that's stupid. I did a dumb,
stupid idiot thing. Thank you for joining our recovery and maintenance effort after the
devastating flood. We need all help available to repair the bridge that collapsed. It's our only
link to the other side of the river. Disposable income, Andy. Stop it. Hey, there's a lot of new
people here. Okay. We got to like, I'm Jerma and I'm cool. First need to find a watch tower to get
a view of your surroundings. All right. I need to find a watch tower and you'll have to find a truck
capable of transport. Is this like a, do I walk around as a human? You have to find a truck capable
of transporting the materials need to repair the bridge. After the bridge is repaired, you will be
able to reach your first garage. Find a watch tower, find a truck. I was going to say, what the
hell is that? Oh shit. Plus one letter grade automatically. All right. Remove handbrake.
Start engine. Your first move should always be to scout new areas. Open the map. Your tracked
objective always shows up here. Let's go find that watch tower. Uh, okay. Is there a straight line?
It's already an F. You can't give a game an F before I've even hit the accelerate button. Okay.
We're in Michigan, Alaska, Tamir, Kola Peninsula, and Yukon. All right. So these are different
areas. So we're in the flooded foothills. Big Salmon Peak. All right. Whatever. Except that
we're in the flooded foothills, right? Oh shit. All right. So here's a watch tower right here.
All right. So can I just put a waypoint on it? Did you pirate the game? This game is on Steam.
What do you mean did I pirate the game? This game is available on Steam. I got it on Steam.
I wouldn't even pirate the game. Okay. In order to access this region, find a garage. Why can I
keep thinking of like the English way to say that word? A garage. A garage, right? I don't know why
I keep it just to say garage. Don't do like the English way. Please travel to Alaska. No. All
right. Well, what do I do? All right. Find a watch tower. How do I drive? Oh, why would the handbrake
be on? All right. Hold on. I got too much of mud. I wouldn't want to drive through this. When driving
on rough terrain, you can switch to low gear. It'll slow you down, but will lower the risk of
getting stuck. Okay. So low gear. It makes me, I won't get stuck. LB and press R to the left to
activate. All right. Low gear. I won't get stuck in the mud. I already lost. No, I didn't lose.
Your truck is all wheel drive capable. The AWD will also help in tough terrain, but will increase
your fuel consumption. Oh, should I have fuel? Hold LB and X to activate all wheel drive.
I don't need it right now. You should get off low gear when you're on a normal terrain.
This is not normal terrain. All right. All wheel drive. Let's go. Oh, there's just a guy in here.
I like that. Plus 0.5 letter grade. How is this normal terrain? It's not. All right. Turn off
all wheel drive. This only happens in the pirated version. I bought this game. I own this game.
Okay. Old people will be driving circles around you. It's raining in the mud. You guys have no,
you just don't know anything about like all wheel drive or anything. Guess what? I don't know
anything about all wheel drive either. I drive a Honda Civic. All right. Should I take off the,
let's take this off. How do I change that again? How do I change the gear? I want to go back to
normal gear. Let's hold LB and there it is. Okay. A, auto. Wait, no. How do I? No, that's
all right. Yeah, that's fine. Oh shit. No, stay in low. Oops. All right. I got to go all wheel
drive. If you're stuck, you can try using your winch and see if there's anything around that
you can attach it to. Activate the functions menu with up to use your winch. I'm not stuck.
All right. How do I do all wheel drive again? All wheel drive. How do I do all wheel drive?
It was right bumper and something else, right? What was it? An X, right? Okay. There it is. Let's
go. I'm not stuck. Fuck out of here. Why am I just driving the grass? Why am I driving on the road?
This thing is so dirty. This is too low of a truck. You're going to get stuck. I'm fine. I think I
would be fine. I would never do this drive. All right. Turn off all wheel drive. Good.
Here we go. There's a road right here. Take it off low. There's no need. All right. Well, I'm
about, I'm about, here's a road right here. All right. Find a watch tower. All right. We're back
on. We're on the road. What's nitro? All right. This drives way, way different than I thought it
was going to be on the road. Sit the brakes. All right. Hold on. Can you die? Okay. I don't
get you die in this game. All right. There's a, what should I go left? Should I go right?
No, fuck that. We're going on the road. How do I activate the rockets? Did I put in an all wheel
drive and just fucking hit the gas as hard as I can? Oh, I've been playing for like 10 minutes.
All right. I'll do it one time. You will encounter different kinds of terrains such as road, dirt,
mud, deep mud, water, rocky slides, snow and ice. Only the most experienced drivers with well-equipped
vehicles can drive on any kind of terrain. When in doubt, there's no shame in avoiding danger.
You can find out more about the different types of terrain in the codex. All right. So
can I just drive through this? Can I, can I drive through this? Yeah. All right. Well,
I'll just do this way. How high is this water? Is the water too high? All right. Should I put
in an all wheel drive? I don't know what to do. What are you supposed to do in this scenario?
All right. I'm going to drive as fast as I can over this. I'm going all wheel drive. I'm putting
on the boosters and I'm just going to hit the gas. All right. Let's go. I've played the Oregon trail.
I'll make it. It's okay. Jerry got typhoid fever. Who cares? He was dying anyways.
You can refuel here or near any vehicle that may. Okay. So how much gas? How much money do I have?
If I drive into these things, they explode. If I drive into them, fuel three gallons. Okay. How
much does that cost? Find out. No, but there's like, I don't want to, what is, how's the game
saved? How do I change that camera angle? I don't want to use the winch. Your winch should be
connected to a solid object. It's like the winch point on your vehicle and which point to an object
in your surroundings. Wait, what? Okay. Um, hold on. All right. Attach winch here and then select
the winch point. Oh, wait, what does it attach to? No, I wanted to attach it. I want to put the winch
over here. Show damage. Oh, I'm fine. I got to pull everything. Can I attach it to this? All right.
Attach winch. Put it on the back and select the point. Oh, I see. Okay. You can't do it.
Well, let's just, okay. First, why to pull your winch? Try using your own engine power to pull
yourself. What if I just drive away? No, I'm trying to rip the fucking sign down. All right. Well,
I can't do that. Honk? How do you honk? Okay. All right. I tried to do it. I'm just going to drive.
Open the function window to get more details about damaged parts. What did I just do?
What's my damage? Oh, put the winch down. Delete trailer. Stop engine. Recover. How do I see the
damage? All right. Well, fucking whatever. I'm fine. Let's go. Where's the tower? Wait, hold on.
I have the map, right? Oh, fuck yeah. Let's just drive through the trees. This is an off-road game.
You're not supposed to play by the rules. It's an all-wheel drive. Just fucking drive through the
trees. I've done this in GTA a thousand times. Watch it. Note that watchtower ahead. Such icons
will help you detect objective zones nearby. There we go. Look at that. That was simple.
I did it. Good job. You discovered your first watchtower. Discovering watchtowers will reveal
parts of the map. To repair the bridge, you need a bigger vehicle to transport materials.
Okay. Open your map. Look at your surroundings. Find a truck capable of transporting the materials
needed. Okay. So I got to find a truck, a big truck, capable of transporting shit. All right.
It's just Ubisoft. Yeah, it is. Even the menu looks like Ubisoft. This is way more elaborate
than I thought it was going to be. By the way, I thought those were guns on the left side.
Discovering watchtowers will reveal part of the map. The fog covers essential points of interest
like objectives, upgrades, and vehicles. By pressing right trigger, you can place markers
on your map to help you navigate. You can delete the last marker with left trigger or clear your
route by holding left trigger. Plan a route now. Well, we're going to go to the truck, right?
Acecam? Nah, maybe if you're good. Maybe if you're good. All right. Let's do a route.
There's a lumber mill. What's over here? Sideboard trailer. And there's a truck.
Let's go get the truck. It just drives straight line. It's not even helping me.
Okay. Well, whatever. I'm going that way. How close can I get? Is there a first person camera?
Is there a save game? What if this hurts? What happened? Am I already stuck? Do I feel rage yet?
Not really. All right. Get in an all-wheel drive. Let's go. I don't want the camera. The camera's
moving on in far, big, terrible places. Here we go. I'm good. That's deep mud, but I'm fine.
I got to turn off like the smart camera or whatever the hell this is. You're actually
pretty good at this game. Well, I mean, it's the first level. Just wait till I get the
Mack truck. All right. Now let's turn this way and just drive straight. Perfect. I don't need a
route. I have plenty of gas too. I'm an all-wheel drive. All right. Get off this. Let's go. Don't
crash into any trees. I'll be fine. Vehicle damage. What? You may repair your vehicle in the garage
or use special service add-ons and trailers. Find details about the- What? You found your first
highway truck. This truck is designed for roads, so there are no off-road options included.
Try not to fall into the swamp or drive into deep mud. Fall into the swamp? How would I fall into
the swamp if I'm just driving on the road? Okay. You can find out more about the different type
of trucks in this codex. All right. Well, let's get it. What's going on? Am I hitting this picnic
table? Oh shit. I'm like buried in here. All right. Turn on all wheel drive. Slowly try to get out of
this mud. Mud actually breaks apart physics underneath you. That's crazy. Why can I not go
through this? I'm just digging myself a hole. Where'd it go? I can't reverse. Why can I not
reverse? Can I get out of the car? Okay. I'm going to have to tow it. Okay. Winch. Let's attach the
front to this truck here. All right. Let's go. Nice. Yes. All right. I'm good. Take it off.
How would I still be stuck right here? This is stupid. Don't hit the explosive barrel.
I don't want to fuck that up. All right. Well, come on. Just drive.
All right. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. Now what?
That was just the that was just the every commercial break of return for pawn stars.
I don't know what you're saying, Chumlee. No, no, no, no, no. I don't think any of you idiots know
what you're doing in here. Pops. Pops. We got this new thing. I don't care about that shit. Get that
out of my store. Fucking idiot. Change the truck. All right. Well, how do I get in it? That was just
Mitch McConnell. All right. How about a change truck? Oh shit. All right. Wait. I can't. Can I
save that truck somewhere? I don't want to drive this thing. Didn't they just say that this thing
doesn't do off-road? All right. I need a new destination. Lumber mill. What's my what is my
actual goal? Old bridge reconstruction. Okay. I need to deliver two wooden planks. So we're
going to get this one to the lumber mill. It does off-road if you push it down and hit the gas hard
enough while screaming. All right. I need metal beams and wooden plier. Let's do the wood. Let's
get the wooden planks. It's definitely here. To complete this contract, you need to do two
objectives. They must be done in order. What? What are you talking about? They'd be done in order.
The one in the town is the storage facility. This is storage. Will you be able to pick up the
required cargo? The marker near the broken bridge indicates the delivery location. Let's go check
out the town storage. What do you mean go to the fucking town storage? I don't want to go to the
town storage. I want to go to the lumber mill because that's where the wood is. Okay. We're
going to go here. You have to do it in order. That's I don't like that. Let's go. I have to repair the
bridge. This truck is able to transport two slots of cargo. All right. Wait, this is much closer
than I thought it was. Can I just get it? I don't why do I have to do it in order? I shouldn't have
to do it in order. I'm not doing it in order. It's right here. Do the first do it in order.
Well, I don't want to do it in order. It's right here. This lumber is literally five
millimeters away from me. Wait, why is it? This thing is too big. All right. I'll go this way.
But the order. But the order. I'm going. All right. How much gas do I have? All right. Get this shit
in all wheel drive. Wait, there's no all wheel drive. There isn't? This is so scary. It's got,
it already has all wheel drive, doesn't it? All right. Slow down. Don't be an idiot.
It is safe. All right. Auto saves. That's good. All right. Metal beams and then two pieces of wood.
This guy loves yard work and big trucks. I do. It's all right. I can run over some stuff in this
like PUBG neighborhood. I'll be fine. Easy. Hey, look, they put like hazards. Oh no. I thought
that was a hole. Oh wait. Look at this. Can I drive this car? Can I change truck? Oh, come on.
I can't drive this. I can't drive the SUV. Why not? Everyone is dead. No, I think I don't know.
All right. I need to put in two pieces of metal. Cargo management. There are a couple of ways to
load a selected cargo. Automatic loading provides a simple and fast way of loading without the use
of a crane. All right. Easy. That's good. All right. So how many metal beams? Load it up.
Not enough space. All right. Well, I have enough. Cool. All right. So now I'm going to bring this.
Where am I bringing this? I have to bring this to the bridge. Where's the bridge? Fuel station
lumber mill. Would they go here? I have to bring it here. All right. Get this off. It's on the map.
Oh, shit. Okay. It's this one. That's so far away. Holy shit. That's so far away. Okay. Well,
whatever. All right. I'm bringing it to the bridge. Just drive on the highway. You may attach trailers
found out in the wilds and use them to your liking. Trailer attachments done. Wait a minute.
You may be unable to attach a variety of trailers just for a reason between distance, angle. Okay.
Wait a minute. So hold on. Should I get the trailer and go get the wood? Oh, shit. All right. Yeah.
That sounds like a good idea. All right. Where's the trailer? There it is. I need a gas station
too. What's already in here? All right. I got a new trailer. How am I going to put this on?
Can I pull it? Okay. I need to like get this. I need to move this. I'm going to try to move it.
Good. I actually wanted to dump it anyways. All right. So how do I, how do I take care of,
hold on. I need to flip it. I think I may have fucked this up bad. Come on. Pull it up. I need
to get it up on its legs. All right. Here we go. How do I get it up? Okay. So now I'm going to
attach the trailer. Attach trailer. Attach trailer. I can't. Okay. Attach trailer. No suitable
trailer. Can I like flip this? I have to flip it. I have to flip it. I have to go back on it.
I have to flip it. Got it. All right. Good, good, good. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
God damn it. I'm going to run a gas doing this. I actually flipped it. Attach to here. Let's go.
Flip it. Oh, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop. I'm good. I got it. I now attach this damn thing. See, we're fine. Everyone relax.
Trailer attached. Go. Although, wait, this is going to be hard to do.
All right. I need, I need to get, should I get gas? I mean, what the hell am I doing? I'm going
to get lumber. All right. Now we're going to go to the lumber yard. Turn this off. This game's pretty
cool. I like this. This is fun. All right. Let's go get the lumber over here. This is fun. Well,
I have to drive slow though, because I, I, I, it's pulling me in both directions. All right. Slow.
I got a big load here. You know, every time I ever saw somebody at an intersection, like a big truck,
take these turns, I always imagine like, oh, it's like, it's a red light or they have like a left
arrow and here they are taking the turn. I always feel like the person in that car is just like
pursing their lips going like, fuck, fuck, like screaming every time. And it doesn't, it always
kind of feel like that they're about to hit you too. Like I just, the truck just comes all the way
across. You're sitting there at the light and it just goes across your car. You're like, holy shit,
how can you do this? How is it possible that you can even, how? I'm almost at 700,000 followers.
Holy shit. That's way more than I had like a month ago. Hey, thanks for the follows. Really
appreciate it. Thanks for joining the stream. Yeah, you, I'm talking to you. Thank you. All right.
Let's fill this up. I need two pieces of lumber. All right. Let's go. Wooden planks. I need two out
of two. Put them into the trailer. Load it up. One, two. All right. I'm good. I have a, this is
really heavy now though. This could be a disaster. Um, all right. Hold on. Now look at this. I got a
road right here. It's just a straightaway right here. Don't do anything stupid. Don't be like,
oh, look at this. And it's driving to the water. I know you want to. No, it says go that way.
I'm not driving in the fucking water. I didn't know. No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I'm not going to fuck this up. We're going to do this the
right way. See? Okay. That's not the right. That's not what I was doing, but okay. All right. Pull
this back. I got to give myself a route. No, clear it. Clear. All right. No, this way. I'll get the,
I'll get the gist of it when I get here or whatever. Okay. There's the route. Let's do it.
When are you going to show us your disfigured face? How about now? All right. I'll give you a
face cam for this part. That's it. No, I don't do face cam unless I have to. All right. Here we go.
Am I well lit? I can't, I don't know. I can't even tell. Ew. Hold on. I got to get, I got to
get some like blood flow to my like eyes and cheeks. Okay. Okay. Be careful. See, this is why
I can't do face cam because I'm just like, what do I look like right now? What do I look like right
now? Oh, I have to play a game. What do I look like right now? No, I hate it. I don't, this
distracts me. Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. I got, I think I have enough gas to do this first mission.
Don't go too fast. I'm going to like flip this thing. Is that water? No. Can this stuff fall out
or is it attached? It looks like it's attached by the bungees or something. Stop looking. I got to
stop looking over here. Game just crashed. No, we're good. Okay. If you and I were in a fight,
like I pull out a knife and you pull out like a sword and we're like about to fight to the death.
Put the weapon down. Put it down. Just hold a mirror up. Like over here. Just hold up a mirror
and like you could, you could have like a fist or a knife in the other hand, whatever you want.
As long as there's a mirror here and we're like jumping around and dancing around, I'm going to
be like, ah, like, like fighting. What does it, what does it mean in the mirror? That's what it
looked like. That's how, that's my weakness. You'll win every single time. Uh, wait a minute. I
don't know about this part. Can you tell how deep the water is? Why does it say I have zero out of
one metal beams? Should I just go for it? All right. I'm just going to go for it. You just cover
a room with mirrors. I will forget that I was fighting you and I'll start like punching myself
in the mirror. We're good. Attach a trailer. You should approach it. Let me attach a trailer.
Is there another one? Is there, is it, wait, is there another trailer here? No. Why would they
show me that? I'm not putting, I'm not making a choo-choo train. Not right now. Turn the hints
off. Well, I might, I might need them. All right. This looks like this is getting narrow. Hold on.
I got to focus. My game seems like crashing. Oh, 30, 90, 30, 90. All right. Now we're getting a
left here, right? Come on. You can make it. It's getting to be nighttime. You see that? I was just
taking a left. I was just taking a left at the intersection. That's what they do. They're like,
oh shit. Fuck. What do I do? How do I get out of this? It's this, it's this goddamn
mirror. I don't want the mirror anymore. It's the mirror. Can I attach it? Just wait, hold on.
Recover vehicle to start zone. What? Can I push? Cargo will be lost. Oh, come on. No.
You can't blame everything on drugs and mirrors. Okay. Well, I'm going to,
what if I just quit the game? Oh, let me attach the trailer. Trailer's too far away. God damn it.
I have to do the whole thing again. Pain's truck. Fuck. How? Whatever. Recover vehicle.
Why did I detach the thing? Why? Use the winch? I can't use the winch. It broke. What has the
most damage? This thing is fine. I just need to flip it. Can I like flip it somehow? No,
I'm just going to reload. Truck recovery. Go on. Whatever. Okay. Great. This is fantastic.
Oh my God. I have to do the whole thing again. All right. No, don't fuck this up this time.
Doesn't matter. I don't have to do it in order. Let's go. All right. I'm doing this quick.
Fuck. Okay. Get the, go get the attached trailer. Put the lumber in the trailer.
Head this way. Go that way. I'm going to make, no, do it right. Do it right. Fucking mirrors. I
swear to God. All right. I'm going to go here. We're going to clear all things. Here. I'm going
to get the trailer and then I'm going to get the lumber. We're then going to go this way.
Here. Don't be a stupid idiot. Here we go. Up here. And then we're going to go out this way.
This guy high. No. I mean, look, now I get, now I understand how fragile the car is. Okay. Wait,
what? Hold on. Everything's over here. Oh, wait. Hold on a second. I can skip this. I don't have
to go to the lumber mill. All right. Don't go to the lumber mill. I can go reclaim everything.
All right. That's fine. Let's go. Don't fuck around. I need a gas station though.
I'll put the face cam on when I get to the, I'll get, I'll put the face cam on when I get to the
bridge. Okay. Wait, what are you guys saying? You don't have a crane. What do you mean? I have to,
wait, I have to go get the lumber stuff because I don't have a crane. Oh, for the love of God.
All right. Fine. All right. All right. I'll just go get, it's right here. I'm just kidding. I'll
get it. It's right here. Can I sleep? How do I pass time? Yeah. I'm sleeping. Sleep. How do I
sleep? All right. Sleep. Skip time. Skip time. Morning. There we go. Now I can see. Let's do
this again. You might be able to put a crane on the truck. All right. Let's get the lumber. No.
No, this is wrong because I need to get the, all right. I have to get a trailer. There's two of
those, but I need the, hold on a second. I need the trailer because I need to bring, I can't,
I got to bring the trailer up there. Wait, there's a trailer up there. Yeah, there is. Okay.
Where the metal is, there's a trailer up there. Imagine what your boss thinks about this omega
low. That doesn't matter to me. I'm my own boss. When was the last time you smoked a crack pipe?
I've never smoked a crack pipe in my life ever. So none. Not, no, never. My own boss. I don't want
to run out of gas. That's important. No, no drugs. Drug free. No face cam, no food. I'm going to be
all right. Okay. I will now give you exactly five minutes of face cam starting now. I fucking can't
be trusted. I really can't. What's over here? All right. The trailer is right there. Go get the
trailer. Where's this trailer? This fucking cameraman. Like, oh, stop. Who's flying the drone
around the car? Just stay here. All right. Is this it? New trailer. This thing's huge. This thing is
gigantic. All right. That just went into the windshield and I get the guy in the head.
Attached trailer. Oh my God. It's too big. How? How do I do this? What is this even attached to?
I do have to, but I have cargo. This is, I don't, this is bad. This is the wrong truck. I can't
handle this. Oh for the love of God. Are you serious? Oh shit. So I need to go get a different
trailer. So I have to go recover this trailer down here. That's what you're saying. I don't
think I can. This is stupid. Just drive. Just drive. Don't run over this person's pool.
Why is there a pool made out of concrete? Why is there a pool made out of a tree stump? What?
Why is there a concrete pool in your front yard? I can't, I see you saying I can't put this trailer
on my thing here. All right. Can I, I'm just going to, can I just drop this off of the bridge
and come back? All right. Let's think about this logically. There is where I need to get the metal
here. So what I'm going to do, there's wood down here. Can I get a crane? What do you think? Just
take two trips, my man. I, it said I had to do it in order. La la waiting, whatever. But I have to
do it in order. Remember most pools are made of concrete. Not an above ground pool in your front
yard. Above ground pools are not made out of concrete. Dump the planks? All right. Yeah.
All right. I'm going to dump the plants in. All right. Fuck it. We're doing two trips. I don't
care. What is it supposed to be made of? I don't know. It's like a plastic like bendy flat polymer
thing. I don't know. It's not concrete. It's made out of like a hard weird like polyurethane
plastic. I don't know. It's made it as something that's not metal. It's like plastic and above
ground pool. What is it made out of? I'm going to look it up right now. What's an above ground
pool made out of? Above ground pools are made out of steel, aluminum, and resin. Okay. It's made out
of resin. Here are the advantages and disadvantages. It's resin. It's made out of resin. I don't know
what resin is. I just know what it is. I just know that it's a thing that can be made out of stuff.
Resin is concrete. Resin is not concrete. Resin is like the shit that comes out of fucking plant sap.
Resin is the stuff that like a tree like has like the sap coming out of it. That's what resin is.
That's wrong. It's not wrong. All right. Here we go. Cargo management. Let's go. I need metal
beams. I need to unload this shit. How do I unload? Unpack cargo. Okay. Unpack cargo. How do I unpack
the cargo? Unpack cargo. I don't want to remove the cargo. I want to unpack it. That's exactly
what I didn't want to do. I'm gonna be all right. Everything's fine. Fuck it. Whatever. I don't even
care. Let's go. Cargo management. Give me the metal. Let's go. Okay. All right. Bye. Let's go.
Go. Go. Go. Don't drive into a wall. Resin has trees in it, right? Other way around. You know
what I mean? Say what I said backwards. This tree resin, right? Five minutes are up, by the way.
This thing is pulling to the left. I'm not doing that. Oh, wait. It's like a real car. You have
to actually change the wheel before you go anywhere. There's a Muppet Muppet streamer.
I'm just gonna do it one at a time. Ooh la la. No. Give it a rest. Not with that.
Just drive. Please. I refuse to do that with the camera on because I find it embarrassing.
I need to refuel though. I'm driving this car like there's a bunch of bees in it. Can I please
straighten out? All right. Refuel. Anytime there's a bug in the car, like a wasp or a bee or something,
you kind of just have that freak out mode where you roll down every single window in the car and
scream and just stay still. You just hope that it's like, and he just goes out the window.
I can make that, right? All right. I'm almost at that point. Can I lift this up? I'm gonna do
a tester. Okay. This is where the, this is where the catastrophe started. Can I do anything about
this? Stop. Stop moving. Stop moving. Stop moving. Stop moving. Stop moving.
I'm not gonna fall in there again. Nope. Not gonna happen. Oh, handbrake. Okay. Wait, let go of it.
Can I attach it to the, I'm gonna attach to the, here we go. Right there. Pull it. Come on. What?
Oh, it's the fucking pole. Give me a break. Flip it. No, no, no. I'll just at least get it out of
the, get it away from that thing. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. It's flipped.
I flipped it. Let it go. Okay. I feel like this is probably too dangerous.
I'm gonna deliver this first. I'm not fucking around. I'm not gonna do this now. All right.
Here's the bridge. How do I do this? Do I just drive up and it just does it automatically?
Okay. Nice. Gargo management. When unloading the cargo, you may be presented with different
unloading options as one cargo may be used to complete different objectives. While the cargo,
while the current unloading area is used only to complete your current job, there may be others
that are used in multiple contracts. Okay. Unload. Nice. The bridge is on its way,
but not there yet to click. You need to deliver more lumber mill. Okay. Nice. Thank you.
I was about to step on the gas, just drive off and just watch chat. No, it's too early for that.
Have to do a fall joke. I can't, I want to, can I just pick these up? I don't have a crane.
Somebody said I need a crane. You got to hit that yoinky splinky.
Just recover. You're going to spawn next to the lumber mill. Well, let me just see if I can even
do this. Cause if I can, that's good. Can I just go next to this and wait, can I just attach the
winch to this? Just drag it. I probably can. Why wouldn't I? Right. Oh, what the hell? Really?
Okay. Remove cargo. No, it's the new hot tech talk dance. The yoinky splinky.
This is way too dangerous. This is, yeah, it's too dangerous. Um, I'm just going to go get it.
Like, I don't care. I need to have complete level one. You know what I mean? I love how he
just ignores you all. You got to hit that yoinky splinky. I don't know what the hell you're talking
about. What is a yoinky splinky? Um, that, the yoinky splinky is somebody's legs behind their
head. Like moving. What was that? Yoinky splinky or no food. What a virgin. What are you talking
about? This dude doesn't know the yoinky splinky. Ah, what a virgin. Is this lumber mill? All right.
Yes. Why does he keep reading the worst comments? I'm not. He's pretending, right? He actually
knows what it is. I don't really. All right. Lumber mill. Let's go. And look, perfectly loaded
lumber. Although I'm just going to say, fuck it and just do this. All right. Fargo. I need
wooden plank, wooden plank. Let's go. Done. Move. Just know your meme page for the yoinky splinky.
I don't know. I'm not. All right. I'm going to move on because I don't know
nor do I need to put that much more time into knowing what this is. You know what I'm saying?
I'm just saying. That's been in my head for like a month. I don't know why.
That just keeps jumping in. I don't, I don't know how. I don't know. What setting am I on? Um,
I just normal, a career mode, I think. I don't know. All right. We're almost done with level one
and then I'm going to unlock hopefully the ice level. Slow down here. I don't want to blow it
here. Part of me just wants to take a left and just drive. No, that goes under the bridge. Why
would I do that? I was about to do it or just driven into the water. That would have been a
disaster. Okay. Very good. Learn. Not again. That turn is fucked. It is. That turn comes up on you
hard and it just dumps you if you don't do it right. We're good. I'm concerned about how you
drive in real life. I don't have a, a class truck license and I'm using my left thumb to drive a
car. This is not how you drive a real car. All right. So now what? I got promoted. I just think,
I just see that guy's face. I just, I just think of the, the pawn star as a guy. Now I let me change
that guy every time he just keeps popping in my head with like a hat on. All right. When you get
enough experience, you can get a new driver rank. Every rank provides you with new options
regarding vehicle and add on purchasing. Cool. Objectives may also require you to reach a certain
driver rank before they are unlocked. Press down to access your driver profile. Oh, now we can leave
the peninsula and reach the garage. Oh, I got 2100 bucks. Nice. Every contract completed will provide
you with money and experience points. Every watch tower discoverable will avoid you with experience.
XP allows you to unlock new driver ranks. Cool. All right. Nice. Let's go and find the garage.
It's now marked on the map. My driver ranks. I'm never going to change that profile picture ever.
That was the please don't recognize me in Team Fortress 2 Avatar. This is your driver profile.
You can learn a lot of useful information about your progress here. Cool. Yeah. There's 89 missions
in this game. Holy shit. All right. Let's go to the garage. Yep. He hates his fans. No,
no. When I used to play TF2 and make TF2 videos, I wanted to make sure that I was at like the same
exact level as everybody else. So if my name was Jerma985 and I was like, hey guys, it's me,
Jerma985. Two people on the other team we switched to spy. There'd be three snipers that were just
aiming for my head. Six people would just stand at the spawn holding their hand in the air and it
wouldn't even be a game of Team Fortress anymore. So when I was hiding, I was just another player.
So it was just completely, nobody knew. That's a guy on the other team. I didn't want to like
fuck up games. I didn't want to go in there and like there's a whole game going on and be like,
everybody, it's me. I'm here. Where's the line of people? I'm in the server now. Hello.
My name was like dogshit burrito and I had like weird avatars that weren't connected to me at all.
He's a celebrity. Oh, look at me. He's a celebrity. No, that's not what I'm saying.
Oh, watch tower. Oh, look at this celebrity. No, I'm not a celebrity. You're too important to play
TF2. That's not, that's not even what I'm saying. Oh, fuck. I'm stuck. I should have paid attention.
Can I get out? I'm not going this way. Where's the winch connected to? Get me out. I'm buried in this
mud. I can't go anywhere. Shit. What do I do? Well, how was I supposed to know there was this
weird terrain over here? Low gear. All right. We're just going in. Come on. Just dig through it. Just
dig. Is it true that you sharted when you jumped through the window? Yes. I'm just going to give
you that one. You probably just like started laughing. You're probably like, why did you even
respond to that? What the fuck? All right. I'm stuck again. All right. Now I'm going to attach
a winch to something over here. Go. Pull me. Pull me through the mud. Come on. All right. Now winch
and not winch something else. Handbrake right there. Let's go. This was a huge mistake coming
down here. Come on. Come on. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop. I don't want to screw this
up. I probably shouldn't even drive down this. Wait. Can I go that way? All right. I'm going to
go across this way. It should get me at least over here. I don't want to drive through the mud. This
car can't go through the mud. But I can't go through this either. What the fuck? What?
What do you mean? This is so wet over here. Can I not go here? It's so wet over here. Is it another
car? It's still mud. Oh, well I think I'll be all right. I can just pull myself. All right. I'm going
to stay in low gear. Let's just stay on the road maybe. Yeah. This one's not deep. It should be
okay. There's water here though. Oh God. Don't drive through that. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
What is that? That's deep mud over there. I think I just screwed myself completely.
I think I'm such a guy. Do I have to just go for it? I have to turn around. Oh my God. Give me a
break. Really? Can I just get out of the car and sprint? Drive through or no balls. Full send. Full
send. Yeah. All right. Let's laugh about the fact that I have to start over again. Where's the garage?
Okay. It's right here. Come on. Go right. How deep is this? This water's not deep at all. Hold on.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. I'm all right. Okay. I'm so close to just touching this. I just want to
touch it. There it is. Like, no. I'm fine. Look it. I'm going to be all right. Check this out. I'm
going to get up here. What in God's name are you doing? I'm trying to get close enough where I can
just drive into this and activate the fucking watch tower. Swamp joke. It's not a swamp joke.
Stop pretending. There's nothing to. I was. There's nothing to pretend. Okay. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Okay. Now that's exactly what I wanted to do.
And everybody thought I was fucking stupid. Everybody thought I was an idiot.
I'll show you in just a moment. You'll know very quickly here. Thank you. Thank you. Oh, what's
that? Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Hold on. Thank you. Let's go. Just get me out of the water.
I just have to touch this and I'll be fine. I'm not even in the water anymore. This is so stupid.
There we go. Got it. I want you to. I want every single person that said, I want you to go through
the logs and find everyone that said he's going to get stuck in the water. Fucking idiot. He sucks.
He's so stupid. He sucks at everything. And I want those people to be timed out for exactly one
second. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I'll be fine. Hold on. The laws of physics. I'm a physics major.
I just have to get far enough over here. This sucks. Stop. I'm fine. It sucks.
It's I'm do I just have to touch this and I'm going to reset. I'm almost out of gas. All right.
Come on. Oh my God. I can't move it up. Just winching myself. This is bad. It's actually
pretty bad. Can I get close enough to be able to attach to that? I'm almost there. Look at how
close I am. See the I can attach the winch up here. Come on, dude. Let's go. Yes. Yes.
Yes. All right. Let's go. I just made so much more work for myself. That was so stupid.
Pull me. Just pull me in. Pull me in. Pull me in. Pull me in. Pull me in. Yes. Touched out.
Watch tower updated. Yes. There it is. And there I just have to get on the road.
I probably have to go back. Arm in the garage. All right. I need to I get a different car.
Can I actually get out of here though? I might be able to. No. Nope. Goodbye. I'm just going to
yeah I'm just going to recover the car. Look at that. Look at that shit. Change the truck.
Thank you. Let's go. Wait. Can I attach to this? Wait. Holy shit. Okay. I should just
I can take them both. All right. Don't be an idiot. I'm going to change. Let's change to the
truck. Yeah. I'll just bring it with me. Now let me it's can I attach it? Okay. How about
attach trailer? No. Okay. All right. Attach winch to you here. And we're just going to pull it.
What's going on? I'm going to drive. Load the truck onto the other truck. I don't think I can
do that. I'm going to have handbrake on. All right. Let's go. Now I need a good route here.
Oh shit. I got to go all the way down here. God damn it. Okay. Let's get to here first.
Who trucks? Yes. I'm thinking it's abandoning this and just getting in the goddamn truck.
Don't you have a face cam? Cool. Because if I ever get in trouble, then I could just switch
to the other truck and just walk off. It's simple. Simple. Yellow shirt. Yeah. I never
usually wear yellow. You're right. I'm a blue, gray, dark, purple, black. My shirts are usually
kind of in that zone. Sometimes red. Sometimes. Hope we can make this. We can. Good. Blue. Yeah.
A lot of blue. I love blue. I'm running out of gas. Don't touch your hair.
Where's another fuel station? Oh shit. There's a watch tower here. Okay. There's not another
gas station anywhere. Should I fuel up or just say fuck it and just go?
I feel like I probably should get gas, but I'm not going to. Whatever. Did I? It is just right here.
I'm going to get it. It'd be dumb to not get it. It's right here. Don't drive over the edge.
You're going to be stranded if you don't get gas. Why don't you go to the garage?
And that was the plan before. And then I went into the swamp accidentally.
It was water here? Since when? Oh god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. That's not. Is that fucking up that truck? Oh shit. Like water is just going
into that car. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Get out. Change. Change. Change. Change. Change. Change.
Okay. Here we go. No. Okay. Fuck. I don't want to do that. All right. Let's take care of this first.
Then I'm going to drive across. Car alright. What's the damage? I think I'm okay. 100. 100.
100. 82. That's all right. I'll be fine. Yeah. I'm good. I'll be good. Now I'm going to refill
this one. Should I? I'm just driving. Whatever. I don't care. And I want to sleep too. I don't like
the darkness. I don't like it. I can just press two buttons and it's bright out.
Ram. Gas pump. No. I did that already. It doesn't do anything. I'm not doing it again.
Go faster. How far? This car is going like 25 miles per hour. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. All right.
We're good. Let's get it on the road here so I don't have to worry about it. Handbrake. Park it.
Nice truck. Some guy's sister hates you. Okay. Camera in the top left. Actually you're right.
Put it up here actually. I'll flip it. That feels so weird doesn't it? I'm not going to put the
camera in the middle. That's bad. Can I get. Am I able to get out of this? Okay. Only out of the
mud. I'm going to drive around this. This was stupid. I'm going to drive around this because
why would I do this? This is the dumbest thing ever. I just broke the fucking tree. All right.
How do I get out of here without causing a problem? No, no, no. Up here. Oh. All right. Thank
God. Now how do I get out? Watch out. I'm going to abandon the truck. I'm going to abandon the
trucker thing. I'm abandoning the trucker thing. I don't care. I don't want it. I don't want this
truck anymore. I don't like it. Wait. Go. Go. Go. No. It's going to get trapped in the fucking
lawnmower blades and I'm going to get stuck here. Oh, thank God. We're good. Finally. Okay. Fuel up
and then I'm going to drive around the creek. I'm not doing that again. Let's go. What's a better
route to get over here? Oh, look at that. Okay. We've got the creek here. I could go down. No,
there's another creek. Okay. I'm just going. I'm just going. Let's go. I'm going. Fuck it.
I'm so impatient. I can't. I'm going to get over here. Handbrake. Handbrake, please. Okay. Attach.
Let's go. Come on. This is the mouse taking the splinter out of the lion's paw. Yes. All right.
We're good. This is going. All right. I don't know if I should do this. It's getting too close.
It's too heavy. It's too heavy. Okay. Stop. Stop. Stop. Slowly stop the cars. Slowly stop the cars.
Slowly stop the cars. Okay. Stop. Handbrake. Okay. Switch cars immediately. All right. We're
good. This is Karazhan level. What do you mean? Karazhan. All right. We're good. All right. I'm
fine. Don't say those words. Are we ever going to wear a wig? Probably not. I don't know. It means
comfy. Oh, they're comparing it to the worst stream I've ever done. I don't know. I disagree. I'm
having a good time. During the Karazhan stream, I was just like fucking hate streaming. I hate
broadcasting. Like that was honestly like I just wanted to turn off my stream and never come back.
I was like I'm actually having a good time. Sunflowers? Yeah. I'll show you the sunflowers.
Next stream. I'm going to start No More Heroes 3 this coming weekend. This is far from the worst.
Yeah. They're just trying to get, just trying to push buttons. They're just trying to like
push your buttons. I get it. Okay. I got to be careful because I'm not going right.
We need to go. Where's the garage? All right. I'm going to go down this road here and this is an
intersection here. Let's figure it out. I'm just going to go this way. We hate you for real.
Oh, whatever. There's gas over here. That's fine. Good. All right.
Take the regular road. Don't be an idiot. Don't go that way. What does that sign say? That sign,
um, I don't even know what that is. That's a, that's like a truck.
Okay. All right. I thought it was a mountain. Okay. It's a don't. Watch out. It's bumpy. I get it.
Bumpy road. It's a beached whale. Okay. This is not that bad. It's pretty good.
Okay. Well, that's a problem. That's an issue. Can I go around it?
Flores. I just did like a foster do raw. Why did that all get knocked down? Wait,
can I honk on it? We'll break this. Uh, I'm going to get, I I'm getting in the other truck.
I'm not going to screw around here in the other car. First of all, turn the engine off of this.
How do I do that? The handbrake on, turn the engine off. Let's go. I'm not going to mess around
here. I have to get around this. I go through it. I can just go through here. Excuse me. Um,
excuse me. I can't go through it. It's there's a wall there. I'm going to keep all wheel drive on.
Should I be doing this? Is this the correct thing to do? I can't even see in front of me.
There's no way I'm going to be able to get the Mack truck over here. All right. Back on the road.
Garage. I'm going to the garage right now. That's the plan. All right. Well, that's what that truck
is. I can come back later. Maybe. I don't know. All right. Where do I go from here? Straight down
here. Let's go. That's enough of the face cam face cam has been allotted. Stop. I'm not just going to
drive that way. It's a bad idea. This is the first area I want to get. I at least want to see like
one or two more areas. I want to see the snow level. I want to see the, I don't know. I want to
see like the other zones. I don't want to just see the mud area. This is cool, but I want to see snow
and ice. Stop driving in the middle of the road. Why? The drunker I get, the more that I enjoy.
You drinking and just hanging out. All right. All right. There's a watch tower over here. All right.
Um, so we need to go right to the farm. We need to go down here. That's probably, that's like a,
that's going to be like the Lord of the Rings part where they're on the side of the mountain.
Like the rocks are fighting each other or whatever. Don't even tell me. Don't get stuck here.
Are you kidding me? How? Oh, how did that even happen? All right. Let's go. Keep it on low gear
and just, am I going to get stuck here? Is there another car? You have all wheel drive off.
Shit, that's right. Thanks. All right. New area farm. I wonder if there's a, a new car. Is low
gear better? I think it is because it doesn't move the tires. Look, I'm going to say something really
stupid probably. And those of you that know anything about cars and off-roading is low
gear better because the tires like grip the ground and the tires spin slower. Is it like,
oh, the tires spin slower and that grips the ground harder. That's correct, right?
There's more torque, right? It spins slower. Yeah. Okay. So I had it right. There's less
displacement to the ground. Yeah. Yeah. Nice. Um, what's even over here? Not really anything.
All right. This is where it gets dangerous. I'm kind of afraid of this part, but let's just go.
Whatever. Screw it. I got plenty of gas. I'm going to make it. I hope it's very rocky over here. This
is bumpy. This is getting bumpy. Do this in real life. I would have died an hour ago.
Stream would just be live of wherever I ended up. So no, the camera would just be pointing to the
sky. So whatever like ravine I fell in. Nope. No, thank you. Leave it to the professionals.
All right. We're almost there. This is, I don't, I got to be careful here because this is really,
really muddy. I'm going to try to drive away from that because I don't want to get stuck in that.
We avoid it. Don't tip. Don't tip. You're good. All right. I got to assess the situation here.
I kind of need to, uh, go around the left side. Uh-oh. Uh, okay. How are you supposed to do this?
Don't fall in the water. Oh my goodness. Don't fall in the water. I can't move the car.
All right. Just all wheel drive, floor it, pull. We're good. When does the stream start? Uh,
starting soon. No, no, no, no. Attach here. Right here. And then we're going to go all wheel drive,
pull floor it. Nice. I made it up. I did it. We're almost there. I'm almost in the garage.
I've almost completed chapter one. I've almost done it. I don't think I have to be in a low gear
right now. Yeah, this is fine. Oops. Hold on. In the grass. Remember the road you avoided in
the beginning led to the garage. Yeah. We got to do it the hard way. There it is. Nice. Finally.
I made it. You've discovered your first garage. What you have done so far is the meat of the game.
Explore and discover watchtowers, complete contracts, earn rewards and find garages
to improve or buy new vehicles. Vehicles. All right. So what do I do? Upgrade location
discovered. Get upgrade. You can find upgrades in the world. They may not apply to your current
vehicle, but will be useful for others. An all wheel drive powertrain that can provide torque
connected. Not available for the current truck. Okay. Whoa. What happened with that? Garage
discovered. You can use the garage to turn your truck into a real monster. All right. 850 bucks.
What do I do? Customize. The garage is used to store, upgrade, customize, buy and sell vehicles,
but also for traveling to other regions. Okay. Holy shit. All right. The engine. You can upgrade
the engine. That means more power. That's what I currently have. Explore Michigan to find this.
I don't have any of these things. Stock gearbox. More control. Suspension. What the hell?
I want that. And I want huge tires. Ooh, wait a minute. Highway all-terrain or all-terrain?
What do I have? I have 8,800 bucks. On-road good, off-road average. Off-road. Okay. On-road average,
off-road good. Mud average. Mud good. Right? I think I want mud. Mud good. But on truck nuts.
Excellent on-road, but this is okay. I have terrible in mud right now. I definitely want to get,
who cares about on-road? It's a regular road. You're going to be fine. Let's go with,
let's go with mud. Let's go with the 31 inch AS2s. I think so. A winch. Whoa. A low strength winch
set up with a dedicated battery unit. Not as powerful as more common variants. It can operate
even when the vehicle's engine is turned off. That's a lot of money. I'll keep the stock one.
Engageable lock? Snorkel? What do you mean a snorkel? A mushroom-shaped snorkel that protects
your engine from taking in water. Wait, wait. Actually, I put my mouth on that and breathe?
What does that, what do you mean a snorkel? I gotta get that, right? Yeah, I want the snorkel
because then I can go into water. Frame add-ons. Can't do any of these. Can I do any? Oh, rear
bumper. I have 10. Oh, I definitely have to get the park ranger beacon, right? Yeah. I want the
Jurassic park vehicle. Alright, front bumper. I like that. Miscellaneous. Side pipe thresholds?
Sure. What about rims? Why would I want rims? They just don't, they just get really dirty.
I can change the color. Did I make it the German 985 mobile? Okay. Can I do any other colors?
Well, I can do that one at least. That's fine. The Jurassic park vehicle is that color, isn't it?
Bobbleheads? Oh! Auto! I can't believe there's an auto! Accessories. Hearts, ace of spades,
autumn leaf, golden leaf, pine tree. Uh, how about um, dream catcher, hype monster,
ranch. How about let's go with uh, let's go with rental car. There. Stickers. Shut up and take my
winch. Light my fire. Your adventure. Should I do what like those people do when they have like,
Clinton Gore, like 1998, like still on their car. Bush Chaney. I'm in charge. Wild. Off-road. How
about his mud? I like that one. Exterior stickers? Oh god. Hot warning. Harsh driver. I kind of like
the bullwinkle one. I like mud monster. Swamp surfer. Off-road club. King of the hill. Mastodon.
Wing mechanic. It's crazy that like, all these could be the label of every craft beer I've ever
had. Oh, the crazy elephant! Oh, I like the tiger. Hide. Pedal to the metal. Pumped up. Young
driving. Top gear. Truck. Truck. For mother Russia. I like this one. This reminds me of like, every
90s fucking beverage that you had that was available. That was off-brand. That wasn't like
Pepsi or Coke brand. I like it. Windshield stickers. Don't these get in the way? Where's um,
live laugh love? Where is it? I hope it's here. Must eat mud. Just putting that shit on an off-road
car. I like must eat mud. That's a good one. Bulldog. Dolphin. Cobra. Stavortooth. How about
the, uh, how about the cobra? All right, cool. I wish I had more to do. Well, at least I got better
tires. Can I clean it? Truck store. Oh, man. Are you serious? All right, truck store. This is your
truck store. You have to be a certain rank. Oh, Chevy CK 1500. What else is there? 126,000.
What is that? Wait, wait, you, I can actually buy these? You can drive around in a crane? Why?
There's a lot of cars. Is that a fire truck? Oh, that's pretty cool. Highway. Heavy duty. Heavy.
Off-road. Scout. Damn it. I want this so bad. That sucks that I can't have it. This truck is
not available in North America. What? I can't buy this because I live in America? Not available in
North America? Am I getting like country gated? Why? Oh, in game. Oh, I was going to say that's
insane. Sorry, sorry. These are, these are only available in, uh, in like Russia. These are only
available in like EU. Only available in Europe. I was desperately trying to figure out what that
actually meant. All right. Well, I got my cool car now. Some interesting trucks or resources can
only be found in other locations. Let's do some traveling. Prepare your truck for transportation
by using the retain function with X. Retain. Vehicle is now placed in the truck storage.
You're ready to travel. Go to the global map with Y. Oh shit. Okay. You're currently in Michigan.
Let's go to Alaska. Let's go to Alaska. Yes. Awesome. Snow time. Let's go. You have a garage
waiting for you here. This is your primary base of operations for the time being. Let's get inside,
select the garage and the objects tab and enter it. Garage. This is what I was looking forward to.
We finally get to play the title. All right. Truck storage. Where's my truck? DLC. Oh, look at these.
There's so much cooler. That's, I want this, but I don't have enough money. Why is it $20,000 to buy
this? Oh, I can sell it. Oh, I can sell this and buy this. What's the DLC? How much does it cost?
Can I deploy it? Holy shit. I actually do own it. Why do I own? I own the DLC. Did I buy the like
exclusive edition? How do I own this? Are you kidding me? That's awesome. I'm so happy. Just
sell it all and just put like a bunch of truck nuts on the car. I think I bought, I must have
bought the digital deluxe version of the game. Oh hell yeah. I want to see how this works.
All right. What am I? I'm going to sell one so I can upgrade, I think. No, I just want to see what
it looks like. Over to Alaska. Now, you know, the basics of the game is up to you to scout,
accept contracts and upgrade or buy new vehicles and conquer the wilderness. Completing contracts
in Alaska might be tougher because of the weather conditions. If you want to be more prepared,
you're free to come back to Michigan and explore Alaska later. Let's, hell yeah. All right. I'm
going to go, I want to just take a look for a minute. I was going to go up down. I was going
to, I went into the watch tower. I'm going to go down the road. All right. We have enterprise.
Let's look at how much shit there is here. Type, line, instruction, oil delivery.
And this is very overwhelming. Drilling equipment, drill rig, from water to land,
oil delivery. Okay. Deliver to the service site. I need oil barrels. I need to deliver oil barrels
to a bunch of places. Where do I get the oil barrels? Okay. I'm invested. Let's go. Wait,
it's locked. Why? Oh shit. I have to go in the straight line here. We've got an urgent contract
for you. Local fuel company is building a pipeline and just hired us as a subcontractor.
Deliver everything they need fast. I need service spare parts times two. Okay. Service spare parts
times two. You have to go through the tunnel that connects locations to reach your target destination.
So service spare parts are here at the service hub. And then we have to go to the pipeline thing.
All right. Let's go. I'm ready. Buy and sell trailers. All right. Wait, I need something.
How am I going to put oil barrels on here? All-wheel drive is always on on this thing.
I need a trailer. Put them on the seats. Just put them in the back seat. That's very slippery.
This is very slippery. Maybe I should get the big thing. I wonder if I can pull them with the
winch. Does this thing have a winch? Yeah, I got to put snow tires on here. I have no idea what's
on here right now. Uh, this seems to do okay in the snow. This is important. Press one for auto.
Oh, he's not even in here. Oh, this is the first person. Cool. All right. Service spare parts.
I can load it. What do I get out of this view? Two, one. Oh, load. I can't load it. Shit. Well,
hold on. Yeah, I can't put it on here. What is this? Your task are small additional objectives
that will often make your life easier. What opportunity to earn money that discover when
exploring the world. All right. What is this task? Name's Pete. I work for a transport company called
Alaskan Transit. We've had an unfortunate accident that's resulted in containers of tools stuck in
the river. Can you locate them and get them to the base? Yeah, sure. Yeah, I need it. I need a
bigger car. I'm going to take the big thing. I have an important question. Do you freeze your bread?
I don't. I mean, if you buy more than one loaf at a time, I guess maybe you could do that, right?
I don't freeze my bread. Let's go to the garage. There's a trailer here. All right. I'm ready. I
freeze my bread. Yeah, it lasts longer. But if you're going to eat it, if you know you're going to
eat a loaf of bread in a week or two, why would you freeze it? It's for the crunch. So it's crisp.
Why are you eating crispy bread? Are you talking about like toasting it? Why does it need to be
crunchy? When you toast it, wouldn't it? The moisture kind of be weird. I don't know. I feel
like it would just start dripping water. Where's the garage? It evaporates. It doesn't. I just did
it. It's a little dry though. Yeah. No, I'm not freezing my bread. No, thanks. I'm taking the big
thing. I'm going to put some new tires on it. I'm going to sell some shit too. Why not? All right.
Truck storage. Which one of these do I not give a shit about? This one's awesome. This one's really
cool. This one's ugly. Oh, wait, hold on. Highway mud tires, all-terrain. All right. This is the
mud. This is the one that I can, is going to be good for the snow. This one is a highway car.
It says all-wheel drive switchable. This is worth $40,000. I'm selling it. Now I've got $40,000.
All right. Let's go like this. Customize it. I'm just gonna, I got to go too crazy here. Tires.
Here we go. What does it have right now? This is on-road, off-road. Mud is average,
which would be snow too, wouldn't it? On-road, poor. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Keep this. Who cares
about on-road? Yeah. Definitely keep these on. Okay. Get a snorkel on here. Saddle high. Roof
rack. A roof-mounted trunk carrying supplies, fuel, and some basic repair tools. Oh yeah. Let's go.
Sideboard bed. High saddle. Yeah. And give me the bed. This looks pretty good. All right. Rooftop.
What does one even mean? 1X. All right. That's good. Front bumper. Solaneous. I like the orange.
No, I don't. Big horns. What is this DLC? It's a bowl. No, I like the, like this one.
Can you change tires? I could. Get auto in there. And then, um, where is it? Mud. And then we put
the mud monster here. And then mud up. Mud up or shut up. Hide the fire. Looks good to me.
I don't think I can do chain tires. Yeah. They're not unlocked. These would be good for now. All
right. Let's try it. Uh, what the hell? That was weird. Now, should I get? I have a couple things
going on here. Let's do the, uh, okay. I want to do the pipe thing. Let's go to the service hub.
Let's just do, let's get this out of the way. And then where's this other thing that has the
parts in the river or something? Containers in the river. Yeah. This one. Oh shit. It's right here.
Perfect. All right. All right. Now let's really actually move. Let's go.
Where are those markers I just put? All right. This has got a all wheel drive too. Doesn't it?
Oh yeah. It does. This thing is a monster. There's an Easter egg. If you hit 80 miles per
hour with this truck, which way should I go? Stay on the road. It's so distracting. It's too
dark. You're being unsafe. Well, I'm just trying to. How do I turn the headlights on?
I don't know how to turn the headlights on. H L B plus B. Oh God. I can see. I haven't been able
to see this whole time in the dark. I was like, it sucks being out at night. You can't do anything.
All right. Here's the parts. We have a spare parts loaded up. Looks good. Deliver those parts.
You're playing with a controller. Omega lull. Yeah. Why? Wait, you.
Why would you want to play this game without a controller? W A S D in the mouse does not
translate well to car movement. It just doesn't. It's not a natural turning of the wheel motion.
Like being able to actually have a stick move left, right up. A D no. And the trigger is almost
like a gas pedal. It's like step on the gas, not pressing W with like your index finger. It has
like a little bit of resistance. It's like pulling, stepping on the gas. All right. What
do I need to do first? All right. I need to deliver these to the pipeline, but wait,
uh, I gotta go here first. They're everything. We're going this way. Let's go. Oh, there's a
watch tower right here. Do you get the watch tower first? Are you going to get the steam
upper decker? I don't, I, are you talking about the steam, uh, game pad like switch thing?
I don't know why you're calling it an upper decker. Like you taking a shit in somebody's
tank in their bathroom. What do you, why up? Why are you calling it an upper decker? That's
freaking me out. Are you calling it that? Hey dude, you're going to take an upper decker
in the steam box? Um, I know. Why did you say upper decker? I need to know what you mean.
It's called the steam deck. Yeah, but a steam upper deck. I just imagine a guy playing that
thing on the toilet. And like, that's why you called it that because he's taking a shit playing
the steam deck. It's being correlated that way. I'm like, yeah, no, no, it's nothing wrong way.
I was terrified to go this way because it was weird. I'm going to go this way. I'm going to,
I'm trying to go on the actual road up for a decker. Here we go. All right. I just want to
get the tower. Shit. This is supposed to be good in the off road. I hope I don't get stuck. This
is half a winch. Thank God. Blow it down. I'm in deep, deep snow right now. But to answer the
question, I, well, I don't know. I might get the steam upper decker. No, I'm good. I can move.
It depends. It really depends on that thing. If it has a game gear battery or not,
like if that thing doesn't last from a Vegas to LA plane ride, I don't want it. If lock was H
if law, they didn't teach me that. What's a diff lock. I heard it lasts about
four to nine hours on depending on load L B Y. Div log is only available on low gear.
Is this, should I have these both on whenever I'm trying to go through rough terrain?
So this turns this thing into like a tank, right? Like treads. I have no idea what this does,
but holy shit. I'm about to go up a hill. This is not going to happen.
I don't think this is going to happen. Very concerned about this. Okay. All right. Didn't
even give this truck a chance. All right. Left or right? Uh, right. Hopefully. I hope I don't get
killed here. This is a comfy game. I did want my first screen back from the dollhouse to be,
to be like a comfy stream. I mean, hang out, man. I got to turn off this lock because I can't move.
Well, it looks like we're going this way because I can't turn the tires.
This is stressing me out. I mean, it's kind of, it's, it's not a high stress. I feel like we're
going to get a probably a high stress few streams this weekend because I'm starting no more heroes
three. Probably did that on, I want to, I don't know, Saturday started on Saturday because I
really do want to go back to being on the weekends again. How am I going to get that? I, am I going
to activate this? Whatever I'm going for. I don't care. I just have to get, get close enough.
Careful. I'm going to be careful. Did I cliff? No. Hope I can get out of this. All right. Unlock it.
Come on. Yeah. We'll be going back to Saturday, Sunday streams, Friday, Saturday, Saturday,
one or two times a week depending on what we're doing. Uh, we're at, we're going to have to do
at least two streams in a row because of no more heroes. God, what is all this? Where am I? Oh,
what? Oh, I'm up here. Cargo container. I can't get this right now. All right. Shit. I need to do
this. This, this was worth a lot of money. All right. I know what I'm doing. I'm dumping the
cargo here and I'm going to pick this up because I need these two. Yep. Okay. I need to get these
two things. This thing not back up. Let's go to the pipeline. No, no, no, no. What do you mean?
Why, why, why? I need a crane. Oh shit. Okay. Can I, am I just going to break if I drive across this
thing? I feel like this is a rickety ass bridge. I am scared of going over this. How much do I
weigh? Like 40,000 pounds. This doesn't look sturdy at all. I think this is a good idea.
Easy. Okay. I'm on it. All right. Turns out it was safe. Now I got to get out to the road here. Can I
just drive straight? All right. Straight. And then we're going to go up here where the, the pipe
things are. All right. Let's go. Get out. It was a 27 point turn. Yeah. Well, when you're in,
when you're in like an original Burger King chicken sandwich length car, you have to be
fucking careful. Oh, I want one of those now. So bad. Am I doing this right? Is there, was there
a tree? You can't just pull, just pull me through the, just go. What the hell? I can't see anything.
Why did I go this way? What the fuck am I doing? I can't, why would I drive through the woods?
What the hell am I thinking? It's so dark. Go to bed. Just wake up in like an hour. Come on,
back up. Back up. Back up. Oh, what a comfy stream. I'm working on it. Pull. Come on. It's so close.
All right. Pull me this way. There we go. All right. Stop. This is a great view actually. Keep
this view. Shit. No, I can't see. Is this a tree over here? No, it is a tree. I didn't even load in
my game. Fuck. No. There's a tree on every side. This is the worst possible thing I could have done.
This is the worst possible thing I could have done. Oh my God. I think I have to pull myself
backwards. Fuck. Hold on. I think I'm okay. Wait. Hold on. There's a spot right here.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn. Strain it out is the opportunity right here. Make sure the tires
are straight. Go. Yeah. Stop. I can't see anything. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where's the road? I'm not even halfway. I turned around. How did I turn around? I'm facing this way
now. How? What? I don't understand. What are you talking about? I didn't turn around. I've been
going the same direction the whole time. You put these mirrors down. Hold on. Settle down. Relax.
Not a big deal. No, I'm going the right way. Why is it looking like that?
All right. Attach. I have to pull myself this way. I feel like I was playing Madden. I wanted to
select the guy all the way to the right so I could run and try to fucking kill the quarterback.
That's what I did every time. Every play. I've got to take a hard right. That's what I'm going for.
There it is. Okay. There's an opening. All right. I'm going to get through here.
There we go. Just go right through the needle right here. Where's the next tree?
It's right in front of that, isn't it? Which way are the tires turning? Looks like a pretty
straight shot right here. No, there's a bump. There's a bump, but give me the first person.
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. All right. Okay. Straight ahead. Straight ahead. Fuck. All right. Now what?
I think I can just go straight. I need the first person is probably better here.
You see a road yet? Where's the road? Is that an opening? All right. Listen. I'm going to. Okay.
Careful. This is the dumbest thing I've ever done. I don't know why I did this. I could have
reset 20 minutes ago. All right. We're going to turn this way and pull it. No, wrong way. Good.
Good. Okay. Now I got a shot this way. Is this ever going to end? I'm trying to go this way.
Fucking God. I give up, I think. It's time to give up. It's time to give up. I'm facing. I've
given up. I don't think I can do this. I need to keep a marker here. Delete all markers and put one
right here. My God. I've made it harder. I was here and I could have just gone this way and now
I have to go through this. What happened? I'm so confused how I did this. What did I think was
going to happen? I'm so distraught. I don't understand. Okay. Settle down. I'm going to get
through this shit. You and me. We're going to be, we're going to get through this together.
Oh, he doesn't even know, dude. Hold on. First and 10. 40 yard line. Okay. Got a, huh.
Sprint. Tackle. Tackle. I don't care. Come off sides. Heard a, did I break it? What happened
to the winch? Winch is okay. I got to, if I just go straight from here, don't be an idiot. Here we
go. Oh, by the way, every time I played Madden, I just selected the safety every time and we're
just running around with them. By the way, I think some of you may have like not been here when I
talked about how my brother and I used to play and I would lose like a hundred plus points to zero.
I would just throw Hail Mary's and miss every time. Okay. I think I can back up and recalibrate
this and just go this way. God, what am I doing? All right. I'm going to go to the right. It looks
like an opportunity to go to the right side here. No, it doesn't. I'm fucked. I'm just restart the
game. I have to restart it. There's no coming away from this. I'm never going to get out of here.
I have to go that way. Waiter. All right. Fine. I'll, I'll get, I'll do it. We're going to,
I'm going to lose like two, 3000 viewers. I'm going to lose like 10,000 of you, but I'm going
to go for it. As long as I can turn the wheel. There we go. All right. Keep going. Now if I go
to the right. Yeah. Okay. This will be all right. I need to pull in a different direction though,
because I don't want to get too close to this tree. We're going to pull this way. We're going
to grab one of these trees over here on the right. This one here probably will do it.
Uh, no, easy. Is it even attached? What is it doing? What does it even attach to? Um, what the
hell? Pull it. God, let it go. Come here. This one back here. Oh, hold me. No, no, don't. Okay. I'm
fine. Don't back into that tree. Now we're going to pull it this way. Let it go. I'm going to grab
this side here. That's closest. This one right here. I'm going to grab this tree back here. Pull
it. Where'd it go? You're not in reverse. Oh, hold on. I got to grab the tree on the right.
Come on, dude. Come on. Now we're going to back up. Back up. I'm so screwed here. I don't think this
is going to happen. The Venga bus is coming. So the poor video game in-game character has not
eaten and you just have him stuck here. Okay. I obviously can't go that way. I'm going to try
something different. Oh, that's the definition of insanity is trying the same thing without
the same results happening. They keep going. You keep doing the same thing with the same results
happening. All right. I figured it out. I got it. I wasn't in reverse the whole time. Now this
will make sense. Just wait. I'll get out of this. Don't worry. Everyone can relax. Look, I know you
guys are making like dinner or something anyways. Hold your residence sleepers till I get out of
this. Well, actually, no, go ahead. You go to sleep. I'll wake you up. I promise.
He's just smashing the horn. Stop hitting the horn, dude. I don't know if I can get out of here.
I don't think I can get out of here. Fuck. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You know what? It's probably
just going to be easier if I just drive this way. You know what I mean? Like, watch this.
It's going to be. I'm just going to turn the whole fucking car around. I'm angry at this point.
Watch this. Ah, ah, ah, ah. Got it. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. All right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Don't do anything stupid.
Here we go. Drive. Oh my God. Drive the car. Boys and girls, we got it. I'm ready. Everything's good
to go. Here it is. There's our exit right there. Nice and easy. Back it up again. We're still
fucked. And no, we're not. Look at that straight shot right there. You see it? Here we go. Come on.
Nice and easy. Just thread, thread, thread, thread, thread. All right. Left or right?
I'm going to say stay right. Right here. Fuck. There's a tree right there. It's all right.
It's so close. I did the same thing. Yeah. This time I'm getting out of it because look. Wait,
I did. I did the same. Oh, no, I didn't. I did the same thing. I went to the same place. No,
I didn't. I went to the same spot. I went to the same spot. I did go to the exact same spot.
Oh my God. What are you? You're right. You guys are right. Okay. Holy shit. You're right.
Oh my God. You got to be kidding me. Okay. I'm done. All right. I'm done. We're going to go this
way. I don't know how I did that. What an idiot. What a fucking total, just absolute moron. Okay.
I'm going to try this again. Go this way. Turn the wheels. Come on. Okay. That's this is a
different path. There we go. I got it. Right. It's right there. I see the road. All right.
Don't panic. Don't freak out. I think this way is the correct way. Can I fit through that?
I think I can fit through this. Can I fit through here? I think I can fit right here. Like right
here. Oh, fuck. Yeah. I'm almost there. Okay. Slow down. What's in front of me? Yeah. Let's go.
I did it. Thank God. I can finally move on. Oh, it feels so good to get out of that. All right.
Let's deliver this. Hey, Larry, you were you were like an hour late with the deployment. What
happened? I had traffic. Oh, yeah. Traffic. I'm in Alaska. There's no cars. All right. Let's go
tasks. This one here. I got the repair parts. Track it. Let's go. You wasted 40 gallons of fuel.
Yeah. I want one of those long chickens from Burger King. So bad right now.
Stay on the road. How many viewers did we lose? A thousand. They were the smart ones. Find all
the tutorial hints. I know what I'm doing. Okay. Where do you buy the crane? Everyone keeps saying
I need the crane for some of these other missions. I have a crane. I do. Why do you own a red sex
t-shirt? Because somebody people made I look it was a reddit thing. I don't know. I have no idea.
I just somebody linked me a thing where he's like, Oh, look, you're like a serial killer. And I'm
like, Oh, okay. I laughed for a second. I was like, Oh, ha ha ha. German with a serial killer with
the AI technology. I woke up the next day is on the front page of every reddit and people thought
it was a real thing. And everyone just associates me with a fucking like a murderer. That's like
50,000 upvotes on the front page. It's like I just like to close my phone. I was like, Okay, well,
I guess we're doing that now. Alright, 1400 bucks, 180. This is now open. So this opens to
another spot here. But I want to go. I kind of want to do that. Timber. Hi, the sawmill near
the port is running out of wood. So we'll pay to have some delivered. Log loader crane is recommended.
I don't have one of those though. I guess that's on the way. So again, explain to me how I get a
crane because I don't understand. I get it here. Trailer store or something. The other car has a
crane. Oh, okay. You don't have a crane. I hope the murderer joke at least brought attention to the
dollhouse stream. No, I don't care. It's funny. Logging missions are kind of hard, my king.
We'll find out. Is this the sus guy? Join me on the next stream. The imposter is sus guy plays
werewolf. The imposter is sus guy plays mafia. I don't even play among us. Okay, let's see which
hat would have which one of these cars has a crane. Alright, so it would say it whichable
compatibility. How can I tell if it has a crane? I mean, that looks like a crane on top of this.
If I was a crane, I'd be that thing, the blue thing on top, but we have to mess with it.
I could buy something now. Can I have 30,000? You know what? Let me take a look because if I sell
a couple of these, I can get like $50,000. What do I actually need? What should I actually buy? Oh,
I know exactly what I want. How much is this? I don't have it unlocked. What the hell? That's
annoying. Alright, let's customize it. Tires are fine. No, no, I want mud. I don't have anything
unlocked for these. That's not good. What is it currently using? What's the difference? Get the
freeze. Fine, I guess. Mud pour. That's not good. Okay, well, whatever. Oh, geez. Oh, geez. Alright,
there's the crane. Is there a better crane? Nah, keep the crane on. That's what I'm using it for.
I like that. Twisted metal is like missiles. I like that. I like that. I want it to be like a fire
engine. Yeah, that's better. Alright, cool. Let's go pick up those things. So now how do I use the
crane? I'm sure we'll find out. Alright, we need to go down here. This is worth like
three or four thousand dollars or something crazy. This car is way too big to go in the woods,
so don't worry, I'm not gonna do that. Let's go this way. I'm gonna have to just kind of go around
here and up this way, I guess. It's really the only way I can really go besides here, but is
this water? I don't think I can drive through this. That's definitely the better way to go,
but I don't know how deep that is. Is it ice or water? Let's try it. I'll give it a try.
This thing's terrible in mud. We'll find out. I'm gonna turn around if I don't want it.
I don't want to do it. That's a scary horn. That's the kind of horn that makes you just
jump at the red light. That's the kind of horn that gives you a stomach ache. It's just so st-
shit. It's okay. Is it ice or is it water? It looks like- I don't know. What? It's ice? Alright,
it's ice. I'll be alright. I have no control over this car. I just held left on the stick as hard
as I could. Oh lord, hold on. Wait, this is always on? This is ice. That's fine. Face cam,
good sir. You've earned five minutes of face cam. I'm gonna have to blink my eyes a bunch.
What a great time to turn it on when I'm like- I just realized I haven't blinked in an hour
and my eyes are watering. Yeah, my eyes are full of water right now. Anybody else have really
watery, liquidy eyes? My eyes seem to be so watery all the time. If I go outside and it's windy out,
at all, tears will just be streaming down my face, down my cheeks. I've got very sensitive
eyes. Pinching your nipples helps with- I'm not even gonna finish the sentence. I think I can-
no, keep it on. I don't wanna get stuck. No, I don't need to. It's not that deep. This thing's
pretty good in off mud terrain. You're a lizard. You just lick them. I am like a lizard mouth. I'm
always like kind of moistening my lips. I'm always going like this. I always bite my lip and I was
like like this. If I could lick my eyes with my tongue, I probably would do it. It'd be like-
happened all the time. Capstick Charlie, yeah. We're getting there. I'm not going that way.
You're a fucking freak. Hey, I still don't have any gray hairs. Not that that like means anything
for what you just said. I don't know why. I was like flexing on you for some reason. Like,
oh yeah. Well, you ever think of a freak? I don't have any gray- I don't know. It didn't really
correlate together, but whatever. I turn 36 really soon and I don't have any gray hairs.
You dye your hair. I don't dye my hair. I'm afraid of dying my hair. I feel like it's gonna fall out.
What about one? It already is falling out. Yeah, I know it is. It is. I can't stop that. It's called
age. All the garlic and radishes. Don't eat too much garlic. Don't eat too many radishes.
Only eat them when you feel like you want a snack.
Don't do the YouTuber quirky hair color thing. I- I'm not gonna do the YouTuber
quirky hair color thing. Don't worry. I'm not gonna do like the hair color YouTuber thing.
Garlic snack? Yeah, well not- maybe not nowadays, but like, I don't know,
George Washington used to like rub garlic on his feet to like cure his fucking cold.
You know, you know, garlic has something called allicin in it. It's actually really good for you.
When you crush garlic and it stinks, you're actually smelling the chemical reaction to
create allicin. It's very, very good for you. Hey, look it up. That's fine. It's all right.
I'll be the smartest one in the room today. Maybe not every day, but maybe today I will be.
No, A-L-I-C-I-N. Not like A-L-I-S-O-N. That's suedo science. It's not. It's like documented
fucking proof. All right, let's go. You went to the wrong place? No, I didn't. Yeah, I did.
Do I need a crane to pick up the logs? Timber. Log loader crane is recommended. All right,
well let's- I'm gonna get them I guess. Let's pick them up. What? Okay. All right. Anchor. Okay. How
do I pick it up? Attach cargo. How do I attach it? Pick it up. Attach cargo. It's the wrong crane.
Whatever. I need a logging crane for the logs. Fine. I'm just gonna go do the- I'm gonna-
We were talking and so I didn't pay attention. Back on the road. Let's go. Come on. Get fired?
I'm not. Put this shit away. I'm gonna fix your shit. I just did. How do you drive with
passengers in the car without getting lost? That's what GPS is for. Garlic's really good for you
though. I would say you should add some more- Well, hold on. I'll hit this thing. Garlic is very,
very harsh for some people. You know, if you have acid reflux problems, if you're trying to do like
kind of like a low FODMAP diet, if you have irritable bowel kind of problems, you don't
really want to eat too much of it. But if you can handle it, it's really, really good for you.
It's for vampires. They have a garlic burger at Burger King. I don't think I want that. I want-
I like fresh garlic. Garlic that's fresh, smashed, and immediately used either to put in the pan
or like garlic bread or something. I don't- No. Give me the real stuff. I want the real stuff. I
don't want the fake shit. I'm not saying that it's fake whatever they use at Burger King or
whatever, but it's not the real shit. It doesn't- They don't smash it in the fucking restaurant.
What happened? Why don't you grow fresh garlic? I don't know. I never really thought to.
I'm not saying it's fake. I'm just saying it's not real. No, I just- It's not- It's real. It's not
fresh. Fresh squeezed, fresh pressed at the restaurant. Like somebody just smashes it
with a knife and like smashes it with a knife. You know, you turn the knife sideways and you
smash. Spread, spread, spread, spread, smash. Spread, spread, spread, spread, spread.
Sink, sink, sink, sink, smash. Spread, spread, spread. You know what I'm talking about?
That's what I do. Where are we going? All right. Don't be an idiot. All right. I gotta go right.
Hey, watch the road, buddy. I'm fine. This is the second time I've heard you rant about garlic
because I find it to be an incredibly important addition to your diet. Your armpits smell like
garlic. They do. All of you- Okay. Here's the thing. Garlic like permeates every inch of your
body. It like crosses your like brain barrier and it like goes through all your pores, right?
From what I've read. I don't know how true it is. So that's- If you eat garlic, you smell like
garlic. Especially if you eat a lot of it. Don't eat too much of it. Don't eat too much. You shouldn't
be eating too much of it anyways. This dude's got garlic brain? That's what I've heard. Garlic just
permeates like every single like cell in your body. You become more garlic than person when you eat
it. It's garlic science. It's suede of science. I don't know. Let me just pick up my boxes. Okay.
Here we go. Activate anchor. Get that crane out. Catch the crane. All right. Lift it up. Why is-
Why am I moving? Why am I moving? Anchor, anchor, anchor, anchor, anchor in the ground. Anchor. Let
it go. What's happening? What's wrong with me? Put the handbrake on? Oh shit. You're right. Okay.
How do I get this in the bed? I can only put one of these at a time? Can I stack them? Oh my god.
I don't even know where this is going. Just fucking sleep. Thank you. Actually that's better. I can
get it right in the middle. Okay. Can I drop it now? Wait. Lower it down. It's almost in there.
All right. That's in. That's in. All right. There's one. Nice. Okay. Let's get the other one.
How high can I lift this? Let's see how high I can get this first. That can go pretty high actually.
This might work. It's kind of hard to tell which direction. Okay. No. There we go. That's better.
Almost there. It's actually on. Don't. Garlic brain. The fucking face cam's staying on fine.
How's that for garlic brain motherfuckers? How's that for garlic brain motherfuckers? D. Where's
this going? Where's this going? Where does it go? What mission is this? Bottom left? Log station? No,
no. That's not the right one. Deliver to the sawmill. Medium logs. Why is that being tracked?
I don't want that. It's the wrong one. It was like it was up at the garage. Yep. Okay. Here it is.
No, it's not. What was it? There it is. Okay. Here it is. Here. Here. Here. Containers in the river.
Okay. So I need to get over here. Back out to the road. If I pulled this off,
this is a huge deal for me. Get off. Get off. No more. I didn't think it was going to happen
immediately. No. I was so ready. Wait. God damn it. I was like, if I was slow, if I was actually slow
enough, I was just not centered. God damn it. I'm so pissed. I can't believe it. It's because I
turned the face cam off. Yeah. Cause I was like, so I don't want to even look at me. Don't look at my
face. Nobody look at me. Nobody look at me. Nobody look at me. Who is that? That's a character from
like a Christmas show. What is that? I was sleeping in my class in broad daylight. That's from Heart
of Darkness. Heart of Darkness video that I made. It was a, it might as well be. Yeah. That's what
it is. I'm so mad that I have to do this. I'm so pissed. I really thought I was going to be able
to do it. And you got like a Mario's ass went into the fire sound effect too. Great. Okay. Well,
I guess we're going to recover. Aye, aye, aye. Just leave Alaska. No, I have to do that.
I'm going to get these because like, I'm not going to let it just fucking beat me. I'm sorry.
Sleeping in my class in broad daylight, daylight, daylight, daylight. There it is. Enable aye,
aye, aye. Is it like 2017 again? Like is it 2016? What are you talking about? Oh, this is actually
really important. Have I, have I ever done the record scratch Aaron thing? I've been working on
it for a while. So I've done it, right? I have. Yep. Good. All right. Just making sure. If you're
going to play No More Heroes 3, aye, aye, aye is crucial. It's not. Yes, I didn't. I feel like I
did. You haven't. I haven't? Someone that goes. I've never done that. Well, now I have. So now you
can remember it. You've done that before. I'm sure I have. Yeah. What are you guys talking about?
Remember, you don't have to spend a hundred thousand dollars to entertain us.
Well, about that. You got the price wrong. That was a dad laugh. I said this in the pre-stream
and I'll say it again. It's, it's not about how much money a stream costs. It's, is it fun to do?
Is it worth trying? I don't care if I spend a hundred dollars for a stream or a hundred million
dollars. As long as it's an idea that I think is fun or that I want to do and I'm stuck. It doesn't
matter. Look, if I can do it, I'll try. Right? I don't care. I actually am stuck though. I just
realizing. Okay. I'm going to have to winch. Come on. This sucks. There we go. This was a horrible
way to go. I, dollhouse friends is going to be living in my head rent free for years. Well,
that makes me happy. Well, not that it's like, I don't know, living in your head rent free is
like a, isn't that like a, don't you not want that? Um, I don't know. If you thought it was fun,
then that makes me happy. That's all I care about. I really mean that. I'd like to get out of the
mud though. I'm so close. All right. Pull myself up with this. What the hell are you doing? Come on.
I'm going the right way, right? Okay. Why? This was such a dumb way. I was driving. Whatever. Just go.
Don't be modest. You knew it was going to be a great stream. That's it. You watched the behind
the scenes show yesterday. That's not necessarily guaranteed. It could have been very bad. It could
have been a disaster. We could have had extension problems. We could have had, because we were doing
it for three days. Is it going to still be even interesting after the first day? There was a lot
of potential for it to not really be that fun. Yeah. It could have been awful. So did I think
it was going to be worth doing? Absolutely. Everybody involved was so into it. That's how
you know that the project is probably a good idea. When every single person that's working on it is
like, this is really fun. Like we were having, we were actually, we were all having a lot of fun
during that week and the weeks before too. So if, as long as what some of you guys got out of that
stream was, you thought it was interesting. You thought it was fun. You had a good time
participating and everybody on the crew and the set had a good time too. That's, that's a win for
me. And I really hope to do way more stuff like that in the future too. That, that, but there's
no, I want to make this really clear, kind of how I started this part of the conversation.
I don't ever want people to think, holy shit, the dollhouse. Oh man, he's gonna have to do
something even bigger than that next time. That's kind of not the goal. There will be huge projects
like that. Maybe like, hopefully I try to do go to once or twice a year, but there's other stuff
that does not have to be that scale that I really want to do that I think would be fun to do.
Like I've said before, I might just call Jake like tomorrow and be like, hey, uh, I kind of want to,
what's going on in a couple of weeks? You want to do something? I have this idea.
It doesn't have to be in an elaborate, huge production, right? All right, let's try this
again. And we, we had significant backing from Twitch and from Coinbase. And I would like for
those, I mean, if it's possible, right? And I think you can't, you know, I hope that continues,
but if I can get the capital and get the funding and the money to be able to do stuff like that,
you're going to see stuff like that way more than you, way more often. If I can,
are you doing better medically? Oh, sure. Let's, uh, because now I can kind of just relax and we
can talk about this very briefly and I'm going to fall over again into the fucking water.
Uh, the medical thing that I was talking about, like a week before the stream was actually really,
really annoying. Uh, something I have to deal with now. Um, so it was a very stressful week leading
up to the dollhouse stream, not just because the dollhouse stream was happening, but, um,
I started to get dizzy and feel like pressure in my head. And it was like, don't even fucking tell
me this is something else that's going to start here. Uh, so I had to go in and get like an MRI
of my head. This is literally four or five days before the show. And thankfully there was nothing
really majorly wrong, but I have, um, cysts in my sinuses and I guess that can potentially cause
the problems that I was having. So I have to get those removed. So I have to go to like an ENT
and actually get some type of surgery, I think, to remove them. And they were not there before
because those of you that have been keeping up with the channel for a long time, at least the
last year or two, I had a brain and head MRI because of the unrelated other problem, right?
Like a year ago. And that, they, that, this was not there a year ago. So this is new. So I have
to just kind of go in and I was essentially told, yeah, you're going to have to go to an ENT and
they're going to have to get a better look. And I'm just probably going to have to get them removed.
So apparently it's very, very simple. It's a thankfully very easy thing to do.
And I'm not like in any pain or anything like this. Don't, don't get me wrong. I'm, I'm fine
completely. It was just, I think it's like putting weird pressure in my sinuses. So yeah, but I want
to kind of give you guys sort of what was going on there. Cause it was kind of, I was just kind
of weird. I'm just like, Oh yeah, I can't stream for like a week. Sorry. I got like an unrelated
other issue going on. And people were kind of like, what the fuck are we, what, what are you
talking about? What, what now? So let me clear the air on that, that like I'm fine. But I do have,
they're called like maxillary, they have an insane like five syllable name. It's like
something about maximiliterally sinus. Wait, let me, let me see what it is. Max, what's it called?
Maximus. Somebody knows what it is. Mucus retention cysts in your maxima. Yeah, there you go.
Max of the maxillary maxillary sinus retention cyst. There you are. It's a, it's a mouthful. Yeah.
Bro, no offense, but your, your body is making me angry. Yeah, me too. I'll be honest, but yeah,
I'm good. Don't worry. I'm going to be probably going in next week to see an ENT. We're just going
to just get rid of them. And then those problems will probably go away. Maximus. All right. Let me
get back to this. It's definitely not the garlic. He's still going to have the hernia surgery.
Probably. Yeah. Just to see if it fixes anything or helps anything. I forgot how to play the game.
How do I play the game? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is going to be bad if I don't.
Did I, this is not going to happen again, is it? I think it is. I'm, oh no, this is going to happen
again. Wait, put this, put this away. Take it easy. What happened? What happened? How does it?
Hernia, hernia, Andy, Andy. Why do I say that like that? What's wrong with my voice?
Hernia, Andy. That scared the shit out of me. And I pressed it. All right. Pull me out, please.
What the fuck? I'm about to just say who cares about this mission? Cause now I can't do anything.
I have to attach the this and spin me around. Oh my God. I'm going over. Oh no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Oh, you've got to be fucking kidding me. I didn't, I'm not coming back here again.
I'm not coming back here. Get the fuck out of here. Come on. Stay up. No, stay up, stay up,
stay up. It's like a giant kickstand. Stay up. Come on. Am I up? I am. All right. I'll go into
the fucking water, please. Okay. Well that was annoying. Galaxy brain. Top gamer moment of 2021.
No, I think getting out of the forest deserves that slot. So I got a question about No More Heroes 3.
I've been really anticipating that game for a few years now. Is it good? Be honest with me. I need
to know. I need to know if it's good. Is it good? I'm not reading reviews on it. I don't want to
know anything about it. Besides, is it good? Is it good? It's fucking amazing. I've heard it was good.
Okay. That's great. Perhaps. No mega low ups and downs, but it's good because I heard it was long.
All right. Is that in there? Not really. Shit. All right. Move. Just turn it. Oh my God. Put it
down. Come on. Can I just tilt it in there so it slides in? All right. Well, handbrake. Come on.
You should play Travis Strikes again. The only reason why I didn't want to play Travis Strikes
again is because I heard that game was even longer. And it's like a top-down game, right?
Isn't Travis Strikes again like 30 hours? I don't know if I want to do that. Come on.
That was awful. I can't do that three and a half hours into the stream after talking.
That was really bad. Oh yeah. You can oof. That was an oof. It was horrible.
Do we go for the other one? Come on. Let's do it. Let's go. How do I actually move this thing down?
All right. Yeah. Yeah. You're right. You're right. No. Stop. Stop. You're right. Turn it off.
I'm leaving. Now we're going to go this way. Straight ahead. Bang the left. Okay. Be careful.
Pack. Pack the bloody cargo. Pack the bloody cargo. Pack the bloody cargo.
Oh shit. I can do that. All right. I packed the bloody cargo. This thing's really heavy.
All right. Easy. There's no way I would have been able to do two. Not a chance. This mission sucks.
How much money do I even get? Like three grand? It seems like not enough for how annoying this is.
It just says you suck. I like that. I like that person. If you listen to Donda, I, I,
oy, oy, oy, oy. Handbrake. Handbrake. Handbrake. Handbrake. Handbrake. Oh God. All right. We're
good. I have not. Let's, I'm just going to attach the winch. I'm not going to, no bullshit here.
Pull it. Why is this breaking? Stop breaking the trees. You idiot. This shit's too heavy. I can't
do this. God. I can't, you know, I was supposed to upgrade my cars before I did this. That's
absolutely sure. Come on. Come on then. Come on then. It's too heavy. It's just too heavy. It's
too heavy. Now I'm in a lot of trouble. Now what do I do? I'm just going to have to pull myself
the whole way. All wheel drive. All wheel drive I think is on by default on this one. All right.
There we go. I'm all right. Come on. You can get through. Am I going to play No More Heroes 3 all
the way through? That's the plan. We'll see though. This weekend when I start it, we're going to do
probably Friday, Saturday or Saturday, Sunday. Keep an eye on the sus. You'll see. And after that,
I'll see how far I am. If I have another stream's worth, I would just try to finish it the next day
or a few days later or something. And then we do have the Sims 3 mod hell that I had actually
all ready to go before Dollhouse. But I didn't want to be a, I didn't want to just do the Sims
only for like a month. So that's ready to go. Wait, he actually is the sus guy. Thank you.
That's right. Okay. I love that person had to search for that. They looked it up. They were
like, wait a minute. No way. Did I, did I just get that person star struck? Are you? Can you believe
it? That's right. It's me. Uh, how do I unload this? Be with a face. I, it's not even my face.
How do I attach the card? Unpack card. How do I get rid of this? What? I have to, I can't,
I need both of them attached? No, I don't. Better not. Is it all right? Name's Pete. I work for a
transit company called Alaskan Transit. We've had an unfortunate accident is drilling containers of
tools stuck in the river. Can you locate them and get them to the base? Deliver to the port.
Fuck you. This is so far away. Oh, fuck you. Really? This is so, this is not worth this,
but three grand. Well, I have to put this back in now. God. Ah, do both, do both trailer trailer.
I don't think I can get a trailer in there. This engine that's in this car.
See how slow I was. I'm going to get stuck in that little weird spot where I was stuck before.
No, it's been the other way. Spin the other way. Turn, turn the other way. Oh, I'm getting that
like antsy. I'm just like wanting to shake and stuff. You know what I mean? You forget that.
I just want to start shaking around. Oh, okay. I could have just done that. Really? I don't want
to deliver this all the way to the port. That sucks. All right. First thing somebody puts in chat
is what I'm going to eat. And it better be burger king, long chicken sandwich, soy. No, nevermind.
Hi. Hello. How are you? Sorry about that. We should be good to go.
I'm going to need a refresh chat though. This chat crashed. I'd like a chat refresh. Clear chat.
Yeah, that was, that was my fault. That was my fault. Give me one sec. There you are. Okay.
What did you do? Uh, my VPN was on and I had it on a, I had it on a bad, um,
I had it on a server I shouldn't have been on. That was my fault. Sorry about that.
Oh my fucking God. Don't tell me that that's going to ruin everything.
No, I'm good. He did pirate the game. What does that mean? That means that some VP,
I thought that was on fire. Uh, some VPN service can get like junkie, especially at certain times
of day, certain times of night. And I was on one of the ones that was junkie. So that was my own
fault. New objective. Can I not go across this bridge? Oh, come on. What? How am I supposed to
get to the port if I can't go? How am I supposed to get over there? I can't go. Oh, are you serious?
I think I can drive over that. I'm just going to have to leave this here. All right. They stay,
it's permanent. So I'm just going to unpack it and leave it here. That's why you take the scout
first. Yeah, I know that you're right. I'm starting to understand how the game is played now.
You don't just drive around with the big guns. You have to take the little guy.
You got to go take your, um, hold on. I swear I'll make a reference in a few seconds when I
figure out how to get my fingers out of my eyeballs, like the Humvee in red alert.
You just drive around with it. Who cares if that car explodes. You're looking for where their bases
there. Okay. I got it out. Don't not. Oh my God. What the fuck are you talking about?
Why did you just die? Why did the engine stall? I'm all right. Give me the scout. I'm just going
to drive around the scout. At least I got the cargo out. All right. Give me, give me like,
just give me this thing. I'm going out with the truck. Let's go. This thing on all wheel drive
and let's fucking just hammer it. Let's move. I'm going to drive. I feel like I haven't completed
a mission in like an hour. Um, can I take it this way? I'm going up. Yeah, we'll go. I'm going this
way. Let's take the little scenic drive here and just see what we find. I'm just going to take a
little drive. Let's go. Plenty of gas. I'm ready. I just looked over and said I was live for four
minutes and I was like, how is that possible? I actually thought I was only live for four minutes.
It's like I am on drugs. What do you, how is that possible? No way. Because I've been live for about
four hours and it says four minutes. It's like, is my concept of time just ruined forever? I feel
like I'm really going to get into No More Heroes 3. It says three hours and 43 minutes for me.
I got to get those chain tires for real. We politely say what his shirt says. Uh,
this is a shirt from, uh, Omega Mart, the Meow Wolf exhibit in Vegas here. Omega Lul Mart. Yes,
I knew of course. Is it as awesome as it looks? Yes. I can safely tell you that this is, there's a
Meow Wolf in like three or four different cities. It absolutely is worth it. It's amazing. I'm not
going to say anything. I don't want to talk about it because there's a lot of interesting things
going on when you do it, but it was really, really cool. Really. What the flying fuck, dude. I can't
go anywhere. A rock slide? What do you mean a rock slide? Time for you to suit up and save the day.
I'm going around it. Now what? Rock obstacle. A shipment of cargo. Oh, oh, oh, nevermind. I
thought I just could, I thought I couldn't go around it. For some reason I thought it was like,
you can't go around. Sorry. No more swearing. Okay, fine. I won't. I promise. Can we say what
the shirt says? Not where you got it from. The shirt says thank you a bunch of times. Here, look.
I mean it's flipped, but here I'll flip it for you. Shirt says thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. And then there's a image of the Omega Mart.
I like the shirt and think it looks good. I'm not going to do the sus face.
I'm sorry to really break everybody's magic here. The sus face is a computer generated image. That's
not even my face. It's my eyes and hair. And the rest is a weird stretched out CGI or something.
What's this? Gas over there and factory that way too. Oh, shit. There is a, okay, there's a tower
over here. Let's see if I can get the tower. Oh, this looks like a clock. I definitely don't want
to do this. Contest. People say you're one of the best drivers around. Maybe, maybe not. How about
a little challenge to see if you can beat my record? Okay. Reach point A. Oh my god. Um,
okay. Hold on. Uh, I guess I'll, let's go. What, what, how much time do I have? How am I supposed
to get up there? Do I turn my headlights on? What's, what's headlights? Fuck my eyes. Dude,
you can't do this. No, you, nobody can. This is impossible. I need a moped. I really don't think
I can do this. No, I don't, whatever. I think I can, I think I can count the whole time. I don't
care. I was wondering if you were ever going to eat a big hot dog on stream. You want to hear one
of the stream ideas that never happened. That would have been maybe funny for like maybe five
minutes. I wanted to do an eating contest of like steaks or hot dogs or whatever.
Be like a Coney Island thing. And the only reason why I thought it was funny is one of the contestants
has a fork and knife and is eating it really slowly. He's just enjoying like a dinner and he
eats just one. That was it. Don't get stuck. Don't get stuck. Don't get stuck. Don't get stuck. Don't
get stuck. Don't get stuck. Don't get stuck. Um, it's over. I'm stuck. Maybe not. Hold on. I'm almost
through it. Come on. We're going to go muddin. Come on. That's an actual family guy joke.
That probably is. I didn't do it. Obviously. Like I just was like, nah, nevermind.
That's a TikTok skit. Were you guys around when I said that I thought I think I'd be huge on TikTok
if I gave it really an effort? I think I would be the biggest thing on TikTok
ever. Like if you rewind the clock and I just started and it's like 10 years ago, but it's now
and I'm like 22, 23, 24, 25, I would be the number one most subscribed person on TikTok.
Guaranteed. Guaranteed. What an ego. No, I was just saying, you know, the, look at the, you know,
the dances I could do. The dances. Imagine me coming out with a new dance every week.
You don't think I'd be number one in the world? Travel to mountain river. Holy shit. Wait a minute.
This is a new zone. Okay. Maybe not the biggest thing in the world,
but I would be at least the most subscribed. I'd be the most subscribed person on TikTok
from like people in New Hampshire or something. You know what I mean? Like I'd have something.
I'd have that. I'd be able to claim that. New zone. Wait, this isn't a new zone.
Show us a dance right now to prove it. No, I can't show you a dance right now to prove it
because I don't have pants on. Restore the bridge, right? I'm just taking quests every time I see
anyone. Wait, hold on. I just need to know. Like, can I, can a car, can I explode this car?
I don't think I can even drive through this. 250 million off the debt if you make a TikTok.
No, make it way more than that. It needs to be way more than that. Nope. Nope. This is low ball
bullshit. I will agree to creating a TikTok and making one TikTok a week for the next,
well, starting, no, no, I literally don't feel like doing that right now. Starting like next week.
I just don't feel like doing that. Like I'm just gonna be honest. Why am I sliding? What the fuck?
What's wrong with the car? Close functions. What? All right. Enough of the bullshit. Let's go
clear the debt. I want to just, I want to see what the service hub is. I want to go there.
200 million per TikTok. But the TikTok has to get over 2k likes. Oh, fuck that.
Come on. I would have to hop on every trend on TikTok. Although that's kind of funny though.
Okay. All right. We're fine. 2k likes isn't much. That's kind of a lot, isn't it? Did I ever tell
you guys the idea of how I wanted to make a children's YouTube channel and not tell anyone?
Never speak a word of it and try to get like a billion fucking views on it.
God, I wish I was able to do that. I wish I was. Just make like a real good like children's
YouTube channel. That was like really, really well made. And don't tell any of you guys
until somebody had to find it. It's still time. Maybe one day. I wouldn't be Jerma. I would be
like Mr. Happy. It doesn't, I don't know. I'd be, I wouldn't be me. So you wouldn't be able to type
in like Jerma children's channel. No, that wouldn't work. And try to be more popular than this channel
here. I feel like I could, I think I could do it. God, what? Like, I really, I got to dial back
that narcissism here. Yeah. I think I could have a billion view children's channel. I'd be the
biggest TikToker in the world. Oh, Jeremy, right. Is this anything you can't do? I can't move. I
think I'm stuck on a log. Yeah, I'm stuck on a log. I actually, there's a shitload of stuff that I
can't do. A lot. Like a lot, a lot. Come on. That was a bunch of bullshit. There we go. I want to
see what's down here. I might be in trouble here. Maybe it's time to wind down and stop the stream.
No, I want to at least do one. I wanted to get to here. I can get out of here.
Four hour Andy. Yeah, that's me. Go back to Michigan. You know what? That's a great idea.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to do that. Okay. Leave garage. Can I just, can I fast travel?
How do I fast travel? There was a menu I could go to before. Was it in the garage?
Where is it? What did I get to that menu before? Do I have to just drive there? No,
you can't drive from Alaska to Michigan. Can you? Yeah, you can. You gotta drive through Canada,
though. I gotta go to the garage. The actual garage. Mr. Slime. Yeah, there's been a couple
of concepts over the years of I just put a shitload of time into something and never tell you about
it and hope that I eventually you figure it out after like a year. And every time I come up with
one of these things, I think it's funny. I always have to go back to the fact that I have to do that
thing. Like I would, I would have to stream as Mr. Slime TV, like six hours a day. It's actually
streamed for like a year. That's like, that's like, I would, I don't even stream that much on my own
channel. Okay. So now we got to go to map. I can go here. Oh shit. I can go anywhere I want now.
Yukon. Let's go back to Michigan. Michigan. Think of the profits. I don't know if there would be
very many profits. Yeah, let's go. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
We don't. Oh, I have to move to garage, right? Okay. You never finished the TikTok discussion?
I don't think there's much else to discuss. Dual Twitch personality. Yeah. I think it'd be funny
for a little while, but then here's the problem with that. Both of these ideas. Who gets to take
priority? Let's say that Mr. Slime TV, right, or whatever his name is, gets to a point where he's
pulling 10k viewers a stream what do i do who do i even who am i who should i stream with if the
children's youtube channel has a billion views like that's i would have to i have to prioritize
it let's get this here did i already get this one no i don't i don't think so just sell out
completely just have one of my streamer personalities be the ultimate sellout and they just sell a
shitload of merch and it's sponsor space and like bounties and shit that's so fucked up but it's
funny wouldn't be the first time you abandoned the channel i want that guy timed out for a day
no don't actually do that this is dangerous but it's kind of the way i have to go what the fuck
what what the fuck what the fuck why is everything what the fuck it was literally the worst noise
was it you fucked up bro
that's my favorite yeah yeah hey you fucked up bro you fucked up dude go listen to it
somebody let me play it let me see it any any clips nine human goose baby wouldn't be the first
time you abandoned the channel not that bad it sounds that sounded like a seagull sounded like
a seagull with like a big dog bone in his throat or something like in a cartoon you know when they
swallow the big piece of meat and like and the bone like gets stuck and sticking out of both
sides of their skin like a car horn you know like tom like takes a big bite of the meat and he's
like and he's like got the bone is like sticking out of both sides of his like neck why am i
driving i'm not pressing any buttons squidward with the thing with a fork in his throat yeah
that's what it is yeah stop it all right i'm stopping oh what's over here i won't okay i
won't do that noise ever again i promise that happened to squidward bro but yeah i i won't do
that noise again i promise i promise i won't make that noise ever again unless i eat a gigantic ham
on a big bone and it gets stuck in there this is very okay you want to hear my final assessment
of this game um okay you ready so snow runner sort of reminds me of when you just take a car
in gta 5 and just say fuck it i don't even care i'm just driving in a random direction
out into the wilderness and they made an entire game based off of it it's pretty cool i was so
scared you'd make the sound again i'm not gonna look if you get booed and do stuff throwing
tomatoes at you you don't keep doing the thing that they booed you for i took my booze i said
all right and i moved on unless i look unless i think it's funny which maybe i do you might
hear it again sometime i've made that sound like a half dozen times before it always gets
nominated that sound always is there at the end of the stream worst of the year awards always
it's every time go look back at worst sound category i guarantee you that sound is there
each time we've done it the last two or three years it's definitely there this is really pretty
stop making that noise stop stop stop making that sound it's not me doing it the frogs are
going like i'm not gonna do it but you heard it can't wait for part two of the german awards
oh yeah that's right warehouse is this what it's really like to drive in one of these
this looks like hell this sucks yeah it is do you eat beforehand i hope you don't
this is just turbulence plane simulator you eat during it oh my goodness this seems so rough
wait where are we going oh all right cool i'll go this way i didn't even press that that was my
elbow all i'm going through thick thick mud this is cool this is a cool game i don't know if i'm
gonna play this again i probably won't you know i'm one-off andy but this i like this it actually
was pretty cool how much is this game how much is 30 bucks 30 dollars yeah i think that's worth it
if you're a truck enthusiast but you love off-roading he's just like kind of exploring
and doing the difficult missions of trying to load cargo and go through mud and stuff
i mean it's 30 dollars i think is pretty reasonable so anticlimactic it's not even funny
i was going for a big finish and i'm just stuck that was there yeah that's resident sleeper come
on now i just have to call triple a you know what i mean i was going for a big leg oh there they go
land and keep driving no fuck oh well i can't impress the horn should have gone faster than 10
miles per hour all right let's repair all all right now what can i turn the engine on what does
this guy look like there all right there you go you got what you wanted everybody that was here
you got the imposter is fucking stupid ass sus face that you got it i did i just realized that's
what i just did there it is you've been asking for that for like two hours and i did i just did it
so there you go oh whatever did you see that and it was the same exact scenario too
have i learned nothing in the like four years since that picture was taken it was the same
the webcam was off somebody said i bet you what does this guy look like do a scary face and i
turned it on doing a weird face and it turned it off immediately we're just in a never-ending
circle it's just never gonna end anyways dude sus 2.0 dropped well not really and i'm just as
sweaty too all right uh i'm gonna call it here i wanted to stream at least once here until the
weekend because yesterday was like a two-hour andy with the behind the scenes show so i was
like let's just do something tomorrow too so here we are i actually had a lot of fun in this game
if i had a little bit more brain power and more patience i'd probably keep playing it
but i will see you guys again we're gonna start no more heroes three uh probably on friday or
saturday so in a couple days two three days we'll go two days in a row because i i'm really actually
very excited for that game very much excited to play it still kind of coming down from the dollhouse
uh still that high is still there and i'm just sort of trying to pace myself a little bit but
thanks for watching we'll see you again some other time hopefully in a couple days what about hard
time hard time is going to be i'm going to play it on the ipad probably or maybe the pc version
because it was kind of confusing there's like three versions but i was going to do like an
m dicky night there's two or three games that are only on mobile devices and one of them looks
really funny it's a superhero game you make your own superhero and you live in an m dicky universe
so i mean i kind of want to play that one so maybe we'll probably just do them all one night
just kind of cycle through them uh yeah let me remember how to stream here here it is thanks
for watching thanks for the subs there's a lot of them there's a lot like a lot a lot now i haven't
really had a chance to take a even look at my twitch dashboard uh but the amount of subscribers
here now are way more than i've ever had so i don't even know what to say about this kind of
uh subscription account it's crazy and obviously i mean i know this is probably even if it's
temporary i don't i don't know how there's many people that have given this channel five dollars
per month uh join us on the next one there's plenty more there's a lot at least a few more
things this year hopefully they come out we'll see you this weekend for no more heroes three
wait 700 000 followers oh shit we did 700 000 followers on twitch that is more than i have
youtube subs on the original youtube channel right is that is that accurate let me see
no we're close 789 000 subs on youtube i probably lost a fair amount of subs on this channel
so i kind of want to say maybe like somewhere around 800 000 total 850 000 maybe so we're
getting close to trumping original germa 985 i wonder if it'll happen that's crazy though
and a ton of those people are new i think there was like 90 80 or 90 000 new followers in the
last two weeks if you if you just got this is your first stream ever after watching the dollhouse
maybe you saw the bts stuff uh i don't know we'll see maybe you were gauging if you were
gonna continue to watch from this stream hopefully i made a good impression if not
then i'm sorry welcome the new germamites but thanks again we'll see you this weekend everybody
much love to you as always no more heroes three i have to figure out what i want to use for a
control scheme probably the joycons right have a great remainder of your evening see you this
weekend good night goodbye and as always thanks for watching take care of yourselves and good night
uh i i'm sorry hold on i'm gonna switch to this the view of the game because it's really kind of
ominous and fucked up it's like this dude this dude hasn't gotten out of the car he's just still
lying here it's like dude call somebody man it's been like it's been like six hours why am i still
sitting in here like i can i'm just staring at the all right i'll see you guys this weekend goodbye