Where am I supposed to bring this guy? This is a gigantic base with people in it, how am I supposed to sneak him out?
Leave the base with the captive. Oh, the body can be hidden in a truck, and that makes sense.
Okay, well you stay put, I'll be back. I killed him.
I've been sitting here for at least a few minutes, trying to figure out what exactly this fucking guy is doing.
Is he wiping down this old rusty cabinet with his hands? Or is he looking for a stud?
What are you doing? Stop, stop it please. I had to do that, you had...
Who was that? Oh he found me, he found me. He is trying to figure out how to shoot me right now.
Oh shit, did you guys see that? That fucking hat over there. I can't seem to hit it. How do I hit this fucking hat that's on the ground?
You guys are so stupid, you can't hit a fucking hat on the ground. Is that what you're seeing?
Who is flying by and dropping missiles on this place? Stop with the fucking bombs being hidden by this guy.
Are you kidding me? Are you guys kidding me right now?
These people are all out of their minds. They keep coming in here, realizing where I am.
And then somebody throws a grenade into the room and they have to leave. And some of them actually die.
There he is, I found him. Oh wait, Jerry, did you just throw a grenade into the room?
Which one of you morons is going to throw the grenade? That's the question.
We got the whole troop in here. Who is going to be the trigger finger moron? That does it.
What's the hold up? I don't understand what the hold up is. Was it you? Was it you?
What's going on? He's pointing his gun over.
What happened over here? I heard an explosion of some sort.
Throw it. Throw the grenade. Here we go, it's my chance. Throw it.
Did you just throw one in here? Why would you walk in the room after you threw it? You threw it into the wall.
I can't stop playing in the grenade room. I've just been reloading this over and over again.
That guy didn't even attempt to get out of the way.
Something interesting. If you take a look at the minimap you see all the green blobs.
Those are all the people, all the guards, all the hotel staff, all the people here cannot see through my disguise.
There's one red blip. Do you want to know who it is? The chef.
There are other chefs in here that can't see through. I'm just going to throw a fucking plate in this guy's face.
That just hurt me. Did this guy grab my leg? What is going on? What is hurting me?
What the fuck just killed me? Did I freeze in the freezer?
Oh, don't tell me you can freeze in the freezer. Do not give me that kind of power.
Hey, Gary, just the man I wanted to see. Hey, look, can you go ahead and grab me some extra kebabs from the freezer?
What a fucking idiot. What an idiot.
All right, now do me a favor, Gary. Fucking freeze. He's not freezing.
Is this guy immune to cold? Why is it? Why do I freeze in here but he doesn't? That's bullshit.
Gary. Put the guy on the chair. He won't even suspect a goddamn thing.
I wasn't supposed to kill that guy. It's easy.
Hey, I'm not doing anything in here. Are you seriously wondering how that guy died?
You opened the door and I did it. Don't fuck with the chef.
0800 hours. My mission is to find the mole.
I've got to be quick. I've got to be silent and unseen.
I find my target. He's this guy. I throw a piece of china right in his mouth.
Mission accomplished. I can now escape undetected.
You know, I really wish they would play something else.
You're right, Jerry. And I agree. I think this piano player really needs to shut the fuck up.
Get some rock music in here. You know what I'm saying?
I'm just being annoying right now. That's all I'm doing.
I'm just ruining these people's dinner.
How am I going to go about... Excuse me. Excuse me.
Are you serious? Occupied. Get out of here.
What are you doing? Get away from me.
Oh, good afternoon. Yeah, there's somebody in this one.
Yeah, no, somebody's still in it. Thank you for understanding.
Second time. Third time. He doesn't... He's going to piss in my face.