Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with FaceCamp Fortress 2.
Damn it. Anyways, playing as the Soldier on Barn Blitz.
Using the, let's just take a look, Beggar's Bazooka, the buff banner, and the escape plan.
Also got on my something special for someone special. Helmet without a home and these summer shades.
So, what do I want to talk? Oh, yeah, I wanted to bring up the fact that I just got back from Virginia.
Sister's birthday party was a success. Thank you to everybody that said happy birthday to my sister.
She really appreciates it as well as me. Now, let's get out here. These pyros! Give me that health!
Come on, please heal me. Oh, this is starting out starting very badly. Oh, wow, we're dead. Let's go ahead.
We're on Barn Blitz right now, right?
Let's go ahead and make some animal noises. How does that sound? Ready? So we're gonna go with a cow first.
So, how does a cow, what does a cow do? My god, we can't even get out of spawn.
Let me just do my cow noises. I think we're gonna get spawn trapped this whole game.
I don't think we're gonna get out. Hold on. Rain check on those noises.
Get up there.
Where's the soldier? Get out of here.
Somebody...
Okay, I'm going up here. I'm going around the other side. Forget this. Oh, there's a sentry! Got it. Get this pyro.
Got him. Oh, I got him too. Somebody please cap the cart. Come on. We need this extra time. There you go. There you go.
There you go. Uber on the cart. This is fantastic. Oh, I'm all like giddy right now.
Excellent boys and girls. You did it. So, I was gonna do barnyard noises because we're in Barn Blitz. That's a spy.
I always think snipers are spies every time. Oh.
They are! Snipers are spies every single time you see one. If there's a sniper that you see that looks like he's on your team,
he's a spy. That's like the case 99% of the time for me. All right, let's get out of here.
Two.
Three. Go!
Give me that. Give me that. Come on. No medic. No medic. No! No, I refuse to be burned to death.
Before I die, all right. Now I can do the barnyard noises. I promised you I would do this.
I didn't really promise, but... All right, so here we go. Let's start with a cow.
Moo.
That doesn't sound like a cow at all. That sounds like a cow on like crack. First, hold on. Let me burp.
Let's do a chicken. Of course, chickens are on farms as well. Sorry, let's go with the chicken already.
Why am I holding down the button?
I can do a chicken pretty damn well.
What does that look like on camera? I probably look like a fool. And a pig. Let's do a pig.
Oh my god, we got a hacker! Oh my god!
No!
I just wanted to make animal noises, and this like hacker had to ruin everything.
Report. How do you report him? Where's F7?
Abuse report. Let's go. Submit now. There he is! There he is! There's the hacker. Oh my god. What's his name?
Hold on a second. That was just such a chain of insane events. Got you. I got you.
With the heels spread around.
Spread all in your face.
Overheal. Overheal. Maybe we'll just win this instantly. That would be pretty crazy. Watch it. Watch it, man. Oh!
That pyro is a- holy crap. Oh, I didn't get that pyro on time. Trying to heal everybody. I'm only one person.
He died right in front of me. Go, go, go, go, go.
Medic on medic. This guy charged? No, this guy's not charged yet. He will be soon.
You know, we're gonna go out here. Me and this soldier. Boom! This could be it. This could be it. Right away.
Let's go. Cabot. Cabot. Come on. Come on up here. Oh!
Get clubbed. Yeah. All right. Well, that's one way to win. Come here. Gee-gee. Wait, that was a spy?
Interesting. But anyways, um, let's do one more. One more round because that was, uh, that was a little too quick.
Mission begins in 10 seconds. Gonna skip the setup time though, for sure. All right, let's push on out of here.
Let's push on out of here with, with, um, as much might and mystery. Whoa!
Huntsman sniper uber, you want it? You want a huntsman sniper uber? Is that what you're saying? No, screw that.
Here we- no, don't run away from me!
Let's get a second uber on this guy. Do we even need it? Oh my goodness. Just running around with an uber.
This is bad. With this team, we're crushing this team right now. My goodness gracious.
Might as well just run in. Just run in. They probably don't have any defenses. Whoa, yeah, they do.
Come on, we need somebody. We need somebody. We need like a heavy. Come on, heavy. There we are. Here we go.
Move on up. I'll take the heat. I'll take the heat. Oh, come on. Get rid of that sentry. Oh!
Kill that sentry. Oh, come on. I got it. I got the engineer. I got you. I got you guys.
I'm only one person. I'm only one person though. You're good. You're good. Come here, man. Come here, sister. Sister. Get that spy!
We're gonna win right now. Oh my goodness gracious. That's two in a row.
Well, all these teams might need to be balanced, but I've built a views report ready to submit.
I don't even know how to... the guy was like changing his name. But anyways, thank you guys so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. That's gonna wrap it up here.
Sorry about that hacker, and I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care everybody.