What's up? How's everybody doing?
Disable Slugpog. That's the first thing you're gonna say to me?
Right when I get back? That's the first thing you're gonna say?
Not Jerma.
Oh, how are you?
Jerma, what's up, man?
Jerma, how you been?
No, what's up? I'm not gonna delete it.
Not for a while.
Look, here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna let Slugpog get to the point of the seagull saving,
where it was a little funny thing that was enabled for an hour,
and then became something that lasted two years,
and now I can't delete it.
Because now deleting it is, I mean,
what about all the people that saved all those seagulls?
Now a year from now when I delete Slugpog,
or I even mentioned the notion that I'm gonna delete Slugpog,
there's gonna be a bunch of Slugpog enthusiasts
that are gonna be pissed that I'm even questioning that.
Don't let it multiply.
Just wait till Slugpog X2 is made.
And then Slugpog X3, and then Slugpog X4,
until it's like Slugpog X100,
and it's just a bunch of fucked up pixels on the screen.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, I'm feeling a little better.
For those of you that don't know,
I didn't plan on not streaming this almost whole week.
VR kind of shut me down for a few days.
And then I got like stomach problems in the middle of that.
So it was kind of a double whammy.
But I'm here now.
We're gonna be playing Tear Down today.
Yeah, it's been recommended a lot.
And it looks really good.
Now, this might end up being a scenario where,
my computer, this is a,
is your computer good enough stream?
Again, like the third stream in a row.
Resident Elect Anthony Vanthony.
You know, I saw that image and I thought it was funny.
But the one thing that I didn't like,
I should have lost my hometown.
I should have lost Massachusetts.
It's like, I'm from there.
And everyone fucking hates me from there.
Because the only people that truly know me,
and I've somehow convinced the rest of the country,
that I'm this good person,
or like I'm a good policy maker.
The Massachusetts is just in, just done.
Oh, the completely, the complete opposite.
Or like Hawaii or something.
Somehow the Hawaiians just know.
You are a bad politician.
You have about running for office.
I never will.
You want to talk about me running for office?
Look, my mother has asked me before.
It's like, you know, you should like,
run for like a local office or something.
You can get up on the podium.
You can be well-spoken.
You have some great ideas.
And I'm just thinking like, mom, you don't even understand.
The first thing I would do is,
I would erect like 15 baloney factories.
We would have a baloney-based economy in Las Vegas.
That would be bad.
I don't think it would be a good idea for me,
for the world, the country.
But if I were to actually run for president,
or run for senator or something,
sure, you guys would think it was funny.
And a bunch of you might actually vote for me.
Most of you wouldn't because it's like, holy shit, no.
I'm going to vote for like an e-clown meme machine
over a guy that's a politician that knows what he's doing.
You would make the joke
and maybe like a thousand of you would actually vote for me.
Can you imagine the dirt?
Can you imagine the ad campaigns?
There's so many clips of me saying insane, awful shit.
I've talked about like shitting my pants.
I've talked about like shitting in my own mouth.
I've talked about like, I've like hit myself in the face.
I've talked about like eating,
like biting the dentist's hand and shit.
Like I've said some crazy things.
All they even need to do is just play an unedited stream.
And I would lose the whole country.
You just have to be an unedited stream.
And the first time that I turned over and I was like,
what did you say?
Hey, did it remind me of something?
I was in Dunkin' Donuts drive-through
and I got double, two of that.
And just my demeanor is not good enough.
You would have won in 2016.
I not anymore.
Oh, it's getting political.
No, I'm not getting political.
I'm just, this is just what's going on right now in the world.
This is one of the most volatile elections
in the American fucking history.
Okay, look, if me not even mentioning the election right now
is as if a fucking meteor on camera landed behind me.
And it was like, and like a fucking smoke cloud
took over the camp.
And I'm sitting there playing tear down like,
oh man, what's that?
Oh, did you guys see what I picked up?
And you hear like,
maybe the wind outside is getting a little weird.
I think I can use this in my inventory somewhere.
It's getting a little hot in here.
And like the fucking heat is just going in my window
and I'm like sweating and like red.
I'm sweaty in here.
AC, Las Vegas sure is hot and dry this time of year.
Of course, like, okay, of course.
The election was like literally decided an hour ago.
Like the, well, the projections were decided.
Now, I'm like, I can't turn the stream on
if you're like, hey, buddy, don't worry about that.
Jeb won.
Veggie turned on TV and it was like,
and ladies and gentlemen, the president-elect Jeb Bush
has been elected president.
I'd probably just be like, yeah, I guess.
That makes sense for 2020, doesn't it?
What happened?
All right, whatever.
Bring on 2021, let's go.
It should have clapped.
That's a millennial joke.
It's like fucking four years ago.
Wait, so what would have, I'm confused.
What do you mean that's a millennial joke?
Wait, we have boomer jokes.
Now we're saying LOL millennial joke.
Now, so wait, the zoomers have taken over now.
Uh-oh, zoomers have taken over
because now it's like, okay, millennial.
It's like we say, you know, as millennials, okay, boomer.
Now it's okay, LOL millennial.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, getting too, I'm getting too old.
Uh-oh, I am now one tier above
who is considered annoying to the last generation.
Uh-oh, stinky.
I did kind of say that was pretty close, you're right.
But I will say, regardless of how you feel about the election,
aren't you just happy that this shit's going to be over with soon?
Like, I'm fucking so happy.
Like, can we breathe like a collective sigh of relief at this point that,
okay, can we just like move the fuck on, please?
And I know this, and look, and I know over the next couple of months,
it's going to be kind of wild,
but with like coronavirus, unseconomic uncertainty,
presidential elections, Trump, Biden.
Can you imagine being on the highway in 2021?
And you get to look in the rear view mirror in like the summer of 2021,
and like the fucking world is on fire in your rear view mirror,
and you're just like, holy shit, I'm on the road still, this is good.
Whoa, that's back there, what's ahead of us?
And it's just like big fucking beautiful clouds and rainbows.
There's like flying unicorns and shit.
Once we get over the coronavirus,
we get over all the like the heated political shit.
That's optimistic.
Well, I want to be optimistic.
Why, you don't want to be, I don't want to...
Woody, what would you sit here and be like,
yeah, I can't wait for in 2021 for the whole world to collapse
and everybody fucking just gets wiped out.
No, this is a doomer stream.
Economic Andy?
What the fuck?
Zoomer, boomer, doomer.
That's fucked.
Okay, I actually had a conversation with the mods about this
before I started the stream, because look,
I haven't been live since the election happened,
since they even started counting votes,
which by the way, if I have to fucking hear the words,
democratic stronghold one more time,
I'm going to eat a glass bottle.
If I hear the words, you know, we're still counting.
The counts coming in, you see, these are all real people.
These are people.
We're not saying they're not people, but we're still counting.
And this can change, it absolutely can change.
But the president obviously is seeing some trouble here,
but we're still counting.
We're counting.
Eight minute news cycle.
See you in eight minutes for the eight minute news cycle.
We're still counting.
Let's take a look at this county.
Democratic stronghold.
No, stop.
Nevada, Omega Lo.
Yeah, I know.
They just shut the lights off like four days ago.
We have, Nevada is ready for the election,
but we're only going to be counting votes between 4 a.m.
and 11 a.m.
And then we're shutting the fucking lights off
and everybody goes home for three days.
Were you counting the votes by yourself?
Yeah, that's where I was.
That's where I've been.
I saw that video, by the way.
Political, political.
Of course, I'm going to get a little political.
Look, like I told you, the meteor is currently crashing.
It crashed at Earth.
I have to tell you about the meteor
for five minutes before the stream starts.
Come on, I live here.
I live in Nevada and we're currently
like the butt of every political joke
in the sphere of politics.
I have to address, I have to defend my domain, okay?
Look, Nevada's like 50 in education out of the 50 states.
Let me defend this.
It's literally the worst.
Hey, but let me tell you something.
We have, in Nevada, we've got one of the most
up-and-coming strong economies.
Our infrastructure is like top five in the country.
Our economic growth outlook is pretty good.
We are one of the, we are number four
in the country for infrastructure.
Did you know that?
Number four in the country.
We've got the beautiful roads, bridges, structures.
We have such good structural integrity.
We just can't count very high.
Once you get past a thousand,
you need like 30 more people to all count to a thousand and one.
Derma 2024.
You see, I can think about it.
Think about me on the stage right now going,
I just said fucking no more taxes.
That's it.
I don't say anything else.
I have no other policies.
I take a sip and I take a sip.
I pulled from underneath the podium.
A sip of a Bud Red.
And like the crowd's just like, oh, oh boo.
What the fuck?
And then I do like one of those fucking gross side burp muffles
where you go like, your like cheek fills up and it sprays.
It goes out the right side of your mouth really quickly.
What?
How is that stuff?
All right.
I look, it's been 15 minutes.
I talked about the meteor.
I talked about the smoking meteor that's in the backyard.
I get, I know where the people are on edge right now.
I know.
I get it.
I've been watching the news and flipping between channels
to see like what the fuck's even happening.
I get it.
But I'm going to play a children's fucking Lego game.
Okay.
Play the game, funny man.
And another thing.
Go home.
What is Otto's stance?
Otto was one of like the 8,000 people that voted for Kanye West.
Hey, by the way, I think Mickey Mouse got more write-in votes
than Kanye West got real votes.
I feel like that's real.
Oh, that's pretty sick.
Somebody said poor Kanye.
I think he's going to be just fine, by the way.
Damn, that was cool.
All right.
Get your tools.
We have an extinguisher.
Ooh, I love this thing.
This is awesome.
It's just like, it's like a marshmallow sprayer.
Why is there an extinguisher?
All right, sludge hammer.
But you're supposed to be able to break everything in this game.
Oh, you can.
Wait.
Well, this is my house.
Why would I be doing this to my house?
I got my sludge hammer.
I got my spray can.
Replace the fuse to turn on the power.
You can paint?
Does it all...
How do I switch colors?
Does it all have to be Halloween orange?
Dude, the home wrecker.
This is my favorite one.
I just smashed the desk.
I just heard electricity noises.
That's probably not good.
Okay, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I can't help it.
Everything's breakable.
I'm going to do it.
There goes the toilet.
All right, this is a bad game for me to play.
Luigi's Mansion, I can't play it.
This is Luigi's Mansion.
Wait, did I just steal money out of a safe?
There's like a bunch of gold bars in here.
Oh, wait, no, that's fire.
Replace the fuse.
Dude, this is cool.
This is actually pretty cool.
He'd hammer his own children.
Okay, that's really like just a fucked up thing to say.
Switch gear station, okay.
Replace the fuse.
All right, fuse is on.
If I hit this, it's going to explode.
No.
All right, I'm telling you right now,
nodding for a million dollars.
If you said, hey, dude, I'll give you one million dollars.
If you take this sledgehammer and you swing it really hard
at this electrical grid, I'd be like, no, dude, I'm sorry.
No, I wouldn't do it.
No fucking way.
I wouldn't even do it for 10 million.
It would be too scary because it would just explode and kill you.
Go inside and check messages.
10 million dollars.
No, because what?
The chance that you do that and you just,
the metal from the sledgehammer just instantly sends like 50,000 volts into you
and you just explode into a splatter of blood and guts like that would probably happen.
Gas bill.
Gas bill just dropped on the floor.
Honestly, I'm not sure we can make it through the month.
Are you getting any requests?
At this point, we pretty much have to accept anything.
Be creative from mom.
Use this.
This just came in.
Sound kind of fishy, but we need the money.
You up for it?
Good evening.
My name is Gordon, general manager at the Evertides mall.
I have a slight problem with an old building that's blocking our plans for a new wing
and I need someone to knock it over.
I need it gone by tomorrow and I'd even be willing to pay more than the standard rate
for some extra discretion.
Quick execution and uncomfortable working hours.
Would you be able to take care of it?
Yeah, is this England?
Where is this?
What country is this?
Is this fucking Northrend?
Where are we?
Is this a made-up country?
Lockhell.
Lockhell what?
It's Finland?
Oh, okay.
This would be a pretty sick Warcraft map, don't you think?
This is like where a raid would be.
Like you don't actually get to go over here.
You just get to go look at it for a second and get instanced into the raid.
Fucking stupid, by the way.
Let me explore the cool area.
But I don't want to get instanced into your bullshit yet.
Uh, all right, what are we doing?
Right.
Evertides mall.
The old building problem.
An upscale shopping center by the waterfront managed by Gordon Wu,
also in the area, is Lockhell Municipality Folk Museum.
All right, so just to destroy the building.
An old building's blocking Gordon's plans for a new wing at the mall.
Is somebody in there?
Oh wait, it didn't say that there's nobody in the house.
The old building problem.
What?
Okay, escape.
Why escape?
You need to clear all the targets first.
What do you mean clear the targets?
Highly explosive propane tank.
Oh my god.
Okay, wait, it didn't do anything.
Wait, wait, wait, just do it just like um, just like in Jenga.
If somebody ever asks you to play Jenga and you don't want to play,
just deliberately take out like the two or three bottom rows secretly
while you pretend to play at the top row.
And then it'll be over and you'll be like, oh no, you got Jenga.
All right, now put the fucking thing away
and don't take it out for another five years.
Look at this.
It's still standing.
Why?
Go down.
What?
Oh, the fucking chimney is holding the whole thing up.
All right, let's blow up the chimney.
Come on, blow it up.
Is this not working?
Use a bulldozer.
What?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Shovel.
Left mouse button, right mouse button.
It's a full letter grid, yeah?
All right, get this out of the way.
I love this game already.
Okay, dig it out.
All right, lift it up.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll just do this.
That's so much easier.
Imagine you saw somebody doing this.
I guess, I guess that works.
This is just what happens when somebody rents one of these.
To like move their pool.
No, I can do it.
I can do it.
I don't need to hire a company.
All right, I'm almost at the pool.
All right, lift it up.
Why is it stuck?
Dig out that chimney.
How do I get rid of the chimney?
Get out.
Fall.
Why would...
Wrong house?
No, it's not.
I mean, wrong house.
It's the wood one.
Yeah, bullshit.
I know.
Okay, let's get this.
This is so cool.
All right, I gotta calm down.
Is this a fire extinguisher?
Or a...
No, this is just a children's drawing of a Minecraft creeper.
And it's hung up on the fridge.
Oh, it's a stove.
Does this explode?
I swear to God, this is just what rich people do
when they're done with the house they live in.
They just smoke a fucking bunch of crack
and then they just destroy their house for fun.
They just do coke until they can't see anymore
and then they just destroy their house.
Read the sign.
We're not fucking reading.
Who wants to read?
The fuck did I throw that with my bare hands?
Okay.
Oh, more explosives.
Oh, sorry.
Whoever that was.
Right there.
There's a weak point.
All right, now let's fuck this thing up.
Somebody pulls over.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, is everything okay over here?
Yeah, don't worry, man.
We're just really rich.
Oh, okay.
Okay, have a nice day.
All right, let's do this.
Let's do this.
Let's do this in the right system.
Go up.
All the way up.
And then we're going to clasp down.
Ready?
Go through the roof.
Yes.
Rip it apart.
Is this a Mr. Beast video?
Yeah, but the only difference is Mr. Beast would do this
to somebody's house without them knowing.
And they'd show up and be like,
Mr. Beast, what the fuck did you do to my house?
Don't worry.
I bought you a million dollar house
and it's two miles down the road.
And they'd be like, wait, what?
What the fuck did you do?
What about all the pictures in the attic of my grandparents?
You don't need those anymore.
You've got a two million dollar house.
Oh, thanks, I guess.
Mr. Beast video.
Dude, okay, I saw a Mr. Beast video before
where he had like a bunch of fireworks people
and they blew up like nuclear bomb-like fireworks.
Out somewhere.
I saw like the fireworks Mr. Beast video
and I was like, holy shit, man.
What?
How are they?
Where are you doing this?
Like, oh, this firework is $150,000
and we have like four fire departments here with us.
It's like, what?
It was it in Nevada?
All right, I did it.
I won.
FOV?
Too small?
Probably.
Let's go with like 100.
That's a little better.
No, I don't think I could ever do a Mr. Beast video.
I don't think I could swing on a swing set
until I piss my pants and make 10 grand.
I'm not sure I could do that.
Like for 24 hours.
I don't think I'd be able to do it.
He does have, look, all right.
He does have some crazy fucking videos though.
I saw another one where he like slimed his brother's house.
They like filled his entire brother's house with slime.
I'm just like, imagine being one of this person's fucking neighbors.
Every window of every floor, green slime is shooting out of it.
And it's like, did you just like drop my property value
by like 50 grand by doing what you just did?
Imagine like looking over the fence and being like, okay.
Um, I, uh, is it time to sell?
Less taxes though.
Woohoo.
Ah, turn it off.
Look at this bed.
Look at this little Minecraft bed.
This looks like a person sleeping here.
This is like a person just lying down on their back.
Wait, don't I need this stuff?
I feel like I need this stuff.
Isn't this my house?
Why would I be?
Why am I Mr. Beasting my own house?
Okay.
Oh, how much money did I get?
This just came in sound kind of fishy.
Got it.
Cool.
New investigation.
Oh, what a morning.
Shouldn't have taken that job.
I knew something wasn't right.
That building was under cultural heritage protection
and the demolition is not part of a criminal investigation.
What?
Mr. Turdy Man at the police just sent me this photo.
They must have caught you on a traffic camera heading towards the mall.
The very last thing we need right now is an investigation.
I tried sweet talking her and she thought she could get the case dropped.
I don't know what she wants.
Just do it.
That's pretty.
Oh my God.
This is terrible.
I did this.
Wouldn't the police, the perpetrators, did a quick job on the old building?
Oh, right.
I would have a TV that's indestructible.
So to wipe my record clean, I have to do a favor?
Just so you know, I don't usually do this but I'm stuck on a case
and I feel like I should try something new.
I've been investigating Lawrence Lee Jr. over tax evasion for months now
but he has so many friends in town that I can't get a warrant.
How about you use your skills to borrow the computers over at Lee Chemicals
so that I can finally access his customer registry and sort this mess out?
If you do this for me, I'll make sure your little blunder will be forgotten.
Lee Computers.
Lee Chemicals, okay?
Marissa wants access to Lee's customer registry.
Pick up three computers at the site for her, okay?
Pick up three computers.
Don't destroy the building, right?
But that's it.
I can't, I have to do every single one of these.
I'm going to be on the news every day.
Press tab to toggle map and objectives.
Ooh, that's cool.
That's very much appreciated.
Okay.
Security, there's a fire alarm?
Large fires will trigger the fire alarm.
Shit, all right.
Let's compute it right in here.
Is this illegal for me to be here?
Am I like not allowed to be at Lee's Chemical Plant?
There's no security besides fire, right?
There's one.
There's the other one.
Right here, okay.
Where is it?
Right ahead, okay.
I stole valuables.
There's no people in here, right?
Don't erase.
Attic is off limits for all employees.
What?
There's two?
All right, now I need one more.
Why would I walk down the stairs?
Oh, it's a fake wall with a real wall behind it.
Bullshit.
Wait, go in the attic.
Let's see, there's illegal stuff in the attic, right?
How do I get in the attic?
Oh, up here.
All right, this is the attic.
How do I get up to the attic?
All right, I'm almost there.
All right, I'm in the attic.
I just got Lee's Tax Deductible Pension.
Nice, that's it.
All right, cool.
All right, on to the next one.
Is this car okay?
Last one is, I'll just bang a right and right.
Okay, so bang a right.
I'm doing the thing that everyone was so afraid of GPS is doing.
Let's drive straight.
I can't drive straight.
There's a building.
Drive straight.
What?
Oh, shit, nice.
That gigantic explosive.
Don't break this.
Okay, I gotta go up there.
Oh, it's easy.
And go, we're done.
Wait, any more things to steal?
Yep, coffee maker.
And I don't know what that is.
Get out of the escape vehicle.
All right, should I fight something?
All right, where's my vehicle?
I didn't even start any fires.
This is perfect.
Where's my escape vehicle?
All right, down this way.
Is there a sprint?
Raise every building.
No, that's not part of the job.
That's it.
Raise every other building.
No, I want a bunch of money.
Raise all.
All right, I promise I'll destroy the next one.
See, I got four points for that.
Breaking news.
Breaking at Lee Chemicals.
The perpetrator caused property damage and managed to get away with electronic equipment.
CEO Lawrence Lee Jr. says they will upgrade security
and should be up and running again soon.
Faster with the teleprompter, please.
Public school reading.
Yeah, that's just the morning announcements.
If it were you or if it were me, I want that job.
When I'm done with streaming,
there's like two things that I would want to do.
And one is work with animals somehow.
Or be the person that does the morning announcements in a middle school.
That's what I want to do when I'm done with like streaming and like online stuff.
I just want to, I want to, I'll come in.
You don't have to pay me that much.
I will, I will make that fun as fuck.
I will make it so exciting.
People are gonna be so happy to listen to the morning announcements
because I'll just be like, I would be, I would be so much fun.
But I guess, I guess that at like six o'clock in the morning,
maybe you don't want to hear that.
I guess that might be like a little annoying.
I'm tired.
I don't want to hear a guy be like a clown on the PA system.
But would I be able to like just jump in in the middle of the day?
You know what I mean?
Just be like, don't say emergency.
Oh, right.
Yeah, don't say emergency.
That's not an emergency.
I would be thrown the fuck out immediately.
You're like, yeah, you can only like pretend
to do an emergency announcement for like a funny backwards words day thing
before we take you out and you've been removed.
You've been fired.
I would hate to fire me though, wouldn't you?
Wouldn't you hate to fire me?
Because it'd be like, fuck, we just brought this guy into like a hype up the students
and have fun and like it's been three days and we hate this fucking guy.
And I have to, he's so positive.
He's like so happy.
He comes to work with like ready to go.
He's got like a jumbo iced coffee from Dunkin Donuts
and he's like ready to go for four hours straight,
whatever we need him for.
But you got to go like get the fuck out of here.
I'd be like, no, I'm over the PA system.
I would want to do it over.
I want to get fired over the PA system so we can do this weird like drama.
We can start like this weird like skit kind of drama
where like the PA guy gets fired.
Okay, if you guys in the morning, instead of the announcements,
it was like drama between the teachers and the principals.
Don't you think that would be like interesting?
You knew it was made up, but it was like, you know,
my favorite teacher versus like this.
Like they're like inside of the,
they're like arguing back and forth with like music behind them,
like sad music or like intense music for a big argument.
Yeah, it'd be like WWE.
But there'd be no fighting, just like arguments.
It'd be a soap opera, yeah.
PA announcer.
I don't think you could do that in,
don't think you could say that over the middle school PA system.
Sorry.
Or if there was fighting, you just heard like, god damn it.
I'm sure some of you have been aware Professor Michaels
took a paternity test to find out if they were the father of Mrs. Stevenson's baby.
Those results have come back.
Join us today for a new episode of the morning announcements.
Just know you are.
It's impossible.
I can just no way I am the father.
You need to go back to the doctor and get a real test.
Not one of these fake ones.
It has to be Professor Johnson.
I don't believe you.
I'm leaving you for good this time.
I don't want to ever see your face again, ever again.
And by the way, after school tutoring will be from 3 p.m. to 4 p.m.
How dare you talk about after school tutoring?
They should be going to dodgeball after school.
You piece of crap.
I'm leaving.
What are you doing here?
Get out of here, you maniac.
I know that you're the real father.
It's Professor Johnson.
Yeah, I'll tell you something.
Science class is going to be delayed today while I go out.
While I go out.
Science class is going to be delayed today while I go out
and spend some time with my grandmother.
Just whatever your fucking name is.
I can't believe you want to tell me it's my baby.
It is your baby.
No, it's not.
I am.
Why did you throw something at me?
Ow, my face.
You, stop fighting, you two prints.
Also today, assembly will be about staying away from drugs and alcohol.
Should be really, really interesting.
That'll be all.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Next time, with the morning announcements.
How much more excited for school would you be?
Think about that.
If you knew that you were going to get that shit every day,
people would get so into it.
You would hate it.
No way.
There's no way.
If the teachers were pretending to like...
Actually, that would be...
No, it would be fun.
What did that even sound like?
That would be cringe.
Hold on.
Did that even sound the way that I wanted it to?
Hold on a second.
Did it?
Yeah, no, that was fine.
That didn't sound right.
That's not what I was going for.
It's all right, though.
It still works.
All right, I gotta play the video game again.
I forgot.
If the world...
What?
If a Roomba was a person,
I was trying to do pitch shifting, not like robot.
Whatever, who cares?
Ah, fuck.
All right, let's go.
The customer registry indicates
that Lee has worked almost exclusively
with a single client recently.
The client is what they refer to as BT
and no further details.
So I really have to bother you with one more favor.
Head back to Lee Chemicals
and fetch their employee login devices.
I should be able to cross-reference
their log files with the delivery schedule
to figure out where they are moving the product
and what BT means.
Install the new security system.
Be careful.
All right.
Pick up three login devices.
They're protected by an alarm system.
Security arrives 60 seconds after an alarm is triggered.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I gotta be careful.
All right, now there's new security.
The cameras show up.
Wired alarm boxes.
Breaking an alarm box or wire triggers the alarm, okay?
Is this an alarm box?
Anti-theft protection system.
All right, so let's just jump over the fence.
Wait, it's just a sign.
It's locked.
Don't fucking ram it.
All right, I got through.
All right, where's the first one?
Up here.
All right, don't fuck anything up.
Just go in normally.
This is one right here, right?
No?
No, it's other building.
Shit.
All right.
Watch out for the security.
Wait, can I shut down the security system?
Dude, what's this?
What's this?
It's like cash under here.
Hidden cash.
What the fuck?
Okay, hidden cash.
I'll give you 10 million.
Give me it.
Free money.
Free hidden.
Okay, here we go.
Is this open?
All right, wait.
Can I just drive through this?
Just break everything.
But I don't want to break anything because it's bad now.
They have security alarms everywhere.
See, this is good.
Go up top and then...
There we go.
Okay, it's a security alert here.
How do I turn that off?
Key card.
All right, wait.
Hold on.
Can I do this like in a row?
There's one, two, three.
Why don't I just drive into every building
and just pick it up and run as fast as I can?
Quick save.
Go, go, go, go.
Open the door.
Open, open, open, open, open, open, open, open, open, open.
The door's locked.
Shit.
I didn't plan accordingly.
Use scroll wheel when clicking on doors.
Oh shit, thanks.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got to plan accordingly.
So this is this one.
There's one right across here.
Let's make a plan.
So if I jump out of here,
I'm going to jump from here into this building in front of me.
From this building in front of me,
I'm going to jump to this pipe.
I got to get on that pipe.
So if I go from here, jump to this pipe like this.
Fucking idiot.
How did you miss that?
It's so easy.
That gets me right here.
Window.
Through the window.
It's in the back there.
So I got two.
Let's get that.
Let's see if I can, let's get that.
Run it backwards.
Yeah, yeah, I'm just going to get a good look.
So that works too.
Let's get through here.
Whatever.
They don't give a shit about this.
So up there, grab that one out to here.
Get this one and then through the pipe.
Is there a window there?
Okay, here we go.
I got it.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Work save.
Use spray paint.
Oh, yeah, I guess that makes sense.
We'll try that next time if I don't do it.
In three, two, one.
I tried to hold it.
Fuck.
Restart, restart, restart.
I turned too quickly.
I was holding right click and I turned too fast and hit the wall.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go.
Did it do it?
What?
Fuck.
Was that the last one?
Oh, get me out.
Where's the car?
Fuck.
I got it.
It's I got to do the other.
Oh, I'm arrested.
Why did the I can't blow up the wall.
What the fuck?
What's the point of these things?
Okay, here, pipe.
Got to get in here.
Doing it backwards.
Plan a route.
Okay, where's my spray paint?
So I need to go in here.
So let's just do.
Okay, in here.
Okay.
And then from here we can go.
Is there a window there?
We're right here.
Don't go this way.
Don't go this.
This is wrong.
How do I erase?
How do I erase that?
All right, we'll go this way instead.
That takes us to here.
There's a window right there.
Wait.
Okay, hold on.
To here, this is the window.
All right, then this goes out.
And that leads me to out here.
Nevada IQ.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Well, I want to let me get in this building.
This is the hard one.
This is the one where, like, how do I get in here?
Where's the actual way to get out of here?
Right here.
So it's open.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Because this is the best way to go from here to here, right?
Getting in this.
All right, so we're going to come through the door.
We're going to go in the door, up, grab through the window,
out here through this window.
So now we got to go this way.
It's the landing zone right here.
All right, I got it.
I'm ready.
All right, I'm ready.
You ready?
Um, how did I get up there?
Melt his Lego brain.
I don't want to plan any routes.
I just wanted to blow up buildings with my hammer.
All right.
Are you ready?
I'm doing it.
Let's go.
I got my route.
I'm ready.
One, two, three, go.
Go.
We're out.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
How do I get out of here?
How do I get out?
There's a car.
Where's the car?
Oh, shit.
The door is locked.
I glitched through that to begin with.
Wait.
Wait, what?
How do I open this normally?
All right.
Let's fucking go.
The whole game is about smashing, dude.
Are you really asking?
How do I do this?
Just drive through the fucking building.
Done.
All right.
This is it.
I'm going to get it right here.
Hit that game, please.
And one, two, three, go.
Hurry, please.
You'll never catch me alive.
11 minutes and 18 seconds.
Cool.
Amateur, you've reached a new rank.
A new tool has been delivered.
You fucking kidding me?
What is it?
Blowtorch.
You can upgrade your tools in the computer terminal.
How do you start fire?
Where's my house fireproof?
I love burning bricks.
Are you using it through metal?
Oh, that's cool.
That's a pretty good slugpog, if you ask me.
OK, tools.
Sledge.
No upgrades available.
No upgrades.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
Attribute.
Short range tool causes medium damage.
No upgrades.
No upgrades?
Oh, I'll think.
Yeah.
Whatever.
I max it out.
Messages.
OK.
Investigation.
Didn't I already do this?
Oh, right.
Need coffee.
They turned off the gas.
I can't even make a proper coffee anymore.
We really need to bring in more clients.
I'll reach out to Gordon and see if he has something else.
Haven't heard back from the police.
That thing sorted?
Supposed to be.
Thanks for helping me out with that building.
The police was snooping around a little bit,
but it seems to have cooled off now and we can finally start construction.
I actually have another job for you.
See, I bought this yacht recently,
and it's too large for the marina.
How much does marinara?
And the board says there's no space for a new dock.
Would you use your demolition skills again
and remove one of the timeshare cabins?
If the original documentation also disappeared,
then tada, like it was never there.
OK, so let's go.
Make room for Gordon's new yacht at the marina
by demolishing the outermost cabin.
Destroy proof of ownership by dumping safes in the ocean.
All right, let's go.
Let's escape.
I like the way this looks.
The outermost cabin needs to be destroyed.
There's a fire alarm and large fires will trigger a fire alarm.
OK, outermost cabin.
It's that one.
OK, there's the office safe is in there.
Throw that shit in the ocean.
Let's do that first.
There's still a cast register from the window of like the fucking Dairy Queen.
Why is it not detached?
I'm taking the ketchup and mustard too,
and I'm throwing it in the ocean.
I'm taking the cutting board.
I should come back from your break from work,
and there's no sign of entering,
but everything is gone and the register is gone too.
Like the register and the ketchup and mustard are gone.
It's like, OK.
Oh, and the window is destroyed too, I guess.
Oh, can I get glasses?
I'm just stealing shit.
That's like just fucking rude.
This is just awful, like environmental damage.
Why am I doing this?
Let's sneak in the back.
Anything else in here?
Impressive mustard selection.
Oops, very sneaky.
Yes, very sneaky.
This place, this person, people really like that energy drink.
I have one.
All right, let's move.
Oh, there was a door the whole time.
OK, if you looked out your back window at that exact moment
and there was a full wooden door that flew past your window into the water,
what would you do?
All right, we're going to throw the safe in the ocean.
All right, I'm going to be like the Grinch.
Oh shit, that's 30 bucks.
Oops, I was trying to open it.
You're a wild one, Mr. Grinch.
You're...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Grinch, Grinch, Grinch.
No, no, no, you're supposed to be stealing toys.
Oh, what is this?
Valuables.
It's in the desk.
Shit, don't destroy all the lights, then I can't see.
Thinking face.
Expensive chairs, expensive wood, expensive...
What about up here?
Are there like company secrets in here?
Right, get on the table.
Fucking another light conch.
Nothing up here?
Oh, I have a flashlight.
Okay, that's helpful.
There's nothing up here.
All right, I got to get that safe.
Safe is behind me in the room behind me.
All right, there's the safe.
Throw the safe out the window into the ocean.
All right, where's the ocean?
All right, the ocean's right here.
Shit.
Okay, let's go into the ocean.
This thing's heavy.
Open it.
Come on, open.
Damn it, the safe is rated for fire.
Whatever.
You just welded it shut.
Can I throw it?
No, I can't throw it.
I have to just dump it around the edges.
Throw it overboard.
Push.
Get out of here.
What's the optional thing?
Warehouse safe?
There's another fucking safe.
All right, let's go.
There's a person?
Where?
I thought that was a person.
You're right, I thought it was a person.
I see a danger sign.
Okay, don't do that.
It was opening for me.
All right, where's the other safe?
It's the wrong warehouse.
Be careful, be careful.
Now, fuck it, I'm just gonna drive through.
Who cares?
Save the game.
Okay, I got it.
Forklift.
Forklift, forklift, fork, fork, fork, fork.
Forklift?
All right, then we gotta go all the way down in here.
Forklift certified.
Hypers.
All right, we're in.
Wait, should I take the daddy forklift?
Yeah.
I don't want the baby forklift anymore.
I want the daddy forklift.
All right, lift.
This is safe.
All right, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta put it on the forklift.
Why can't this raise?
All right, there we go.
Ready?
Check this shit out.
It's gonna be-
I'm gonna get it right on the forklift.
Got it?
I got it, right?
Okay, let's get it out.
Shit, it's okay.
There's too much shit all over the ground.
We're just going out the easy way.
Fuck, I can't get it-
I can't throw it this way.
It's all right, we'll drag it out here.
Yeah, a nice perfect square.
Dude, new emote incoming.
Derma slug torch.
All right, be gone.
Be gone with you.
Into the ocean.
Counts.
It counts.
All right, die if I go in the water.
Whoa.
That's on fire.
That's on fire, fire, fire, fire, fire, fire.
Just cover it in state puff marshmallow man.
The state puff marshmallow man saves the day again.
Wait, there's probably like hidden secret gems in here.
Look at this.
Are you serious?
You don't think I'm gonna do this?
There's probably secret hidden gems over here.
Come on.
Secret gem?
I see gems.
No, that's just guts of the car.
Really?
Isn't a secret like valuable in there?
Oh, my computer can run this game.
This is more optimized than Watch Dogs.
And this game, I think, is made by like four people.
Every single thing in this game is a physics-based object.
Every single thing in the whole game.
And it's running flawlessly.
I open up the game Watch Dogs,
which has like a 500 trillion dollar budget
and like a thousand people working on it.
Whatever.
I'll just drive the go-kart.
What is that?
Why is there like water coming out of the car?
Is that oil?
I mean, it looks pretty sick though, don't you think?
We're gonna go back here.
All right.
Uh, there's the escape vehicle.
There's the thing I have to destroy.
Let's go.
New car.
And this one's wet.
It's fast too.
This is a fast car.
All right.
Which one do I have to destroy?
Not that one.
Oh, get out!
Get out!
Anybody home?
Holy shit.
What was that?
It's just free stuff in every house.
What's this?
Oh, nothing.
All right.
Open this.
Damn it.
Everything's like a magic box of goodies.
Did I just throw their bed out the window?
That mean?
That's kind of mean.
I mean, yeah.
Look, at this point, if you're gonna do that,
you might as well just go all in.
And just hope they get like all the insurance money.
Like, let them write all this shit off.
If I'm gonna look, if you're gonna go in
and like throw the person's bed out the window,
just let them have like the $400,000 check.
You know what I mean?
Don't just like break the bed.
Because then it's like, fuck.
Mr. Beast.
All right.
This is the one.
I have to destroy this.
This is such...
Wait, hold on.
I like love this house.
Is it weird that I love this?
It's like what a view of the ocean,
right where your bed is.
It's just a little spot.
It's like you can eat dinner over here.
You put like a little...
I love this place.
Perfect little bathroom.
This is sick.
No kitchen.
Who cares?
I don't cook anyways.
I would actually prefer a house with no kitchen.
Like if I could have no kitchen,
an extra room for like,
I don't know, like a shelf or something.
Or like extra TV space or extra...
Yeah, I don't even use my kitchen.
Okay, so this will work pretty easily, right?
Fire alert.
Okay, at what point does it become too much?
Okay, put it out, put it out, put it out, put it out,
put it out, put it out, put it out, put it out,
put it out, put it out, put it out, put it out.
Put it out, put it out.
Okay, we just have to get it to a point
where the fire alarm doesn't go off.
And just don't spread to this house.
This is crazy.
I know I've made a...
Looking out your window reference
like five times this stream.
But looking out this window here
and being like, oh, come the fuck on, dude.
It's like, what the fuck are you doing?
If I fall in the water, do I die?
All right, now let's clean the rest up.
Good, that's tall enough where it'll get there.
Okay, cool.
Is that gonna hurt me?
Irma, what are you doing?
It told me to burn the place down.
It said burn, it said destroy this place.
I don't let that get too out of control.
What is this?
All right, it's, hold on.
It's starting to use the boat, punching.
Oh my God, the boat's on fire.
Oh God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Oh my, what do I do?
How do I get out?
Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get safe.
What is holding this up still?
Drop it into the ocean.
Oh boy, fall.
Oh no, don't burn.
Okay, I need to, we have to cut it off.
Oh shit, oh shit, shit, shit.
Okay, I gotta, do I die if you go in the water?
Do you die if you go in the water?
No, shit, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it'll be repaired.
Here, I got it.
I'm out.
Did you drown?
Is firework underwater?
All right, escape.
That was kind of fun.
That was cool.
This game's really cool.
This game's awesome.
I'm serious, this is really good.
Okay, escape vehicle is, oh, right here.
Destroy all the houses.
Here, I'll do this for you.
Too high.
Shit, too high.
All right, last try.
Damn it, whatever.
Throw wood that's on fire and I'm the maniac.
It can't be like burning down this building.
You psycho.
Wow, like this is not even like funny.
Hey dude, stand like really safe distance back
and throw burning material into the other houses
that have nothing to do with the mission.
You psycho.
Porn week, see you next week for Porn Week.
You reached a new rank, a new tool has been delivered.
Oh, I have to fix my own house.
It's raining.
It has to be perfect or I can't move on.
I don't care, just let me in.
Look, I have a better idea.
I have to go all the way down to the soil.
Oh, bathroom?
This is a really, really weird stall.
I feel like you could see everything.
Isn't this enormous?
Why do I have a stall in my house?
A new tool has been delivered.
New tool, shotgun.
It's actually a shotgun.
That was just a really stupid joke.
It's an actual shotgun.
Why is this game so good?
This is so cool.
Am I out of bullets?
How do you reload?
Classic cars.
Fantastic work at the marina.
Looks like it worked because they just cleared
a construction permit for the new dock.
Another thing came up.
It was this classic car auction up in the Black River
the other day and one guy just kept overbidding me.
Lawrence Lee Jr., that youngster who inherited
the chemical plant a few years ago,
absolutely no interest in cars.
He's just looking for ways to rotate his dirty money.
Okay, it's this thing.
The one they used in Seal the Deal 2
and Colonel Wilson's personal,
Jacobi from Normandy.
Lee is about to put those cars on a ship overseas
in a day now and they'll be out of the country for good.
If that's not criminal, I don't know what is.
Can you help me acquire these two gems?
I'll take good care of them.
Okay, we gotta steal classic cars.
Get the two classic cars for Gordon.
Drive them to the marked area at the back of the truck.
If possible, also pick up spare parts
and vehicle registration documents.
No, my tools, my tools, my tools.
He's stealing.
Was stealing worse than burning a house down?
Okay, sledge, no upgrades.
Spray can, no upgrades.
Fire extinguisher, no.
Blow torch, no.
Shotgun.
Ooh, range damage.
How much money do I have?
Okay, I could range damage, no, damage rounds.
And, all right, there's another one.
I've been up all night digging through the login devices
and managed to find a connection to the West Point Marina.
I haven't been able to figure out more on BT,
but Lee has a warehouse in West Point.
I guess whatever fishy business he's up to,
the marina is not the final destination.
I was thinking the boat GPS device can give me an idea
where he's moving the product,
especially if I could compare their recent destinations
to the shipping log.
Can you get them for me?
Are we just, are we a double agent here?
This is a double agent.
Watch the news.
According to harbor master Jim Delish,
we searched through all available records,
but no proof of a fifth cabin could be found.
Without evidence, the rumors still persist of a ghost cabin.
Next week, art or remnants from the afterlife.
Oh, wait, we're gaslighting the neighbors
that that person's house never existed.
I mean, couldn't the neighbor clearly just be like,
hey, there's a shitload of damage right where the dock meets
and there's a hole in my house.
Oh, and I saw the guy outside.
I didn't like that fucking chair or that picture.
All right, let's do the classic cars one.
That sounds fun.
It's unexplainable, dude.
Okay, classic cars.
What do we got?
Car in warehouse, car on ship.
Do I go to documents in office?
All right, let's go get this one first.
Wait, no, let's get this one first.
This one is car in warehouse and spare parts.
Let's go to the warehouse.
Bangle right, shotgun.
Wait, check the warehouse for materials.
Easy mode is over.
I was, what do you mean easy mode?
Ooh, aluminum propeller.
That's 60 bucks.
Oh, what's that?
Misaka premium spark plugs, 80 bucks.
Drive car out of just two drop-off point.
I'm gonna use a boat to get there.
$80 spark plugs.
Oh, mega.
All right, is that a car?
Car is inside.
All right, let's, I want to get this in a good spot.
Say toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat.
Get out of here.
What do you think?
I'm not talented enough to do that.
Is it money in the oven?
Money in the fridge.
Room.
Anything on the shelves?
No.
You used a sound board?
What?
Think of a money.
Think of things to steal that cost money.
Okay, there it is.
Not yet.
Anything valuable in here?
This office chair looks pretty valuable.
I haven't used doors.
Mr. Amenatides, visit Lee's birthday, other topics.
Now you'll forget that one.
Wait, this has an alarm on it.
60 seconds?
Wait, why am I?
All right, are you cool if you just get one?
So here's the deal.
You have to do the cars first.
Then I gotta come back and do these if I want to.
Just drive this.
Where's the drop-off point?
All right, there's the drop-off point right here.
Just get to the drop-off point.
What the fuck are you stuck on?
Put the bed down.
It's gonna hit a bunch of shit.
Just don't let the thing fall off.
There's no time limit.
If it was up, it would smash into stuff.
Okay, now, so get it here.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm gonna give you the plan.
Plan is, do not unplug this yet.
Keep it right there.
Get the other one.
I'll get the other one.
Save it.
The other one's over here.
All right, isn't it right here?
Melt this shit.
Let's take a look.
Other car is, it's not here.
Somebody got here before I did, and they took it.
It's here.
But unfortunately, this one is also plugged in.
I have to forklift this.
I gotta forklift this all the way out.
Let's make some room.
Can I drive the boat?
Oh, shit, you can drive the boat.
Okay, so this is gonna be like a James Bond movie.
Get this over here.
We're gonna park it right there,
so I can just drive over there.
All right, go, go, go, go.
I got it.
I got the idea.
Put on Mission Impossible music.
Well, in the world of new Twitch DMCA's,
I don't think that that's a good idea anymore.
No more Doom music.
Well, I don't think that's accurate.
Oh, dear.
We're dropping lots of frames right now.
Why is this so frame-ready?
Okay. All right.
Don't move, don't move, don't move, don't move.
Oh, don't, hey, don't, shh.
Keep it, where am I?
Okay, holy shit.
It's perfect, it's perfect, shh, it's perfect.
It's perfect.
It's fucking perfect.
Okay, don't touch anything.
All right, we're gonna have to melt this.
Just to make sure it can fit in here.
That's not gonna, that fits through there, right?
It's absolutely perfect.
Okay, now, save the game.
Now, this is where it gets tricky.
Now, I gotta go steal this stuff.
I gotta get a car.
And I gotta go, we're gonna go here, steal this,
boat, steal this, car, drive, everything go in.
The ship is sinking right now.
It is?
No, it isn't, it's fine.
You see money?
Okay, I need a car.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, this is cool.
All right, we gotta go here first.
Let's get up there and I'm saving it.
I'm ready to James Bond the fuck out of this.
I got a perfect ramp.
I'm ready to, that's gonna take less than 15 seconds.
Wait, I know a lot of you just were about to Pepe left.
I gotta get this all the way across to the other side,
to the other building after I James Bond one way.
I need a car to drive down here.
All right, let's do it.
Okay, let's, am I gonna do anything else besides that part?
Turn this around.
DMCA?
You can't DMCA ass voice.
You cannot, don't break that.
Okay, this is ready.
It's gonna line it up.
Go, it's ready.
So the plan, that's there.
This is, hear me out.
Start here, grab it.
Out the window.
Into a boat.
Across the water.
Down, in here.
Over here, park it.
In there.
Yeah, that was the Pirate's Thief song.
I was just trying to do it so shitty so that I couldn't get DMCA'd.
You can't DMCA a shitty sound.
That's like, okay, you know like the Lord of the Rings song like that.
Just change it a little and you're fine.
So like.
See?
And then you could just say, that's my original song.
It's not, it's completely, the notes are completely different.
Ready?
Let's do it.
Just change one note.
I would, we'd be grateful if you didn't do that anymore.
And do what?
You got, you got something to say?
Wait, what do you got something to say?
I'm gonna save it.
We'll see if I can get this to work.
So the deal is here.
Okay, where is this?
Okay, right, right, right, it's upstairs.
All right, I'm gonna quick save it.
And we're going right off this fucking window.
Right in this window, to a boat.
All right, make it easy.
Boat.
Jump.
One.
I thought it was gonna be a jump.
I thought it was gonna be a cool jump.
I'm sorry.
Wasn't cool.
I thought I was gonna launch.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
This is just like a relay race.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Watch it.
Fuck!
Shit!
I got time, I got time, time, time, time, time.
I got time, I got time, I got time, I got time, I got time.
Where is it?
Oh shit, it's back here.
It was a little sloppy.
It's okay.
And not even close.
I could probably do it if I get it clean.
Turn the cars in first
You did it again, ah
It's so hard to turn
Whatever. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. I it's gonna get that turn right now. I'll get it. I'm gonna get it
I'll get it next time. I'll get it next time. I'm gonna get it next time
I'm gonna absolutely get it next time 100% chance that I get it right this time. Just don't crash the van
This is the one that's the one. Yeah, go wait. Wait, wait, wait, what? How do I leave? Okay, that was fun
What is this? It shows you the route you took. Oh, yeah
Take a look at that perfectly executed. I messed up a little on the turn on this right turn here
It was a little too heavy on the handbrake. Yeah a little too much. Just his hair. Oops
I was trying to back up into the circle so it would register. How about this? Come on. Look at this setup
You tell me to look at this raise the bridge. No, thank you. Let's go a 14 only have $260
I did every optional thing too. That's all I get
What did a lot am I corn I eat this was taxes
Really? It was taxes. I had to pay taxes. We got all right about tools anything new
I want to upgrade the sledgehammer now keep the money. Okay, not really demolition
But you don't know me but I've had a series of break-ins recently in the last one
I lost two very rare classic cars and guess what I know who did it
Gordon whoo that absolute prick is now bragging to everyone at the club about his two new fave possessions
The break-ins caused me a lot of property damage and I'd like to let Gordon take some of his own medicine
Since you're in the demolition industry, I thought well, I don't know if you do this sort of work
Well, let me know if it sounds interesting. Yeah, dude. Let's just go play the complete opposite
the home of mall manager and racing enthusiast Gordon whoo his daughter Freya and finance
Inid Cummins an exclusive mansion with a private racetrack in the backyard
Dump at least three of Gordon's expensive cars in the water. Oh, what about the news shit?
All right dump some cars in the water. This dude has like a military base for a house
Wired alarm boxes breaking an alarm box or wire triggers the alarm, right?
Okay, I'm gonna dump them in the ocean. Oh, this doesn't do anything. You got to be kidding. This dude probably has
Tons of money in this house. I won't forget bingo at the marina
Forget about the cars. I'm just gonna take a bunch of money
This is the first mission and hitman 2 this game just is hitman 2 with breaking things
This is just break stuff hitman. I take the painting upper class table manners. Damn you got strong windows
Okay, this is too big. I hate this. This is this place. Okay, I want my entire house or apartment or wherever
I only want it to be like this big. It's too I hate that everything about this
It's too much. It's too much space. We have your own
You have your own personal grocery store. It's too big. This is sauna. It's too much. It's too huge
I would get my dad is a sauna. I knew it. Of course there is no I don't want a sauna in my house
Do you know how much maintenance goes into this as you cannot treat a sauna like you treat your toilet bowl?
Like I guess it's been like few months might as well like stick the thing in there and brush around the edges of the disgusting
Stuff that's in there. Oh, you have to be somebody has to take care of this every single fucking minute of every day months
Well, I mean like a week
vacuum cleaner
What do you have all these explosives? What's this? I say hit the light exactly. It's got to be valuables here
Rich people can pay for that. Yeah, I know but
It's like why?
Look having a nice house is one thing but having like two saunas in your house having an elevator in your house
It's like this is I would hate this I this is just and you anybody that can see through here
Sees if you have an elevator in your house
If you have an elevator in your house, there's a bag of money in there somewhere that you don't care about
So why the fuck would you give a shit if you have an elevator in your house?
What about if you're disabled? Yeah. Yeah, that makes perfect sense
But I'm gonna just take a wild guess and say that this person is doing it
Because they're just they want to look at this what practical reasons is for what is this?
I mean, you cannot tell me for like some kind of excuse that like he's like a dr. Seuss fan or something like
Just looking for money. Yep, definitely gonna be a safe back here. There's absolutely gonna be a state way
That's very worth a lot of money. No safe behind the painting really? Okay, so I just destroyed this whole painting
There's just a frame here and I don't see a difference and when it was not broken elevator
No, wait bedroom. I'm in the bed. It's just I just looks like a fucking Oreo cookie. I want to bite this. Oh
Doesn't it doesn't it doesn't it doesn't look like an ice cream cake. I want to bite this ice cream cake
You know what to talk about when you bite in and it's like so cold in the middle here
It's a kind of frozen and you teeth just smudge through it really freezing cold and still I've wanted
But anyways, there's nothing under here. Wait, they might be
weird with the weird super rich people like this probably have
This prep this I told you I told you there's like fucking 30 BTC back here sleeping pills. Oh, no
Nothing. Nothing. Come on. That's like a super huge bed. What is this? Oh, I turn it off. I don't like it
expensive shoes
Behind the mirror expensive shirt. Oh, no blind blind blind. What do you mean blind?
Something expensive that I missed missed him on the shelf right next to where you smashed
What do you mean? Oh right here
He goes a wallet
The this bright flashlight was making it fucked up
All right, and then we're really then we're really gonna make this work on our favor now
He's gonna be like fucking Steve. I'm not my nice Steve. My name's like fucking Jerry. That's real
Let's really confuse the fuck out of him. What do you say?
You're gonna be like wait, they played tic-tac-toe out here. What the fuck? Why one two three four? We played it wrong
Look there's no erasing. Okay, it's no erasing with spray paint
So we had to just do it. We had look we fucked it up. We just whatever
Wait, wouldn't this technically be a tic-tac-toe up here? Okay. So yeah someone he won. All right lined. Oh
Three shit. Whoops plant dude plant. No way. Oh, wait a minute. Fuck. Yeah, that was fun
Oh this car is supposed to be doing car stuff. No, no, no, let's be an asshole ready. It's like my painting. Oh, no
And then we're right this yeah, yeah, what do you think about that? What's the difference the Joker does that?
Oh, and by the way and leave my calling card. Yeah, it's supposed to be the Joker. Hold on
If you're good at something never do it for free. Well, okay, let's steal some more stuff
I'm gonna like ice climb up his house
Pretty shit you have such an expensive house and you have an antenna TV. Fuck. Are you doing? What's this?
So I can press this I can't press this button. Oops. Well, hopefully I didn't need that
Draw a helipad
From something anybody that flies over he'll never know how about like just like I eat ass
Cuz you're gonna be able to see that if you fly over even after the people come in
They're like, yeah, we took care of for the burglary. Everything's all sorted. It's been all cleaned up shit
I gotta move this stuff. It's in the way of my art project. All right, what if we what if we write I eat my own ass
Possible is it too long. It might be too long. I eat my own ass. No, it'll be it'll work
Shit, I can get out there. Hold on. Fuck. I need to get back up there place is too big. We're good
So I eat my oh
And sucks fuck
Sucks this is terrible. Hey, can I burn it away? I can know I can fix it. I can fix it
Ow
Move on I can't I have to finish this. I saved it. The ends just very thick. I saved it. It's saved
Okay, got it. It's the wrong way. It doesn't what do you mean the wrong way?
Fuck that dish. Yeah, that's good. Now. There's more money probably in this house somewhere. Can you have it? Can I die?
Oh, look at this artwork. I can spin it. Holy shit. I can't screw it. It's kind of fun
Just explore in this house. Oh, this is expensive. Hey, hold on. I'm an idea. Hey, I gotta okay
I'm gonna go this way. This is important. Hold on. You can't destroy it. Oh, that's too bad
I was gonna draw a huge line that went around the entire house and at the start it said where is your art and now
It's gonna have to be just broken at the end. Oh, there we go. He's gonna have to follow this around as they call a fucking house
Okay, where is your art? Let's say where?
Hmm, what where'd it go? What is this? Oh, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait my tapeworm go
It's gonna be in here somewhere. Where did he put it? You know, he's gonna get take a guess
I spray paint the water get wrong. He's gonna backtrack. He's gonna go over here. I
Guess he wouldn't like follow this like an idiot. You would just go to where it looks it and here it is the end. Oh
And we need a message here
See I drew him a new one. This one's free. Yeah. Okay. This is car illegal. Okay
I'm gonna I gotta play the game main garage. Okay, where do I have to bring them to they got to come out to here?
Okay, they all have an alarm. So I gotta make a I gotta make a route shit the spray can. Oh shit
Okay, save the game. I have 60 seconds to do this. Alright, this one can just go straight through
So let's go like this make a good way to get out of here. Give me the shotgun. Let's just stop blowing holes
I'll just burn it down. I just burned this place down
That's a pretty cool table, but I just ruined it. I want a good clean place to drive here. So go through here this way
right here
I'm gonna take this I need like a demolisher. Whatever that okay. I need to demolish her
It's thinking go into water. I bet that I don't think any but as long as I can just drive straight through here
Take the alarm take the pillar off and put it on top of the car. That didn't work
Yeah, I like I got to destroy all this shit didn't save you I did. Okay dump at least three of the cars
I want this. Okay, we're gonna do this one. It's three here. Now. That's me. Okay, I want this one this one and
This one let's make it let's make a route. I'm at least three of the water. Oh, okay
Well, that makes it a lot easier
This is this one here. Just right that way just right that way dump them in the pool
Is it water in this pool? Oh, there's no water in here doesn't need to be in the ocean
Wait is where is there is there what there is water somewhere isn't there?
There's a cool now right here. There's this pool here. I guess I could try to do that one at this one
I could just drive off. All right, let's keep this going though. I want to is that one
There's the one that's in this showroom here. That should be fine. So we're just gonna
That way I open a door straight that way right that way and now
So those two can just go get dumped and what about this one? Oh, there's one here, too. Holy shit
That's like there's like four right here. All right. Well, this one can go straight fuck the gazebo
Alright, we're gonna say there's one right there, too
Wait, can I do that? I do that. Oh, you can't oh, this has got to be way cleaner, too
It's like I got to destroy all this grass you 100% can no you can't it was patched. Oh, well, they patched it
Alright, we're gonna take care of all this grass
Or not, I need to be able to get out of this
So don't yeah, let's drive straight and then I guess I could just I could just drive this thing straight straight
It's a hot tub right here. Hold on. I have to test something. Is that hot tub? Oh, it's upstairs
Never mind
Drive up the stairs. I can't drive upstairs. It's not upstairs
Yeah, it is. That's clearly upstairs
Alright, so this one goes straight drive it straight all the way into the ocean this one
Drive it just drive it out there that one drive it out there. This is like a big jump right here
I'm just gonna fly off this and just ghost ride it off. Okay, let's ride that one drive that one
Alright, let me plan so
Ghost ride it and take this one
We'll do this one first. This one can just be driven straight. Let me see if I can just get these four
I'm not going for the fucking hundred percent. Who cares? Let me see if I can get these four. This is one raised car lift
I'm gonna go for it. Ready? One, two, three go. I don't have any tires. Okay, so
Looks like I'm gonna have to carry it. There's tires over here. Can I put them on?
I don't think I can put these on. No, you can't wait. Hold on. You can't like push it lift the car
Wait, I you can't do that. That's made up. You made that up
No, it doesn't work. I gotta carry this out with a good tractor or something
I just put a car on top of a car. I just kind of squished it a little. It almost kind of worked
I'm gonna lift it's like snow. You just got to make the tires free. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second. Wait a second
It never said anything about the car needing to be in one piece throw this fucking thing in the ocean
It didn't say shit about that. Hold on a second. Move out of the way. It's on this fucking car now
Wait a minute walk it to the ocean. That's what I just I don't know how I fucked that up
All right, here we go. Where's the nearest ocean? I just drag it this way game over
I win imagine this worked the pond in the racetrack. Oh, holy shit. There is you fucking genius. I'm driving it
I'm driving it. I'd like everyone to apologize to me, please. He just Flintstones the car. All right now, so that's one
I just need to get two. Yeah, let's get out of here. That's that one. Now I can just go
Straight I'm gonna dump this one first. We're gonna go this one straight dump into the pond. These are all going to the pond
I'm ready save this fucking shit. Let's go
Just get out go. There we go. Ready? One, two, three
Get off move this. Why is it those shit in the way? Why did I drive backwards? I don't know
I fucked up. All right, let's do it. Just gotta get him the pond. Just two more. Here we go. It's pond
Get that pond. All right, dump it. I need another car here. I need you the car to be take me
But wait, that's okay. The ass is wrong. I gotta get another car. It's fucked up
I gotta get another car to do go that way. I fucked it up
I was supposed to go straight over the thing. Remember I was gonna fly over. All right, let me get this more
Correct. Let's put this car down here. I'm gonna jump that. I need an escape car
Once I jump that I'm gonna end up like there. It's gonna go in the ocean
Perfect opportunity. There's okay. There is a car already here. We're gonna go
Over here wait
So I can just fly over that take that car back
I'm gonna take that car back to here and I'm just gonna drive this one in the ocean and then it's and then escape
Let's see if I can do it are on truck. Oh shit. Give me that meat on bone meat on bone
Piano, what's a piano doing out here? All right, so this would be two and then we just need one more
That's it. What and anything after that is icing on the cake. Hold on if I go take this one
I'm gonna make enough room where I can just speed through that. I have my escape car
I might be looking more than one. Here's a car. There's a car. There's a car. There's a car. You see plucky
We're gonna play our favorite game
It's called there's a car
Anytime you see a car plucky you say there's a car
There's a car. There's a car. There's a car. There's a car. There's a car. Did anyone know that is that's from?
Tiny Toons how I spent my summer vacation
Nice go nice going one person. How do I fuck that up? I have no idea. I could just end this right now
All right. No, no, no, no, no. No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Watch this shit. You ready?
I'm going straight this way ditch straight that way ditch. There is a car. There's a car. How do you unsubscribe?
You better not do it. You're gonna unsubscribe better not
Open open. Oh
Stupid game. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I'm good. I'm good. I'm leaving
Anymore. Nope. I'm done who watches German in 2020. I don't know man you
Coffee oh this coffee's kind of gross. Mmm. I'm now a trespasser a new tool. Nice. I this guy's love this game
I love the tools new tool who uses doors anymore
Blanks blanks can be used to build primitive for ramps
You can also attach objects with planks to lift or drag heavy items really build complex structures
That's pretty cool. That's really cool. And then I can pick it up. Okay, they can attach to walls too. Nice
It stays there. All right, that's cool. How much money do I have?
600 oh nothing nothing planks maximum length. Oh
Feel like I want maximum length and more planks. Yeah
24 planks. Hey, what about this one? I think the login device submitted to find a connection to the West Point Marina
I've been able to figure out more on BT
But Lee has a warehouse in West Point
I guess whatever fishy business he's up to the marina is not the final destination
I was thinking the boat GPS devices can give me an idea where he's moving the product
Especially if I could compare their recent destinations to the shipping log. Can you get him shoot for quantity almost always
Steal the GPS device from Lee's boat and get the log files watch the news
I keep forgetting to watch the fucking TV just spawn me in front of the TV. Okay log files in the office boat trailer
Okay
Fishing boat
secondary targets are boat and boat house
Let's go to the office and just take a little peek of what we're working with here
I got my long planks. I still have a VHS tape of how I spent my summer vacation
I remember renting that at blockbuster over and over again
And sometimes it wouldn't be in and I would be so pissed because there was only like one copy of that at blockbuster
And those you guys don't know how blockbuster worked
They had display cases and if there was a second case behind the display case
That means that that was currently in and you could rent it
so it was always so horrible when you would go into blockbuster and they would be a new game or a new movie that you want to
Watch and it'd be two or three rows of these display cases and none of them had a single secondary case behind them
It was just so defeating because then you had to rent something else and it was like I don't want to fucking rent something else
I don't want to I don't want to rent
That's the glove game 364
I've rented that like five times in different places because they didn't have like Donkey Kong
Lover waiting room. All right, I'm stealing something here. What am I stealing all the way across the whole room. What are we stealing?
Holy shit. Whoa
That's 400. What was the antique pirate dagger? Holy shit. Okay, be careful. I don't want to trigger this save this
This is gonna this is gonna trigger same technique I did last time although
Did he grab this steal the GPS out of there and then steal the GPS out of here and then fuck off
It's my escape. All right, that's gonna you know, let's just go for it. Whatever. Fuck it. Let's just write a little one little boat
This is too slow. This is really slow
Way too slow just burnt so much time fuck what no take the what the fuck are you doing?
What Wow, oh that is just not gonna happen. We're gonna plank the fuck out of this
If we can I can I I can't right?
No, I can't build a bridge
These are so slow. I need a faster boat. Okay, is it was like a speedboat? I guess I could I dump
I'm gonna I'm gonna dump that in the ocean. Yeah, let's go
Big boat is fast. Are you sure?
Okay, it is it's very fast. You have to commit to the bridge. It's not gonna work. I only have 24 planks
All right, but not hold on a second. I want to go examine this it shaves off at least 10 seconds
All right. I've got an idea
Here's my idea. I got to get over this thing. So I got to steal the GPS out of here. Why not?
Yes, okay. Why not just bring this all the way back put it in the water. Yeah, just put it in the water
You know, just have this be the last thing I do in the for the escape. That's not a bad idea
Hey now, it's the escape right there
This is a family guy joke. How wait? How is this a family guy joke?
Why did I think that backing this up was a good fucking idea? Somebody tell me there we go
All right. Now that one's ready to do the last I can do this one second to last
What the hell is going on here? I think I'm gonna build a bridge
You know what just I wonder if I can build a bridge from here to the boat cuz I need to steal this
Hey, can I just I drop this into the water? Yeah, get off. What are you attached to?
Get off stop it, please. You're making me look so bad right now. What is it still attached to?
No, I wouldn't want to pick that up. I didn't want to pay I wanted to now get this in the water
I can't drive this can't drive the boat. I can carry it though worst possible way. Really?
All right, let's drag this back to the truck. Are we gonna get this? That's good. This is optional
You're like a dog with a stick. Oh
Shit, I gotta wait. I'm not gonna waste this it fit through that at the ends. If only I was as smart as you
Yeah, I'm playing chess and you're playing I'm playing checkers you're playing chess. All right, so here is
Target number two. So there's grab that grab that
Escape what else is there? This we have to grab this take the fast boat over here. There's nothing else over here
Grab this take the fast boat here. Oh shit. Okay way to get that to drive big boat
I will just burn it all to the ground Jeremy. No, I gotta burn it all to the ground
Okay, this one is
Well, let's do a little experiment here
Now what if okay I can raise the bridge I can drive through here and just
This is this has to be the last thing I do is if I start up here at that 60 seconds go this way
I still haven't figured out what the hell has to happen here. Get that I have another boat parked right here. So we go
Get that
Get that real
Click click click click click done. Let's keep that in mind. I can drive the big boat. Well, let's let's find out
Let's take a look. What is the big boat? That's inefficient. I'm not looking for efficiency. I'm looking for completion
I
Lost the physics
I'm gonna need to hold this for me. I can drive this wait. What about secret or
$100 40. I don't know that was that the engine
Inefficient, I don't care about efficiency. I sort of beat it. I don't I want to complete it. I don't care about efficiency
Okay, this can be driven. Where do I want this? So I gotta take that GPS. Let's get it over here
Oh, this is done. This is done. This is done. This is done. What's wrong with the boat? Oh
I have to like smash the thing and now this is done. I just did it
I got all the conditions what the fuck is going on? Is there not this is another cable right here
Are you kidding me? Let go of me. How am I gonna get back on fuck? I need to know the bridge
Okay, easy. Come on. Come on. Don't do it. All right, watch out for the iceberg
Okay, so this is good. I just have to get this in the right spot over here. That looks good
One two, three four, this is the last thing on the list so I have to get this thing
This thing is way too slow. I need the fast boat here. So I'm gonna just I'm gonna park this thing
Who cares? I'm gonna make a wait. I have to raise the bridge. I like shoot it from here. Oh
Shit, I almost had it. Come on. Get out of the way stand on top of it. What the fuck even is
This is like the Blair Witch project thing. I'm whatever fuck it bridges up pretty sick. No, it's shitting
Oh, don't say that it is doesn't look at goldfish shitting one of weirdest things to ever look at when a goldfish shits
It's just just so strange stay right there. Don't move. All right, we're good. So one two, three four
What was this? Oh, okay. I thought those are objectives. They're just tables. All right
It's time to make the put this plane in motion in here. I want I need this boat. This is the fast one grab it
speed this way grab this boat speed this way collect collect collect collect collect and
Eat that boat. I'll save it. Yeah, I will need that tail. What's that from? I need that tail. I need that claw
What is it? What is that from? It's for me. But what is it? What is it? It's a little hilarious monster hunter bit. I
Alright, you didn't put hilarious in quotes. So I think you actually did you think that you thought that was funny?
Monster hunter is weeb trash
It keeps like that gives fun. What do you do? What?
All right, I'm ready. It's time get the hell up here steel drive steel drive don't fall
Oh, there's a hole here VIP that guy. Why would I VIP that guy?
He said something incredibly bad that I didn't like okay. This is it save the game here
So we'll go in here bang drive this straight through here to this boat bang drive back collect collect collect collect out one two
Three get out of the boat hurry
Okay, then we take a transfer to this boat transfer one, ah
No kid. That's it. Right? I did them all yeah sick. That was pretty much e rank
There's no ranks in this game. You just have to get it done. I do see new high score of five
I feel like that's very low. I hope that's not out of a hundred we get off sloppy
This was yeah, that could have been cleaned up. Just look at how bad this is. This is terrible
Okay at this point in the line, I I took drugs
I mean it started to kick in yeah
Clearly clearly it started to really kick in about here. How much money do I have? Oh only then is when you took drugs
TV Marina and several boats were damaged yesterday as
thieves broken and got
away with expensive
GPS navigation units Harbor master Jim delish says the Marina has been
subject to a string of
vandalism and
burglary incidents lately you tool right was it pipe bombs? Oh
Oh my goodness. This is fun. Okay, I
Upgraded pipe bombs. There's no upgrades for these really really glad I spent like 500 bucks on this useless thing
Upgrade the fuel count great last rounds. I want these so bad
Yeah, 18 still need those GPS devices would be ashamed to open that demolition investigation
But wouldn't it I just do that. Thanks to take care of the GPS device
Just one problem
They seem to be of a new more secure type and I can't find out there are recent locations without the decryption key
My best bet is that Lee keeps the decryption key in his office safe, but it might also be in that production safe
I have one last favor to ask of you and I think you already know what that might be
the lifting
GPS decryption key is in Lee's safe move the safe to your escape vehicle
If possible also get
fire
Yes, my house
Right. Okay. Well run. No, I can take care of it
No, I can't what happens if this happens. Is it what happens? This is gonna be alright. Okay. Ow
I'm sorry that hurt smashed my fucking hand. Okay. So now let's take a look
Hmm GPS decryption key is in Lee's safe move the safe to your escape vehicle
Possible also get the other safe and pick up all key cabinets. So we're gonna draw this safe is too heavy
We have to okay. I'm gonna pick the safe up with this claw. That's easy enough. All right office safe is right here
Let's go see you. Let's go. Take a look at the claw drop it here. Probably money up here. Oh
Really? Wait, no, I'm gonna do the thing. I'm gonna play chess. That's cash right there. That's a
Wrench, I'm not gonna whatever that word is don't open. Nothing even in that what is a dump truck?
I could put the safe in here. I really wanted to
All right. This is kind of like the fun part of Minecraft without having to play minecraft under box
I don't have to build a house. I just can just break blocks with my
Mining pick it's like more fun. You're a griefer
Griefing simulate minecraft grief simulator. All right, what can I do with this? I feel like I can make a bridge with this
Hold on. Hold on. Let's take don't stop rushing. Just get out there and take it and just survey the area for a little bit
You're good
Must be locked. Well, and that's just too bad, but I've just done that to the lock. Yes
Well, all right, let's take a look. Let's see if any any valuables
Mmm valuables in the couch
valuables in the in the value bill machine money or it is
200 bucks
Bathroom toilet say I don't know. I'm not gonna just say a random word that I don't know what it means
Thing just I cut the thing in half. Hey, you get the money. Let's say what this is something
Let's say
Going to race Atticus off-limits
Really is it now shit. I keep fucking that up there
Sick rollercoaster, dude. I'm gonna break this staircase and just get off limits. Nothing up here. Why'd you say that?
There's nothing even here. I already got it. Oh shit. I thought it like a reset 40 bucks
Capitalism trophy whatever that was nothing paper. Jam. Oh something there. What is it? There's something there. I saw it
Did you see it? I swear to God something was here shit. Okay. Well, whatever
So this is the safe we obviously have a few ways to do this. I'll break that
Okay, so I can load the safe onto the back of the I just beat the level
I just beat it. I'm gonna drop the safe out the window on to the truck. That's safe. There it is
Alright now if I can wait use the dump truck. Yeah
Yeah, but hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Okay, that looks good
I'm gonna drop it in there. Is that set up for this? That's that one. What about what's this over here?
This is another safe. All right, then we're gonna jump jump. We need to jump towards that one. All right. Um, just a key cabinet
I can steal that
Okay, let me just see if this works. This place is fucking filthy. I gotta clean the place up
There's too much debris everywhere. I have to get rid of it. Look, it's just a joke get it's getting caught on everything
What a massive cleanup job. I just gave myself. No, okay, if you hit it again, it just disintegrates. There we go
Cool. All right. We're good. Jot gun the fuck out of this right there. Okay. Let's see if this works. Holy shit. That's
400 okay, where's the escape car?
I don't even care. I'm done. I got like 800 bucks through the walls and shit that makes up for the other objectives
I didn't do minimum minimum minimum. No just for that one. I just made a thousand dollars
I have 900 bucks. What are you talking about? Lee chemicals suffered as the place still on fire another spectacular break-in last night
Where properties were damaged and the perpetrators got away with heavy security?
Equipment according to the police what is happening to look hell you need to locks for your locks now
Says CEO Lawrence Lee jr. Turn this shit off
Thanks. Now. I just need to find someone who can work a safe
I'll get back to you in a bit and let you know how it goes. Okay, hold on tools
I think I want to do the shotgun
I like this a lot and I want more damage more damage and more rounds and more rounds in the pipe on
How much damage is it though? Let's find out
Hmm. I mean, it's that much more than it was before
Bumps. Oh, yeah, let's test that I can die. All right that worked. What's next Gordon? Ooh water tower
I still don't know how but Lee found out about the cars and totally overreacted
I just saved the life of those poor cars and it goes completely mental and vandalizes my property
Do you believe that good thing? I'm properly insured
I thought about ways to get back at him and finally nailed it the iconic water tower at Lee chemicals
His grandfather built it with his bare hands and it has since become a symbol from the entire Lee family
They even use it in their logo type making that tower a little less tall would be a suitable symbol for the small man
He is hmm tower Gordon wants you to get back at Lee by making his iconic towers shorter
Remove the upper part of the tower the fire. Yeah, I didn't even look at it assumed it was there. What's all this bomb?
I have pipe bombs though. Who cares?
What do you mean do it with the water tower the tower? Yeah, watch watch this up there, right?
All right, this is gonna be fucking easy. Oh, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's plank this up
What's the timer on this? Oh
doom eternal
No
All wasn't not falling. Why is it? Why is it? It's keeping this up? Oh, there's one P. All right, hold on ready
This is where I saved the game
inside
Like a squished inside the edge. Holy shit. Let me go. I'm gonna go to the shoot dude. Watch this. Holy shit
It's gonna be fucking awesome. Oh my god ready. I can't fit wait. I I took it down
I shaved it down. Wait, so I push it. I really did just play Django. Whoa
All right, I did it still too tall I was so lazy I won't even do this the right way
I'm so lazy. You know what? Just get me in the fucking side door. I don't care
Huh? So what's the problem? Why don't think I could reach there's a part above the line. Okay, hold on
So those secret hidden stuff it might be I want them. I want money man. Okay, so I'm up here. All right
It's gonna it's connected right there. It's connected right there. Fuck. It's too far away. It's hanging by thread
Bomb I don't try but I don't want to blow up the whole tower 20 bucks. Hold on
I think I just gave myself an opportunity. That's an opportunity right there. Get out of the way. Here we go
I can cut it from here. Cut it down
Cut it down, please. Oh shit. All right, it's been disconnected. It's still point nine meters too tall
Thank God. There's like a weird loony to his hole
Yes, all right, it's this piece right here, okay
Is that the only one I don't have any more shotguns five meters too tall. Oh
No
No, it's the top of the window shit. It's not soft-locked. I was gonna throw shit at it. It's I'm bigger
Give me this defeated the entire purpose. This looks pretty heavy. Oh
It's still I was like this is one of the cars from cars look at his eyes
This is lightning McQueen, but he's a little down. You're alright, dude. You look a little sad. He's high as fuck. Yeah
One two, three. It's even better. Oh you stupid asshole. Come on. Oh
Catch it. No two more shot two more opportunities to do this. I have to get it. I'm so close
Okay, it any more bombs. Wait, here's a bomb that dude. That's shaking it. Oh
Yeah
What's in here? Look what the cat dragged in get out of where is it's too tall that little point right there you game
No, how did I screw that up? Try another I'm gonna try. Okay, put it down. I don't think about just do it and go
Okay. Now I'm I'm gonna go I'm gonna look go look around to steal stuff out of this guy's house
I'm gonna steal shit. Now. Let's go find some stuff to take. I don't be an asshole. Like what are you doing?
Nothing in here. Yeah. Oh no goodies in here. No goodies in here at this cart. It doesn't move anymore goodies
Oh, definitely goodies in here. You kidding me? No goodies, but he's in the dumpster
Oh, what about behind the dumpster? Am I in the dumpster? Nothing behind the dumpster. Are you serious?
Okay, I think I've gotten all the goodies I can get here. Am I blind? Am I though? Am I what did I miss 80 bucks?
Nice. Okay. Huh? Okay. What about over there? It looks alright. I'm let me go over here. There's no time limit or anything
What's going on in here free stuff 120 bucks? I'll take it toilets. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Look at that 75 bucks
That's it. What about in here? There's like a strangest door. I've ever seen what the hell is up with this door
Steal the toilets. I don't think I can do that. What is all this weird scooby-doo house? Uh, is this right?
I don't think I should do that. I don't know what that was, but I don't maybe I shouldn't have broken that
Some like portal shit. You just freed it. There's nothing even up here. All right, I'm out. Let's go
Destroy the dam you nuts blind on the roof. Yeah, is it
Super blind but hold on super blind on the roof super super super blind
Super blind. Okay, you're super blind on the roof at this a laser a distance lasers only with 140 dollars
I found wallets with more money in that. All right, I'm going they're gonna kill me so too tight
Drive the truck into the dam. Well, I can't really do that anymore. Can I how much CBD oil? Did you take none?
I have not none today zero. Well above the dam. That's not the mission. That might be the mission
Next or something. I don't want to spoil the mission that plus that weird
Explosive blue sphere. It's gonna be the next mission. Just watch there's also a sandbox mode
Yeah, that looks pretty cool, too. You do a porky pig impression
That's all folks not very good it was mega bad
Whatever I just what's all this drugs super blast super blast and
All I can do looking better. They turn the gas back on coffee never tasted better
I was skeptical about working with mr. Wu in the first place, but he does pay well
So does the new client Lee chemicals did they contact you directly? By the way, I heard on the news
There's some madman on the loose around here. Hope you remember to lock the door at night
Okay, Gordon really took this shit a step too far. You probably heard it on the news, but he hit my tower
The Lee tower my poor grandfather's probably turning in his grave right now
It'll cost me a fortune to rebuild that get back at Gordon
But he's so loaded with money that whatever I do you just pay someone to fix it. They land way to get to him
Strike where his fat wallet can't protect him this precious art collection
Some of those paintings would also make a nice contribution to the restoration
fund for my new tower
Also, by the way, there's some construction work going on at the marina
Seen a lot of high-end tools laying around I could actually use some of them for rebuilding the tower mind going there and getting
Some no get that on your own time. I'm gonna fucking steal the artwork
There is a lot of stuff to do here steal at least four paintings from the art museum
From are you high be honest? No, but I am gonna take a break and go pee and get some water
In about four hours. I have not gone to the bathroom right back. Oh
Sorry, that's like a little longer. I drank a full water and I refilled it and drank it again
How was the bong rip? It's fine. It was fine. Okay, let's keep going here
All right available targets to steal all the paintings steal at least four paintings
Okay, they're pretty spread out too. It's time to investigate wait
Where were you didn't we already fuck up this guy's is it still say eat my own ass on his house?
Oh, no, he got it removed. He got a room. See sorry. Yeah. Yeah, he got it
He actually got it removed one full water, please waiter
Oxwine, that's good shit find the fireplace guaranteed. I guarantee there's something back here. What have you?
I'm so glad what have you? Oh
Swiss chocolates 20 bucks. I'll take it sauna. No beer. No shower
valuable soaps know like expensive soap
Really? Of course you have expensive soap drug money right in here the sauna
Precision thermometer. I'm doing I'm getting some stuff here. Don't just explode
That's it for this house. Let's go to a house, too
Alright, let's check this one first. There's a painting in here
That could not have been uglier. That was the most non-clean. Oh, look at these fast cars. Okay, so pick it up
Do I have to deliver it anywhere or do I just have to get them just take them? That's it, right?
I don't have to drop them off anywhere. There's just they just get them. Just take them 30 bucks. This is a joystick
Alright, let's get it about that's a I like that painting. That's like one coin
And plan this shit out
Extremely fast car worthless worthless. All right, we got very fast car which we can steal
Drive straight or drive over here. Wait, can I make a
Hold on. Hold on just a second. That's not gonna work. I didn't even want just make a ramp up the stairs
There are literally stairs right there. I know I just seen if I could just boom like up there
Okay, drive up these stairs. Okay, drive up get out of car here
What does what is here we get four of these fucking things? Okay, there's one right there. It is the doughnut
Deal that one. So that's one
Alright, I can go looks like I'm gonna I'm probably gonna go like this, right?
You would assume that I would go I start on the left and go all the way and then drive to the boat
That's probably the idea. That's a muffin. It's not a muffin coffee maker
oysters
Silverware nice. All right, I'm making some money. This is good
Expensive something expensive. Give me something expensive now. Oh
Holy shit. Oh, that's a nice. That's a Simpsons car. It's a Homer Simpson car
That must be the Simpsons house. No, I think I okay. So one two
Okay, let's back this up a good idea. Oh check this shit out. We're gonna Simpsons the fuck out of this
I'm gonna leave this car here. You can get the one here
No, I want to go in the elevator bring it back down. Why do I I am evil Homer? I am evil Homer
What is that from? Oh a car table. There's some blackjack. Nothing expensive here. I hate these lights underneath
Puke inducing fluorescent weird neon lights get rid of them all of them up corn machine. You have a popcorn machine
That's awesome
corn machine maintenance utility
Coffee under the table, which one I'm a blackjack table. It's there how to become a snooker champ. Oh
It's cool. All right the expense of alcohol
Guys own drive-in movie theater. I guess it's not it. I guess it's just a regular movie. Why would this be driving?
Oh, well, I'll show you how no I thought I was on the ground floor
I was gonna say that it could be a drive-in movie theater if I wanted to be
182 bucks. Oh, well, oh, okay. Here's one right here. All right, so it's one
This one's kind of all the way back here though, please spend the next 20 minutes driving all the way up there
I don't think I can even do that. I'll break the boards and I drive over it grab grab grab grab
Our all right. Hold on. Let me let me we're gonna make some room here. I go
What is like through here? All right, wait, wait
Leave this don't break that. Okay, so then I can go this way
Smash this shit this one in here. Okay, there's one in here too. Where's this one 120 bucks?
That's a lot. Is this one upstairs? It's your favorite number. Um, I don't know
I think I'm just gonna go for it. Wait, cuz then I can go one two
Three four one. Oh, yeah. Hell. Yeah. Okay grab this one straight through there grab that one
Out the window into the car down here grab that one grab that one grab that one and we're out
Let's give it a try. Not yet. I've been well
valuables valid valid valid words are hard
valuables not valuables
Valuables I
Promise I am NOT high right now. I
Swear on everything. Hmm. Hmm. Oh good makeup
Let's get a shot. I don't remember where this one is fuck again face cam
No, I don't have a shirt on but far so good. Let's go. Wait, I didn't even what did I even do that for?
Where's this one in here? Isn't there there is one in here? Where is it? I gotta get this down. It's up there
Okay, hold on. I fucked it up beatbox the Simpsons intro
Inefficient inefficient using stairs in it using a fucking staircase and now what I don't know what's next. Oh the gazebo I
Need a car
It's so inefficient. This is horrible. Do it again. You don't fuck going upstairs
We're driving right by this and going to the gazebo. Oh
Why are you stuck here? Oh, no
minimum minimum minimum
Show ankles
Why do you want why it's a little show ankles?
I need a car. I need a car. I need a car. I need a car right now. Give me a car
I need a car
Got this first part down the ideas you grab this shit and then just keep driving
All right. I gotta keep I have to keep the Simpsons car
Simpsons cars the key to all this the key to wellness. Come on. What's with this weird computer thing?
That was weird. All right, I kept the car
So laggy I can't even drive it
Just like stuffed. I don't think my dog does
This is just a pair of covers just stuffed his face under it
minimum minimum minimum
This should be motorcycles. I've reset already right reset
Okay, okay. I gotta go break that shit. I'm clearing that up. You know, I'm saying I'm clear
Like that's just gonna fuck me up every time I just jump this
Remember to feel like this should be doing more damage. Why this it's a bunch of flowers. Don't why can't I just burn this?
Please don't tell me this is stuck. I'm gonna try it
Why even put that here
You broke the wood
Mmm, whatever. It's this we're gonna do the same thing the same thing stands
It's a little different get these trees the fuck out of the way
First and foremost get out of here move the stumps
Push it push the tree into the ocean, please. How did I make this harder?
How did I make this harder? I just made the obstacles harder to get by watch out for the car. Hold on
These things are terrible. I can't even pick it up burn move this fucking thing
Wait, I it's not enough. Okay. Hold on. You set the bed Oreo on fire
I good because then it'll burn this whole place down. Okay, does it fit? It's crap out of the way
It's fucking lettuce out of here the alert. Oh shit. Yeah, nice toasted Oreo bed still spreading
He's high for Oreos. No, I you know, I would take something else though. I take like a large
Pepperoni pizza right now, but my stomach's kind of all fucked up. So I can't really do that. Oh
Like it's rice and bananas for me
Looks like it's good enough. It'd be fine. Let's just make sure I can get through it
But and I can still use this car, but hold on hold on now
Now I got to do the process of taking this shit down. No, just keep it as one piece throw it in the pool
It's we're turning this way. I have to go that way
Going off this pick this up change cars and get the fuck out of here gonna be sick load load
What's wrong? There's something was raising. This thing is still raising up and down. Yeah. Oh, yeah this piece get this out of here
This is gonna be a piece of glass
Think I bumped into this last time. All right, I'm gonna use this car to carve the path for the other car
Damn it, dude
Just leave it who cares? Yeah, I bumped into something. Okay, this looks this looks better
Looks better. This is better at the cement truck. Genius. I dumped cement a path carve. Here we go
Half has been carved out grab that back in here. Take this right carve this out
Perfect done. We take we get in there steal the painting that's in here grab that car fuck off to the exit
Going this way. Okay, we get in there jump these jumps and pull there forward. Perfect right here
Something underneath this car there is and the lettuce. Hey good. That's set there. This one's set here
Hey, it is the movie theater. All right, save it and I'm ready to go
I think it's now time to actually complete this mission. What do you think? What do you say and
Fuck I should have broke that beforehand
Straight through I drove a little too far over the line
By the way, why don't I put one of the insane sports cars over here?
What drive what happened?
What the fuck? How did that even happen? I don't understand. How did that fucking happen? How did this happen? Come on?
This is a good plan
Holy shit. Oh lost like three seconds so far. Did I fall out?
Whatever
Where am I driving to where am I driving to where am I driving when I drive to all right, I get it
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it die
Fucking mulch
No, I just don't make it. I can still make it. I can still make it take the Jeep. All right
I need to get a running start here. Yeah, take the Jeep. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna take you. Yeah, there's no time in the jeep
Yeah
Only four. Oh getting all of those. I wonder what the perfect route is. That's hard
I guess when you get the actual route down, it's probably not really
Yeah
How is the Jeep faster than the car speedrunners ride the planks to go away faster Jeep can drive off-road
Is a perfect run. Let me see. Let's watch the perfect run
I actually am come totally totally interested and see how this works save it here just to make sure I don't crash
Watch the perfect run highly facing
Hey, why why whoa? Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what's going on my voice? Wait, wait, wait
What's happening with my voice? What's going on with my voice? Do you hear this? What's going on here?
Don't move because if you stay like this sometimes they could stay like this for a long time
I need I'm a new I'm a different person now today. We're gonna I think it's gone. No, it's still there
No, it's still there coming up next on the morning news
We have a large amount of people have been returning their or no, it's gone. It's Tom Hanks
Shit, I could have done a Tom Hanks right there. Oh, yeah
Why did I not know it was Tom Hanks? This is huge. So wait, he just like falls out the window. Okay, you ready?
Let's I want to do this again. Okay, so he falls off grabs falls into the car
What? Holy shit. What the hell was that? All right, that was weird. Hold on. Is it what's wrong with my my player fucked up?
an 80 dude
That's a great tech technique you fall off
blanks up what wait, how are you know, he's making holes to take them out. What a genius
He's moving the whole shit
What the fuck? Why is he spraying?
Why is he spray? Oh my god. He's got all the cars in the perfect place, too
You gotta be kidding me. This part up that part right here is unbelievable
What does he what how does he even do this?
goes up the
Up like a mean what?
That's amazing. You spent three hours doing a bit. I've never gonna be capable of doing this
I don't know why you think I am. I think I'm gonna be capable of doing that. That's never gonna happen, man
Okay, I am a breaker. Everyone stay indoors and away from windows. Oh, it's uh, we have a a
Storm outside when you are looking for a bright future
choose
Bayrans missing artwork. Oh
Good evening. I am a claim adjuster at curate the insurance group investigating an art incident that happened to Gordon Woo
Recently, mr. Woo claims to know who's responsible for the stolen paintings a mr. Lawrence Lee jr.
But he's very keen to not involve the police
Gordon's account has caused us some financial strain recently and is in our interest to bring back the paintings as discreetly and swiftly as possible
According to our intelligence the paintings are hidden at the marina
I know Gordon's been working with you in the past. Maybe you can help out wait to have to bring them back
I just got rid of him a shotgun. How about I feel like I don't I'm not very good with the planks. I'm going full
Chaotic evil mode chaotic neutral. This is like this is like lawful good, right?
This is like chaotic evil. This is like chaotic neutral. This is like chaotic good. This is lawful
Neutral. No, this is probably lawful. Yeah lawful neutral lawful evil and
true
Neutral and none of you like that at all
All right, let's bring the art back
Let's go Lee has hidden four paintings at the marina help the insurance company retrieve them stop farming minus twos
Well, how what else am I supposed to do?
Okay, I have to get all the art back. It's definitely there's a fire alarm. That's it
Don't set off the fire alarm with this and they're not rigged for anything else. Oh look just happened lightning. Oh
my goodness, uh
Where's the first one? So don't set up the fire alarm
What if I'm out of that's out of my control?
All right, we got it struck the house. All right, I get this. Oh god. Okay, I get it
I get I understand what it wants me to do move out of the way, please
Uh, I get it. I get it. Yes. Where's the painting painting? Where's the painting? It's painting upstairs
Do you not have stairs to go into the top floor your fucking house? What were the stairs?
Alright, I got one. That wasn't even it
There it is. Okay, there is secrets up there. Hold on. I can't do this. I can't I I'm supposed to do
I'm about to rip the fucking power cord on my computer. I can't do planks
dude, dude chill
How come it blew up the stairs the one place it shouldn't have 400 400. Okay, I got everything I need
Let's go. No fire in there. All right, move on to the next building which is it was worth it
Yeah, it was no fire fire alert. Well, it's buried under a bunch of rubble. I can't get under there
Destroy the stairs again. Fuck. What the heck? I was this one in the back. I'm gonna chill. Okay. No
Oh
Shit this whole place is burning down any secrets up here. I don't see any money or anything
All right fires out any anything to steal not really. All right
Now we need that painting paintings up in the top left. All right
I just write on it like Timmy's room. Is it on the outside of the house bizarre place to put that? Okay
Oh, I'm gonna take a boat. We're gonna go cross lightning strike. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no
I got it. I got it. I'm on it. I'm on it. I'm on it. I'm on it. Oh fuck. I gotta get up
It's someone the rain be helping you would assume right? All right, that's taken care of is it one in here shit
There's one. Oh
It's been all the way down. I was just when I just in this one. I was attached there. Oh
What am I doing? I just don't know. I'm going back to do this last one. So I don't have to wrap around
No, I'm not high. I'm not high every day guys. There's no fires anywhere. I'm fine. I got it. There's another fire
No, it's on another house. I gotta get up there now up up up
Up knock all the houses into the water. You're a mean person. You're a mean person. All right now where was it next?
I only got one more just the warehouse the boat is sinking. It's fine
I just had to get it over here so I can go over here. Next step warehouse. There's no sound
Yes, there is he's gonna hear a sound oh when we watch the video, the sound was really loud
So I had to turn it down. I thought you guys just fucking with me. All right, give me a car
This is slow as hell. This thing sucks
No fire?
I can walk faster.
How did I miss?
That's not even possible to miss.
Sorry I pressed tab during like an exciting moment.
Okay go go go go go go hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry!
Where's the painting?
It's up there.
Alright fire alert!
Fire, there's a fire!
Fire alert!
Alert there's a fire!
I gotta get in.
Get in get in and get in and get in!
OW!
No no there's a fire in here!
It's quiet, I gotta do these planks.
Oh my god, you just gotta do it right here.
Oh!
No!
I just gotta give her the painting
and get the fuck out of here.
Give her the painting and get out.
Give her the painting.
Where's this fucking painting?
Fuck, I just reload.
Oh, I'm so pissed.
I'm so mad.
Somebody just dipped me into acid.
I just got dipped into like hot fucking...
Ah, this is so far away.
I gotta bind save to left mouse button.
I'm doing that one last.
Like, I'm not even there yet.
Like, why would you put it that crazy?
I'm not even there.
I'm not even here.
Dude, how does one get rid of this fire this quickly?
How does one do that?
Where, where's the...
Excuse me, where's the fire?
You see a fire?
Where am I going?
It's cause I fucking skipped it.
You asshole.
I have a solution.
Throw them, just throw them in the water.
I just don't feel like detaching that.
Could have just opened the front door.
Where is it?
It's the last piece.
All right, yes.
Last one.
It's one, that last one,
I gotta go all the way down here.
Save this shit.
What about goodies?
They could be goodies.
And I'm gonna leave without at least one or two goodies.
In the attic.
Yup, 240 bucks.
Antique fucking coins.
What was I, what am I doing?
Why did I just do that?
Okay, we're ready to drive.
This car can't drive.
Oh, I'm just taking the boat
around the whole damn place.
I don't care.
What are your thoughts of collabing with...
I don't know who that is.
Is that place on fire?
The building's on fire, isn't it?
Just don't, who cares?
I should have been paying attention to the road
that's made out of liquid.
Why did I do that?
You just ignored a raid?
I got raided?
Oh shit, did I get raided?
Who raided?
Did I get raided?
Who came in?
I need to get up on top.
Oh my fucking God, please don't do this to me.
Where's the rest of it?
Oh shit, this is where planks have to make some sense.
Stop spreading.
Stop spreading, please.
Why is it spreading so much?
I just told it not to do that.
Sorry, to put the house fire out, I had to shoot it.
It's out, we're good.
Save the game.
It's okay, it's just this bottom row of teeth.
All right, sayonara, fog.
That one was fun, I like that one.
I like the idea of needing to use your tools
besides just steal something that's attached to an alarm.
A new tool, by the way, which those are fun too though.
What's the new tool?
Another gun?
Why would I care about gun when I have shotgun?
It's more accurate.
Should I do range?
Yeah, shotgun, I like the shotgun.
Let's max this out.
TV, I did this.
No more TV.
It's time for you to go to bed.
It sounds horrible.
You feel like this is gonna pop?
This is like a bee's nest.
It's growing.
It's a silent hill enemy.
I killed it, don't worry.
Hey, nice job with the paintings.
A little charred here and there,
so I'll have to find someone to retouch them a bit
before they return to Gordon.
He won't know the difference.
Now, Gordon has an insurance problem.
Not only did Lee steal some of our most beloved paintings,
but the insurance company is causing me headaches too.
I'm a premium customer.
I still haven't seen any money for those paintings.
I'll deal with Lee later.
But right now I need to take that insurance payout
in my own hands.
I don't have a personal grudge with anyone at the company,
so I'd like to just poke them a bit where it hurts.
Any respected company the most, their bank account.
I have a top notch policy of my cars,
so if some of this were to be stolen,
they'd need to cough it up.
I'll hook up a few cars to the alarm system
to make it look legit.
Please be gentle.
Help Gordon steal at least three of his own cars
to help him with the insurance payout.
I feel like we just did this one.
We did it for the other guy,
but it's in the daytime this time.
They steal three cars.
Steal, not drown.
Oh.
What are the go-kart track?
We'll in a minute.
This car has some pep to it.
Nice.
Ooh, welcome to Mario Kart.
That was super low effort and very low energy.
I could have done, welcome to Mario Kart.
Select your player.
60 seconds.
How the fuck do you do this one?
Is it already on fire?
Restart this.
No, I can't drive this around.
Sorry.
So how am I supposed to do this?
This is wired.
They're all wired.
So I have to drive them back here
and then is there any other cars that are on the map?
I guess I could leave them around.
Take a look.
I could play, okay.
I guess the idea is this.
I just have a bunch of spare cars here.
You know what I mean?
Like, so I drive that one up here.
Take that car to the next one.
Take this car back here.
Mr. Raid?
Who raided?
Raid Raid?
Oh, this one's a prized position too, isn't it?
All right, hold on.
I'm moving around so much.
This is gonna fuck me up.
I know it.
This one, we got one here.
I'm not gonna drive away.
I'm just gonna get it in the right spot.
Come on, wait, wait, can I?
Save it here.
Hold on.
How far does the tether go?
Raid song.
Thank you for the raid.
Yay, it's okay.
All right, perfect.
All right, keep that here.
Keep going.
Thanks.
That one's this one.
This one's that way.
This one's this way, that way.
That one's this way.
Take this shit out of the way so I can move this.
All right, they connected.
Drive that one down here through the, okay.
All right, here's the deal.
You start, drive this one, drive this one.
Up, ding, drive this one.
Down, ding, we need another car.
I need a second dummy car there.
Buy me a car.
And a new viewer, can I get a song?
Hey Jack mate, welcome to the stream.
I love.
Don't say that, don't say that.
Don't say that.
Do not say that.
Not that part.
I need a second car.
You don't love us?
What are you talking about?
What was I doing?
Oh, I'm kidding, relax everybody.
I'm kidding.
It's a joke, we're joking around today.
It's a joke stream.
I lost a fucking tire, I lost a tire.
I lost a tire, is that gonna be bad?
I think that's gonna be bad,
but I might still be able to get there.
All right, I need another car.
Ah, there's a car.
Ooh, I might be able to actually carry this.
I think I can, yeah, I can carry this.
Save it, I will, shit.
Scoop it up like a fucking pancake, easy.
No, what?
Get on here.
Okay, success.
There's no timer, right?
What if I just deliver this?
Oh shit, okay, thank God I saved it.
Why did it explode?
It was ready to go.
I didn't do anything.
That was, that would've taken anything.
Okay, well now that I know that, I gotta be careful.
It's rigged to explode.
No, fucking idiots, don't.
I'm just, I don't wanna be in the,
when you touch the circle, just leave it?
No, but hold on, but look where it is.
You know for a fact I'm gonna speed up here with a car
with five seconds left and I'm gonna crash
and this is just gonna explode.
I'm trying to get it on the grass.
There, okay.
Don't explode, oh, let go, please.
I know everyone's freaking out.
I know, I know, just give me a second.
Okay, okay, it's ready, it's ready.
Those who have, I want this back.
Okay, it was ready before?
No, I want this back.
I wanna see if I can do that to any other car.
Boom, right here.
I'm gonna get this one too.
We're hooked up to walls?
You only need three, yeah, but what am I,
just gonna do the minimum every time I do a mission?
No, I wanna at least get one, good one.
All right, what am I gonna try?
I wanna try, I wanna get this guy over here.
Oh, minimum, minimum, minimum.
That's from a video from like 2012, by the way.
On Star's channel, we played a game called Minimum
and I don't know, we just played new games sometimes.
All right, that just looks fun.
All right, let's take, let's pick up the whole thing.
All right, this is attached to,
I have to attach that to something, to a crane.
First time I've used a crane the whole game.
Almost happened, almost.
You were close to being able to write Omega Low.
Almost, it's close.
How am I gonna do this?
How do I extend the crane?
I never did this before.
Arm, hook, arm?
Shit, is that gonna work?
What's going on?
What is going on?
Kanye in chat, Kanye is not in the chat, man.
Okay, I got it.
Slow down, slow down, slow it down.
I need to make some, hold on.
Hey, the device, this is the device,
but this can't fall off.
How do I get this off without doing that?
Berman Supreme is in chat.
You know, I probably would be like more excited about that.
It's like that was the boot on his head
and always runs for president in like New Hampshire, right?
Okay, we're gonna pull this.
You know, it's just like, fuck it,
let's just pull it off and see what happens.
Easy, which way do I go?
All right, I gotta go back that way, so we're gonna,
okay, this is that, what happened?
What?
Why'd I fall over?
Fuck, there are no raids right now.
I wanna go on this road, this is the safest road.
I'll win, raid, here comes a raid.
Raid, raid, raid, raid, raid, raid.
Can you believe it, can you believe it?
Can you believe it, there's a raid,
can you believe it, there's a raid,
can you believe it, there's a raid.
Why do you guys like pretending there are raids recently?
I've noticed that.
Come on, down here, get down here.
I don't think I can even do this.
How did I fuck this up?
Don't hook the plank.
Oh wait, I can get, yeah, I can get rid of this shit now.
I don't even need this anymore.
What the fuck am I doing?
Perfect, that's better, all right, let's go.
Hook both of them?
Can I hook both ends?
I can't, can I even do that?
I don't think I can do that.
I mean, like that?
All right, that worked, yeah, that worked.
Slow down, slow, slow, slow, slow, I'm good.
Oh, that's gonna cost a little bit of money to fix that.
Get off of me.
Get the fuck off of me.
You dick, look what you did.
I would just wrap her on.
Gary Busey raid.
What's up, Gary?
Thanks for the raid, man.
Everyone didn't think I was gonna do this.
Look at that, just being shown up.
Bill Murray just came in with a raid.
Bill, what's up, Bill?
What was Bill Murray streaming today?
Amnesia, oh, that's cool.
You like it, is it any fun?
Well, I hope you had a good stream, Bill.
All right, I'm ready, I'm ready to get four.
I need to turn it around a little.
That's fine, that's okay.
Wait, look forward a little bit.
All right, right there, save it.
All right, I got one, two, let's get four cars right now.
Let's go.
Here we go, ready?
I'm gonna get this one.
I'm gonna get, I'm gonna get them all, I'm gonna get them.
All right, ready?
These two right here.
He's still playing this, yeah, man.
One, two, three, go.
Look at how much time I have.
Shit.
All right, I got four.
I could have maybe gotten five.
I have to leave.
Sick.
I'm the developer.
Hi, I'm the developer of this game.
I'm very happy to see you enjoying Teardown.
It's my passion project,
which I worked hard on for the last year or so.
Want you to know that we left a little Easter egg
specifically for you under the furnace in the base.
Check it out.
No, you didn't.
Not at the real depth.
Furnace under the base?
Let's go check it out.
What if it's not a lie?
That's what your laundry machine looks like inside.
Okay, under the furnace.
Is this actual, wait, is this real?
This is not just some elaborate debate?
Banana.
Oh, what the fuck?
Cause we're the banana bros.
Are you kidding me?
That's unbelievable.
I call you guys like the banana bros.
I'm always eating bananas.
I'm always talking about bananas.
I'm always showing bananas.
I did a banana costume last year.
That's unbelievable.
Have we talked about banana splits?
Every time there's a new sub,
I peel a banana and I fucking go,
mmm, banana bros.
That's crazy that you put that in.
Thanks, dude.
It's a great game.
It's a really good game.
It's really fun.
Thanks for the shout out, dude, seriously.
How do I get out?
Oh shit, it's obsidian.
I can't leave.
Oh, whatever it is.
Thanks for the Easter egg, man.
And hey, I see that you're not subbed.
I mean, we gotta get you in the banana bros.
It's me, the depth.
What an elaborate thing that that person just did
to tell me to go into the furnace to get $600
for the hidden money.
You could have just said,
check under the furnace, there's money.
There's a banana for money.
No, pretend Easter egg.
Me, playing to my ego.
I got two more.
Guess what?
I managed to decrypt the GPS locations
and appointed me to Hollow Rock Island,
an old fish processing plant
now making some kind of energy drink.
BT is short for blue tide.
Why didn't I think of that before?
My daughter's totally addicted
to that disgusting sugary slug.
I'm drinking water, by the way.
I'm here right now.
It's a bit worn down, but pretty.
I need to find out where the Lee payments go.
Have a look at the blue tide computers for this one.
I just got this awesome idea for humiliating Gordon.
You know that ridiculous undersized racetrack
he keeps in his backyard to pretend to be a race driver?
Wouldn't it be funny if he came home
to a new track record on that display?
You're a decent driver.
By the way, those paintings you helped me with earlier,
they didn't make it through the thunderstorm,
burned up every single one.
What are the odds?
I gotta do the racetrack?
Help Lee annoy Gordon by beating the track record
on his private racetrack.
Oh, let's do this one.
We just got a new sub?
Oh, potassium power.
Can I see some potassium power emotes
in the chat, please, guys?
Power, power, power.
I love that word.
Finish lap in 25 seconds.
Finish lap in 20 seconds.
I get to choose what car I can use.
Total corruption, total power.
Total corruption.
Sing the banana song.
Yummy, delicious banana.
I can't wait to eat.
Okay, where do I find a car?
I just love delicious banana.
Do I do it with like the Winnebago?
What a dog shit stream that would be, seriously.
If I did that, if that was my thing,
we were like the banana bros?
For what?
That's what my entire channel identity is around.
I like bananas.
What a stupid persona that would be.
We got a new sub.
I love to eat bananas.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Like a banana?
All right, how do I start?
Go, start the race.
Oh, start the race.
What's your fruit sona?
What does it say?
Um, how do I go?
Oh, get ready.
Two, one, go.
Oh, yeah.
Did I win?
Or did I just cheat?
You're too slow.
I was.
All right, no more.
I'm just gonna do like fucking noises.
Ah, here we go.
Take the fast car.
Take the other fast car.
Yeah, this thing is blazing.
I'm gonna smash this dude's record.
Here we go.
Ready, one, two.
Oh, I can't move until it.
Well, let me get it right on the line.
Car's way too fast.
I should have saved it.
Why did I not?
Why did I not save it?
Why did you not save it?
Is there a reason we need to attack
this coronavirus head on?
How do I?
Ernie, that's Boris Johnson, dude.
What are you talking about?
Ernie, I'm home.
Ernie, I'm gone.
Oh, I didn't get to do the funny thing.
Where's this cool car?
I'm lost.
Oh, it's over there.
Remember, just clear a path so you can cheat.
No, I wanna do it for real.
You know why I wanna do it for real?
Because the last time I had to do a race,
I just made it easy.
I didn't do it.
I chickened out and I skipped it.
I'm not skipping it this time.
Here we go.
How far away can I be?
Get ready.
Damn it, it knows if you cheat.
Let's go.
Boo.
No.
Game sucks.
Game's not good.
Ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready.
Yup.
Did I forget to turn the car?
I was so happy about doing that.
Hey, dude, I've been a viewer for over six years,
but I've always wondered,
what is that liquid you inject yourself
in the pre-stream video?
As a diabetic myself,
I can really relate to having to inject insulin.
What?
What are you talking about?
That was a mega drift.
Too much drift.
Missed the punch line.
I've never seen insulin that was disgustingly brown
like that, thanks for the laughs.
I don't get it.
I don't inject anything into my body on stream.
What?
Wait, here it comes.
Eric, is this Tom?
No, I thought that, no, it was on the way.
Pfft.
Ha ha ha.
Stop, I'm not drifting.
It's just the game is hard to control.
I'm not, I'm not drifting.
The car's just incredibly fast and it's a slick crack.
It's slick.
I was here, I was here.
Fuck, I didn't do it.
Get back on the track.
Oh, it's too much drift.
Don't spin out.
Don't, don't, that person is gone.
Guys, yeah.
That drift was perfect.
Yeah, but look, it's hard.
Use a controller.
No, I'm a PC gamer.
Pfft.
Holy shit, that's a lot of community subs.
Shady Seas, thanks for the 20 subs.
Actually, actually a shitload of subs.
Thanks for the 20 subs.
Thanks for the 20 delicious bananas.
Not bad.
I was here, I was here, I was here, I was here.
Wait, there might be stuff in here.
Free shit, I have 900 bucks.
I'm gonna buy something after this.
On more, remember that one.
I sounded like a tool shed coming down the stairs.
Let's finish the job.
This isn't a pasta.
Jerma, who are you talking to?
It's been 12 years since the accident
and you haven't been taking your medication
for a few months.
Okay, thanks.
Five month subscriber.
Jerma, who are you talking to?
Money, lots of it.
Oh, I missed a shitload of stuff.
What the hell am I doing?
Hey, Zurich.
Zurich, duh, thanks for the $50.
5,000 bits from Zurich.
They say banana bros.
Thanks, man, appreciate it.
Welcome to the banana bros.
That's 5,000 bits.
That's a shitload of money, thank you.
We had Shady Seas gave 20 community subs.
They also gave 100 bucks.
I missed that a long time ago.
This was like three hours ago.
Shady Seas, 10,000 bits.
They say, hope you're doing well, Jerma.
I just got back from the hospital
for an infection in my see-some
that they haven't seemed to figure out what's causing it.
This is the second time I've ended up hospitalized for it.
It's frustrating.
Streams like yours that help getting the recovery easier.
What's the see-some?
Wait, where is that?
Is it in your stomach?
Connects to the appendix.
Oh shit.
Well, hopefully you feel better.
Second time you've been hospitalized for it.
Hopefully you don't have to do that again.
As some of that has medical problems
that are sort of just don't go away
and kind of come out of nowhere,
I can understand where you're coming from.
But I wish you a complete and swift recovery.
Medical problems suck.
Oh, there was a raid too.
There was a raid from Charborg.
Thank you, Charborg.
If any of the Charborgs are still here.
Thanks, guys.
Atmostarfish gave five subs.
NormalOwl gave seven.
TheFoolie gave five.
DestroyDude gave five.
And InkCat gave five.
Community subs.
Thanks, guys.
I missed them from earlier, but as always,
if anyone wants to give this channel money,
it's, wait, we have another raid right now.
Lazy Purple comes in.
Lazy Purple with a raid.
Hey everybody from Lazy Purple's stream.
Hope you had a day full of...
Streams.
That was terrible.
Potassium.
Hope you had a day full of potassium.
Cream.
Banana cream.
Look, it's been six hours.
I don't have any comedy routines left in my fucking mind.
Anyways, thanks for the raid.
Welcome, everybody.
Hope you had a good stream.
Thanks, Lazy Purple.
Welcome all the Lazy Purples.
What do you call your community?
Purples?
Purple.
The lazy fucks?
Is it really?
I don't know what it is.
It's pretty funny, actually.
Thanks, though.
Welcome, guys.
This is called...
You don't know what this is.
Maybe you do.
Maybe Lazy's played it.
It's a game where you just break everything.
It's a whole game about breaking stuff.
Every single pixel can be destroyed.
Every single one.
No exceptions.
And the game is called Air It Down.
I need that computer.
Oh, thank God it's still standing.
Tools.
Hype bomb.
More.
I've got a lot of money.
Should I do...
I'll be...
I'm so bad with the planks.
I can't even use it.
Max out the shotgun?
Yeah.
Let's do max shotgun.
That's good.
What's next?
It's still going.
I'm right here.
It's a bit worn down.
All right.
Yeah, this is where we have to decrypt the GPS.
Blue Tide Computers.
This is a new place.
Steal computers for Parisa to investigate lease payments.
This is a new area.
Blue Tide Computers.
I gotta be honest.
This game's early access.
I did not expect it to be
like a six plus potential hour campaign here.
And there's a sandbox mode
and there's a create level mode.
I mean, if there's ever an early access game
that I would say this deserves to be supported,
it's definitely this one.
I'm shocked that there's a full like six plus hour campaign.
And it's not done, apparently.
Better than Watch Dogs?
Yes, it is.
This is a better game than Watch Dogs.
I will say that a thousand times.
All right, what's our objective?
A lot, actually.
Okay, we need to steal this.
We'll take a look.
That just repeats whatever words Jerma says.
This is the best stream on Twitch.
Oh, don't say true.
You're supposed to say the other thing I just said.
This is the worst stream on Twitch.
This one looks elaborate.
Very elaborate, actually.
All right, we gotta go that way.
It was the best of streams.
It was the worst of streams.
Is that Charles Dickens?
Who is that?
Can't break that?
Yes, I can.
I kill, excuse me?
That can't be broken?
What is it, Veggie Tales?
Yeah, Veggie Tales.
It was the best of times.
It was the worst of times.
Not Veggie Tales.
No secrets.
This is stupid.
What?
Nothing in the fridge, either.
Why even do that?
Why open them when you can just smash them?
I mean, it's fun to just break stuff.
That's the only reason why I'm doing this.
Just fucking throw this thing out the window.
Who gives a shit?
Stream's wild.
I'm too high for this.
Don't take as much.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Whoa.
What is this bank vault down here?
It's a literal bank vault.
Shit.
Okay, can I?
Wait, I can cut through this.
We're getting in this.
Oh my God, this is a lot of money.
I can't get in there.
Are you serious?
Don't burn the place down.
Can I go through the ceiling?
Dig?
I don't think I can dig underneath that.
Keep that in a, keep that over here.
Wait a minute.
Go to the ceiling.
Shit, how do I get in here?
Where'd that go?
Shit.
I always torched this whole place.
I gotta find a way in there.
All right, what do we got?
This has gotta be like a side entrance, right?
Or like a little thing to go in.
All right, here we go.
Look, is it great?
Is it great?
Damn it.
Maybe I can crash into it.
You think I can just drive into it?
There is gold down there.
It's glowing and it's gold.
That's like probably five grand.
Side of the house.
What about the side of the house?
I'm gonna try the side of the house.
Give me, oh shit.
Oh shit.
I found it.
I just found it.
Wait, this is even better.
It's like a gold mine.
Wait, where's the house?
Cube, where's the house?
This is it?
I think I found it.
Let me out of here.
No, it's not.
Wait, what did I just find?
No, this is not even right.
Get me back over there.
Wait, how did I end up over here?
Where the fuck am I?
I don't even remember where I was.
I'm hitting things with the hammer.
That's all I know.
I don't know anything else.
I gotta go down there.
There's a whole underground facility.
I gotta, ugh.
Junk.
What is this junk?
Here's computer number one.
All right, not ready for that yet.
I swear to God, I don't even know what house I was in.
I don't even know what, I have no idea.
What house was I in?
Here?
I was inside of this, right?
How did I end up all the way down here?
No.
Where the fuck did I go?
This place is so vast and expansive.
I don't even know where I am.
Oh, I've been here.
Okay, there's damage.
I've been here.
This is it.
Okay, okay, okay, this is it.
I found it.
I got it.
Another computer.
Okay, computer two.
Okay, nothing.
Is there a secret in the wall or something?
What's this?
Oh, binoculars.
See, I gotta have something in the desk, first of all.
There's nothing in his desk.
Do I get over there?
This can't be the end here.
There's a button.
Do I have to press this button?
Oh no, it's a light.
Really?
Go this way.
Fucking asshole.
I don't even see a way to get in here.
There's a grate there.
On the other side there.
Okay, wait, wait, see what that is?
It's down here.
Where is it?
There's a little, okay, right here, there's like a vent.
Oh, that's a welcome mat.
Oh shit.
Found it.
Goodbye.
No, that was a vacuum cleaner.
Secret vacuum cleaner?
Oh, no, this is just a closet.
This has to be it.
Okay, hold on.
How do I, is it, no.
Shit, is it over here?
Fuck, no, this is just another one.
Don't ever come near me again.
Throw some Chef Boy ID down here.
I don't understand.
No, I can't, it's not, you don't swim?
Did I find it?
Oh, I think it's connected to something over here.
What is this?
Okay, I found it.
And then there's, where the fuck am I?
You're gonna plank my way out of here?
I only have 10 planks left.
I don't think I can do this in 10 planks.
I need like 30.
Wait, what's up there?
What is up there?
What the fuck happened?
Am I inside of the earth?
I went underneath the game world.
Is that what really happened?
Well, I gotta find my way back up.
Sound, water, wait, I see blinking light.
Something's blinking over here.
I think I'm in trouble.
It's just water.
Hey, I made it.
All right, now how do I get in the vent?
Okay, vent is right there.
See that?
Therefore, we're gonna go just straight this way.
It's right there.
It's, okay, I gotta keep my, literally right here.
It's like right here.
Oh, found it, he found it.
I found it.
How do I get up here?
I can't go up there.
Hello, I can't go up here.
Everything okay?
Am I flying?
I feel like I'm flying.
Fucking light, what do I do?
This is a big one, hold on.
Can I rotate this?
How do you rotate an object?
Leave it here.
I feel like I'm pretty damn close, guys.
I feel like I'm actually pretty damn close.
No, shit, I'm trying to like just stuff myself up there.
I don't get it, I don't get it.
There's no other vent, I don't get it.
What did I think was gonna happen?
I need to get up here somehow.
I'm just gonna stack boxes, see if that works.
No, that's not how you do it.
I don't know, I don't understand.
All right, turn off the emote,
let somebody tell me.
Turn off the emote, let somebody tell me.
Turn off the emote, turn it off, I wanna know.
Tell me, I don't care.
Tell me how to do it.
Turn off the emote only, I don't know.
Turn off the emote, I just wanna, just tell me.
Spam it, I don't care, tell me.
Don't you have planks?
No, they're gone, I don't have any.
I need planks for this?
How am I gonna do that?
No, turn off the emote only
and I want somebody to tell me what to do.
Somebody tell me what to do.
I'll turn it off, I'll turn it off myself.
Tell me.
You climb with planks.
Planks, don't tell him.
Restart and use planks.
Shit and piss.
Reset and use planks.
Okay, let's go.
I don't remember what the house was.
I'm serious.
Just jump higher.
All right, it's this one here.
Over here.
There it is.
Okay, get the fuck out of my way.
Let's go.
Get this shit off.
Wait, no, leave that.
No, get rid of that.
This is wrong, this is fucking wrong.
This is wrong, hold on.
I need to get up high enough where I can go like this.
No, fuck, wrong one.
You punk.
I've jumped over it.
This is embarrassing.
I know I'm not supposed to go this way,
but I don't care.
Which way do I go?
That's the wrong vent.
I need to find a vent.
Vent.
That's the right vent.
You had it.
It was the right vent.
That's the right vent.
What?
Literally won't fit in that vent.
No, it's not the right vent.
The one guy, it's not.
That's like a thousand guys.
Vent?
Is there a vent up here?
Ow.
I don't understand.
Stay determined.
Did I say stay determined?
Shit.
Oh shit.
Oh.
I got it, I'm in, I'm in.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
I'm so in.
Shit, that's it.
I'm almost there.
God, oh my God.
Okay, slow down.
Don't do anything crazy.
Don't do anything insane.
Don't do anything insane that I wouldn't do.
I can't be a...
I stuffed myself in.
Oh shit.
I can't walk forward.
Hey, where's the gold?
$2,500.
Always believe in yourself.
2,500 bucks.
Save.
Okay, now how do I open the door?
You just don't.
Just vent, right.
Oh yeah, I could vent.
Put a hole in the wall?
Cracked wall?
What?
This one means a cracked wall.
That was the wrong button.
I thought it was a plank.
You know what?
I don't fucking care.
I'm just gonna go.
Load the game, right.
Is it a cracked wall?
I didn't even see it.
There is a cracked wall.
Intriguing.
That's nothing.
I'm done.
I have it saved right there.
I had to get the 2,500 bucks.
I had to.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're gonna do...
It's a good question.
I don't know.
I'm sure we'll figure it out.
Quick load?
Yeah, I will.
Yeah, I'm good.
I am actually surprised.
Is this a sandbox?
Is it free?
There's more to do.
Coin game?
Oh, wait a minute.
Did coin game actually come out with the new arcade?
Did it?
With actually the new arcade is out?
The new one?
If that's correct,
I'll be playing coin game tomorrow.
Only if it's the new arcade, not survival mode.
I know that they were working on a new,
actual, full arcade again.
I'll have to take a look at that.
If it's, like I said last time,
if it's just the survival mode,
I've already played all the games.
I've already got all the tickets and everything.
We'll see.
If they added a new arcade,
I'm gonna play it tomorrow.
All right, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Probably around,
probably around the same time, noon, 12 noon Pacific,
12 to one, maybe.
See you guys tomorrow.
We are going to go over.
We're gonna go take a look at the,
obviously the subs that came in.
These are all the subs from today, from this stream.
A lot of them were gifted.
So thanks guys for the gifted subs, as always.
It's a pretty good song,
but no, here's what I was gonna say.
What I was gonna say is,
it's rare for a game like this to be in early access
and be good.
It's pretty rare.
So I would,
here's a full stamp of approval on this game, for sure.
For sure.
A German Rumble update.
Well, I'll just tell you what's gonna happen.
So at the end of the year,
there's gonna be a stream on New Year's Eve.
We'll include both the awards show
that we typically do the last few years
and the German Rumble card.
You know, like four or five matches in the Rumble
and in between matches,
we're gonna do like three or four categories.
Because the idea was,
there has only been a certain amount of streams this year
because I took like two or three months off.
So an entire quarter of this year
was deleted from this stream.
So there's a little bit less to kind of choose from
in regards to nominations and categories.
So we'll do a double whammy.
I just scraped your face, I'm sorry,
on December 31st.
And you can,
the nominations, Discord channel,
and that'll all probably exist in the next few weeks.
There'll be some around the first of December,
first week of December.
Show ankles, show ankles.
One of these days, I'm just gonna do that.
I'm just gonna like show my ankles
and it's gonna be just these big, gross,
I'm gonna put like prosthetic feet on
and it's gonna be these big, just gross hobbit feet.
These gross, just prosthetic ankles.
And I'll be like, see, oh yeah, that's great, isn't it, huh?
You like it, huh?
Oh, look, I'll show ankles.
Here they are.
And then everyone would be like, no, no, no, no.
It would be a Vindigional Impression.
Ooh, how's it do?
But no, it should be fun.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'm going to run away from the computer now.
Have a great night.
See you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.
Oh, there's a $50 donation that came in.
I missed it.
It's from The Zat Zuck.
Oh, The Zat Zuck IRL.
Okay, good name, right off the bat.
It's a 5,000 bit, so it's 50 bucks.
And then another one just came in.
Another 5,000, you just,
$50, $50, back to back, okay.
Right at the end.
The Zat Zuck says,
Jerma, I've been watching your content for over six years now.
Started when I was like 14, high year old.
I always watch your VODs,
even if I'm working on a college assignment or something.
You're usually in the background.
I've been working a great job,
and I've saved enough that I can finally give you support
like I've always wanted to.
I made this Twitch account just to do so.
You're a funny, genuine guy.
I hope you're doing well.
Please use your flashlight.
I said this to other people before,
but knowing that some people have watched this channel
since they were like 14, 15,
and they're now in their 20s.
It doesn't make me feel old.
It just makes me feel like I hope,
I hope that I haven't shaped your brain
in a way that's not good.
Yeah, man, all through my incredibly important
developmental years,
where I'm incredibly influenced by a lot of things
that I'm really developing as a person,
I've spent the whole time pretty much watching you.
I'm like, oh, well, are you a good guy?
You're doing good?
Things are going good, right?
I didn't like fuck everybody up, right?
Although people do write like a show,
like show your dick and like show your ass crack
and like show your feet on stream.
But I don't know, did I mess you guys up?
Nah, thanks though, seriously, that means a lot.
And then KXZ just gave $50 with no message.
Just here's 5,000, bitch, just here's 50 bucks.
Thanks, KXZ, thank you, that's a ton of money.
Now, last time I streamed, or a couple times ago,
I wanted to scream.
I screamed really loud and hit the end stream button,
and the delay fucked it up.
So we're gonna try again this time.