Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with a pre-thanksgiving live commentary.
I just want to say from the bottom of my heart, if you celebrate Thanksgiving, if you live in the
United States, or if you are overseas somewhere but you still happen to celebrate Thanksgiving,
then happy Thanksgiving. I hope you have a nice safe holiday everybody.
Gonna do a quick live commentary like I'm saying. Oh goodness.
I thought I was gonna kill him. But yeah, happy Thanksgiving.
And I got some crazy crazy things planned for the holiday season. Not gonna tell you
what I'm doing yet. It's involving a lot of insanity. I'll get into that in a later video,
but expect a crazy Christmas video at some point in the very near future.
So what do you say? Let's get C. Let's get C. Playing as the pyro with the reserve shooter
and the degreaser along with the power jack. Pretty much default setup for me.
Except the reserve shooter. I don't really use it a whole lot. Oh, I was trying to sneak
behind everybody. What the hell was I doing? I like ran. I was talking and just ran around
everybody like an idiot. But yeah, I'm gonna fill up on so much turkey. I'm gonna eat a
ton of turkey sandwiches the next day. Should be a hell of a good time. Me and my family,
we go up to New Hampshire. And when we go there, we get a big hall rented out, like a big hall is
rented out for us. A ton of our family goes there every year. It's pretty cool. Pretty interesting.
I got a big family, guys. So we can't really have Christmas and like Thanksgiving at one little
place just because the family is so enormous. I want to get Oh, man. Oh, this could be epic
right here. This could be epic. Get out of here. I don't want you up here. Oh, there's a tree up
here. Oh, I should have known. I should have known. That's what I get. You know, I'm going
to change to demo man because that's just not going to happen as a pyro. Give me my... There we
go. All right. I'll do this right here. Ready? You guys ready? If I don't do this right here,
then something's wrong. Okay. I got to go the other way. Oh, no, no, no. Got to go around the
other direction. Here we go. Who'd I get? Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I mean, they're all like pouring
in here. Oh, come on now. Come on now. How did that not hit him? I was going to say, Jesus.
Jesus, criminy. I need a medic. Oh, Chris Krieg, look out. I'm dead. I'm so dead. Where did these
guys all come from? They're all just pouring into this one area. No, we have two medics. What's
going on here? What is the deal? This is gravel pit if you did not know. If you were unaware
of where we were playing. Where we were playing, not where we were playing. Oh, come on. At least
I got the teleporter. That's one thing. That's one good thing. All right. If I can get even close to
that and I could, I could probably get something done. I just need to overheal. Big time. Oh, no.
Demoman. Got him. All right. This is just, we have two medics. Where are they?
Where are these two mysterious medics that just are nowhere to be found?
Somebody's on the point. Oh, we might win. Come on. I'm just going to jump up there.
No. Oh, that was great. I just launched like 10,000 feet in the air. God. Jeez. Spy. No,
we can't lose. Oh, get him. Nice shot. What? Oh, where is this medic? I haven't seen the
medic one time. Where is this guy? I'm going this way. I'm not going that way. I'm going to get
myself killed. Oh, did I make it? I did, but not really. I was just completely silent right there.
That was just try hard mode. Wicked bad. Too bad it didn't work. We're definitely going to lose.
This is it. That's all she wrote. So yeah, thank you guys. So look at this. What?
What is going on here? Anyways, we lose, but thanks everybody so much for watching.
I wanted to make this quick video just to get it out here and wish you guys a happy Thanksgiving.
And I wish you the best and stay safe, guys. Take care, everybody.