Good afternoon. How you doing? On time. Yeah. Yeah. Anybody bet on this? No bets for this?
Oh, okay. I figured maybe there would be a bet for that.
Wait, you mean I could have been like 10 minutes late? If there was a bet, I was like,
oh, maybe they bet on this. I better get in there and turn it on. No, I'm kidding. I'm here.
I'm going to play Slime Rancher again. Played it last night. I think it's great.
And I'm going to get my fill. So we'll see after today if that's the case.
After three streams on German985twitch.tv, we have to decide if I'm going to continue
or if three is enough. We'll find out. I do love the game though. It's a chill, fun thing to do.
I'm really into it. Please wish me a happy birthday. Your name is so dark I couldn't
even read your name. It's like a dark navy blue. It blends in with the background. I can't read it.
I couldn't even read your name. Happy birthday, whoever you were. What was your name?
Happy birthday. Can you not wish me a happy birthday? That's just every day that's not your
birthday. We're going to get right into this. I don't need to introduce this at all. This is
three streams in a row of Slime Ranchers, so I don't really need to talk that much about it.
There was something I wanted you guys to remind me of and I was thinking about it before I turned
the stream on. I have a drill, right? I have two drills. It was something else. It was the drills
and something else. Explain the game. These little creatures, you feed them and they shit out money.
That's the entire game. There's nothing else in the game. It's just collecting creatures that go
to the bathroom and then you make money off of their bathroom. I mean, it's pretty cool.
Okay, let's go. Let's go. Don't need to waste any time. Here we are. I'm already in the game.
I've been waiting. I've been ready. I've been sitting here the entire day just waiting for
exactly 2 p.m. to go through or 2 30 so I can turn it on and play. Move this a little bit. That's
going to distract me. Okay, it's done. Can you guys hear it? Yes, you can. We're good to go.
Get to the dentist. For what? I need to go to the dentist? Remember, people are going to start
thinking your name is actually Andy. I don't think so. I don't think they're going to think that.
All right, the last thing. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. The drills, the drills. We got to go to the drills.
All right, suck up. Your name isn't Andy. Oh, we got, okay, okay. Good, good, good. Yeah,
I remember the plan here. I got a lot of money. Right. No, it was buy the docs. That's what you
guys supposed to remind me. You guys supposed to remind me to buy the docs and take the stuff out
of the drill. That's not what you're doing right now. You're just saying Andy. That's not helping
me. It doesn't help me. I tried. No, it's not just one of you that has to try. It's like 3,000 of you
have to try because I can't read one person's comment. You have to all just amalgamize into
one comment. What about the one guy's? Yeah, but that's different. Okay, those drills are over here.
No, I want to get the oka oka. I need the hive mine to yell at me. Yeah. If you missed last night's
stream or you didn't stay the whole time, we just got crystals and we just got rad slimes
and I combined the crystal and the rad slime and made a crystal rad slime.
Oh boy, you missed it. I'm saying among us. Okay, let's go. That's sick. Why? Why are you saying
among us? I said that. I didn't. When did I say among us? All right, let's get some money
and then let's let them eat oka oka is their favorite food. Okay, I'm going to sell this.
Look at those crystals. Has the price gone up? I wonder you forgot what I forget. You did
among us in a nutshell. Oh, Michael. Oh, but what did you do? You guys got like collectively hit by
like the fairy godmother. Why are you guys? Oh, what's going on here? Like somebody will have
a wand over this chat. What are you guys doing? Are you going to kill me if I stand on that?
Shit. I didn't mean to do that. It'll be fine. It's the hive mind. But why? Why is the hive mind
saying among us? All right. I know you're a hive mind, but why is the hive mind saying among us?
I need an explanation for it. We're toxic.
Why are you guys doing this? Because we're toxic. Oh, okay. What are you doing? 38? This
these went down in value. I should have held. We know it pisses you off.
No, it doesn't. It's a joke on you. I don't care. I don't even care. They think that like it makes
me mad. I don't even fucking care. Oh my god. Imagine thinking like I cared about that.
Oh, you're really getting to me. I don't care. He was just wasting so much time saying that.
I don't fucking even care. I need to donate this stuff. Jerma, you're a valley girl.
I want to donate and then we're going to check on the drills. Yes. How am I a valley girl? What's
this quest? This guy. Working on a new recipe. Help me out. What does he want? Oh, those rewards
are terrible. I mean, eight chickens. I can go get eight chickens right now in my backyard. No,
not even worth it. All the upgrades are done. Let's go this way. Do it. No, I can go pick up
eight chickens right now in 15 seconds. It's not worth it. When he said I'm willing to pay you to
talk to my friend. She's anti Jerma. I don't. That's okay. I don't care. That's fine. That's
what you can. We don't all have to like the same TV shows. Oh, I need to donate these shit. Yes,
we do. No, if we all like the same TV shows, how would we argue with each other about what the best
TV show is? Or what season was the best? Guys, there are a lot of you. There are a lot of you.
There are a ton of you among us here. God. God. God. God. God. God. God. God. God. God. There's a
lot of you here that would argue about the arcs of this channel. Oh, yeah. Boston Arc was better
than Vegas Arc. No, no, no, no, no. Jerma Basement Arc was better than Jerma Boston Arc.
I mean, that happens here. Jerma Arc Tier List. Okay, there's been like two. There's been two.
Actually, no, there's been a there's been actually quite a few arcs, hasn't there?
Are they arcs or are they what would you even call them? There's seasons.
It'd be kind of funny to name streams with the title like seasons in them. Like I said,
what's the title right now? Like, oh, Slime Rancher, like getting that money.
Jerma Season 3 Episode 40 or something. But that season finale is like something crazy would
have to happen. We'd have to have season finales. Are these ready? Oh, only two minutes. All right,
two minutes and 27 seconds and I can get these. Catboy is season finale. I don't know if I agree.
I don't think I agree with that. I think Catboy would be series finale because Netflix ain't
picking it up for another season after that one. Netflix is going to be like,
we didn't like the direction of the Catboy stuff. We're no longer we're not going to be
renewing German N8-5 for a fourth season. All right, put these hens over here. How do I burn
two minutes? How do I kill two minutes? What's your opinion on the word plort? I think it's pretty
sick. Next question, please. What are you doing? That's your question. Hey, what are you doing?
Next question, please. What are you doing? What are you? What are you up to? What are you doing?
How are you? How are you doing? I don't know why I thought that was so funny. Look at all this.
This is day. Excuse me. How am I feeling? I'm feeling pretty good. It's been a good day.
I forgot that this existed. Now I'm going to have a lot of these.
You free tonight? All right, I'm not free tonight. I didn't. I got to put something over here.
Like, all right, what do I put over here? High walls, music box, but just do it. Air net,
what collector? I got to put something over here. Auto feeder. I got to get something in here.
What should I put over here? I'll figure it out. All right, chickens are doing good.
I got my mangoes. I already asked if I could sleep over and then your mom said yes. Oh, I get it.
Was that like an insult or something? I don't know what that means.
That's like an insult. What do you mean? No, he just asked. Wait, that wasn't like a,
hey, man, I already asked your mom if I could sleep over. She said yes, I'm sleeping over
your mom and your mom. That wasn't what that was. I thought that's what that was. What is this?
Oh, shit. There's a mango in here. That'll fill up. How are we doing? All right. Now,
it's two minutes going up. I think it's time to check out the drill. Real time. They asked you
for your mother's permission. Okay, but wouldn't your mother need to ask my mother for permission
to make sure it was real? In this scenario for both kids, you have to ask my mom if you
can sleep over. Wouldn't your parents need to be the ones to be like, hey, can Timmy sleep over
tonight? Like, hey, can I sleep over tonight? Well, we have to check with your mom. Yes. Yeah.
Ready? Oh, these are blue. Oh, no, they're not. Oh, okay, I get it. They're not different than
the regular ones. They just do three cycles. Okay. Oh, pretty cool. Do I sleep with? Okay.
I'm going to stop. We're going to stop that conversation right there.
You guys, what the hell are you doing? I want some more advanced drills. Don't you?
What's the, what's the shit from Avatar on, on obtaining them? Advanced drill. All right,
I can make some more of these. I'm going to put one on the one I'm putting on there.
That's a real element. Unobtanium is a real element. I don't, I feel like that's a lie.
That's an unobtanium. I don't think that's real. I want crystals. I'm going to do one more cell,
and then I'm going to get out of here. I'm going to go explore. I have a, I have another key.
Among us tanium. Actually banned that person forever. I'd like actually, I'm sorry. I'm very
sorry, but you have to be banned forever. At least like for 15 minutes, like among us tanium.
How dare you? You know what I mean? Like let's just say, let's just be real. How dare you?
I want that person timed out for at least 10 minutes. It's hard for me not to say forever.
What if 10 minutes? I don't even know who said it. And I may have added extra syllables and extra
words to it. I find the person that started me down that path and I want them out of here for
15 minutes. No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to.
I don't even need these hens. Does anybody eat meat over here? Somebody does down here.
You can't ban us all. No, you're right. I can't, I cannot ban you all. I can't, but I can.
There's some things I can do. I can put it into sub only, five minute slow mode, and then that's
goodbye. Can't hear you anymore. Okay, good. We'll have one more haul to deliver.
I know these guys have a shitload. Yes, they do. Not really. Do it. No, I'm not. I just, I can do
it. That doesn't mean I'm going to do it. It means I can. Oh, I wonder if I should. No, I'll just
sell if he cares. All right. Now I'm going to buy the dock and we're going to go through the dock.
Oh yeah. 15 grand. I'm going to go, I'm going to sleep and we're going to go to the dock and
here we go. I'm a dog that just got out of the bath. I had to really shake violently around.
The point where you look at the dog and you're like, does their brain shake around like crazy
when they do that? Doesn't that give them a headache? All right. The dock was down here,
right? When a dog shakes that like, you know what I'm talking about? They shake, shake, shake.
It starts off kind of slow. It's like shake, shake, shake, shake. That seems like it would be like,
holy shit, that's fast. No, no, no, growling. Like that's the vibrations of them shaking.
Here we go. The docks deep down in the great blue sea. I saw a thousand slimes smiling back at me.
Let's go. Dock. What? Here we go. Boys and girls. Oh my God. Oh, it's just another area. Okay. Fuck.
I didn't even need to do this. There was, is that, there's nothing here? Oh, it's just extra space.
Well, I don't even need this. Not, at least not now. You got baited. Well, not really. So where
can I use this other key? Where do I use the key? You need to sing a raid song? Thanks for the raid.
Who, who raided? C or Max. Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody. Playing, uh, I almost just said
playing among us. Yeah, currently playing among, you guys keep fucking saying it and then you keep
writing it. You're burning it into my head. I just, it's, it's half of every message.
It's half of every single message. Every single one. I can't get, I can't, I can't get away from
it. It's all I can read. All right. I need to, I need to open up a door. Wait, couldn't I,
didn't I get a treasure unlocking ability thing? I did, didn't I? All right. I need to, I'm going
to open up a door. Where is there another door I can open? I have a, I have two keys, don't I?
I have one key. Isn't there one down here? I swear to God there is. I swear to God. Yeah, there it is.
All right, cool. Let's go. I'm going to open this up. What's this way? I don't know. Why would I, is
this, should I get this? I don't know if this is like worth doing. This doesn't look worth it.
I got to go back here and then open this over here. This is a shortcut. Yeah, I gotta get the
last area. All right. I'm going to go back to here. We'll go back to the crystal place.
Okay. Yeah. Back to the crystal place. I already unlocked that area. Yeah. Is there a cave that I
can open a door? Because I got the two keys last time. Ban the word among us. You know, that sounds
fantastic, actually. That sounds like a great idea. That sounds like a fantastic idea.
Among us. Why? You know, I, when I watch like meme compilation videos and a bunch of shit about
Among Us pops up and I'm in a room with more than one or two people, I have to pretend to know what
their laugh, but what's, what's funny about it. And I'm just like, Oh yeah. I mean like, I don't
know that crew member. I have no idea what's going on. Are you five? What do you mean? Watching
meme compilation videos? What's wrong? Is there nothing wrong with that? Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Everybody, I want to, I'm silenced.
I need to go over this. You guys have not had auto play on and you just don't care what plays next.
And eventually it always leads back to a meme compilation video. Eventually, even like a few
hours could go by and then somehow for some reason that cannot be explained you end up on the daily
dose of internet video page and you just let them play and you don't stop you just sit there for like
two hours you don't it doesn't even it could be four hours you just sit there i didn't i didn't
click on that it just it was like oh this is like auto playing and this is this video is next and
the autoplay roulette and then this and then here we are the daily dose of internet here we go i'm
just i guess i'm just what's gonna i'm gonna be it's gonna be on tv for like an hour but i've
reached the controller and like turn it off like on my like tv or my ipad or my iphone i could
but how am i kind of wipe my ass don't you see uh like an iphone propped up with like two or three
tubes of toothpaste on the sink facing me while i'm sitting there just like enjoying myself
i need to go to the bathroom
okay okay we gotta pivot away from this right now uh
okay jesus christ i'm sorry i know somebody said
i'm sorry
thank god there's no webcam one i can't be trusted with a live broadcast i can't see on
youtube on youtube i would say i would be recording and i would say something
fucking stupid or crazy like that and i who just would would not appear in a video it
would happen all the time okay i want to go let's forget that was going on and let's go
oh i have a shortcut to here i'm stupid wait oh treasure pot oh give me these don't touch these
slime fossil holy shit i know there's like a lot of those around the world
advanced pump oh i forgot i had a shortcut to right here i'm i'm an idiot and now i have to go
back fuck okay i promise we're gonna make progress in a second here i'm gonna go deposit this oh oh
oh god it's the among us shit you guys just walking me up you're just messing me up it's
just completely screwing me up he threw me off the friday right at the very beginning of the
stream i just think like among us among us among us oh yeah i can't even pay i can't do anything
look at i got like my oka oka is overgrown i can't even pay attention all right shit hold on you
realize you're in almost all the among us meme compilations fucking frankenstein's monster
okay this is how i feel so like in frankenstein like frankenstein got up and was like
it was like no my creation oh and he like bites dr frankenstein in the neck right and like
getting it murders dr frankenstein as it happens in the movie and i don't know whatever the tv
show the movie whatever the book was so like dr frankenstein gets like murdered by iron man
i promise i'm not high i was just thinking of like if frankenstein was in the marvel universe
i promise i'm fine uh hold on let me get these you guys fucked me up bad today so anyways how
that's how i feel i feel about the among us meme i begged you guys to stop using that photo
to like show people me oh yeah have you heard of germa oh here's a picture of his fucking
wicked ugly face and i'm like i hate that photo stop doing it get rid of it i do anything else
please and then you got that imposter face woke up with two bolts in its neck and i was like oh
excellent that's a new meme to replace the old one and before it was annoying to me and i didn't
want to see it and uh yeah get off me it's like crap i'm sus you're sus i'm not sus what are you
talking about yeah you are supposed to be sus that was a sus thing to say
i'm passing up he's drinking a ton of blood he's sus he's sus yeah i can't see anymore i'm passing
on that's what happened we did it i'm gonna store a lot of this shit this is a chilling slime
rancher stream uh well look it's been let me hey let me get a little bit of credit here
it's been it's been 33 minutes and if you would look at the log of this stream i know it's
available somewhere do select control f among us and i guarantee it's at least 10 to 20 000
messages i guarantee it i would put i'm not going to put any money on it but i would maybe if i
thought about it it's so many like what the hell is happening oh i need to get the uh they're not
gonna despawn right shit wrong way how much money huh an amount that if you were comfortable maybe
putting a bet down if you felt like doing a bet maybe i would play among us for 1.5 billion off
the debt no i would you would have to pay me 1.5 billion real dollars for me to do that okay go oh
is this a level one pod shit now i'm ready to explore full debt wipe if you play among us no
that's just watering the meme plant no i can't no no no no
well you know what actually hold on a second here i i could i could stream among us and have the
title be imposter is sus guy plays among us and i could just be me and i could be smiling and be
like oh that's sus i'd get probably a hundred thousand viewers wouldn't i that's a huge brain
play i think i could look into the camera and smile big and be like man that was pretty sus to
me i'd get a hundred thousand concurrent viewers that's brilliant and then and then and then ban
every new account that came in that day before that after that okay no then ban all accounts
that were made and ever uh followed this channel and then retire just retire from streaming forever
the imposter is sus guy and coming up next we've got an interview with the imposter is sus guy
you guys lean into that should i just go to like conventions and be that guy i'll be on like a
twitch panel oh we've got the imposter is sus guy on the panel i'll just travel the country
and like do the face and and that's it i guess go on like go on fox news
oh my god go like a news program you understand that being the imposter is sus guy requires no
work from me at all i just have to be that guy i just have to be that guy on some form of imagery
i don't have to do anything set for life all i need to do is just do one imposter is sus guy
has a stream and have like $20 tts donations that trigger a tts and i think i would probably
be able to just retire forever sus for life
sus for life but the thing is though i i would never do that because i would wake up on my like
i don't know i could be like it would be like a 45th birthday or something i would wake up in a
cold sweat and be like i'm no what happened face i would just see that face i would see it
everywhere i would look at every brushing my teeth in the mirror with that smile like just smiling
and be like that image is that's me that's sus okay i'm good i got 12 000 let's see okay let's go
wait what do you think i'm worth okay let me ask you a question so if let's just say
like let's say i have put a price tag on like me being in like an imposter
video right like some youtuber or streamer wanted to do like oh i i love i'm a bit i love among us
i play it all the time man i wonder if i could get that imposter is sus guy on my stream to like
like i open like the closet and he's smiling there what do you think that's worth
how much could i sell that for you think what could i actually get from that like 100k
10k at best that's a lot of fucking money like 10k just to be the guy like the imposter is sus like
in like somebody's like bathroom vent or something they like show the camera and like i'm like in
their like ac unit like looking out like it's 10 000 i'm like they pan up like in their bedroom
and i'm like in like the ac vent why did i just collect all that money i need to hold on that
would be 50k big subs we had 25 from soda cat 10 from albion thank you guys thanks everybody
giving subs you don't have to okay i'm gonna store this and i have to actually i'm gonna go
open that door i want to go open the gate no no no no no no i gotta pay attention
pay attention pay attention to the game store the oka oka sell everything else i'm not trying to
make money right now update you need plorts to unlock this door not a key oh shit okay well what
do i need let's find out what do i need anyone know what i actually need well let's go find out
among us sus you know the reason why i say that is because i i don't i don't really address
the sus stuff because i mean like wow whatever if people it's memed it's gone into the meme
stratosphere whatever i don't care it's out of my hands completely have fun with it fine okay
whatever i don't care uh but like kentucky fried chicken tweeted it up like the the spanish kentucky
fried chicken chicken put the sus guy as colonel sanders i think i could probably make some money
on that i think i could probably be like the sus guy and like i'm fucking among us commercial
on like nickelodeon or something right that's big money nickelodeon's big money that's not
that's not 5k that's not the nickelodeon's big money if they wanted to get me all right it's
uh up here i make that sell out andy well call it what you will but i mean well you all know how
i feel about that image if if i could make like a shitload of money by just smiling in a camera on
nickelodeon one day are you kidding me i don't have to do anything i just have to be like hey
i think green just vented and then like chatter my teeth and then the director's like okay cut
and i just i just sit there and i'm like all right that's it somebody comes over with a huge like
prices right check a giant one that's like fifty thousand dollars on it i just put it under my
armpit and fucking put it in my trunk and leave i you wouldn't do that too okay i want to go this
way what does it take to get in here i have self-respect i wouldn't do that i mean i
i'm just smiling into a camera as the sus guy i'm not like like deep frying 100 iphones or
something and being like look what i did right where's this door in there oh oh mommy i don't
like the sus man we're like talking about all this and just fucking around and making jokes
and stuff but you know how funny it would be if i realistically like thought about pursuing
something like that and being like i'm available as the sus guy it's worth like 300 dollars it's
like yeah yeah yeah yeah i mean you just you're just smiling into a camera and it's like a meme
kind of and i'm sitting here like 50 grand a big check uh what made you think you are here we go
i'm going in you guys lied to me wait this is the i've already been here do a cameo now cameo would
not work you understand if i did a cameo as the sus guy every single cameo is the same one person
would buy it for ten dollars and share it with everyone it would be me doing the sus face and
saying like yeah happy birthday then nothing would change all right how many do i need
what do i actually need to do here do i need to shoot pink into there or just shoot it into the
door i need what do i need to do there are statues okay so this is like a hunter plort statue okay
what about you green plort statue looking for the hunter statue are you a hunter you are that's
honey all right oh i just need one i don't need more than one there's no hunter one oh okay so i
need this is boom rad crystal i think i have all these i have all this oh okay i think oh oh i have
all these we just have a regular germa 95 cameo sure absolutely that sounds good to me yeah we'll
do it right now let's do it right now you ready here so here's what you're gonna get ready hey
thank you for uh hold on hey good to see you good to see you just want to say real quick
happy birthday i know it's your birthday today i know you've been a good boy happy hold on i'm
gonna get the whole thing in frame like this hold on you know i heard it was somebody's anniversary
happy anniversary youtube i heard the story i heard how fun it was oh it the proposal was fantastic
i heard that was fun too happy anniversary guys you're gonna do good things you're gonna do good
things happy anniversary yo germa 95 here just want to say oh i did i excuse me is it somebody's
birthday today oh of course it is happy birthday i'm so happy to see you on your birthday i was
told you're a big fan and i'm coming to you personally nobody paid me to do this except
they did if there was at least five dollars and if i talk for more than 30 or 40 seconds it's
another five dollars i believe some of these are over 200 dollars mine wasn't happy birthday
though have a great one okay here we go ready names popular names okay here we go
i need names by alphabet alphabetical order listed baby names in alphabetical order okay here we go
oh this is a lot of names names of names of common common american names
in alphabetical order baby names in america here we go
uh
alexander benjamin carter daniel elijah finn grason henry isaac kaden liam mason noah oliver
parker quinn ryan sebastian theodore wait theodore burial vincent vincent william hey Xavier hey
useph hey Zachary Ava Brooklyn Charlotte Delia Delilah Emma Faith i just spit all of my mouth
don't don't we'll do that one again Faith Grace Harper Isabella hey Josephine hey Kennedy hey
Luna that looked concerned hey Luna Mia Nora Olivia Penelope Quinn Riley Riley Riley Sophia
did you hear that like frog sound Sophia Taylor Unique Victoria Willow Zimena Zimena Zoe Uritzi
Julie Crystal Katherine Mike Joe Joseph John Greg Gary Ed Edward Eddie Ed Jeremy Jeremy
Eddie what give me more more oh no no no and i gotta say and too and so you can do like uh uh
Jeremy and uh Joe and Julie happy anniversary right okay hold on what else we got Alec Alex
Avery Lauren hey Nick Case Trevor Cody John Frederick Daryl Luke Katelyn what Preston Lawrence
Colton Andrew Andy Lily Otto Victor I did Victor already Miranda i'm gonna look so
bored in half of these hey Miranda Tiffany Tiffany Sydney all right i'm done hey hope you're having
a good day today thanks happy birthday hey i want to wish a very special happy birthday to
heard you had a big day today happy birthday to you hey your friends put me up to this your friends
put me up to this but happy birthday nonetheless heard your fan it's been so great to hear from you
have a wonderful rest of your day yes the streams wink there and now it's all for free
i don't have to ever do a cameo ever if you want to make get a cameo for your friend
just take that chop it up and put their name in it and it's fucking free yeah i don't have to pay
you don't pay anything for it you didn't say my name you missed David i did hey David Dave Dave
Dave David hey Angus hey what's going on Angus Matthew Matt Matt Gary Alice Becca Keith Mark
Zane Evan we have forgotten Peter hey Diler Lois i'm fucking done i'm done there's how many names
are there in existence there's too many hey Bernie Thanos wishing happy birthday to Thanos
Goku hey Goku happy birthday Chloe Natalie Brianna Rose Rosie Jesse Arthur Kyle Paul
Paul you can hear me laughing you can hear me laughing Paul why is this one so hard
Paul what the fuck is wrong with me Paul why is it why do i sound so evil hey Paul oh i look like
fucked up hey Paul there you go Emily Logan Amy all right this is getting i'm done i did too many
names i'm over it's over it's over it's over josh josh joshua josh anthony all right give me give
the fuck out of here i'm done you say Stephen Stephen Steve all right that's it is my cameo
you got it you've forgotten me sorry okay let me play the video game look i can just say Justin
and one of the other J's just superimpose Justin over that when i say like John just put Justin
Brandon James Rupert all right i'm not saying any more names i'm done i need to get a what are
the i need pink i need i need plorts i need plorts i need plorts what i need for plorts i need
probably puddle tabby i have a flashlight what the fuck it's been 12 hours and i didn't know that
puddle tabby rad boom crystal now get me the hell out of here where do i even end up i don't know
i'll go the other way it's faster is it faster yeah how was your day today it's been really good
i've been having a good day hope it's going good for you too now we're going back to saying among
us i really thought i could just pivot away from that with my guy says every single name stream
all right get me out of here i gotta come back with plorts how do i get out of here here we are
back underground wait a minute oh it's a new slime pretty cool this is a ladder no all right
i gotta get the hell out of here get me out just get me out get me out get me out this way
teleport i gotta come back with plorts is it in here i think is it in this way no what the hell is
this thing i wish i had like a verticality meter see i forget what this thing is here
and then around the corner right yeah it's over here right right yeah all right give me the
plorts that i need i don't need these get rid of them i need pink no i don't what do i actually need
rad i need rad boom crystal rock what do you guys want eat something
eat up okay i need a rock i need i need tabby too right rad good thing i have access to a tabby
okay phosphorus one rad let me get some radishes or whatever the hell these are
i need boom which i need to i'll get meat let's feed somebody so i can get a boom
uh
the mandalorian all right you guys give me one of these oh i don't think i have yes no
you guys who explodes here i need exploding freya need uh what do we need i'll sell these
do i need crystals i don't know if i need crystals i know i need
um i'm gonna have to do another trip i don't need crystal okay i do need a bomb though one of you
guys give me a bomb thank you boom flort rock flort tabby flort get rid of the crystals and
then rad and then i i'm missing one rad i need pink uh pink has already done i think
yeah i need a phosphor i have to come back for a phosphor of course i do great well let's at least
get the rad and i'll come right back i'm gonna do this quickly hurry up from here we go up i'll
get these later chat cringe spam stream uh what is it i'm going the wrong way oh
remind me to get that remind me to get that should we put it you want to put it on slow
mode you want it on slow mode joey joey joey joey put it on slow mode what do you think
i'm gonna go there what's this i've got a coverage i think honk honk
and then this way the ipad talking about i know i dude i words come out fast and sometimes i
cannot put the stopper in fast enough oops setting it up with the toothpaste all right here we go
it's this way and then go through here shoot it in there and then we get to run back again and do
it again we get to do it again do it again check your diaper check your diaper i do appreciate the
uh what's the what is that mario something i would need the boom floor where is it always red
where are the other ones ah all right no and tabby and then where's the you are no
bad bounce what wrong one where's tabby where's tabby where's tabby where's tabby left of the
sus portal get out of here god damn it okay i just what so what is this one this is the flying one
okay then let's get that door open left of the sus portal and i knew exactly what they were
talking about it didn't even take me one second to figure that out it was immediate i knew what he
was talking about immediately all right let's go get it need uh fruits still not just a few
we'll fill it up get the treasure pod yep
okay uh one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve okay time to get the door
open the treasure and get the drills yes that is exactly what i'm going to do right now after i go
the wrong way you know how many onions are probably over there so many say onion ring
okay and the treasure pod minty grass patch um no nothing in there 1080 omega logad whatever
all right return sell store go among amongian rings you know i might as well just lean into
it today because that's how i i i don't know what happened look at all those onions why today though
what happened today that meme has been around for months why today i didn't start this you
were acting sus no i wasn't i didn't do anything why not yesterday how come you didn't do this
yesterday i streamed yesterday what happened in like 12 hours holy shit whoa oh my god there's a
lot of stuff in here deep brine hexa comb strange diamond cool i need to it's overgrown
i'm gonna stuff this in the auto feeder look man we don't choose when you are sus or not
it's true i'm gonna build some drones i do what happened it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's all right it's okay i don't know what i just did i think he has to die does he no he can just
be the one that rules them all okay that's fine i need that i need that though shit that out oh
my god 91 okay thank you you can go back in don't go over there okay we're good he's gonna turn them
all yeah he is he is yep he's gotta go yeah get him out he's gonna turn them all yes my mistake
is your demise i'm sorry he can fly he's fine oh my god there's a hundred in here all right i
think i i don't need to feed these guys anymore oh i just heard something a glass break roommate
ejected okay i'm actually i'm not going to read anymore i'm not going to read anymore among us
posts you wanted to talk about among us take it take it somewhere else take it somewhere else
okay i just need one of these let's go sleep get for it let's get for it i don't know what that
means let's go for it and get it he can't ban us all no yes i can with just a simple snap up my
fingers you guys would just be fucking gone this way no more fortnight yeah i'm gonna take away
your fortnight privileges you want to keep this up no more fortnight you're only gonna get to
build you only get to play educational games not fortnight all right we're gonna go up left straight
fortnight is educational i want these slimes is he gold no i just want the slimes that's all i want
and we still probably play super frog of course you can play super frog i almost just died i didn't
have any energy left yeah you can play super frog that's completely fine absolutely super frog
teaches you uh skills it teaches you about oh my goodness should probably help them although
you're right it does got candy it does have candy it teaches you educational number counting
but it does have candy in it everyone good good how could you not like it yeah but it
candy's not good for your teeth hey what the heck's going on with this how come there's no
video game where you have actually like use the analog stick to brush your teeth there's no brushing
teeth in video games i've never played a video game where like you brush your teeth with like
the controller why have they never done that it seems like kind of fun no not i'm not talking
about wario where i'm talking about like a 3d game rpg or something you go and you spit you
spit use the actual analog stick to brush you can do that in heavy rain
i have to play it it'd be fun one time no you could do like a red dead redemption thing with it
where if you just didn't brush your teeth they turned like brown or something or like gray
like over time you don't like clean you just have these like gray brown teeth like yellow teeth
all right we're finally gonna open this door see what happens that's it now um
into the past all that is lost is eventually found and lost once more okay any new slimes
it's this thing i don't know if i should press this what is all this where am i on the map
oh press it press it hold on okay um i can open doors we're going further into the temple
is these weird hologram things all over the place excuse me new slime give us a new slime
give us a new slime give us it give us every once it oh yeah yeah yeah yeah quantum slime
quantum slime hurry get as many as i can quantum crystal is the new play cool what do quantums eat
oh we're going this way like oh oh this is gonna freak me out all right how about down here
what is over here anything read my lips what about this tree oh can i open it nice something
valuable come on i deserve it a sunburst sweet
let's try to get a good like 10 20 20 quantum slimes i'll take the puddles
you know i like them oh what's this a red echo oh red echo how far into the game are you
um i believe this is the final area so i've unlocked all the areas i don't know exactly
how much is left but i mean enough for me to like just mess around and sell things and buy things
and there's another one oh pink echoes i need that device that shows you the map
whoa this is like this is quantum fruit how do i turn this on look this is like a quantum fruit
tree how do i get that to work they probably eat these they eat fruit okay hit it with a fruit
okay one whoa a phase lemon holy shit okay that's definitely their favorite food
there's no way a phase lemons not a quantum slime's favorite food oh i gotta go back
i gotta get out of here i gotta go but is there another slime to get here hold on come here
and there's another treasure trove there
here
can't open it though lava i i'm gonna get it there's a treasure pod oh i don't have any room
no what do i do oh shit i don't want to open this what if it's good i don't want to get rid of the
puddles is it good okay we're fine urgent grass patch i want at least 20 slimes before i go
anywhere i want 20 of the slimes i want 20 of them we have to do a lot of uh slime combination
here how do we get out of here you have 21 you don't need the echo i don't what do you mean
where's the among us what nine plus ten is 21 quantum slime echo is a decoration
echo is a cosmetic decoration it's a lie that's a lie that's definitely a lie you just you want
to shoot it into the ocean so you can write omega low like 100 of you oh wait a minute what's this
what do they love phase lemons are their favorite i gotta grow phase lemons
feed him an echo i know what that is now but i need to feed him a fruit so he shows up on the map
anything really this is like okay no no i don't i know where he is i'll put like the weird lake
up here okay i don't remember how to get out of here you have a phase lemon i'm not shooting that
i want to grow these i need to see what that lava is though right we gotta go over there
i need to see what this is or we get out of the way what's the lava it's a lava slime
that's a boom gordo he eats meat oh wait wait i want to be able to mark this
can't like bounce it off the wall go around idiot and i i mean go we need to go around
all right just go around go go where's the button to press this need to open that door through the
door what door fly over the wall hold on grab more quantums um every time i see him i'm trying
to pick him up ah yes i'm out thank goodness oh there's the teleporter all right now
i don't know what i did all right i gotta where's that gordo is over here where is he he's in here
right he's right there so can i go around here like where do i go let's see he's in there the
door is open dropped from what do you mean the door is open door is open door the door is open
oh the door the door the door is open now he's marked now i know where he is thank you
the other guy's like right here the door is cosmetic it is not cosmetic and i'll like it
actually get me out of here and i'm gonna do some quantum slime computing you guys know that the
quantum computing stuff you guys hear about that isn't the whole scary thing with quantum computing
that it can like crack your password in like three seconds can't can a quantum computer crack
any password in like less than a day or something what we're gonna do pick him up what the fuck
we're gonna cry no not even close what do you mean not even close quantum computing also allows
for ultimate privacy ultimate ultimate privacy well i don't have a quantum computer i'm not
going to be able to have when they first come out the person with the first quantum computer
is gonna get everybody's password i got 27 quantum slimes is there does it i gotta get
that teleporter all right all right all right let's make this happen quantum quantum computing
has been around since before you were born jeremy yeah but just because this one in some random
nasa warehouse when we all have one when it fits inside of your hand like a smartphone
it's not how it works yeah and guess what 40 50 years ago we didn't think that we'd be able to
send our voices through the air to each other that that's that's fucked up isn't it a radio
no you know i hold on a minute we're not talking about radio we're talking about i can i can through
the air to satellite to satellite call you if you're in tokyo and i'm in vegas and we can have a
clear perfectly normal conversation i'm not talking about like hey hey hold on
yeah and they're like 200 feet away from each other yeah telephone goes through wires
what do you mean the telephone yeah the telephone went through a wire into the wall
through into the ground this overgrowing fruit the internet is wires not wireless internet
that sounded like i was elvis oh look at all these puddle slides we're gonna put it here
mobile phones eventually go to wires i don't even know that yeah i okay i took a networking
class in college i took networking one i learned how to crimp a ethernet cable so okay okay so
what you're but you know right i was in like 1989 look at all these cute little ports networking
andy oh shit i don't have any more crystals because i turn them into rad crystals well
looks like we're getting rid of some shit what are we getting rid of oh i know we're getting
rid of out here does quantum need something special because it is time to get rid of the cats
didn't i get rid of the cats already why are they still here wait what happened
i thought i got rid of these already oh i made a new plot that's right that's right that's right
i know where it is are they gonna phase out of existence if i put them in here are they
gonna disappear let me read quantum quantum slimes appear to have resulted from some sort
of event that took place in the ancient ruins long ago yep at all times the quantum slime
is capable of admitting other possible realities of their being called ghosts these other realities
can come true with the quantum slime aligning with the reality of the ghost effectively teleporting
quantum slimes can be one of the most difficult slimes to manage given the unique abilities a
rancher needs to learn to detect when quantum slimes are primed to take over the reality of a
ghost and i quickly such as feeding them or just splashing them with some fresh water as a temporary
measure so i have to keep them fed these guys got to be kept fed or they will just disappear
at all times read puddle slime puddle slimes aren't risky to manage they just require a fair
bit of maintenance a rancher needs a pool of fresh water like a pond available for a puddle
slime and it's plorts to sit in as they will evaporate it away from water finally puddle
slimes are exceptionally shy and will not produce plorts if they're in close proximity more than
three others hopes overall pulse time is barefoot yeah just sleepy okay so i have to i can only have
four ocean no no no no no no no come back here i don't want you to teleport out of reality all
right i'm not i gotta hold on to the quantum slimes for a little bit what's that i need to plant uh
garden we are replacing mint fruit with phase lemon in fact we are going to do two phase lemon
gardens folks this is right here they're right over there oh i said a bad idea it's they're
right here what's wrong with my brain i want i want a ton of production of that fruit i want
to be able to constantly keep an auto feeder going on going on that thing mint fruit gang rebel
eat mint mangoes please read about echoes get rid of the cats already um okay hold on let me
these guys eat fruit so i mean i could here's what we're going to do i that that that that that that
stop it quiet they eat fruit i'm going to just load this up we're going to put the quantum slimes
in here and start production hey they eat fruit so i can fill that up they'll be eating here we go
plenty of food let's go way too many you're going to be in trouble how the fuck did you
how they why they're flying why are they floating away why are they floating away
give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me give me
why are they flying away feed them i was feeding them it's fake what oh wait i have 27 still
all right feed feed them before they all leave hurry up and feed them with the auto feeder
feed them why's i'll do it these things are freaking me out they really are they're just
spreading out everywhere all right i got gold plorts i got quantum plorts hell yeah
let's uh keep feeding gold plorts now i'm gonna do i need crystals or maybe another one maybe i'll
save it water then water quick water quick do i have to do i have to do this save how often do
i have to do that you don't need to do that if you keep them fed okay that's what we're gonna do
all right so that i got the i got all right i gotta keep that filled i'm gonna keep that
filled up we're gonna go stuff it in there wow this game is like seriously can we give like
how do we get the developers of this game like a hundred million dollars to like make more stuff
like this okay looks good how much do these sell for that's what i want to know i'm very interested
in this all right let's go back for a sec i want to see what the quantum plorts sell for
and then i'm going to get crystal ports i'm gonna make maybe not is there is am i missing
the slime that's in there 118 is there another uh is there a new thing i can get i have so much
money you never read what the echoes do that's that cool i'm kidding relax within the crumbling
walls of the ancient ruins small traces of energy can be found never staying in one place for very
long called echo ease they are believed to be a phenomenon resulting from some kind of ancient
event since they are harmless echoes are often collected by ranchers as good luck charms are
used as decorations echoes appear regularly in the nooks and crannies of the ancient ruins
as well as from extractors echoes can be used as decorations simply vac them up and shoot them
anywhere you want they'll hover in that spot until you vac them up cool oh puddle porch
one two three four five seven eight nine eleven twelve do i sell these or hold on to them
maybe i'll sell sell seven sell more more more i just need one two i need one all right i gotta
go get another okay is there another slime in that area where it just was there's like a lava
slime or something right you have sugar hands guys all fed sugar hands there are more areas
oh okay all right now this is what we're gonna do i'm gonna bring a shitload of meat and a shitload
of fruit what was the where are what were they it was this guy which is meat and then there's this
guy which was fruit he loves these things i'm gonna i'm gonna bring these and i need 15 of
these right there it is i can now feed that guy 25 shit okay when i said upgrade the seven z
rewards oh yeah i have a lot of money path upgrade torch upgrade rewards promo station
cobalt chroma milkshake chroma classic or sparkly sparkly classic or heavy metal classic classic or
tiger tiger classic or radiant radiant classic or arcane arcane classic or cheshire cheshire
classic puddle slime lily pad gold slime gilded ooh lucky slime guardian i think i'll build out
this will show up better i think i'll recognize that more i'd be like whoa it's uh it's got like
red and green and it's got the huge okay yeah definitely that one ice cream cat yeah all right
hi guys hello need to bring a lot of fruit no i don't what is the boom slimes favorite food
briar hens okay how many briar hens do i have because i'm bringing a shitload what do you what's
it i need to keep one of these in case i need to grow them gold oh no no it was an awful joke what
joke i made a joke what joke did i make i wasn't aware of a joke what are you talking about what
joke joke you said among us i didn't that is too what's going on you didn't what i don't know what
i did you didn't change them i didn't briar hens i have a lot of stony hens this is unfortunate
briar there we are briar hen briar hen
come here take all the briar hens we need to do this sorry i'm going to wipe out the entire
population so i need 25 hens right so therefore i need 10 i'm trying to calculate this how much
are the roosters worth roosters are worth more right how what do i need the rooster is not worth
more they aren't well i could i could do with some clearing out here all right stony hen it is
no regular hens there's a lot of them running around i only need like two roosters per coop
all right let's let's fucking get rid of them all right how you guys doing bad are you well fed
we've got plenty of food over here so i need 17 right somebody said 17 regular hens
okay is that right 17 8 that's enough right one escaped what everybody escaped what are we
talking about who escaped everybody escaped is that real that's real what are they getting out
isn't there a net no i want how do they get out i don't know how you guys get out but whatever
they teleported out but why they're well fed you need to water them 31 all right i'm going to do
those wait whatever all right come on hurry up i need these get away from that back in there not
in there this way get in there get in there oh he whatever he just eats fruit i don't care
i need this fruit to hurry up you know i'm just i'm getting rid of the roosters so i can bring
more fruit yeah fuck this i'll get more red hens on the way there yeah i mean come on now i can
bring a shitload of fruit yeah i'll bring a full stack of cubits so let me open up both of those
big guys all right i'm ready i'm ready let's go i need to go this way to the quantum computer
realm to go up here i'm trying to remember where this whoa hello what the he's got like
electrocuted like i'm okay i'm fine this way there's so many how do i make one of those drones
okay i need a drone now drone 12 quantum plorts i can make one right now yep i'm making a drone
watch out for the explosions you know what it's time to do this too fuck it's like rotting all
right we're doing everybody just stay still give me a second done i just hold on i'm making this
i'm making this a phase 11 place but not this one maybe the other one i got i this is too much
it's way too much of this bullshit yeah i'm just that's i'm not doing that anymore
i'm making one of these phase lemon the one back here at the lab if you thought about going cold
turkey what am i cold turkey goodness all right just hold on just feed the fuck out of everything
feed feed the fuck out of every well these oka-okas i have too much oka-oka supply
way too much oka-oka supplied right now and way too i have a full stack of a hundreds i need to
oh boy okay what do i do here oh boy okay we got a what the fuck happened to them oh they turned
okay i need a auto feeder okay i need to just dump the oka-oka in here what's that oh put it on slow
feeding suck all the uh all these out okay sell this sell the rad plorts do it again we're gonna
crash the market that's fine i have to get rid of these i have so many
okay
i can't even pick it up i does birds lead them i don't even care
it's too it's overflowing it's overflowing these motherfuckers are overflowing right now i just i
jump i'll be back i'll be right back i just have to do this two more times oh my god there's so
many in there all right i have to i gotta delete some of these guys it's time to get rid of some
of these fuck this is mario running up the stairs to bowser's big star level but a little bit faster
hold on i need to go a little closer all right that's enough remember how badly i wanted these
last before i was like oh man i wish i had some more plorts to work the fuck what if they're
gonna eat those it's fine thought i have too many 44 crystals i'm gonna leave those i don't need
them right now he's stuck in a loop i really am but it's a very very expensive loop for them to
pay me i'm at 23 000 right now all right mario running up the stairs kind of all right now
just scoop them up might as well okay i'm gonna get the last of the oka oka's on the other farm
replace it with a phase lemon and then be done with it i'll be done with it job never ends
no it doesn't does it constant i need one of those buzzy bees right now okay wait i need rad
don't i how much did i need how much rad do i need i just sold all of it how much do i need for the
bee all right we're taking a full stack to the beat okay now i'm gonna go back to the lab we're
gonna suck up um okay deposit ports suck up remaining oka oka's turn that into a phase lemon
crop center okay what do i need utility drone where the fuck do i get wild honey
and do this but change style to actually change the style keep upgrading the seven z rewards
uh they do not see the cats are they they changed back they changed to the honey or did it
think you can debate me right now i just i saw the change in real time in the game world
what do you think i am all right kill this crop remove crops phase lemon let's go more lemons
oka oka deposit oka oka into oka oka depository oka oka has been deposited oka oka deposit is
complete oka oka is ready to be harvested oka oka is now in your inventory we're done see look
it changed these were cheshires before and they didn't have the honey thing on their head
oh each one of these is hiding from the other one they're all hiding from each other
quantums are all gone they better not be i'll be very upset with you well check on the quantums
drop the chickens i i'm about to go feed the chickens they're not all gone they're here oh
bingo all right he was he was that was actually a real one okay all right all right all right
phase lemons ready for harvest this will be enough that's enough all right i've got enough
to feed that guy completely all right i need i got the hens now 21 hens what did i need how
many hens did i need how many red hens did i want finish feeding that guy 25 more we're gonna
replenish i'm not using the phase lemons right now and restock them 25 is what you need okay
keep them fed it shouldn't be too hard right now all right let's slow that down a little mid
are you real all right we can keep that in there okay quantum port to sell some quantum ports
yes sure i'll sell 25 of them and then i'm gonna leave finally with 26 thousand dollars
more than that twenty seven thousand dollars bingo how do i do that how do i change my gun
it's outside house cobalt oh no definitely strawberry milkshake oh yeah heck ranch house
yeah strawberry milkshake cobalt strawberry milkshake cobalt what does cobalt look like
this classic look like what does the house look like oh well oh yeah definitely i like that one
oh this is like a medigun now is this what it all is this is this is this is what this always
looks like oh i like the boom hunter i think it's time i i think i have to get rid of the boom
hunters they just annoy the fuck out of me i just keep hearing the boom boom boom boom i don't even
need the boom floors anymore all right expedition time how do i i don't i don't remember how to
fucking get up there i have no idea i forget how to get all the way up there teleport from here
are you based i'm based i don't know probably not he's like do whatever wait are they all out
all right back to the expedition from here we go up through there through here feed this guy
go here feed this guy get their keys get their stuff have extra cool things to do cool we're
gonna go not that way this way slime rancher slime rancher ancient memes ancient memes
looking for briar hens that's it what the hell are you two doing in there oh
the cycle of life where am i going this way so i didn't even eat them the way how is it the
cycle of life i'm like this one cave system oh this way finally he figured it out he's
going the right way everybody can relax oh shit i think are the puddles holy fuck i thought that
was a giant monster in there i was supposed to scream i looked over the sunset and it was like a
fucking octopus was here i thought i thought that thing was a fucking monster
i was shit my pants i finally fucking made it all right let's go nope am i fucking no correct
he's muted no no i'm just fucking i had my mouth open for a little while though i'm not gonna lie
my mouth was just this is why i'm so glad face cam is not turned on ever my mouth was just like
open and i was just looking at the phase level i was i was so excited to like just i can't wait
to go feed this guy i can't wait to feed him i don't i don't want any more of these
just all right you know you know the guy from hey arnold the guy that would just be like
hey helga and then she just like punches him in the face every episode i was just doing that
by the way she like beat the shit out of that kid all the time he used to get punched directly
in the face and it wasn't like oh you like pushed him or you like but no it was like
she would put her fist back behind her head and it was just jammed into his fucking nose
i wonder what that that kid's hospital bill oh my god this glass is shattered every episode
like think of the bills all right i gotta go up fuck is this i have to open where do i open it
hey helga i feel like was there an episode where he did a full they did a full episode on that kid
right am i misremembering this they did an entire episode of that kid like his his life
his like daily life right am i just making that up all right where was that door all right wait i
gotta pay attention no it's up here it's this way and then i lost it where do i go he's like
down there hold on open this back up where's this motherfucker god damn it where the fuck is he
oh my god how did i go the wrong way i don't like this part get rid of the icicles i don't like this
it's like uh worthless just like this one way okay there he is so i gotta go all the way around
this one dumb ass way to get over here recharge i'm gonna lose my fucking mind oh wait wait wait
wait no am i drowning oh my fucking god i hate this place oh my fucking god i'm furious oh my god
oh no that was oh i am fucking furious right now that was so many fucking resources the stupid
icicle walls were like and everything's verticality and look at all these ruins and oh my god fuck that
place i hate that place we all hate this place agree oh we all hate that place i'm so fucking mad
right now that was i took so much time to do that you gotta fight you gotta find the one place to
go in to go around the stupid fat fucking boom lava guy and and this one way to go in and it's
gonna go up and then you're gonna go up and then you're gonna go around the side and go around
the corner watch out for that pole oh my god i am fucking mad i am truly mad that was so much
shit and if you touch water you die instantly that's the first time i've died in the water
stay in here stay in here i'm so fucking mad oh they're starving i can't believe it oh my god
fuck that place damn it oh you don't have no idea how actually annoyed i am about that of course
stupid jetpack the re watch this recharge time like i hate this ready one to start recharging now
why does it take what why does it take that long why does it take that long
all right i'm taking i'm rage eating fruits right now claim items of the dock what are you talking
about was it not bait i this is very specifically what i had on me i don't i think i don't think
that's bait i think that's accurate why would there be phased lemons and briar hens and shit
that was not a bait okay oh look at that pretty cool it it scatters oh all right well nice all
right all right everybody relax i'm fine i have enough for the so mad right now it was just the
fact that i was i just missed the edge by a tenth like one tiny step and i went to dunked like a
fucking shit loaf into the toilet water it was so infuriating i'm still mad about it
this is gross
that was disgusting man i know that was fucking vile i'm sorry i don't know why i'm dude i don't
know where they came from all right i need 25 of these take us a raid what raid we got a raid
i don't see right we got a raid i'm getting distracted i'm i'm good all right i'm gonna
sell these ports wait i'm gonna put these ports into the machine is there i don't i don't see
the food is piling up i miss a read i don't see one oh big hall
i feel like these are so sour eating one of those is like i would imagine it's like the commercials
steam would come out of my ears my face would turn like green you'd hear a big choo-choo train
phase limit i mean what if i get wild honey all right i got 50 phase lemons let's go
dump them in there and then i'm bringing i have enough oh i'm so annoyed i just keep seeing the
image of me falling down the legend it's making me so mad these are in the forest okay look at all
this food this is so terrible i have not fed these cats in like seven or eight days and food is just
overflowing here this is horrible here i'm sorry here here here here here i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm
sorry here here here here here here here oh way too much feeding this is on low put it on low why
is it even on there all right and then i'm gonna take these oh so many things to do all right i
don't want to get i'm stuck in the loop again where i'm just running back and forth feeding
vegetables to these things when i should be going and feeding the big guy and now i'm gonna get
stuck in a fucking loop again where and then i'm gonna jump into the lake again into the water
i'm so annoyed it's all right settle down i'll be fine i'll be okay don't even who cares don't
collect them do not do that this is gonna be very enticing i know it looks really hate these things
holy shit there's a 94 of these okay i have to do this i have to sell a shit no i don't yes i do
it one stack i'm gonna sell one stack of crystals uh he's in a permanent slime loop
not after this done done i'm leaving you stupid asshole
now i need a lot of hens i'll take care of it let's go hens hens hens hens hens hens back in there
let's get food you've got food in here okay whatever i'll fill it back up no i won't let's
go i'm leaving no i'm not here just take these okay good get back in here i'm trying to get
okay i need i need to take two back and collect red hens and if i fall i swear to god
if i fall into the goddamn ocean i am going to miss i don't know i'm gonna be very upset about
it though i'm gonna be very very mad about it i'm here where to go he phased out dick all right red
hens yes hello hello yes yeah yeah yeah yeah how many do i need a lot more okay this should i
should be able to get there just by walking around and picking up hens let's move this is the wrong
way all right we can relax now i can settle down let me just chill for a sec all right this last
red hen over here this one and this one do not under any circumstances fall in the goddamn water
okay i'm gonna take a few deep breaths and we're gonna be fine okay okay there we go back to what
we were doing everything is good there's no issues at all follow me i should probably pee
could i pee it's time to pee it might be no no peeing until i do this i will pee when i'm done
let's try this again this is a majoris mass thing or something by the way do i only have like a
few days how many days do i have to do this this way i have seven more days to do this
wait what do you mean is there all right get up there oh i have to go this way okay go just
collect chickens on the way there and i'm gonna feed that those two guys one likes meat one likes
hens i'll take another hen thank you scream if you see a briar hen scream as loud as you can
okay this way don't jump into the water i almost did that was very close i had zero oh that would
have been very bad i would have freaked the fuck out we're good a lot of hens up here oh that's
good good good good good good i think i'm i think i have enough let's just get another one just in
case all right and then we have to go this way i really need to go in the teleporter where is
the teleporter up here all the way at the top i have enough i don't know i'm not picking anything
up i need 44 hens i think you're actually i think you're right 31 i'll get it by the time i get
over there world famous among us mega fan excuse me all right i'm back it only took like 20 minutes
to get back here i am here and i'm ready i'm not going to let anything bad happen slow
i'm gonna go slow take this in play nancy drew no no i'm not gonna play nancy drew right now
hey listen drew crew hey drew crew settle down this time get it right i'm not don't sprint
everywhere just walk just walk get that 250 cool all right keep going we're up here
hang a left over here and then i'm ready to go in it's right here where's this guy there he is
and we go down this way uh-huh there's the door i almost thought i was gonna fall because i thought
i didn't have enough rocket here we go relax how many do i need i need like 10 more or something
all right that's fine we're gonna go up to this this guy right here what was he like right here
we're gonna be fine see any turkeys let me know you go here bang a left this way
which will bring us i need to go there um he's like up here
wrap all the way around i thought that was a no uh all right this way and then go all the way around
i don't know maybe give me that all right three i need 11 right he won't eat the babies four five
okay cool he's up here all right there he is where are you oh oh yeah all right i got it
that's enough five six seven eight nine ten i need one more eleven okay now where's the where uh uh
he's down here right isn't he where's the uh i gotta open the door oh my god oh my god boom
what do i get key what else a fruit okay a hen i have one key now cool all right let's feed this
other guy i have to pee so bad nice got the key i can't believe i made it three hours though peeing
it seems kind of bizarre usually i pee every like hour and 25 minutes on the dot
all right let's kind of float over here uh-huh here we go shit why is this closed now
yeah where's the thing to open that oh no where is it where's the thing to press the button to
open that is it this one okay yeah oh um hold on i'm not peeing yet got it nice what do we get
uh i don't want boom slimes what was that for is there a key there's literally no key in there
i do i what i just used oh my god it's right here okay i was gonna say i just i fed him like
40 chickens i don't need these i don't want the plort either wait i want to see what happens can
you eat that what do you turn into a quantum bomb oh shit it's gonna explode every fucking reality
i have two keys now okay what's here where are the keys to i think this is a spoiler all the way up
here go to the teleporter all right teleporter tele teleporter teleporter going up teleporter going
up tele teleporter going up use that one i gotta press this button it opened it opened i just want
to get up there open mouth andy again uh do i get up there um i think maybe this way and go around
i don't know maybe i can just do it from here i don't know nope nope nope nope
i'm gonna go around this way then wrap that way but that door is open though hold on
sick i know i have to pee just wait i'm busy that leads us to here which is all the way up here
open this go through this thing which leads me to here which leads me to here and then i turn this
way which leads me to here which leads me to here i go over here that leads me to here and then i go
up this way and it'll lead me to here open that door and it'll lead me to there i oh i get it okay
wow and there's the door and this teleporter there it is but what is in this room i don't know
a secret slime i hope so monochrome no no i don't think i'll use that one
there's a slime key it's just a waste of time hopefully it's not i'm just gonna do it
spaceship the ruins used to be some kind of warp station used by whoever created it
to connect to one of the most distant corners of the far far range be careful beatrix
once you cross over you'll be in truly untamed country the beautiful the other side can be an
unforgiving place oh okay all right activate it oh we got a fill with quantum quantum plorts
quantum quantum quantum quantum quantum i'll be back yes yes my god dude what the where the
fuck am i right now okay i don't know okay this is fucking terrifying i have them no i don't
you already have enough but i thought i needed to be quantum plorts not quantum slimes what does
this take me just get some fruit and feed these ones yeah that's right just need some fruit
crunchies how many do i need 10 crunchies crunchies excuse me crunchies where are they
is this the fruit ninja guy yep i hold every world record i got to 5 000 points
eat that yeah can you believe it i got to 5 000
hog fruit eat it use the teleporter i'm already invested play fruit ninja uh you know that would
be really boring i don't really necessarily even mean that for you i mean that for me fruits
plorts here we go oh three six seven eight need two more more plorts and i'm good is that enough
that's enough i'm good i have enough remember you're only playing this game because you have a
feeding frenzy fruit ninja made you dickhead
how do we turn it on smoke fire and mirrors glass desert oh this hurts my head this is okay this
is what i see when i wake up in the morning right when i open my eyes and or you can replace it with
this going into a dark room after being in the sun that kind of change that your brain does and
your eyes do adjusting to a dark room when you come in from brights holy shit butterscotch warp
depot this place is really cool definitely gonna be new slimes here i bet you there's new slimes
here where that starts with letter g i don't know what is it the new fruit sir oh saturn slime thank
you durafish slime what is that i don't know what this thing is what's this thing what do i do with
this go pee go pee go pee i don't know what that is go pee go pee go pee i don't know what that is
shit i gotta go pee wow that's what you guys meant oh i'm sorry i'm fucking weird i should i need to
have like reverse aging is that movie the guy like reverses it going backwards he ages the other way
give it a plot oh not click yeah benjamin button lick well i can do quantum dervish
what's up here there's a cheshire trust over there that's where i came oh that's where i came
from never mind i turned around all right pee time hi we're back go pee if you need to go get
a snack go refill your coffee if you're drinking one or if you're drinking in water have some more
water i'll be right back in about two minutes three minutes hello is that me on oh huile sick
i love you if i had a huile here right now i'd go like this oh cool look at this dude in the beach
oh everybody loves fireman come on who's that one eating the hamburger you see so many hamburger
gifts but that's really good all right let's move on let's go we'll catch that one oh in the next
break the imposter is sus all right i need to get more slimes i want to go for 20 like at least five
they can multiply all right wait wait wait wait wait i'm going all the way up i see a big guy
okay is this heat or something it was standing to the oxygen i don't know what's going on is it
too hot for me here i have no idea this looks like i'm suffocating who's throwing rocks i'm
just sneezing somebody's throwing rocks who's doing who's doing this hey who's doing that get
out of here Bowser's fury oh that's a slime that's a new slime that's a new slime
oh fire slime shit that is a turkey what was that it's dead but i don't it was
what the fuck is what is all this stuff happening are these what are those i have this overwhelming
that was a new that was like a turkey or something making a lot of money now
we can have dervish fire quantum fire quantum dervish fire dervish and there was another chicken
these new no rock oh what's up there it's meat angle gordo what's tangled okay this this three
new slimes in a row that's a lot thank god all right cool so what's all the way at the top
i mean i kind of i'm using it i'm using it geez this is death what the hell is that
your style is shattered oh that's cool what was that i just saw like what how do i do what do
i do with these things i mean you want something what do you want what does he want you're an
everlasting gobstopper what do i do with him what something over there what is that
shit is a fountain this is a water fountain i need to suck up water damn it need water oh my god oh
my god oh my god i'm fine holy shit what was i doing what am i doing relax that was almost
a complete disaster i'm gonna go this way i don't need the quantum slimes painted hen get away from
me i'm still going i need a where's the teleporter i need a teleporter right now i'm going in too deep
i need a teleporter teleporter damn uh i kind of need to get to the wait a nightshade
that looks like a teleporter or that's a boss i can't tell yet that could be the end game boss
we will find out just looking for a teleporter all i want i've just got to walk around till i
find a teleporter oh shit hold on give me these guys it's this way this way goes back there or
let me just see what's at the end of the rainbow here what's at the end of the rainbow two doors
beatrix left is filled with moments where though there's two doors and you can only choose one what
i came to the far far range because a search for the unknown is in my bones
and in time even a thousand light years away from earth wasn't enough so i searched for secrets
within the ancient ruins that led me here this place was my ticket to go even further there's
door left or right the ruins are actually great engines that allow for travel through space and
maybe even time after years of study i knew how to activate them and i alone would be the first
to cross over into the true beyond it was the ultimate adventure but then there's that other
door i met thor and fell in love what are the chances of that she had a piece of my heart and
the universe had the other two doors beatrix all right that one has like a space pod in it
what's this one have it's the same door it's actually the same door at least the same place
the same door didn't have to choose it's actually the and we've got weird pork you pine fruits
i need to fill my water i chose my door i went back to the ranch and promptly sold it
i packed my things and took a tour of this beautiful land one last time leaving these
little notes for you there's time i said goodbye to the get your fucking mouse off the screen life
i had my hands and feet tingled as i approached this monolithic warp terminal what lay ahead of
me was an adventure unlike anything i'd ever known in my life stepped on the platform my heart racing
but i didn't go i had packed for a new adventure but it wasn't going to be beyond space and time
so i said a little goodbye to what could have been and headed to thor's ranch
i'm looking forward to hearing the sound of those wind chimes i've never been in love before and
never known anything yet you're fucking up my goddamn monologue i like it it's time i got to
knowing what all the fuss is about so good luck to you beatrix as always remember to use your head
but let your heart do the thinking every now and again it might surprise you well i chose my door
it didn't work out though choose the door there is i you know i think this guy got to the end
and realized there's nothing here and then decided to write this uh yeah i chose there's nothing here
there's supposed to be like a teleporter leading to like another time period or something
nothing here but uh i guess i'm gonna have to like say that they was my adventure along the way
just leave breadcrumbs and say like yeah i chose my door you choose your door uh there's a giant
x on the ground there is no treasure on the ground beatrix no treasure in there i've already looked
the map is fucking useless all right get rid of the hens i want whatever this is a cool pair
i'd want if you chose your door is that all that's over here i think that's all i can do
cool all right well i chose there's a huge beam on it though i don't believe that
go check your emails no it's the same door no what they're trying to say is all paths might
lead to the same outcome you still got there i'm really kind of disappointed there's no
teleporter that can get the hell out of here and go back to earth all drains lead to the ocean
do they i don't know it has it gets like processed
i'm peter my name is peter this is your play through oh that's fucking terrifying
you can't do minus four only minus two works check the emails i'm going back to the emails
i'm gonna check the emails i got slimes to take care of all right give me out i've got a lot of
i've got a lot of science science projects to do i gotta get out of here down i'm stuck
how do i get out of here um this map doesn't really help me at all i get up there that way
5g gum can you make the diablo 2 barbarian shouts again um okay
oh
that's fine potion where's it going this way oh how could i forget this one
okay goodbye thank you for coming i hope you got the clip you were looking for get out of here
oh fire fire oh i can spray that with water
i don't have any water fuck all right i'm going back to the ranch and i'm gonna do a bunch of
research i'm gonna i have to play the video game let's go go go go go go go go go go go
i don't know how i got here i don't even remember i opened up one of these a door over here right
i have no idea how i even got over here oh there it is any teleporters i know man i really do
let me work on the farm for a while i'm sorry farm your cousin from boston
what's in there that's an ipa oh it's a wicked ipa what kind of ipa that's a well you serious
dude it's a wicked ipa your cousin from boston we just drink beer every day was that sam adams
yeah i love that stuff oh shit there's another one i don't oh i need another key okay wait wait
overwhelming myself let's go i remember the heat level stop it oh what do you got a lager oh i love
boston lager cover the fire now like i want the i want to get at least 10 fire slams i feel like
this is going to be worth a shitload it's pretending to be the bot well you guys don't know like that's
the sam adams boston commercials the guys like uf cars and from everybody they're on tv all the
time of course you do i want wait what are these can i suck those up no they're just
explosives i'm actually surprised nobody has like put a deep fake me onto that guy okay i got enough
i wanted 10 someone's gonna do it now yeah it's okay i thought there was water i thought it was
water i thought it was water it was blending into the whatever all right r2d2 is gonna be fine
just spray a little bit of oil in his can good let's go back to the farm sam adams omega l tv
omega l boston omega l resident no his resident sleeper not omega l there okay there's the
teleporter they got r2 oh no they got r2 back to the farm i've got what i want move while you were
away what happened they make that stuff what did they make their own like monetary system or
something while you were away the boom cats made a trade route with the rad slimes
quantums are probably gone wait i was going for a very long time wasn't i okay i thought they were
all dying like they they weren't yellow anymore and they were like
fucking just like disintegrating they're very hungry though um hold on wait wait wait wait
wait i need uh i gotta hold on shit i need to make uh i don't know what to do i don't know
what to do stop stop stop slow down slow down i don't know what to do i have too much shit
i need um i gotta i have to do this i have to do this i don't know what to do
Hair, no, no pears. I need hold on
Give me a fucking empty slot with those lemons lemons lemons lemons lemons lemons
Lemon lemon lemons. Oh
Slow why am I doing this? I don't know why I get in like some of these moods sometimes or just
Making a loud noise is the option. There's no other options. I don't know. I don't even know why
Are you?
All right, we're good missed every shot. I did not miss every shot
Okay, fill it up
There we go. What?
Hey
Hold on get back here
Get back here. There's food in there. I promise
Stop leaving
Stop. Oh, they're trying to get that
I'm gonna spray them. Stop. No
Get oh my god, there's a hundred
Welcome, whatever. They'll be free. I need two new pens
Email thanks be it. I never knew you felt that way. I picture you are there on a safari
Well for that is where I missed you too when I was in LA
Oh that bar was just awful, but at least I got some stage time case appears the chimps name was Colonel bananas
Alright. All right. I need to make
new
Going here. We're going to the docks and I'm gonna make two new pens
You know what? Just come with me
I'm gonna use you guys anyways wrong email
I mean wrong email. I don't have an email slime toy shop. Yep slime toys firecracker. Ooh firecracker
Ooh, where's the toys scroll down?
grapes
ooh
grapes, ooh
grapes
Okay, emails. There are no emails. I was the toy thing. Oh over here. Is that a toy thing?
Scroll down on the emails. I don't have it. Yeah
What are you guys on about didn't get a new style did I get the new style for I don't like that one
Mosaic slime didn't even seen these yet tangle slime sleep. I slept. There are no emails. I'm going to the dock
I'm gonna put new pens up and no, I'm not actually I'm getting rid of these guys. It's over. I'm just gonna pull
I'm just gonna pull plug. I'm gonna pull the plug. Okay, it's time to pull the plug. Ooh
All right. Look at that later. I'm putting dervish slimes in here get an incinerator
I don't have any room on this plot
Should I just delete this and put an incinerator here? I think I'm gonna do that. I think so. It's time
guys wait
Let me clear this out first to make sure nothing in here suck all this up
I'm gonna deposit this into the inventory. I'm gonna put the hens somewhere. Oh my god. I need a
Get in there. Can I put these hens in here? Okay, cool. All right, what are the docks?
It's a far run though. Hey
You guys are just getting out stop getting out. Oh my god
Jewels I can't get this
It's too many. It's too many. It's too many. I have to I have to get I don't know to do this
It's money is everywhere
Too many quantum escape artists. I don't know. Okay, I have 50 quantum ports
Sell them I'm gonna sell everything
Get drones. I need the honey to get hold on make a teleporter to the dock. I will after I'm let me just do this
Make it to square one. I need an apiary. Okay
Get rid of the boom cats. Yeah boom cats are gonna go away and I can replace it with dervishes
Yes, good idea. I hope somebody likes vegetables
I
Broke his neck. How are you coming back? Here's my plan. Here's my plan
Okay, good. We are gonna see we're gonna be very very careful here. What do the fire slime?
Dead okay, I'm gonna make this an incinerator and we're gonna keep this and put fire slimes in here to see what happens
Good plan. I like that plan. Goodbye incinerator
An ash troll allows you to collect the ash of incinerated food at its base, which is eaten exclusive. I blow
Accidentally just created exactly what we needed and
Got an email from Casey. Hi Casey. What can I do for you? Hold on?
I'll reach your email in one second. Apparently just murdering some cat slimes
I ain't saying all right these guys you better not fucking kill me get away from me. This is so dangerous
Oh my god. Oh
My god, you little dicks. I swear to god
I'm so glad to get rid of these things feed them feed them to incinerate them
That doesn't make any sense ahead. All right, we have successfully eliminated the least by least favorite person in the game. Here we go
What does it normal food? I've got anything in there
Lean that out. Oh, these went up in value. Oh shit. Nice. Okay fire slimes going in here
So fire slimes eat. Let's take a look at the slime a pedia. They eat ash
They live on ash
Delete just about any food, but not without it being burnt to ash first
Use an incinerator with an ash throw
Upgrade our slimes need ash to survive and will quickly snuff out if left on any other surface for too long
When keeping fire slimes and an ash throw simply burn any food item to put wait they go into the fire thing
They go in here
Well, I just placed them. That's like that's annoying
Okay, I need to burn food. How many can be in here three or four. I need ash. Okay
They're working already full how can I tell one escape
Um
Upgraded it's already upgraded. Okay. Can I have four in here?
And what can I have as many as I want in here or is the limit as many as you want?
All right. How do I collect this?
Fire ploy nice. Oh, this is gonna be swell
Make sure you feed them. Is there like an ash meter? Oh
We're in any food item to produce some ash and fill the tro. Oh
I see. Okay, I get it
It's just it's just a sand. Okay, I get it. I get it. I get it cool
How much of these worth very nice? All right, so then what I can put Dervish slimes in here
Will they be mad about that? Okay, so should I can I feed a fire plort to a Dervish plort?
Cool. No fire plorts just worth just money
Okay, cool. So these guys what are these guys like?
Oracle pair is their favorite a Dervish lime is a swirling whirling bundle of energy in a slimy form
Dervish slimes are commonly found in the glass desert cruising across the dusty dunes at high speed atop little whirlwinds
One thing's for certain wherever the Dervish slime needs to go. It needs to get the tickets or it goes quickly
Dervish slimes can cause total chaos on a ranch if not cared for properly
in addition to frequently riding atop whirlwinds at high speed and collecting objects along the way a
Highly agitated Dervish slime can produce giant cyclones of air and vacuum up and toss about anything they touch
Cyclones are roaring across your ranch. There's little you can do other than brace for the chaos. Oh god
Okay, but keep them happy. They love prickle pairs. I know what I'm doing
They eat well, we'll just keep them happy for a second here. Oh
Plarts
How's this Ash doing? Pretty good. Pretty good. Okay, suck it up
Dervish plort
I'm assuming Dervish and quantum is what to do. Is there a way I can reliably get these out without sucking these guys up
All right, we're changing this move the crops
We what do I want in here a prickled a prickled pear
Where is it a prickle Rick?
Here you go your favorite food
All right. So now
It'll be okay for a little while. We'll get that shit to grow. They got food. How are you guys doing?
I'm gonna refill this throw
A lot of you guys I need a bumblebee thing to refill this
It's got to be a better way to do that
All right
Oh
Okay
Don't do it for you. He's doing this on purpose
Roth throw whatever
frog
I despise you
I think that's kind of harsh man. Are you though? Really? I'm sorry. Why?
All right, i'm gonna do
I want to combine something here
Look at all those floors. Hell, yeah
They don't have any food in here and they want prickly pears
All right
I'll give you ten dollars to pour you maple syrup down your pants pockets
These pants bought I think these pants were more than ten dollars. So it'd have to be way more than that
But I would just ruin these pants
All right. These guys are
I'm a toy. All right. What are they? Uh, what are they like? What kind of toys do they like a buzzy b?
honey slimes rubber ducky
octo buddy
nightlight
power cell
rad slimes
big rock
phosphor slimes rad slimes boom slimes
honey
huddle scuba pod
Nightlight phosphor slimes. No
big rock
the buzzy b
What did you get out? Hey
Yeah, they love buzzy b
um, I want to
Stay there
I wish I had five more inventory slots
inventory
I didn't do that on purpose
Keep this shit over here for a minute
Build we're good. These guys eat fruits. Well
Just have these for now
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
Any other questions?
Email right
Maybe the year we both came home. Do you ever think we'll have whatever it doesn't matter
I should have told you then what I never did. I should have said it a hundred times
I think about all the time that if we had been best
Honest about it. We how might still be running on that garden shop and i'll be writing music in the basement
You guys eat a lot
You guys eat too much. All right, we're gonna thin this out a little
We don't need that many. Okay, I took out four
let's have
We'll do
One two, three, four five six six is okay
What do we do with the other ones?
Just destroy
Put them in the water
These guys have food
Put them in storage. You can't store a fire slime
All right, that's good
He's ready. They are ready
Very cool
Now we'll get double
eventually
I have a lot of points. I'm gonna I think i'm gonna store these or something. How much are they?
Money is i'm not really spending money anymore
Money sink, I think until i'm done playing this game is this
Advanced slime toys. Well, that was a lot of money
Market link
I just bought it grotto. I just i'm just buying money
Okay, I don't know what I just did
advanced toys
stego, buddy
soulmate
Dark hole brick. Ooh
Gyro top they love it
Hey guys, look look at the toys. I got you and then these guys want the flaming rock
It's kind of creepy. I did not
No, no, no, no, no, no stay don't I have to play with that toy
No guys get over here, please get back here
Come here. Ow
Get in there
Get back over there
No, no, no, no, no, no put the aritha put shit down. He's gonna burn out. He's gonna burn out. He's gonna burn out
They're good, right?
Okay, come here
There we go. Thank you
good
Give me the toy
Puzzle cube
Quantum slimes love puzzle cubes
Oh, I don't
It's bringing me back bad memories
You guys good?
No, they're not
Solve it
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
Fill it up. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
I am going to go deposit all of this shit
I would appreciate if you guys got back in the thing though, whatever
You'll know you'll just die or whatever and I only need like four you anyways
Look, uh
The next thing i'm going to do is get a bunch of drones
To have them do all this work. That's next that's coming up now
So let's do some selling
How much is this worth fire ploys are worth 51. That's it. Dervish is worth 74
I need quantum ploys. Don't I save them?
The pairs are going over here
These guys love this shit what about the quests
The quests haven't really been that good
They've been kind of lame
But I you want for for a fucking two turkeys four strawberries and 250 bucks. This is worthless
All right. I'm gonna go deposit this stuff and take a look at what I need to figure out how to do these drones
I need honey
I have to build
some
Excavators or whatever the hell they are
Do the metal and unlocks a new area. All right utility drone
I need six wild honey
Wild honey
I need to make apiaries to get the honey
I have one of them already. I need pink plorts
Let's go get pink
tons of pink plorts
moss blanket apiary
That's the one
Okay. Hi guys
Who's hungry?
Pink see you needed these. That's right. You're that's true
That's absolutely accurate. I did need them
You're right
These lemons look so good. I really just want don't you want just squeeze one of these in your mouth
How do you feel like these are really cold ice cold lemon juice extra sour that sounds awesome right now
Okay apiary
One two three, how many can I have at once three, right?
And put this in the moss level, which is the moss one this one up here
I can have six
Eight I can have eight. I know that's six, isn't it? No, it's six
The genre of germa joke where he over describes food good stuff. What?
I I want that I want to eat that right now
Over describing food
Wait, I didn't put those fire plorts in here
Well, I did it already
They added so much to this game. So am I just right now enjoying
A fully just complete how much of this stuff wasn't here?
Three four years ago tons of it really most of this
Holy shit. Okay. Cool. Uh, let me see. I need pink again. I'm gonna eventually need it. Ah, whatever
Uh here just eat this i'm gonna need pink again later
Everything before the temple. It seems like a lot
Uh, you i'll throw this into the fire
You guys got food?
You do? Okay. Good
Uh, I don't I just don't I don't even want this
Okay now
I just lost everything. I was just doing what am I doing?
I just lost everything forget everything. What was I doing?
I was about to go and oh it put apiary, right?
I still have the gold
Up here. We need to we're gonna teleport
I think I know what i'm doing
I think I know what i'm doing. I think it's eating right? Yeah
Okay through this teleporter
And they're gonna put apiaries everywhere how much of your blood is heal at any moment?
Um, I don't know it depends. Okay. Let's say I had a heal in the morning
that's
What?
16 ounces of heal
Which how does that get into my bloodstream does it goes in my stomach from my esophagus into my stomach
and then down into my intestines and everything and absorbed
so
I don't know over the course of the day. I don't know what I would be like maybe like
1.2 1.4 percent heal at any given moment. All right, we're gonna put them all here
Apiary you
Okay, then up here. Oh, i'm sorry that hurt you
All right. So that's one two, three, four five six
12 minutes
Until I can come collect
In the meantime, we're gonna go sell a bunch of stuff. What do you think of fuel? Is it yummy genuinely curious?
Uh, I can give you my review of all three flavors
Uh chocolate is the best tasting out of the three
But unfortunately it is also the thickest of the three
so
If you want to sip on something for a long time, it's kind of like a it's it has the consistency of a milkshake
It's pretty thick
Tastes the best though
vanilla
Is it a decent flavor? It's probably I'd say it's second. Maybe it's a tie between berry and vanilla
The only the problem that I have with vanilla is it has kind of a weird
consistency
It tends to have sort of a weird after texture in my mouth
It tastes great, but not my favorite now berry on the other hand
Berry on the other hand is a best of both worlds. It's thin enough to drink
So it's really easy to drink. It's thin. It's not super
Thick and heavy and it also tastes good
It tastes like a strawberry milkshake like almost like a berry gogurt or something. I'd say that's probably my favorite one
nobody asked
Yes, they did dead
A voice crack
Clip it
And put it under my bed
And the voice crack very will show up and give me five dollars
Okay time to sell a bunch of shit
I got 12 minutes. Tell me yell at me when 12 minutes has gone by
Oh
My god, what's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? Get that out of here?
Get that out of here. Go the other way
Go the other direction
Who's doing that in there what the fuck is wrong with you
What's wrong with you in here?
Stop this shit
Why are they doing this?
They're hungry. The feeder is the feeder should be going
They're gonna kill everybody. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait settle down settle down settle down everybody quiet
Prickly pear prickly pear eat eat eat eat eat eat eat. Thank god. They're up here
Thank goodness. They are up there
Relax settle down
Don't do anything eat food
I make the all right. I have to the feeder is going faster, but
I have to uh, I gotta throw some other fruits in here
Selling every single one of these. Oh, I got a new email you guys good. Okay back in there, please
Okay, I you know, why can't they be like a gentle shoot? Why do I have to just fire them in here?
Why can't there be a gentle shoot?
That seems like why?
I'm gonna sneeze again and I have to mute. I'm sorry. I just sneezed like three times in a row
It was twice. I lied about it. I sneezed twice
Okay
I'm gonna I have a ton of those mangoes. Yeah, I do
What am I holding these weird onions for?
I also have the uh cubits as well. This should be fine only three left
I'm gonna go actually fill up not this way
I'm not gonna read
Somebody said say something inspirational streamer, okay
Well, what do you want to do?
Say hey, dude, say some what the fuck say something inspirational. What the hell?
Okay, um
You get go get it
Go for it
Go get it
Uh lycos go get it that's running out
These guys are just little bastards i'm saying i'm telling you
These guys are little bastards. They keep getting out and they just they're messing everything up. They're little these guys are little bastards
Look look at this little bastard. All right filling up this one
Up this way put them i'm gonna fill this up with mangoes
We're gonna incinerate the rest of the mangoes
And then we're gonna be on our merry way
Now these guys will be happy for quite a long time
This six in here. I think that one died. Whatever. What about the slimes in the grotto?
Oh, it's probably a mess in there
It's probably like poop everywhere and they probably I don't this I don't even want to go in there
deposit this
Go check on
Stay in there. Why would you jump out?
You're making me furious
Well minutes. Yeah, i'm gonna go there now
Cool. All right. We have novice gordo snare. Don't worry about that
blue teleporter
Hell, I don't oh my goodness. I just punched you again. I'm so sorry
Let's go see if I can get some honey
I'm gonna wrap around here and just see what it's like in here. I feel like i'm not gonna like what it's gonna
There's gonna be a 100 of everything
Okay. Um
What a mess
Yeah, what a mess what a mess, um, there's so many crystal plorts
Okay
I'm gonna throw 50 crystal plorts into the uh thing. Oh boy. Um, these are all just going into the yeah
Excuse me
There's the guy
There's the guy that hasn't fed us in six weeks
Everybody trying to get out and kill him. Oh my god. They really are getting us to kill me. Oh my god
It's an uprising. It's an uprising. Oh my god. They're so mad
They get away from me
You came in to collect your very expensive poop
What the fuck?
They're hollow. They've gone hollow. All right. I'll bring back food. Just sit down
Settle down. I'll bring back food. Just sit down
Why can't you be more like the green slimes? They're very docile
What do they eat?
Meat, okay, i'll be back. This is a full 50 50 50 50 50
Oh
Not satisfying at all. I ruined it
Oh, that sucked
I need pink plorts. Remember that
All right, they eat anything they eat anything. All right, i'm gonna go get vegetables and run in there and just i'm gonna start feeding people
Sell the rest of the shit that's in there. I have to clean this up. I can't just leave it like this
What kind of zoologist would I be?
Get in there before you die
How many
am I
Not worth picking up yet
So I need they i'm gonna just fill them with cubits
What are we doing over here? You know, here's just just say your favorite food is just gonna be in here
Keep them happy
Otherwise, they're gonna cause a problem
Eat the juntas. Okay, i'll feed the juntas
Stay in here. I don't want you guys to die. These guys are hard to take care of
Do some do something correctly. Holy shit
What have I done? What have I done incorrectly?
All right
I this is my least favorite part of the whole game
Am I am I supposed to shoot them out? They they just bounce everywhere
That's good
How are you guys doing? I need pink
12 minutes. I know I know I know I got it. I got it
I'll get there. I'll get there. I have to do this first though
Pink going into the not the incinerator. Let's go
All right, go go go go go go go go go
What's happening in 12 minutes?
I have to collect honey to make drones
I need to do this first. What have you done?
Now we're gonna feed everybody in here like I promised
collect
Stacks sell them and then we're gonna go collect the other shit
See, I told you I was gonna come in here and do this
Are you guys hungry?
See look i'm here
Everyone can be happy now good
The vegetables I don't have any. All right, we need I got the full stacks
I'm just gonna take the expensive ones and just i'm gonna store these. I don't think i've put very phosphorus in there
Wrong food. No, it's not
How many crystals were in here?
Too many. Okay. Another thing of crystals
So i'm gonna sell all this
another full stack of
rads
Buy toys for the grotto
Can you hold multiple stacks? I don't think you can you cannot
Do not believe you can
Do you guys have anything in here?
Too many
Okay
What's your problem?
Remember jokes are just family guy jokes. He just replaces the remember when to this is what happens. See I do
You still here aren't you?
You must really like family guy and me
You're you're here
You might like you must love that show
All right, i'm gonna sell these
Okay, well hold on how fair is that that means all referential humor is family guy I can't reference anything
Is that what they've cornered the market on anytime you can reference anything referential humor is not allowed because it's family guy
What would you prefer I do?
Those are the rules
All right, save these poop your pants
And what caliber of joke is poop your pants?
Should we go over that one? What caliber of humor is poop your pants streamer?
If i'm a family guy screamer
What is that? What's the poop? Where's what's poopoo?
I think that's um
Where does that fit on the scale of of uh humor of where we're how we're all right. We got a lot
It's very funny unless you do it
Oh
Allows you to remotely deposit resources into the refinery. Um
Yes, how do I get that?
All right time to go to
I gotta go this way. No this way. Where is it?
Uh, where do it's over here somewhere, right?
Where's that teleporter to get to the cat?
this way
Who the hell is that thing?
I've been streaming for four hours and 20 minutes. Oh nice
Hey, you guys remember that time when I streamed for four hours and 20 minutes
on 420
Kind of something like this
Hey, you guys remember the time
No
I think you guys say I have family guy jokes because I talk like peter griffin because I have a boston accent and he's got
A boston accent too. So whenever we do like I whenever I do like a weird voice
It's just peter griffin because I we're from the same place
ooh
hexacomb
Wild honey and buzz wax. Nice. How many of these do I need?
You're from red island. Oh new england
Oh poor chuckett pat poor chubba poor chuckett pat
I we have the same accent
I'm sorry. I talk like a cartoon character that has my accent. Well, i'm so i'm sorry
I'm from new england, but I don't talk like an idiot omega law. Oh, you're so smart
You're one of those smart new englanders what you're so smart
Hey, yeah
Oh, that was wonderful
all wild honeys
Yeah, yeah, you just moved here. I don't even live here. I don't I don't live there anymore. Who cares?
I don't have one of those. I don't have one of those new england accents
Yeah, would you just move here kid?
Okay, can I pass me a pass me a sam adams lager your cousin from boston
I'm so sorry
Yes, you do. I'm also from there
All right. Oh, hold on a second
I have a yeah, I have a boston accent. Sometimes I have a new england accent. I do
I don't sit here and talk like this. Everyone. I sometimes I enunciate my accent sometimes for fun because it's fun to do an accent
That's not listen to me talking. I don't talk like that on a regular basis
I do it like to do like the hey, i'm from boston joke guy
Even though I talk like that sometimes I talk it was right there cockies. Yeah cockies. Where are my car keys?
I don't know where your car keys. I don't care
I don't know
Say dollars dollars
dollars dollars
Say room. Yeah, go to go to you go to your room. Take clean up your room room room
He's a family guy streamer
I gotta go to my room and clean up on my car. He's not a family guy. He says family guy things
He's a family guy
He's so bad
All right. I can make a drone. Can I make more than one?
I just made one. What do I do with it?
Where is it? I have two drones
t oh
Okay. Um
What should I do with them?
Place it down. It's a gadget. Okay
Read the manual. Yeah, let me see if I can
All right, so if I
Drone a help learn more drones are a highly useful gadget that can reduce
Some of the work a rancher needs to perform on the ranch to keep things running smoothly
Once you build a drone simply give it a program using three simple inputs
target what the drone is looking for on your ranch
source
Where the drone gets its target?
Destination where the drone targets it takes its target
If you give a drone an impossible task or a drone simply cannot complete their task presently it'll go idle
A drone can run for about a day before it will return to its station. It must be powered again up again
Simply give it a refreshing blast of water to recharge it
The drone only works on your ranch and will only work within the ranch expansion in which you place it
Sometimes the drone will overflow an auto feeder
Or silo due to the bug in their software the 7c corporation insists. This bug is a feature
Am I fucking making you angry by talking like a guy from new england? This is all an act guys
This is that's how I normally talk. I'm I it takes me it's difficult to do this
I'm trying very hard not to talk like that as you can tell that's my real voice
Okay target what the drone is looking for on your now. I'm like gonna start doing it
What the drone where the drone gets its target where the drone takes its target?
So I want to take so target what the drone is looking for on the ranch
So if I put him down
Install let me see what this does
so
activate target is gonna be
This is so cool. The target is gonna be
um
fruit the source will be from a garden and the destination is going to be
Auto feeders, but no what?
I don't want to just kind of go around and fly around do this
Get the fruit from the gardens, right?
Pick a specific fruit
Can I?
Okay, specific fruit. So you want to get
Prickle pear
From a garden and put it into an auto feeder, but can I say specifically?
Can I say specific? I can't put this one. Does that matter? It'd be all fruit
Do all fruit
From a garden. That's what I did before everyone screamed at me
Let's see what he does
Wake up. Okay. Now I want to put uh veggies into the incinerator
target veggies
source
gardens
destination in the incinerator
activate
I need water. There's no fruit to collect
Yeah, there is this the prickly pear. I gotta get water. Hold on
Um, where's the fountain thing? It's like here somewhere, right? What's the water spout?
Do I not have one here?
I'm just gonna go to the pond
Hi guys
Okay splash
But the fruit needs to be there for okay. Oh, there he goes. Look they he's gonna put this in the incinerator
Let's see him do it
Whoa. Wow
That's kind of Arnold
Wow
I need to move this
All right. What was that? What was the next thing I was doing? Oh, just fill this up. Um
Build it more. I yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Sorry
Okay, uh, I'm I need to fill I need to fill this with the thing. They actually like come on
Then he'll put it in here. Okay, suck that up
And i'm gonna do some upgrades
I also kind of want to combine some people
rato upgrade
I don't know what that did, but I guess I got it
It's like there they go the bees
Sounds good
We've got plenty of food in here. I sucked that up. All right now
I have a couple of bees. I need to do advanced apiaries, which what does that need? Let's go find out right now
advanced apiary
make
six of them
Water the bees
Oh, look at the grotto. Good idea
Oh, that was not worth
7500 but okay scream where this is pre-recorded. Uh
What a fun game this really is all right blue warp depot
taming bell
refinery link
Remotely deposit resources in the refinery. Thank you. God give it to me
advanced apiary
I can make
Wait, hold on utilities
warp tech
binary link market link
need
Mmm
Royal jelly I need royal jelly from something
How do I get royal jelly well advanced apiary I can make them let's go one two
Pinks I need pinks shit
You get it from the jungle. Okay
What are they what's their favorite food? I don't think I even have it. Whatever
They're wasting the lemons. Uh, i'm about to completely remove a lot of slimes
once I
I'm gonna make crystal
I'm gonna make a crystal
spinning guys
Though i'm gonna make mostly crystal crystal spinning guys
Where's your cracker mk2? Oh nice
That's worth it. Those things are really good
I can make money. I got look. I got plenty of money. I'll be fine
Are you done with this game yet?
um
Maybe after tonight, I don't know maybe
I still really like this game. I'm still having a lot of fun
Maybe we'll see
I do really like it
But I have a lot of other stuff that I want to stream
I got to get on some other projects some other stuff to do
So I don't I don't know
I have to go through a couple of processes to start getting ready for some stuff next week
by the way
Uh on march 6th, if you haven't been to the stream in a while
Uh, we're gonna get it. It's gonna be an interesting stream. I would not miss at 1 pm pacific
you shovel
get your um
you know get your
Doubling
I don't want to give you any whatever just just it's a we're gonna be it's archaeology and
I need to
I gotta figure out a few things and you need to see it
Not cat boy. No, it's we're doing we have to do some archaeology
Why be vague about it?
Do you want me to spoil all the things that i'm gonna do on that stream?
Do you want me to read you the wikipedia article before you watch it? No
All right deposit these pink ports and then I can make another couple
When's the stream march 6th at one o'clock pacific can we get any hints?
Uh, it's an archaeology stream
It's the only thing you really need
All right advanced
one two three
Ah, I can get it
Freeman doesn't know the difference between archaeology and geology
Well, I can't can't it be both why is it why can't it be both?
Why can't they be both things?
You don't know
whatever
Why I get why I want i'm doing archaeology and i'm an archae i'm doing archaeologist stuff
It's not both. I didn't say it was both. I said the stream could have both
Does it have to be one or the other? Why can't we do multiple things on a stream?
You putting up with them kicking down
Don't spoil I'm not spoiling anything
Need more pinks
Is it gonna be on the same level as the carnival stream?
Um
Mmm, I would say more on the lines
of the halloween stream
It maybe okay a little a little more involved in the halloween stream
I need food
That means bugleberry that does not mean bugleberry. That just means the same kind of
The same I guess effort to what the fuck are you? Okay
Are you doing like the anime character thing?
Running around like a piece of food in your mouth
eat those vegetables
hurry
You feel like you don't have enough time on your hands
Yeah all the time
I would say all the time
How many do I need how many pink floors do I need? Come on somebody eat
Thank you
Oh another email
And people want me to breathe there's another one. I want
Remail from casey
Whatever life is different now. I had a year to think about things while you slept on your way across the stars
I think who is this person? I feel like I haven't replied to casey, but I keep getting gigantic emails from them
Hope the sun sets over there as gorgeous as they are over here
I'm glad I've shared part of me with you beatrix lebeau
I'm having to know that maybe one of these stars I see up there in the sky is you
Okay, how do I am I gonna stream blizzcon? I don't think I can I don't think I can do that
I don't think I'm not gonna stream blizzcon. I think don't you have to pay to watch blizzcon?
Isn't it like?
$500 it's free this year. Hmm
All right, i'm going
He's so cute. Look at this bushy bee
Get back in there. You're gonna starve
Don't fall out
You're gonna go to blizzcon. They don't I don't think that's happening this year
Have a drone collect the fire ploys. That's actually a really good idea. All right advanced apiary. There it is six
now
Do I want more drones or do I want to try to get that royal jelly?
Should I start with just to get a shit load of drones have him do everything for me?
Yeah, that's a good idea. What are we doing in here collection?
Yep, i'm gonna sell
I want to make okay before I do this
Yeah, all right. Hold on
They eat vegetables. They don't like that food. I want to make some I want to make some crystal
Wind crystal wind I think that'd be kind of cool
I'm making crystal winds
Yeah, we're going for it crystal winds
I'm doing it
Save it for the mosaics line. Oh
Do whatever you want. Yeah
Good
I could but I feel like i'm right in the next area anyways
They make a lot of money. All right
it's time
Plant the apiaries into the that jungle area. Let's go
Go get the mosaic slime. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let me plant these first
How fast can I do that? Yeah
And pretty fast I don't want these in my inventories i'm just gonna feed them
The atmosphere is beautiful in this game. It is really nice. It's very nice
They've not usually it's a sharp looking game
Okay, here we go
advanced apiary go
advanced apiary
advanced apiary go and
Okay, let's put the other things here too. Why not?
Uh novice pump go novice pump go for it
Novice pump go for it
Go for it
Okay, i'm ready. I'll come back here in 15 minutes
Next step make sure I have water and i'm gonna go and i'm gonna collect one of those mosaic slimes
And we're gonna make a mosaic wind slime
I can open this now
Oh, that's royal jelly
Cool. I got all right nice
Well, I have one now
Do mosaic crystal?
Yeah, i'm gonna do mosaic crystal and then mosaic
Wind it'd be fun. Oh, what's that? What you say?
Another email from casey
These guys are just going wild
Almost all as it okay. I don't care anymore
I don't even care anymore
I really don't I don't need quantum anymore
I'm just gonna store like one quantum plort and then these guys can just go free they get out too easily
Save one quantum plort in the event that I want to make a quantum
Of lemons, I need more pinks eventually
Get it
email
games
Email that's the homestar runner webpage
Homepage somebody said it. Wow, i'm surprised you got that a lot of you are getting that. Wow, that's interesting another tour
Hey b
There's another tour coming up and I have a feeling that this will be the one
Here I am packing my bags and thinking to you
Maybe this is how it felt when you were leaving for your big adventure lots of excitement
I keep thinking that maybe i'll catch you somewhere out there in the crowd
Whatever happens. I promise i'll sing a song for you. All right casey. Thank you
Wait, what he just took a moment to reflect
He thought about hobson and thora and the adventures he'd had exploring the far far range
Most of all, she thought of casey and wondered where life would take her next like at the end
Am I getting like enrage timered?
I just hit the enrage timer in the game
what
I took too long
I took too long. Are you serious?
I'm like i'm gonna go get these slimes over here. I'm gonna go do this one. I'm gonna do that one
No, i'm done. I hit the games and rage timer
No, it's then. Yeah, it's it. No, that's fine
It takes like in 40 days or whatever
You do this
And the game kind of ends and you can keep playing. I yeah, that's definitely what it is
Hey chris lum
What a god of a game designer. I love this game. It was fantastic
Hey, hey game development studios
just
Give that person a hundred million fucking dollars for the next game do it
Again, I want investors on there
Whatever okay, whatever budget you were gonna put into the next call of duty give it to this guy
I'd give it a hundred million dollars
Don't limit creativity with contracts. Let them do what they want. Oh, they would be no strings attached
If I had a hundred if I had a billion dollars right now
I would be writing checks left and right like I don't even fucking care if you pay me back just make something cool
And then I would pace around my living room for four years until it came out
Isn't that what death stranding was I have no idea, I don't know cool. All right. Well
I'm just kind of in the middle of something
Wait, do the credits take more than 12 minutes because my apiaries are probably done be brave pile of shit
Oh cool. All right, let's sleep
Hello there. Thanks taking you to the old ranch
I've acted wait a minute. It's a little thank you
I've activated three secret vaults that I built years ago to stash a small fortune
You know me. I like a good adventure. I'm not telling you where the vaults are located
slime key
Single spare slime key just in case you can't seem to find the last one
Okay, what?
How many you'll never find it? No, probably not
all right, let me uh
Let me store this and then we'll keep we'll do the thing. I want to go um
I'm gonna go back to that crystal world. I have water the teleport to the crystal world and then i'm just going and with empty
The lead dev musician and artist of this game made spiral nights a free mmo on steam
It's very fun. It's the exact same atmosphere. Please try it
You usually get to the boss in two to three streams spin up there over time. Oh, well, okay, cool
Why have I heard that name before?
All right, we're going
Where's the teleporter to get here? I feel like this is ridiculous
Where's the port here?
I'm way too far away
I don't want to walk all the way over here. This is that's just a one way to I have to walk here
I have to build one. Oh shit. I'm definitely not doing that
That's not happening on this stream. I guarantee it. I'm telling you for real
Uh here listen
Uh, we're gonna get to this part here
I'm gonna clean up a little bit. I'm gonna make the slimes. I want to make I want to make a mosaic crystal
And I want to make a mosaic wind
And then i'm gonna make some money i'm gonna buy i'm gonna open this this game is
Uh, no, i'm not gonna make that joke because I love it. Just move to boston the beer here sucks
Well, sorry to hear that try the cider it's it's way better
That doesn't make me mad or anything though
I don't have some attachment to
boston beer
What'd that guy say what the fuck that dude just say you don't like boston beer
What kind of fucking beer you drink? Oh, I don't care. Yes
It's lime fossil three of them
Hope I have enough room
Carry what I want to carry
That suck
Yeah, and tom brady won the super bowl on another team. I know i've and gronkowski's on that team and shit
I know I get it. It's like
I don't care though
I mean, I cared I cared when
when tom brady left the patriots it was like
Oh tom is this new kid coming up this new kid coming i'll get a fucking cannon for now
What do you even need tom anymore?
No, what we're doing we're gonna build up our farm system. We're gonna do
Take a couple years sub 500. It's fine. It's okay
Our farm system is gonna come up
All about farm system the farm system our farm system
And I mean that person has not watched a single minor league game at all or a college game
Our minor league system is our farm our farm system is great. I love our farm
We got we got tomatoes
Uh chili peppers
Yeah, hopefully hopefully Pedro martinez can pee into the ground
He was the best
All right that way
gronk ball
Didn't gronk used to spike balls into the ground and they would explode or am I making him up and making him a superhero?
I don't why I have this memory of gronk spiking a ball in the end zone and it exploded
Did I said that that was a dream?
That must have been right after we won in two one eight fifteen
I gotta go this way all the way around
Gronk in the rumble. No, i'm not gonna put gronkowski in the germ of rumble. Why?
That was mr. Superbowl
From blitz the league two not even a real person not even a real game
That's that's what it was. Okay. Well, you can tell how much I pay attention to football
I played that I streamed that and that was one of the things you could do
right
We're not even talking about that gronk. We're talking about the one from spore
You are
Did I go off on a football thing for no reason you guys talking about gronk from spore?
there
Tom brady
You know like here's the thing. I'm like tom brady. Wow, the new england patriots. He won so many times
What a legacy tom brady the best football team ever dynasty, right?
But part of me kind of wanted him to throw like 40 interceptions in that game
You know
He didn't like part of me wanted every single pet one of his passes to get intercepted and break every single wet record
a hundred times
It's the most unbelievable thing we've ever seen at the super bowl every single pass attempt by tom brady has been intercepted and run
Back for a touchdown
This has never happened before ever in the history of all sports. I'd be like, oh, that's fucking kind of funny
The other team is up by I don't even know what the other team it was there's the buccaneers and somebody else the
Kings, I don't know why the kings the kings
The chiefs, okay. Why did I say kings or whatever?
Okay, anyways, they would be up by like 200 points
And they would do the thing right before they go to commercial break with tom brady
Screams fuck as loud as he can and it's very clearly. That's what he did
It's a kind of a close-up. He's sitting on the bench. He spits he spits twice
Dumps water all over his head and he goes
Fuck i've seen that so many times
He's like after like the 25th interception in a row. What would he what would he do?
Okay, I need crystal slimes. I have water. I'm gonna get back that way water the plants
That's not doing anything
It needs special water
Need holy water. Okay, that's bullshit
It's new
Oh, no, I had beats already
What the fuck is going on in here?
What do you mean what's going on here drop kick a rotisserie chicken across
Uh, no, no one does the drop kick like doug flutie
When the only guys in football will do that
He drop kicked the ball
into the end zone
Past the uprights. No one's ever done that before doug flutie is the only one
Okay, here we go. So where are those mosaic ones?
They have a face. Where are they?
Underneath, okay
There we go. All right, so spray this guy with water
Uh, that's not that didn't do anything. You need holy water, dude. I where do you
Where am I supposed to get holy water? He needs to get a mosaic plort. Where do I get a mosaic plort?
Need mosaic slimes veggies
Yeah, and i've got to put a plort in there, but i haven't seen any mosaics slimes. Are they in this area?
Have I just missed them?
They show up at night or something. Thank god. I almost fell. All right. I need to get out of here. How do I get out of here?
Eat the gordo slime
Shit
I really thought I was gonna be able to get in here. Come on. Give me a crystal
Oh a mosaic. I mean damn it beat a big slime. I didn't come here with that. I I came here with the intention of
The intention was to fill up on oh man. That was painful
I have nothing to add. It's when I have had my message highlighted. Well, that's all right, man
It's nighttime. I don't see anything. It's nighttime though fill up that first fountain with rock plorts
Hmm
Read this
I hope something gets whatever that's a really mean thing to say
Really mean thing to say to somebody eat that I what does this mean? What's my favorite color? Uh blue?
Or green or teal?
My favorite color is the green stripe of the aqua fresh toothpaste
Not a lie. I truly that's what I truly want
God damn it
No, I
I don't this is not working. That's not the first fountain. This whole place is coming down
You have to have to do the first one first
Where's the first fountain?
I don't I don't remember even passing one. Is it on here?
Same as the door puzzle. You have to shoot plorts into the mouse. Okay, he's ignoring the chat. No, no
So I have to do arrow earlier in the level. Okay
Well, i'm probably getting close to calling it
I'm getting close to calling it
I'll do this part here and then we'll probably call the stream
I've had a lot of fun. I've had a lot of fun with you today
Get out of here rock plorts in the fountain
We'll go slime lamp. What's the verdict on next slime rancher stream?
I don't think so. I think that's it the stream content of slime rancher
probably
probably going to
Oh, no, if i'm gonna play I will probably just grind and play on my own if I feel like it
Just have my mouth open
Maybe after all this time. He hates it. No, I just
I I think i'm pretty much almost at the end game
I'm going farther away
Wait, I want rocks
Can you guys give me rocks? No
You have a plort too
You're not even that close to the end game. Well, well
Maybe one day i'll get there
Uh, so what you can expect in the next
three or four days
I'm going to try to get I haven't done it yet
I have to sign up and do some stuff with the gta rp server
So i'm gonna like go through that process over the next few days
And see what happens
I am not guaranteeing that i'm gonna be playing gta rp. I don't know. I think there's like a system where you have to get
Uh broad you have to get like approved and white listed and everything I think or something or other I don't really know
Uh gta rp. Yeah, we'll see. I once I if I get in maybe we'll do a few streams of
You just fucking around an rp. That's on tap potentially besides that
There are a lot of random games that I still have to play. I still want to play
I still have a thousand year door by the way
Maybe if gta rp doesn't work out next week start thousand year door, maybe if gta rp doesn't work out in the next week
I'll play
I don't know figure it out. I got a handful of games that I have installed that I want to do
All right. I am very lost this way. There's one at the beginning of the level. I'm curious about this
Where is the one at the beginning of the level?
Rock fountain is this guy too?
Rock fountain
You gotta say a rock. Oh
I found him. I need more rocks
Oh crap. I need oh, I need rocks. Damn it. I need food to feed. I need a okay. Where's rocks?
It was a crystal rock jumping around here. I said i'm from where I am
It's just wrong. I jumped around here down here around here, huh? Here, huh here
What the fuck was that?
No, I need to come here you eat two more. Oh you
You fuck auctioneer
Okay, these two let's see what this does. I'm very curious about this
And wait, I hear water
I hear water. Where is it? I hear water. It's down. Whoa. What does this mean?
Ancient water
Oh dumbass
Whoa, wait, that's a secret cat. That's a secret cat. That's a secret cat. How do I feed him? He eats meat
I need food. Oh my god. That's a I don't know what that is
I don't have any food down here. I need food food food food food food food food food food food
food food
I got oh I got mosaic
Holy shit. I got mosaic slime. Who cares about anything else? Whatever. I missed out
He's gone
All right. Now I can do the thing I want to do
What's that?
Ooh, give me this rock floor. Give me that don't nobody touch that get away from me. Oh, fuck you
Yep
Everyone's in the way
Good eat each other
All right. I got what I wanted
Wait, I gotta i'm gonna get food
Where's the uh, there was some
Chickens down here. Where are they?
Chickens chickens chickens chickens. There you are
If another one of those comes out, I want to see what happens
Okay, get the water
And run for it. Nope
There's another one. Okay feed
Holy shit, he just exploded. Come here. Come here back here
More money. No, no, no, no, no, no back back. Come back here. Come back here
Oh
Well, okay
I did get mosaic. That's pretty probably pretty rare
I didn't I didn't even know what that thing did
I've never fed that before
I fed him once and he exploded
That's really cool though. I like that
All right. I want to go come I want to do mosaic stuff
Uh time for me to get out of here
Let's use
Let's just run
I want to do mosaic crystal
What do mosaics eat? He sounds like he wants to do another stream of this
Um, ah, you know, there's probably enough there to do it but
You know, i'm
If I don't play another if I don't play a game for a week, you'll never see it again
All right
Just the way it is. That's the way it's always been
So if I get into gta rp
next week
I'm I just i'm not going to play this
And then that'll be one week
And then it just it's gone in my mind completely
What about yakuza? Oh, yeah, I do have to play yakuza because they won the in the rumble
That's true. All right teleport back. Let's check out these slimes and then they we're gonna call it there
You said it was gonna you said it was gonna happen in like june or july. I did
That's so long. That is so long from now. That's not even funny
All right. Here we go
mosaic slime
I'm gonna put you in here
What do you like veggies? Ooh, they're so pretty
Okay, let's feed a veggie and let's start the process here. I'm curious
What's your favorite veggie though? It's important
Silver parsnip. Well, I don't have any of those
Okay, let's do slime wind
Well, it doesn't matter what his favorite food is because I he's gonna be combined with um
Why are they angry?
Oh fuck. There's no food left
Uh
The fuck just happened. Holy shit, what happened to that guy?
No, no, come here my babies my babies my babies my babies my babies my babies
It's okay. It's okay. I got them
Two are dead
Where are my bees? What the fuck are the bees doing? What are you doing?
Get up
I'm mad about that. Absolutely
What the hell?
We'll have a oh, yeah. Oh, no, you just sprayed me with water
Oh get out of here
Why?
What do you get 50 community subs like two hours ago? What the fuck? I missed that
Well, that's an insane amount of money. Holy shit
Vin smoke if you're still here, that's 50 community subs. Oh, that's a ton of people
All right. I'm going for it
Here we go mosaic slime going in
Let's make some slimes
You guys all right?
And do it
Wow, really cool. Really really cool. Really cool. Really cool
Really cool actually
very cool
Give those to me
Here it comes
We're gonna turn them all
We exploded
Who's fucking raining hell down here? What's going on?
What are you doing over here?
How did you get all the way over here?
They attract other slimes
Sparkles make fire. Does that hurt them?
It really are so pretty
Solar roof solar roof solar roof
Whoa
That looks really cool. All right, I gotta sell
Why are they so angry?
Why are they so angry? What's going on? Why so angry?
Get over here you fucking little weirdo you weirdos. What's going on? Why are you so hungry?
Why are they so hungry any fruit?
Oh fuck. I don't have any fruit
Uh, it's fruit this way
This is my last fucking failed experiment
I gotta go hurry
Hurry hurry hurry
I come back to the planet every once in a while to get the groceries and I leave
ow
Whatever. I i'll see i'm done
That's game over. I'm just gonna sell some of these because i'm gonna see how cool it looks
It's over for the fire guys. I'm sorry. I they're so cute, but I well, no, he's okay
He's okay. He's okay. He's okay
Pick him up
Pick him up. Let him in. Oh my god. He's okay
Get inside of here
Why does this have to be so difficult?
It just is like I why is this so hard to make them stay in here?
You guys settling down
This thing is very intimidating
Wow, they're like prismatic
Cool
All right. What do they sell for? Let's get some money
Yeah, just for fun just for fun
Let's do let's make like mosaic cat
Why not? I'm done
This game is really fun. Well, i'm going to make mosaic cat for fun
Or mosaic rock
a guitar farm
Uh, it's I think that's too involved. I'm stream's gonna be over here in a minute
Okay, let's make a mosaic cat
Cool
Thanks for the kiss
cool
All right. Now these are mine sell
It's just kind of hell of that looks really cool. They'll go sparkles
Very sparkly
I love it. Very very cool. Let's sell these and then i'm going to
I'm gonna call it here
70 80 bucks each nice
Free the whole ranch. Uh, no. No, I because if I play off stream for any reason
I don't want to destroy the save file. I mean obviously put
Like what like 17 18 hours into the game so far. I don't think I want to just delete it
That was really cool. Very very good
This game i'm gonna give a rating. Here you go. Everyone wants me to rate games. Sure
This game is a
Hmm that's way higher than a seven
um
Much higher than 7.5. I don't think this I don't know. I'm not sure this is quite
I'm not sure this is quite 9.0 territory
might be
Hmm
It might be
8.7
This is an 8.7
Very very very very it's very very good
I would say this is probably one of the best games that came out in 2015
elaborate on that
How much more do you want me to elaborate that's not when it came out
B plus best game of 2015
What else came out in 2015 that you liked?
This is an 8.7. What have you rated 10 out of 10? Just curious
And then
Bloodborne's like a 9.7 for me 9.8
I mean, no 9. Yeah 9.7 because the points where he's taken off for that stupid ass swamp level
Undertale is 2015
Sounds like a pretty good year
I thought it was your favorite game. How is it not a 10?
well because
10 just seems too easy to give something
Nothing is perfect
I have not come across a game that I thought was
Perfect
That has not happened yet
Well, hold on. Hold on
Team fortress 2 might
Might be close to perfect
Well, wait, hold on tf2
tf2 like circa
2014 like 2013
tf2 2013
It could be close to a perfect video game
If I would have to give tf2 a 9.9. I don't I mean
that seems so stupid to say that but it's
Probably a 9.9
And i'm trying to think of the reasons of why
and I think
for the most part
It was based around
Oh
Like some of the little things that irritated you about tf2. He gave spore an 8.7. Did no I didn't
Spore's an 8.5
Sorry underneath this
You think sacrificing tf2 for alex was a fair trade-off. I don't think they sacrificed tf2 for alex
They stopped really caring about tf2 more way before alex was a thing
Spore is like a 7
No, I didn't give spore a 3.5. I gave the civilization phase a 3.5
I gave the creature creator a 9
I gave the space like a 8
Or like a 7 and then I gave the tribal stage like a 7 spores a 9.8. Eh, I don't know about that
Space is an 8. No space is like a 4
That adds up to more than 10. Well, no, I'm rating the different portions of the game as 0 out of 10
I do that shit
Don't that's how we do this on this stream
Remember resident evil 7
The first I based it on time and and portions of games
different areas different acts
Well, what what act are we in and how shitty was this? Resident evil 7's first act
Was a 9.4 out of 10
resident evil's
second act was like a
Seven and resident evil's third act was like a two
Resident evil seven's third act is a literal fucking almost one out of ten. The first act is a fucking 9.4 9.5
So, I mean overall you think about okay, how how much and how are you weighting the third act?
What what what's the weight of the third act? What percentages is that is that weight?
The guy ended up giving resident evil 7 like a
I mean eight two or something
How good is the forest versus indigo quarry versus desert versus ancient ruins? Okay now here you here's the problem
Ancient ruins you heard me flip out a little bit. I thought that was a fucking four out of ten
I don't like that place
These are the first these first two areas
9.7
8.6
then that third area with the um
With the caves and the crystals in the cave system. That's like an that's like a
Look at 8.4. So I wait
That ancient ruins part like that's like that's like 10 weight. That's not like a full like 20 30 weight. Absolutely not
I could overlook it. It's all right. I I just I I wasn't a big fan of the ancient ruins place
I like the place after that the crystal place the part where you're on the boat in resident evil seven
I thought was just stupid
And I waited it kind of high because it was to kind of ruin the game for me. What would you give stardew?
It's at least a nine
stardew is probably like a
uh
Stardew's uh, hey
That's pretty that's close
Stardew's really close to being perfect as well. It is
Is it weird of me to say? Oh, no, that's so unfair
That's very close. It's probably like a nine eight
Star oh man stardew valley might be perfect
What was wrong with stardew valley that I didn't like
I don't know if I can think of anything that might be a perfect video game
But a stardew valley better than bloodborne
oh
Shit bloodborne is at 30 fps ps4 exclusive
has some technical problems
ran like shit in some areas and
There's one area of there's one or two areas in bloodborne that I wasn't a huge fan of
Stardew valley is oh, oh man
I don't know star. I started valley might be a 10
It could be
I don't know if i'm willing to give it that score though
Combat's not good in stardew. Yeah, but it's like that's like extra stuff
Yeah
There's such different games. I know they are start of no stardew valley is a 9.8
It's a 9 8
tf 2 is a 9.9 stardew valley is a 9.8 bloodborne is a 9.7
There you go
On diablo 2 9.9. That's not a game's like at its very core. That game is like a 7.4
but
The fun factor of diablo 2
Is like a 50 the fun factor of diablo 2
Way higher than a 7.4 is at least it's a 10
One of the most fun I've ever had playing a video game was diablo 2
What hades?
hades is a
Hades is like a 9.2. That's a 9.2. I don't know if I'd call it perfect
It's like probably 9.2 9.3
That's too high. I don't think it is. No, I don't think it is 9.2 is pretty high, but it is
You gave saw an 8.9. No, I I gave
Uh outer wilds at 8.9
And half of you wanted to kill me
You guys want me to give you my scores for video games, but if I don't do a high enough score for your favorite video game
I you want me to like drink poison
This dude's an 8.8. Eugene 8.7. Andy. I don't give everything an 8.7 or an 8.8
I just told you three games right there that were a 9 9 9 8 and 9 7
7.8. Andy. I what what other games have I given a 7.8?
sniper elite 3
Um, but maybe like a 5.5
Didn't I play that game for like two or three hours and I just said this game's not fun. I stopped
What? Rate the world of warcraft expansions
wrath of the lich king is is okay. Well, this is just in the universe of world of warcraft. This is not
In like the actual universe of all video games that I've ever played. This is just
Bracket put in brackets world of warcraft corralled in one spot wrath of the lich king is a 10
burning crusade is a 9.7
legion is a 9.5
And then everything else is a zero. That's it. It wasn't saying you loved the latest expansion
Well, actually, hold on. Hold on
Miss I miss a pandaria. Okay. Hold on miss a pandaria was like a six
Everything else is zero
I didn't I I played miss pandaria was okay
I'm just like still going here. I'm not even like playing the game. Just talking
Let's get to the end here. We can still talk but let's do the credits
You're just meandering around the ranch. I know
Uh, but yeah, we can keep talking while we see the credits
Thanks for the subs. Thanks for watching. Sorry. I missed a bunch of them
It was a huge 50 community sub drop that I just was I must have been screaming at the tv
What about jedi academy? Um comedy factor was like a 10
Video game factor was like a 7.4
Maybe even lower like a 6.8. What would you rate fistful of frags?
A solid 8.0 and I know that's a joke of a score, but it just is that's that's a fact
Now that's an 8.5. It is
I had so much fun playing that game
You know how desperately I wanted someone to make a fistful of frags into a full non-mod video game
Where it was just it was just a full triple a video game of that caliber
Uh too bad. I would love it red dead redemption 2. No, but red red red dead redemption 2 was not
an fps
Multiplayer shooter it would have been really good. I know rate day's gone and jump king day's gone is a four
jump king is a
7.9. What would you rate the last whopper? Uh, probably a five or six
Portal two stop ignoring me
Portal two when it came out I think was like a nine four
But portal two kind of five ten years later. I kind of almost looked back and it may have been too high
Maybe like if I were to go back and think about it without the like holy shit
This is the greatest thing i've ever played it my entire life. I feel like i've portals. Yeah, maybe like
Um
I haven't played it in a long time. I would probably say probably like a nine two nine three
I think it should be docked like point one or point two points
I had just I had just I was so excited for it that I was just clouded my face clouded my face
I gave it like a nine point five. It's probably like a nine points free. What about tetris?
I know the reason why I can't rate the portal games like tens like everybody else does because those games made me sick
I powered through playing portal one and portal two and it's like this is the this is so much
This is the funniest thing i've ever done. I love this game. It's so good
I had to lie down every couple of hours. I couldn't play that game for more than an hour or two
I had to go actually physically lie down or throw up at my desk
So I can't give it a ten. It made me almost throw up five times
So it's a nine point two
How do you play vr? Well vr is a lot different. You have a full
You have a full essentially a hundred eighty three sixty degrees of vision
it's the
Looking through the portals and moving around through the portals and jumping through them and doing the speed thing where you run
And then through another one
The world kind of turns sometimes in portal is here's the worst part about it
Sometimes in portal when you go through a portal
And your camera flips upside down right side up because you went through backwards or something and it's like you flip forward
That would kill me every time motion sick ridiculously easy
I wouldn't say ridiculously easy, but like enough where I it can be an issue
Sorry, what about noita?
Noita was not really my kind of game
I would say terraria was not my kind of game either and I put them in the same category
I love what terraria does and I like that terraria is cool and I think it's a really fun experience
But I don't know if I would rate terraria that high
It would probably be pretty low for me
They're not the same. Well, they're they're like this they're played very similarly. They're not the same exact game
I think they're really cool. They're just kind of not the type of game that I like to play
What about super mario bros 3?
Wait, there's a game ratings wiki page of mine
What?
No, there's not hold on a second
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Why is among us up here as a 10?
That's somebody edited somebody's doing bullshit editing here
That shouldn't be up there. What why is a whopper on here? A whopper is not a game
What an art of wilds is is not even right either. Wait, didn't I i've read
I retroactively went back and gave art of wilds a 9.1 because I cracked under the pressure andy right it was it was an 8.9
Binding of isaac binding of isaac is is a 9 binding by isaac is a 9.0. Get that off among us a fucking 10
No
Even if I played among us, I probably wouldn't think it was that good of a game even if I played it
Not a 10
If I even if I if I was a big fan of among us, i'm not I wouldn't give it a 10. It would be
I don't know
I don't know. I haven't played it so I can't give you a rating
Refresh I just where is it?
Somebody linked to me again. I don't know. I can't get back to it
Stop ignoring hollow night. Um hollow night's probably like a
I can't give it a full. I didn't finish it
I feel like I would need to that's the kind of game that you need to finish
Before you give it a real rating
Binding of isaac 9.0 bugsnack 7.95. Why 9.5?
Germa won't write black and white 2 feels bad man. Hi germa lots of love from the navy. Well, thanks
black and white 2 um
Which one was better black and white 1 was better than black and white 2, wasn't it? I forget flip it around maybe
Black and white 2 was an 83
Black and white 1 was like an 86 flip it somewhere around if I forget which one was better
Asthma phobia 7 7.1. No, it's 7.0 dark souls 3
Dead rising. Yeah, okay dead risings dead risings probably like us
uh
Dead risings probably an 82
No, it's not it's higher than that. It's an 86 85 dead rising is an 85 dead rising 2 is an 85
I don't know. I don't rate video games
I just play them and think they're fun sometimes or I think they suck or I don't like them. I don't know
I can't rate video games
Sekiro, oh i'm gonna piss a lot of people off with Sekiro
Sekiro is the worst souls kind of like video game. It's the worst one
I think I gave it like a nine. I was lying
I gave it a nine. I was a liar
I was like, oh, you know, it's like a 9.0. I think after I finished it. I said that
I think that might be the worst one
No, dark souls 2 is way worse. Never mind. Okay. Well, I need to how many games have they made?
From software hold on
Okay. Yeah dark dark souls 2 is worse than uh, okay. Here we go. Dark souls 2 is worse than Sekiro
Dark souls 2 is like a 6.5
Sekiro is like a 7.6
dark souls
three
Is like an s
like an eight point
No, it's not. It's a eight point. It's an 8.1
Dark souls 1 is an 8.5
No, it's not. It's higher than that 8.8
Bloodborne is a 9.7. I don't do I don't even remember what they were
I think I think I honestly I think I just said random numbers there
No, let me get this right all the dark souls games besides dark souls 2 are eights
I think yes, that's accurate. I like I got all jumbled up here
Dark souls 2 is a 6.5. Sekiro is a 7.9
Dark souls 3 8.5 dark souls 1 8.9 darks, uh
Bloodborne 9.7 done
Did I say was that what I said twilight princess? I didn't finish it
These are getting updated
What about left for dead 2 who cares?
You don't need my opinion on this
You've already played like a thousand hours of that game. You want me to tell you what I think about left for dead 2
You we both have probably one to two thousand hours and left for dead and left for dead 2
I don't think it really matters what I think at this point
It's great. It was very very good
TV robo 9.9
9.0 day's gone as a four on here. Oh shit. It's almost six hours. You're right
He's obsessed
No more heroes one and two
No more heroes of the games are kind of bad, but in a really really charming good way
I think both no more heroes games are like seven one and like seven four
That's not really bad
Refresh the page
Yeah, can I I don't think spores in eight five
Oh, but what but it came out it was revolutionary left for dead 2 is who cares?
That's I mean, but really though, it's like so everybody played that game with shit load does it matter
All right. I'm only gonna write three more games watch dogs legion
Watch dogs legion realistically was a
4.6
that game
Sucks and i'm not afraid to say it
Was it better than day's gone?
You know, it might actually be worse than day's gone. What is day's gone of four if that's a caliber for four
Watch dogs legion is a 3.6
That's only because your computer sucks
What that's my that was my experience with watch dogs legions. It's a it's got a 3.6
I was flipper. I was flippers in 8.4
If i'm gonna be realistic about it one more
Skyrim I can't write skyrim
I played
Two or three hours of skyrim
Modded the hell out of it made a bunch of monsters
Never played it again
And then watched it re-release
15 fucking times
I can't give you a rating. That's not rateable for me
hotline miami
Hotline miami 1 is an eight point
Nine hotline miami 2 is a seven
rhythm heaven
eight eight point five
bta 5
9.5. No, it's not it's a nine point. Yeah, it is 9.5
Gotcha for us. The game is a probably like a five point six
But I loved it so much that it raises it up in brackets
It's a seven point six
For some it's a five point six video game, but in brackets, it's a seven point six
Outer wilds eight point nine and then in brackets nine point one
Refresh the page it got to the page is deleted
There's nothing in here. You guys somebody deleted it all
What the fuck
It's it's gone
All right. I'll see you guys later. Goodbye. Good night. I gotta go
The next time you see me will be
Uh, I will be back on monday
Either monday. Yeah monday i'll be back on monday
What time on monday though?
monday might be a later stream
We'll see maybe I gotta figure this out either monday or oh
I
hmm
I think I have an appointment on monday
We'll see check the sus it's either monday or tuesday
I'll see if I can stream on monday late if not then tuesday afternoon
great sorcery nine
sorcery one 9.0 sorcery two
9.8
sorcery three
7.5 sorcery four
6.8
Combine them all together sorcery two makes up most of the game
As a whole remember we weight them differently here. We weight them differently
I put
Like 75 weight into sorcery two
The rest of them just trickling
What do you mean? Wait w e i g h t
Go to bed jeremy. I mean, it's not that late
Right among us. I can't rate it n slash a not applicable. I have not played it
jewel wizardry, I mean
Two
That's a deck game is a two not even it's a 1.4
super frog super frog is a
a one but in brackets
9.5
Undertale. Oh boy
Oh boy, i'm about to rate
Undertale
This is where
This is where i'm good. Oh, this is best. It's gonna this is a monk a s scenario. I think
Undertale
Oh
If I gave outer wilds an 8.9 and I don't give undertale a 9.0
Undertale
Is definitely not
Um
This is a career end. This is a career ending statement possibly
It's it's a nine. It's at least a nine, but I don't know if it's I don't know if it's the nine that you think it is
zero point nine
Uh, it's undertale for me was a nine point nine point two
six
five
Not quite a nine point three, but it's almost there
And then in brackets for undertale
Point five one
Nine point two six five is locked in what about the brackets? You need the brackets are very important
And the mud the point five one gets added to the score. No, no, don't put the brackets there
Put no, no, no. Okay. What's the dude somebody do the math? What's the math? So it was nine point
Okay, you need to calculate it nine point
nine point six nine point two six five
plus
point five one
so in brackets
Undertale is a nine point. That's not accurate
No, no in bra and hold on
It would be point
All right in brackets. It's a nine point
three
Two zero nine point three two zero
Nine point three two zero in the brackets. I have to go. All right, well we're going brackets if we're multiplying
No brackets are four that could be the score two
On a given day. However, I might feel like giving it that one
I have to give two scores sometimes because on a given moment it could range between those two
It could be one of the it could be one of the other
All right. Good night. Goodbye. I'll see you later. I'll see you on monday or tuesday. Have a great weekend everybody. Take care of yourselves
Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for watching as always
See you soon
Good night. Goodbye
Rate your channel
Nine point eight five