Roll up your sleeves. Everybody roll your sleeves up. Oh, hold on. I'm gonna roll my sleeves up cuz you know why we're rolling the sleeves up. We're on one of the coolest maps in the game. We're on the main thunder. The striking thunder. The big thunder. Thunder Mountain baby. Crashed it.
Why is it a fucking Egypt? What? No, no, no, no. I like Egypt. Please, please, please, please. No, no, no. Please, please, please, please, please, please, please. Is it supposed to be Thunder Mountain? Please, please, please, please. The title of this video was Bring on the Thunder and we're not even on Thunder Mountain. Uh, how about Double Flo Geistinator Pyros? That sounds dumb enough to work. Okay. Double Flo Geistinator Flo Geistinator Flo Geistinator. Are you ready? Oh, everybody. Welcome to Thunder Mountain. Tricked you. It's Egypt and we're both flog pyros.
Did I hit that? I hit that guy again. Here we go, baby. Turn it up. Turn on those cricks. That's two. That's three. I can't go over there anymore. That's a sentry. Yeah, I can't really go over there. Did you die for the sentry? What killed you? I'm not dead. I'm at the secret entrance. Secret entrance. Do they have two sentries? I can't even tell. I can't even tell either because I'm not really. That guy. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy. You ready? You ready? Go, go, go, go, go. Let's go, go, go, go, go.
Hold the button down. That's the most important thing. That's kind of obstructing my view. Stop doing that. No. Sentry is going to kill us. You're not going to make it. Where are you going? I'm going. Come with me. No, you're just going to let me die in the corner. Well, there's a sentry over here. Nobody here. This isn't the tunnel that I was talking about. It's all right. We can just go to spawn. Okay, let's do that. Let me just hide right here. Don't make any noise. Oh, anyone who's down here. I got you just stepped on a stick and it made some noise.
You're on a stick. Yeah, it was a very large branch and it went. Why are we doing this? Why is nobody coming over here? Because they have a teleporter. They do? Oh, well, let's get rid of that. Let's go take care of that. What the hell is this? It's just a hat.
All right, now we hide, hide, hide, hide, hide. I help help you. We're not supposed to be here. We're supposed to be here. Are we really supposed to be here? We're supposed to be here. Is this really what we're doing? Are we this much of like douchebags?
Douchebags?
No, we're not doing this. I don't want to do this. This is horrible. I'm glad I died.
Worst Simpsons joke ever. Worst joke ever. Who's that? You get 20 German bucks if you can say who that is. Worst episode ever.
Al Gore. Got it. Al Gore, ladies and gentlemen. Star wins the 20 German bucks. What are you going to buy? There was no contest. Nobody else is even in this call. Okay, time to turn it on. I'm going out left. I'm turning it out left. You're going to bring the thunder?
Yeah, I'm bringing the thunder to Dubspawn. Yeah, I'll show you how you bring the thunder to the Dustbowl. You take a couple of pot shots right there. Watch it. I don't know where that guy went. That guy disappeared. Oh, there's a mini up. Oh, that's a spy.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he? Give me some coordinates. Tunnel left side. Bravo Bango. Bravo Bango, got him. He got the heavy. Bravo Bango. Bravo Bango. Thanks for the wrong coordinates. This is Bronco Bongo, you idiot.
You should have told me the right coordinates. See? And instead I ended up going to Bingo Bingo and I ended up getting myself killed.
Oh, headshot. Watch out for this guy. Watch out for this typer. What do we got anymore? We got any more? We got any more peeps? We got any more creeps? We got any more sweeps and creeps and beeps?
Eat a whole box of creeps in one sitting? Peeps? Dude, one time I ate a host. Just tell me your poop scenario.
Did I ever tell you the story I ate the whole sleeve of Oreo cookies and I threw up in my mother's bed? No, that sounds like a good story. Like, why wouldn't you tell this? It was actually pretty recently.
Dude, I threw up. This is like, what the fuck was that? Wait, wait, you mean recently. You recently threw up in your mother's bed. And you couldn't prevent this from happening. You couldn't like lean to the side. This isn't like a mother's floor carpet throw up story.
You demolished her bed. Did you have to get a new mattress? Because that shit goes right through. I don't think so. So every night she goes to bed, you just think about what's going on here. Maybe it's kind of fucked up.
Alright, where coordinates Brinkobongo? Can we hear the story? No, I'm too busy. Hold on, I don't need a second, man. I'm trying to play a good game of Dubspole over here. We actually are going to steam room now. Okay. Is that confirmation? This is confirmation.
Go ahead and call up the hotline. Okay, hotline is Brinkobongo. Hello? Hello? This is the Team Fortress 2 Stompfest hotline. Who's speaking, please? Star underscore. Okay, yeah, what is your inquiry? I want a pub stomp Dubspole.
Okay, do you have German 985 pocket medicking you right now? It's this guy named Stadium seating, but I guess it could be German. Okay, then that has been confirmed that you will do a steam roll, my friend. Thank you for calling Team Fortress 2 Stompfest hotline.
Okay, can we get the Uber? Can we speed it up the process here? They hung up on you. You're too abrasive. No, they have to apologize first. That's like what they do. Don't get blown up by this guy either. I'm not going to. You're going to. I did. You are going to. You're such an idiot. You didn't protect me.
Ring ring ring. Oh, they're out to lunch.
Oh, you hear all those things? No. Did you hear all those things? Oh, quit. I did not aim that. I'm not gonna help this out. Angie. I don't care as long as we get the Uber. We'll have it. Bye bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Scout. You ready for the? Yeah, I'm very ready. Okay, let's get ready. Yeah, 98.
99. Is it 100? Oh my God. Holy shit, dude. There is like five centuries back here. You've got to be kidding me. I'm going to need stickies. That's my evaluation. Don't get yourself killed. I'm going to have one Uber for you. You have to really make it count. Make sure we get this because I
I know Jerma in times of crisis. He throws times of crisis. Okay, go, go, go, go. Times of crisis. Got those stickies. Come on. Come on. We can't have the team fortress to stomp vest hotline. Lie to us. It's still in the century. Oh, come on. Can we at least get on that point? I died like a crit. Oh my God. No, they have like the perfect team.
No, they just have like six engineers. That's what I mean. They have that many NG's. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We're just we're bomb rushing it right now. I think we have totally bomb rushing. Everyone just rush it. There's only two people on that point. There's still two centuries around the corner. What what a joke. TF2 hotline is now not in service anymore. I ripped the phone out of the wall.