How you guys doing? We're nice. Great night. See you tomorrow.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Alright, see you later.
Welcome to another stream, guys.
How you doing?
I did just brush my teeth.
They're nice and clean.
Can you hear it?
I'm running my tongue across the front of my teeth.
So tonight, we're gonna play Hotline Miami.
Because I know I'm kind of...
I'm kind of jebaiting everybody here.
Last night, I said tonight we're gonna play EDF.
But that was determined to be a lie.
Well, not a lie, but...
I wanted to play Me, Star, and Italics are gonna play it.
But we couldn't...
People had to get this stuff ready.
And we weren't all on the same page for today.
So tomorrow, we're gonna play it tomorrow.
So stream tonight, stream tomorrow.
So Star needed to set up some of his stuff.
He wasn't really ready to play it.
And we're gonna wait until tomorrow.
Because I obviously want to play with friends.
And the game is way more enjoyable that way.
So we're gonna play Hotline Miami tonight.
Somebody just wrote, this is gonna be very bad.
Why? Very bad?
Is that true? Yeah.
But why though?
Should I prepare myself for something that I'm not gonna have fun with?
Yes.
It's a very hard game.
Well, whatever. We'll be fine.
I'm not concerned about game difficulty.
You guys have seen me play plenty of games that require skill and focus.
And I just run them over with a lawnmower.
It might be jagged.
When the baseball comes shooting out of the lawnmower, it's gonna be torn up and all fucked up.
But at least I did it.
And no, somebody said, am I gonna do a face cam tonight?
Because I'm brushing my teeth.
No, I don't have any clothes on.
Everybody thinks this is a joke.
And thinks I'm making this up.
I don't have clothes on.
I have underwear and pants.
I mean, that's clothes. That's it.
No, I can't wear clothes.
I only wear clothes when I have to go out somewhere.
I don't have to leave the house.
It is an absolute nuisance for me to wear clothing.
Oh yeah, prove it. Sure. Let me turn it on.
No, I don't wear shirts.
I only wear shirts because I sweat through everything I put on.
So if I put on a t-shirt, oh yeah, I'm gonna do laundry.
Nice, fresh, clean laundry.
And I put on a shirt and in two hours, three hours, it'll be wet.
And it's not gross.
It's not gross or anything. I don't understand.
If I go out with that same shirt on, right?
If I put that same t-shirt on and go out of the house,
I will not sweat a single drop.
Not one drop will come out.
I'll be dry all day, all night.
I sit in a chair and just sweat comes off my body.
I don't understand why.
Does anybody have a logical medical explanation as to why that happens?
And I'm not like smelly or anything. I'm just wet.
It's like somebody threw water,
and a basin and like under my armpits.
It's just liquid.
But anyways, we're gonna play Hotline Miami tonight.
I've heard it's a very hard game from people in the chat room here.
It's a very hard game.
So everybody be careful with it.
It might be a little loud. I'm just making you aware of that.
Stalling. I'm not stalling.
I'm just talking.
It's been six minutes.
I'm at the title screen. I'm just gonna make sure it gets captured correctly.
Because if it doesn't, then I'm gonna be really, really, really, really, really, really angry.
There it is. Okay, Hotline Miami.
And it should pop up on the screen literally right now.
Hey, there it is.
So I have not played this game before.
I don't know how this works.
I know it's a top-down...
That almost looks to me like original GTA.
The same kind of top-down, right?
And the same animations when you punch people.
Did I tweet this? Okay, I did.
All right.
The music's incredible. I've heard it's really fun.
I'm playing keyboard and mouse. Please correct me if that's wrong.
Should I be playing with like an Xbox controller?
Okay.
So Hotline Miami. Here we go.
I'm here to tell you how to kill people.
This game is controlled with your WASD keys and mouse.
Press left mouse button to punch, aim for the face.
Once you've knocked someone out, you have to finish them.
To do this, you press space. You got it? Are you sure?
Left mouse button to punch, space to finish.
Do you understand me? Don't mess it up.
Okay, so I'm...
All right, I'm Pinocchio.
So...
All right, now you should try killing the next guy.
But use the bat in the red room over here, okay?
This game's too hard. I can already tell.
I can already tell this game's too hard.
When you press the left mouse button to swing it.
Okay, did that get through your head?
So right click and then left click.
All right, right click.
And then...
Oh man, this is fun, but it's gonna be very hard for me.
Well done, so let's get to the gun, shall we?
You go and get the shotgun in the blue room.
You do it the same way you picked up the bat.
Just press the right mouse button. Can you handle that?
Use the shift button to look for enemies out of view.
It's very useful for not getting yourself killed.
Press the scroll wheel to lock onto enemies.
Just make sure to place your crosshair over them first.
Right mouse to grab, shift to look.
Left mouse button to shoot, scroll wheel to lock on.
Okay, hold on, let me check that out.
So, shift lets you look.
Where that's lock on.
So, scroll wheel, lock on.
Okay, got it.
All right, that about sums up the basics.
However...
However, there's always more tricks to learn.
You can throw any weapon you pick up by pressing your right mouse button.
You can use doors to knock enemies over.
Guns are very loud and will alert your foes.
So, plan your moves and use melee weapons when you can.
God damn it.
You'll just get yourself killed.
Why did I do that?
Won't you?
Phone calls!
I don't know what that accent was.
And who do we have here?
We've got a horse man.
Oh, you don't know who you are.
Maybe we should leave it that way.
We've got a horse.
We've got Bro Jack Horseman, Chicken Little.
I know you.
Look at my face.
We've met before.
Haven't we?
I don't know you.
Why are you here?
You're no guest.
That's an O.W.O. face.
You're no guest of mine.
Do you really want me to reveal who you are?
Knowing oneself means acknowledging one's actions.
As of lately, you've done some terrible things.
If you don't remember me, I'll give you a clue.
Does April the 3rd mean anything to you?
I believe that was the day of our first encounter.
You look like you might be remembering something.
April 3rd, 1989, Miami, Florida.
Okay, this is just the intro to Earthbound.
Same music, too.
Am I gonna get attacked?
You have one new message.
Hi, this is Tim at the bakery.
The cookies that you ordered shall be delivered by now.
A list of ingredients are included.
Make sure that you read them carefully.
Click.
Okay.
Music needs to be louder.
Like, I can't.
I can't right now.
Just wait.
Just wait till I get through the first level.
Cookies.
That's my D.P.I.
It's not bad.
The target is a briefcase.
Discretion is of essence.
Leave target at point F32 inside the dumpster.
Failure is not an option.
It will be watching you.
All right.
It's gotta be louder.
I'm getting...
Why is everybody adding me?
Can I go on my balcony?
I don't even have a balcony?
Do I get to upgrade my house?
Is this a game where you make money and upgrade your house?
Can I have, like, cool stuff in the way and I turn it into a sim?
Okay, I'm just...
Get inside of Christopher Lloyd's time travel car.
The Metro.
Richard.
Unavailable.
Whoa.
Okay.
Looks like I'm Richard.
Do I have to talk to anybody or is this just time to play the game?
Oh.
Break his neck.
Win?
No, I lost.
I...
Okay.
You gotta be quick.
You gotta be very quick.
Yeah, there's a guy on the phone.
A guy walking around over here.
Ha ha!
Ah.
Thank God there's a checkpoint.
Okay.
Got it.
Is this a gun?
I don't think this is a gun.
What?
Whoops.
This is too stressful for me.
Is that a...
Whoa.
Okay, good.
Oh, man.
Oh, no.
Wait.
How do I get rid of the briefcase?
How do I throw the briefcase down?
I wanna drop briefcase.
What?
You fucking idiot.
Oh my God.
Just go.
Go.
Hurry up.
Break his neck.
All right.
Go to the car.
I did it.
Is there more?
I gotta leave it in the dumpster.
Who's there?
I can hear you.
I know you're there.
Stage clear.
Chapter clear.
That's true.
Wait.
Was I not supposed to kill that guy?
Was that the guy in the...
Did I do it?
Was I not supposed to do that?
Killing...
Bologna.
No, that's...
Sorry.
That's what I'm saying.
That's the Spanish way to say it.
Bologna.
Time bonus.
Flexibility.
Mobility.
Whatever.
I got a B.
Execution.
Exposure.
Two times combo.
Execution.
B.
I got a new mask.
Erasmus.
What do you mean mediocre?
Generic.
A B is not generic.
A B means you did a good job.
Generic B.
Give me a break.
Hi there, man.
Haven't seen you around.
Thought something might have happened to you.
You seem really down over losing your girlfriend.
Don't remember seeing you after that.
Maybe we should talk about something else.
So out for a midnight snack, huh?
Nah, don't worry about it.
It's on the house.
Good to see you.
Have a nice night.
I didn't do anything.
What is this guy eating?
Oh, is that sushi?
I love sushi.
Sushi?
What else do I got?
What?
Everyone's upset that I said sushi?
What's happening?
I said sushi because it looked like it was sushi.
And I love sushi.
And all of a sudden, I'm a bad guy?
You have one message.
Hello, it's Linda.
I need a babysitter.
Right away, I got a few kids that need to be disciplined here.
I'm at East 7th Street.
Make sure you have a long talk with them.
I really need someone to get through to these rascals.
And like last time, please be discreet.
Turn it up?
I have to quit the game to turn it up.
Just wait.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Guys, I was at a B, okay?
I'm at a B for music.
That's the kind of person that I am.
I'm only a B or...
That's as high as it goes.
Take music to an A plus?
No.
Music seems to be an A.
Just 97.
That's fine.
It's up.
It's up all the way.
This one's called No Talk.
Look, I'm getting the...
I can see the whole level now.
Start with intro?
No.
Don't be afraid of dying is what this thing says.
Richard.
An eye for secrets.
What does that mean?
All right, let's go.
Let's take a look.
Who's inside?
Long corridor.
Long corridor again.
That's it.
Nothing else.
Discipline the people in here.
All right.
We've got...
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Guy up here.
Leads to guy...
Nobody in living room?
Kitchen.
All right.
Kill guy in kitchen.
Shoot his head off and then take his gun, right?
That's...
I almost just passed out.
Psycho.
Okay, I got a gun.
Two rounds.
Two...
All right.
Guy with a gun and a guy sitting on the couch.
I can take...
Shoot guy, throw gun at guy.
All right.
I got it.
Who's in this room?
We got a guy on the couch, guy with a gun, and that's it.
Wait.
I need run.
I need bullets.
This one...
Is there anymore guns?
No gun.
Okay.
Six rounds.
Check this out.
Ready?
Bingo and then bango.
What just happened?
Oh, come on.
What?
What the fuck was that?
I missed him and he hit his head on the door.
I gotta wait till he turns.
No lock on.
Lock on is gonna hurt me.
Lock on is gonna be bad.
Unless I can plan what I wanna do.
This guy had a crazy gun too.
All right.
I'm good.
You shift to look further?
That's what I've been doing.
What are you talking about?
I've been doing that this whole time.
I've been using shift the entire time.
Quite the discreet operation.
What a 2010 streamer.
You can look further away.
What?
A minus.
See, I turned up the volume.
All right.
Now you're just being bastards.
Now we got Tony.
We got three masks now.
God, I love pizza.
You know what?
It's crazy.
I haven't had pizza in like three months.
Because I've been trying to stay away from bread.
Because my whole body is like all fucked up.
I'm not going into minute details.
I'm trying to stay away from gluten.
Because I feel like I'm developing a gluten intolerance.
And I've got a dark disappointment coming up.
I miss pizza.
Hey there.
Welcome.
Oh, you don't need to order.
Your pizza's already done.
Gluten-free pizza.
Yeah, but you have to like go specially get it.
You can't go to...
You can't go into like pizza hut or Domino's or...
And order like a gluten-free pizza.
Can you?
Don't get me wrong.
I would eat a whole entire pizza to myself right now.
But every time I've been eating bread.
I get like sick.
And it's...
I don't know.
And I've got a doctor's appointment coming up.
So you'd find out what the fuck's wrong with me.
Let's leave it at that for now.
Shall we?
Yeah, I agree.
Don't worry about paying.
It's on the house.
And then I don't know if it's something to do with like colitis.
Or I have no idea.
But it's really, really not cool.
You forget just how much shit has like bread or wheat or gluten in it.
When you try to avoid it.
It's wild.
So I got my pizza.
And a phone call.
I got one new message.
Just eat it.
And then I could, but it doesn't feel very good.
This is Thomas from the Methadone Clinic.
We've scheduled a short meeting for you tonight.
We're at North West 840...
184th Street, Apartment 105.
And don't worry.
We know discretion is of importance to our clients.
Click.
This game's pretty fun.
Why have I never played this game?
In like the seven years that it's been available to play.
It's called Overdose.
You can shoot through some walls.
Fists of Fury and Eye for Secrets.
I'm going to assume this means harder punches.
So guy sitting on the chair.
Guy at the front door.
We're going to go front door.
Punch.
Break guy's neck into the other room.
Avoid the piano.
We got guy with a gun.
Guy pissing.
Break his neck space.
I need that.
All right.
I got a gun now.
I don't think I want to use it though.
No, I don't.
We got a guy down at the piano.
I knocked him out.
Oh shit.
I don't have any more weapons.
What am I doing?
Okay.
We're good.
Oh fuck.
Oh no.
Oh.
No.
Give me this.
Is there somebody left?
Who's still alive?
I don't.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to walk in a room.
Okay.
That guy down there.
He's the only guy left.
All right.
I got it.
Let's get out of here.
Can I get this thing?
That's not real.
Crab?
What do you mean crab?
Crab.
Grab the crab.
Dead guy.
Give me a fucking A plus for that one.
Didn't even need to restart that one.
Boomer accidentally activates sticky keys.
What?
Combos.
I had a few combos there.
Flexibility.
Like I threw the thing at the guy and it bounced off the wall and I bounced back
and I hit him and I shot him.
New weapon unlocked and it's an A.
New mask.
Aubrey and Earl.
Okay.
New weapon.
Do I get to start with this or something?
Samurai sword.
This is fun.
I'm glad I played this.
Hey, dude.
Good to see you again.
Did you hear about the massacre the other night?
A bunch of rusties I heard.
No loss.
Did you ask me?
They say some maniac wearing a rubber mask did it.
Jesus.
Sounds like a scene straight from a slasher flick.
I have the perfect film for you.
The one on the desk.
Take it.
It's on the house.
Enjoy yourself, dude.
Why does this guy keep giving me free stuff?
I should play the second one too?
Well, one step at a time.
April 25th.
Hi, it's Kate from Hotline Miami's dating service.
We have set up a date for you this evening.
Should be waiting for you at Southwest 53rd Place.
As usual, make sure you wear something fancy.
Do I have to go to my wardrobe?
All I have is a Nintendo console with two games.
I don't have any clothes.
This is called decadence.
Alright, what did we unlock?
More guns.
Or where's Earl?
Survive two bullets.
That seems kind of crazy.
That seems like it's...
That makes it...
No, I don't want to be Earl yet.
Not until I need it.
Let's do more guns.
Alright.
Scope it out.
Front door.
Okay, we're going to do this in one shot.
You ready for me?
Front door.
Knock the guy out.
Grab the gun in the left room.
Head to the left.
Shoot all three people with gun.
Run out.
Throw gun at guy here.
Punch guy here.
Break that guy's neck.
Shoot that guy with gun that he drops.
Go!
Oh, that didn't work.
Alright, so...
I'm going to go this way.
Oh, hit me right in the head.
Whoa!
Shoot a fake Earl.
I've got to take it slow.
Who's in here?
Is this guy watching TV?
How do I get in there?
Alright, it's possible.
It's very possible that I go...
If this guy turns...
I can get this guy without this guy knowing, I think.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
In my pants.
Damn it!
Oh, the guy's next to me.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
I didn't...
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I've got to calm down.
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god.
Oh, my fucking god.
Damn it!
Oh, my god.
Put the other mask on.
Did I not kill that guy?
How did they not hear this?
He's alive.
The door blocked it.
I've got to do this quietly.
I need a melee weapon.
Is there a melee weapon in here?
You know what I'm saying?
It's got to be shoot, shoot.
You've got to shoot.
I need six rounds here.
I'm not sure I can do this silently.
Oh, my lord.
This is fucking hard.
Get back in.
How do I get in the car?
Wait, did I fucking ruin everything for myself?
I think I did.
I think I understand what happened here.
That guy's got a melee weapon.
Get him.
Did I...
Hold on a minute.
Hold on a second.
I'm curious about this.
Yeah, okay, I've...
Look at this.
That's why...
I figured it out.
Oh.
That's why I can't do anything.
This guy's trying to get away.
No, I can do this without alerting the whole house.
All right.
So, this is what's going to happen.
I said I don't want him to see this.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do this.
Oh, my god.
That's enough of a movement of punishment.
Is this guy trying to get away?
Now I can do this without alerting the whole house.
Alright, so this is what's gonna happen.
Like, now, listen.
Now I've figured it out.
Once these guys are out of the way, I'm gonna kill him and leave the room.
Three, two, one, go.
Fuck me.
I forgot about the guy at the end of the hall.
Oh, I'm gonna be here all night.
Is he dead?
He's not dead.
Hit him with the door.
How far does the door go?
Shit.
Alright.
I know I'm not fucking around.
I'm almost done.
These guys down here need to die first.
We've got guy walking, patrolling, I'm gonna hit him with the door, I'm gonna shoot the
guy in front of me, and then I don't know what I'm gonna do after that.
Now I'm gonna improvise after that one.
My whole body just...
That's not over.
I need a good weapon.
Homer Simpson.
Ah, fuck.
At least I have a checkpoint.
Legit scared.
I know.
I'm just panicking.
Give me the melee weapon.
Oh, it's the DPI.
It's gonna be faster than this.
That's actually better.
No, it's not.
I'm lying to myself.
Hey, what?
How did you see me?
Alright, hide.
I can get these two guys.
I can get a guy with the door.
Here we go.
No, wait.
Guy with the door.
Oops.
Oh, oops.
Wait, wait.
Okay.
I need a melee weapon.
Give me the knife.
I gotta throw it at this guy's fucking head.
That didn't kill him?
You motherfucker!
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Who shot me from behind?
Wait, somebody...
Oh my god.
What an idiot.
My fists are instant kill with this character.
Are you kidding me?
The guy!
The same guy!
Oh my god!
Where the fuck is he?
Shit.
Can he see?
No, he can't see through, right?
Oh boy, my boy.
Oh boy.
Okay.
These secrets.
That was fucking crazy.
What a fucking fun game.
What a wild game.
I can't believe I missed this.
This is like my favorite game of the year and it's like 10 years late.
Uh-oh.
Gotta do everything by myself, huh?
Oh no.
I gotta hide.
Okay, gun.
All right.
I'm getting flashbacks to the butcher in Diablo 1.
I'm actually scared right now.
Oh my god.
He's everywhere.
Oh!
Break his neck!
What?
Oh god.
Please don't.
Can I do anything here?
Is this person okay?
Can I like save this person?
Oh, well.
I don't know.
I've just reached in his eyes.
Oh.
Throw this.
I don't want this.
I don't want this equipped.
Let's go.
I did it.
That was intense.
All right.
What grade am I going to get here?
It's the C plus guy, aren't I?
New mask.
Don Juan.
Hey there.
Welcome.
Why is this guy every single employee in every store?
You don't look well, sir.
Are you all right?
Are you sure it is okay for you to be drinking?
All right.
Then I'll get you something special.
Do you like sweet or sour?
Maybe you want it bitter.
It's me again.
Yeah.
Leather jacket.
I was going to say.
Yeah.
The resemblance is there.
For sure.
It's me again.
And there you go, sir.
Enjoy.
No, it's me.
Are we puking?
I think I'm rushing these scenes too much.
Is there other things to see in here?
Apparently not.
Really?
All right.
Let's go.
Next mission.
I do like how they break it up, though, because I am like a rubber band ball
right now.
I'm in the center of it.
Oh, it's you again.
It looks like you've been busy since we last met.
I see that you remember me now, don't you?
But you still don't know who I am.
You don't even know who introduced us, do you?
Why did you come back here?
You're not a nice person, are you?
You make me sick.
Split personality.
It's me.
I'm talking to myself.
I wear the masks and I talk to myself.
I already figured it out.
The picture is starting to take form here.
I wonder if it's accurate.
Some pieces don't quite seem to fit.
Maybe I just don't like the way it looks.
I think our time is up, but we'll leave again.
Before you go, here's our questions to ponder.
Question number one.
Do you like hurting other people?
Question number two.
Who are you leaving messages on your answering machine?
Who are leaving messages on your answering machine?
Question number three.
Where are you right now?
And final question.
Why are we having this conversation?
I'm talking to myself.
He said the line?
What do you mean, the line?
This is Blake speaking.
We have a job for you.
We have a power outage over on 24th.
We want you to take care of it.
We already sent someone over a while ago, but it seems he didn't do a very good job.
Head over there right away.
They're expecting you.
Keep it quick and clean.
I mean, like, guys, I don't know.
This is like we're watching the prequels of Star Wars.
And Obi-Wan Kenobi is talking to Anakin.
And spoilers, by the way.
Who cares?
Star Wars...
There's no such thing as a Star Wars spoiler.
They have a whole ride based on this encounter at Disney World.
And he says...
All right, if you haven't just seen Star Wars yet, just fucking...
You know...
Why am I so worried about that?
When he screams, you are the chosen one, right?
If I've never seen that movie before, I don't know the line.
I'm just like, oh, that was an interesting line.
And then you sit next to me, you're like, oh, he said it!
See?
I'm just like, I don't know, man.
Lethal doors.
Let's try it.
All right, first try.
What happened to the lethal doors?
Am I missing something here?
All right, well, anyways, fuck it.
Oh, you heard me.
Where's that dog?
What?
The fuck?
How did I miss?
Got them both.
Double kill.
Woo!
Oh, no.
Another Mike Peek.
What happened to the lethal door?
Give me another mask.
Wait, I need a gun.
Yeah, that works too.
Okay, whatever.
I don't give a shit.
As long as it works.
Is anybody up here?
I can't see that far.
No, I'm safe in here.
Holy fuck!
The guy behind me!
Oh, my God.
I'm so mad.
Dog.
Gun in the gun.
Do I have to use a gun on the dog?
What the?
Oh, oh my God.
This game is so hard.
It's fucking so much fun, but holy shit.
They fuck kill him.
It's this is the guy that opens this door.
I got to get the guys down here.
Give me the melee weapon.
I feel like I'm better with that than I am anything else.
All right.
How do I do this?
Here we go.
One.
Two.
Don't count.
Just go.
You fucking dumb motherfucker.
I swear to God.
Oh, my God.
He's not dead.
He is.
All right.
Lethal door.
Let's lethal door this guy.
That didn't seem very lethal.
Oh, the fucking dog.
Oh, my God.
I can't handle this.
Oh, my fucking Lord.
I really need to change masks.
I was waiting for him.
I got it.
I got to get these guys.
The guy that comes out of the door here is the one that keeps killing me every
time.
I'm so nervous.
Why did he turn around right there?
God damn it.
Give me a new mask.
I'm not going to use this thing.
I can kill one guy with this door thing.
You know what I mean?
Like, I could get one guy with the fucking door killer in this level.
Give me something else.
Give me this thing.
I got to get in here.
I think this is the only.
I'm trying to think of the only way I could go is probably straight on.
Maybe around the corner.
That guy's alive.
Fuck.
Oh, my fucking God.
You got to be kidding me.
How did he get blocked by the door twice?
Let's get a gun.
Nope.
Gun.
Give me a gun.
Ah!
Who's left?
Is there anybody left in this house?
I'm scared to move.
There's two guys with bats.
Two guys in that room.
The dog?
The dog is gone, right?
This only has five rounds.
Okay.
Do it.
I know you can do it.
You can do it.
Just shoot him.
That's all you have to do.
You have to go in the room and just get it lined up and shoot him.
I fucking hate you.
Okay.
You're fine.
I like you again.
No, I need melee.
Get back over to the door.
These are the last few guys here.
Wait until he's at the door and then just rush him.
One, two, three.
Oh my fucking god.
Mom!
Okay.
I'm good.
What the fuck?
What happened to my DPI?
I pressed the fucking button on my Razor Deathadder.
Okay.
There we go.
Get the guy at the door.
He's going to go all the way around, right?
Holy shit!
That guy didn't shoot me.
I hit the button again.
I did it again.
I got to keep.
I got to wait like a second before the fucking door opens.
That's it.
Last guy down here.
There's two people hanging out in here.
Two dudes in here.
I think I have to go.
I'm going from the back.
Give me the pool cue.
All right.
I'm going to throw.
What's this guy attached to?
That guy's a gun.
I have to go around.
How am I going to do this?
What?
The fuck was that?
I don't understand.
What the fuck happened?
I know the bomb is rigged to the door.
Okay.
Well, that was unnecessary, but whatever.
One guy here.
No bullets in that thing.
Okay.
I can't use either.
I got to go.
How do I get in there?
Can I go through like the bathroom?
There's only two ways to get in there.
How do I disarm the bomb?
Just shoot the door.
But if I shoot...
Am I going to...
I could kill a guy in here.
Don't I want to save this guy?
Can I like do this?
No.
Can I get...
It doesn't matter who they are.
All that matters is you kill them.
Can I...
I can't like shoot through anything.
Shoot the door.
I just did that.
Look.
What are you talking about?
I don't have any bullets.
What?
So wait.
How am I supposed to know that I had to shoot it with the...
I shoot it with different bullets for it to explode.
Come on.
Oh, fuck.
Those guys are going to kill me.
I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Shoot door.
What am I going to do with you idiots?
You're like...
You're behind cover.
Hmm.
Okay.
So, um...
Hmm.
I don't know.
Diffuse the bomb.
I can't diffuse the bomb.
They stand up before they shoot to get the guy with the gun.
Oh my God.
I just want it to be done.
I'm trying to go so fast because I don't want to do it again.
Where did he go with that gun?
Where'd he go?
He goes in this room?
What?
Why did he even go in there?
That's the first time he's ever gone in there.
Like 30 attempts.
For real.
Turning into a pig.
I did...
That didn't kill him.
I hit him with the door, apparently.
Why did that not hurt him?
Why did it hurt him the first time?
Okay.
Now, let's blow up the door.
Alright.
Now, give me...
Do I have a gun?
I have...
Here's a rifle.
They stand up before they shoot, but I feel like the guy down here is shooting me
before this guy does.
And I can't see this guy.
So let's keep zoomed in.
Holy fuck.
Okay.
Oh my lord in heaven.
He stood up first.
Alright.
We're fine.
Everything's good.
That's too much.
That's too much for my puny brain to handle.
I'm definitely going to get a bad grade here.
No, that's fine.
I'm okay with that.
Uh, $50 just came in from Peanut Chan.
Thank you for the 50 bucks.
Hey, Jerma, your content got me through the stresses of college.
I was lucky enough to get a nice job when I got out.
So I want to pay you back now that I can afford it.
I'm sure you'll pay me back when you spend it on something crazy to make me laugh and
forget about the challenges of everyday life.
Jerma Hart, Transgender Pride, have fun with this amazing game.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Thank you, Peanut Chan, for your 50 bucks.
And congratulations, obviously, on getting through college, getting a job.
Thank you so much.
It means a lot.
Graham is the bunny.
Glass bottle.
That's the one I'm fucking talking about.
Yeah, Transgender Pride is the emote, right?
Yes.
Okay.
What are you guys doing out here?
Should I be worried about this?
Who the fuck?
Who the fuck is this?
All right, well, hey, something bad's going on outside your store, man.
Oh, hi, there.
Good to see you again.
I was a bit worried about you.
The city streets don't seem so safe anymore, you know, with all the killings and all
that.
Don't worry about paying.
You're my friend.
Your money's no good here now.
Have a nice night.
Do I just go in every day to this store and the guy's like, hey, yeah, here.
Want a stereo or something?
Oh, wow, I forgot, by the way, I installed it and everything and I completely fucking
forgot about it.
I just dropped a shitload of frames here.
I installed Fortnite and made an account on Fortnite.
And the joke was I was going to do a play a round of Fortnite every time I died in
this game.
I'm so glad I did not think that that was funny after installing it and doing
it on setting everything up.
It's Dave from Miami Pest Control.
We need you.
A client at Southwest One of Hoist Street is having vermin problems.
Try to handle it as quick and swift as you can.
Someone else will clean up for you after you leave.
Make sure not to bother any of the neighbors.
How many times have I died so far?
Imagine playing, like, a hundred games of Fortnite and I've never played it before.
This is called Full House.
Be fast and efficient.
All right, who do we got?
Lethal doors.
Walk fast.
Mmm.
This is for speed runners.
I don't know if I'm in that category.
Ooh, that's a dog, dog, dog!
Can't punch the dog.
What am I doing?
Pick it up.
What?
It's a knife!
Holy shit, how am I still alive?
I have no idea.
I just threw it.
What am I doing?
This is the sloppiest fucking time I've played.
And somehow I'm still a living.
I gotta get this guy in the door here.
Still a dog alive.
I gotta be worried about that.
You gonna come up here, dog?
Holy fuck, it missed!
Barely missed.
Oh no.
I tried!
I tried to fucking break his neck and it wouldn't do it!
Oh, I was like standing over his body for so long for no reason.
Fuck!
Did I not kill him in one hit?
What?
In the name of God, just happened there.
Almost done.
Give me the pool cue.
It's bigger.
Okay, just the guy in the kitchen.
Does that guy come out?
I don't think this guy comes out.
Oh, and okay, you gotta explain to me what the fuck is with the turnaround there.
What's with the turnaround?
Why did he turn around?
You gotta explain it.
What's with the turnaround there?
Why did he turn around?
What's with the turnaround?
What happened?
Why did he turn around there?
Why did that happen?
I'm still, I'm still reeling over why the fuck that happened.
Still a dog.
Alright, two guys in here.
Oh my, what happened to me?
I don't know.
No, no, no, no.
I think, I don't know what to do here.
I just keep annoying this guy.
Give me a fucking break.
Damn it.
Same deal.
Don't have that happen again.
Don't throw this shit at him.
Alright, melee.
Two guys with melee.
Two guys with guns.
I gotta go in there with a gun.
I gotta go in there.
I've gotta knock one guy down.
Shoot guy in front of me.
Play it.
Play it cool for a second here.
So, knock out guy.
Shoot guy.
Guy comes around.
Got it.
This guy right here is the one that's gonna get shot.
One, two, three.
I don't even know how, I went through, I went through the door.
I went through the door.
That's not what was part of the plan, Jeremy.
I didn't wanna go through the fucking door.
That wasn't the plan.
Holy fucking, he turned around all the far, that was so far away.
You know what?
Fuck the plan.
I'll give you a plan.
I'll give you a fucking plan.
He, how did you turn on me that quickly?
Fuck you.
Come on.
How?
Through the fucking door.
Fuck the plan.
I did, I killed one person.
I just tried to, I ran out of bullets and I fucking ran out of bullets.
I'm so fucking, I'm so, don't have a plan.
Forget about a plan.
Fuck the plan.
Again, it works.
Alright, let's go.
Fuck the plan.
Oh, somebody was sitting there.
That guy's still alive.
What does that item do?
What does that item even do?
What the fuck item did I pick up?
I was trying to melee.
What the fuck did I just pick up off the ground?
What did I pick up?
A glass bottle.
If you could see my face right now, my fucking teeth are showing.
I look like a dog.
One guy in here.
This guy was easy last time.
Wasn't a problem.
Here come the other two guys.
Don't, they didn't hear it.
One, two.
That guy over here is definitely going to be more of a problem than this guy.
For sure.
And I missed.
We're good.
This is fucking crazy.
Oh, this game is so much fun.
But I like, I hate it.
I love it though.
Damn it.
I thought that was a B-.
No.
I hate it.
I got Dennis.
Yeah, don't, I'm never picking up, okay that, that's probably a good gun.
But I'm never picking up that stupid bottle.
Good evening.
How are you doing?
You look a bit distracted.
Something got you worried.
These are harsh times we're living in, I know.
Haven't seen many customers lately.
Maybe they've lost their taste for pizza.
Maybe it's time to close shop once and for all.
Anyway, got your order right here.
Take care.
What is, what is going on in this game?
A bottle gets you execution points?
That would make a lot of sense.
Hi, it's Don from Hotel Blue.
We need you tonight.
Our receptionist went home due to stomach problems and we have some VIPs who will
be staying with us today.
Make sure you give them a great stay.
That will be your top priority this evening.
Get going.
Wait, what?
What?
I just skipped the dialogue sequence with this guy.
How?
I just like, accidentally clicked.
I thought I had to click on him.
What did he say?
He just says dot dot dot.
Go back.
I'm not gonna be stuck.
Check the VOD.
Oh, this one's called Clean Hit.
Tip, you can throw weapons.
Yep.
Alright, so let's see.
You start with a knife with Dennis.
Alright, guy in the toilet.
Room full of weapons.
Guy in the toilet.
Guy in the toilet it is.
I don't think I even want to use those right now.
Although there are a shitload of people in here.
This is, yeah.
How the fuck am I supposed to?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think this is like a turtle mission, isn't it?
Are the waiters?
Are the waiters gonna pull out guns?
Of course they are.
Of course the fucking waiter is gonna pull out a gun.
No, I wanted to...
Holy shit.
Okay.
Alright, I gotta be really careful here.
All the way in the back.
Up top.
Guy in the back has a good shot.
Okay.
Last guy over here.
Can I just cheese him?
Oh, of course I can.
Stage clear.
Let's go.
Anywhere else.
Nothing else.
I'm gonna make sure I have a weapon up here.
Anybody right out the front door?
Are we sure about this?
Whoa!
Okay.
Where the hell did you come from?
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
You're just down there.
So what's...
What's this trying to tell me?
Oh.
Okay.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
What about this window?
Can I open this window?
I can't open the window.
There's somebody else in this room, so I think I'm alright to walk over here.
This is gonna be very, very hard.
I gotta be prepared for this.
I don't...
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three.
I gotta get like two people in one shot.
Go!
Whoa!
What?
What's going on?
Okay.
Well.
What is this floating?
Is there anything else in here that I need to see?
I feel like I'm gonna be missing a lot of secrets if I just blast through.
So give me one second.
Nothing?
I mean, what about the janitor?
No.
No secrets.
Whatever.
I'm gonna miss the secrets.
This is my first playthrough.
Did I actually miss a secret?
I feel like I'm gonna get a fairly good score on this one.
I only died like two or three times.
Right?
That's probably gonna be...
Alright.
I'll take it.
That's fine.
Dying doesn't matter.
Okay.
George the Giraffe.
This game's three times and I've never found a secret.
Here we go.
This guy again.
Hey, man!
Boy, am I glad to see you.
Have you been following the news about the killings?
Now, this is top secret.
You can't tell anyone.
But I have a friend who's in the police force.
He told me there's rumors going around.
There could be more than one perp.
Maybe a whole bunch.
A group of people wearing masks killing Russians.
It's like it's from a movie or something, right?
Well, I think it's fascinating.
Right?
So just grab any movie you want.
It's on the house.
Okay, I want this one.
No.
Any movie.
And I have to take this.
I have to take that movie.
So we're now what?
A little more than a month and a half from the start of the game.
April.
Right?
This girl is still here.
Harry!
For management, we have a problem.
This big mess over by the condos on 122nd S.E. Street, one of the president's...
One of the president's water pipe burst.
Wet all over.
The whole building is going to be flooded soon.
Hope you can get on this shit as soon as possible.
Don't go easy on the mob.
Quick.
Neighbors.
Start with a knife.
Look further.
All right, George.
That sounds...
Well, George is the best item in the game.
I mean, that's the best item in the whole game.
In my honest opinion.
Got two guys with guns.
There's a broom right there.
All right.
That's my opportunity to...
I could probably sneak in.
All right.
Sneak into here.
Sneak in here.
Punch this guy.
Kill guy.
Take gun.
Shoot guy.
One, two, three, action.
Nice and fucking clean.
What?
Oh, that guy.
Okay.
I got to turn on punch that guy.
All right.
Don't use the gun.
I don't think I need to.
Actually.
I think I have to shoot, don't I?
Maybe not.
Oh, fuck.
Mistake.
Fuck.
Is that guy still alive?
Don't.
Give me this thing.
No more bullets in this thing.
Give me...
All right.
Let's go.
I'm doing it.
Secrets.
Ooh.
That's a new gun.
Is this my first playthrough?
Yes, it is.
It's the first time I've ever played the game.
All right.
We got one dog.
There's more than...
No, there's only one dog.
Two guys at the front door.
Holy fucking hell.
Oh, I thought that was a door.
Shit.
Fuck.
Dog.
I should have backed up.
What the fuck?
We got one bullet.
Fucking DPI on the Razor Deathadder.
Please.
Let me see.
What?
All right.
Here we go.
I have to shoot this guy.
I can't fuck this up.
All right.
Easy.
That door's closed.
Here's this guy.
One, two, three.
Got him.
Last guy.
All right.
Good.
Anything else?
We're going to go with the...
No.
I'm going with at least three rounds in this shotgun here.
We got one, two, three, four.
I think I can get them all.
Ready?
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Action.
Oh my god.
I was trying to fuck.
Oh, I'm trying to pick up the gun on the ground.
Motherfucker.
What the hell?
What are you going to...
Honestly, did he not die from being shot by the gun?
What the fuck was that?
Oops.
I'm going all the way out.
Okay.
Wait.
What?
Oh, that's it.
I bit it.
Yeah.
So wait.
You shot a door and the door knocked the guy down so he didn't die.
Oh, well fuck.
So any secrets?
Okay.
Am I losing my mind right now?
What is going on?
What the fuck?
Last guy.
Make it quick.
Make it easy.
Phone's ringing.
There's been a small change of plans.
We have a prank caller at the telephone company.
Why don't you go there and see if you can talk some sense with him.
You know what I mean?
Go there now, Florida.
Okay.
Can I have it?
Give me a new gun.
This one.
Oh, wait.
We're not done.
We're just going.
Uh oh.
Phone mom.
Okay.
Are there any items on the ground?
Can I go in there with a weapon?
Is this a boss or something?
They want me to get the giant Mega Man gun.
That's like a giant machine gun.
Okay.
How am I going to hold that?
Hello?
You're dead meat.
Alright.
Give me the gun.
I got the...
It's not a gun.
It's...
In fact, it's a set of golf clubs.
Oh my god.
I need a fucking golf club.
What is this?
I understand.
You got to go after he swings.
Oh, but I fucking got cornered.
Oh shit.
I got him.
I beat him.
No, I didn't.
What am I thinking?
Oh.
I'm so fucking nervous.
Why did it not lock onto him?
Okay.
Do it again.
What's what the fucking corner there?
What?
He spins around you.
Why was he just walking with me?
Oh.
I throw and it just went face through his body.
Holy fuck.
Throw it.
This can't be happening.
It can't end now.
Not like this.
I'm so close.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Well, I did it.
It was only two hits.
That was anxiety-causing.
You don't even know what you did.
116 total deaths.
That seems like a lot.
All right.
So what's a typical total deaths for an entire play through for a first try?
I got Ted.
About 15.
Interesting.
Machete.
We really should be playing Fortnite now.
No, we shouldn't.
I even installed it too.
What the hell?
Why would I even do that?
What a waste of internet.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm never going to play it.
I'm just going to uninstall it.
Welcome back, sir.
How are you tonight?
I look so happy.
To be honest, I don't feel too good either.
Something in the air.
I don't know.
I just have this really bad feeling like something terrible has happened tonight.
I haven't felt this way since San Francisco.
I don't like it, but not one bit.
So how about a drink?
Yeah, before the stream started, we were joking in the chat saying things like, if
I turn on Fortnite, even as a joke, I will lose probably 1,500 viewers.
And then the argument was made.
But what about the potential 3,000 or 4,000 that you'll gain?
And I don't even know what to do about that.
I don't think I would want that to happen.
I don't think I want that.
So you came back.
How are you feeling?
You look ill.
Maybe you should see a doctor.
I told you not to come back here.
I see that my opinion of you doesn't matter.
If you insist on returning here, then I should leave.
Have you thought about what I asked you last time?
I'm not here to give you any answers.
If you're not feeling well, maybe you should rest.
Some things work out best when you don't try so hard, and no matter who you are,
bearing too much weight inevitably leads to the collapse of everything.
Next time we meet, we'll be the last.
I can see it in your eyes.
Before you go, I'll leave you with three predictions.
Someone you know is not who you think he is.
Something will soon be taken from you.
On July the 21st, you will wake up in a bigger house.
Okay.
Alright, where's um...
Let's just go.
Hi, it's Pat from the club.
We want you to DJ tonight.
You're free to play any kind of music you want.
Beer is on the house.
Dressed to kill, see ya.
Why is she wearing the matching colors of the Nintendo?
That's such like a streamer thing to do.
You know what I mean?
Like, look, I'm wearing the colors of the thing that's in my room!
Like imagine if my character was dressed up in like, this color scheme, and there
was a webcam on me.
Drink from the sink.
Push it!
Dermot would do that if he had the foresight.
That's probably why he would.
Dogs don't attack.
Yup.
I don't give a shit.
Well, why would there be dogs here?
Oh, there are dogs here.
So the dogs don't do anything.
That's...
Okay, I might have to keep that on permanently.
Holy fuck.
Where did you...
Okay.
Through the glass apparently.
Yeah, that's what we call a fucking triple.
That's what we call getting it done.
Only one more guy down here.
He's got a knife.
Who's left?
Was it somebody left?
Wait, I have to...
I have to kill the dogs even though they're friendly?
Oh boy, okay.
Um, that's not very nice.
I have this special dog mask on.
Brain gun.
I'm gonna go...
Left room is more dangerous, I think, in my personal opinion.
Why is a dog coming over here?
No bullets.
Oh, you fucking...
There was another guy pretending to be dead on the ground.
Give me a break.
What am I doing?
What?
How did I do that?
That just threw me off.
Watch out.
He's gonna come in here.
Why?
Why are you throwing them?
Oh, fuck me, man.
Can I pick it up?
Get them both.
One, two, three.
I didn't...
I thought it was just the dogs left.
I thought it was just the dogs.
That's why I ran through there.
Oh, man.
I'm so...
God.
I just thought the dogs were left.
Give me a fucking break.
He was locked onto.
Unbelievable.
No, I don't want to pick the guy up.
Just get rid of the dogs now so I don't have to think about this later.
Why was he not dead?
I'm not gonna forget about that guy now.
Who's left?
One guy right there.
Bingo.
One, two, three.
Bug wasn't there.
I thought the dog wasn't there.
I thought it was just the dogs.
Is that it?
Well, they both had the same idea, apparently.
Get off of him.
All right, is there a way that I can jump off somebody?
Hey, guess what I did.
I hit the fucking DPI button on the mouse again.
Fuck this.
All right, let me disable it.
I think I have to download the, like, virus software to disable that, don't I?
Don't I have to get, like, Razer's virus shitty Synapse program thing to do that?
Turn it off, you nuts.
All right, that's it over here.
Two guys down there.
Nope, a guy in the bathroom.
I want to go in there with the super shotgun.
Nobody on the DJ floor?
Okay.
Go.
Just solder it.
Holy fuck, I was talking and I almost just ran into death.
Go to the car.
Wait, did I just go back up the stairs?
I did, didn't I?
Fuck me.
Mask, mask.
What?
I, I, whatever.
I didn't pick up the mask, but read chat.
All right, let me tell you something.
When I'm in the middle of an insane game where you have to focus 1000%, I can't look
over here.
I can look over here like now.
Level was over.
Who cares?
That mask sucks anyways.
How do I know?
It's easy.
Because Leather Jacket just told me and he's in the game.
He's right here.
What you just saw now did not actually happen.
If you don't even, you don't look like you believe me, then allow me to demonstrate.
Hey, man.
Nice to see you.
Friendly faces are few and far between these days.
Just take what you want.
My treat.
Have a good night.
Am I living in a simulation?
I think this is a weird simulation game.
You have one new message.
Hi, this is Rick from the real estate office.
This is showing for an apartment downtown today.
It's at Southwest Street 35 open house.
Just swing on by when you have the time.
Get the mask.
I'm not going to get the mask.
It doesn't matter.
I'm just playing the game.
I'm not going to peek my microphone.
Survive.
One bullet.
I kind of like the dog zone attack thing though.
Walk fast.
Lethal doors.
More guns.
Fists of fury.
I like this one.
Let's try this one again.
Holy shit.
Two guys.
And a dog.
Whoa.
Alright, we're fine.
There's only one guy left in this room, but he has a gun.
Make it count.
One, two, three.
You didn't make it count.
You didn't do it.
Oh my lord.
Man, the dog's not attacking thing.
It's seriously so good.
It's so good.
I don't even want to pick up a melee weapon because I'm going to kill instantly.
But I mean, a little bait that guy over here.
Dogs are so erratic.
I thought the other guy down there didn't have a gun.
Fuck.
Tried a different approach.
I had it.
I can get it.
Alright, no.
I'm not the fuck I'm going to do about this.
Pull Q.
If I poke my head in here, I'm dead.
I've got to be careful because he's just facing this way.
Got it.
Alright, now I've got a gun.
We can go...
Watch out.
I can get three here, probably.
I hate everything about what I just did.
There's no bullets in this gun.
Oh, there's no bullets in that gun.
Where did that guy go?
Opportunity right there.
I'm going to get picked off by somebody who's going to peek a corner and I'm
going to die.
Alright, I'm going to door the guy, punch him.
Any of you guys?
Nobody?
No?
Okay, let me tell you something.
You press the space bar on somebody and try to break their skull and sometimes just a
dumb one do it.
I'm trying to rush.
It's not going to happen.
It's not going to fucking happen.
Stop doing that.
I didn't kill them both with that?
Is he dead?
Yeah.
Dog, dog, dog.
Dog!
The fucking...
Honest to God.
The fucking door.
And the door...
The door saved them both with two bullets.
The fucking door.
Do you know?
You ever heard about a door before?
Guys, have you ever seen a door in your life?
Alright, got it.
Who the fuck are you guys?
What?
What's happening?
How do I get out?
I got to get out of here.
The guy has a laser beam.
That guy has a laser.
What am I supposed to do about this?
Um...
Oh my God.
I'm so defeated from that.
That sucks.
I'm actually defeated.
I feel terrible right now.
How did you pick that up, you fucking idiot?
Wait, I'm just trying to rush it now.
There's a dog.
What the fuck?
Oh, come on.
Motherfucker.
Give me a break.
Are there any more bullets?
This is the guy that killed me every time.
Nobody comes up here, right?
Fuck, he can see me through the glass!
What the...
No!
What the fuck?
Oh my fucking God!
Damn it!
Fuck the dog.
Fuck you, dog.
What the hell happened to my body and my brain?
No!
I don't...
Why do I have to do this whole thing again?
You give such great checkpoints and then all of a sudden, like, the fucking entire police
force shows up and you just have to start the whole thing over.
Fuck.
I'm losing it now.
I'm like just exhausted.
Fucking hell.
Fuck the gun.
There's no more bullets in that fucking thing.
Dogs.
No, no.
Time to leave, right?
The police are here, right?
How do I get out of here?
Where's the exit?
But where's the exit, though?
I don't know where the fucking exit is.
Oh my God, why does this exist?
Holy shit, I actually made a checkpoint.
Oh my God, I actually made a checkpoint by leaving the fucking room.
Oh.
Oh my goodness gracious, that was fucking too much.
Calm down.
How are you supposed to calm down?
Where I...
I would have had, in my brain, I'm starting the entire level over again if I lose there.
Hey, dude, calm down.
You almost just had to do the whole thing over again after doing it.
Chat is gone, okay?
Makes perfect sense.
All right, there we go.
I don't know why that happened.
Hey, what do you want?
I know our friend looks like he's dead over there.
Could you hurry up?
We're closing soon.
I usually get shit here for free.
Is that not a thing anymore?
I'm gonna have to throw a flag on that round.
Come on, that was fucking hard.
That was no joke.
Anything else to see?
Hello there, this is Thomas from the Downtown Relaxation.
We need you to fill in at the reception tonight.
One of our employees has called in sick.
Wear something fitting and discreet.
Okay, let's go.
Here comes the best song.
Tenth chapter.
Hot, hot G-heavy.
All right, how about extra ammo?
Let's try extra ammo.
Anybody down the hall?
Oh, fucking yeah, there is.
Okay.
Hmm.
Well, I have to bait you guys down here.
That makes sense.
I got one of you.
Guy with a gun comes in.
Fucking Jesus.
Okay.
Maybe I can run up.
I have an idea.
Let's see if this works.
Okay.
Then this guy's gonna come down with a gun and I can backstab him.
Or is he not gonna come in here?
Isn't there a guy?
Yeah, there he is.
Just wait until he comes through and then one, two, three.
The long fucking animation there.
That's what I'm gonna do though.
I probably, I don't even need to wait, to be honest.
Let's just go wherever he turns the corner.
All right, where are you at now?
Come investigate.
All right.
One guy over there.
Look, I'll make sure I'm not gonna see the glass.
I'll take a gun.
More ammo.
I have the mask on.
Why am I not using it?
All right.
Nobody down?
Nobody over?
Okay.
Yeah, there is a guy there actually.
There's two.
Oh, what the fuck was that?
What was that weird corner bullshit?
What the hell was that?
What the fuck was that?
Aye, aye, aye.
I missed him.
You know, I got a better idea.
Would have worked.
This guy almost got me through the fucking wall.
He's coming over here apparently.
I can't go over there.
All right.
Gun.
Let's go.
Come on.
Aye, aye, aye.
Oh.
Fundamentals here.
Don't be crazy.
You have to beat it.
Come on.
Oh my god, I missed.
Really?
Is it the last guy?
I think it might be.
No.
There's two guys down here, aren't there?
Yeah.
Give me a shotgun for this.
Eight rounds.
I'm going to pull.
Oh, man.
I got an idea.
I'm going to shoot through the glass.
Okay, that takes care of those two.
Don't shoot it again, you dummy.
My question is, how do I take these guys out?
I'm going to have to pull them through.
I'm going to have to shoot this guy when he comes down, and then hopefully they
didn't react at all.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
Do I have any grenades?
I got to be quick.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Why are they not moving?
Again.
Oh my god, I hate this mouse.
One bullet hits me.
All right, slow it down.
I just assumed the guy was going to run through the room when I shot the other guard.
Why wouldn't the guy run into the room when I shot the guy on the right?
I don't know.
Okay.
I got to get rid of this guy.
Through the glass.
What am I doing through the glass?
They aren't friends.
Yeah, but you wouldn't listen.
You wouldn't hear this and be like, oh, maybe I should not.
Oh, no.
I forgot to shoot this guy.
I got to get them both in one shot.
I ran out of bullets again.
Thank god.
Okay, let's move.
I'm going to be down the hall.
Down window.
Watch out for the wall.
Did I get him?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
One up.
One to the bottom right.
I'm going to get shot through this window, and I know it.
Is this the last guy up there?
I'm so paranoid.
There's a dog.
Dog?
Guy with a gun.
Okay, I'm going to go from the top.
Is there any windows here?
This is just a guy with like a baton down here, right?
Right?
Right, guys?
There's just one guy down here, right?
Okay, good.
Right.
Okay.
Apparently, that's how you do this one.
Oh, it didn't even.
Fuck it.
What happened?
Where am I?
What?
God!
He's not dead.
You're shot with a gun, and then you shoot with a shotgun 10 feet away, and you're still
alive.
It's happening.
I can't move.
I can't fucking move.
Why can I not move?
Fuck this.
How did that guy not die by that?
I don't understand.
It was this guy.
Just run.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Anybody going to get up?
You sure no one's going to get up?
Okay.
What happened?
Who is this guy?
What?
Who is he?
Oh, the door.
The door actually just saved my life.
I would have been so upset.
Where did he come from?
I looked both ways before I crossed the street.
Why?
I looked both ways.
I can't move.
I looked both ways, too.
That guy came out of nowhere.
Son of a...
Goodness.
That dog just fucking ate me.
No.
Relax.
One more round.
Dog.
Okay.
Let's take a minute here and realize that I'm going to die because I'm going to die.
Fuck.
Nobody coming this way.
Right.
I kept getting collapsed on.
Okay.
Give me that gun.
Fucking razor death batter.
Did somebody just shoot me from down here?
Oh.
All right.
Is there like a secret in here that everyone's going to scream at me and get
very angry with me that I don't pick up?
Guy right here.
I'm not going to alert anybody.
In fact, let's see if I can do melee here.
I need some extra points.
Oops.
Well, I didn't know you were going to come over here.
Okay.
Up.
Got the gun.
All right.
I actually need the gun for this because I need to shoot that guy, right?
Dog.
Okay.
The dog.
You can't hit the dog with the door.
The dog doesn't get affected by the door.
Apparently, it's too...
It's these two small doggos over his head.
I didn't time it right.
Do it.
Kill him.
Snap his neck.
All right.
Give me the shotgun.
This...
These guys over here almost need to go first.
Fucking dog.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
The same guy just killed me and I'm trying to...
I'm trying to get to him.
Fucking door, man.
Break.
This is called...
I'm just going as fast as I can now.
Got to wait till they're together and then they weren't together.
Just fucking pull them out.
And what the hell is the dog doing in here now?
Fucking motherfucker.
What?
The last ten times in a row that I did this.
You're dying first.
I don't care if I...
I don't care what happens.
Wait.
Wait for the dog.
Oh no.
All right.
Don't blow this.
Because I just have to get these two guys with the bane of my entire existence.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
How is you...
Three guys up there.
Anybody going to aim down the hall and shoot me?
One guy here.
I don't think so.
I think I'm good to go right here.
Grab this gun.
Yep.
Okay.
Nobody alive in here, right?
Is this guy...
God damn it.
I'm so, so depressed right now.
I tried so hard to look around and I just...
The glass is just so many...
There's so many avenues that I have to pay attention to.
Thanks, door.
To get rid of this guy now.
Come on.
Get over here.
How do you not see me?
Why?
That guy's still alive.
He didn't come out of his room.
How did you not come out of your room yet?
He's dead.
Did I kill him?
I don't even remember killing that guy.
The glass.
Is he dead?
Jake.
I got Jake.
The Jake mask.
I got it.
Everyone, don't worry about it.
Chapter done.
Is this really the same guy that died to Pinwheel?
He's changed so much.
I don't know about this grade.
This game is so hard and so ridiculous.
But I can't stop playing it.
It's...
Everything is so clean and it just feels very satisfying to play.
I can't really stop.
I don't care if I get a C-.
Is there anything lower than a C-?
Or is that as low as you can go?
Can you get an F?
I got Willem and Jake the snake.
You can get F.
Okay, that's all I need to know.
Alright, dead again.
What are you looking at?
Hey, I recognize you.
You look very familiar.
Have we met before?
Alrighty.
I don't get a free VHS.
Did it say something about July?
What the fuck?
Get out of my face, asshole.
Who the hell is this?
Alright, this is Jim from the office.
Just want to remind you that your report is due tomorrow morning.
Have it on my desk by eight.
It's the address in case you forgot.
Click, click, click, click, click.
Okay.
Eleventh chapter, Dead Line.
Who do we got?
Alright.
Rip and steal is Willem.
And then we have survived two bullets.
Killing throws.
Let's try it.
There's glass everywhere.
That didn't kill him in the first shot.
Somehow you managed to live.
And there's glass here and a guy here.
I got to be careful.
We're going to go grab the...
Killing throws.
Holy fuck.
Okay, I'm good.
Oh, best song in the whole game here.
Oh, I thought there was a window.
He's still alive.
Oh!
He got...
He died.
Oh.
Okay.
Slow-mo rewind that right now.
Do it right now.
Go back and rewind the fucking game.
And watch those bullets go through the guy's face.
What happened there?
I want a full rewind.
Door.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Melee weapon.
Holy shit.
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm panicking.
I need a...
I don't know what I need.
Glass.
All right.
Let's go.
Two out of two.
I'll take the big shotgun.
Why not?
Oh, fuck.
He turned on me quick.
Really?
Fucking really.
Like, fucking really?
I'm just going to shoot you then.
Well, no.
Okay.
I want to throw.
I don't want to grab anybody.
I didn't want to grab that guy.
Glass.
I'll shoot this guy through the glass.
Wait.
Speaking of glass.
Oh, my God.
I'm so...
Okay.
He can shoot me through that glass.
Any more glass?
No.
I just got to go through this room.
Get them both in one shot.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Holy fuck.
No?
I'm okay.
Am I though?
Now I have three people in this room to deal with.
Hi.
Okay.
I think I can thank God it's long enough.
All right.
Two to two.
Where is he?
Right here.
That's the last guy in this whole place.
Make it easy on yourself.
All right.
Okay.
No masks in here, right?
Holy...
What the fuck is this?
I...
Oh, no.
I can't go anywhere.
There's no bullets in this gun.
Fuck.
Holy God.
Oh, now I'm in trouble.
I got to hide.
Who's throwing this shit?
Oh, my God.
I don't have any more bullets.
Holy shit, man.
They don't give you a second.
Jesus Christ.
It's pinpoint fucking accuracy.
I'm so dead again.
I need a different gun.
Holy shit.
This is insane.
I'm trying to pick the gun up.
I just didn't...
I couldn't get it.
Lord, this is the hardest thing I've done the whole game.
It's not enough to kill all of them.
Jesus, my Lord.
I give up, you win.
Don't even think about it.
I'm not going over there unless I have a gun.
I don't have a gun.
Are there any guns on the ground?
He's going to stand up and shoot me.
Okay, good.
All right.
Get to the car.
Let's go.
Oh, hey.
C minus.
No, I'll probably get like a B.
Give me a B.
C plus.
I'm all right with that.
Oh, I got a...
He's dead.
Hey, you.
VIP's only tonight.
I think you better leave.
Why is it VIP's only?
I am...
What the fuck are you looking at?
Oh, it's that guy.
Okay.
Interesting.
Get out of the way.
Part four.
Connections.
That's a new mask.
Hey.
Oh, why the...
Why does clicking skip?
I like went to go click on her and it skipped it instantly.
What did it say?
I tried, I like didn't know that...
Literally clicking the button one time skips the whole cut scene.
I can't restart this.
What the fuck is going...
What did I just do?
What happened?
What?
What's going on?
Why do I watch the...
Play level 11 again.
What?
Why?
You told me to go back?
I have to play the last level over again.
All right.
Give me a TLDR.
What did the girl say?
And what happens when you talk to the rat?
I don't want to play that last level again.
You watch it on YouTube.
It's a one minute cut scene.
All right.
Hold on.
What should I search for?
Like rat on couch Miami?
No, there's going to be a shit load of articles about like a rat problem in Florida.
There's no way to...
Chapter 12.
Chapter 12 intro scene.
Hotline Miami.
This is not very...
I don't think I can find a decent video here.
And these are all like Let's Plays.
There's somebody to be talking.
All right.
Hold on.
I just saw it.
Okay.
You get shot and then...
Looks like it's only you and me left.
I'm sure you know by now that this won't end well.
Soon you'll be all alone, but that's okay.
Before we say goodbye, I'll let you in on a little secret.
What you do from here on won't serve any purpose.
You will never see the whole picture.
Here's the chicken saying this, and it's all your own fault.
Now it's time for you to leave.
There's a warm bed across the hall from here and you look like you could use some rest.
Then he goes over and he turns into like another character.
He turns into...
Now he's in like a hospital.
And his head explodes and then he lies down.
All right.
I got it.
I figured out.
I understand.
I don't know if he's been in a coma for weeks now, but he's going to wake up, right?
Chat didn't see it.
Why did you tell me to restart?
I gotta stop listening.
I gotta stop listening to chat every time.
Show it.
What?
It was one guy?
No, it was like 400 guys.
It was like three to four hundred guys.
He's going to wake up.
All right.
Listen, I'll give you the TLDR.
You walk in.
Guy on the couch shoots you.
You fall down.
You get back up.
He says, hey, this is fucking all this fucked up, ain't it buddy?
And you're like, yeah.
And then you walk out and your head explodes.
There you go.
This guy is a prime suspect in a major case.
Look, my guess is as good as yours.
Though I can say that it might be a while.
He's still not even fully healed from the surgery.
Is there nothing you can do?
We need this guy.
Here.
Look.
See?
Just pretend I'm playing this.
Holiday sale.
Hey, make sure you check out Fry's Electronics.
God damn.
All right.
Fuck it.
Who cares?
Wait, wait, wait.
Get.
Here.
Watch.
Ready?
See?
There you go.
So I'm in a coma.
See?
There you go.
But that asshole ain't saying shit.
And what makes you think this guy will?
July 21st.
Wait, I'm in the hospital.
Hey, where do you think you're going, prick?
I guess we better put restraints on you.
July 21st.
Oh.
I thought every day was counting.
All right.
Well, I gotta sneak out.
You get a bigger house on the 21st.
The world is just spinning around now.
Okay.
This is hard to control.
I don't like this.
I hate this.
Oh no.
Don't.
I don't want to do this.
No.
How do I get out of here?
Just can I go back outside?
Oh, like, cause I turned the...
Here.
Hold on.
There you go.
Am I missing something here?
The other way?
I can't go back outside.
I can't open this window.
Okay.
He's distracted.
All right.
So I can go up there.
And is there any patrol over here?
Is this guy right here?
You can see through the window, right?
Oh fuck.
I gotta move now.
Can you see me through the window?
I have no idea.
I gotta go that way.
Okay.
Let's go forward now.
Through that door.
Watch out for that guy reading.
I'm gonna go on the next attempt.
Wait.
Watch out for the doctor.
Is he gonna come down here now?
What?
What's going on?
Holy fuck.
Oh.
Come on, man.
Is there anything in here I need to get?
I think so.
I'm assuming I just have to go over here.
Oh my god.
Give me a break.
Really?
What?
The fucking window.
Fuck you.
No.
Okay.
More escape mission.
Is there anywhere that I have to go in particular?
I'm just gonna go slow room to room.
Oh, that's not gonna happen.
Go back in.
I'm down.
Hey, hold it right there.
You're not allowed out of here.
Get back to your room now.
Fucking idiot.
This is not fun on hardcore.
I can't imagine most of this game would be very fun on hardcore.
Jesus.
I have to make it over there.
Okay.
I'm gonna go in when he passes.
I'm going to go into this room here.
And never mind, there's another guy there.
I actually can probably make it there in one go.
Into this room here.
Watch out for the window, nobody can see me.
All right from here it looks like.
Can I?
I'm gonna go through this side and I could hear the sound of the game.
There must be a door over here or something.
Isn't it?
Oh.
Oh my god.
Can I? I can't punch anybody, can I?
I mean, there's a spot.
Is it one second here?
Like if I go right
now
I might be able to make it all the way over here.
Okay. Next run through.
There's another guy coming. One.
There comes two. Alright, now when he's gone
this guy comes around. Time to go.
One, two, three, go.
What the fuck?
It drunkenly walked me into the other
way. Fuck.
What's this door for here?
What? What the fuck is going on?
Watch out for the windows.
You can just skip
that whole sequence.
Okay. Why put all that
nonsense down there where
you could just walk out and leave?
I guess so.
Somebody's fucking up my car.
Caution tape. Dead body.
Looks like this is a crime scene.
What was in? Like a clothes?
These are my clothes.
The car still works?
Assault.
The 13th chapter.
Richard.
Let's see. How about
rip and
steal. Quiet gunshots.
Okay.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
Is this like a...
Well, okay.
We got one, two. I could probably go
like this.
Wait for him to come around.
Knock you out. Watch out.
Oh, I thought I hit a gun.
That looks like a gun
in his hands.
I'm so confused right now.
What the fuck am I holding? Is it a baton?
So these guys don't have...
Who has the gun then?
They don't have guns.
I'm so worried about being shot. I thought
didn't I get shot at first?
I could have sworn that somebody shot me here.
Well, now they did.
I didn't get it. Damn.
No, I wanted to hold on to that.
I don't like this weapon.
The weapon is like awkward for me. I don't know why.
Where did you get the machine gun?
Alright, hold on a second here.
It's the same as the other weapons.
You know what it is? Is it the fact that
he's switching hands?
Does that happen with the other weapons too? Is that something I've never noticed?
Let's try going in here.
Okay.
I got a gun now. Watch out for the window.
Okay, guy in there.
What?
I was across the whole game.
Oh my fucking god.
Pull me back in here.
Here comes the guy with the gun.
Speaking of guns, please give this one to me.
I'm not going this way
again.
Although I might have to do this.
Okay, got him.
I think there's somebody behind him.
Alright. I gotta do this a little slower.
Um.
I can tell there's a guy right here.
Oh fuck. It's silent. It's okay.
Alright, up here. No. God. I don't know.
I just don't know if there's a guy right down there.
Let's exterior that.
Let me get the window here.
Right there. That guy would have killed me.
Thank goodness. Okay. Be careful.
Is there another guy down here?
Oh, there's another window.
Oh yeah.
What about down here?
Okay, only guy.
Watch it. He's going to be at the window in a second.
Watch it!
What? That's not a window.
How did he shoot through that? That's not a wall?
How did he shoot through the fucking
black thing?
Wait, is that not a wall?
That's a metal detector. Oh come on.
Oh my lord.
What the hell?
I was so caught. That's the first time
ever. You see it.
That's just a doorway.
That's the only doorway that's not brown.
I'm so, so unhappy.
In here.
He's going to get up.
Stupid metal detector.
I'm actually more comfortable.
Just running in there and fucking hitting him with a baton I think.
Where's the other guy?
He's right down here.
I think I want to get the giraffe with us.
Not being able to see down here really sucks.
I got him. Okay.
Wait, wait. Watch out for the fucking windows over here.
How did you? What the fuck?
Holy shit!
Oh my. I did it.
Oh my goodness.
Okay. Oh right. The metal detector.
Jerma sounds so scared
of this dream. I am.
This is hard, man.
This is like one thousand
percent focus.
Window guy. Can that guy shoot?
I don't think he can.
Alright. I'm going back down this way.
No, I don't want that. Give me this back.
Okay. Take it easy.
That's it for that.
That guy. No windows, right?
He can't shoot through. He can't shoot me through here.
I'm safe. I almost died right there.
Garret. That was a one hundred percent
almost died.
Okay. One guy left right here.
Holy fuck.
He turned on me so hard.
Got it. Keep going.
Okay, boys. The bastard will be here any second now.
It's time for us to show him what we're made of.
Remember your training and play it safe.
Follow protocol and we'll all make it out alive.
Okay.
Whatever you say.
You did it. You won. You got the bad guy.
And what did I die by again?
I'm not entirely sure.
He's alive.
Window. Out of bullets though.
There's another guy in there.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
I missed.
Did I death out of myself?
Yeah, I did. I can't even tell anymore.
I'm going to rip these fucking buttons off with pliers.
I don't know if this doesn't feel right.
Watch the fucking idiot that comes through here.
Why is he using the
motion controls?
All right. All of them are dead up there.
I just have to worry about the guys in this room.
That's correct. Who's left?
Guy up there. Easy.
No walls. No windows to deal with.
And then here comes his buddy.
And then here comes his other buddy.
Oh no. Don't go out there. Don't go out there.
That leaves us with the guy
in the top room and the right side.
Right side.
I don't know what I want to do.
I think I want to be careful.
How do I get in here?
Like open the cell or something?
Oh shit! I got wrecked here.
Is there a way to like...
Do I need to do anything else?
I was kind of blending in with the blood.
I thought it was blood on my peripheral.
Do I have to shoot this guy?
No. You got to be shitting me.
Why are you... Look man.
Girl, it wasn't anything personal.
I know you made it all the way here,
but I think you're in for a disappointment.
I don't really have any answers for you.
Damn, that hurt.
You know, I think we might not be that different, you and I.
Have you also been getting those weird phone calls?
Kogka.
I wish I had something to tell you, but I don't.
The police seem to know more about this mess than I do.
They probably have a fire on the case.
A file on the case around here somewhere.
I'd ask you to spare my life, but...
Cough.
You look like you've made up your mind.
Spare or kill?
What should I do?
Oh, I'm already killing him.
I killed him. He's dead.
Well, see you later.
Alright, we're looking for that.
The filing cabinet with the file.
Chapter done. Go to the car.
Am I going to get run over by another one?
I got the mask.
Wait for the car to explode through here.
No worries, boys. It's not canon.
Did you just spoil me on the whole game?
Did you just spoil everything for me?
What?
See.
Zack the Frog, I don't care what this does.
I will never take this off.
Uzi Machine Gun.
July 23rd.
More weird shit in my house.
Spreading out all the files.
Suspects claim to have been threatened into
instructed to kill by messages on
their phone calls
traced to a club on South 86th
Street. Ties to underground Russian
mafia network. Multiple accounts
of illegal activity reported.
Insufficient evidence for a warrant.
Okie dokie.
Looks like that's where we're going.
This one's called Vengeance.
Uh, we're not going to do Peter.
Longer combo window.
Just want to see what the other one does.
Killing froze. Start with a
silenced Uzi. That's pretty great.
But, I need to put
the Frog Mask on.
Longer combo window. That's it.
I did it. I beat the level. Whoa.
Damn it. Damn it.
Want the gun? I want the gun!
I want the gun!
Hey, actually a good thing.
Turned out to be a good thing.
Alright, what do we got? Hey, hey, easy.
Oh, fuck.
Come on, man.
How does one attempt to reliably do
something like this over and over again?
That didn't connect.
This could be a bad mask for this.
I'm starting to realize this right now.
Start with a silenced Uzi. That makes this room
a thousand times easier.
Only one shot left and it's for the dog.
And I didn't even get the dog because I missed.
I need this now. I'm dead.
I can't kill this guy.
Yeah, I have to put another mask on.
I feel like I'm not going to
complete this without a different mask.
Window through there. I gotta kill
this guy right now.
Watch out for the dog. How did you
saw me through the window?
Okay. That's not fair.
Not fair. That's going to make
me escape the game and go put a new mask
on because that was fucking dumb.
That was dumb? Everything about that was
stupid. He spun around like
three times and then landed on me.
Alright, let's do the rat.
Silenced Uzi. Easy enough.
I'm not going to use it yet.
Why would you? Get on him.
Get on top of his head.
Give me the Uzi. Silenced. That's not
an Uzi. Where's my Uzi?
That's not an Uzi.
There it is. Alright.
Beautiful. This is going to be so much
easier. Through the wall
here. Gonna get this guy through the window.
No, actually I'm going to get you.
Holy fuck. He tripped
and died I think. Alright, we're good?
Much better start than anything I've done
before. Here comes the dog.
Oh my fucking lord.
Of course the monster truck's in the way.
Which way though?
Which way is the way where I'm not going to get
sniped by some random person?
That is the right way. See?
First time I put the Uzi on, it's over.
I just feel like this is wrong
again. I feel slower
again. Why?
Blaming mouse? Yeah,
I am going to blame the mouse with the two buttons
right sitting on your index finger
and middle finger where if you press them
it changes the DPI of your mouse.
And the only way to change it is if you
download Razor's
program that boots up
every time Windows starts. You have to go in and force
it to not turn on. To change
one combination. I can't believe I'm going to do that.
I'm about to give in.
I'm about to give in and download the
worst piece of fucking software that currently
exists. It's Razor
Synapse. Yeah, Razor
Synapse is if Skype and Uplay
had a baby and forced
your peripherals to use it.
What killed me?
Alright, somebody, wait, first of all, somebody correct me if I'm
wrong here, okay?
Is that the only possible way
that I can change is what that does?
Or can I go into my actual
Windows mouse settings? Is it correct?
Or do I have to go get Razor Synapse?
Change the settings and
uninstall it but won't uninstalling it
remove the settings? There are some
softwares to disable them.
Super glue.
I can't go, hold on,
I can't go this way.
Why would, come on, invisible wall
Yeah, because this is wrong again.
I just click the button
up for higher DPI.
Put that button on the bottom of the mouse.
Anybody following me?
Oh, shit!
No, that was so cool too and I blew it!
Alright, I swear
to God, guys, it's
changing it even when I don't press it.
I just impressed all my friends and it didn't even matter.
Dead, alright.
He's up there, nobody, nobody down following me.
Door's gonna knock this guy
out, right? No, it's not.
It's not gonna do that, actually.
Window, I would just rent
What the hell happened? What?
That guy came all the way down from over here.
Get rid of the guys in the toilet.
Oh, no!
There's no guns, there's no bullets.
Okay, now I don't have to worry about that anymore.
I have one shot.
Thank God there's a gun right here.
No,
no, I have to, I have to kill this guy.
I have to shoot this guy
with one bullet, I have to.
Trying a different technique there.
I can't, I can't, I'm trying to pick
the fucking knife up.
I'm just tilting. I'm just on full tilt
right now.
That guy was just lying on the goddamn ground.
Fucking God, I'm going
to scream.
I, no, oh, don't.
Fuck am I gonna, fuck this.
God, this is
unbearable!
Ugh!
Why didn't these guys get attracted this time?
Why didn't the whole fucking left side of the entire game
come down this time?
Why? Why does it only happen like
40% of the time?
What are you doing here?
No!
I'll be right back. I'm gonna go pee.
Fuck!
What am I doing? I didn't even say hi
that I'm back.
I'm almost at that point where
nothing I do works because I've lost it.
I've lost it all.
You know what I mean? Like I'm almost at the-
And here he comes! And I need a gun! How do I do
this to him?
Not even one pellet decided to go around the fucking
wall. Jesus, fuck
me. Here he comes.
Okay, this fucking guy's
dead. It's over. I don't have to worry about
that anymore. It's done. Just don't lose
him, the toilet guy.
I'm fucking panicking right now.
What are you guys over here? Why?
What the hell?
Why? What the fuck? It threw me off
so bad. It threw me off
so badly. It just threw
me off so badly.
Okay, I don't even- Shoot these
guys. Shoot them!
Be done with it!
Is he- Is fucking- Is the butcher coming
over here? No.
Deal with the butcher first. Here comes the butcher,
right? I didn't-
Okay. Now I don't have a gun.
I don't have a gun. I don't have any bullets.
Same exact problem last time. No, we're good.
Here's one. Just a melee.
Oh fuck. Who's next? Who's
left? Anybody else up there? I have ten rounds.
No windows. Good. Just get in
here. No windows. One guy with a shotgun.
Nobody else in the room?
Just this one guy with a shotgun. That's it, right?
Watch out for the window.
Just go like this. Beep! Okay, I beeped him.
And now beep this guy.
And there's one more guy to beep over here.
This last guy right there.
Beeped him. Okay. Let's go back the other way.
That's it. It's just this
guy right here.
Is this a bad guy or
is this- I don't even-
I'm just gonna unload him when I open the room.
Okay, look. I don't want no
trouble. The save is open.
Just take what you want and go.
Look, I'm not the owner and he's not here.
I just run the club. Let's be
civil about this.
Alright, alright. I'll give you his address.
Just please don't hurt me. Can you get
shot from the residual
bullet or something?
Please just go now. He's on
114th place.
My goodness.
Anything else? Any money or something I can grab?
That's it, right?
God. Hey, look.
It's the car. Remember this?
I can feel my sanity
slowly slipping away during that level.
New weapon unlocked.
Combo, combo, combo, combo, combo, combo.
C+.
I'm alright.
New mask. We got Oscar.
And the weapon is a sledgehammer.
Showdown. This is the
last level. Final chapter.
Alright, let's take a look.
This is called darkness.
I don't even know what- I don't know if I want to do that.
I didn't get the secret mask. Survive two
bullets.
I want to start with the gun.
Okay, here it is.
Alright, two. Okay.
Just making sure there's nothing in here.
Holy fuck.
That was right when I opened the door.
Alright, I got another gun.
Another gun.
No, no. I want to get that- why did I do that?
I got it, thank god.
And who do we have here?
You must be one of the assholes
killing off my men.
Doesn't look like you are here to chat, so why don't
we get this over with?
Pick it up. Pick-
Okay. Leave him to me.
What the fuck?
Oh. Leave him to me.
What in the name of god
do- you don't even
give me a quarter of a second to react.
Where am I supposed to go?
Behind a wall? Leave him to me.
They swing
twice. The dash twice.
One, two-
Shit.
Damn it. Leave him to me.
Crush her head. Crush it. What do I do?
I'm not- not bad. I'm impressed.
I wonder what gave you this thirst for blood.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
Now I want to see who's
hiding behind the mask.
Like, not bad. I'm impressed.
I wonder what gave you this thirst for blood.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
Now I want to see who's hiding behind the mask.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna stand back here.
Come down here. You come fucking
get me over here. What the fuck?
Really? Why?
So I can't do that. She instantly
will kill me. She instantly throws a knife at me.
If you try to hide behind the
fountain. She just throws a knife
behind cover. Yeah, she
does. Alright, I'm just gonna
fucking sprint. Not bad. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. Odd.
Well, I fucked it up.
I'm just gonna run to the fountain right to the right.
Go ahead and see what happens. I need like a
knife. Jesus Christ.
This is ridiculous.
Why did they drop? Fucked here.
Ah, okay, so does he reload?
Okay, so he goes, reload.
Oh, fuck.
Did I get him? What do I do now?
I don't understand. Do I have to go
and attack him or something? He only has one
hand. One, two.
I did it. I can see where this
is going. I'll spare you
the pleasure.
What the fuck was that? I don't understand. My body
can't handle what just happened. What happened?
That's it, okay. Give me
this. Hello? Hello?
Hello, hello?
It's your first day. What's going on
down there? I'm trying to sleep. Is there anyone
there? Can you hear me? Hello? Goddamn
phones. I fucking hate these things.
Okay. There's more? Oh, shit.
It's the architect.
Oh, so you're the one causing the ruckus.
What's your business here? Actually,
why don't we skip the details?
I've done so many horrible things.
Garfield, no.
Nothing seems to really matter anymore, does it?
I'm not going anywhere, as you can see.
Just go ahead and do whatever you came here
to do.
Alright. Take the mask off.
Smoke a cigarette.
I'm one of my children from Pokemon.
Did I take a selfie? Oh, I threw the phone.
Okay. Yes, the iPhone
from the 80s.
The end. Well, that was fun.
That was, at some point,
it was kind of like chewing on
nails. But that was fun.
Music by Moon.
Very good. Very good
song. Very good
composing.
What's everybody doing?
It's not over.
Well, we're getting the credits. Is there
an after credits Infinity War scene?
So, should I press space
or something? Or are we just going to
watch all the credits?
Watch the credits, you boomer.
How is not watching the credits
a not boomer thing?
You usually get up from
the movie. Yes, that after credits
scenes have been a
fairly new phenomenon over
the last 15 years, 10 years or so.
It really was only in a
handful of movies and almost every movie
has an after credits scene.
That 33 year old boomer
that doesn't watch the credits.
But there was no reason to
20 years ago. When the movie
was over, you were like, oh, okay, that was
a good movie. And then you would
this is the time where you'd hear like
okay, did you get your phone?
Yeah, yeah. Don't leave any trash there.
Pick that up. Okay.
Anything left in your drink? Can I have a sip of your drink?
Let me check my phone.
Okay, you get keys?
That's what happened here
during the credits.
How can you be 33 and bald?
I'm not! Dude,
you understand that?
Hold on, listen to me, guys.
Some of you guys might be young and
so full of energy.
But let me tell you,
everybody starts to kind of thin a little bit
when they get to be 30 years old.
It happens. Some people
they get the real good
dice roll there and they don't lose any hair.
But for the most part, most of us
lose our damn hair after like
28.
28 to like 35
is when you start to really thin out a little.
So it's going to happen to all of us.
And some of you guys here have probably already
happened it to. It's fine.
There's nothing wrong with that. There's nothing wrong with it at all.
Maybe for you, Boomer, but I'll have
future hair. No.
No, your Fortnite skin doesn't count,
okay? Part 5!
Answers.
That's the
exact same sound effect.
That's the same sound effect.
You think I'm stupid, huh? I look stupid to you?
I know you aren't telling me
everything. You helped
me get into this mess. You told
me it would be exciting, didn't you? Well, I'm
fucking bored. I'm done, man. I've had it.
I want out and you're going to tell me how.
This stupid game is going to end now, you hear me?
All right, all right. Calm down, man.
You don't realize how much trouble
I'll be in. There's a guy
hiding out at the Blue Dragon.
A tiny Chinese restaurant
downtown. He knows more.
Just don't mention my name to anyone, okay?
I'm as good as dead anyways.
New character.
Is that...I don't know what that is.
Motorcycle?
I get to play as the cool character.
Safe house.
This is 16th chapter.
Three knives?
Like, I have a
butcher knife. What the
hell? Oh, there's a...I didn't
even...I didn't even see.
Okay, I gotta get back into this. I spent a whole, like,
30 minutes watching the credits.
Oh, you fuck.
We got...I crawl...can he shoot me from there?
Oh, idiot.
Any windows?
Wait, I can't...can I not pick up guns?
Is this this character's thing? He can't pick up
any...I can't pick up weapons.
Can I pick up anything? I have...it's only melee.
Alright, let's go! Let's go!
Fucking let's go!
Alright, can I pick up the knives that I drop?
Can I pick these up?
I'm so confused right now. What the fuck?
You can't pick up the knives.
You can only pick up missed
knives. Okay, well, now I'm
screwed again. I'm
dead. It's impossible.
Okay, so I cannot pick up knives unless I
miss. So just don't throw them.
Except throw it at this guy,
because I have to. Alright.
I need to get this one more
knife and use it on this guy, because
these three guys I can take out with the knife.
The question is,
what's the angle here?
Okay. Alright. There's no
door. Be aware of that. No
door. Got it.
Okay, here's the plan. I have to
run through. Fuck. Why are you
not noticing me? Why did you not
notice me? Why did you...I'm so
bad. I'm so mad that they
didn't notice me. What's going on?
Look here, punk. I've got some
things I need to know, so you better answer my
questions, okay? Who are the people
who keep leaving me messages?
And don't even think about bullshitting me now,
okay? I won't hesitate
to pull you apart if I have to.
I'll just tell you what I know,
just don't hurt me. I can't tell you
who's calling the shots, but they're using
Phenomenon
to sweep up their trails.
I only helped them set it
up at the station. You'll have to hack
into their system to trace them.
I went into hiding as soon as the job was finished.
They seemed to have some form of political
agenda. Scared the shit
out of me. I spent all my savings
on getting this rat hole. That's all
I have. Okay.
Charlie! Alright, now
roll the credits. That's the first
A of the evening.
We unlocked Rick. And
Charlie.
You have one message. Hello, it's Mark
from Miami Drop Off. It looks like you
missed your delivery last night.
We've got another parcel for you today.
Please drop it off at
...
Our clients will not tolerate further delays.
Fun Games
17.
How come I don't get to pick a mask?
What's going on with him?
Alright, that just freaked me out.
Anybody we need to throw a knife at?
Maybe. I think I can get this guy
without anyone knowing.
And his buddy?
I think I can do it all without
throwing a single knife.
So no, maybe not this guy right here.
I can definitely bait this guy in the room.
Now, the question is
can I kill this guy without throwing a knife?
That's gonna be very... I don't think so.
Maybe if he goes in the bathroom?
Got it. Okay. Clean.
Very clean.
Oh fuck, I thought that was a statue.
Whoa, you saw me.
Oh come on, you butt head.
Oh my god, I'm...
I can run into that.
Wait for him to come around again. Another dog. Good thing I waited.
Alright. Anybody left?
We got two down there, both melee.
Two guys with guns.
I should be able to get one too. Is there anybody else
in there that can shoot me
through the fucking window?
No. Okay. That guy can, but
they'll let these guys first.
So, I'm talking about a
go through, kill the...
I'm talking about wait till he goes up.
And then we'll talk. Alright.
Now we can talk. Oh fuck!
Okay, we're good.
Only these two guys left.
Don't get shot through the door.
This guy's gonna come at ya.
I seriously just panicked so hard
for no reason and this is the last guy.
One, two, three.
There's another guy! There's another guy!
Okay, we're fine.
My heart is killing me.
I kind of have a heart attack on camera.
I'm just gonna start going like...
Boomer gets heart attack.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go ahead, say it.
Go ahead. Chat wants face cam.
I don't have any clothes on. I'm not doing it.
Get Brandon.
There's another weapon that's been unlocked.
I'm not seeing these anywhere though.
Sludge hammer? I haven't seen a sludge hammer at all.
These people.
Give one new message. Hi, it's Jane.
It was nice to see you again. How about another date tonight?
Pick me up at
Northeast 158th Street around 9, okay?
And put on one of those nice suits you got.
You're taking me somewhere fancy this evening.
Show us your sweaty chest.
Sweaty chest.
Eighteenth chapter, prank call.
So, we got...
Uh, they have guns?
Um, okay.
Do it.
I didn't get points for that.
Uh, sorry. It was just a prank call.
I don't understand.
Wait, am I the guy at the computer?
I'm the guy at the computer.
Stay away from me.
Security, security. Look, sir.
Please don't kill me. Please, I'll do anything.
Interesting. North
87th place, huh? So that's where you've been hiding.
That's me.
Get out of here if you don't want to die.
Okay, have it your way.
Wait, do I have to fight myself?
What the hell is going on?
You had your chance.
What?
I'm so confused.
That's not...
That's not canon.
You guys, that's not canon.
That's what that comes from.
They were just in the way.
That's why everyone said that.
And that's why I got spoiled.
So, what really happens?
You have one new message.
Hi, it's Ben from Miami Funeral Home.
I'm just calling to tell you we have the tombstone you ordered done and ready to be delivered.
With a little luck, you should be getting it before the weekend.
Click.
Okay.
19th chapter.
Resolution.
Here we go.
It was the janitor the whole time.
What's this? Looks like I need a password to access this computer.
It was the janitor.
I could have killed the janitor too when I had a chance.
Okay, this is just
the Riddler from Batman.
Didn't this happen in Arkham City?
What's going on down here?
Who are you people?
We're playing a game, aren't we?
And you're one of our pawns, aren't you?
I guess this means game over.
Who are you working for?
You're the phone guys.
What a stupid question you really need to ask.
What does it look like to you, asshole?
You don't know anything, do you?
You think this is a game?
Why are you doing this?
We were bored, that's why.
Why would we need to justify our actions?
You've done far worse things than we have, haven't you?
Do you even know how much money we're making?
Why are you killing people?
We haven't killed anyone, you have.
They were all scum anyway, weren't they?
You think they deserve to live, do you?
That's it.
You seem disappointed.
What were you expecting?
I think we're through with your questions.
Yeah, your move, creep.
Okay.
Where's the password?
Phil? Okay, I just got Phil.
So I don't have a password.
Uh.
The password is the secret from each level.
Oh, okay.
You have to find letters throughout every level and put them in order in the computer,
meaning you have to play through again if you want the true ending.
Oh, okay.
That's pretty cool, though.
You gotta collect the pixels.
So I can't even access it. Alright.
Gotta catch them all.
Each letter for the password is a tiny dot, so they're hard to find.
That's cool.
Watch the credits, boomer.
That was an entire after credit sequence.
But we're earning another credit after the after credit sequence.
Now imagine if that happened.
Oh my god.
The after credits of Deadpool.
I can't believe it.
Cable's gonna be in the next movie?
Alright, now roll all the credits again.
Wait, they do that, actually.
Did they do that? That was fun.
No, that was really, that was good.
That was rage inducing in a lot of places, but
you know, you have to
put your fucking pants on and play the game and do it.
How many times did I die?
Okay, I'm gonna guess like 2,
2 like 40.
240? 300 plus?
No, no way.
Now I have to play Hotline 2.
Okay, I'm gonna play Hotline 2, but
I wanna save Hotline 2.
It was 351?
Yeah, I expelled
all of my energy
playing through this game.
I could not jump right into that again.
Right now. I'm gonna have to wait a few days.
You're gonna shit yourself playing
Hotline Miami 2.
I've hit gamer fatigue.
Watch the trailer for 2.
Hotline Miami 2 ramps up the difficulty a lot.
Well, we'll give it a try.
If I lose my mind, I lose my mind.
That's all good.
That was a neat little game. Yeah, it is.
Thank you for playing. Yeah, that was
a lot of fun.
That was just a fun game. It was very hard.
Well, no, but
it was.
You just kind of had to learn where to go and what to do
Sometimes you don't have to do that. You can play however you want.
Hey, thank you for making this game.
We got a new mask. Phil.
Louis.
Let me just see. I'm curious.
Let's just open up a random chapter
because I wanna see what those masks are.
Just curious.
Let's see. Walk fast.
Look further. Survive a bullet.
Here we go. Alright.
Good. I thought that just said
good shit.
Walk faster. More melee weapons.
Nice spot. French
translation.
French translation.
I just got an achievement for dying like that. I don't understand.
The game is just translating to French? How?
What? I missed.
Ah, fucking dog.
Do I have to throw it? R to restart.
It's not even in French.
I didn't want to let go of that. Why is it letting go?
I'm confused
right now. Am I breaking this thing
on people? I am.
Throw it. I get it. Okay.
It took me the whole game to figure that out.
I'm curious about this French translation though.
Beat one level with French.
Oh, fuck.
It only works on cutscenes.
Alright, well.
That was a fun game.
Play the bonus level.
Which one?
Bonus level. Chapter 14
18, 19. Bonus
chapter. Wait.
Special chapter. What the hell
is all this? Bonus chapter.
Does this game ever end?
I want to go with
hard to spot. Let's try hard to spot.
Holy fuck, he chased me all the way out there.
I need that French translation.
Oh my god.
Um, okay.
That's a little odd.
I can't shoot him out here.
Is that Minecraft Steve?
He's still alive. He's still alive.
I can't see that down.
Oh, shit!
My brain almost just
Now, I need
I need Jeffrey for this one.
Huge open room. I need to be able to see
everything. Window.
No, those aren't actual windows.
Dammit, they're behind a wall.
Alright, so we got a guy
down here. Really.
Why did he not shoot me the entire time
that I was doing that? What the fuck, man.
Really. Guns bug when
you're outside.
That's called a bunch of bologna.
That's a bunch of bologna.
That's, like, actually a fucking
bologna and cheese sandwich.
Is there anywhere else I can go?
I guess not, because I have to go that way.
And he gets to shoot me, but I can't shoot him.
Fuck off.
What? What?
Where did he even come from?
To find cover?
Oh my god. Why the hell does that exist?
Why can't Out of Bounds be back here?
Why does it have to be here?
Rush inside? That's not going to work.
He's over on every corner, here and down here.
These guys over here are going to shoot me.
How the hell? Are the tables covered
or am I going to get shot right in the face here in a second?
How am I going to get the other guy?
This?
From here? Rush him? No, I don't want to rush him.
This is covered.
Just waiting. Nobody comes out of their rooms
down here, do they? Is there anybody? There's probably some guy in the fucking bowling alley.
Holy shit!
There's a guy in the bowling alley!
Oh no. Oh boy.
I'm in trouble. Oh my god.
I'm dead. I'm dead. No I'm not. Get a bullet.
I picked up the one that didn't have any
fucking bullets!
Oh my god.
The fucking terrible luck.
The one gun that doesn't have a single bullet in it
is the one that I picked up. Are you
fucking serious? You've got to be
kidding me.
I'm so fucking annoyed by that.
There were like four guns on the ground
and the one that I picked up is the one that I let go.
Oh, I'm so annoyed.
I threw the rifle with bullets away?
I had to.
I was getting chased.
I need to keep this.
I can't see. Anything.
Where's the one where you just can't fucking die?
Holy shit. Give it to me.
Yeah, I'm pressing them very
hard.
Open room.
I'm about to destroy my entire office with a fucking
sledgehammer. And I'm not even going to put a
camera on too. So you won't even be able to capture it.
You'll just hear loud crashing noises.
Is there any gun down here?
I knocked him out, but that's not going to do anything
for me.
I need the knife.
Is he coming out?
He's coming out.
I'm so paranoid
about a guy just being right there. There's a guy right here
right there.
He's going to shoot me.
There's a bowling alley guy down here too.
There he is.
The only guy in here is this one.
What about across the fucking way? Yep, two guys with guns.
No windows here though.
Okay, go in this room.
Kill a guy on the toilet printer.
Why is he running over here?
Why are they all here?
Alright. Hey buddy. Oh.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, it's just this one guy here and that's it.
Oh fuck.
One round.
That's not going to cut it here, man.
There's still somebody alive down here, right?
No?
Is it one guy taking a piss and then I'm done?
Oh, do I have to kill these guys?
Nobody left, right?
There's nobody sitting down.
There's nobody hanging out over here, right?
It's just buying crap, Steve.
Thank God.
Oh, Dark Lord, grant us your eternal power.
Hey, Brandon.
Did you hear something just now?
Shut up, Willy.
Not while I'm chanting.
I can't get over there. That was fucking hard.
Can I not do anything about this?
No, I can't get in there.
Alright, bye.
Is there another door on the other side of the bar?
No. What am I going to go do?
Put her back together?
That's fucked up.
I've got to go there and tell them it's not okay.
I don't think that's going to work.
C plus streamer.
And a dart has been unlocked.
There was one more.
Let's take a look.
So we just go backwards.
So this is a bonus chapter,
highball, and then special chapter called
Exposed.
Let's go with
extra ammo.
Speaking of exposed, I understand why
the level is called Exposed.
Ah, shit.
Two guys in this...oh my God.
More than one guy.
Oh my God.
My asshole.
I'm serious.
I don't mean to be gross here, but holy shit.
What did I just pick up?
Can I play the slot machines?
No, they can't. Okay.
But he's going to run over here.
Is he going to shoot through this? He might.
What about up here?
Take the slow. I'm already doing well.
I don't need to freak out about this. Anybody up to the top left?
Doesn't look like it.
Nobody else. Alright.
Just a few more guys over there.
I'll take the other gun because it has more rounds in it.
Okay, don't try to cheese it.
Just do it right. Three guys left.
One guy at the back. Let's go for this guy first.
He's going to be quick. One, two, three.
That's it. Okay.
That actually was fairly easy.
That really wasn't that bad at all.
Why is it called Special Mission?
I didn't get very many style points.
Get it with a full combo.
I'm sure there are people that play this game.
That can do the wild, wild shit.
Alright, that's cool.
Is there anything else that I missed?
Is that special chapter? That's bonus chapter.
World record is 15 minutes for the whole game.
This one was good.
I almost lost my mind.
This one not so much though.
I guess for comboing and trying to find interesting rounds.
Probably.
Stream ending voice.
Well, pretty much.
But let me explain.
Let me explain the deal here.
EDF was supposed to be tonight.
But if you came in a little later.
I had to postpone it until tomorrow.
Because we wanted to get...
Star wanted to get ready.
He didn't really have all of his shit set up.
He needed to set up his Playstation 4 and capture stuff.
And he wasn't really ready to do it.
So we just said, alright, we'll just do it tomorrow.
So today is just kind of an extra stream.
While we wait until tomorrow.
So, EDF tomorrow with Star on italics.
Oh, you're throwing Star under the bus.
No, I mean...
I could have just played it today.
I could have just played EDF today.
But I would rather play with people that want to play.
You know what I mean?
If there's a multiplayer opportunity there.
Look, Star and I played the game last time.
EDF 4.
So if he wants to do it and we want to do it.
And we think it would be fun.
We're going to do it.
And that's what we're going to do tomorrow.
He just wasn't ready today.
But for the purposes of tonight.
I think I'll just call it there.
That was a lot of fun.
I will definitely be playing Hotline Miami 2.
Just not immediately.
Rat movies at a million views.
Alright, we'll watch it before I leave.
Thanks for joining me if you're taking off.
Let's see you tomorrow.
Probably around the same time.
Around like 3 to 3.30 Pacific.
EDF 5.
I'm not sure how good it's going to be.
But the last one was a blast.
And as long as you take it for what it is.
You can have a lot of fun in EDF.
So, see you tomorrow for EDF.
Let's call it there.
I'm going to get that.
Okey dokey.
So let's head over to the bits.
From a few four and a half hours ago or so.
Yeah, hope you join us tomorrow.
And then after tomorrow.
Let me take a look at the camera.
Because today is kind of pushed a couple things forward.
So the Birdhouse stream was going to be on Friday.
But because I'm streaming tomorrow.
So that'll be Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday.
So I'm going to take Thursday and Friday.
So I'm going to take Thursday and Friday off.
And then the Birdhouse stream will be on Saturday.
Birdhouse in the winter.
I need to make a birdhouse.
We'll watch Rat Movie at the end.
That'll be the sign off for the night.
Are there even any birds in Vegas?
I'm just realizing this right now.
Are there birds here?
There might not be any birds here.
Have you ever really seen a bird?
Yes, many times.
What the fuck German lives in Vegas now?
Yes.
I moved a few months ago from Massachusetts to Las Vegas.
Turkeys.
No, there are no turkeys in Las Vegas.
I can assure you that.
I haven't seen one.
It was last month?
I got here in October.
The wind took me around a bunch.
When did we land?
At some point.
It'll be about three months when we get to the first or second week in January.
How long are you going to keep up the balloon charade?
I broadcasted it, so it's real.
It's real.
I did it.
Anyways, thank you to GamingHash for the 250.
They say nice. Hey, nice.
Sticks Renegade, thanks for the dollar.
So I was getting a snack in the vending machine and I was about to pay via Apple Pay.
I dropped my phone and tried to catch it.
I involuntarily stuck my foot out.
I kicked the screen and broke it.
It doesn't sound like a good thing.
I hope it wasn't a nice phone because that's a pain in the ass to repair.
I'm sorry to hear that, Sticks.
Extra Cheesy, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jerm, I'm sorry for the low brow, edgy, crab-related constellation joke I made yesterday.
Please don't annihilate me.
I can do better, I swear.
Low brow.
This is a high brow stream.
Although I did just say something about my asshole like 13, 14 minutes ago.
But yeah, let's put Jot Hotline Miami 2 down for next week.
Because that actually was a lot of fun.
I'm actually into that.
I'm into it right now.
But thank you Extra Cheesy and don't worry about it, sorry.
Thank you Divus for the three bucks.
Every stream, Divus.
Every stream.
That's going to add up after a while.
But thank you so much.
Peaceful Haley, thanks for the one dollar.
And unfortunately can't go to Vegas.
But that's okay.
I've been trying to pursue my passion with streaming on Twitch and I think I'm doing okay.
Hopefully I can make this a career someday.
Love you Jerm.
I wish you the best of luck.
It's a tough world out here.
In Twitch.
Very competitive atmosphere.
Especially nowadays.
I get asked for advice on streaming.
It's hard to give advice.
And hard to kind of say, hey this is how you should do it.
Because I don't really have an answer.
Here's my advice, good luck.
That's not what I mean.
What I mean is everybody does it differently.
And it's hard to replicate somebody else's.
What somebody else did is not necessarily a recipe for success.
I know a lot of people compare themselves to other people.
And it's hard not to but you can't.
You just got to do you.
And hope that you can maybe gain some viewers.
And if you do, you do.
I wish anybody the utmost luck.
When they try to get into a passion or try to get into content creation.
Are you saying that this person is trying to steal your shtick?
No, no, I'm just in a general sense.
A lot of times you compare yourselves to other people.
And you, oh how'd they do that?
How did they do those things?
Steal your shtick.
No.
When am I gonna get a vibe?
Probably like a few years.
But no, good luck.
I don't know what games you play or what you do on your streams.
But hopefully you have fun doing it.
Because that's important as well.
You have to make sure the first thing that's on that list is.
Are you enjoying what you're doing?
The whole career aspect happens after that.
You know?
I think a lot of times people get into content creation.
They're like, alright, I can't wait to do this for a job.
But you have to be realistic.
You know?
It should go the other way around.
As long as you keep an open mind and you don't.
Because when I first started my YouTube channel.
It was based on, I just kind of do this and I want to do this.
It wasn't about like a career or choosing a career.
It just kind of happened.
Just make sure that you are doing what you want to do.
And you're having fun doing it.
And try to set realistic goals for yourself.
Even if that means on a week by week basis or a month by month basis.
Hopefully you could maybe take something from that.
I'm not an expert.
I really don't claim to be.
I'm not an expert on.
Here's how you market yourself.
And here's how you do this.
No, I don't fucking know.
You know what I mean?
What's the point of slow mode?
Make it so the chat goes slower.
But with that being said.
We will move on.
Good luck. Peaceful lately.
Thank you for the $1.
Thank you, Lakranda, for the $5.
Jerma, I have been listening to you since middle school.
It's been a long six years.
And I can't thank you enough on how much your streams and videos have impacted me.
Much love.
Thanks.
Thank you, Lakranda.
It's a shock on a daily basis when I hear people say things like that.
I'm incredibly happy that you can take anything from this stream.
Or from the videos that I've ever made.
So thank you.
Dr. Clay, thanks for the $1.
Jerma, quick.
Duck.
Duck before it's too late.
Duck?
Like in the game?
What are you talking about?
Duck.
Right?
You can't duck in Hotline Miami.
Wholesome content.
He has headphones on.
I don't even have my headphones in right now.
But thank you, Dr. Clay, for the warning four hours ago.
I didn't duck four hours ago.
And I don't know.
Was this a streamer that mentioned his ass?
Yes it is.
Wholesome in quotes.
I don't live by labels, man.
You know what I mean?
I just do meat.
Yeah.
Labels.
Get rid of them.
Yeah.
That's too much coffee.
I'm not drinking anymore.
Why am I drinking coffee at 9 o'clock at night?
What am I, my fucking mother?
My mother drinks like three coffees a day.
And she'll sip on one at like 11 o'clock at night to go to bed.
I'm turning into my mother.
Anyways, thank you, Dr. Clay.
Thank you, ExtraCheesy, for the $1 watching.
You formulate possible strategies and play this game.
It's sort of like if there was a model of Terminator
whose processor was an old Texas Instruments grade school calculator.
Thank you, ExtraCheesy, but I beat it.
And it only took about four hours and 10 minutes to beat it.
So come on.
I only died like 265 times.
That's pretty good.
I got Bs and Cs.
At the very beginning of the stream, we made sure to talk about Bs and Cs are okay.
I didn't get any Fs.
I didn't get any Ds.
But thank you, ExtraCheesy.
Thank you, Swiggity Swanky, for the $1.
What if I happen to wanting to play a relaxing game before EDF tomorrow?
This game will take a year off of your life.
It absolutely did.
But I think it was worth it.
It was fun.
ChubbiestThread, thanks for the $20.
They just say fail fish, fail fish.
Fail fish, fail fish.
I must have done something worth facepalming for.
But thank you for the $20.
Really appreciate that.
Thank you so much.
PeanutChan, $50.
Big money from PeanutChan.
Thank you again if you're still here.
Flanktank gave $5.
So I was watching this random vid from my YouTube homepage
and I had to double take it.
You are now famous.
What are you talking about?
Let's turn this down for a second.
I've got to get out of this.
You were on Ellen.
Can you imagine if I was?
Imagine if she was like,
okay, so let's take a look at this weird guy.
He's kind of a weirdo.
Here he is on the screen there.
And he just gets up and starts dancing.
And it's me doing the Fortnite dance.
So next up on the program,
kind of a weirdo, he's a weirdo.
Here he is.
I like him though.
He's a really nice guy.
But there he is.
Jerma985.
Odyssey DLC after a year.
And you know what happens?
Someone goes, fuck you.
I'm making my own kingdoms then.
And I'm making Bob-omb battlefield too.
For good measure.
And because Nintendo cracks down so hard on games,
the only way you can really access this kind of stuff
is through homebrew.
Only to Iranians.
Sanctioned only to Iranians.
Why am I being linked?
What did he say?
Nintendo wants everything that's made
to be sanctioned under their own approval.
But then they don't give people what they want.
For example.
Oh, I walk by on the green screen.
What the fuck?
I just walk by on the green screen.
What?
Why?
What the fuck?
That's fucking funny.
I didn't even pick up on it.
I didn't even see it.
That's wild.
Funky Mouse also made a green screen video.
And it was fucking wild.
But anyways, thank you Flank Tank.
Flank Tank for the $1.
Kraft tank thanks for the $1.
They say hello, hello.
Flank Tank again for the $1.
Nightbot deleted my bit message because I had a link.
And I was not a sub.
So I had to sub.
And there it is again.
Jesus.
Well, thank you Flank Tank for your $12 here.
$11.
For sharing the link.
Thank you.
That was interesting.
Somebody wrote, I was looking at the Reddit
maybe like a few weeks ago or two weeks ago or something.
And somebody wrote, I don't think he realizes just how like
how he's going to appear all over the place now.
Like even people that don't even.
And I thought about this too.
It's like even people that don't even know this channel
or watch this channel.
Somewhere on some page or some website.
Just oh free green screen footage.
I'm just going to appear in random fucked up shit.
Random crazy shit.
Random videos.
I have no control over it.
I have no idea.
It's like seven years from now.
I'm going to be fucking Chad walking on somebody's random video.
20 years are going to go by.
My hair is going to be white.
And I'm going to be doing like the Disney Channel opening
for some new like up and coming YouTuber in like 25 years.
What hair?
It's going to be nice.
It's going to be white.
It's going to be slicked back with grease.
I'm going to get just like I'm going to get like oil like olive oil.
I'll just slick it back.
Bright white.
But thank you.
Thank you to Dark Star 700,000 Games.
Thanks for the $1.
I have a Python practical exam tomorrow.
And I'm afraid all the programming knowledge
I've accumulated throughout the semester
will leave my head the moment I walk in the classroom.
Wish me luck.
No, you think that but you'll be fine.
You'll wake up tomorrow after being like oh shit.
You'll sit down.
The paper will be in front of you.
And you'll just pull it out of your memory.
That's how it works.
Just get some good sleep.
That's one thing a lot of people,
big mistake people make when they're in college
is they prioritize cramming all night before the exam
and getting 45 minutes of sleep
and then just slumbering just to class
with your eyes half closed.
And then you're just delirious.
And you actually do better.
Your mind retains information
when you have a full night's rest to process
and kind of break it all down.
Get a good night's sleep.
Go over some basic stuff when you wake up.
It's better for you if you do it that way.
Don't sleep so your memory doesn't escape from your ear
as you lay in bed.
I skip a good night's sleep to watch your stream.
Don't tell me what to do.
Hey, some people it works.
It never worked for me.
I would get better grades when I just was sitting there going
okay so I have all this stuff I need to remember.
I kind of know it but let me just go over it
and repeat over and over again information for fucking 12 hours
and then like go to class.
Wait, what? I forget.
What if you just go to sleep and you study a little bit.
I'm not saying don't study.
Get some good knowledge in your head.
Eat a good dinner.
And I'm talking fish.
Eat fish before dinner.
And then go to sleep.
Wake up and eat some more fish.
You want like salmon.
You want tuna fish before you go to bed.
And then you want salmon in the morning.
You want those omega-3s to be just
I can't go high anymore.
I really am getting old.
Let's try that again.
You want those omega-3s in your head to go
See?
Fuck, I still got it.
So then when the omega-3s go into your neuro area
it's much easier for memory, for cognitive ability.
It's great.
Fish.
Eat salmon tonight if you have a final tomorrow.
Omega-3, is that a new steam game?
No, it's for your brain.
Anyways, good luck on your finals, guys.
Where am I going to buy salmon at 12 p.m.?
At the grocery store at 12 p.m.?
Are you talking about 12 a.m.?
No, and do not supplement this with like a
Filet-O-Fish from McDonald's.
It's not the same thing.
You may as well eat cardboard with fish flavoring.
That's not the same deal.
You don't do that.
Oh, he said eat fish.
I'm going to eat like four Filet-O-Fishes
and have diarrhea in the morning.
That's not going to help you.
That's going to be bad.
And if you can't get fish, then eat
a bunch of macaroni tomorrow morning.
Load up on some carbs.
Carb out in the morning so you just get brain.
You got like the energy.
You know what I mean?
No, lose the cheese.
Lose the cheese.
Don't put cheese on that.
Just macaroni.
Cooked macaroni.
Drizzle a bunch of olive oil on.
Sprinkle a little bit of maybe a little bit of Parmesan.
You know what I mean?
Parmesan.
Am I saying that right?
How do you?
Parmigiano.
It's Parmigiano, right?
How do you actually say that word correctly?
It's like Parmigiano, right?
That's the correct pronunciation.
It's not Parmesan, right?
It's like Parmigiano.
Yeah, it's Parmigiano Reggiano, right?
Okay, good.
Boomer pronunciation.
Well, that's what they do on the Food Network when I watch Chopped.
The guy's like, okay, so what we got?
What's in the basket?
Well, what I've got here is I've got a salmon steak.
I've got some salsa.
And then what's over here where I've got some Parmigiano Reggiano?
Okay, I'm like, all right, now I know how to say that now.
Why is it always the same three judges?
Because they're experts.
Food Network uses fake ingredients?
What?
Hey, how are you doing?
Can I get a sausage mushroom pizza?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why would you put that in all caps?
What if you're not watching Guy Fiery?
I've seen every single episode of Diner's Drive-ins and Dives.
Every single one.
There's not one episode I've missed.
What happens in episode 34?
He goes, this?
That's killer.
You knocked it out of the park, man.
I just, there it is.
Anyways, thank you to Drosophilia for the $1.
Hey, Jeremy, I used to use a razor death adder for a few years,
but the clicks started messing up and I had to get a new mouse.
I've been using a PIC Tech mouse for several months now.
It's insanely good for how cheap it is.
And I promise the customization software isn't malware.
Thank you, Drosophilia.
I just got this, though.
That's the worst part.
And then they say I'm not sponsored, I swear.
I didn't think you were.
It's alright.
Uh, Drum Mage Door.
Drum Mage Door.
Thanks for the $10.
Greetings from Finland.
Glad to see you playing one of my favorite games of all time.
I hope you'll suffer through the second one, too.
That one also has a hard mode.
I probably will never do it.
But thank you for the $10, I really appreciate it.
I hope you'll suffer.
Thank you.
Uh, Parfalo Mule.
Thanks for the $1.
Can you be my father for five minutes, please?
Um, how about five seconds?
Son?
Okay.
Thank you to one, uh, Demonic Cucumber.
Thanks for the $1.
Hey, Jeremy.
I'm here to say, I'm here to pay my comedy dues.
I'm in a worse place than last month, but your streams are pulling me through.
Thank you for the wonderful community.
PS, anyone else think that the Jexy mode looks like a guy doing Coke?
What?
I don't think so.
This looks like my face.
Thank you, Demonic Cucumber.
Uh, sorry to hear that you're in a bad place.
Take care of yourself.
Thanks for sticking around.
Hopefully you get better and feel better soon.
Thank you.
For the $1.
And Smelly Boy, thanks for the $1.
Hey, remember when Demon Lord Zaraxos played Five Nights at Freddy's?
I do and I won't let you forget.
Yeah, that, that is a video that I, I did not delete.
Or did I?
I may have deleted that.
Yeah, that video exists, I think.
Does it still exist?
It might not.
It's still up.
No, it's not.
All right, we're going to watch this video right now.
Because this is going to be fucking painful for me, but I, maybe not.
We'll see.
Five Nights at Freddy's.
Hey, what's going on, everybody?
It's me, Demon Lord Zaraxos here.
Uh, you're probably wondering where, where's Jerma?
What happened to him?
How come he's not doing this video?
Well, it's because I have taken over his soul.
And I will only release it after playing around a Five Nights at Freddy's.
Because everyone wants to see Five Nights at Freddy's.
And who better than me?
You got to be ten at EP.
The lord of all hells and demons and hatred.
I'm not scared of anything.
What could I possibly be afraid of in this little shit game?
I don't know.
We'll find out very shortly.
Let's go ahead and play a new game.
This guy sounds kind of like an asshole.
I'm going to ignore him.
Let's go camera 4B.
That's what we're on.
It's too stretched.
Hold on.
Let me, let me reset it then.
So how come it's not happening over here?
That guy has to be stretched, apparently.
Supposed to be 1080, man.
Oh, whatever.
You get the idea.
Let me turn this off.
Camera 5.
It's in full screen.
Is it bad?
I don't like birds.
Oh, this sucks.
Camera 1A.
Camera 7.
Close the door.
What the fuck was that?
Okay.
Well, that was a little weird.
That was like a bird in my face.
I wasn't scared.
I was not scared of that.
I was just startled at it.
It jumped up at me and it scared me.
So obviously, that'll scare you.
I wasn't, don't think that I was scared though.
Because like you were scared.
I wasn't the one that was scared.
It was you actually.
And you look, there's a blinking light over there now.
Freddy.
This has 300,000 views.
I'm embarrassed.
Where are you, Freddy?
You can't hide from demon lord Zaraxos.
I will boil you.
I will eat your flesh and tear off the bones.
And use them as toothpicks in my stew.
If you think I'm going to be scared of your...
One of them is missing.
Okay, one of them is missing now.
There was a rhinoceros that was here before.
And he just ain't here.
This bear might have moved.
I might have seen him somewhere.
I don't know.
Pirate Cove is out of order.
Let's just go back and make sure there's nobody potentially trying to kill me.
But I will kill them first.
That's what you need to remember from this whole thing.
I will kill them first before they try to kill me.
We're halfway through this video.
There is a guy standing there.
There is a guy in a funny little suit standing there now.
And I don't really know what to do.
Should I...
He's still there, okay.
I got it, it was so boring.
I had to like...
Hold on, let's keep going.
Oh, there's more.
You get killed by the people, the participants in the suits.
I don't know why you would ever do such a thing.
You come work for me.
At least there's benefits down in hell.
You know, you get a good dental plan.
You get good dental.
You know, we're gonna continue.
I'm going to get...
I don't even know what the goal here is.
I do not see him anywhere.
Where is he?
He's in the kitchen.
The son of a bitch is in the kitchen.
We're doing the same thing again.
That means he's coming out here.
Yeah, he's in the kitchen.
No, he's in this one.
Oh, by the way, I remember this video.
I actually have a distinct memory.
This video had a lot of dislikes.
I remember uploading it.
And after those of you guys that don't know about like YouTube-ing and making videos,
I would sit there after an upload and I would go,
Oh, okay, let me see.
Did it publish correctly?
Did it go into subfeeds?
And what are people saying?
And okay, like the first hour or so of a video being live,
I kind of hung out to see what people were saying and how it was being judged
and what people were saying about it.
And like 40 dislikes came in really quickly.
And that was a lot.
I remember that back here,
this is back when I think the channel had maybe like 100,000 subs,
125,000 subs at that point.
So I was not used to like 100 dislikes over the course of the first hour.
And I remember going, what do I do about this?
Do I delete this video?
Should I delete this video?
I actually was going to delete this video.
Okay, now he's right here.
He's going to be right here.
No, he's not right here.
Where is he?
Oh, he's right.
Okay, he's right here.
He's literally staring at me.
It's 4 a.m.
Don't let them come in.
Do not let them come in.
Is the door locked?
Both of the doors are closed.
You stay where you are.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
None of that.
We're not going to have any of that.
I must have had like nothing to make for a video today.
It's closed.
We're at 4 a.m.
now.
Just got to get through the night.
No, no.
I got through the night.
I did it.
I was staring.
I got through the night.
This is come on.
We won.
I won the game.
No, the same.
This is two videos.
I was staring at him.
What the hell?
Oh, boo, here he comes.
He's going to come.
Oh, oh, boy.
Don't get scared.
Oh, get them.
That's not my mouse.
You know what?
I'm just I'm just going to go play Super Mario Brothers.
It's just I don't want to play this anymore.
Jerma, Jerma, your soul is now free.
I'm releasing you.
Whoa.
Where?
What happened?
Well, just calm down.
Calm down.
Everything's OK.
Everything's all right.
I have it under control.
I stole your soul so I could get it.
I stole your soul.
I stole your soul so I can come to Earth to play Five Nights at Freddy's.
Oh, that sucked.
All right.
I'm deleting that video.
I'm deleting.
It's deleted.
All right.
Anyways, let's we're almost at the end of the bits here.
Thank you to thank you Smelly Boy for reminding us of that video.
Demonic Cucumber, thanks for the $1.
$2 actually here.
I was introducing your streams to my mom on the way to therapy yesterday.
She really liked the videos.
Also, we both agree that you look really attractive for $33.
Anyway, keep up the good work Mr. Boomer.
All right.
For $33.
Thank you Demonic Cucumber for the $1.
Ugly old man.
Come on.
Get out of here.
Boomer is attractive to mother.
Oh, come on.
Thank you Demonic Cucumber for the $1.
Thank you Leather Jacket for the $5.
I've been waiting for this day for a long time.
Good to see you play one of my all-time favorites.
That was good.
That was really fun.
That was a great game.
Thank you Leather Jacket.
Thank you Leather Jacket for the $5.
And for being in the game.
That was you.
Demonic Cucumber again says, thanks for the $1.
Loud crashing noises should be the name of your autobiography.
Claire of Astora, thanks for the $4.
So when is Hotline Miami 2 planned to be played?
I would probably say next week.
Next week.
Maybe that's the first thing we'll do next week.
Let's just start with that and play it.
Let's see.
How long is it lengthwise compared to the first one?
That was about four and a half hours.
It's a little bit longer.
It's like three times as long.
Really.
Way longer.
So what is it?
Is it like a 10 to 12 hour game?
8 to 10?
All right.
We might be able to do that in one stream.
I might just completely hunker down.
Why didn't EDF happen tonight?
I pushed it to tomorrow because we wanted to make sure that we could get the party
of three that we wanted.
We wanted to play with a party of three.
So I didn't want to just play by myself or just one person if it's more fun
with like three or four.
So we have it's happening tomorrow.
Yes.
Star and italics.
Those are the two.
Thank you to Peel Peel Peeling for the five dollars.
No message.
Thanks for five bucks.
Dinky Duper.
Thanks for one dollar.
I had a lot of fun watching your PG Hotline Miami stream tonight.
PG.
I've actually never played it either.
By the way, what the hell was with that missing easy shots joke?
Maybe I'm not Boomer enough to get it.
Have a great night.
Man, excited for tomorrow.
Well, whatever.
Thank you, Dinky Duper.
Thank you, Timmy Tim Tam for the one dollar.
Back to your regularly scheduled bookstore conversation.
Oh, right.
OK.
Thank you to Peel Peeling again for five dollars.
I hate to get up in the morning.
Me too.
What time do you get up?
At six o'clock.
Why do you get up so early?
I have to be at work by seven.
I don't get up until eight.
You're lucky.
What do you do?
I own a bookstore.
What time does your store open?
At eight thirty.
I hate to get up.
I hate to get up in the morning.
Me too.
What time do you get up?
At six o'clock.
Why do you get up so early?
I have to be at work by seven.
I don't get up until eight.
You're lucky.
What do you do?
I own a bookstore.
What time does your store open?
At eight thirty.
The best part about Daily English TV, which is the best YouTube channel I think that currently exists.
This video has 39 views.
Daily English TV.
What a great channel.
I think it's so you can have more than 30 now.
Yeah, and probably all of them are from this channel.
But thank you to Timmy Tim Tam.
But Peel Peel Peeling, thanks for five dollars again.
Boulder City here.
You'll become more native when you see a stream of quail run across the road.
A stream of quail run across the road.
You definitely should sub to that channel.
Quails are like ducks, right?
Quail is like a mix between a duck and a chickadee, am I correct?
Aren't they like little mini ducks?
Quail.
Yeah, look at this weird bird.
It's like a duck chickadee thing.
It looks type in chickadee into Google.
You type in chickadee and you tell me that that's not a chickadee.
That's like a weird duck chickadee.
I'm sorry, guys, but that's a duck chickadee.
That's a that's a duckadee.
Thank you Peel Peel Peeling.
Watch out for those quails.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Clueless sniper.
Thanks for the one dollar.
No message.
Thank you.
Dr. Clay.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Thank you.
I was hoping you would literally duck in real life.
I was trying to make a time travel joke, but it failed.
Anyway, take care.
Thank you.
Maisie kit for the one dollar.
They say reasonable Frieza.
It's Frieza from Dragon Ball Z.
Set reasonable goals for yourself.
But remember, it's OK to take a break if you need it.
Wholesome Frieza.
Did he say this in the show?
I own a bookstore.
He did.
That's interesting.
I thought he was like evil.
Well, I guess.
Whatever.
OK.
KXZ 501.
Thanks for the ten dollars.
Thank you, KXZ.
Great watching you power through Hotline Miami.
Looked like a tough fight, but you did good, friend.
Plus, it'll be good training for Hotline Miami 2, so be ready for that.
Lol.
L-U-L.
I am looking forward to it and not looking forward to it at the same time.
It's going to be very interesting.
But really appreciate the ten dollars here, man.
Thank you.
Mr. Pigeon, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey, I hope the ball thing isn't getting to you.
For thirty, your hair is doing incredibly well.
I'm twenty, and it's happening to me.
You have an iron brain for not letting it get to you, bud.
No, it's alright.
Let me just fuck around on this channel.
Everyone's just having fun.
It's alright.
I know.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
It's all in good fun.
It is.
Doesn't bother me.
It's OK.
Hey, Flugboy, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, Eve's Flugboy here.
Hope you're doing well.
Finals are a thing this week, and I'm feeling the pain.
And I'm hoping my mental perk up after it...
I'm hoping my mental perk up after it just wanted to let you know how much your streams
make me happy.
Thank you.
Thank you, Eve's Flugboy.
Good luck with your finals.
It's a stressful time.
Just take it easy.
Do what you can.
Try not to drive yourself crazy, because I don't...
Let's talk about education, OK?
Can we talk about the education system?
Listen to this.
Let's hear me out.
Let's just...
Isn't this interesting?
Why do finals...
Why do they do them just all in the same fucking week?
Why wouldn't you...
You can't spread that out so...
Does it have to be seven major tests in a row that determine 25% of your whole
grade?
Why you can't have something happen?
There's no way to spread that out to make it easier for the students.
Some schools do it.
I don't know why.
I don't understand.
How would you make a schedule for that?
I don't know, but that's tough to do.
To make students do 20% of their grade four days in a row on every single class.
My final on Thursday is 65% of my grade, and what's up with that shit?
What?
No, that's not...
Why?
You know how many...
OK, listen.
You know how many people in the world don't test well?
You're intelligent, you're retaining information, but you don't test well.
That should...
Come on.
This has got to be more indicators of somebody's knowledge retention than one single
50% of your grade test.
People were not born to do tests.
I know.
What?
Why?
Give our students a little bit of slack.
I was there.
I remember that shit.
And not all college teachers care to teach.
No joke.
I had a bad teacher who was an hour late every class.
Is that for real?
Yeah.
I don't know.
It just seems a little odd to base your entire education around four days.
It's like, you did the lab work, you were there, you were in class every day.
Gosh darn it.
Give a little slack to our students.
Anywho, thank you to Butt Squire for the $1.
This is a game from a developer I've been following for ages by the name of CosmoD
called The Norwood Suite that I'd love to see you play on stream.
Cosmo's in a band called Archipelago with his friends and uses the band's music as
a soundtrack for his games.
It's super soothing.
I don't know how you feel about walking simulators, but you should definitely check
it out.
Here's a link to the trailer.
I will.
I will definitely watch the trailer and see if it's something that I'd be willing
to play.
For sure.
No you won't.
What do you mean no I won't?
I will watch this trailer.
He won't.
Oh my god.
He'll get back to you on that.
Come on.
Give me a little bit.
Give the streamers some slack, okay?
I just gave students slack.
Now I'll have the streamers slack.
He already forgot.
Uh, thank you butt Squire.
I will definitely take a watch and see if it's worth my streaming time.
Which it probably is.
I say it's worth my time.
What does that mean?
He won't.
Stop.
It is worth it.
It's probably a very good game.
He never watches it, italics told me.
That's not true.
Hey moo means moo, thanks for the one dollar.
I took your advice, grabbed a fish out of the local river and ate it raw and I still
failed.
Thanks a bunch.
Hey eating fish does not guarantee good grades.
Eating fish prepares you mind for knowledge retention and memory pulling.
Okay?
It's not a guarantee.
Hey eternal, whoa thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jermbo, you ever planning on going back to picking oblivion back up or has
that ship sailed?
Love the streams, looking forward to 2019.
German 95 reboot season.
Now we don't do any reboots here.
Right now, no.
Unfortunately.
There's just too much to do.
There's so many things that are planned and so many things to play and do.
Going back to oblivion right now, I can't do it.
Maybe if I need to, okay what am I going to play today?
I don't know.
I mean I did that today.
But my brain functions on, I don't know, it might happen, it might happen tomorrow.
It might happen never.
It might happen in a couple weeks.
I base every stream off of what's happening today or the next day.
I'm very scattered.
Still won't stream ultimate.
I got scared to stream ultimate.
There were resident sleepers in the chat when I said I was going to stream.
I didn't even press the play button.
And it was like, I don't know, resident sleeper.
I was like, already?
That was just a joke.
Well there's no context with resident sleeper.
It's just resident sleeper.
Okay, there needs to be a Kappa sleeper.
Like, oh I'm just fucking around.
Like have Kappa with his head tilted with a Z coming out of his eye or something.
You know what I mean?
Like snoring.
Because then I would know.
Kappa sleeper.
Oh look it's boring but I'm just kidding.
It's not.
Go ahead.
Kappa sleeper.
I'll look into it.
We'll see.
Hey Ginzebo.
Thank you Ginzebo for the $10.
Kind of hard to catch your streams here in Sweden.
But here's for years of laughs and Chadwalks.
Cheers.
Thank you so much for the $10.
And I do have to apologize to people in the EU.
I'm really sorry.
I moved even further back in the United States.
So it's very difficult to try to please every time zone living in Pacific time.
For me to do that, but I mean it still would be hard.
Because if I start streaming at let's say 11 or 12, 11 a.m.
A bunch of North American audience now is I'm doing at work, I'm at school, I can't watch.
It's very difficult to try to pinpoint like a perfect time.
So I start my streams around 2 or 3 p.m. in the afternoon here.
Which is 6 o'clock Eastern, which is like 11 p.m.
11, 10, 11, 12 p.m.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could stream at 8 in the morning and be able to have everybody watch.
But it's just time zones.
But I did, I have pulled back.
We used to start consistently at 7 plus Eastern.
And since moving to Vegas, I've tried to pull that back an hour or so.
At least like an hour or two.
And tonight we started at 7.
We started at 7 yesterday, but we've been pretty consistent with starting at around 5 or 6 Eastern.
Just eat fish.
But thank you for the $10 and welcome from Sweden.
Thank you.
Emooch, thanks for the $2.
Pogchamp, hey Jerma, wish I could have been here for the whole stream, but it appears I missed it.
It's okay though, much love and when are you streaming again?
Tomorrow.
I'm gonna be playing EDF5 tomorrow with Star and Italics.
Hey Darkstar, thanks for the $1.
Let me get this straight, I should wake up, eat fish, or cheeseless macaroni?
Figure out how the hell to say parmesan, take the final, eat a filet-o-fish for dinner, and then have horrible diarrhea.
Thanks for the advice.
Is that what came out of my mouth?
Is that what you guys took from that?
No, I said don't eat filet-o-fish.
That was verbatim your advice.
I don't believe that.
But thank you Darkstar.
Thank you Mr. Pigeon for the $1.
Here's sausage, mushroom, and pepperoni.
Sausage and mushroom pizza.
I don't get it.
This is what the person, that person was in here screaming that.
Was that the guy that made the video?
Was he in there saying that in this stream?
That's the video.
That says it was a million views.
Well thank you for that Mr. Pigeon.
Mu means moo, thanks for $1.
Guy Fieri bore like diarrhea.
I ate at his restaurant and I can't stop shitting.
That's the best joke of the night.
Without even a doubt in my mind.
Diarrhea.
No, my joke is good.
I know, but like come on.
Diarrhea.
You should put that on a bottom.
Put that on a top text, bottom text.
You just got on the front page of like every reddit.
Hey Smarky, thanks for the $1.
Hey Jerma, I dislocated my knee recently.
Sorry to hear that.
So I've been cooped up in my house.
Thankfully you've been here to keep me occupied in the meantime.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
That hurts.
Hope you recover swiftly.
Thanks for choosing this channel to hang out.
Thank you.
Maybe the top page of every reddit in 2012.
You'd be surprised.
Hey Extra Cheesy, thanks for the $1.
Here's another dollar because I wanted to balance my mean calculator moment.
Comment.
With this nice one by saying you're my favorite internet dude
and your funny hotline jump scare screams
make me go hee hee ha ha.
Also I'll bump you up to a T183.
You genius of a streamer.
Make me go hee hee ha ha.
Thank you Extra Cheesy.
Appreciate it.
It's time for slime, thanks for the $3.
You should re-release all your old videos with an audio track of you giving embarrassed commentary.
Reaction videos of my own videos.
Where I'm embarrassed of my previous...
I'm embarrassed of my children or something.
Like what does that even...
Like ah you know my son was gonna be a doctor.
Now he just screams swears on the internet.
He was supposed to be a lawyer.
Now that's my dad.
Whoops.
That's the boomer voice.
Are you still drinking coffee?
Fuck I am.
You're right. I need to stop doing that.
I drank the whole thing this whole time.
What does he do? He's a streamer.
What does he stream? Online co- no online media.
Now we've watched a couple of the
videos from before.
From years ago.
I love all of my video children.
Okay?
There was a reason why I made them, each one of them.
Except for the Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3 ones.
I...
Those, I don't have those anymore.
And maybe another
40 or 50 different videos
that I may have removed because
I didn't think they were good at all.
Come on. I have...
I had like 975 children.
I am essentially like a beehive.
Okay?
I can't see and take care of all of my children.
Make 10 more.
Have 10 more. Bring them back.
Let us click.
No I'm not gonna let you click.
So you guys can put a
penile shaped apparatus on the screen.
No.
You lost privileges forever.
But thank you, it's time for slime for the three bucks.
Thank you lazy look for the one dollar, what's your voice line
when someone opens the germa game I'm making?
Uh...
Duh.
That's pretty good I think. I think that's good.
Or if you want like a good one, how about like
Welcome to the game! No, that's weirdly bad.
How about
No?
Strap yourself in!
How about
I hope you enjoy
playing my game.
But it's not my game because I didn't make it.
Somebody else didn't. I bet it's gonna be
real fun.
How about I got one for you.
You can do whatever you want with this so here you go.
Softwave Studios presents
You fucked it up with
the sub sound.
Whatever.
It's staying. Hey thank you
Shooshroom for the one dollar rats. Rats were the rats.
And lazy look thank you for the
another dollar here. By the way all your 2013
to 2014 YouTube videos are absolute
perfection. Seriously.
Thank you. I did have a lot of fun
making YouTube videos.
It was great. Mr. Dunwich
thanks for the one dollar. They say I have bad
news. What's the bad news?
Thank you flaming pizza for the one dollar.
How you doing today? Please know
you're loved and appreciated. Thank you
flaming pizza.
Don't be upset.
I'm sure the insurance will pay for it.
The company didn't take out insurance
this time. You're kidding.
No. But my
boss says he'll pay for it.
See? Everything will be alright.
But he'll probably never let me
work at an art show again.
Oh don't think so negatively.
I'm having
trouble trying to figure out if these
are actual people reading
a script or if they are bots.
Just really well trained bots.
What's wrong? I can't
tell. I really screwed
up at the office.
Oh. And I got fired.
That's too bad.
But it's not the end of the world.
No. Actually
Barbara and I broke up.
You are kidding.
And it is the end of the world.
Oh don't think so negatively.
What?
That went back and forth very very quickly.
Actually
Barbara and I broke up.
You are kidding.
Actually
Barbara and I broke up.
You are
kidding.
And it is the
end of the world.
Think so negatively.
I don't never get
sick of that. Thank you
Mr. Dunwich. Flaming Pizza
they said how are you? I'm doing well. Hope you're doing
well as well. I said well
like seven times.
Thanks for the one dollar. We should all watch Norwood's
sweet trailer together. Think of it as a bonding experience
with chat. Say do you like
pie? Cue it up.
It's Danny. Thank you. It's Danny for the
one dollar. Hey Jeremy will you ever consider playing Hotline Miami 2?
If so when? By the way great stream. Yes
playing Hotline Miami 2 next week.
Gonna try to do it all in one
stream but we probably won't.
I might have to break that up into two streams so I don't
lose my absolute mind.
Cause I could see myself getting exhausted
and getting very very sledgehammery.
You know what I mean?
You guys know what I'm talking about.
But thank you Danny.
Toby Laron
Ed. Thank you for the
one dollar. What a terrible fucking pronunciation
that just gave. Hey Jeremy do you have any
advice after a bad break up?
Not my first time but it always feels pretty bad after
it happens. Also love you streams really helps
every time when things are rough.
Honestly here's
the best thing that I could say.
If you're having romantic trouble
and you know it's a break up or
whatever right?
Eventually
eventually it's not gonna be
as bad. Eventually you'll move on.
It's just right now
right now it sucks.
And right now you're thinking this is fucking
the worst. This is the worst thing ever.
How am I ever gonna recover from this?
In a month or two
after like a couple of months
you'll just start to
you'll start to move away from it.
It takes time. And it's the worst because
right now everything fucking sucks.
Right now. But if you can reach
into the future to future you
you'll be able to see that
that future you will look back and be like hey man everything's
fine. Everything's fine.
Might take a little while. But the last time I
had like a real oh no
like romantic
problem or break up or anything it was
I wish like future me could have just
looked back and been like hey dude everything
everything is just fucking fine.
Just need to give it some time.
And let yourself grow you know?
Let yourself, let yourself grow.
You keep yourself in a box
and you keep thinking about this one thing that happened
you know
you'll look back and be like alright I'm good.
Let yourself grow more than 5'8".
That person's banned for life.
But take care of yourself
Toby. Thank you for the one
dollar. And hopefully you
feel better.
Take some me days.
By the way. Those are very important.
Hey thank you. Moo means moo for the one dollar.
And here it is.
Alright it's the Guy Fieri
more like
Diary Fieri.
Alright now get that
I'm telling you.
I'm telling you that's like a
4,000 upvote
image. It just is.
If I was scrolling through a subreddit
and I saw that image and I looked over to the right
and I saw how many upvotes it had
I'd be like I understand
it makes sense to me. I'm putting that on
a t-shirt. Well I hope you wear it in public.
Thank you. Thank you Cool
42 for the one dollar. I've been trying to farm
bits for the past month since the
Labo car stream but then I found
something that I needed to show you this
stream. So here it is.
I'm two more bits away from another hundred.
So I'll give those next stream.
Well thank you. Thank you for
bit farming for months.
And what you wanted to show me was
Why are we watching all these fucking old videos?
Hey by the way they like
deleted my entire
Modern Warfare Grandpa
series. It doesn't exist anymore.
I made like 15
to 20 videos and they're gone.
These used to be on Machinima Respawn
and they like took them off. I haven't
been able to find them.
An annotation.
An annotation on the whole screen.
Fuck.
Jeremy!
Jeremy come down here!
What?
How do I restart recordings?
I can't hear you. What?
How do I restart a recording?
What are you doing?
You're recording?
I just fucking told everybody I was going to give them six thousand dollars!
I don't have that kind of fucking money!
It's F9!
It's F9? Yeah.
Hey everybody
it's Jeremy's grandfather here
bringing you a first ever
Modern Warfare 3 gameplay
on his channel and I'm going to tell you
all the tips and all the strategies
on how to be the best player
in Planet Earth.
I'm pretty good at this game.
I'm not that good but I've been
people have told me that I'm pretty good.
So this gun is the
Scar L and the attachments on it
and you got to be the red dot sight
and it's got to have
a readerless recoil
I can't believe I've
I'm actually saying this though
and
I don't remember the third one
so I found that if you want to be
the lighter you want to throw all your
grenades out within the first
two seconds of the game and every time
you respawn because you don't
want to carry that extra fucking weight you know
that's just extra weight and if you happen
to hit somebody on your team with a flash
ping fuck them
that's not nice
oh there it is!
there's the diarrhea
wow
wow you are
old
I did not doctor this photo
so it looks like this for everybody
and if it doesn't look like this
then you have a computer
bug so I'll talk to you guys
later see you have fun
in the game you fuckers
that's a long time
ago that is
you want to know how long ago that was?
that was November 9th
that was more than
seven years ago
that's ancient by internet standards
I wasn't even alive
seven years ago
some of those I really thought were
really really fun they were really fun to make
there's one where I was
editing a video
those of you that don't understand
this like I did a series on machinima
where cause call of duty
and like montages and people
spinning around in your headshot
and throwing tomahawks to cry
it was like the biggest videos on youtube
like large youtube stars
if you had like a call of duty montage
on your channel that was the biggest thing
on the whole website
so that's what these videos came from
and there was one in particular where I was making my own
montage as grandpa
and I pulled back
there was a huge premiere timeline
and I think that video has gone forever
but yeah that's
some history there
I made a lot of those videos
I made at least fifteen of them
private or removed I don't know what the hell they were doing
who knows
but we're at the end of the bits here
thank you cool 42
for the link to that video
that's the only one I think that's still on my channel
maybe one more floating around somewhere
critical corn thanks for the one dollar hey germ it's one of the
it's one of the georgia guys
from pax did you ever find
a way to crack open that pecan
and enjoy some of them
still loving the stuff and we both still love
everything you make and so it's
untypical of content creators
to keep making great content like you do
keep up the great work love you
no I never figured out how to open them
I had no idea
just like nuts
they brought like food
they drove
are you ever gonna make more videos on the main channel
I don't know
I kinda got really jaded
after a couple of things that
I don't really even need to talk about
on stream
but kind of like the fall
of youtube in a sense
and how twitch was a more
it seemed like a more inviting
platform at the time
but there's a whole lot of other reasons that
there's so many
I could go we could sit here for
a couple hours and talk about why
I've essentially moved
completely away from making
youtube videos
and we could be here all day
but okay let's do it
oh no
but there was a chance there at some point
a couple years ago
where I wanted to start to do
productions and videos
and move sort of
split the channel in two different directions
have gaming stuff
and gameplay stuff
and gaming videos but then also do other
big kind of passion projects
that I've really always wanted to make for a long time
and it became very difficult to even
attempt that
I've told you guys this a million times
that I need to keep myself interested
and remember I've been doing
this for seven almost eight years
straight I've never
stopped you know there's never been a
time the only real honestly
this last October
was the only time that I was really away
from making a stream
or a video in probably eight years
I've never gone
more than a month or
three weeks or four weeks without kind of
doing something but I want to make sure that I stay
interested because I can't
do anything
unless I'm interested in what I'm
going to do I can't put on a face
I can't pretend
some people can I can't
I want to make sure that what I'm doing
is fun well the stream just kind of
ate shit there for a second but I want to make
sure the thing that I'm doing is I'm having fun
you didn't stream for almost a month when you moved
oh yeah but that's what I'm saying
besides this last October
which is what I meant by that
from this move
before moving to Vegas I
was you know I've been doing it for
eight years straight I've taken some
small breaks here and there like a week or two
okay whatever I've never
much longer than that the music is pitch
shifting in the background what
is it really that's weird
it's probably
because the internet is like kind of
coughing right now we're in a little
rough patch but yeah I
don't oh yeah YouTube bye
see you later I'm never going to make content
again on YouTube I don't know
I'm just going with what
I am my gut tells me
to do and it was I
feel like doing streaming because that's in that
interests me and I'm really really interested
in that I hope you guys stick around for the
ride because it's I'm going
to keep going you know
end of content creation voice
new vlog
I don't know what's going to happen next
I mean this twitch
once I'm on twitch for as long as I've been
on YouTube things are will
probably start to get interesting for me because
then I have to figure out okay so is this
it I was on YouTube for
five years this is
the year three of Twitch
having you know streaming more
than three times a week so
I don't know in another couple years I'm going to have
to kind of reevaluate where I am and what I'm doing
and what I what's next I
don't know I cannot give you the answer
because I don't know what it is but
I'm going to go as long as I can
Facebook live I don't
think so no but But Squire
thanks for the one dollar how much of my very very
little money do I have to throw at you before you actually
watch the trailer please my crops
are dying we're going to watch it don't worry
and then killer Krakow
Meyer thanks for the five dollars
and they said is this true
let's see it's Mr
Slyne
you and him are the same height is that
true thank god he's going to finally put this to bed
no yeah
what wait
what is he doing
why is he doing this to me
why are you doing this to me what
what wait I thought
he was going to come to bat for me
this is a big joke this is a
huge joke he's pulling
a big joke on me right now
no listen to how he says this
you hold on process this information
they hear that
now that's like I'm joking around kind of
I'm lying here
he's just
he's just being funny
take a look at that fucking image
I really thought he was going to be like yeah
betrayed
are the same height is that true
no
not even close
he's made this is a funny little reference
he's playing along he's
doing a really great job playing along
and that's fine and funny
one of these days I'm going to prove this
once and for all
and we'll see we'll see who's laughing
when I stand it up straight
I'm just standing there and it's like
oh look at that look at him
look at him measure
the height on stream no
I'm not going to do that I could do
that but like I don't but that's so
why not I
I'll do it I'm going to measure my height on
stream maybe not tomorrow but
maybe at some point the next
I got
betrayed I've been betrayed
this is like when
like I just got backstabbed
by one of my most like
loyal friends like I'm like the king on
the throne and like
the second like the second
command is like yes king whatever
you say and I'm like yes absolutely
send them all and like I get
stabbed in the back and I look back and I'm like oh
you too you too
he's a really really nice guy and he's
funny and he's making a funny joke
I appreciate the joke and it's a very funny one but he's
a really great guy just know that Mr.
Schlinn is a great guy he really is
thank you moo means moo for the one
doll a huge joke played on tiny streamer
hee hee ha ha ha hee hee all
jokes aside hope things are well for everyone
looking forward to watching the vaude yeah
hope everyone's doing well too so let's
watch let's watch the trailer for
this game and see if I'm going to be into it
maybe I will maybe I won't
maybe I will let's see
it is
right here here's the trailer
for butt squire
no the name isn't that that's not the name
of this the name of this is the the northwood
suite here it comes
alliance digital media
okay I like the characters
produced by online media
you make sandwiches
alright you get to make
sandwiches that sounds fun
he played this did he like it
he loves it
that's a pretty good recommendation then
the norwood suite
okay seems like fun
it looks neat and surreal
yeah it looks pretty cool
actually alright and
finally Dr. Steen thanks for the
one dollar doctor's appointment checkup stream will you get
your height weight hearing and sight checked
it'll be kind of funny actually
but without further ado we're going to end the stream here
with let's see let me make sure
this is correct
rat movie rat movie
has passed a million views on youtube
so why not
the credits are going to roll
while this plays in the background
rat movie
the original one
didn't we just watch this like
like not even a month ago
we actually watched this like
a month ago doesn't matter
alright here's no such thing as
the perfect writer this is why I use
grammarly to check my work
I just fucking
mash my hands on my keyboard
please
correct it for me
youtube alright here we go
here come the subs
thank you everybody
that's the end of the movie
this is like
a
I don't remember it looks like this
this is like a gigantic patreon list
this video was made possible
by all these people which is
probably that's arguably true
I need to pick another one of these
this takes so long to make
the program is so old
this runs like shit
make it a community event
how would that work though
I mean I guess it could
okay no but that would be so hard
because I would say oh yeah
we'll just designate scenes to different
people but how do you designate that
live action remake
that's actually kind of a funny idea
that's cool yeah let me tell you
something over my dead body are you
getting this treasure
very low sodium
oh that star I know that guy
frozen is that old
yeah it is this video is like
five years old
hamburgers
it's the worst guy in the whole
video I hate this voice
and I hate this guy
wouldn't it be funny yeah I don't know what I was doing there
I don't know what that was
I'm so glad they didn't return
yeah they did they came back in the second one
yeah
no there it is there's the
explosion of the earth oh yeah
I remember that from the green screen
movie night there it is
million views
what the fuck is happening
another video playing
video is playing
700,000 no it's not playing
nevermind they keep
playing how do I get rid of this
oh there it is okay
alright I'm gonna get out of here
thanks for all the subs thanks for all the resubs
thanks for all the bits I'll see you guys tomorrow
probably around
between like 2.30 and 3.30 pacific
I didn't have auto
play on I had the browser plug in
still running on OBS
but thanks for watching hope you enjoyed hotline
Miami that was actually very very fun
that was a had a really good time
we'll play the second one next week
and I'll see you tomorrow
have a great rest of the night take care
everybody