What's up? He made it on time. I mean I had to sprint in here. Okay, you know when you're like
really uh you really don't want to disappoint anybody or it doesn't matter if it's people or
one person or whatever you open up on your phone the clock app because you want to make sure
that you can see the actual fucking second hand like I told people I was going to be there at four
okay I'm looking at the second hand right now and it's down by like the like the six
so I'm just gonna watch that until I have to run to the room all right hello oh hypers sunflower
stream ladies and gentlemen I have a huge announcement to make on par with the dollhouse
stream are you ready huge fucking announcement tomorrow I'm gonna show off the sunflowers
that's it better than the dollhouse stream lying Andy I'm not a lying Andy can that be our fan base
name what sunflowers you guys are my my sunflowers that's weird I don't want to call you guys my
sunflowers I want to call you guys up fucking wankers all right I'm ready I got I got my
strawberry banana smoothie right here that's in glass number one I've got my iced coffee over here
that's in glass number two I've got a water over here that's in glass number three I have two
thirds of a coca-cola left right here that's in bottle number one I have a sprite over here
that's bottle number two I have two peanut butter crackers here snack number one I have
tuna a can of tuna snack number two I'm ready or in two hours to not take a sip or a bite out of
one of these and it all to go bad in front of me we're starting with comedy I've got a smoothie
in front of me whatever relax isn't gonna be a 14-hour stream no it's not I can guarantee you
that I'm very excited though tweet you don't oh shit no more heroes three what we're doing
thanks for the reminder I've been looking forward to this game I wanted to play it since they
announced it I was a big fan of the first one and I hated the first one I was a huge fan of the
second one and I hated the second one I think that's just how it is when you're a no more
heroes fan you love these games so much but you also don't like them at all it's a really
weird way to go about it this series is one of my favorite actual series but I hate these games
it's weird he's gonna hate this one I'm just fucking around everybody come on
but you'd have been here before actually some of you may not have been here before
now but I like the games are always really fun but they're a little they're a little grungy
that makes any sense I'm fully expecting that no I didn't play Travis Strikes again because
I don't know it's like three times as long as all the no more heroes main games and it's a
top-down game I want to like slash around the sword and jump around and don't be paper don't
let paper Mario thousand year door be a wicked lie it's not a lie it just it was reality if I'm
going to stream like twice a week somewhere between one and two times a week on the weekends
I can't like thousand year door is like a thousand year long game it's a thousand hours
I don't think I could do it it would take me I would take forever
all right I'm ready I'm ready to go I think thousand year game yeah
thought you were streaming on Friday I figured we would just go back to the weekends like we
were supposed to so from here on out you are to expect a Saturday Sunday experience maybe Friday
Saturday Friday Saturday Saturday only Saturday Sunday I think it's a it's a good place to be
and I wanted to kind of get back to that schedule so this is going to be
uh we'll do Saturday Sunday because this game's obviously not just going to be one and done
because I have to I'm playing through the game because I fucking love this game I love this
series I hate this series so you know we have to do it uh this one actually is I think it's
supposed to be a little longer than the uh than the other two so we'll see like a bug just no
let's bring it over all right I'm ready how come there's no audio can you guys hear anything bad
controllers here we come I am playing with the joy cons and I know that that's I I don't like
these things but it says for the best experience use the joy cons and I just got 10 community subs
from James Morris thank you appreciate it but I also want to play the regular difficulty not
the hard one I'm not going to play this mode this is just like the cutscene mode I'm going to play
bitter formidable foes normal recommended difficulty hey Taylor uh thanks for those 10
community subs you didn't play Travis strikes again you aren't going to understand anything
no I don't I look they're gonna they're going to do the thing that they do in all these games if
you there's a one gigantic side game in the middle they're gonna do a previously on the next game of
thrones cutscene that happens before I start the game we're gonna get caught up in the first cut
scene that's how they do it because then I don't have to play the game and would you look at that
we've got another 10 give me to do subs from uh Vince smoke thank you I've not been calling out
any of the big community subs recently because I really haven't been able to look
all right here you go ready previously on no more heroes I'm starting I'm ready I'm gonna milk this
because I've been waiting for this game for like three years you hear anything there's no sound
once the difficulty level has been set it cannot be changed later during the game are you sure
I'm sure there's an audio oh there is oh suda 51 loves his like retro I'm looking forward to the
minigames are there any minigames in this one press any button death hand death claw was it
stage one I remembered this game I used to play nobody at school had it but I was super into it
for some reason it was called death man oh it's called toe jamming earth was a side scrolling
action game it was like a clone of one of those famous Japanese games but it was so cool these
aliens from the planet death take over earth and they print the human scores on their arms
intelligence and beauty if either score drops below 100 they get killed a murder show begins
oh the murder show trope right but one man put a stop to this terrible game that's right it's
death man death man fights against the death aliens to protect the planet earth he kills off
all 10 of the top evil death aliens then when he kills general death at the end
death man reveals his true identity it's Travis touchdown is that man how did it end I totally
forgot the watch mojo and is still unsolved for me and we're pretty sure oh yeah that lady that
does that voice remake version and we're pretty sure that they're looking for a comeback we find
out who death man really is finally they probably have they probably
death oh and don't forget the uh the the 10 to 20 gift clips of a friends episode oh there's
chandler and he's shaking oh shit i play how do i punch it looks like roger from american dead
all right can i jump i fight this no i can't all right it's just it just waves
do i have any other moves and i just have punched this is pretty good
it reminds me of um it's that old nintendo game where you play as jason oh this is sus
splatter house yeah that's the one wait oh shit okay that i just had to punch that
what is what's that doing get away from me why is it attacking me oh shit all right cool
i thought it was trying to hurt me oh shit okay i'm almost out of power
oh she's island i don't think in yoshi's island just yoshi put a jason mask on and start killing
people no you're thinking of like a fan game that came out give me give me give me this got hit
fuck there goes my no damage run got him next game shoot up oh cutscene quiet oh community subs
thank you spiegel it was a bust too it's the e3 trailer i remember this i remember the concept
of this game was really cool god i'm so excited can you tell best friends forever foo
rain parasite so that's figured out the end where's the part where he goes in 20 years i will return
it looks like this is goodbye foo you're going back to your home is it damon hi love you
in 20 years i will return yes 20 years you really mean it foo promise sonequa martin green
carl no matter look outside your window you might want to look out your window now
huge fan of your show fire at will sonequa that ad has been in my head for the last two months i
can't get rid of it happens every time i open twitter they must have me on an algorithm i see
it every time sir it is time for the board meeting we need to go back in just give me a minute i've
got an appointment but i am not aware of just watch i just opened twitter i just opened twitter
and here it is but i'll wait is that you back damon i love you looks like you've been living
large damon you used our powers to get yourself a pretty sweet piece of the pie
are you really foo thanks to you i was able to return to my land and now here i am a full-on
prince congratulations but i'm hella bored i got nothing to do animation so weird i worked out
the neighboring planet but then i was court marshaled in exile to the black hole prison
them these dudes are my buddies we met in the hole nice to meet you everyone
hey damon let's team up and make this planet ours
ours what do you mean i'm talking about taking it over sir do it my god what did you do
holy shit apparently superheroes are popular in this country so we're gonna jump on that right
mr big shot what are you i'm a goddamn superhero well
there's your intro we saw most of that during e3 but it's still it's a cool concept i like it
is it old travis it is old travis isn't it access door all right before we get started though i'm
sorry people think i'm fucking crazy but i just opened twitter i just opened it
i just i every time i open twitter it happens every single fucking time i can the thing is i
watch it every time too like they they have me i'm like a twitter ad whale okay i watch the ad like
400 times i don't know how many impressions i'm giving this company or whatever but i i don't
know i i think it's it's i like listening to it i don't know why i just it's something about it
and they have like three versions of it and they're all so like dumpy they're all like such shitty
ads all right hold on is there anything i can do in here this is the apartment right from this
first two games those are on my leg you got influenced did i go to the bathroom is it the
save in the bathroom no i think we just have to do we just go it's on my hand i'm like the
infinity gauntlet next stream you should eat shit on camera well next stream you won't be here
because you're going to be banned for 24 hours was today the fourth of july if not is the empire
striking back or what it looks like things are going to get weird today give him like five
minute timeout that's fucking what are you doing god there's like big satellites
what is this game when you talk about bringing in like cosmic shit and superheroes from other
dimensions suda 51 just drew every character he thought was cool looking and just put him in a
game like he just got a bunch of concept artists and was like just make a bunch of crazy shit and
there's no creative anything you just do whatever you want that's kind of refreshing in a way i
like it can i ask you something are you guys aliens i think they're here to talk oh i know
these people they take these guys down strategy is born from battle i'll take the one in the middle
if you want with the rest of it has like the get like the snake like scar start the game wait how
am i supposed to fight a gamer fighting for their life is beautiful hey there my name is taro gita
my gamer buddies usually call me master gita from here on out i'm going to be popping up in
this window here and there to teach you some basics of the game of course you can go ahead
and skip over this if you want to i'll send you all this info via mail later so check it out when
you get the chance so you might just discover something new all right all right we normal
attack heavy attack jump dodge all right that's pretty easy i think basic controls yeah yeah yeah
so we're gonna swing heavy swing jump dodge why why why is it like an ipad video on the corner
it's pretty good quality so far
your good old girl next door dodge all right that's back another new game today
today
all right shut up after the opening how do i close the ad
no wait i got a perfect thing for the video put the put the put the something put that
shit in the corner right here but i don't is that legal but you can't do that never mind
but imagine if that was there just destroy all those nasty aliens
i want to get the banner ads off view oh wait viewpoint control i just i didn't do the tutorial
oops i like killed him already
oh there's a guard all right guard is locked on and guard is hold zl
gotta kill kill and then kill some more zl that's what i'm doing right
hesitate and you are okay you blocked right there all right yep yep attacking and guarding
with the beam katana will consume power end up with no power and you're screwed so pay attention
to the power gauge at the top right of the screen all right yeah yeah yeah all right so r and right
or r and shake is charged beam katana right okay so let's do it all right you can actually move
around this time before you have to stay still that's actually pretty good that's awesome
estimate an enemy with your beam katana or deal hardcore damage to a boss r or killer slash
you're playing the joy con in both hands swing the r in the direction of the arrows right yeah
just like in the other games feels really good yeah nice okay it's fun that was the guy that
was talking about that shit wasn't it let me drink some more of my uh smoothie face cam or riot nope
power crystals this is really alien juvie check this out all right it's atomic composition is
unknown this is this might be travis strikes again info search to include the entire galaxy
head a hit out ending supernova an energy stump of the planet gest baptiste so they really are
aliens things are getting real funky real quick mission accomplished easy where the rest of them
it's only polite to accept an invitation to kick ass master i believe the time has come to use
it loading the dd system okay we missed a lot in the last game oh he does a hinge in a gogo
they don't explain how they got this oh so okay maybe we didn't miss very much it just has this
fuckhead here's the travis i know he better be in smash brothers eventually like i'd be upset if
he wasn't you're behind enemy lines it's just always assumed you were are you tweaking this
is how i've always sounded that's pretty badass if there's anything you're not clearer let me know
i'll lay it out for you ah so you're basically my navigator huh come on man don't underestimate
my prowess in battle i'm right up there with yeah rick what is gonna make things more
who is that let's go
i like the heavy slaps oh this is good this is fun this is fun oh i got a battery so much
android blood what is he saying voice the fuck out as you can see things got all funky
quick probably some planet eating type dude waiting all yoked and powerful and trying to
take over the world or something this looks so good but don't you worry let's hold on
what i don't read any reviews i don't care they're totally i just go in blind i don't touch down
let's let's play here to save the world i'm also just a passing assassin
here we go taking a kill trip on death road especially with the game even looking forward
to right it's me now i feel bad for the people that did that with cyberpunk but you know what
to do i've been looking forward to this for like the last three or four years more than that
kill them all the insanity travis let it fly there we go primitive insanity
safeguarded insanity so we're just going right into a boss or something like this right immediately
into a dash oh okay press it in too many beers oh shit i need a toilet perfect location oh yeah
don't forget always stop by the toilet if you find one especially before boss fights you need time to
get your thoughts in order so you know save your damn game i like how they did make him older
right saving i'm i want to play the mini games i'm so excited i can't wait access the sushi shop
this is the sushi shop hey irash i i am bug zaburo yummy yummy yummy get some fish in your tummy
probably thinking what's a sushi place doing inside of a ufo like this right well but listen
i used to have a shop in santa destroy but it got sucked up in that light from the sky and i
ended up in here somehow anyways enough about my problems how about some sushi buddy use l and r
to choose take out or eat in take out is well exactly what it sounds like grab a quick bite
when you get hungry during battle what's this a counter over on the right side why is it counting
okay so you can take with you eat it means you can sit here and get filled up and get
ripped rarin to go for the next battle it's like monster hunter okay we have excellent choices
i'm a huge fan of dawn my sushi they've got all sorts of sushi to choose from so she's actually
a crucial item in battle eat in sushi effects will last till your next battle ends okay so it
is like monster hunter you know like what gamers call a buff take out sushi can be eaten during a
battle you'll be left vulnerable while eating so be careful use the left and right d pad to select
you take out sushi and eat it huh interesting replenishes health when eaten during battle
wait is this like a this is the one listen to this for a second this is the theme song
holy shit this is good all right the good old cucumber roll replenishes power when eaten so
that how fast how long does it take to eat so why would i eat these outside of combat why wouldn't
i take it versus your attention when eaten during battle temporarily increases attack power when
eaten improves your chances on the slash reel when eaten during battle partially replenishes
death skill gauge during cooldown when eaten during battle so wait does this okay so increases your
tension is that just gonna happen press r oh shit there's two tabs what am i stupid all right what's
this load with only the best fish when you die you replenish your health that's huge enter into
battle with greatly increased health attack power and tension significantly increased health attack
power intention all right so this is the big one of the of these three i feel like i want to spend
all this money just try it out and see what happens chef's choice enemies more easily stunned
celebrates the all right let's it's the tutorial boss right i'm gonna just take i'll bring some
of the health health and power three two i can only buy one wait can i only buy it once oh shit i can
only buy i can i have to i get it when i buy one thing i get out of the menu all right well
whatever this is fun no no we're good all right well not that i'm not gonna spend let's go i'm
gonna let's kick the guy let's i'm gonna kick the rest did i save it probably not no don't save it
let's see how just how bad this is is that five thousand dollars i don't want to spend it all
i got two heels crystal body from outer space bone they came to take over the earth his right hand
seems to be holding a weapon it's actually the mutated bone of his hand oh and he's able to
stretch it far out this is where the name bone comes from cool one-on-one he's not so tough
but watch out his weapon attacks have plenty of range this dude's just a goomba
here we go he has a switch controller that's so oh i love it i'm not gonna hold back jumping
attacks okay first b to attack while jumping normal jump attacks y are great for showing off
homing function will bring you right to your target too all right you want to scatter a bunch
of surrounding enemies try unleashing a heavy jump attack it feels so good it's addictive
they leave you wide open though okay that is cool yeah it's like a big down smash
once an enemy attack is just about to land use a to dodge and slow down time that's a perfect
dodge this is your chance to beat the living shit out of your opponent or easily only some
pro wrestling moves all right cool let's win sweet perfect dodge oh you wanted okay you want
to follow up with it while pummeling enemies you'll sometimes see a star up here above their heads
this is your chance to stun them right once done an enemy can be knocked the hell out with zr
succeed and you'll get your power replenished as an extra added bonus all right so when you're
beating people up they get these these star and you can like boom you can stun them
oh no they are stuck yeah let's do that so it's done somebody
done oh he's done he's done he's done he's done he was already done
now zr nice cool death glove skill after the beam katana and pro wrestling moves your third
set of techniques is your death glove skill start off by mastering the death kick skill hold l and
use b to activate it warp right up to your enemy and drop kick their ass into next week the death
glove skills are all powerful but they require a cooldown okay so was it l and b hold l what's
l hold l b hold l b oh that's not b that's okay wrong one that's awesome i was hitting xbox b i'm
sorry estimate an enemy or pull off a successful killer slash and the slash reel will spin match
up the images on the slash reel yeah you get like the strawberry on the shortcake
all right get 777 on the slash rule to unlock full armor mode press l and i whenever you like
an icon of these plays i don't miss it okay yeah strawberry right there it is all right
full armor mode standing by wait you did you actually get in the suit
that's awesome oh my god zr holy shit number throws oh that's an s-frame okay all right i'm
i'm figuring out okay so that was that now what oh i'm on my screen i'm gonna save it here
this is good i don't want to spoil it but all right well i'm not going to read
anymore after that and i'm not going to spoil it but that's where i stopped reading all right
should i buy something else i'm going to get a couple more sushis or something wait am i
streaming i am on air i'm live right now what does that even mean why am i live at the restaurant
that's so weird why all right let's get one more of these and then i'll get the yeah i don't want
any more than that three heels is good 12 viewer andy that's definitely gonna keep going up i
guarantee it gene where are we in the core of the spacecraft so this is where the real hardcore bad
guys are what's that egg eggs you know like in that famous movie where a monster pops out of the egg
attacks hey the egg is cracked something not so good is gonna come out of that thing
give me face huggers probably you're so good at walking are you yes you are it's gonna bite
in the face let me pick you up little guy oh my god what uh where am i okay this is my planet
well now it's a hellscape with nothing but a graveyard and a galactic waste
titan was like most plants this is where we're crazy destroying the whole it is indeed so why
not get revenge revenge against foo we wouldn't last three damn seconds against him are you okay
with a life of submission well that's how i've lived it's my destiny rethink this you can still
go back go on back to space nope okay now either way who's gonna kill me i see yeah about that
destiny i'll put an end to that for you sounds good well okay okay want to get started well
shit okay i'm fighting in he disappears okay he's got like a lightning move he's got a hand comes
out all right he's the hand that comes out let's see if i can first try the tutorial boss
all right he goes back away run that's fine i'm just trying to see what he does for move
he leaves his hand out let's go leaves the hand out here yeah just like that game where you don't
want to get greedy what do i have the power are we good all right unless he has a phase two which
probably does oh yeah by the way i've seen the seal video hey
i've seen it it's fucking hilarious
i've seen the seal video i can stun him how would i do how to do a wrestling move to this guy
oh there it is what i get you you taupe you toppy coins
you don't know how hard i was laughing at that video for the last like
i got yesterday into today like this morning oh i'm out of colon i want that that seal is so cool
you would just do that to everybody they would come over to the seal tank
i'll play i'll play it in a second hold on you'll see i don't think i even need to dash there why
am i dashing oh okay that hurts not that bad though i'm all right you just saw the seal what
the fuck yeah it's so funny he puts his head up over the water and just makes these weird noises
and people said it sounds like exactly to my voice or something which i can understand like
that like hey hey hey yeah it does it's really weird why why would that seal make those sounds
why is he going like get out of here get out of here get out of here get out of here get out of
here you can't train a seal to do that he looks i think we're in phase two well is he adding anything
all right he's pretty easy because he's easy as a warcraft boss would be if you could run around
this fast and well and swing this fast so i'm not concerned about it okay now i am now i am
concerned okay so how do i how do i eat that thing how do i eat that oh my god okay how do i eat how
do i eat food how do i eat food how to eat food there it is all right what's that i got money
how do i get away from that i have to jump over it shit okay i get it jump over it jump give me
something good don't fall in that oh hey hey i gotta get out of here i don't want to fight him
over here he's got this like how do i get him out of the puddle get out of the puddle i don't
want to fight you there oh shit stay open there it is okay oh i timed it wrong sorry give me a
power nope oh fuck you okay don't get greedy he's almost dead don't be an idiot it's a fucking
goddamn tutorial demon no shit i tried to the camera changed now i'm getting in one more move
and i'll jump over it and get him don't don't be an idiot don't touch these everybody relax
it's tutorial demon i'll be fine this one's easy to dodge just don't move around like an idiot
all right we're good we're good we're good
whoa shit that was that was fast this is the end right here say bye tutorial boss down yeah i think
i'll be all right the hundred years of playing bloodborne is training me for this one that is
the end mr black hole dead get to kick him lb plus oh right because the stun all right yeah
i'll get i'll be i'll be all right we're basically in his universe i'll begin searching
wait this is not it oh no that was phase one what the hell is going on in this game
did i go in this hey what the fuck i hit this um all right is it pointing it's going this way
the ball is going over here should i go with this one oh that's gene okay gene you go first
is safe i think so all right gene where we going he looks like they're going this way all right
should i go in there let's go this is freaking me out play the seal video does everybody have a link
does everybody have a link to like to i'll just play the audio i can't show it on screen but i
have like my switch is plugged in hey now i'll play the audio here you go it's just a seal on
camera like with his head poking out of the water all right here you go july 1984 1047
oh hey there hey there hey it's literally you and but it's not though it's a seal
the seal died two months before you were born can you answer that i don't know i have no idea
i've reincarnated i don't know maybe that was my previous life oh shit come on gene wake up
i didn't know which way to go well i'm gonna say this way wait is it are they all the same
did look the same i got it it was right can i just attack him it is such a funny video
where is he where the hell are you black hole calm down left thanks for the 10 community subs uh
dretch what the hell is going on oh my god full armor travis move move sights and lock on l is
boost i have to lock on multi-laser hyper mega death particle cannon
grab this full armor is designed for impeccable mobility in space and is known as
booga in vilia mode i don't i don't use l to fly in the direction of your choice move r to lock
onto a target after locking on hit zr to fire off your multi-lasers it's gonna take a little
while to get used to use l for a boost while boosting your charge meter will deplete it's
zl to fire off your mega death particle cannon okay so i have zr is a laser zl is a mega death
particle cannon holy shit okay this is really weird so it's just like starfox i just lock on
his shit and shoot that's a dodge how do i go up okay up is just up and i lock on okay you can
lock onto the meteors and then where's the charge of the cannon all right let me try this
um what am i firing at what the hell does this do oh my goodness gracious okay what about
i don't know what the fuck is happening all right i'm gonna try shooting the head with the mega
cannon okay you have to aim the cannon i get it i get it all right it's fine all right now right
ahead this is so weird how many all right up in the air because avoiding this is actually really
easy all right he's dead one more time so you have to do these gigantic like i can't even
mech suit fights after you fight the people in on the ground so every fight is at least
two phases that's maybe not maybe that was just a cool one that was very cool
fine do whatever you want with that i'm more badass than a black demon
okay everyone i'm leaving the rest up to you so this was that this was the fall guy oh that was
the fall guy to collect the data on my move i get it okay cool see i was because i didn't use any
skills and i didn't do any throws i was playing the game like bloodborne but you look whatever
you got a fang moon dust satellite fragment is like a crafting system
congratulations travis silvia is it really you oh they're back you have managed to take
downs in number 10 ranked yeah the 10 ranks yeah of course and you have been recognized as number
10 well they can't do a normal heroes four because what do you go from that
you are in the eye of the storm so you cannot escape or just disappear you can
only fight here so i need to win huh yes and what happens once i take everyone out
for reals i'll do it please i do have to leave a message okay now go out and earn the entry
weird long okay also what are these guys where they even come from sorry i'm sort of in a hurry
i'll mail you later so be sure to check it out hey wait silvia there's something i need to talk
to you about oh that's just like nacks ramis up there just hanging out okay so we've got sonic
juice sniping lee yes okay gold joe black knight direction vanishing point velvet chair girl
onto gold joe
yeah see that was the tutorial boss that was that this is how you play the game
that was really that was quite the intro i will say very very good intro that was the entire game
well that was the entire game on the playstation demo disc killed i see
that's kind of funny it was that man somebody you know looks like not all humans are weaklings after
all this ought to be fun sir it is time okay oh time for a meeting sweet let me watch
foo wait this is a board meeting it's important this is a bitch in room nice work damon you're
really coming up huh and you even followed my orders like a good little boy too just like i
feel like this is the meetings that like kiss work please keep quiet and the rock star comes
in they're like talking about sales of record numbers and stuff of course they're specialists
in a wide range yeah bunch of losers we're even more capable so it's cool if i go ahead and fire
these guys right damon what's his hair stop this oh don't worry you're a good secretary
i'll allow you to live okay that's enough for the entertainment time for a strategy meeting damon
what about the blueprints for the fighting arena it's here red ever dimension 2 is that charles
who made these i think it is that voice actor was just built without permission it is isn't it you've
heard of lasik before right oh that's cool do you still remember you mean ah taking over this
planet is too simple and boring so i decided to go with a game of conquest wouldn't it be
hella fun if we got some humans to take on the galactic superhero like spore monsters took out
black hole hey you secretary get the president on the line the president
did you not hear me so destroying the planet feel like i'm in vr chat or something ever since way
back then or it's got like an avatar you little me from back then and the handsome ass me now
we're the same nothing's changed come on damon trust me he is on the line sir
mr president you're gonna hold an emergency press conference let's make a joint announcement
i will not whatever you thought oh okay then i guess i've got no choice do it
just baptiste the sixth aka fool i'm prince of the baptist system and you can call you lord fool
listen up earthling aliens i'm about to conquer this planet but simply conquering it is no fun
and there's probably going to be some resistance i understand you people so i'm going to provide
you with an opportunity we're going to play a game a game of conquest i won't run or hide
i'll be a damon tower in utopia land anyone looks like we've got a contestant already
it's a bunch of like newts i admire the quick thinking nice move oh shit oh my god what was
that where was that there's really got some balls make no mistake you think you can kill me with
those primitive firecrackers you want to kill me come kill me you'll have 10 of the most elite
dudes in the galaxy awaiting you well one of them got killed so nine i guess take us all up and
we'll go home otherwise we take over elite right the game of death begins holy shit 2021 the huge
entertainment-based theme park built in center destroyed utopia land would no longer it's an
amusement park in two months it was instead converted into the garden of insanity
disney world what do they do they think they're in like a capital city
foo and his aliens are dispatched into formation prepared to destroy the planet anytime five on
two in the sky one on the moon one in space foo sits in the central tower and his nine soldiers
all recognized by the united assassins association descend to earth as the galactic
superhero ranking members the following 10 have been registered as members of the ranking this
is so cool this is insane number 10 the passing assassin travis touched but he has it
number he has an action figure the space ore dealer gold joe for eight the alien kidnapper
the knight's direction those spoilers number seven the memory thief vanishing point number six
the gastro cannon velvet chair girl number five the dark world princess midori midorikawa
number four the galactic sniper champion sniping lee sniping lee number three the demon god sonic
juice number two the master of explosion paradox bandit number one our own king of destruction
just baptiste the sixth will all be there at this year's wrestlemania battle of space versus earth
the ultimate battle of top class space criminal versus assassin is about to kick off
it really is just a rumble are we rewinding or are we fast forwarding this is the fourth title card
goddamn superhero i wonder if this game was supposed to just be goddamn superhero but they
just made it no more heroes three because they were like why the hell not this is a no more heroes
game nine more hours of gaming a day it has been an hour it's actually been one hour because they
said 10 right this is weird does it actually know all right i gotta i i want a first impression the
first like hour of the game it's been a lot of cutscenes and stuff and some actions too but
i mean this is 9.4 first like hour i love it not bad we'll see not bad it was designed it was
like netflix yeah what the fuck is going on could show a bit of appreciation you know
did i not just say help with the next one too mr gold joe has arrived
let him in all right i'm looking forward to gold joe's voice it's an old prospect i think so
i think it i think gold joe is back that earthling i love gold joe already
i'm honored all the credit shall go to you of course what's that it was dug out of a nebula
behind the nokiway it's galactica rolling thunder rainbow clap trap it's got a nice shine to it
i'll take good care of it it'll give you great clap traps clap traps blow up
he's much weaker than you but be careful he's a wily bastard you have nothing to worry about
don't kill him off too quickly a quick kill that sounds like a nice plan
i'm going out where to i want i want gold joe to be my friend i don't want to like heart kill
gold joe that's another title card what is going on what the fuck is happening this is supposed to
be a tv show that's so funny like we're just sitting here binging a television show we're
playing a game so what do you think about miike's latest production the girls series was a proving
ground miike used it to help him get to the next stage it's like a treasure chest of production
by preparing so many different stages to test out just how far japanese cg technology can go
attention channel he's pouring his passion into the improvement of systematized techniques
damn travis you really hit the nail on the head the incubator of the new idol chosen in the audition
that's just his transient form and nobody notices that the true awesomeness of miike
is in the fact that he used this film shoot as a way to further his own technical stuff
so basically in the next yakuza apocalypse style full-on miike film these systematized
techniques are really going to come alive right so weird case of greedy dude the hell of greedy dude
that takashi miike man i guess they're here looks like it's about time to get to work yeah
let's go who is that who am i talking to all right here we are save oh it's bishop okay
teacher noise it really is okay what about can i can i still play with gene i guess i can i do
anything else i don't have clothes access the wardrobe in the motel to swap t-shirts and change
up your outfit the only changes are aesthetic but sometimes changing your look for a new gaming
session can help you feel nice and refreshed get your hands on all kinds of new costumes by
talking to the t-shirt aliens on the map and progress through the game jacket off no i don't
i don't want that one i mean it's i want this one jacket off yeah just t-shirt travis no yeah i like
the t-shirt t-shirt with jacket off no more heroes known pleasures what color should i do i like the
blue palm trees i like the palm trees do you even understand this is literally star's t-shirt stir
holy shit bad service good coffee devolver old school devolver digital i put on this just put on
stirs shirt i kind of all right we'll come back but i kind of want this that's funny just picked up
sup assassin you're the one who killed my buddy i saw you on tv
what a lame ass little speech that shit was just stupid we had our own meekade night over here
thanks to that i came to the conclusion that andro media deserves to be reevaluated unlock the glue
man shirt keep talking all you want you're already dead we're close enough anyway because
you've pissed me off when the conversation stops that's when you die oh so you're challenging me
huh you talk a pretty big game prince dumbass you a human ridicule me that shall not stand
i have to fight him do i this ranking bullshit all i gotta do is take prince dumbass his head
off and it's over bring it on i'll give you a little kiss this is over i'll show you how it
let's go what what the fuck hey what get away from him his head's gotten half oh my god
fucking punk who's this that stings who the hell are you that's about enough from you oh it's my
turn where are you he's from he's from driver strikes again okay well assassin this a friend
of yours let him go he's got nothing to do with this you're here for me that doesn't make any
sense you killed my buddy right and so well this is how it's gotta be
now you're really fucked you goddamn scumbag now we're even oh no we're not kill you literally
just like ripped off my friend's arm kiss son of a like to see don't forget you're a scumbag too
clipping nice clipping with the cape ruined my fucking immersion ruin the game
and see what the hell can see this break he broke it fuck through it
well that was interesting baseball girl looks like i was too late oh okay i get it i understand
looks like johnny noxville now where is he oh man shinobu he's based on johnny noxville
that's the intention yeah did a good job what if i pull what do i do with the pole okay okay
where's gene what's up gene if animals could talk it would be really weird wouldn't it it would make
a lot of things really awkward i think i mean like you just sit on the couch like if auto is sitting
next to me it's just like oh man this is so comfortable i feel so good right now oh this
feels so good i'm so happy right now this is awesome dude bro this is the best ever
like man just sitting this talking like dude i'm hungry i'm so hungry man i'm starving man
i'm hungry can i get some food let's get some food man i'm starving can i have some food man
it'd be really like weird i feel i feel like because we we turn animals for some reason in
our heads into babies like oh it's a auto it's little auto oh he's like two he's like hey uh
i'm hungry dude you take me outside i'm gonna go shit in your backyard and it's like oh auto's
two years old he's always little he's a little boy we treat animals like they're like little babies
like forever it's a simpsons joke that's an every person joke okay that's such an easy joke i'm not
even making a joke i'm just saying like it's weird well i can't make a reference to something being
weird why can't i make a reference to something being weird without it being on the simpsons
i don't care if it was on the fucking simpsons can i go how do i go up and do anything else on
here i can't sneeze yeah i was i was thinking about saying that but i feel like people would
have been pissed what is this capsule toys do i have any i thought i did god damn it this
collectibles all right can i play anything on here no nice we're on the minus two storm would
have been nasty it would have been that's like a simpsons joke you board aim for the circle and
throw the moving ball there's a to throw the ball enters the circle gene will shoot it back the
more you succeed the smaller the circle will get so be careful not to lose concentration
okay so aim it into the circle what's up huh oh this is weird it's it's i'm not doing that
it's just spinning around how do i get it over there oh shit i get it okay i thought i thought
the ball was already on the ground i thought the ball was already on the ground i thought i was
rolling it what's the matter fuck you suck what's the matter see i don't want animals to talk
because i don't want to have auto tell me i'm like i'm shitty it's throwing a ball there i get it
oh i just no that's it can i do it again it's fun so sleepy
do it again all right what's up i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it you know what i mean
whatever come on now that i understand how the game works yeah he's avoiding chores no i'm not
i can't wait to do the chores that's my favorite part all right hold on
yep i gotta get to at least 10 10 to 20 i'll be happy
yeah i got three lives that's in there
well that was a bait you see that it didn't go it didn't move it didn't move it spun in a circle
all right i can't all right i get it i get it
oh my god it's it's so hard 50 i don't think i can get 50 man
jesus no into the circle now bring it got it oh it's so hard it's so i i have to do it one more
time please let me do it one more time one more time that's it i swear to god i promise
what's up huh i gotta get to 20
or 25 25 is a better number come on bring it this chat is full of instant gratification zoomers
okay why do you say that oh because i'm playing a minigame for more than five minutes
instant gratification zoomers
yeah i mean here's the thing people talk about and you know you've heard me say before like
oh zoomers well what like it's not a tick tock video it's not a vine yeah it's more than five
seconds right but this is also the same generation that will binge watch an entire series of an anime
in three days into the circle now that's that takes a look that that's attention that's a
lot of attention span so i don't know if i buy the like zoomers don't have an attention span
anymore but that's instant gratification i guess you could say that right
fuck it's actually hard to do because like you can you can load up the next episode immediately
yeah god all right all right my previous high score i'm just gonna beat that
come on what's the matter you're telling me you never zone out and be a couch potato oh no all
the time yeah i would but i was giving a reason as to why i didn't believe the attention span
thing that i hear because you have to sit there for a long time come on bring it that's in that's
in that's in that's in it's all right whatever this that's really difficult and i will be stuck
there for at least like two or three hours later come on bring it you probably get something to
do in at least 20 i love that i can't wait to do that again but for now time to there's a time
to do it's not a worse noise i do that all the time downstairs okay i remember when i had to
wait till next week for the new episode netflix changed things yeah but it's almost like a 50
50 shot some series just dumped the whole thing up there don't they although they kind of stopped
doing that so they started that's become a new thing again she's still unconscious but her chances
of recovery are she is in stable condition now kind of like waiting for weekly episodes i wish
it was twice a week seven days for me is like uh for like a show i'm invested in is just barely
enough time i think i would prefer like a like a two days in a row like a saturday sunday like a
germany night five schedule you only stream once a week yeah i know that's why i said one week is
just barely enough time silvia did something happen they got shinobu i think we're actually
about to enter the real game she is a rambunctious one too she was drawn to the garden of slaughter
enough talk now let me out those sons of bitches oh the ranking battles but this is open world
first you have to clear a test battle otherwise you cannot participate in the ranked battles
then hurry the fuck up and make it happen you are so serious was she so special to you spare me your
bullshit okay then preparations for the test match are complete oh shit okay perfect world perfect
world perfect world no i'm not a game you can check mails you perceive via the menu screen
you'll get stuff like important info on ranking battles and my handy little tutorials be sure
to check it out the mmo yeah all right i've got mail this folder contains important mail
thank you for using the thunder tiger mailing service important mails will be automatically
sent to this folder thunder tiger mailing service congratulations on achieving rank 10 in the
galactic superhero rankings about to burp we're good we are contacting you to inform you regarding
entry conditions for the next ranking battle after winning required numbers of the designated
matches prepared by the uaa please use an atm to transfer the below listed amount which covers
your registration fee and general expenses 20 000 utopia coins okay any 20 000 bucks there's also
spam this folder contains spam though okay that's gonna there's gonna be some funny laugh out loud
stuff there i think la la waiting room it is open world zoom through the city on your bike hit zr
to accelerate and zl to break okay y for speed boost b to emergency break and you can uh hit
the brake to do a drift if you lose your bike on the free map try pressing x you can summon
your bike i gotta pee real bad i'll be right back clog the toilet no just get into water
but i'll tell you clog in the toilet at a hotel is one of the most embarrassing things you can do
if you clog your toilet in your just house or your apartment or wherever uh you have just a plunger
you just easily do it on your own but hotels don't have plungers it's not there's not a plunger in
the room like there is an iron which i think is a mistake if you're gonna have an iron in every
single room there should be a plunger in the closet too or something no one on the closet
because if you you don't i mean like because if i clog the toilet in a hotel room you have to call
the front desk and you have to say hi i'm having them uh having a problem with my toilet device
i can send uh maintenance up to have a toilet issue and then they have to come up and they go
all right yeah what's up i was up does it pro is a toilet problem like how why it's so embarrassing
to be like i clogged the toilet it's like yeah i've said toilet toilets uh screw this up i'm
wrong with it nobody wants to i don't i don't i want to take care of that i don't want somebody
else to take care of that i want to take care of that like i can i just can you just hand me
the plunger at the door and like the the cleaning team can kind of i don't i don't know like but i
i don't want someone to have to deal with that that's like my problem this is why you need a
some crazy guy took a monster shit in his room no they're not doing that no one is saying that
that's absurd no one is saying that no one's doing that i'm ready to uh why would you eat
taco bell on vacation i love i love taco bell and that doesn't excuse me watch the slander
okay because that i don't buy that anymore that's a that's like the joke right i don't buy that
anymore i've had diarrhea from far more like fancy businesses than i have taco bill just being
honest all right let's go get on the highway and head to perfect world all right well you can't
pause me right there all sorts of access points got to throw out the free map including missions
shops and more yeah this question marks gene get us there on keep going this way and punch
over take the wind oh look at this open world it's not a no more heroes game if it doesn't
have like a incredibly ugly ipad game level open world oh my god i'm fine so which should i go to
the i'm afraid to hit the nitro wait there are pedestrians okay what's the nitro okay the car
this is this is really really sloppy what i don't know why how do i hit the brakes okay
what's the question mark is it a question mark oh shit it's right here what is this
number five take on the defense mission is this okay eight waves um i guess it's okay
why does it get sucked up into the next ramis okay let's go i'm gonna go full on one out of eight
is the fighting
oh 32 hit combo can i keep it up what's the stun when they're stunned what do i do
certain button to like dash around right to grab them oh i got money nice nice nice l l2 and r2
is he stunned right now right no he's not
never stood a chance zr is blueberry captain r2 and d2 that's kind of funny i do miss that though
i missed that are you that's not in this game is it now that's what we call a string
what a pain you're a joke what a pain yep i remember
oh oh come on that was my perfect score my perfect game
well every time he says strawberry every time he just goes strawberry i just think of uh let's
say kaisen jujitsu kaisen tuna tuna and i like hate i hate it i hate that because he's so dumb
whatever oh he's stunned he's done he's done stunning stunning stunning
you buy my yearly anime that's right i missed i miss it's not yearly if you walk every single
night before bed hey all it is if you do that for like a few days or a few weeks out of a year
oh
i do it really good too i do it really well those of you that have seen that show dubbed
you're probably like fuck that's identical it's the same it's an actor talking that was pretty
clean that's a good b all right i got nice that's fine yeah nobody watched the dub i did so somebody
did am i loud or my how's my audio i i messed it all up since the dollhouse i'm gonna get back i
screwed it up do i sound fine yeah all right that was just a little random mission cool i just do
these why not can you get my cars in this game i don't remember there being other cars well all
right that person's gone uh we got the motel then no one here's motel what about what's this over
here what's that it's like a bar what is this like a video store this is a game store oh it's bishop
yo travis you want to make some quick cash this dude looking for death man trading cards came into
the shop there's 20 of them all together says he wants to complete his collection he'll pay for
each individual card too you find any bring him to me i'll cut you in on the deal did he spell
people with problems you can help them out in volunteer missions clear volunteer missions to
score rewards like utopia coins junk and wesson i'll preserve the culture of the city collect the
death man card spread around the city and hand them over to bishop sure what i'm talking about
get out there and search till your eyes bleed all right there's also i got mail my god there's
so much mail here important spam recommendations for you not flicks you got a new movie recommended
for you based on your viewing history in my list the 51st chamber of shaolin this mail is sent
automatically okay all right so we got that i need to go that way but hold on what's this
another mission right here oh oh it's a sushi place um no i'm saving my money for now what is
going on here i already did this one right this is another one wait hey how's it going you want
to help me out buddy i got me an idea for the ultimate ramen recipe but i don't have enough
ingredients for it i'm gonna need some scorpions oh no i'll pay you nicely for each one bring me
oh it's they brought the scorpion mission back you can find scorpions all over the city help catch
the scorpions needed to make broth for the ultimate bowl of ramen that's disgusting
hey you're a real good guy um so this is not even a mission it's just a kind of permanent
collectible thing all right well i kind of want to i want to see what the other one is
that's pretty cool um can i go back i want to go back all right break what's this something else
all right uh hi so this is actually just a sushi uh sushi place
oh i bet all right health yeah i'll buy like i need i'll buy a it was three last time i'm gonna
go with five i love this song i want to hear this sushi sandwiches i see you're a steve
brolin joyer and we're off gets you plus 10 chat points all right let's just do them oh let's
just do it right i'll make some money i just want to see what happened car can't be destroyed
so is this this is the highway technically it looks like it but why the indicator is saying
to go this way this is the highway weird um stand to destroy perfect world this multiple maps
perfect world what are the wait hold on wait wait wait find a designated match to try out
what is going on general location of designated matches will be displayed with the circle once
you found a designated match get in there and fight designated match is this a designated match
very confused jesus i think i have to find it oh there it is all right so this is a designated
match yes this is weird so is this replacing the minigames we just kind of go right stuff up with
the all right hold on chest hole watch out for his range attacks he sucks at close combat though
dodge his minds and getting close this guy just screams i'm an alien i'm getting a nasty vibe from
that big ass hole in his torso okay close oh there still are odd jobs all right cool okay
i think there's a lot in this game i don't want to say i'm overwhelmed but you know look at me
it's gone whoa those are those are explosives those are explosives we got a raid we just raided
what happened the raid we did have a raid robert ninja thanks for the raid that was like an hour
ago how did i not see that it was like two hours ago why are you guys saying great now that's like
a fucking hour ago do it do it swing what's going on swing zr what happened all right getting close
to this guy there's another raid hold on i can't late andy i'm out of power oh did another raid
come in i think just messed up that's cool you're ignoring all raids i'm really not
because i accidentally sometimes miss but thank you though welcome two hours ago welcome to the
stream the fame got to him that was cool does this go away can i do this again it does go away
and i get a red coin cool find a designated match to try out and we're off well i want to do this
one then 100k andy streamer doesn't care about raids well there's not i'm not there's not 100k
andy happening right now i'll be chasing that high for the rest of my life so just in case you were
wondering suda in chat this game is amazing i love it so far it's high quality the juggernaut
of mass destruction diversity planet destroying freak when his shields are up your beam katana
will be deflected aim for the dark fog when attacking that oatfish looking form tells me
this guy is going to be pretty tough watch your beam katana power while fighting him
so he puts a shield up and then aim for the fog let's do this guy this is great i am very very
much interested all right you get that shield up that's fine
oh he's on the ground what's on me is there a bomb on me how did that happen
not yet strawberry oh no oh i'm out of power you have rage ah i don't think so here's the problem
when i'm really excited for a game i've been waiting for this game for at least a few hours
i can't get angry yet no it's gonna take at least probably two or three hours for me to care about
thinking mad again oh mustang mode what is mustang mode get up i want to see what mustang mode is
stop come on let's see what mustang mode is this game sucks fuck all right these guys are kind of
tricky i don't want to die to this he's mine yeah they're annoying these guys are annoying
they fuck with me these guys are annoying they fuck with me i don't like it these guys are annoying
that sucks blue sun thank you blue sun for the 26 community subs i just don't want to hit the
thing whatever i'll go for you i have a ton of health too jesus i'm not gonna be getting s on
this one hey hack it fast thanks for the five community subs it's been almost a year and you
have not streamed x-men world war ian origins okay sorry i was even reading the chat and also
playing that's why i lose half the fights i play all right that was bad it's all right if i get
about perfect dodge does perfect dodge count for this shield or probably it's probably the mine
no you're just bad whatever whatever see if i give a shit i don't care i don't even care like
okay fucking that's a hater like i don't care about and i fucking care about the hater right
you're bad at the game all right that's a hater fucking hater whatever
i thought i just got okay i think i'm stuck in the fence no yeah i am
come on what all right we're good hey dude did you um did you have cheerios this morning uh
honey nut cheerios it's okay it's a fucking hater like people that like hate on me and
shit for no reason i don't care fucking what an idiot no i'm not gonna let that guy piss me off
you should know though like you should know by now but i'm not gonna let a hater fuck with me
you know what i mean it is what it is you just know i'm on the internet right this is the worst
joke i'm sorry full face he'll rush at you suddenly when he draws his space katana try to pull off a
perfect dodge all right 100 000 haters among us guy calls out his haters if only the joke lasted
30 more minutes you want me to i'm not gonna keep that up for 30 minutes that's not worst joke 2021
come on because i'm pretending to have like way more people hate me than that actually come on
that's not the worst joke of 2021 i thought it was plus two personally all right so he has a do a
perfect dodge that's not what it's perfect but i'll take it all right it's like one let's see
one it seems pretty perfect to me
strawberry all right perfect dodge right before you get hit there it is
stunned nope now he is for the four pixels on the block yeah i actually don't know what those are
that's a good question i've yet to figure that out what those are oh it's item slug
that's sushi okay all right finally an s with dead pixel you know what's really weird about
dead pixels so like 10 years ago i feel like they've solved that problem because 10 to 15
years ago every monitor i ever had it was always such a tragic awful event when you would just see
the green dot appear i have not had a dead pixel on any monitor that i've had in the last probably
five years but it used to happen all the time so what i have to do three coins or something
this is my bike i remember sitting there with my fingernail out just tapping it a hundred times
there was so many weird old wives tales how to fix a dead pixel get a cloth put the cloth over the
dead pixel take a hammer slightly tap the hammer onto the cloth onto the pixel and then rub garlic
under your armpits none of them ever actually even did anything oh it's a scorpion how do i
get it i get it it smells fruity it reminds me of uh creepy crawlers creepy crawlers those weird
like plastic gel um they like smelled didn't they oh goodness triple putt watch out for his charges
when he turns invisible if you can dodge him then get behind him and whoop his ass bouncing all over
the place like that he's gonna try to hit and run me i gotta find a way to take him down they can
turn invisible and then wait for them to come out of invisibility i all right i will say that i
really like this one so far out of the two or three of them that have been out there so far
because it's not just guy in a suit almost every single enemy in the other normal heroes games
were just dudes with bats or guys in suits so there's like actual variety in the enemy
types which is really cool all right let's see what do you got come on whoa he jumped over it
what's the pokemon that is looking all the huge arms like this man champ yep grab him grab him
it's not his name what's his name my champ whatever man champ my champ so there's a blue
and a red one the blue one is probably just optional i assume right well i'm becoming
obsessive so i'm starting to become a little obsessive i want to do them all although i
there's a toilet over here hold on i did not hit that lady that's a lie fake didn't touch that
person they just rolled over because they i don't know they think of the what are you trying to give
money for me what happened didn't touch that person what it'll be um power tension attack power you
know what i'll take a couple of these i need 20k for the fight i have five of those already
wait there's a stranger over here dead food market wait who's this isn't it just terrible
the public toilets in the city are always clogged i'd like to test out your true fortitude could
you please fix the toilets before the whole world is flooded with excrement as a show of respect for
your winfully good heart i shall reward you handsomely once you've entered a new area on
the map first you'll need to find a toilet repairing a busted toilet will cause the map
to update itself and info on various locations in the vicinity will be displayed via icons
okay call the front desk use a plunger to fix the clogged toilet first move l locate the clog
and the radar will change color keep that position next shake the joy con to suck out the clog
beep all right shake it log where is it where get go in this first i feel like i'm gonna sneeze
i am i couldn't hit the mute button i know i tried to do that but i couldn't
i was like somebody punched me in the stomach in a like a beat-em-up game that was a beat-em-up game
henchmen die sound it was like
yeah good work seeing you work hard has truly moved me like this in a movie flyer it's a golden
axe death scream that's what i'm saying yeah okay so i did that what is there anything i can do now
besides that now i can save it that sound made my dog start barking log it again i got mail let's
look at the mail there's more tutorials there's something here though what is this number 12
take on the defense mission is this okay two waves yeah sure let's do it you're gonna play
this game all night i'll be playing this game for the next two days oh yes start the game
that's two waves
let's get uh let's get a perfect right seven seven no don't you think about it
no oh i did get a double nice okay cool where are they whoa all right let me get no hit
perfect let me get a perfect there it is throw crazy mode what's that throw crazy mode what's
that mean oh shit i can just okay cool i get it that was perfect one minute s nice highest is ss
boring dude just unclog into the toilet already all right i'm guessing you just can do that over
and over again for money because i don't have enough where's my bike so what is like the sushi
place is the toilet repair thing there's something else on the map back oh shit okay what is this
i am here to propagate fashion you show promise i will make you more stylish friendly aliens can
be found throughout town there's some really nice dudes who will hook you up with some cool t-shirts
each time you fulfill certain conditions you'll be able to score new t-shirts
are a total of over 5 000 bucks and i get the carl cs shirt you do not meet the requirements
how oh wrong money it's two different currencies there's a gold and then there is a clash of clans
gems got it all right i'm gonna do the last fight mission which where was it it was down here right
where was that mission it's not this way maybe it is that way come on is there a map map minus
all right where is it oh it's all the way down here okay like the tip
i fucking can't even oh you can zoom in and zoom out that's good to know t-shirt and something else
what is that somebody thinks to look at in this one this looks like the level from hitman 2 this
exact street is just that neighborhood like the mafia boss is in his house in the suburbs isn't
it just terrible one cannot even play catch with all this grass i'd like to test out your true
fortitude could you please clean up all this grass as a show of respect for your wings whimsically
good heart i shall reward you handsomely lawn mowing we go now oh the lawn mowing is back
mow all the grass before time runs out the lawn mower moves forward automatically press r to dash
move the lawn mower back with zl during moving backward press zr to return forward b to chant
all right whatever that's just that's that's the way you just do it when you you're pissed off
dad's like knock knock knock knock hey i thought you're gonna mow the lawn this weekend
i was but fuck i can't hey you're supposed to be mowing the lawn right now
but give me a hand out here man oh fine just fucking do it quick i don't fucking give a shit
i have five minutes to do this oh my god that's so me turn turn turn turn i gotta get this last
piece he's so relatable oh my god such a relatable thing to say i've got a gold rank what's that
worth i didn't have grass the basics next is the real thing prepare yourself appropriately
okay next is the real thing new level is unlocked well i want to do it level one volunteer mission
yes oh this is where it becomes real okay all right no messing around here all right whatever
d in turn makes you turn sharper okay let's do that of course the camera move with you this
actually was a better tactic how is that a better tactic all right now let's clean the rest up and
i'll be good back it up inefficient andy it doesn't need to be efficient just need to get done fast
you see that silver those controls are weird i think this is reward all right now i got 5000 um
wesson now i can get the shirt is there another level a little too everything's fine let you know
if anything comes up all right getting it done fast is what efficiency is well but what an
efficiency you can be really fast and do a terrible job that's not efficient if you go so fast that
you fuck the whole thing up you're just doing it as you're rushing that's not efficient if it's bad
efficient is fast and well exactly just because you sprint 100 miles per hour and go really fast
doesn't mean you did a good job that means that's inefficient you're bad at both though that's fine
don't listen to the haters yeah i know what the fuck there's a bunch of haters
if one of his shots hits you it'll screw up your death glove if he gets you in his sights dodge
he's small but definitely tough this could be a hassle but that name though leo pardon is pretty
badass okay so be careful just be careful here we go blood berry this guy's a boss
all right he's got like a cube all right let's go for a dodge nice you know i kind of like is
this how the game is i actually kind of prefer it like this shit i'm out of battery come on give me
a break oh what does it shoot what does it shoot that's a stun that's not all right i can i got
that one down strawberry throwing battery andy i don't i'm not i'm i'm you know i'm saying i
haven't took any shit i just did oh there's no i frames don't act like there's i frames jeremy
oh that's good oh battery andy god damn it fuck that hurts
what hit me that was cool i think that was pretty clean i was like an a what i thought that was
pretty clean to kick more for the high score yeah i keep forgetting i have it so that's that now
what cleared all the designated matches needed to enter the ranking battles we need to do next is
get to an atm and transfer the funds for the tournament entry fee it seems to show on the map
with a icon that looks i don't i don't even know what that is there's like a house like a bank
there's a really weird icon does that say atm oh it's okay i thought it was like a city you can
check out the coordinates on the map what the fuck is wrong with me you can check out the conditions
required to enter ranking battles via mail in the menu be sure to read them carefully
new mail i want to go to the mail how do i get to the mail what the hell pause this isn't mail
system records oh mail there it is all right 20 000 bucks at an atm this dude is smoking garlic
heroin but this t-shirt is over there and there's nothing else can't get my cards what is this
what is that it's a marker i put a marker down oh i didn't even know i did that
wait t-shirt i'm here to give you fashion requirements use death skills a total of 25
times i don't think i've done it i have not done it 25 times fine i mean atm how much garlic oil
do you smoke that's a nice watchdog's frame rate yeah it is a nice watchdog's frame rate here's
the difference this game stays on and this is actually fun no for a second i thought it
crashed i was about to laugh old family has served the royal family for about 23 700 years now
it has been pretty long this is apparently a specialty of this planet these humans line
up for more than two hours for this shit and you got some just for me i had damon's secretary
line up for it long lines delicious these little balls they drinking boba really that good
damon gave me some once back in the day i liked milk better so you two are like super close friends
right you and damon yeah we're real close how nice you're a good friend too sorry i got you
mixed up in this fight especially when you helped me break out friend i'm so honored i will give you
my life your majesty life isn't something you give away it's something you protect your majesty
didn't he like nuke like 600 million people in the beginning of the game
they kind of grow on you damn okay we gotta clean up here a lot of pizza okay here we go
rank matches access this entrance and you'll be thrown into a series of life or death battles
against the other rankers basically it's a bunch of boss battles okay you've got toilet breaks
sushi you can buy the power-up machine and death glove chips use all these to add your advantage
and be sure to prepare yourself for the deadly battles ahead good luck interesting
if i'm feeding the cat a candy bar this is weird what was that that's okay
the cat tree oh bonito flakes all right let's change i want to change clothes
put the jacket back on oh i have a mr black hole shirt i like that kill kill kill i get the kill
kale shirt all right kill kill kill back it off yeah keep the jacket off and what else can i do
now i'm about to do i'm about to fight um what's his name gold joe what the hell is this power-up
machine hey creepy ass otaku i'll use my power-up machine to enhance your skills for you stick in
all the wesson you got it's a power-up machine in dr naomi's lab by feeding wesson worlds and
supernova into the power-up machine you can enhance your health attack power power and
cooldown time required for using skills you can also use it to acquire new techniques
you can readjust your various status levels so try tweaking the balance till you find your
sweet spot and don't worry you can get back the wesson you put in power how do i do this a down
okay this is my power health attack power battery power level two death skill
for dash attack shake that to special ties when handheld style hold on i'm not gonna read this
again while dashing shake allows you to special attack okay so while i'm running i shake and i
can do a jumping slash cool is there anything else i can do i probably should do health right
that makes the most sense right now well i love this game i love this game this is very good
i'll do attack as well yeah i'm gonna do attack again hey i'm gonna do attack again
fuck i don't have money power level definitely i'm the battery andy let me i'm gonna do this twice
i don't want to deal with this can i do any more it's 1200 that looks pretty good for now
no special moves though i'm sorry that's cool time machine what is a time machine
it's a time machine in dr naomi's lab you can use it to have rematches against rankers you
fought in the past set the difficulty level higher to receive more awesome rewards for winning
so you just it's like a boss farm interesting okay death glove chip here you can equip and
create death glove chips what do you want to do equip here's the supercomputer access this to
create and equip death glove chips items which provide a wide range of special effects up to
three death glove chips can be equipped at once each chip has a strength and weakness find the
one that best suits your needs because i don't have any chips so let's say we're going to create
this keeps up this game of the year let me tell you right now the security access that's great
and equip death glove chips okay to create a chip you'll need junk for raw materials
and utopia coins to pay for development costs okay that's what the weird material i've been
getting junk is dropped by enemies and can be received as a reward for clearing volunteer
missions right like i've been doing and junk has different rarity the rarer the junk the harder
it is to find right so i have 500 bucks number one great chip trigger chip
what the fuck what there are 52 of these which i do how about number 35 that's how old i am so
noah chip when health is at 80 or above damage taken is 77 down oh i need to remove vinyl dolls
okay hold on after successful guard power consumed 20 down you'll get it later oh this is cool
normal attack power down five percent heavy attack power 10 up i don't know i kind of like that
it's five start at the top so as you take more damage but you do more damage
the world got psychonauts 2 and no more heroes 3 in a week we really do not deserve this
should i do damage yeah let's go mash the a button hard so there's one out of three do i have to wait
i have to do it three times to get it so i have to do this three times now once enough oh oh i have
three slots i've got three slots holy shit oh my god this opens up so much stuff okay
and i want this too i'm gonna do so much damage all right cool cool cool cool cool cool cool
all right let's do it this is awesome this is so cool this is so cool this really is
okay so damage taken so i'm gonna take five percent 10 more weapon attack all right so right now i've
got 30 heavy attack power but i take 10 more damage and my normal attack is a little weaker
very cool okay nice last cannon i'll take that sugar glass andy hey my dude this is don my sushi
we uh work with jeeber eats make sure you get your sushi nice and quick my sushi is the freshest
around even after traveling through time go ahead and pick some out of the menu
five of these already i don't have very much money i'll take one of these that's really cool
what a game tutorial room no no no no i don't even need to talk to the story we don't
there anything else i can do here the stairs exit no there's another room to check out in here
we're here oh wait shinobu i'm sorry i couldn't do anything can i not do anything
oh shit i probably can do something later right live streaming your injured friend
yeah that's pretty fucked up all right let's save it and now i'm gonna i'm gonna do the mission
let's go for it old joe see if i can kill him cat cat bet your ass i'm gonna well i'm
feeding the cat a cat stick that's okay uh i'll check upstairs before i do the fight
so you guys remember megaman legends that chip thing in your hand reminds me of megaman legends
that's like the coolest part of that whole game capsule toys i don't have any
am i ever gonna stream megaman legends 2 i have it back here so the plan is yeah i just don't know
when one day transfer tournament money time for the ranking battle head to the motel parking lot
take my mail all right we're good wait what is this that's not the ranking battle what is that
stalling no it's not called stalling it's called experiencing wait this is my apartment never
mind i am stalling fuck sorry i thought this is somebody else's apartment didn't he used it
wasn't his apartment upstairs that's his old apartment wait it's the same apartment i have
two apartments and no more heroes one and two you live upstairs but whose house is this it's not mine
either if i end up in my house i'm gonna be really upset so this is bad girls house how you
doing daddy daddy daddy daddy daddy charlotte watch this it might make you feel better i recommend
spice run with while being vogue to the still i don't know what that what they're saying
there's still some hope for this world spice run away this will prove it space run away well i don't
watch that much anime and that's not even a real anime there's another door over here i'm not
stalling andy i'm experiencing the game i've been waiting for three years to play andy that's what
you can call me you put in quotes experiencing game been waiting three plus years to play andy
what is this watch this you got a new t-shirt cat how much longer am i going to scream for
i don't know maybe a couple hours few hours i have to play at least a little bit with the kill kill
kill shirt all right let's do it gold joe sunflowers that's tomorrow
he is a space or dealer he smuggles and sells hazardous ores and minerals
the ores are made into weapons of mass destruction sands voicing sands is a threat to the peace and
safety of the galaxy go crazy travis welcome to the garden of insanity
no that's a disaster hold on i was oh my god that was really embarrassing remember the
uh all right hold on everybody slow down do you remember the joke from like an hour ago when i
said that sneezing wouldn't my sneezes sound like i'm a guy getting beat up in a beat-em-up game and
i die that's the die sound i started to feel the sneeze coming on and i was like fuck i gotta i
gotta be ready so i was gonna go like cuckoo cuckoo cuckoo cuckoo sneeze and but it didn't
work out that way it actually just kind of came out i couldn't even do the first part of the joke
let me move this that's then it's not the joke worst unfinished joke you're so cringe germa no
that said never change germa i just that was what i wanted to say matted it for some reason why
all right what'll be what do i have i've got five heels um i'm just gonna get a couple of these
because it might be an opportunity to use them fuck the haters that's my favorite of that i love
that oh i love that you guys are doing that now it's not just me all right i'm ready let's do
old joe this is totally different from the last spaceship so if their technology is different it
means these guys have all come from different planets this sounds dangerous we got to think
of a way to strike back just remember that earth also counts as a planet in space bloodthirsty
people are generally the same everywhere now come on let's go all right so what's your deal
he's about to change uh to get into the shower that's the only that's the move you do before
the pixelation comes on
something to think that you'd be ahead of us in this sort of artwork also that's way too much
time wasted on something like simple projection mapping don't waste budget money on shit like this
well judging by what i see i'm assuming you use magnets huh
snap crackle and pippity poppity poopity so you're going to use blue and red magnetic north south
to bust out some just slightly puzzlish attacks right damn that's what i thought bingo okay i'm
just gonna put this out there for red throw up an n mark above your head and throw up an s for blue
okay will make it simpler gamers like that kind of thing what does that mean i don't know if i can
it's a red and blue as you say but i'll try my best nice now show me a good time what do how do
i attack him when he's red and attack him when he's blue whoa blue he's blue
he's i gotta stand on blue to hurt him how does that what's that how does it work
all right he's red no he's blue what color is he i don't i don't understand i wasn't paying
attention i was i was looking he was making they were doing they were doing all right he's blue
he's blue now now that means i attack with blue i can attack whoa he's gonna hit the wall and
it's gonna hit the blue and i'm gonna get him points for it what that's not how magnets work
all right but when he said the really important line i didn't even my brain was not processing
what he was saying so i need red red red red red red red red red red red red i got red
it's a lot of damage spin it oh dodge it again again he's blue
whoa stunned him oh sorry about that red oh my god my health is zero
what just happened what happened oh my god i got insta killed don't let me down dude
what is this nothing in particular retry what happened what's going on i don't get it i don't
even know what happened he hit me i instantly died holy shit that was crazy okay let's go what
i'm so confused no no red dumb red red red red red red red red red red red where's red
am i red already you're standing on the red whatever done what's he doing here all right
All right, once again, blue.
No, no, don't, don't, idiot.
No, you fucking idiot.
I just hit him into the wall.
Come on.
What color, red?
Red.
Blue.
Ha, ha, ha.
All right, phase three.
Back it up.
Holy fucking shit, that was a lot of damage.
Red, got it already.
What do you got?
Oh, I'm already blue.
I'm already blue.
What's he doing?
Oh, red.
Get over here.
Goodness.
We don't want color, color, color, color.
Color, what color?
Pick one, pick a color.
Blue, got it.
All right, say goodnight, so.
Oh, oh, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
God, I got him.
I almost just died there.
That was cool.
I don't know if that's it, we're still in space.
Old Joe is dead.
Oh, I guess not.
I guess he's just dead.
I know, Adam Sandlin noises.
I'm gonna do those when I get into a situation
where I'm scared.
Is this the shit you've been smuggling?
Wow, you're a real shitty guy, huh?
Um, you probably shouldn't touch that stuff.
It's super dangerous.
It'll melt stuff, like everything.
That's why it makes such good money.
All right, then.
Bon apptit.
No, anything but that!
It's a Stardew Valley.
Damn.
It's the ones who don't look like bad guys
who are the real bad guys.
I see again.
Oh, well.
Somebody's saying I gotta use that.
How often does that kick refresh?
I did take a lot of damage, though.
I mean, come on.
The first time you see a boss,
I can go back in time traveling and get an S.
It's like every 30 seconds, every few minutes.
That was a cool fight, though.
That was fun.
Congratulations.
You have been recognized as number nine
in the galactic rankings.
What's that light?
Is it flying?
Well, yeah.
Talbot?
You guys are up.
You know, I never actually knew those dudes' names till now.
The series is going to keep going, right?
So we kinda had to give them names.
Council style, huh?
You like it, don't you?
They have names, yeah.
Not bad, but whatever.
This is space, right?
Can we do the small talk later?
Space?
You're still at the number nine spot.
You've got a ways to go.
Okay.
I thought you couldn't touch those.
But before all that, I wanna ask you something.
Also, I need to talk to you.
You ask me something?
Why are you helping them?
Is it because it's your job?
It is for you.
I mean, being your wife and all.
I do what I can to help my husband out.
What does that even mean?
These guys are basically evil aliens.
We do not know when they might swarm Earth.
So we need some kind of order here.
Yeah, that's true.
If we're using the same type of ranking system as usual,
then I've got a lot more experience.
That is why the UAA is running this thing.
Are they married?
Are the kids doing okay?
I don't remember that at the end of the second game.
We do not have time.
I will set up the match for the next ranking battle.
I said, what, did you say kids?
Make sure you kill them dead.
Sylvia, I still need to talk to you.
That's Travis Strikes Back lore.
I'll just read the Wikipedia page
for Travis Strikes Back, whatever it is.
All right, so we're number nine.
Oh, the intro.
Never skip the anime intro and outro.
I almost just accidentally did.
Every time you watch an anime intro and outro,
you experience those same internal dopamine hits.
Probably you never want to skip them.
Because everybody has their favorite moment
in the anime intro or outro.
Like their favorite character's on screen
doing something really cool, animated at 60 FPS,
because they don't do that in the real show,
the actual show.
Your favorite character does this like dash, slash, slash,
jump, eye into the camera at like 700 frames a second.
You know you're never going to get to see
that actually happen in the show.
Maybe you will in some shows.
Man, looks great in that intro.
So many shows intros are better than the actual show.
Game's already over.
It is not already over.
Travis Strikes Again next stream, loser.
Tell me what to do.
I hope we get, are you still watching?
That'd be hilarious.
The guest has arrived.
Mr. Black Knight direction.
Huh, let him in.
All right.
And just who do we have next?
The emperor of the night.
What?
Do you doubt our power?
No, no.
That's not what I meant.
I was hoping I could be of help.
You want to help?
Then sit there quietly.
Dick.
Lord Froon had to get to see you again.
Any wish of yours is old Black Knight directions command.
Travis must be dealt with.
I'm leaving him to you.
Don't let me down.
I will not let you down.
Interesting character.
I feel like there's three people in there.
Just people standing where the shoulders are.
And they're all moving as one.
They're on a custom map, GM flat grass.
Oh, that's funny.
What's Mieke's best film?
That'd be Gozu.
What do you think?
Gozu, of course.
What's the most bad ass Mieke film then?
Dead or Alive.
You?
Shield or Straw.
Nice.
What's the most fucked up Mieke film?
Audition, right?
Everything you need to-
Hold on, here it is.
Visitor Q.
Oh shit, I haven't seen that one.
For reals?
Oh, you gotta see Visitor Q.
Let me borrow it.
Nope.
I'm totally gonna keep it.
I'll keep it back.
Come on, you know I will.
Hell no.
You always steal my shit after borrowing it.
Okay, then check this out.
I'll lend you the whole Kaoru Chan series.
You're so badass.
Yeah, Mieke is hella badass.
By the way, this is all actual film commentary?
What do you mean?
That'd be the shit.
They pulled transcripts from actual film critic stuff?
They're real.
Really.
Oh, I got the Gold Joe T-shirt.
I kinda need to see that.
I feel like I'm gonna put that on.
Ooh, I like that.
No, no, no, no, no.
I wanna see.
Come on.
I pressed L.
I don't know why it didn't register.
L, R.
I can't switch to L.
Oh, it's cause this is a whole outfit.
Oh, I get it.
Till.
They're talking about real movies.
Oh, it was Gold Joe.
I wish the Gold Joe shirt was actually gold.
You think it should be gold?
I'll put that on.
I'll wear the jacket for a little while.
And we gotta change our outfit every time we get a chance.
I don't wanna just wear the same thing.
Okay, save it.
Wait, Gene.
What is the last Japanese movie you watched?
I don't know.
I can't tell you the last movie I watched.
Can I?
Oh, yes, I can.
Cromwell.
Was it good?
I don't know.
It was free on YouTube,
and I was just like,
this is kinda funny to watch this.
It's one of those movies where everyone talks like this.
Will it please the court for them to know
that Cromwell, I will be exiled?
Like, it's one of those movies.
Parliament, parliament needs to,
I will not stand for parliament.
We will absolve and dissolve parliament.
That was the whole movie.
And then there was a bunch of fight scenes and stuff.
All right, I gotta kill some more people.
What was the last Japanese movie you watched?
Cromwell.
No, I didn't.
Cromwell takes place,
it's based on the English and Ireland and Scotland.
They're all fighting each other as priests and shit,
and because they ride horses,
they throw knives at each other and stuff.
They have sword fights,
and I don't know what his name is,
something Cromwell.
He ends up becoming the King of England,
or whatever it was, I don't remember.
I've slept and woke up three times.
The ads woke me up, okay?
I'll be honest with you.
If you watch YouTube movies for free,
the ones that are on YouTube,
there's like 10 ads throughout the movie,
and they'll wake you up if you're fucking asleep.
I don't know when the last Japanese movie I watched is.
I have no idea.
I don't know.
You level up, like, oh no, you have to get, okay.
He never became the King.
No, he owned Parliament.
He got rid of Parliament,
and then he brought back Parliament,
because the King got rid of Parliament.
So it was like, we need to fight to get Parliament back.
I don't know, they said Parliament,
they said that word like 400 times in the movie.
Oh, nice.
Shedded snakeskin.
And then he became King of Japan.
What was the last, like, okay, movie based on Japan,
or in Japan, or like a Japanese film?
Name some Japanese films that have come out.
Maybe I've seen them, I don't know.
Oh, I got a card.
Romwell's really good.
I mean, it was entertaining.
Need to watch Akira.
I've already seen Akira.
Two decades ago, whatever, a decade ago.
Seen Spirited Away, yeah, a long time ago.
Ooh, Flame Tea.
Romwell is 45% on Rotten Tomatoes.
Was it really?
I mean, I didn't watch the movie
because I thought it was gonna be a good movie.
Oh, I also saw the one Lindsay Lohan
pretends to be pregnant.
The whole movie.
I forget what it's called.
Guys, these are free on YouTube,
and I'll just load one up for fun in the background.
Just not even pay attention.
I don't know, the movie's called, like,
I'm Expecting or something.
What's it called?
Labor Pains, yeah, that's what it's called.
There's a fight here, hold on.
Lawn mowing.
What was the last movie you actually watched?
I don't know.
What was the last movie I actually watched?
I sat down and watched Start to Finish.
It's, like, so gone from my brain right now.
The Force Awakens III, what was it called?
The Sith are always, Eternal Sith, what's it called?
It was, they all have the same name.
I'm not gonna look at chat
because I need to figure this out on my own.
Star Wars, Attack of the Clones,
Star Wars The Phantom Menace,
Star Wars Revenge of the Sith,
Star Wars A New Hope,
Star Wars The Empire Strikes Back,
Star Wars The Return of the Jedi,
Star Wars The Force Awakens,
Star Wars The Last Jedi,
Star Wars The Never-Ending Sith, what is it?
It's something just like Revenge of the Sith.
What the fuck is it called?
I'm not gonna look at chat.
I'm gonna sit here until I get it
because this is embarrassing that I don't know this.
The Way of the Sith, the end of the Sith.
I don't know the movie.
Apparently, I don't give a shit about this movie.
Star Wars The Next Generation.
No, that's Star Trek.
I don't know.
I don't know what the lightest Star Wars movie is
and it's gonna kill me.
I am turned around in my chair right now
to make sure I don't look at the screen.
Phantom Menace Clone Wars,
Revenge of the Sith,
A New Hope,
Empire Strikes Back,
Return of the Jedi,
Force Awakens,
The Last Jedi,
and The Last One.
What is it?
I can't do it.
I'm not turning around until I get this.
This is fucking embarrassing for me.
The end of the Sith?
No, the Sith of the,
the width of the Sith?
No, that's not it.
Although that's probably on Pornhub.
I give up, what is it?
I have no idea.
I don't know, what is it?
I give up.
What is it?
Rise of Skywalker.
Oh my God.
God.
How, right.
The movie was so bad that he forgot it.
No, it's, ah, whatever.
I'd like to test out your true fortitude.
Could you please clean up all the grass?
As a show of respect for your whimsically good heart,
I should reward you handsomely.
But let's be completely honest.
I don't even,
if I don't even remember the title of the movie
and it's in one of the most celebrated franchises ever,
I probably didn't care that much, right?
I can't pretend I did.
All right, let's do another one more.
Lag X just gave 50 community subs.
That's insane.
That's a massive amount of community subs.
That's hundreds and hundreds of dollars.
Holy shit.
Three, two, one.
Thank you, Lag X.
That's insane.
That's a lot of money.
All right, I'm gonna do this right.
I really do blame the camera though.
I'm going to.
I think doing this like a little spurt, it helps.
I missed a piece, but all right.
Next game.
I'm not doing next game.
I'm playing this.
I'm playing Heroes 3, but I've been waiting
three years for this.
No, turn, turn, turn.
Didn't even have to look, but that's good.
Is there anything higher than gold?
Thousand, that's it.
All right, well that's lawn mowing.
And then I've got this.
Volume one volunteer mission, sure.
That was the tutorial.
Oh my goodness gracious, okay.
Shit, I didn't know it could overheat.
Only three minutes.
I got plenty of time, I'm good.
I hate turning that camera.
Camera's the worst, damn it.
I wish that just turned with you.
Why do I have to use my other right stick to turn too?
Oh, fuck you.
Oh God, give me a break.
That was not clean, but I'll take the money.
Using turn signals with a mower.
Bronze, yuck.
I don't care.
New level has been unlocked.
Be cool.
All right, new level unlocked.
It's probably later on.
There's a toilet over here.
Oh my goodness.
Have you ever mowed a lawn in real life?
Yes, many, many times.
When I'm mowing the lawn, I don't turn my head backwards
and use my left and right thumbs to turn.
Oh, excuse me.
Where is this?
Where's this toilet?
This game blows and it really doesn't.
I assure you.
All right.
Where is it?
Fuck the haters, no.
Cereal shitter.
Oh, the recording thing.
So confused by that.
We'll save the game.
No more heroes is if someone turned the combo's pizza snacks
into a video game.
Why do I know what you mean?
I, yeah, I get it.
Yeah, that's true.
It's such a weird thing to understand,
but I know what that means.
It's over here.
By the way, I can't find those anymore.
You know what else I can't find?
This is really starting to agitate me.
Pretzel goldfish.
What happened to them?
Where are they?
I can't find them anywhere.
Have you noticed that?
Those are my favorites.
They still exist here.
I feel like there's like a few places in the world
or in the country or something
that are not getting the supply or something.
All right, you have the driving skills of a true champion.
Could you possibly entertain a request?
These vulgar thugs only able to follow their flock
have been utterly terrorizing the highway.
The day my grandmother was on her way to work
when these cretins almost ran her off the road.
It was probably me.
I absolutely cannot abide.
Please put these criminals in their place.
Destroy the head runaway car before time runs out.
Destroy the followers to extend the time limit.
Don't hit normal cars.
There's actually a,
there's a pretzel goldfish shortage.
It's really sad.
Okay, accelerate, brake, boost.
Do I have to smash into them?
What?
Holy shit, I'm going too fast.
Those gems.
I'm so close.
Oh, I'm sorry.
So avoid the cars coming this way.
That's all I have to do.
Shit.
This is, you know what?
This is the stupid toad level in Mario Kart.
The highway toads, whatever it's called.
That's my least favorite Mario Kart level
in the entire 30 years span of that entire series.
I hate that level.
It looks stupid.
All the toads driving the wrong side of the road.
Come here.
There he is.
Silver, that's fine.
Make a funny sound.
I just did.
I just did the toad finish.
You just heard it.
I just did it.
You just got a funny sound.
That wasn't funny.
The whole world doesn't drive on the wrong side of the road.
But where, okay, but our toad is toads in England?
Toadville in like Europe?
Japanese.
Doesn't Japan drive on the right side of the road?
I thought Japan drives on the right side of the road.
There's one or two other countries on earth that do that.
Where is it?
Singapore?
Is it Japan?
Who does it?
South Africa, the United States.
No, I'm serious.
It's more than a few countries.
Well, who drives on the right side of the road?
USA, China, Russia.
Japan too, right?
No, not Japan.
Mexico does, yeah.
All of South America.
Japan drives on the left side.
Well, I haven't seen a Japanese movie in a long time.
So I don't know anything about Japan apparently.
Most countries do drive on the right.
I'm thinking of like the metric system
versus empirical, right?
Who is it?
I got it wrong.
I'm thinking of like the metric system.
Who uses empirical?
Imper, whatever, whatever it's called.
Who uses it?
It's the United States and like three other countries.
I'm not drunk.
No, I'm not.
It's the US and Myanmar.
Okay, let's go.
How much money do I need?
Shit.
I need $25,000.
How much do I have now?
I gotta turn around.
Dude's got a garlic aioli brain.
No, oh my God.
There's a toilet over here.
Let's make some money.
This game is, this game's tight, it is.
This game is awesome.
Where are these missions?
This one's like over here.
Hello.
You eat raw cloves, admit it.
I mean, look, I don't wanna tell people
to eat raw cloves of garlic because it's really, really harsh.
I already did this shit like three days ago.
I'm not gonna go over this again.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, garlic.
When you crush garlic, allicin comes out
and when you cook garlic, it gets rid of a lot of the allicin.
I don't know, we don't have to go over this again.
It's actually, eating raw garlic is really intense
and I do not really recommend people do that.
But, you know, just I'm telling you.
Pickled garlic is really good.
Garlic, anything is good.
I love that shit so much, you have no idea.
Empty cans littered everywhere.
He's going to dispose of all the garbage.
Pick up all the empty cans.
Okay, press the A button to pick up trash.
If you're attacked by an alligator,
press the button displayed on the screen.
Uh, watch out for alligators.
Crash, crash, I couldn't even read what that said.
That was an A upside down.
That was an upside down A.
I can't, this is hard.
That's what I know, but like it looked like a fucking A.
Where's the rest of the trash?
Crash, I don't see anymore, where's it?
Where's the pieces of trash?
There's no trash left.
I don't see any trash, that's, okay.
Ugh, listen, this is why I'm going to go
on a fucking rant here.
I'm going to go on a huge rant.
I don't know if people are going to think I'm an idiot
and stupid and whatever.
Why, there should have been a goddamn Congress law
that all video game consoles should just have
the same letters and same button mappings.
But they're like face buttons.
Cause like Xbox, X is where the Y is.
B is where the A is.
Triangle is where the X is.
If you play all the consoles equally,
I play all consoles equally, all of them.
When I put into muscle memory where A is on Xbox One,
that is where A is on Switch.
There should be a goddamn Congress law
that states that has to be there.
And that's not even important,
it's a literally first world problem
and nobody really cares, do it again.
But that's my only defense.
Is when I see Y on the screen, I press Y on Xbox.
If I see X on screen, I might press X
where it is on PlayStation.
It's wherever my muscle memory of my brain
decides to go for that moment.
Unless you play on one console, obviously,
then you're not gonna have this problem at all.
But you know, whatever.
It's usually the last console
that I spent the most time with.
So I was playing a lot of Xbox before this
and I use my Xbox controller on PC all the time.
So, and where is the rest of the trash?
Am I freaking out here?
You see that?
Rotate, the camera wouldn't rotate anymore after that.
I was literally trying to rotate the camera
and it wouldn't rotate any further
to see the other side, I promise you.
Play the seal video, I already did it.
Hey, is it tutorial again?
I wanna do the actual mission, there we go.
Play it again, I will in a minute.
Why, fuck, that's not why, that's Xbox Y.
I just pressed the up button, the top one.
I get it, it changed the layout.
I feel like I would do the reverse problem.
I would start overthinking it
and try to hit buttons that were,
it says X on screen, I'll press the right one that time.
60 seconds, wait till it gets ported to PC.
Nobody tell them, nobody's gonna tell them.
Just emulate it with a switch emulator.
I don't think that makes it, I don't think those exist.
The thing is, I don't think I would ever emulate anything
on the current gen because it's available to just play.
The problem with emulate, oh my God, I have nine seconds left.
I don't know where it is, it's right there.
Ah, I have 0.4 seconds to press A.
Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Did I get it?
Got it.
What was I saying?
Oh, right, right, right.
So the reason why emulation is something
that I have done in the past, right,
is because sometimes you just can't get access to anything.
Even when I play a game from like 20 years ago
that is never gonna get released ever again,
that you may even have in a closet,
up in your attic or whatever.
It's just, it's impossible to ever do it again.
And like, I'm gonna, okay, I'm gonna take a shot
at Nintendo here.
You don't solve that problem by releasing
like one Super Nintendo game a week
that nobody gives a shit about on like the Switch Online.
Like, oh, new Super Nintendo games available.
It's like one or two, it's like every like week or two.
Not even, sometimes it's like once a month.
It's like you, like I would actually pay for this.
I really would.
And I understand like, oh, but we don't want to just
dump everything on.
I would pay a very hefty, more than like Netflix fee.
I would pay a Netflix style fee
if they just dumped whatever they were able
to actually license still.
Just give us everything.
I'll pay a monthly fee for it.
I want to play the games and I will pay for it.
But like, well, there's like 31 games on the Switch Online
and you know, maybe we'll, maybe you'll get like Rygar.
Okay, yeah, I guess.
I don't want to rent, I want to own.
I will pay for these games.
Yeah, they had the virtual console
and everybody like loved it.
And then there was probably some licensing problem
to bring it over, right?
But still, I would pay more than what I pay for Netflix.
They have access to like every
available licensed regular Nintendo game.
And they wonder why people like emulate it.
That's the why, is they want to play.
You talk, look at the younger audience, right?
The younger kids.
They hear all these stories.
Oh my God, you have no idea.
Super Mario One, Super Mario Two, Super Mario Three.
No, you didn't play, you didn't play Unicycle.
That game was amazing.
The Unicycle racing game for the Super Nintendo.
You idiot Zoomer, you have no idea how good it was.
I want to play.
Oh, you're never going to get a chance.
Like they want to have those experiences.
Dude, I remember Clay Fighter.
Yeah, me and my like 30 year old buddy
are talking about Clay Fighter.
Oh, Frosty the Snowman, it was awesome.
Purr, purr, purr, hurt, hurt, hurt.
Oh, I loved, Taffy, it was awesome.
Was that this guy that, this kid's like 19
where you didn't play it?
Good luck, idiot.
We loved it, we played it.
Don't you wish you had an experience like us?
They kind of do, they want to play it.
They would love to do it.
So like they have to find a way to play it, right?
It's not rocket science.
And I don't know, but like punishing like,
I don't have like a reason to go get Clay Fighter
for the Super Nintendo.
Like I don't, or like Clay Fighter 63 and third, whatever.
So I already experienced that.
I played it a shitload when I was younger.
And if we're going to hold these games
to this like really high, almost like gatekeep standard
to like the younger gamers,
they should be able to play it.
They should have an opportunity to play it
without having it being illegal.
That's just what I think.
Why is it being illegal stopping you?
Well, I'm not saying it is, but the fact that like you,
look, going and getting like an emulator
and downloading ROMs and shit,
it's like you'd nobody, people like actually kind of
don't really want to do that.
Like a young audience.
Like if you're talking, like when I was like 13, 14, 15,
oh, what you got to do, you got to go
with this piece of software.
You got to go get this ROM.
You got to drag the ROM into here.
By the way, hit escape.
And you have to do a configure
a bunch of fucked up video settings.
And oh, by the way, maybe the ROM doesn't work.
Oh, maybe, but I can't feel like viruses and shit.
It's like, it's just, it's just troublesome.
It's not the same experience.
Yeah, and look, I am forever grateful
to the people that were able to kind of archive
a lot of this stuff.
Because without emulation,
without people doing ROMs and emulation,
and having to be like a real passionate thing
that people did, we probably wouldn't be able
to even have half of these things.
We wouldn't be able to even care
about half of these franchises, I don't think.
All right, what do I need?
Get C rank or higher in one defense mission.
I did it already.
Otaku Freak is the name of this item.
I guess I'll put it on, okay.
But here's the thing, I'm also not naive enough
to say that, oh, just put all 700 Super Nintendo games
up on the Super Nintendo online Switch thing.
Like there's licensing deals.
There's like music that probably was
in some of those games that they can never
like actually release ever again.
I do, but it'd be nice to see like a real actual effort
to really put on a bunch of stuff that they can put on.
Like Super Mario RPG can't be released easily again.
Right, isn't that a huge reason why we're never gonna see
Turtles in Time?
Probably, but who stands, I hate, okay, here we go.
You ready?
Who stands to gain from that?
They're not selling copies of Turtles in Time
really anymore, they remade it, right?
Didn't they like redo like Turtles in Time
or like a version of it?
They made like a new beat-em-up
like five or six years ago, right?
They're not selling Turtles in Time anymore.
Like, I don't know, I just don't understand why.
It's such an awesome piece of media
that people should be able to enjoy.
And even if they were to get it together
and like charge for it again, like a few bucks or something,
whatever, that's fine.
But just to like delete this shit from all history
and say, don't ever look at it ever again.
Don't look at it.
If you look at it, then it's illegal.
But like, I mean, it was awesome.
I like wanna look at it.
You can't like, okay, you can't like have the Picasso
be a painting that existed.
And then you like put the Picasso behind a fucking,
like a black screen,
just because it's fucking like more than 100 years old.
Well, you see, oh, I wanna come see,
I wanna come see all Picasso's paintings.
Well, see, there's an issue there.
You can't look at them anymore.
Why not?
Well, because it's been a pretty long time
and we just kinda don't feel like
showing it to anybody anymore.
So what about, can I,
but there's images of Picasso's paintings online.
You look at them, you're going to fucking jail.
Okay, thanks.
Appreciate, I guess I get,
my like older, like 35 year old boomer friend
will tell me how cool they were.
All right, I'll rant over.
Don't give him any ideas.
All right, what am I actually supposed to be doing right now?
I've lost all control of the stream.
What was I doing?
Okay, ATM, I gotta make 25,000 utopia coins.
So let's go do a mission.
Get on the highway and head to the thunder dome.
Okay, friends with 35 guy,
friends with older 35 year old.
No, I'm just saying, like,
you get to watch like YouTube videos
of dickheads like me telling you,
oh my God, and it was the coolest thing ever.
It was the best experience ever.
It was so fun.
I said rant over, I know.
I love the weekly rants, keep it up.
Ooh, something right here.
Where is it?
ATM, wait, where's the, there it is.
Oh, it's the rant.
I can't say that.
Those are facts.
Oh, there's Twitch here.
Twitch dev, what's going on?
Hello.
Wesson mining is dangerous and can prove fatal.
No one ever returns.
I'd like to test out your true fortitude.
Could you please take over Wesson mining in the cave?
All right, mining, it's Bonzi buddy.
It is.
Okay, dig up Wesson before the time runs out.
Just swing the pickaxe, run around in mine.
Did I get it?
I got it, okay, go.
Shut up.
Okay, I got to count how many times it takes to do it.
It's lava.
Like, can I go over here?
No, where is it?
Is that it?
It's two out of two.
How do I leave?
Is that it?
Yeah!
Tutorial, oh, okay, okay.
I heard you talk shit about Nintendo.
I'm not talking shit about Nintendo.
I'm just bringing up a point.
I'm playing on a Nintendo console right now.
But here's another part two to this.
This is a really important part two.
I think we don't think too much
about this particular part two.
What happens in another 50 years, 100 years?
What happens in 30 years when like 10 more consoles are out?
Does this all just disappear,
all this shit that we've done?
We have to like preserve this stuff,
otherwise it just goes away.
Dude, there are people that like,
they turn off like the servers to play games sometimes.
Like all these, that's like the big proponents against
always online games, right?
What happened?
Well, let's try that again.
You can fall in the lava.
Look at the seal video.
No, no, I refuse.
You mined straight down.
Yeah, kind of.
All right, well, I'm gonna go this way.
Watch out for the fire.
What happened?
I have to fight enemies in here too?
What the fuck?
I'm so confused.
Grab.
I gotta remember how to get the hell out of here.
This is two.
Two heavy hits and that's it.
Seven, two out of seven.
This is gonna be my least favorite one.
I'm gonna get so lost here.
Aye, aye, aye.
Get it.
Oh my fucking God, this sucks.
Same exact place.
I'm gonna try this one more time,
then I don't even care.
This is level one.
Okay.
I'm gonna go left.
Wait for this fire to go.
I can jump.
I just jumped in the, whatever.
You all saw what happened.
I don't need to tell you what happened.
These missions are tough
because they have to actually fight them too.
I don't know where I am,
but I apparently...
No.
Pretty good dodges in this fight corridor though,
I will say.
No seal, no meal.
I'll show the video again.
I'll play it again.
Get the fuck out.
And dig.
How are you?
It's two heavy, one normal.
It's two heavy.
What the fuck?
Gonna explode and...
Shut up.
I'm gonna see, is it three swings maybe?
Three normal swings and then one.
I gotta get a good rhythm here.
It might be one, two, three, three.
Seal, seal.
Stop.
I'll show the seal in like 10 minutes.
Invincible mode.
Ooh.
What's wrong?
It's gonna be one, two, let's see.
One, two, three.
Let's do, two, let's do three.
Let's do four.
One, two, three, four.
Nope, that's a bad strategy.
We'll do one and then two heavy.
There's only three more.
Take it slow, don't be a fucking idiot.
I'm probably not gone.
Went down there.
Haven't gone this way.
I did go this way though.
No, not all the way.
Hey, don't be stupid.
It's up there.
What about this way?
One up there.
Two more.
Where's this last one?
Where's the last one?
Come on.
Where is it?
I gotta leave.
There's the exit.
Can I jump?
Can I make this jump?
How many noises today?
Yeah, you're getting a lot of slurps tonight.
That's for sure.
All right, 25,000, right?
I still have to do those missions before the boss.
So, probably should get over there and start doing this.
There's actually one over here.
Seal time.
Yes, it is.
Here you go.
Here's the seal video.
Five, four, 19, 84, 10, 47, 10, 47.
Hey, hey.
This actually might be,
this actually might be the best video ever
I've ever seen.
It's pretty high up there, I think.
I think it is.
We can't see?
Oh, well, you'll just take,
I can't put it up right this second.
It's on the subreddit.
RGerman985 is there.
If one of the parasites shot up from its mouth
lashes onto you, you'll be rendered immobile.
Watch out for the parasite face attack.
I'm pretty sure I've fought this dude in the tutorial,
right?
Okay, bring it on for real this time.
Show me what you got.
Get ready.
Okay, it moves really slowly.
Because you can't even touch it.
But I thought it was like a pistol or something.
Here are the ads.
All right, let's go.
What?
I was in super mode.
Heavy attacks only, Jeremy.
Doubt.
Yeah, this guy is a pain in the ass, isn't he?
Can I get rid of those?
Is there any way I can actually kill those things?
Good toss.
Again, grab.
Oh, it didn't work.
What's that?
Oh my goodness, that hurt.
I want to dodge.
Stop swinging too much.
You're being greedy.
Stop it.
Wait for an opportunity.
I have to relax today.
Here we go.
Here comes a C rank.
Yeah, whatever.
Dodge when it's purple.
Hey man, it's either just easier said than done though.
You get like a 10th of a second to make that decision.
Just be happy they're not Ds.
Ds what?
You know.
There's another one.
There's another mat.
There's something right here.
I'm kind of standing right on top of whatever this is.
What is it?
Number 33, take on the defense mission.
Two waves, yes.
Are you going to do another royalty free movie night?
I thought about it,
but I feel like we've watched the good ones.
It's two of these Katana guys.
All right, let's do this right off the bat.
And get it from behind.
Grab it.
Ooh, nice.
Recommend the second game.
Um, hold on.
Can't talk right now.
Hold on.
Come here.
Can't talk while he's focused.
No, not at all.
My brain can only focus on one thing at a time.
Only one, nothing more.
That should be a B at least, right?
That's a B.
I was wave two.
Oh my God.
This harder than that.
I forget what these guys do.
Oh my God.
I forget these guys explode.
I got to activate these.
Ow.
Be careful.
Holy shit.
What's my opinion on sardines?
Love them.
No.
Oh, come on.
I hate these guys.
I hate these teleporting bullshit enemies.
Ugh.
Oh, fuck you.
What?
Oh.
If that's a C, then this game is hard.
I may have probably,
I could have done that a little faster on the second phase.
Skill usage.
Another C.
You gotta be perfect to do that shit.
Okay, somebody said,
do you recommend the second game?
I would say you should play at least the first two.
The only reason why I didn't play Travis Strikes again
is because I wasn't a fan of the top-down stuff.
I was gonna play it before this,
but I heard very, very mixed things about that game.
And not only that,
it's all top-down.
I think there's a couple of segments that aren't.
But, where's this fight?
Oh, there it is.
Transform!
Travis Strikes again is better than two.
Um, I really have to give it a chance.
But someone actually please correct me if I'm wrong here.
Change bucamelia!
Isn't Travis Strikes again a 40-hour game?
I feel like these games-
That's huge!
Whoa.
It's like 12.
I guess I'm, is it just wrong?
Fuck no, definitely not.
Like 15.
Okay, well this isn't new.
This is like a boss.
This giant suddenly appeared in Stratosphere
and has grown miraculously
in minus 270 degrees Celsius temperatures.
His ice cannons are powerful enough
to destroy entire planets.
Stay calm.
Your eye camera sensors will scan enemies for weak points.
That's gonna help.
These super big dudes always have a core
serving as their weak point.
All right, so let's get up here.
Phase one.
Wow!
Okay, so I hit him in the head.
Ice core.
Okay, we're good.
Mouth's open.
Yeah.
All right, when his mouth opens,
it's like a big clam.
Shoot it in the ear.
Oof.
I'm gonna open.
I just, I didn't get it.
His mouth is open now.
Shit.
Oh, I messed up, I messed up, I messed up.
Wait until he opens his mouth.
Here it goes.
Open up.
Open.
That's the shit on his ears.
All right.
I'm open.
Lockpad.
Just keep saying the same thing.
Say anything else, Travis.
Open your mouth.
I didn't even hit him.
What?
I can hit him.
Oh, I guess it's, okay, whatever.
Stop blocking.
What just happened?
What?
Was I just not even paying attention
to my health or something?
Are you serious?
What?
I don't understand.
I just wasn't looking at my health.
Change Bukabilia.
I had literally one HP.
Oh, that's annoying.
Why was I not looking at that?
I don't think I even had a heal.
Oh shit.
It is over there.
There's so much stuff on the screen.
It's almost like I couldn't even pay attention to it.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm not, fuck the cannon.
Yeah, like fuck the cannon.
I'm not even gonna use the cannon.
Cranberry.
These things are just better.
Poisonberry.
Go for that gas breath.
Over here.
Special kill.
Watch that health.
Lockhead.
Oh, that hit.
God damn it.
It's so hard to avoid that.
Get away.
Okay, now this is where he killed me instantly last time.
In the hands?
Let's get that core.
Come here.
Oh shit.
Where are those things?
I don't wanna hit them.
Phase two and he's dead.
That's a very bad score because I died.
I swear he didn't say that this much when I played.
Yeah, I know what it is.
Really?
Interesting.
Because I died?
Yeah, how many of these would I not get to see on
if I knew what it was, didn't take a bunch of damage,
and could retry it and do it again?
There's two more?
There's actually like three more.
Oh, this is the toilet.
Let's do the toilet.
And this one over here.
This is also a, is it red?
This one's just regular.
Do the toilet first.
This is what Vegas looks like?
Kind of.
A lot of it.
What is that?
Why does it have a big star on it?
Is that what it looks like when you step over it?
No.
I don't think I've ever seen what they look like
on the minimap.
Hey, oh, my hands are shaking now.
Do it already.
My friend is watching.
Please say something funny.
No, I don't really feel like it.
Yeah, we've reached the part of the stream
where I'm just like, my back's against the chair.
Got my Joy-Cons here, I'm just leaning back,
and I'm just enjoying this video game
because it's a good one.
We've reached enjoy the game portion of the stream
where I'm just, my back is just here.
Leaning back.
Evolver burger.
I think I've done it 25 times.
I want to keep the other shirt.
How is my back doing?
I'm doing, I'm good.
What else is here?
The toilet, the bike, and the shirt.
I was actually not horrible after the dollhouse stuff,
which is surprising considering
I kind of beat the shit out of myself.
But yes, the reduced time sitting down
has absolutely helped.
I will be completely honest with you
and I'm proud of you.
Going back to once or twice a week
and not sitting down,
because, I mean, a couple years ago,
two years ago or so,
probably really was not doing myself any favors
by sitting down here for seven to 10 hours a night.
Because there was this part of the stream life
that I've had where when I first started streaming,
I streamed for two hours,
like two or three times a week.
And then when I made the full transition to Twitch
and stopped completely doing YouTube at all,
that I started doing seven, eight, nine hour streams.
Three, four, five times a week sometimes.
At least three or four times a week.
And that probably was not a good thing to do.
This looks hard, hold on.
So my body was already having these issues
and I was sort of making them worse, I think.
But ever since being able to kind of sit here
and stream for once or twice a week,
five to seven hours, four to six hours, something like that,
I don't have like a time limit really.
Hey, this jumping guy is so annoying.
Oh, this place sucks.
I don't think I have any food left.
There he is.
All right, take care of him.
Ooh, Mustang mode.
Mustang, Mustang, Mustang mode.
That's what Mustang mode is, okay, good.
You say you're gonna get a standing desk?
Yeah, and so here's the thing though.
It's stationary.
The more that I am stationary, the worse it is.
So even with a standing desk, standing in the same spot
is essentially the same thing.
Make a treadmill, get a treadmill desk?
No, that's not gonna happen.
I'll be winded in 10 minutes.
All right, now I have enough, I can do the ATM
and start the next fight.
I think you'll bill one halo
for the five community subs, appreciate it.
But it's not been bad lately.
There was a few times on stream where you probably saw
like when the face cam was on or not.
You can always tell when I'm really uncomfortable,
when my shoulders go back and I push my chest up
more than once or twice every few minutes.
He is but a simple human.
I'm going to cut off his arms
and we'll then proceed to slice him up nicely.
Hey, tell me about some of your memories.
Feeling sentimental, hmm?
I don't like it when a friend dies.
This happened a long time ago.
I went on a family trip to the sea
but I don't remember anything about the ocean.
What was burned into my memory was a shop
with a glass bulb hanging from the ceiling.
I was moved by the sound of the jingling glass.
And when I left the shop, there was a white lighthouse.
But as for where that place was, I have no idea at all.
That's a nice story.
Let's go out there and find that lighthouse together.
Lord Fool.
Thank you.
Now go, Black Knight direction.
I'm off.
It's a really weird way to end that cut scene, I think.
You know what time it is.
It's been at least two hours or so.
I get to do this.
And by the way, speaking of doing this,
what am I eating today?
Come on, what's the matter?
What do you think?
Burger?
Nah, I'm not feeling a burger.
Pizza?
Yup.
It's been a while since I've had pizza.
I haven't had pizza in a very long time.
Been at least a month or two, maybe.
Thai food?
Ooh.
That's another great option.
That sounds great.
Shepard's pie?
I mean, I really want that, because you just said it,
but that means I have to make Shepard's pie.
I have to make mashed potatoes.
Yeah.
I have to put some ground beef and some onions
into a pan, simmer that.
That's probably going to take some time.
Meow.
I'm going to get that right.
I don't have mashed potatoes.
I don't have any ground beef either, so.
Bring it.
Ground lamb?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
That just made me angry to look over and see that.
I'm sorry, guys.
That just threw me off.
Look at how bad that threw me off.
I think lamb, I don't like lamb.
I don't eat lamb.
I'm not into lamb.
What's wrong with lamb?
I don't like it.
Shepard's pie is lamb.
I've always had Shepard's pie with ground beef.
Maybe my mother made it that way
because she knew that I didn't like lamb.
That's why it's called Shepard's pie.
I always thought it was like Shepard's pie
because that's like what the Shepard ate.
But if that makes sense.
But the Shepard eats his sheep?
Yes.
Oh, they're not reindeers.
What am I talking about?
Like it doesn't fly around
and deliver presents to people with sheep.
Of course, that's what they do.
What am I talking about?
Cottage pie is the beef one.
Oh, okay.
This is fucking hard.
I have to get at least 10 to 20.
They don't raise the sheep for fun.
Hold on.
It threw me off again.
Well, yeah, I thought it was wool too.
I thought it was like wool.
Sheep are raised for wool and milk, you dummies.
I didn't think that they raise the sheep to shear the wool.
Yeah, they don't like raise the sheep to make Shepard's pie.
That's not why they do that.
Hold on.
Am I getting fucked with here?
Shepard's pie is any red meat.
That's what I thought too.
I think people are just being weirdos.
Well, I got 15.
Wow, that actually counted.
Okay, cool.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, well, that's crazy.
I'll take 17.
That's not a bad score.
Hey, David.
And probably after I beat this guy,
or after I fight this guy,
we'll probably call it here and we'll keep going tomorrow.
Because I'm just thinking about Shepard's pie and pizza.
I combined the two and Shepard's pie just turned into
a hamburger and onion pizza with a side of mashed potatoes.
And I'm gonna try to get that to be a reality.
Yeah, let's go.
Did you end the stream by accident?
No.
You want some starch with your starch.
So who is this?
I have to go to the Thunderdome, okay.
I need a sushi place.
That guy's driving backwards.
See that truck?
What the hell was that?
Try to find me.
Hey there, Mr. Assassin, let's play a game.
What am I?
Find me and you'll know.
Or maybe you won't.
Because I am the imitator of everything.
I will wait for you forever in the glorious land.
Yes.
Okay, recommendations.
We got a new movie recommended for you.
51 Grams.
What's with the 51?
51st Chamber.
Oh, I have upgrade points.
Forgot about that.
Look at how, all right.
I love this game.
I love this series.
Holy shit, that building looks awful.
Truly awful.
I'm sorry, I'm just gonna,
I'm gonna call it exactly how I see it.
It looks awful.
There's more artifacts on that building
than there were in King Tut's tomb.
Good one.
Hey, thanks, man.
That's the only complaint of the entire game so far.
The only one.
And look, I don't even look at the buildings.
What am I looking at the buildings for?
I'm not even looking at them.
So the weight of that problem is very, very small.
Oh, all right.
What I wanna do here,
I should probably get some, a skill.
3,000.
I'll take the health upgrade.
Nice.
2,200.
I'm gonna have to do it at some point.
And now that's a running slash.
And then charge attack.
That's also really good.
Battery.
3,200.
Attack or, yeah, I'll do another attack.
I think I have enough for, no, I don't.
I need, no.
I can do another health.
Yeah.
I have 1,900.
I don't think I can buy anything else.
Can I?
22.
Oh, I can, right?
22, no.
Yeah, wait, I can.
Nice.
All right.
No more health for a little while.
I wanna do more damage.
Like I'm swinging too hard at stuff.
Long dash.
Oh, it's a double.
Mash Y to unleash a high,
that's really cool too.
Mustang dodge.
Ooh.
If you have full health and you do a perfect dodge,
you can just annihilate.
All right.
That's cool.
That's a $30,000.
All right.
Let's also check, look at this.
What can I make?
Can I make a third one of these?
Uh, no, I can't.
Can I make another one of those?
Heavy attack power down, normal attack up.
Currently doing a lot of heavy attacks.
Cannot create.
Death force attack power 10% up.
A lot of materials.
When health is at 20% or below,
weapon attack power is plus 15%.
I feel like I'd be too scared to be that low.
You're at 88% or above, 8% up.
I kind of like that.
I kind of want like a three of those.
During slow down after a perfect dodge,
attack power is plus 10%.
That's cool.
Weapon attack power down, but damage taken down.
Successful guard power consumed 20% down.
How long though?
Health is at 80%.
All right.
Let's make, make this one.
No, where is it?
So when I'm at 80% or higher,
my weapon attack is 8% up.
Cause I'll replace one of the ones
that makes me take more damage.
Yeah, I want this one.
Cause I usually try to stay above 80%.
I'm a maniac.
I freak out if I'm not.
What does the tension gauge do?
I actually don't know.
Okay.
Damage taken 5% up, weapon attack power.
I think I, maybe I'll get rid of this one.
Getting me into too much trouble.
So now I just do 10% more damage,
which includes heavy,
but also the regular attack power too.
Yeah, I like that.
Refill on sushi.
Oh, it's the tiger thing in the corner.
All right.
Eat something, can't eat in.
I need five of these.
Essentially makes me run out of money.
I haven't used any of these.
All right.
I have to pee, but I'm going to hold it.
No I'm not.
I'll be right back.
All right, this is the final break of the evening.
I will take a piss.
I'll be right back.
We're going to try to beat this boss
and we'll probably call it there
and I'll see you tomorrow.
So I'll be right back.
We'll try to fight the boss.
Damn.
You know, it's time to like change the pants you have
or the underwear.
Like what the hell?
So the band of my underwear
has apparently been, this whole time,
so tight around my waist
and I haven't even really noticed
that I have those just two indent lines
where the elastic is around my entire body
and it hurts.
This actually hurts.
Ow.
What the hell?
How fat am I getting?
Dude, it's time for new underwear.
This is nice underwear.
This is, I just don't fit into it anymore.
Oh well, whatever.
Let's come back.
I'm trying to plan a workout stream.
Yeah, I need to, I need to figure that out.
All right, whatever.
Let's go.
Try to fight this next boss.
Save the game.
All right, I wonder what this boss is going to be like.
What's going on?
I just got some cheese sticks.
I just actually got fish sticks recently.
Those things are so good.
You?
You, really?
I love, those are amazing.
I love fish sticks.
Yes, I've seen the South Park episode.
I think we all have.
All right, so we're going to get on the highway
and we're going to go back to the Thunderdome.
You eat like a toddler.
I've, no, I don't.
But let's be fair though.
The kids menu at every major restaurant
always seems to have some real good shit on it
that you know you would enjoy, doesn't it?
I don't order off the kids menu, but I'm just being honest.
You can't look at the kids menu and go, ugh.
Chicken nuggets, ugh, gross.
Mac and cheese, disgusting.
I, ugh, ugh.
French fries, onion rings, ugh.
Apple slices, ugh.
Please, you probably, if you order from McDonald's,
anything off the whole menu,
then don't give me shit for looking at the kids menu.
Him, would be fair about that.
Grow up.
I, look, I eat boring stuff too, like salads.
Caesar salad, ooh, a chopped salad.
I eat, oh, like a baked fish.
That was delicious.
That is fun.
Tuna is one of my favorite things.
Yeah, I love to salmon, I love tuna.
Caesar salad, oh, mega lull, why?
And by the way, what fancy ass restaurants and food,
what are you eating every day?
Do you guys have like a personal chef?
That sucked, the fight here.
Let's just do the boss.
I'm an adult, I know how to cook.
Really?
The number eight ranked assassin is Black Knight Direction.
He is a space kidnapper.
He uses an illegal unlicensed transfer machine
to kidnap important and valuable people in space
and sell them to the powerful.
But dressing, I like a lemon, lemon vinaigrette.
Absolutely wild, Travis.
To the garden of insanity.
I just like olive oil.
Olive oil is pretty good for just a salad dressing.
I actually like olive oil and pasta.
So, I'm less a fan of red and white sauce on pasta
and more just olive oil and salt.
It's like, oh, pasta, that sounds good.
That's how I like it, preferred.
That's drive, mini girl.
Have I done enough wrestling moves?
No.
Olive oil by itself, yeah.
Olive oil, salt, and Parmesan on pasta is perfect.
It is.
I just like to get a really, really good EVOO.
A lot of stuff to do in this game, it's insane.
Where's this toilet?
I like omelets.
I love eggs too, yeah.
Omelets, like a fried rice with egg, awesome.
I love sauteed vegetables
and like just grilled chicken in a way.
I'm a big fan of a lot of different foods.
You like all cheeses, not all cheeses.
I actually don't really love soft cheeses.
I'm not a big brie person.
I like hard cheeses, not soft.
Cringe.
I love horseradish, one of my favorite things.
The wasabi that you get at restaurants,
that's not real wasabi,
it's just horseradish that's dyed green.
I love that stuff.
I wish I could, I put it on everything.
I could put that on literally every single food
that I've ever eaten and love it.
What about sauerkraut?
No, I'm actually not a big sauerkraut fan.
Put it on your Captain Crunch.
I actually, that's falling out of favor.
The Dunkin' Donuts mocha latte cereal
has taken over completely at this point.
Almost 100%.
All right, let's do it.
How is this place?
Looks like something out of Black Raid.
So is this Osaka?
Yes, gotta be.
Everyone's wearing tigers on their clothes.
He's here. Hello.
He's gonna fight in the street?
Probably.
Sense anything.
Some kind of zen thing, maybe?
The fuck?
Culture, huh?
Didn't your mama teach you
that it is not okay to steal shit?
They do this every game.
This isn't your scene.
I got no idea who the hell you are.
But stay the fuck out of this.
This town's problems are my problems.
You're just like they say.
I've also heard that you can't solve a thing
without brute force.
Look, outsider.
Who the fuck are you anyway?
I'm from the future.
It's a long story, but...
Don't bother.
Once we do battle, I'll know all I need to know.
When am I gonna get my next katana upgrade?
I won't hold back.
Hell yeah.
I wonder how many katanas are in the game.
That's what I wanna hear.
Bring it!
Activate Night Reaper mode.
Strawberry on the sweet shortcake.
What?
Oh my God, I'm in Mustang mode.
I'm in, where is he?
I'm in Mustang mode, please.
Oh, that's sad.
It's all the way down here.
Your killer instinct is simply unmatched.
I can feel it all the way down in my bones.
I want to express my respect
for that fighting spirit and bloodlust, grandpa.
This is Death Slow.
It's quite an elegant ability, perfect for you.
Death Slow.
If you're quite a new skill,
use its strange power to slow down time in your vicinity.
Unleash it by holding L and pressing A.
So L and A.
That has a cooldown.
Okay.
This guy should provide it now.
I think I have four viewers watching.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on, they're coming.
10, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Holy shit, here it goes.
20, 21, 26.
Well, I mean, we kinda have to wait for people, right?
I wonder how quickly, something like this.
Oh, there's two people,
like there's two assassins fighting each other
in the street on Twitch right now.
They have like magic powers.
Like how fast would this go up, do you think?
Okay, let's do Death Slow.
Okay, so I slow time down and, where'd he go?
50 viewer Andy.
This is less of a boss fight and more of a,
I'm teaching you moves.
I'm probably gonna fight him after.
This would sit at one viewer.
No, it would not.
And dream about our battle of souls.
I want to see how you do once you're more evolved.
Something I'd like you to have, Grandpa.
This is the Death Force.
It's quite violent, perfect for you.
Okay, X.
Use its mysterious power to knock enemies back.
Unleash your, okay, so it was a knockback.
Okay, try it out.
Oh, all right, that's cool.
That's very useful.
It's just a force push.
Travis not being in Smash is a crime.
I don't know.
They've used mature games before.
Bayonetta.
And honestly, No More Heroes is just,
has been a Nintendo exclusive.
They've ported it years later to other platforms,
but it comes out on Nintendo platforms every time.
He's a Smash costume fighter.
By the way, have they ran out of character slots
to fit on the screen in Smash Brothers yet?
Or is that still, they still have enough room?
Okay, imagine what it takes.
Before we take each other on, I have a present for you.
There's literally one more left.
This is Death Rain.
Use its weird power to pour down a rain of pain.
So it's like a, okay, try it.
Ow, what just hit me?
I get hurt by my own shit?
Did I win?
Favorite burger from Burger King.
It's not a burger.
It's my favorite, it's the Burger King long chicken.
Who do you keep tossing out all this fucking foreshadowing?
I'll explain it all once I take you down.
Really talk a lot of shit.
This is where I actually start trying.
Good, get ready, grandpa.
Long chicken.
What's your damn mouth?
I'm not even close to being a grandpa yet.
Now it's time for a little spanking.
All right, time for the real fight.
Hey, that was not fair, okay?
I just like literally spawned in.
Those of you that are saying long chicken,
omega lol, question mark.
He's stupid, he's an idiot, long chicken.
What's long chicken?
That's not what it's called.
It's the original chicken sandwich.
Original chicken sandwich, Jermo.
What are you, stupid?
That's fine, that's okay.
That's completely fine.
No, that's fine, that's cool.
He's an idiot, stupid idiot.
What's that say?
Something on there text-wise?
Interesting.
What's starting at $20,000?
Is that rent?
What is that?
I can't, I don't know what that is,
but I don't think I can afford that.
Holy shit.
That's not what that meant, right?
Oh my god, that's not a targeted ad.
No, I don't have that kind of fucking money.
Targeted advertising.
That's so stupid.
I would never, ever,
and I don't think that's what that was.
Was that like a dining room set?
I think that was like a yearly payment.
I have no idea, I have no clue.
How much is that a year?
Hold on a second.
I need to do a calculation.
I am so taken aback.
I don't even know what we're just looking at.
Hold on, this is important.
$240,000 a year for rent?
$20,000 a month?
Holy shit.
That's unbelievable.
I really thought that that was,
maybe, are we crazy?
Damn, that's, I don't,
got that money, if you got that kind of money,
whatever, that's not me.
That's a mogul move?
It's a targeted ad.
That's my, okay,
that's my top 10 favorite moment,
I think, that's ever happened on stream.
That's hilarious.
I don't even know what to say.
That's fucking hilarious.
All right, be easy.
Hold on.
I can't get over that.
I don't even know the,
wait, activate it.
Nice flex on your viewers.
I honestly, God, don't know why the fuck I got that.
Oh, I am bashing the shit out of this guy.
Oh, yep, yep.
Reign of hell.
You give me these crazy moves,
I'm just beating the shit out of this guy.
This guy doesn't stand a chance.
Rented a battery, that's what's making me have to leave.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, sorry.
Just get perfect dodged, is that what happened?
I'm embarrassing this guy right now.
Oh, that exploded, all right, whatever.
Oh, double.
You see that?
You paying attention?
Holy shit, I annihilated this guy.
All right, this three, I'm gonna be careful.
Oh shit, easy, easy, easy.
Oh, get cocky, there's no reason to be cocky.
That's fucking battery problem.
Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho.
Oh, see you later.
See you later, goodbye.
I know this guy's probably tutorial to teach you the moves,
but I had a good time on that one.
Not done yet.
That was quick.
Over there.
That's not gonna be a C rank, no way.
Not yet.
You gonna die on me without explaining all that bullshit?
Whatever, you can tell me in the next world.
Oh.
What the hell?
My katana won't budge.
I can't kill him?
That's gotta be S, right?
How?
I did everything so well.
I beat him in three minutes.
I beat that guy in three minutes.
It's a C.
Congratulations, you have been recognized
as number eight in the galactic rankings.
Looks like you're doing okay.
Hey, who the hell was that guy?
There is your answer.
Your body instinctively jumped into action,
trying to prevent his kid from getting hurt.
Why is that?
What the hell do you mean?
Someone starts to fall, you help them out.
Is this my son?
You are an assassin.
What are you doing helping people?
Have you ever helped out any of your other opponents?
Definitely my kid.
Why would someone as bloodthirsty as you
try to save another ranked assassin?
The reason is.
Is what?
A secret.
A secret guy, huh?
Whatever.
Go ahead and sleep here.
Rest it off.
I see you've gotten comfy in the Garden of Slaughter.
Now, Travis, go.
Off to swim the Sea of Blood.
Well, I'm really happy that they pulled the...
Here comes a boss.
Just kidding, someone's gonna kill that boss
and you fight somebody different for the third time.
They really love that joke.
They love it so much.
It's weird, because I'm just sitting here thinking,
which one of these guys are they gonna do that to?
So we got our answer.
It's like the fall joke for me, yeah?
20K.
No.
When are you gonna buy a mansion?
I'm not gonna buy a mansion.
Okay, the prospect is terrifying to me.
Look, and if you got money, you got money, right?
If you got a lot of money, if you got a lot of money,
do whatever you want.
Well, I don't give a shit, right?
But here's what scares me.
With an automatic payment coming out of my bank account
of more than $20,000 a month, that would give me anxiety.
20,000 automatic payment, right?
Like if it was like a mortgage or if it was like a rent,
that scares the shit out of me.
I would never want an auto payment to be more than
like a few thousand dollars a month, ever, for any reason.
I don't care how much money I have.
That's like terrifying to me.
In my personal opinion, that I would be scared
of that much money coming out of my checking account
on an automatic basis.
Well, you can afford the long check-in, yeah.
Just don't check your balance.
If you had that much, just put it towards the house.
Yeah, I don't know if I would rent for that much.
That's a lot of money.
That's a huge amount of money for rent.
Can you really kill this guy?
Shut up!
Sorry, I got a bit overexcited.
Listen, Damon.
I love that underwear he has.
This is a game.
Unless someone shows up to challenge me,
the game doesn't work.
Your guest has arrived.
Missed their vanishing point.
Good, let him in.
All right.
RGB underwear.
Hey, French.
You killed this guy?
Hell yeah.
Who do you think you're talking to?
You seem confident enough.
Just watch me.
I'm gonna kill the shit out of you.
Show me a good time.
Anything you say, Prince.
Nice.
Love how every episode starts.
Just going to the throne room.
Just see this weird back and forth
between the new weird character
that's being introduced.
They are giving off a second life DBZ universe, aren't they?
Let's get to the save point.
If there's another cutscene, we'll watch it
and then we're gonna pick it up tomorrow.
That's it.
Got some new clothes.
New T-shirt.
Play with Gene and then I'm gonna save it
and we'll pick it up tomorrow.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Around the same time, around four o'clock.
We definitely did not get halfway through the game,
but I think this game's amazing.
I'm having a ton of fun with it.
So I, if this has to be like three streams, that's fine.
We'll do one tomorrow and see how we feel
and maybe do another one.
If not, then we'll pick it up like,
but here's the thing.
I'm gonna be staying on the Switch
because yeah, this will work out fine.
So we're gonna stream tomorrow
and then however, wherever we get tomorrow,
on the 10th, the new WarioWare comes out.
You better believe I'm gonna play the absolute hell
out of that on Friday.
So maybe we could do like a Friday, Saturday,
which would be, or Friday, Sunday or something,
which would be WarioWare and then I'll finish No More Heroes.
I think that'll work out perfectly.
So let's pick it up.
I'm gonna be exactly where I'm standing right now.
We'll check it out tomorrow.
Sims 3, Sims 3 will be probably another week or two.
I wanna play WarioWare.
So I have all the mods done.
They're all installed.
They're ready to go.
I just have to do it.
I got like seven mods installed and they're all insane.
Thanks for watching, everybody.
There was a lot of community subs.
Oh, the sunflowers, yes.
There will be a sunflower reveal tomorrow.
You better believe it.
Yeah, there were a lot of community subs.
There was like 50 community subs given
in like 10, 10, 10, 10.
When I looked at the sub count after the all-house stream,
I remember, I did not think it was gonna be that high.
We have smashed every record I ever held on this channel
for subscriptions.
It's quite a lot.
The record of the channel was,
and I'll be upfront with you,
record of the channel was 12,800 subscriptions.
Now, I know that this is not gonna be this high
probably in 30 days from now,
but this is, like I said,
I'm gonna be chasing highs for the rest of my life.
100K viewers, like all this shit that had a lot of people.
I think the peak the day after the stream
was about 17,400 subscriptions,
which is like, are you kidding me?
I do not expect that to continue
because obviously a lot of that might be just people
that primed or that gave during the stream,
whatever that stream,
but that's 20k rent money.
Targeting network.
Yeah, it's, I can't, it's insane.
So, regardless if we stay up here at this,
and I'm saying we, right?
But you know what I mean.
Regardless if 17,000 subs is the highest it ever goes ever,
and we pull back quite a bit maybe,
that's an achievement that I never thought I'd see.
We, I mean, do you remember like a year ago
during one of the,
I think it was the New Year's Eve stream,
I broke 10,000 subs for the first time.
When I went to bed that night,
I was like, this is,
I'm never crossing this ever again.
I remember just like lying in bed,
just staring at the ceiling being like,
this is never happening again.
There's no way I stay over that.
I am, I know I'm saying that again right now.
Parasocial Andy.
But I get, I don't know, just thanks.
Hopefully I can spend the money well
and not on, not on that insane rent.
Don't worry.
Just do dollhouse quality streams every day.
No, I just, I don't want people to think
I'm trying to be like, look at how many subs I have now.
I just, it's a bit shocking
that this many people would even do it in the first place.
So, cause I talked about it before
and I kind of would like to be
a little more transparent about it.
I wouldn't like hide it or anything, but thank you.
We'll see where it goes.
Let's see what streams can happen
because of different opportunities, right?
The more money that I make, the more I'm going to use.
And we've had sponsors,
we've had involvement from Twitch, right?
So I don't know.
I'm hoping to continue to do stuff
like you saw a couple of weeks ago,
the last week or whatever.
Let's give it a shot.
Yeah, we'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching everybody.
Have a great rest of your night.
It's probably pretty late for a lot of you
considering it's 9.30 PST right now, or PT, whatever.
See you tomorrow.
Good night, guys.
Take care of yourselves.