How does my headphones... how do they always get so tangled? I don't understand. No matter what I do,
I put them down, and then they just end up in like a... looks like a nest, like a sparrow's nest.
I don't understand how it happens. So here's the plan for tonight, if you're curious. So we are
going to play Thief Simulator for a little while, and who knows? We might... Thief Simulator
might be so much fun that we just can't stop playing it. But if it gets to be like an hour
or two in and it's like, okay, that's... that's pretty much all there is to this one, then we'll
probably end up moving back to Red Dead. Or something else. Because there are a lot of
options. There's a ton of things that have come out. So we'll see. To give you guys more of
an update on the green screen, the green screen has been officially pushed to Friday.
Uh, I figured Thursday is kind of a weird day. I'd rather try to get as many people to be able
to watch it as possible. So like Friday night, Friday afternoon, I feel like is the best time.
This... the start of the weekend. Because Thursday afternoon is just an odd time, so.
So, and speaking of that, speaking of the green screen, I do have something for you to vote
on. So, for those of you that missed the... I guess everything we've talked about so far.
Well, why don't I just let my intro go for like two or three minutes, you know?
Because people are going to be coming in. So, give me two minutes. We'll talk about this
when I get back. BRB. So, originally, when I first talked about the green screen, it was,
hey, we're going to do the green screen and there's going to be... there's going to be all
these voting periods and I'm not going to know what the actions are and it's going to be a secret
and a surprise that's not happening anymore. I threw that out last week. So, I went through
and I picked from that channel on the Discord a ton of actions. There are so many actions
we'll be doing on Friday, but sometimes there's just too many, right? And some of them
we're a little on the meme-y side, a little a little on like the internet meme side.
And I figured I, you know, I ain't doing a fucking Fortnite dance. I already took that off. So,
I don't... that not even available. So, what you're going to vote for on this poll
is your favorite one of these fucking memes because you only get... I'm only going to
pick the top three. So, you got... you got until like tomorrow or even maybe even tonight.
The poll is about to go into the chat and we will sit here and just look at it for a minute.
So, here are... and remember, keep this in mind, this is not even a taste of the
hundreds of actions that will be happening during this stream. So, there you are. We've
got... you got to pick your favorite one out of all those. We've got the Sonic run, the
Macarena, do the John Travolta thing, do various CSI sunglasses one-liners, spin around in So Long
King Bowers or something, do Infinity War shit, recreate the original Up and Smoke Bee video,
Dark Souls praise the sun, and other Dark Souls gestures, and then do JoJo poses.
I don't know what that even means. What is do JoJo poses? I don't even know what that is.
It's... okay, well, it wasn't a Fortnite dance, so I didn't... should I have vetoed that?
This is so one-sided. Why is... why is this so one-sided right now?
Veto JoJo's? I didn't... I didn't know what it was. I vetoed Dab, I vetoed default Fortnite
dance, and I vetoed re-enact the whole gnome video. I ain't doing... I can't be worse than
those. Is it worse than... is it worse than those? I only got three vetoes. Did I fuck
myself? Did I just fuck myself over so bad by not vetoing the JoJo poses? Look them up.
Well, whatever. So, by the way, the top three... the top three will be brought in because there
are so many things. I could just open up the list. You know, I'm gonna open up the list
and I'm just gonna read you like two things, okay? Here's a couple of great ones. By the
way, I got hundreds of actions. Just make sure you're aware of that. I can't wait to
do a full weather report in a suit. That's gonna be fucking fun. Looking forward to act
like an alien is bursting out of your chest. That's gonna be a lot of fun. Dude, the Looney
Toons outro. That's gonna be fun too. There's so many of these. This is gonna... oh god.
So, this... I'm gonna... I'm gonna take a lot of time. I'm gonna do like some rehearsal
for this. There's plenty... there's plenty of stuff here. Okay, so do... does that include
like the porky pig? Am I gonna have to like put my hands out to the sides and go like,
that's all, folks? Is that like what... that's what it is, right? Well, this should be a lot
of fun. I can just turn into a stream outro. And, again, let me reiterate this one more
time because people... I think I'm confusing a lot of people. And because we're getting,
you know, three, four days out, three days out here, let me make sure people are aware
of what's going on. Because I feel like a lot of people still have no idea what I'm doing.
What is the sonic run? I don't... I don't know. The sonic... when your hands are behind your back
and you like run with your head down. What isn't it? Like Naruto? I don't know.
Why would that be the sonic run? But whatever. Anyways, after this green screen is filmed,
two, maybe three weeks later, depending on how much time I want to... I would say two weeks
is good. Two weeks later, this is not a contest, we're going to have a movie night
where we watch the shit that you guys made. There will be rules and I will talk about them
at great length after the stream is done on what is going to happen. But all of these
videos that we'll be watching will be pre-screened. They have to be at least
10 seconds long and they have to be no more than two minutes long. So those are the rules.
Nobody... there's no contest. There's no like, somebody wins, somebody loses. We're just going
to have fun. But we're here. It's time to play Thief Simulator for a little while.
Do they have to be school appropriate? Yes, they have to be very appropriate.
They have... like you have to be able to be able to like sit down next to your parents
and watch these. All right, let me drop this down. That poll will be going till
at least tonight. Family movie night. No, it doesn't have to be family friendly per se,
but it can't... it can't just... you don't... listen, do I need to spell it out for you?
Hold on, let me just get this on here. All right, I'll spell it out for you.
No sexual content. No hateful bullshit. Fun. There can be violence. There can be weird shit, but
no... none of that bullshit, okay? And it's... they're all going to be pre-screened anyway,
so we'll be fine. All right, I'm ready. Anything is sexual to me. What does that even mean?
Wait, JoJo poses all sexual? No, they're not.
They're not. They're not. And look, we could... we're gonna have fun with it, but
you guys... you guys know. You're all... you all understand. Use common sense. You can be stupid,
you can be weird, you can be fucking crazy, but just no over the line shit, all right? Like
just... you understand. I feel like you guys... you guys... we're all fucking in our 30s here.
We're all old enough to know. Why are we stuck at 99? Oh, okay. Is... am I just playing hitman?
Is that what this is? It's Vinny. Is that actually Vinny? Hold on, is that... is that Vinny?
Oh, wait, hold on. I can't even hear it. Oops. There's no sound. Oops-a-daisy. All right,
I need to change some settings here, because wowee. Quality high. Ambient occlusion,
I don't want that. And FPS 60 sounds. That's... you just couldn't hear it because I'm an idiot.
Any FOV slider? I don't think so. All right, look... I need to like turn that down though.
Mouse sensitivity, that's gonna go down. A mouse sensitivity car. This game already became
a full letter grade. Is it at least a D already? Okay. No, even more than that.
Even more than that. All right, that's fine. All right, pick up the crowbar.
Pick up the crowbar. E. Here's Vinny.
I don't think that's Vinny. I don't... I'm not sure that that's actually Vinny. All right,
inventory. Why does inventory open up my... oh, okay. So, put it in my hand. All right,
quick slot. T. You can add items to the quick slot for faster usage. Go to inventory,
select an item, and press the quick slot button. Okay, so press the quick slot button. Wait, so...
Okay, there it is. So tab is my quick slot. Break the fence. One hit. That's all it took.
I got a strike. All right, that's it. Sneaking. Sneaking allows you to make less noise,
but will make you slower. Default. C. E. You can also lean by pressing space and left and right.
So C, and if I hold space and go like this, I can sneak. Okay, sneak by the window. No,
I was about to hit the fence. All right, so I guess you can see the Metal Gear Solid
windows down there. Light and visibility. When sneaking around at night, it's best to avoid
well-lit places. Your flashlight will also make you easy to spot. So, avoid well-lit
places like that. Go through the bushes. Avoid all the light. Vinnie! Hey, some dope left a
flashlight on the ground. Take it, but don't let nobody see the light and call the cops.
Okay. What's with this 110, 111, one of these addresses? Flashlight. Break the window with
the crowbar. So, flashlight is F. Well, that's huge. Wait, this one. Break the window with the
crowbar. Lockpicking level four. Glass knife. Interact. So, wait. Okay. Just smash the guy's
window. Open the window. How do I go in? Oh. Yeah! What's up, Vinnie? All right. Steal.
Take the bed. Flashlight will help you see the loot in the dark. Remember, you're easy to detect
with the flashlight on. All right. How do I take the bed? Oh, let's just hide under bed. All
right. So, steal some stuff. Shoes. Open slowly. It's hold E. Is somebody in the house? I don't
know. I think they're outside. Oh, that's loud. Getting something WD-40 on here. What is it?
$15. I got it. What else do we got here? Plates. A teapot. 3LD. What the hell? LD. What is it?
What is LD? 11LD. Pot. Load? Light density? There's nobody even in this house, so I can
just do it. Toaster. Yep. Time to bail, man. Get in the car. Don't let nobody see you
with that crowbar. Okay. Take the fry pan. I thought it was not locked. Okay. Unwanted
attention. Unequip tools and turn off the flashlight to avoid unwanted attention from
other people. There's somebody in front of me. Is my voice talking? No. All right. Where's
this car? It's like over here. Can I jump the fence? So, we just have to get in the car.
I get to drive? How do I turn it on? Oh, God. Drive out of the location. I'm not gonna toot
the horn. Why would I blow the horn right now? It's a crosswalk! Press space. No, I'm
not gonna cry. I gotta get out of this tutorial. I can change the camera?
That's... Okay, the sensitivity is insane right here. That's what that means. Okay. Yep.
Figured out what that one is. That's why it's great. You're a thief.
I mean, yeah. I just... I got an A. My thief rating is an A. I took a pot. I took a toaster.
Saucepan. Teapot. New hints available. Mouse 2 is mark. Quick slot. Left shift is run.
Oh. Good job, man. This just might work. Go get some sleep and we'll pick this up
in the morning. You actually have a house? So, do I get a better car?
I can go on the computer! This is cool. Ooh. Simple lockpick. Whatever. I got $42.
Climbing gloves. Electric lockpick. Jewelry tools. Safe cracking. Glass knife. Hacking tools.
A micro camera. A hacking laptop. Why is a hacking laptop? $52,000.
That seems a little... This is called... Black Bay. Car parts. Electronics. Kitchen.
Oh, alright. I can sell this on the black market. Why would you sell a saucepan on,
like, the dark web? Yeah, that's right. I got a cast iron pan. I'll sell it to you for
$10 off what you'd buy it at Walmart. Okay. Now I got more money.
Steal your forums. House security tips. On these, like, addresses? Rent a thug?
Lugged in as thug322. This is not... I did not think this game was gonna be this elaborate.
Okay. So how about, like, simple lockpick? I don't have lockpicking 1. I already have a crowbar. I
got a flashlight. So I just have to go to bed. There's another computer? Device workshop.
Requires hacking tools and electronics 1. What's this RPG? I was sleeping on a couch.
I need a bed. How much is a bed? What? Check the computer. He's about to tell us everything
we need to know. Tools for thieves lets you buy new kit online. But you might not have what it
takes to use them all. Click on steal your forum. Here you can buy secrets. Hot tips on
what's where, who's guarding it, who leaves the door unlocked, whatever. Check out what I wrote
on Greenview 109. Greenview 109. All right. Well, you got possible loot location.
So these are all free. So house security tips. Easy to break the damaged wooden fence in the back.
Old TV worth a dollar. Spare door key in the drawer. And there is no one home
all the time. What? Is that home security or is this nobody just... nobody live here?
Okay. So we're gonna need an old TV to spare key. All right. Old TV.
You'll need empty pockets at Greenview 109. Yeah, I already did it, right?
Stealth stuff at the pawn shop. Isn't that what I just did? Where am I gonna get...
Oh, shit. So could I have gotten more? All right. Can I steal from the pawn shop? That's
important, right? Oh, there's an old regular Nintendo here. That's probably worth a lot
of money. I don't think I can take it. Wait, can I? No. Take the lawnmower?
You have anything in your trash?
An old sofa? Welcome back. Okay, I may need this. An old toaster.
I couldn't even sell that on the dark web. It's time for Greenview 109. Get me that TV
and don't pawn it off. I don't think you can... Nope. Sorry, guys. I tried. Big items.
I don't pawn the TV, he said. Oh, right. I can't... I'm so used to, like, GTA. All right,
let's go to Greenview. Big bits only. Okay, stealing old TV from Greenview 109.
Load it in the car trunk and drive home. All right, 109. Right here. Oh, that's not
suspicious. There's nobody here. Whoa! All right, remember the back. There's nobody even
in the house. I could just take my time. What is this? Who has a dumpster back here?
You have a dumpster in the back of your house? This dumpster is almost as big as your whole
house. You could fit a bedroom in here. All right. There's the damage fence. Get that open.
All right. So, wait, we got a spare key, right? What does the spare key go to? Front door.
Got it. What else you got in here? Toaster! We know those are expensive.
Fridge. Money in the trash. Bathtub. Ketchup bottle? No. All right, so old TV. Hold on.
Yeah, here we go. Okay. Carry. Can you throw it?
No, not really. Okay, well, whatever. Oh, shit! There's a person right here.
Big items. To steal a big item, TV or printer, etc. Put it in the car's trunk and drive home.
The sale begin of the pond. You need to put them next to the shop owner. It's all right. It's just
Wilson. What's his name next door? Tim Allen. The guy with the eyes and the hat.
She's standing on the car. Get out of the way. Can I throw a coin over there? What the fuck?
Sprint with a TV. Am I going to be able to sneak behind? She's always facing this way.
Here comes somebody else. Wait, is she stuck in the door? No, she's not. She's just standing
here. She's just standing here waiting. Can I like do something? Can I like push her down?
All right, I'll put the TV down. What the fuck? Oh, fuck. Oh, a car. Oh, what is it? The
homeowner? So what am I supposed to do about this? Okay, so I can't hurt that person?
It's a Steve simulator. God, now I gotta move the car out of the way.
This car damage. Look at the car. The back fence can be broken easily.
Really? Okay, come on. Get out. All right, that's fine. Get the TV. Give me the money too.
Just leave a big shit in his toilet. That's disgusting.
Oh, there's money down here. TV down. I want that money.
Yeah, big items. You gotta be put in the trunk before the lady gets here.
She's about to cross right now. No, she's not. No, I got the back. I'm in the back.
I'm not going to go to the bathroom in this person's house. Okay, guys, please.
How do I like get it out there? All right, load up the old TV. All right,
get it in the trunk. Okay, well, that's one way to do it. All right, I'm ready. Okay,
uh, steal a TV from loading the car and drive out of here. We're gonna take this road.
How do I? Where's my home? Am I going just to drive out? Oh, there we go. Home. Road.
Old TV. You got the key. Remember to spend unused skill points.
S exclamation point. That's better than S plus. I see you got my screen. Go to black bay.
All right, I set up a page on there for the TV. Go there and sell it. Okay, electronics. Old TV,
60 bucks. Yeah, good work. Now click on the rent a thug tab. Now here you can find a little
extra work. I put one on there just for you. The one with the dishes. Okay, at 110 go break
their dishes. And that's it. This is the equivalent of if you just shit in the toilet and left.
That's going to be one eventually, isn't it? Okay, now break the dishes. Okay,
leaving up a decker at 111. If you don't know what that is, that's when you shit in a water
tank. You leave it. You have to unlock, you have to unlock the couch shitting quest or break
the dishes at 1110. We can't even see it. I just wanted to see it. We can't, we don't even get to
see the damn thing. What the fuck? Did I already do this? Okay, good. Is there just no ragdoll
or physics engine or something? I mean, I didn't even try. Cell pots and pans. But he told me
to go to 110 and smash dishes. So I gotta do that first. He didn't even try to swerve. No,
I was trying to run that person over. I was trying to kill that person because I wanted,
I just needed to know if we could see anything. All right, so 110 smash.
I'm dead. I got some dishes to smash. Somebody in this house? Windows locked,
windows locked. That's not going to stop us. Get in. So now break their dishes.
I can't even take their toaster or anything. That's my house. No, it's not.
Is it? So they have, they have physics and breakable plates, but not run overable humans.
What's up with that? So that's it. This is, what do you got here?
Deodorant. Any money in the liner? What's wrong with the toilet?
Okay, well now there's something very wrong with it. Um, all right, well that's it.
Just gonna get back in the car. Sleep in bed. You can't sleep in bed. All you can do is
crawl under it. Car. For a second I thought somebody was in the car.
No, I'm not gonna crawl under it. I already did that. All right, let's leave.
That is the drive to the edge of the universe here. What's beep?
Can you even, can you even get in a car accident? You probably can't.
Cook poop will pre-record it. Wait, hold on. I don't have that.
I can't even break their mailboxes. Yeah, let's go.
How is that a C? All right Vinny, give me a call. Learn lockpicking level one.
Uh, from where, over here. Car. Okay, rent a thug. Let me sell all this shit though.
Kitchen. Other. Antiques. Art. Uh, this is what they want. Somebody wants this stuff.
So it's just like here. Okay, skills.
The skill what is? Lockpicking level one. Open easy locks and lockpicks. Sure thing.
Notes. Uh, okay. We got some, we got that job done.
Skills. We just learned lockpicking. Here's Vinny.
Okay. DIY simple lockpick. I have $230. Got it.
That's too bad. I was thinking it was gonna just do like seven days.
It's Jerma's day? What? Okay, let's open it.
So you need to find the right angle with the bobby pin and then rotate the lock.
The closer the pin gets to the correct angle, more the lock will rotate.
So rotate is just D. Okay, so this is just, this is just like fallout.
Okay. Somebody in jail?
When close enough you can mark a tenant to discover his daily routines.
Middle mouse button. Okay, you can also mark cameras to show their viewing angle.
View range. Check tenant routines in the top right corner. Blue means they are out.
Tenant routines are also available in the notes menu.
Okay. So go to 111 around 7 a.m. and mark the tenant.
So let's give us a little bit of time here. It's 5 a.m.
I'm really gonna turn off the stereo before I go to bed.
Sell your stuff? I, I can't. Nobody wants it.
Missing required items. I can't. The golden goblet.
Car parts. Electronics. I can't. The kitchen. Go to the pawn shop?
Yeah, but I'm like a time limit now. I just, I would have woken up at four o'clock in the morning.
What time is it right now? 5 20 a.m. All right, I gotta make this quick.
Welcome back. All right, so saucepan.
That's all I bring into this guy.
Hey Jeremy. Hey man, what's up? Uh, you got the usual?
Yeah, I got a couple of toasters, uh, pots and pans, um, in a vase.
Oh, sweet dude. Yeah, I'll be back tomorrow with the same stuff.
At what point is this guy gonna hold his hand up and be like, Jeremy,
Jeremy, you've given me like 30 toasters, man, and nobody buys them.
Okay, so it's 5 a.m. Just gotta get to 111 around 7 and mark the guy there.
Is this person in a car or are they walking? Okay, they're walking.
111 was, it's a three-point turn. You've never seen somebody do that before?
I just broke the road. The road just crumbled underneath me.
Okay, so let's get out of the way with his no, out of suspicion.
I like under the McDonald's heat lamp. That's a great place.
Right under the light. All right, it's 7 a.m. Okay, I gotta get ready.
I gotta get a good vantage point up on the seesaw.
Okay, what time is it? 6 30. He's right there.
Sleeping in the parking lot.
Sleep in the car at the parking lot to pass time.
There's a box in there. Wait for them to leave and get me that box.
So go sleep, wait for them.
Okay, hint discovered. Important box inside.
So what about his routines here? Living room or out?
I can just sit here and wait, though.
Wouldn't I rather do it like this or go, no, look at the timer up there.
He'll be out of the living room.
He just looked over here. So I gotta sprint in, grab the box.
I can look at every inch of this guy's entire house.
I don't even need a camera. I just move back and forth.
I am the camera. All right, we need like a point of interest, though.
He's standing up to change the channel on the TV.
Are you sure he's not using the toaster? He might be.
So all right, go sleep in my car.
So it is currently 7 47 a.m.
So sleep in car. How do I sleep in the car?
I have to sleep in the trunk? How do I sleep in there?
Oh, I have to be over there.
Hey, watch this. What would be the ultimate asshole?
Ain't nobody parking here.
All right, let's sleep until 9 a.m.
That was a good nap. All right, where is he?
Is he gone? Oh, is that him?
Oh, I took, I took the most important thing in his whole house, guys.
I took the TV. How is he going to change the channels now?
Actually, okay. Hold on. I guess I could.
He's got barred windows.
Get me out of here. Oh, I stuck back here.
How did I wait? Oh, my God.
Go through. You can't go through.
Come on. Come on. I want the TV too.
I'll get them both.
Come on. Come on. He's still out.
I'm still good. Hold shift.
He can't run with the TV.
I got another item. Important box.
All right. He's got money. He's got a lot of money.
Take it. That's a lot of money.
Where's the box? I made it.
Every single victim needs to have a smashed toilet.
No. All right.
So wait till no one's home to steal the important box.
How did I not steal the box?
Box with shady content. That's not it.
So why is it telling me to still do it?
Just live. Well, why wouldn't it just say leave?
I got it. Let's go home first.
Then I'm going to pawn the TV.
That's all I want is a B.
Remember to spend unused skill points.
I got a B. I'll take it.
New hints now. Level up.
So what can I level up?
This seems like a branching Diablo 2 skill tree here.
All right. We've got lockpicking level two.
I need to go from here.
Open normal locks with a lockpick.
Open easy locks.
Okay. Well, now we opened it up.
More notes.
So he's out between 9 a.m. and 11 a.m.
And he's asleep from 6 a.m. until 11.
That's not correct.
There's two people that live in this house.
Yeah, he's asleep from 5 a.m. to 11.
And he's out from 9 a.m. to 11.
Okay. So he sleepwalks.
He goes and makes eggs at the neighbor's house.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's see what I can do here.
Send the box via Black Bay.
Just keep taking that guy's TV.
Okay. We got other box with shady content.
It's a hundred bucks.
Okay. Nice.
What's next?
The Lombardies think their friend on Greenview needs a new window.
They think the one they got is fine.
Go prove them wrong.
So smash a window in 112 and then hide or run away.
We got it.
Smash a window in 112.
But first, let's see what we can get for this television.
Welcome back.
Big item.
TV. $40 for the TV.
And another pot.
I got some money now.
You wish you thieves were as incompetent as Germo.
I don't do thievery.
I don't break into people's houses.
Of course.
Why would I be good at something that I don't do?
Can you believe this guy?
He can't even perform like a heart surgery.
I've never fucking performed heart surgery.
All right. 112.
Are those two things equatable?
Because I don't know how to do things.
I don't know how to do what I've never done.
I don't know what like a lockpick does.
I never even touched one.
I've never held one in my hand.
Now these ones are up here.
All right. Let's park it.
I don't even know what it does.
Break a window in 112 and hide or run.
So I'm just like a regular person, right?
So I don't have to worry about it.
If they see me, as long as I don't have the crowbar out, I'm fine.
So this is 112.
Can I peek? Can I jump?
You put the lockpick in the thing and rotate the lock.
That's not how it works.
I can't climb a fence because I don't have enough agility.
Okay. Well, is there somebody in the house?
Can I reach from here?
Just throw the crowbar in there.
Is somebody in the house?
No one's in the house.
Whoa!
Just about to rob you.
All right. I got two people marked.
They're at the garden.
They go to the garden now.
Break their window.
All right. So I got to break this.
I'm sprinting right behind me.
Here we go. One, two, three, action.
What is this?
Stealing stuff from returning home with loot gives you extra experience points.
The first time theft will give 10 times more experience.
If you're not sure what to do, check your computer.
All right. Why are the police here?
The police are called?
Hide? Where do I hide?
Oh, they have an alarm.
Hide in the dumpster.
You can run away from police by leaving the neighborhood
or you can hide in a closet, a dumpster under the bed
and wait for the police to leave.
If the visibility eye is red, someone saw you
and the police will find you.
No one's going to find me.
No one saw me go into this particular...
That is if you go in this dumpster.
When does this stop?
Do I have to run away?
You live here now.
I feel like this is supposed to be done.
Should I get out?
How would they know it's you?
That's a good question.
All right. I'm going to get out and sprint to the left as fast as I can.
Oh, music off. Music's done.
There's one star now.
Oh, no, no, no. They're leaving.
There were no police after all.
All right. Where's my car?
Over here.
Somebody was just playing police sounds to scare me.
What would you be suspicious of?
I don't have anything up.
Why are there people surrounding my car?
The car is parked in a strange place.
The police are going to tow my car.
What? Get...
Don't hit them.
Don't. I can't go anywhere.
Either one of these two.
Open a standard training lock.
Oh, I did it. I win.
This is so unsettling.
All right. We got easy lock.
Standard lock.
Requires a lockpick.
Do I have to buy a lockpick every time?
So I don't get to reuse it?
Oh, man.
That's where the money sink is, huh?
Oh, shit.
Can I pawn those?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. Oh, there.
Anybody need any lockpicks?
I've got this great idea.
It's called buy, buy, buy shit at premium price.
Sell for undercut price.
God.
You need to lock the pin while it's at the bottom.
So how do you lock the pin?
What button do you press?
Well, here we go.
Use a lockpick to open standard locks.
Press the button at the exact time when a pin is at the bottom.
Okay.
But first of all,
let me just try to get a super sweet candy crush here.
Sweet.
Lock the pin.
I have to press S when it's at the bottom, right?
That's what I just did.
Have to click.
Mouse zero.
Okay. So it's mouse zero.
That's a strange way to call it.
If it ain't broke, fix it with a crowbar.
Word on the street is the toilet in Greenview 113 is not broke.
Really?
Break the toilet.
What is this petty bullshit?
I feel like I'm being contacted by like ex-boyfriends and ex-girlfriends.
I go in there and smash her toilet.
Go pee on his TV.
Am I a thief or am I like petty revenge guy?
All right.
So I got home.
Let me, I want to look at this.
Go pee in his toilet.
Yeah. Go pee in his toilet.
All right. We got one, 113.
Possible loot location.
Let's see.
There is a printer worth a lot in the living room.
These houses are so small at this point in the game that this is, why would I do this?
No one is there between nine and two.
And there's a spare key for the front door in the bedroom.
So between, let's get there at 9 a.m.
And let's get the printer.
Steal the printer ink.
That's worth a lot of money.
So we're going to take the printer and then we're going to break the toilet.
There's hiring people to prank.
Did I even pick anything up for my inventory?
Items.
I don't have anything.
All right.
So 113 is the other house that's up on the hill there.
Spend $200 on hints to get $70 for a printer.
Yeah. Well, I just, that's fine.
No, I don't want to get arrested.
I want a perfect record.
Nice.
Nice steal.
I don't want to be arrested.
Drive straight into the stranger's backyard.
Well, then they shouldn't put a jump there.
If they don't want people to try to go off the jump,
then there shouldn't be a jump available.
Look, I'm being very careful now.
All right.
I need to park this car somewhere where no one's going to care.
No one's going to walk over here.
So all right.
So between 9 a.m., no one's there right now until 2.
We've got a printer in the living room and we have to smash the toilet.
So I got a window.
And I think I'm going to, I'm good.
Nobody's here to see this.
Oh, man.
Where's the toilet?
Where is it?
Where's the, where's the living room?
Get out.
Put it down.
Pick it up.
Why can't I pick the TV up?
Pick up the TV.
That's the alarm.
Oh, shit.
There he is.
No, that's a wooden person.
It's just an outlast.
9 a.m.
2 p.m., right?
We got like three hours to get out of here.
Tie shoelaces together.
All right.
We're good.
Now what about toys?
Okay.
Living room.
Find the living room.
I need like the living room.
Where's the printer?
Holy shit, the thing's huge.
How do I get it out here?
Can I get it out of this window?
Fuck.
Oh, they're coming back.
They're coming back.
Get back out of the bed.
Get out of the bed.
So I got the front door.
I can't fit through there.
Can't fit through here though, apparently.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Hint.
There's a spare key for the front door on the bedroom.
Time is it?
Oh, that's a guitar.
Let's see.
Oh, shit.
These are vases and shit.
Okay.
What time is it?
Got to go.
Okay.
What is this?
A camera.
Worth a lot of money.
Can't take it.
Move.
Oh, oh, they're coming back.
I can't even take money?
All right.
Where's the printer?
Get it in the car quick.
Get it in the car.
I can't sprint with this thing.
It's too heavy.
All right.
Open.
And I'm out of here.
That's how you do it.
What about the TV?
I can't put the TV in there, man.
That's all right.
Like a man spider, you know?
Oh, I know.
First, let me see something here.
Car parts, electronics, microwave, radio, kitchen.
Other is the guitar.
300 bucks.
So I have to bring the printer to the pawn shop?
Rent a thug.
All right.
Break or steal the painting.
Break or steal the kiss painting.
So that's like, that's teeth.
That's just an x-ray of somebody biting down.
All right.
Um, let's, let's stay with the tutorial here though.
So learn agility level two.
Here's agility.
Agility one.
Throw bricks.
I don't, I don't need to care.
I don't care about anything else.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's go throw bricks at stuff.
So we got rent a thug.
So break the painting.
We'll just break them all.
One 10, one 12 smack.
Just break their paintings.
Now, can I buy a brick?
Is brick available?
So let me get this out of here.
Sell this.
What can I buy a brick?
It's a, it's a pretty good question, right?
Okay.
I wish you could open the door.
Welcome back.
Favorites.
Oh damn.
Okay.
Well, that was a lot of money.
All right.
Let's go break stuff.
Uh, do we have any Intel on one?
There's one 10.
My trunk is open.
It's all right.
It'll be fine.
Don't worry.
All right.
So, uh, we need to go to one 10 and one 12 and break this, the paintings or steal them.
Do we have Intel on the people there?
Let's see if I have any Intel on one 10.
All right.
I need to like park this.
There's a parking garage right here.
All right.
One 10.
Let's see.
We got me.
This is one 11.
This guy not home.
We're one 10.
Let's go.
I'm going to go over on the back.
I can't, I can't climb this.
I mean, there are no bricks.
I can't throw anything.
There's a guy home.
I don't even know if this guy's home.
What if he's open his door?
Is he going, oh, why are they coming over here?
They're not going to come all the way over here.
And if they do, I think their AI is not going to be smart enough.
They're going to run right by me and turn around and run back.
I'm like wedged up into the wall.
See, I'm going to get caught here.
Definitely.
I don't, I don't think so, man.
I think we're good.
I'm hiding like a child.
Hey, sometimes the simplest of techniques is the most effective.
All right, go on and get out of here.
The painting's right there.
Get out of here.
Why?
Hey, look, I'm going to do signals.
One of them gave up.
They only have one thief in town.
All right.
That, what is happening right now?
Two gave up.
There's the third one.
Why is the third one not giving up?
In fact, I have an opportunity here.
I need to see if anyone's here.
I don't see anybody in here.
And in the bathroom, maybe?
But I have to smash this.
Well, it is, what the fuck?
Get out of here.
Is this going to, what are they, how can,
how can you tell if a place has an alarm?
Why are they walking?
Oh, to go into their house.
Oh, no.
This is their house.
No, is it, or are they just on the road?
They won't leave.
Where's my car?
I think we're in the clear.
There it is.
Okay.
All right, I need one, 111 is this unknown.
I need to go to 112 and do the same thing.
Don't walk past people's windows.
What am I, stupid?
All right, police are gone.
The same shit happened last time and I got stuck back here.
What is this here for?
See, this is, I told you, there's a jump here.
There's a guy right there.
All right, what is this?
Electricity?
I have to go all the way around.
I can get intel, right?
I got a new routine.
Just put it down, put it down.
I'm under arrest?
Well, I feel like it could have outran you
after you flipped over your fucking squad car.
Where, where is this?
No, it was just right there.
All right, so we got, we got a couple of jobs.
Job.
Let's go to break the, let's go to one.
The other one's more expensive anyways.
112.
You can steal it too.
You're under arrest.
You did 112.
I didn't steal a painting.
I need to like go up there.
No, I can mark this person.
Wait, hold on.
Why can't I see these people through the walls?
There's a spare key for the front door.
Okay.
Well, I know that whole routine.
112.
Here we go.
Break or steal the kiss.
But it's 150 bucks for this.
Oh, they're both there.
I wonder if I can get a routine here.
Well, the painting's in there.
I could bust the lock, steal the painting
and get out scott free.
They're okay.
Look at how long they're in the bedroom here for though.
See if I can pick them when they're.
Because if they're in the bedroom for that long,
I can pop the lock, go grab the painting
and get out.
But they're at the end of it here.
It's probably a bad idea.
Yeah, they're about to be out.
Should I go for it?
I'm going for it.
I didn't.
I was looking at chat.
Why would I do that?
Give me the molar painting.
Give me like the fucking chew impression.
What?
Oh, oh, which way are they going?
Which way are they going?
I think I can make it.
See ya.
And I got the painting.
I just walked an antique painting.
I just walked a full couch through the neighborhood.
Really?
I would give that an A.
But the amount of preparation and dodging and weaving
and that was not an F.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Should I pawn this or should I sell it here?
Art.
Well, it's not under art.
Antiques.
Other.
Kitchen.
Electronics.
Car parts.
Yeah.
All right.
So I did it.
I actually still am on that one.
I got to pawn this.
I wonder what it's worth.
I'm going to say 500 bucks.
Scroll down.
I did scroll.
I got to the bottom of the scroll.
Welcome back.
Well, it's 150 dollars to break the damn thing.
Go through all the trouble of stealing.
It has to be something worth doing.
All right.
Apparently not.
I need agility level two.
Required level six.
I just have to just keep stealing things?
That's on top of the 150?
Yeah, it probably is.
All right.
The only thing I can do here is either just...
I can just go into random people's houses.
Right?
What's stopping me from doing that?
What about 106?
Let's just case this place.
Unknown.
I can't mark you.
I can see you right through the door.
Somebody coming down the street.
What are you doing out this late?
Get out of here.
Why are you even on the road?
Ring the doorbell.
Got you.
What happened to this person?
What is this person doing?
Oh, they're going to sleep.
All right.
I got you.
So you are in the kitchen.
You're...
Okay.
So he's in there for a while.
They're both incapacitated for a little while here.
This person is very restless.
All right.
Let's get in here through the...
Keep an eye on that minimap for me.
What the fuck are you doing?
The blue is when they're not doing...
Really?
No, it looks like we're going to 107.
The Wilsons have a huge house.
Just climb over the fence?
See, I can't.
I don't know how to use a fence.
Not until I level up, like, one more time in agility.
I can't use a fence.
I think it's an intel, though.
Any other intel for 107?
I think there's only one way in to 107.
Through the front door?
I can't, like, take the mail?
All right.
I'm going to wait.
Anybody right here?
I need to wait till you walk by.
Just walk by so I can open this.
What's it blinking to?
It's easy to climb the fence.
Yeah, yeah.
Stealing mail is illegal.
Um, so is smashing windows, taking paintings,
and throwing bricks at people.
Okay.
Opportunity is arising right now.
Getting gnomed.
They have all their blinds closed.
You know, this is probably a mission to do that.
All right, here we go.
Back door.
I need luck picking three.
This house is secure.
No, so is this.
All right, well, just take all the cool stuff
they have in their backyard.
Well, I'll take that.
15 bucks.
We got a radio.
Wine.
A couple of nice wines.
On the grill.
I want to whip a brick through that window.
So bad.
That's it, right?
What if I do this?
Can I annoy them enough?
Were they going to open the door?
I can't get in here.
Leave mud here.
Where's their doorbell?
Are they smart and they don't have one?
Where's your doorbell?
Fine.
Throw a brick.
There is no brick.
Do you see a brick anywhere?
How do I throw a brick?
Throw gnome.
I, I don't have anything.
The key definitely under the mat.
Well, I, I can't get it.
Yeah, this house is locked up.
Holy fuck, that guy could see.
All right, what about over here?
I gotta go craft a brick.
I need, I need to just steal a few more things.
All right, here we go.
104.
Nobody around.
What's over in the corner?
That's mail.
All right, the people that are in,
people are sleeping in here.
What time is it?
It's 2 a.m.
Level three lockpick.
What the fuck?
Is that level three?
Nope.
No, it's level three.
Shit.
I was trying to go in with them.
I can open this one.
So I can't do any of these houses.
I need like level three lockpicking to even do with them.
I need like other tools.
All right, I have to stay away.
I gotta go to like 101 through 103, apparently.
Because I really only have one thing to do.
I have, the job that I have is steal the painting in 110.
That's 50 bucks.
I don't have any other jobs to do.
All right, I took the loot there.
I need to like case the places out, man.
Let's see.
Okay, 110.
That's where I'm supposed, let's go.
Let's make our kind of cheese.
Um, I'm a big Swiss cheese kind of fan, but.
You know, Havarti is really good.
What am I answering this question?
What?
Yeah, no, Swiss cheese is great.
All right, I just gotta break or steal the painting over here at 110.
And then I would probably get more tasks.
All right, break or steal the painting.
The people are probably home right now because it is 9 30 p.m.
I don't see anybody in this room standing.
Oh, forget about the flashlight.
Dude, can I just like learn how to climb the fence?
I need to learn how to climb a fence.
Because I, all right, we're going to the front door.
Is somebody here?
Just break it.
All right, I did it.
They're not even home.
Got it.
Okay, that was an original.
You know, they shouldn't have had it displayed in the window.
Why on earth would you display like a fucking million dollar painting right in the window?
And you have single pane windows so people can see.
All right, do I have anything to sell besides that?
They can't afford any more window panes because they already bought the painting.
Welcome back.
I have no items.
All right, is there anything else for me to take from the home?
It was actually only a 50-dollar painting so that doesn't make any sense.
But I mean, come on, if you have like an original Mona Lisa,
if you had the Mona Lisa and you lived in a single level one bedroom
with like 10 windows and you had it on your wall,
like somebody is going to smash your window and take it.
They just will.
You need to have like a home alone style booby traps everywhere.
Well, thanks for giving me more of your routine.
You wouldn't be living in that house if you had the Mona Lisa.
Yeah, you know that that's 100% true.
Like a 50 million dollar painting and you're in like a one bedroom in like a suburb somewhere.
I'm obsessed with these houses.
I got to get over these houses.
I just need to start taking stuff.
What about 103 and 102?
I just need money.
I just need experience.
Does it learn to climb?
I have to do this before I get experience to learn to climb.
Okay, so we got this looks very elaborate.
Electronic door.
Lights are on.
Somebody's listening to music.
Anybody behind here?
No, they're not having like a backyard barbecue.
That's perfect for me to take whatever I want.
You don't have anything back here at all?
Nothing.
Shit.
Damn it.
Do I have to like break in the front door right now?
I can't even do that.
And they don't have a doorbell.
Well, this house is secure.
Mona Lisa would be do very well in there.
There's a person coming right now.
I don't think anybody needs to get home.
101.
How's 101?
Security cameras.
They got they got the whole thing set up here.
There's security here pointing this way.
Cameras in the front of the house.
All right.
Anybody in there?
You don't just have any trash I can take and sell?
Now you get on top of this.
Lockpicking level three.
All right, we have to go back to the other houses.
It's like 110.
I have to rob the same guy over and over again.
Or this one would open.
So sad.
I have to rob the same person?
Okay, I don't know where they are now.
But it is 2am.
They're probably asleep.
This guy's gonna walk right by.
This many pedestrians outside at two o'clock in the morning.
No.
Where the hell do we live?
People just taking strolls at 2am.
All right, please don't come down and get like a glass of milk.
50 bucks.
I hope they don't wake up.
It's three o'clock in the morning.
Who's gonna wake up right now?
$15.
All right.
Oh, slowly.
Slowly.
Oh, whatever.
They're not gonna fucking hear it.
They're in the bed.
Nothing up here anyways.
All right, no money.
There's another safe.
It is plenty of what?
Somebody in a basement underground?
Oh, fuck.
I can't fit in there.
There's oh, yeah, I can.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm gonna pee.
I gotta pee my.
Oh, that's a camera.
And we got a damaged U-phone.
If someone's looking for that.
I'm gonna pee my pants.
I don't know why I have to pee so bad.
Why?
It just started.
I don't know.
When I walked in here, I got nervous and I just had to pee.
I'm like a small dog.
It was in there.
Silverware.
4 a.m.
I gotta get out of here by like 6.
Now turn the light off.
We're easy.
All right.
It's time to go.
I gotta get out of here.
Okay.
Oh, Huey.
What is a Huey?
Is that your door?
What was the door?
I heard door.
5 a.m.
Out.
Okay, let's sell this stuff.
There was something that on that black market,
somebody wanted one of these things.
I'll take an A.
All right.
So there's another level up.
I thought the skill point is available.
Let's take a look.
So I'm level five.
I can't even buy this.
I can do this.
Appraise more items on the spot.
That is the only thing I can do.
So I'd have better appraisal skills.
I need to do more.
I need to steal more shit.
All right.
What did somebody want here?
I have any of that.
Car parts.
Electronics.
Somebody wanted a damaged U-phone.
Sure.
Router.
Radio.
Kitchen.
Other.
Antiques.
What was it?
What did I pick up?
I picked something up.
Oh, here we go.
Break or steal the pear decoration.
At 113.
Easy enough.
All right.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to pee my pants.
So I'll be right back.
See you guys in like two minutes.
All right.
So what do you say?
But yeah, I mean,
I make sure that I have none of my stuff like in any windows.
Like none of any.
Literally all the stuff that I own.
I make sure to just completely protect myself.
Everything I own is underneath my bed.
Every painting.
All my game consoles.
All the money that I own.
I just put it under my bed.
So I have like a house worth of shit under my bed.
So people will look to the windows.
They're like, well, this guy is like fucking nothing.
But they literally realize
I have a vintage motorcycle under my bed.
I've got every DVD of Spongebob under the bed.
See, what I do is I put,
I take the Spongebob boxes
and I leave the boxes out right in the open.
Like, holy shit.
Well, he's got all the Spongebob.
Hey, stupid idiot.
I put the special features DVDs in there.
The real ones are under the bed.
Oh yeah.
You're asking to get robbed.
You got all the Spongebob DVDs.
All right.
What about this one?
What about all the limited edition Happy Meal toys?
They're all under there too.
Guys, I have a quadruple king.
The bed is the floor.
I had it specially built.
You know, you open up somebody's bedroom
and there's, oh, there's carpet and there's the bed.
And no, no, no.
You open up the door to my bedroom
and the ground is a king size bed.
The ground is a bed.
You have to like open
and this like made it a special foam
where there's enough for the door to open
and then you just kind of climb on.
It's possible to climb the second floor.
I want a possible loot location on 104
because that's the one I can get into, right?
It's no wonder it took you six weeks to move here.
I mean, it was an incredibly elaborate project.
It's like $445,000.
And the whole, I don't know if it was weird
because the whole time that the workers were making it
they were like laughing
but the door would be closed
and I would just hear them fucking hysterically laughing
while they were doing it.
And I would just pop in like, you know,
hey boys, like boys, what's going on in here?
And they'd stop laughing
and be like nothing, we're just like working.
Be like, okay, okay.
And I closed the door and like after like five minutes
I'd hear them laughing again.
It was really, really angering me.
All right, there's a pricey guitar in the garage.
They were watching the DVDs.
Yeah, it was weird.
Like I kept hearing like
really, really memorable funny SpongeBob quotes
from inside the room.
I was under the impression
that one of them could just do a really good SpongeBob.
I was like, wow, that one of them in there
can do a fucking great SpongeBob and a Squidward too.
They're like having a blast.
All right, if I got the money,
I might as well spend it.
Let's learn everything about 104.
So pricey guitar in the garage.
You can climb the second floor vines
and there's only one person there between 8 and 7 p.m.
So let's go.
8 a.m.
Go.
And that, what was, which one was that?
This is 106.
All right, wait no, 104.
So what time is it?
Between 8 and 6.
Is that 8 p.m. or a.m.?
So this person is out here from 8 a.m.
104.
I don't have anything else to sell I don't think.
The Jared Leto Joker laugh and the Squidward laugh
are the same laugh.
Are they?
Hold on.
Fuck, you're right.
Wow, it's the same thing.
They're the same laugh.
You're absolutely correct.
All right, 104.
We got all the intro between 8 a.m.
Let's just sleep in the fucking car.
I screwed it up.
8 a.m.
I bet you 100% German has done a Joker cosplay.
I have not.
I have not done a Joker cosplay.
All right, sleeping in the car until 8 o'clock in the morning.
Well, 7 a.m.
To get myself some time.
All right, run.
Another way.
All right, one.
There's supposed to be one person in here at 8 a.m.
All right, so the bedroom is downstairs.
That's really good to know.
Crouching in a weird place.
All right, we're fine.
So I need 104, which is this one.
I don't think I can get in here though.
Is this the one that I couldn't get in?
It's not.
All right, wait.
We're going to wait until the person.
And god damn it.
I don't think I can do anything here.
I can't climb these.
No, I don't have agility too.
But I can get into the back door.
I'm going to wait for that person to leave in 10 seconds.
All right, here they go.
8 a.m.
Which way do you go?
You go over this way, it seems.
No, you're just going to circle around.
Out the front door.
I think I've walked around in a circle three times.
Okay, so there's somebody sleeping down there.
And they're the only one here.
What?
Put it down.
I can't put it down.
Lock the exit E.
Oh my god.
No, I gotta go.
That cop has a shitload of food in his mouth.
He got the call.
He was right there.
He's in the middle of his lunch break.
He's sitting there like eating a delicious fucking turkey club.
Then all of a sudden he gets like the call.
Oh shit, like.
All right, let's try this again.
Between 8 a.m.
And 9 p.m.
Fuck it.
I'm just getting in there now.
Because he's going to walk around a circle.
There's people right here.
Yeah, just I'm getting in there now.
I'm going now.
Get in there now.
Person right there.
God damn it.
Come on.
Try driving through the garage first.
The garage is right above this lady.
Oh, I gotta wait for this person to go.
Multiple people.
Who needs a neighborhood watch when
there's eyeballs on every single street at all times.
The neighborhood watch is just a connected group of people computers.
What do you want?
What's wrong?
What is wrong with this?
I'm just like I'm doing the same thing you're doing.
All right, can I get a second here?
He's gone.
She's awake.
She's going back to bed.
That's what a neighborhood watch is.
Am I ever going to be able to do this?
She's still asleep.
This is the perfect opportunity to go,
but I can't until this person is going to turn the other way.
You walking up here.
I'll have an opportunity right now.
No.
Okay.
Um, okay, right now.
Okay, I don't want this is this is that board game.
Don't wake daddy.
Somebody's an open window.
This is not even the right house.
This is somebody else's house.
Uh, okay.
I don't know where they are though.
They might be here.
This is the guy's office.
Nice painting.
I don't see anybody.
I need intel on this.
He might be in the other room.
He might be in this room.
What if he's in here?
Oh, come on.
You don't have anything.
Turn these off.
No, I thought that was a person.
That door is open.
Somebody's here.
Somebody's in the house.
Expensive, uh, expensive toilet in here, right?
Expensive guitar.
No, that's the wrong thing.
They're definitely home later tonight.
Oh, I got the routine.
Um, he's gonna be home.
What?
I shouldn't see in that.
Oh, that's a pants shit moment.
You just peek around the corner.
You make direct eye contact.
I need to get to the other house.
Is she downstairs?
Oh, can I hide in the bathtub?
Hide?
What can I hide?
That is a nice toilet.
The husband's gonna be home.
I'm in deep shit right now.
What would you even think if if you got home?
And you didn't notice anything strange.
The only thing that was weird about your house was your toilet was in a hundred pieces.
Just be like, I don't even know what happened here.
Like, honey, do you know what happened to the toilet?
What was that?
It's like a golden goblet.
Oh my god.
No, give me the remote.
I got a golden goblet.
I got that.
It's time to go.
I got the ultimate bonus.
I don't care about the TV.
Okay, I got time to go.
Now, where's my exit?
The husband's home.
Oh, there's a safe.
Safe.
Shit.
I can't.
I don't have any more room.
I gotta get out.
Out.
I have the golden goblet.
What more do I want?
Painting?
I can't.
Put it down.
Put the painting down.
I can't put the painting down.
Why?
I can't put down the painting.
I'm stuck in the wall.
My sensitivity just went up by a thousand percent.
Why?
What the fuck?
Why is my sensitivity at 5,000 right now?
What?
That was bullshit.
I couldn't put the painting down.
I literally...
The game broke.
I could not put down the painting.
And when I put the painting down,
my sensitivity was a thousand.
What the hell happened there?
You weren't pressing E.
I pressed E a hundred times.
And my sensitivity still screwed up.
What happened?
Do you see this?
Why is this so weird?
That was total horse shit.
I'm sitting there pressing every button.
E, click, space.
It's E, E, E.
I picked it up with E.
Something feels off.
Like really off.
Even my mouse in the game.
I'm going to restart the game.
Is it saved, right?
DPI?
Well, I don't know why it just changed in this game.
Did I panic hit my DPI?
I mean, there's no...
I don't have a button to do that.
I'm just going to reload it.
Yeah, very effective.
DPI button on your mouse?
Is there...
No.
I don't even have...
I have two buttons on my mouse
that don't do anything.
Yeah, I do have a death adder.
I've been using it for almost three straight weeks
and all the buttons don't do anything.
Let's see.
Why couldn't I just put the fucking painting down?
Why would I use a death adder in 2020?
Because I have like big fucking hands.
And every mouse I've ever owned
that's not a death adder is too small for me.
I swear to God, I'm not making that up.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, you guys are right.
You guys are right.
Watch this.
Why is this on here?
Let's put it all the way down.
Back to where it was, where it belongs.
Why would that be pre-programmed into the mouse?
If you accidentally fucking press that button
your mouse just goes to shit.
By default, that's on?
What kind of fucking brainless shit is that?
That wasn't on the original death adder.
Every mouse has that?
No, it doesn't?
Why?
I don't want that on here.
I want that to be like EAT or Melee.
All right.
Let's see if I can actually not press a button
and not be able to pick up a fucking painting.
No, get off of this.
I need to wait.
I had it too.
Like I just...
But that wasn't even the root of the...
God.
That wasn't even the problem.
Is E to pick up and E to put down.
And I couldn't put it down.
That wasn't even the problem.
How do those buttons get pressed by accident?
Because I'm trying to press every button.
I just want the goblet.
I already had the fucking goblet.
All right, I'm just going in
and I'm smashing windows and taking it.
All right, what time is it?
All right, he's gone.
That doesn't even matter.
Not even the right...
It's a different house.
All right.
I don't care about the painting.
I want the goblet.
Press E to drop a goblet.
Okay.
I want to show you this.
E.
Here we go.
It has to be...
Why did it not work the first time?
I pressed this a hundred times last time.
I promise.
You understand?
Why is it working now?
Need room to draw?
But there was nothing else in the room
when I was here last time.
All right.
Where's that goblet?
Just give me the fucking goblet.
Give me this.
Give me out of here.
Fuck out of here.
Get out of the...
Get out of the window before I fucking freak out.
I'm doing some suspicious walking.
Didn't break the toilet.
Fucking Razor Death Adder DPI bullshit.
That just...
You hit that person.
It's a gamer button.
You wouldn't understand.
No.
And don't when I plug the mouse in
try to install your fucking like parasite software.
That's another thing.
66 bucks for this?
That's it.
That's all we got for that.
Oh, we got a lot of new quests.
All right.
Are you ready for this?
This is 104, 105, 106.
We're gonna try...
Break a window.
Break their TV.
Break their sink.
These are my kind of missions.
104.
Break the fucking window.
105.
Break this TV.
And 106.
Break the sink.
Back to it.
Let's go.
What's a brainless guy that came up with that?
I'm gonna rebind those to like a sound effect.
Like a fucking fart sound.
I'm home.
Oh, what's this?
What did I say I wanted to change to?
To eat?
This is like total fucking rage coming up.
I want to rebind it to eat.
Okay.
What was in here?
One needs to be broken in here.
104.
Break a window.
What else was it?
What was...
Get out quick!
Oh, I'm stuck.
No, get back in.
Get in!
They leave the window opened in the back.
Freeze!
What?
That was house 106.
This game is fucking funny.
This just put me here.
I didn't do it.
All right.
So 106.
Which one's the sink?
106 is break the sink.
And then break...
Okay.
106.
Break sink.
Break TV.
Break window.
Ah, yes.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you please come to the door?
Where's your sink?
He just did the thing when you walk by a public bathroom stall.
You like see the guy and he sees you and it's like,
Oh, fuck!
Police are going to tow my car.
Oh, shit.
The police are going to tow the car.
Break TV.
Are they coming back?
Are they coming to tow the car?
Are they coming to...
I got to...
Do I fail the mission if they do that?
The police are going to tow the car.
No, don't tow the car.
I'm just...
I'm coming out right now.
Fuck out of the way.
I didn't even touch that guy.
Okay.
Well, so get in the car.
Just pull it over here.
106.
Sink.
105.
TV.
104.
Window.
I need to do that one last because that's going to cause an alarm.
So we've got 106.
I don't know if anybody's here or not,
but the doorbell seemed to work pretty well.
Get fucking out of here.
All right.
Sink.
Oh, that hurt.
I have to pick the lock from the inside.
Can I bring the doorbell from out here?
Oh, come on.
Jump out the...
I know, I know.
But like, but hold on.
I'm panicking.
But isn't she in this room?
She's in this room right now.
Ah, ah!
I told you.
I told you she was in the room.
She's not going to come in here, right?
What was that?
Where is she?
What room is she in?
I don't know where she is.
I heard her.
This is open.
But is she right here?
I think she's right here.
I don't know where the fuck she is.
She's in this room.
I hear the footsteps.
It's driving me crazy.
Oh shit, the husband.
It was the husband.
All right.
We take what we can get here.
Come on.
Oh shit.
That was bad.
But no, no, no.
That's okay.
Where are they going to go?
Inside this room?
No, I'm so fucked right now.
Hiding.
Hide.
Get.
Ha.
Uh.
So this is very hard without knowing when the husband's going to come home.
Unlock all the doors.
I like need the other tools.
I need like the other lockpicks.
I need like the electrical kits.
You could have just opened that other window to leave.
Could I have though?
Who locks individual doors to their house?
I don't, I don't know.
Why do you have like locks on every door?
If I had like a person in the house, I had like a tenant call the player.
We got two of them done.
The only other thing is break the guy's TV and uh, where is it?
105.
But I know nothing about these people.
This is going to be impossible without knowing that.
Didn't get the sink?
Yeah, I didn't.
How did I not get the sink?
Was it the wrong house?
Broke the wrong sink.
The kitchen sink?
What you broke wasn't a sink.
That was very clearly a sink.
It was a sink.
I don't have to get the kitchen sink.
Was it bidet?
I don't think I can leave.
I'm stuck here forever.
No, it's the, it is the right house.
So I have to run up and smash the sink upstairs.
He's using the toilet.
So you tell me this wasn't a sink in here.
I'm not breaking the toilet.
The police, like AI is like stuck here.
It's already open.
What is going to happen?
Is it going to close?
I got it.
What's she sitting on?
Okay, sink.
Oh my fucking god.
You guys weren't kidding.
They break the sink.
That was the same one that was downstairs.
That was the same sink.
Give me a break.
How was I supposed to know that?
Where are these police?
Can I please get out of here?
I have three stars.
What the fuck?
Broke a window and you're going to get a helicopter in here?
Is there a chopper?
I smashed a window.
I did the equivalent of like two kids playing baseball.
I don't think I can get out of here.
I think I'm screwed.
I wonder.
See this window is locked.
I can't open it.
I can't open this fucking window.
Ah, seen by a tenant.
The chopper is right here.
How am I supposed to get out of here?
I'm going to break a TV.
I'm just going to break a TV.
Where's the TV?
Okay, this is like, this is getting a little out of hand.
Wait this out.
I can't wait this out.
This is 104?
What do I need to do in 104?
What the fuck?
I'm done.
I'm getting out of here.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, wait.
No.
Just give me a mission to do.
I just need to level up to six and then we can keep going.
I'm not, I'm not leveled up enough.
Am I level six yet?
Can I climb fences now?
Oh, thank God.
Okay, we can continue with the tutorial.
That's Jilly 2.
I got it.
Um, is there a reason why we're not going on here?
Fucking DPI settings.
I'm just going to go home.
Fucking Windows 98.
Hey, you know what else ain't broke?
Is Greenview 104's windshield.
No, I, I, every time you make me do this, man, I fuck it all up.
And then I get angry at my muffs.
Welcome back.
Whoa.
I won't buy this.
Wipe it and we'll talk.
Oh, never mind.
Hey, go smash somebody's windshield at 104.
You know, you've been there like a thousand times.
You keep breaking shit and keep getting arrested.
And then you progressively get more frustrated at yourself and at the game.
And then you start blaming your hardware.
All right, so climbing gloves.
Why would you need 1200 dollars?
Hopefully it, that was a good, that was, that was not a mistake, I hope.
Break a car window in 104.
The gloves cost more than the car.
All right.
Break a car window at 104.
You got it.
It's going to take two seconds, right?
Well, I can climb.
Break a window.
Break a car.
So I'm going to break the car window.
I'm going to break a window and get out of here.
He's not home.
So I need to get down to the garage and break the window of the garage.
I can't carry this.
Put it down.
What else is in here?
I've got like an opportunity.
Might as well take it for a second.
Okay, he's going to be back very soon.
So we need to get to garage.
Car.
Here we go.
So I need.
Inventory is full.
Can I throw shit away?
Fuck the radio.
Give me the guitar.
Okay, break a window.
Can I open this garage?
Okay, here we go.
Oh, no.
Get it open.
Holy shit.
What?
What was the thing that he wasn't even on the screen?
He wasn't even on the mini-map.
What?
What the hell?
He wasn't on the...
And he had a key.
I would have got out.
That would have been...
I would have made it.
You can only climb the fence in certain places.
None of which are here.
I have to climb up there and go down.
Why am I doing this during the day?
Because the husband is not there during the day.
Unlock it before you start.
Car parked in a strange place.
Hold on.
Come on.
I'm going to accidentally hit somebody.
The police are going to tell the car, come on.
I might as well just restart it.
Triple parked.
I would have got out of there too.
All right.
So I'm going to open up all the doors before I do anything.
Let me see how strange.
All right.
What time is it?
Four.
I'm going to sleep until 8 a.m.
Because that's when he leaves
and I have all the time I need.
8 a.m.
So she's sleeping.
This person right here.
I'm going to unlock all these doors before I do this.
I'm going to unlock this one and then I can get...
Let's see.
Make sure I can get out of that one.
I don't have time to do this.
Somebody's walking on the other side here, right?
I don't think I have enough time.
I have to wait.
I'll do this one first.
Because there ain't nobody looking over here, right?
Okay.
This one's open.
Open.
Thank God there's no fall damage.
All right.
Do I have an opportunity to do this now?
Not quite.
Put on the pink pantheon music.
All right.
I'm going to get it like...
Hold on.
Let me get it queued up so I can have it.
All right.
It's loading.
Whatever.
This is going to distract me.
Here we go.
Get out of the way!
Why is it always somebody here?
No!
I went the wrong way.
Shit!
I thought there was...
No.
It's okay.
That's the wrong way.
No.
I can go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
What is playing right now?
Back up quick!
Back up!
Don't!
No!
God, this is fucking music.
Oh, I turned the wrong direction.
I'm going to have a meltdown.
Why is this auto playing?
I think I crashed the game.
I did.
I can't even open the game again.
I like went down too far.
Distracting myself with fucking music blasted in my ear.
Trying to like play the game to the music.
Like just fucking do it.
Why would I do that?
There's literally no reason to do that.
I can't think of one single reason why you would play that song and try to do it.
It's difficult to do.
You know, it's like crap, man.
Did we crash again?
No, we're fine.
Maybe we're not.
All right.
Yeah, like I mean like what the hell would I possibly be thinking?
You know what I'm saying?
Like why would I do something like that?
That was just stupid.
Okay.
Here we go.
I got a very, very small loan from my father.
I think I have to start somewhere.
Wait, what?
Wait.
Oh, I'm freaking myself.
Why is this playing?
No, stop it.
I know I just did it.
I did it.
Get out of here.
Okay.
I'm fine.
We're fine.
We did it.
What is auto?
What is auto playing?
It's playing the Freddy Krueger theme song.
It's not.
Where did Trump come from?
All right.
Should I just keep auto play on the whole stream?
What do you think?
What's going to happen?
At least for like the next few minutes.
Come on.
I don't a D with a five stealth XP bonus.
I can't handle it, man.
I'm sorry.
I need lockpicking three.
Lockpicking three.
I need to be level.
I got to just get to the skill point.
Donald Trump shit.
Like, why was that playing?
What?
Even I swallowed about a million dollars.
Like, I just played fucking the Pink Panther theme song, man.
Okay.
So I just need to, I need to sell.
I have that guitar.
Apparently, I can't sell it here.
All right.
I will turn auto play back on.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
I'll do it.
Just give me a second.
Welcome back.
220.
I'll take it.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's get the auto play back on.
Count Dracula music time.
All right.
Jaws?
Why is this a horror movie theme song?
Let's go.
This is, this is, what is it?
Michael Myers.
No, it's not.
What is it?
The Exorcist, right?
Somebody stop him.
I just did the other one.
They following me out here?
How long is this video?
This is a long one.
I know this one.
This is soft.
And it's loud.
Please like if you enjoyed the music.
Okay.
Well, I don't know what the next thing is.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to, I don't want to listen to this one.
The thing that's coming up here in a second.
Oh, no, no, it's not.
Oh, wait, what is this?
I just saw like the guy like, we need your help.
Whatever his name is.
And he was like one here.
He's up there.
Okay.
So I'm going to break into, let's go to one.
Oh, we've terrorized these people for long enough.
It's Ghostbusters.
Come on.
I'm going to turn this off.
Get.
That's an advocate.
Hold on.
Keep auto play.
Auto play is on.
I just skipped the track.
This is Nintendo me theme.
Okay.
This works.
I need a task, man.
I'm like, I don't know what to say right now.
Just sounds like this is like a Wii Sports menu.
What was that?
What?
A seat?
How do I get in their house?
I have to, I'm going to turn it off.
No.
What do you mean no?
I can't stand it anymore.
I have to turn it off.
I have to turn this off.
E?
I got an E.
What is E?
What is an E?
That's going to make me lose my mind.
I'm losing my mind.
Oh, is this like 40 minutes?
Do I, can I level up?
I can level up.
I think this might be like four hour remix.
Oh, hold on.
I'm getting lightheaded.
I gotta stop.
Okay.
I need lock picking three.
Vinny, what do you have to say?
Break or steal a big TV.
Oh, wait, I need like the device.
Somebody come to the stream.
Oh, thank God it's over.
Oh, I feel bad for the new people that come in
and just think I'm fucking weirdo.
Why am I listening to this?
No, it's going to play like a League of Legends remix.
I don't know what the next thing is.
All right, I need, do I need a new thing?
I don't have enough money for the lockpick.
All right.
This is just like Beethoven.
I think I need to make more money.
I hate this.
Oh, no, I have to turn it off.
I can't stand it.
What do I need to do?
Break the TV.
It's 500 bucks.
Open the fucking door.
Open your door.
Come on.
What?
What the what?
Okay, we're done.
Finally.
We can move on.
We don't have to listen to this.
No, no, no.
I don't want to hear this.
This is going to ruin everything.
This will ruin my whole childhood if I listen to this.
No, don't listen to it.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear this.
Boy, this one's good.
This one sounds pretty good.
You're right.
It's only remixes.
I'm skipping like five times.
Kirby remix.
The same Kirby remix.
King Dedede's theme remix.
Kirby all-stars.
Now I'm on-
It's not about winning.
It's about fun.
What's that?
Fun is when you-
Fun is-
It's like-
It's kind of-
Sort of like a-
What is fun?
Like-
Let me spell it for you.
Get in!
I got it.
Where's the TV?
That's not a big TV.
What?
The cop is in the house?
Get off.
Turn it off.
I'm done.
My overstimulation is over.
I hate this.
Okay.
So.
I need to get-
I could have just gone up there.
I'm so-
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't stop it.
I just had to go for like at least a few minutes.
I'm just very-
I'm gonna apologize for that.
Over and over again.
I'm gonna park and I'm gonna sleep and I'm gonna steal their TV.
Remixes.
Oh, I'm gonna throw up.
This is a remix for every single thing.
Okay.
I gotta turn this down though.
This is not allowed.
It is absolute hell.
All right.
Let's wait until they're asleep.
I don't even know why that-
Oh, because we played the pink panther music.
All right.
I need to see when they're home.
They're asleep.
Leave the lights around in here.
TV's in that room.
I could break it and get out.
Or I could take it.
Can I fit it out that window?
It's possible that I could even fit it through the window.
Definitely not.
I have to just break it.
I'm gonna put it in a different room and break it.
Somebody in that one.
I can't even open this door.
Come on.
I can't even open that door.
I need a level three pick.
I don't have one.
All right.
We're just going-
We're just gonna steal stuff.
Try to get some expensive stuff.
Arrow in the knee dubstep remix.
Oh, that was a sought after item.
Router.
All right.
I'm not gonna get too cocky here.
Phase.
All right.
One more item and I gotta get out.
Maybe some money.
Oh, somebody's in there.
Hold on.
All right.
I got a router.
I can't-
Right here, I'll get another router.
That's two routers.
That's good enough.
Anybody outside right now?
Yeah, I'm good.
Okay.
Back to the car.
Let's sell this stuff.
Clean job.
No more fucking around.
Like, I've just-
I've let like the-
Just the bullshit get to me right now.
I need to sell the routers.
One of them was sought after.
Oh.
What?
4k-
Yeah, there's like 4200 people here.
I hope you guys are having fun.
Doom.
Oh, I'm not gonna play the Doom soundtrack.
I'm not gonna play the Doom soundtrack.
Do I have-
Do I have to play the Doom soundtrack?
Break the toilet in 105.
Sure.
Break the dishes.
Break the toilet.
Break all their glasses.
Can I do something that's not-
Smashing shit?
I don't want to just break everything.
All right.
I need some security tips.
They leave the balcony door open and I need-
I want their routines.
There's no one at home.
There is no one home between 11 and 2 at 105.
Possible loot location.
They bought a pricey painting.
Why am I paying for this?
All right.
Fine.
You're gonna have to give the people what they want, right?
Okay, that was Doom theme sped up by 1.5 times
and then I put it up times too.
There you go.
I hope you liked it.
Please pay attention.
That wasn't me laughing.
That was me for doing the trumpet
that we played for five seconds there.
All right.
There's a lot of-
I'm not gonna do the 108 yet.
We're gonna go back to-
I don't know what to do with 104, man, but seriously.
All right.
So 105, I need to break the toilet and break their TV.
So I need to get sleep in the car starting at 9 p.m.
I got until 2 a.m.
From 9 p-
No, from 11 p.m.
Until 2 a.m.
It's empty.
I can do whatever the hell I want in 105.
You can sleep backwards.
How do you go to bed backwards?
All right.
So 105, it is-
Well, we need 11 p.m.
We gotta be out by like 1 30.
Break the toilet and break their TV.
So here is 105.
There it is.
Just wait for them to leave.
Is there something I can climb in here?
Okay, I can break in here, climb up the vine, TV, bathroom.
Now we just have to be patient until 11 p.m.
Here they come.
Shut the door.
No, I need to be able to get in there quick.
Hydrate.
Come on.
Count it down here.
10, 10, 45.
I'm just gonna be standing outside their house.
They come out the front door?
What about this here?
When are they here?
No, that's this hard.
This is a lot harder for this house.
All right, here we go.
Coming out the front door.
I'm just standing here.
I'm just-
This is what I do.
All right, you disappeared.
It is now 11 o'clock.
There's nobody in this house, right?
This is 105, right?
Yes.
Okay, steal.
I can take it.
I can actually just take it.
Play through the fire and flames.
No, I'm not gonna play through the fire and flames.
What, from like 2007?
It's still good.
I know, it's a good guitar hero song.
All right, with time, we got a time check.
12, we're good.
Nobody coming.
Okay, we got the TV.
Now we need to break the toilet.
Nobody here.
I can stick-
Ooh, chessboard.
That's all I can take, apparently.
Can I fit more than one thing in the car?
I wish I could see.
What's wrong with me?
All right, we're getting close here.
I gotta get-
I gotta hurry up and do this.
Ow.
Me serious.
I can't fit more than one thing in the car.
What's worth more?
This one is 10 experience.
And if I can't have it, nobody can.
Break the toilet.
No!
What?
How?
How did this happen?
Get me out of here.
Come on!
It doesn't-
I don't understand.
How did I even get in here?
Lean out.
Lean-
Freeze!
I don't even know how I got stuck in there.
I turned the corner and like I bumped into the-
I'm gonna have to do that again.
I have to-
What is it?
Nine, 10 o'clock.
God.
I'm gonna do it real quick.
Keep the trunk open.
That was my fault?
Why was it my fault?
Because I ran and bumped into the wall?
You should have fl-
Your ass is too big.
I should have just slept till-
I'm just gonna go sleep till 11.
Park next to the house.
No, that's suspicious.
That's suspicious.
I can't do that.
No, sleep in the car.
Park in their garage.
I can't even open their garage.
I don't have a garage door opener, guys.
Let's make this quick.
Break the toilet first.
I know, I know.
I know I should have done that.
Why am I doing it like this?
Toilet first, you muppet.
But it was-
I had-
Ah, forget it.
Get the TV to last.
I know, I know these things.
But I'm so stupid that I did it in the reverse order.
I'm gonna walk very slowly through this house.
Okay, nice and safe.
We're good.
Turn off the flashlight.
What is blinking over here?
Oh, break or steal the-
All right, can I take money?
Yeah, I'll take it.
I can't take the stereo or the receiver.
Can't take anything else.
I can take-
No, I can't take this.
It doesn't fit in the car.
Does anyone want to break people's plates too?
It's in the other place.
Okay, that's it, right?
Good, go, go.
Somebody's here.
Forget about the ride.
Gotta run with the crowbar.
All right, time to go.
Other house?
I need-
I need more information on those houses.
Raid the fridge, yeah.
All right, that was perfect.
How was that a B?
I did it exquisitely.
All right, I gotta sell that TV.
What do I got?
$8.95, car parts, electronics, kitchen, other, antiques.
All this takes place here.
Okay, $107.
I can't do $107 until I get the better-
I don't think I can do either one of these.
I think I can sneak into $106 if I break the window or something,
but I need the level three, this one.
That's $1,200.
Okay, what do I got for Intel?
No, $104.
I got two of these done.
Nothing to-
Okay, $106.
Break the sink, break the dishes, info.
They leave the window open in the back, right?
So that's the only time that nobody's there.
$107, no nothing.
$108, I know nothing.
They leave the window open on the second floor.
I could probably sneak in there.
Break or steal the big TV?
I can't know because the TV's in the room with the guy with the harder lock.
I can't do it.
Uh, I'm gonna say let's do $106.
Let's actually stake this place up
because I need to do break the sink and break the dishes.
So let's go to $106 after I sell the TV.
All right, big TV.
Hopefully it's worth something.
Here you go.
Welcome back.
What do you take for a big TV?
$120.
How do I unlock that?
I won't buy this.
Wipe it and we'll talk.
Okay, $106.
Time for a stakeout.
Wipe it with a cloth.
I'm not sure that's how it works.
It'd be really easy to delete your whole phone that way.
All right, $106.
Let's get a good stakeout position.
All right, so what time is it right now?
It is currently 2, 11 a.m.
So I need to find out what these, where they are here now.
Are they here or are they not here?
It's a decent question.
Everything I need to do is upstairs.
Break the dishes, break the sink.
And they have a pricey painting.
They got a lot of stuff in $106.
$106.
Front door can be opened and I've got to wait till no one...
Is no one taking the living room or anything?
Wait for this person to get out of here.
This is what purgatory is like.
There's just nine families and one man just tries to rob you for all eternity.
Just have to deal with this one guy.
I would also probably either move or try to catch this person.
Change the locks.
Not that that really does anything.
All right, we're in.
Okay, so I know that right now, they're going to be getting up fairly soon here.
So I need to break this sink and break their dishes.
And then they leave the window open in the back.
So this window here, okay, this is the painting.
So should I just get the heck out of here?
You know what I'm saying?
I think I'm just going to get the heck out of here with this painting.
Yeah, I just wanted to see if the...
I was seeing if the toilet was down here, but they're all upstairs.
But I can get intel.
Hold on.
Intel.
I can't get intel here?
Let me go get it.
Okay.
That guy's not going to wake up.
Okay, I got to...
They're really...
I don't think there's any real window there.
Here's what I'm going to do.
We're going to prop the door open.
Don't!
Okay, they're fine.
I'm going to get this out the door, like right here.
And then we're going to go for a...
We're going to smash the sink, smash the dishes.
And we'll sprint out of the house as fast as we can.
Here we go.
Ready?
What do you think?
Toilet.
I'm not going back to the toilet.
I ain't going to lose.
Have they not hear that?
It was all the way upstairs.
They probably thought it was the cat.
Let's get out.
Good.
Nice and clean.
Look, I'm getting the hang of this.
I'm figuring this out real quick.
You know what I'm saying?
After four hours?
Yeah, but hold on.
You got to give me a little bit of credit here.
Like 30 or 40 minutes of this was like
losing our minds like on acid to Pink Panther remixes.
So I don't...
You know what I'm saying?
Does that count?
1,500.
Let's get it.
All right.
I got the lockpick.
Now we can test it out.
I got the electrical lockpick.
So now I can...
Is there...
Can I test it on something?
I don't have like a training thing,
but I do have the new gear.
So I'm allowed to do it because now I can...
All right.
Lockpicking four.
Here's lockpicking three.
So I have what I need.
I have a point though.
25% more backpack space.
I mean, that's just good.
I'll just take it.
All right.
Let's go to 108 and break in there after we pawn the TV.
This game is like watching paint get a license at the DMV.
That'd be really, really entertaining.
That'd be awesome.
Can you imagine that?
Think of what would need to happen for that to be a reality.
So much going on there.
I would have a ton of questions.
Welcome back.
350 bucks.
I'll take it.
All right.
Break into 108.
How do you wipe the drive?
Probably with like an electronic hacking kit.
I would assume.
So how was it pronounced?
Is it is it jup or jup?
It is jup.
Because it's short for Jupiter.
So it is jup.
All right.
I need to case out 108.
Wrong.
Yeah.
We all love that.
We all love that big planet Jupiter.
Don't we?
Parking space right here.
Only real germamites know the truth.
Yeah.
Come on.
You guys, you got to be like a real germamite.
All right.
Time to case.
I don't know anything.
They leave the window open on the second floor.
That's good to know.
Like how the gift creator says jup.
So we can ignore you.
I mean, come on.
Are you really going to put like a rhesus rheses argument in front of me here?
Say whatever you want.
Okay.
We'll get some intel.
Now I want to go get a bag of rheses pcs and bring them up here.
You need them.
This can be open.
This is a simple lock.
Nobody around, right?
Let's go.
Whoa.
Wasn't very simple, was it?
All right.
We're gonna find a person.
Nothing in the garage.
Not that I can see.
I want a brick.
I've not seen a brick the whole time.
Holy shit.
This game is just actually Skyrim.
Oh, you didn't even come on me.
Like really?
Let's watch from a distance.
Are they still looking at me?
Somebody make an entrance here.
I'm watching that tail end here.
I'm going to be careful.
What about two stars?
I've done a good job of hiding.
Why would I get two?
Why would you pronounce it rhesus as rheses?
It's a name.
And you should respect the creator
by pronouncing it correctly.
Okay.
We're there watching TV.
I don't know where the police are,
but they're apparently still around.
All right.
So I know that somebody leaves here.
Why would you?
There's no way.
Okay.
So I know what they're doing for a little bit.
Living room.
They all go in the living room.
Back window is open on the second floor.
Who the fuck is opening this?
Are they leaving?
I think he's actually leaving.
They're both leaving.
Why are they over here?
What are you police doing?
How long are you going to do this for?
Can I climb this?
All right.
We're getting to the timeframe now.
He's out.
Oh my God.
Would you go away?
Is it Jerma or Jerma?
What else can I even do here?
I thought I could get away with it.
Again, he's not on the mini-map.
I don't understand the whole red
on the mini-map thing.
The police cars are the things
that are red on the mini-map.
So they just have a regular pedestrian?
Okay.
Well, whatever.
All right.
Well, it's weird that you can see me
all the way over there.
But I need to find out more.
So what time is it right now?
8 a.m.
I already know what they're doing.
I'm going to get up here.
Let's see if I can look through a window.
Somebody be in one of these rooms.
It's 113.
I know everything about 113.
Don't need to do that.
I need to get that intel again.
I'm going to go sleep in the car.
Just wait till night.
Go sleep in their bed.
Yeah, I'll go sleep right here.
Sleep like four hours or so, five hours.
Let's go to 4 p.m.
I just want to be able to at least
because three people in the house is kind of...
That's going to be hard.
Anything could be anywhere.
All right.
So all right, here we go.
So two people are out.
There's only one person in the kitchen right now.
So at this moment, I could climb up the front.
I could climb up right now.
I could climb up the front door, pop that open,
and then leave out the...
Yeah, I have to wait till these people are gone.
I'm going to have to worry about this in just a minute here.
He's going to be hanging out down there.
All right, let's do it.
I don't know how this works.
I didn't do the tutorial of this.
Apparently, that's it.
Uh-oh, somebody's coming home.
Somebody's home, somebody's home, somebody's home.
They're coming home right now.
See if I can time this.
When they go in the front door,
I'm going to throw it out there.
I can't get this out there.
I can't do it.
No, it's not going to happen.
I'm going to do this at night.
Put it down.
Really?
Why is the door not unlocked?
It'll be right in front.
They're not going to pick their TV up.
Just wait till it chills out a little bit,
and then go pick up the TV and go home.
You definitely have to do this at night, though,
and sneak through.
I'm not going to do it like that.
I'm just going to go get the TV.
I'm going to pull a car up.
Go arrest that guy, not me.
Arrest the guy that just drove you off the road.
Do the cops give up?
Eventually, yeah.
If you're out of the way.
We're good, right?
No, almost.
It's just like running around in circles.
I need to go hide somewhere.
Where is that car driving?
There's so many bins.
I know.
All right.
Search is now concluded.
I'm just going to get in this dumb thing.
So I'll just sit here.
Don't even tell me that I'm getting in.
This is why I'm going to get caught.
We're good.
Okay, 108.
Let's go grab that TV.
There it is.
The door is still open.
Free TV.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Don't break it.
It's very nice of you.
Thanks.
If you found it on the ground, it's legally yours.
Is that true?
What's the legality there?
So if there's just TV on the ground,
is it legal to pick it up?
No, of course not.
Because it's on their property.
All right, but what if it was on the ground in the street
for more than three days?
Then it's yours.
Don't they have a scenario
where if you find like a bag of money on the ground,
you have to bring it to the police.
Let's say you pulled over on the side of the road,
you're taking a piss
because you're on like a 50 hour long road trip or something,
and there's like a suitcase on the side of the road,
somewhere in like Nebraska.
It's like a million dollars in cash.
You have to bring that to the police station
and then if nobody claims it within like two weeks,
you get to keep it, right?
That's how it works.
Yeah, you pick up a briefcase full of like 50 grand in cash
and you immediately call the IRS.
That's the first thing you do.
Want someone to see their own necklace at the pawn shop?
You got to break it down first.
Okay, learn a phrase of level two.
All right.
Yeah, from my understanding is like
so if you found $50,000 in cash on the side of the road,
first thing you do, just put it down, call the IRS.
Say, tell them you found $75,000
and say, yes, I'd like to report it on my income please.
What do I need for this?
So I need one, how many?
Level nine, one more level almost there.
And then another thing what you should also do is say,
oh, by the way, can you like,
can you just go back and like check
the last like seven years of my taxes?
I had really awful bookkeeping
and can you like just make sure that it was correct?
Go back like 10 years.
All right, dual retool.
I got to get these.
What if you found five bucks?
Yeah, call up and report it.
If you found like a $5 bill on the ground,
immediately call the IRS.
What about a penny?
Yeah.
What else can I do?
And make sure you're crying when you call.
Like if you and your friend split,
you go to coffee together.
So you and your friend go up to coffee and,
you know, hey, I got this man.
Oh, thanks dude, let me at least go
and give you like a couple of dollars.
And you're like, oh, thanks man.
And he gives you like three bucks in cash
because you put it on your card.
You have to call the IRS and cry.
Like, I'm so sorry.
I have $3 to report.
My friend gave it to me.
We were splitting coffee in a coffee shop.
All right, let's see, rent a thug.
Break their window on the second floor
and break or steal a decoration.
Okay, somebody really hates the Wilsons.
Yeah, I just got a dollar.
Oh, shit.
I got a dollar.
Hold on.
Let me, let me just hold on a second.
Yeah, yeah, that's me.
Got a dollar.
But that's not how it works.
It's not like it's a rec line.
Yeah, it's me.
I get to call every time.
Oh, it's me.
No, guys, pay your taxes.
Pay your taxes and just make sure you stash
at least like 10 grand of gold under your bed.
Wait, do I still have a TV in the back of the car?
No, I got a pawn shop.
No, 107.
I got to park it in a different place.
Yeah, I invested all my money in Spongebob DVDs.
Do I get like to claim like capital gains for that?
Spongebob, the season one Spongebob DVD original box,
I mean, has definitely appreciated in value
by at least like $40.
Do I have to claim that?
All right.
Oh, I just know I okay.
I park normally.
That's going to hurt my brain.
All right.
Well, here's the thing.
Okay.
So can I claim a capital loss?
So if the Spongebob DVDs,
if I buy 150 Spongebob DVDs
and 10 years from now,
they're worth like a dollar each
and I paid like $20 a piece for them.
Do I get to claim capital losses if I sell them?
You know, I invested in like 100 Spongebob DVDs
but I've sold them at a loss.
All right.
I got some mid sale.
Break or steal a decoration?
Okay.
Break the toilet.
Break the window on the second floor and break there.
This is a $900 job.
And I know nothing about the Wilsons
but we're breaking in
because it is 1 a.m.
They're probably asleep.
So actually keep this open.
So break.
They got a printer too.
All right.
Where's my escape route?
Why?
What's going on here?
Did they hear me take the printer?
Because they're both upstairs.
They heard me take the printer.
All right.
Where can I throw this over?
Oh, get the fuck out of here.
I can't.
All right.
Printer.
Garbage can.
Now break toilet.
Break window on the second floor.
Break the...
There's so much stuff to break.
I need to know when they're not going to be here.
I think I take the printer and run.
Break the toilet.
Break their wine glasses.
This is all spread out.
I'm going to make sure these doors are all open.
Okay.
Break...
The wine glasses are outside so I'm going to do it last.
So make sure this is open as well
just in case I have a panic attack and I need to leave.
All right.
Here we go.
Wine.
So I get toilet.
Window.
Toilet.
Wine.
Pop the fence.
Break the window on the second floor.
Which window?
Just break any window or break the window on the second floor.
Doesn't matter which one.
You know what I'm saying?
So if it's any window, then I can break...
So they're asleep right now.
So bang, bang.
Out that door.
Here we go.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
What happened?
Why did I teleport?
Why?
What in the name of happening?
Get in the toilet!
I got the printer.
The printer is fine.
The printer is right below me.
Right in front of me here.
Oh, I didn't break or steal a decoration.
Oh, it's a different house.
I'm gonna see the printer.
The printer on the ground in front of where I'm hiding.
I wonder where he went.
No, that's not that smart.
Oh no, he's looking at the printer.
The TV's in the car.
Is the TV in the car?
I didn't see it.
No, there's no TV back there.
Didn't we just look?
I have a TV back there.
Don't say that.
You didn't sell it.
I didn't?
Okay.
I need to be, I gotta make sure this is correct.
Well, I can't go that way.
I can't go that way either.
I gotta wait till these people are all gone.
Hold on, this is important.
I think I can do another job here.
Well, get a better car.
Why can you only fit one printer in there?
Shit!
No, I can't put, I can't put anything else back here.
What an absolute disgrace.
But it's okay though, because now, here's what I'm gonna do.
Easy.
Hold on.
This is open.
107.
There's something to do here at 108.
So, break or steal a decoration.
The car's right there.
Let's go quickly.
I need to break something in their house.
Why is this closed?
Oh, fuck it.
They're gonna be like, oh, your car's in a weird place.
Let's just get out of here.
I'm gonna bring the TV back anyways.
You can't put it in the passenger seat?
What criminal goes in and takes one TV and leaves?
No, you go, you go find their bed and go onto their bed
with all the SpongeBob DVDs, all the gold, all the fucking money.
Welcome back.
700 bucks.
I'll take it.
All right, I got some money now.
I need a little bit more experience.
Close this up.
What do we got now?
We got 101.
There's nothing here.
104.
We already did it.
Nothing at 106.
107 is done.
108.
I need to break or steal a decoration.
On 11, I have nothing else on these.
I got one break or steal a pair decoration at 113.
I feel I'll do this one.
Break or steal a decoration.
So 108.
Let's case it out a little bit here.
I can't believe I played this game for four hours.
I'm still having fun too.
This is I'm having like a good time right now.
This is fun.
I can't believe it either.
I'm having like a good time.
108.
There's a parking garage.
Actually, the other one's probably a little bit closer.
Because I can probably hop the fence back here.
Let's learn about the people here.
Okay.
Break the decoration.
They leave the window open on the second floor.
I'm not tall enough to look.
I don't know where they are now.
This would be a good time to get some.
I don't want to break that.
They'll know.
They'll freak out about it.
Somebody look outside or do something.
Nobody there?
Is there no one here?
Okay, there's a person right there.
All right.
So it looks like they're all upstairs right now.
I could probably just sprint, smash, run.
Yep.
I'm going for it.
Where's the car?
Is that not it?
Drop it and destroy it.
Wow.
Why is it?
Oh, okay.
That was it.
F.
It's all right.
Sometimes you get an F.
No antiques.
You don't want anything.
We're almost...
I need to break or steal the pear decoration from 113.
And that's all we got.
We're at the end there.
I have money.
Jewelry tools requires appraisal too.
I can't do it yet.
Headphones.
So let's go get that done.
I'll be the next level to do appraisal.
And then we're probably going to get some new missions.
Maybe we'll go to a new neighborhood.
New neighborhood.
That'd be interesting.
Welcome back.
Okay, bye.
113.
Because there's definitely a list of neighborhoods that go underneath that.
It's 113.
Is my antenna bent?
Or is it just like that?
Here are the rest.
All right.
Pocket.
Well, now it's bent.
All right.
113.
Break or steal the pear decoration.
What else you got over here?
Headphones.
Those are expensive.
Anybody home?
No, nobody home.
See you later.
There it is.
Okay, hold on.
Nobody's going to be here for a long time.
Take everything.
My inventory is already full.
Are you kidding me?
What the hell?
Really?
There's no money?
What do I have that's so heavy?
Drop stuff?
It's probably the guitar that's so heavy.
The car, there's worth a lot of money though.
$15.
It's nothing.
All right, let's move.
The router.
I can't.
So what's so heavy?
Lockpicks?
Front door?
Key?
Crowbar?
The guitar, the bass, and the headphones are very heavy.
The guitar is extremely heavy.
Leave them without internet.
Knife set.
Can't take the microwave too heavy.
Tea box.
Oh, nice house.
No, give me the TV.
TV's worth way more.
Oh, it's a small TV.
Never mind.
In fact, all right, I'm good.
Let's get out.
Spare key for the bed.
Wait, give me the spare key.
Hard drives?
I can't really move around these.
All right, I gotta get out of here.
It's time to go.
Time to leave.
Where's the painting?
Okay, go, out.
They're gonna be home in like two seconds.
Use the front door.
I stole that kid's money.
He didn't need it.
Is that person gonna see this?
Just drive to the edge.
How could he know that anything was up?
All right, time to level up.
I need appraisal two.
Disassemble jewelry with special tools.
Got it.
Mini.
Greenview 107 don't like our protection plan.
I hope nothing happens to the jewelry in their bedroom.
Do I just have to keep stealing money from the same people?
I feel bad.
Well, here's jewelry tools.
I'm probably going to need them, right?
Whatever.
Well, here's a radio.
Rent a thug.
Steal a painting.
China from 108.
Okay, sell the other stuff.
They keep letting you get away with it.
Yeah, they really do.
This is different.
Jewelry workshop.
No items.
What do you do if your house keeps getting robbed?
You gotta make like an elaborate home alone trap.
Welcome back.
The jewelry tools allow you to assemble jewelry before...
Of course.
Right, what else we got?
We got the pear.
Got the guitar.
Headphones.
And the painting.
Yeah, at that point I would just put the Mona Lisa in the window
and then put like fucking tacks all over the ground right before it.
Or like a trap.
Just build a gigantic trap door underneath.
And then pull the lever when the guy gets in.
Nice painting.
Yeah, it was 10 bucks.
All right, steal jewelry from 107.
When do I get to go to another place?
107.
Well, it's conveniently located right here.
I went down the stairs.
Straight down the stairs.
It was very interesting.
Here we go.
I didn't do that.
All right, jewelry in the bedroom.
There.
Okay, let's case it up.
Because I don't know anything about 107.
Absolute zero.
But what I do know is that radio is not worth anything.
The wine, on the other hand, is worth 20 bucks.
The wine is actually worth five dollars less than the radio.
So I'm not sure why I did that.
Steal the gnome.
Is there a gnome in this yard?
All right, well, I can open this but I don't...
Somebody might be right behind it.
All right, got to be really careful.
Steal the jewelry in the bedroom.
Can I hear sound effects?
Come on.
Are they in the...
They're right here.
Oh, shit.
Is there more than one person in here now?
They're turning on the lights.
I wish I knew where they were.
Dude, they're just going back and forth turning the lights on and off.
Like, go somewhere.
What are you doing?
They're outside.
Okay, jewelry.
Where's the jewelry?
Is she coming upstairs?
Get in the fucking thing!
No, that's towards the cops.
This way.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I got to get up now.
Come on, come on, come on, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Just run straight for the exit.
You can make it.
He's closing the gap, but I'm fine.
I'm good.
I was trying to hide in the closet, but I couldn't fit in it.
Please remember to break down the jewelry.
There's a tool for it in the shop.
Break it down.
Select it.
How do you do this?
Break down the jewelry.
Okay.
You broke it.
I was supposed to break it.
You're supposed to pull out all the jewels.
That's it, right?
Infinity necklace.
Yeah, it does look like it, doesn't it?
What am I detaching?
It's better be worth a thousand dollars.
You know, that's just kind of there.
The best I can do is 25 dollars.
Take it or leave it.
That was a good one.
That was a very good one.
A professional knows how to handle a real safe.
Are you lockpicking skills up to the job?
I don't know.
Do I have to go break into 106 for a 15th time?
And cause them all kinds of problems and anguish?
Do I have anything in here?
No.
I have the jewelry though.
What's it worth?
Bracelet parts.
Well, we're gonna go find out.
Unless, can I sell them on the black market or something?
Electronics?
Nope.
Kitchen?
Other?
Antiques?
Art?
No.
Looks like it's getting pawned.
Steal 15 dollars from 106 again.
I got some stuff for you.
Welcome back.
Well, that's 800 bucks.
That's a lot more than I thought it was gonna be.
So, I mean, now...
107, 108.
Steal the painting called China.
I'm gonna have to do it during this point.
Let's go do it.
Drop off the hard drive?
Where do I do that?
Right here.
All right, let's...
I'm not gonna break it.
All right, we got jewelry tools.
I don't need that until I'm here.
Front door key for 109.
Don't need that.
Front door key for 113.
Put that away.
All right.
That's a bunch of people.
I'm like a janitor.
I have everybody's keys.
Whatever.
Okay, let's go.
Steal China from...
Where was it?
101, 108.
Steal China from 108.
I will do my best.
Is he gonna do it again?
I think he's gonna do it again.
He's gonna try to do it.
Let's see if he can do it.
Well, I got it.
I can't leave.
Uh-oh.
All right, we're good.
No, no, we're not.
Not at all.
Oh, forward I dance!
All right, I think I'm stuck here.
Put him behind bars.
Hey, come here for a second
so I can restart the checkpoint by hitting you.
Be nice.
I should be able to get in the car.
You're a caged animal.
I don't have any V-Bucks.
How much is one V-Dollar worth in...
I have to hold sprint down so I don't hit.
Just reverse.
I can't.
I tried to get the wheels in the inside of the...
Where the stairs are.
I couldn't do it.
Come on.
Oh, no.
I think I may have ruined the whole game.
I think I saw...
Why would auto save right there?
Is that the end?
Is this where I have to end this game?
What if I just don't move?
Oh, I think I can do it.
I just need to get the reverse right.
Okay, if I can just...
When I press S, it goes forward.
I'm trying to reverse right now.
Come on, right here.
Can I get it right here?
Ooh, almost had it.
Almost got it.
Come on!
I think I can go over this if I really try hard enough here.
I think so.
Ask the guy across the street.
I soft-locked the whole game.
It's over.
Was it worth it, Jeremy?
I can't just...
Can I just back up?
I can't back up any more than this.
Save it!
Come on, get up!
Go, go, go, go!
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up!
I did it.
Okay, I made it.
I did it!
Not soft-locked anymore.
Wait, what's the plan here?
Somebody just wrote,
fucking loser.
I...
Hey, come on, man.
Don't be so mean to me.
Fucking loser.
All right, 108.
Steal the china.
If I say it enough times I'll get it.
Say it again.
Steal the china.
No.
Why am I trying to get in the car?
No, just run.
I did it! I did it in one shot! What? I didn't get the china!
Steal the china! Steal the china! Steal the china! Not the daisy! Not the daisy!
The china! Oh my god! That was not the right painting, but it was lit up! Where is it?
There's people! No! No! Steal the china! Steal the china! Steal the china! Steal the china!
No, that's not it! We're gonna go back to the... Ow, my stomach! We're going back to the car.
Yeah, officers! The fuck! Officer, this guy ran into my house. He just kept screaming,
Steal the china! Steal the china! Oh god damn it! The guy sprints in your house,
just repeating the same like robotic sentence. You have a painting upstairs,
you're like, I have a painting called the china? Oh, I do! That's right!
Oh, no! Get in the car! How did I do this last time?
Steal the china. Just saying it so deliberately. You have to remind yourself, it's a fucking grocery
list. Pick up eggs. Pick up the eggs. Wife will be very angry with me. Pick up the eggs. I can't
believe I'm back here again. I can't fucking steal the china. I said it over and over and
over again, and I picked up the wrong one, and now we're back here. It's like we never
left here. How am I here again? Because I stole the wrong painting, and
should have just left the map. I know. What is this? Why are you looking? Say it again.
Steal the china. Uh oh. Steal the china. It's not me talking. Steal the china. My frame!
Oh, no! My computer's gonna crack! I'm gonna blue screen! I'm going! No! Why?
Get me out! I'm like it's a memory leak. I'm in a memory leak. I can't escape. I didn't get
the china. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal the china. Not the... Say it again. Steal
the china. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal the china.
I'm like trying to bring somebody back to life. I'm like sitting around a circle with like
candles around me. Trying to bring like Elvis back. I can't alt tab. 93%. Look at how slow...
I gotta pull this out of here before my computer breaks. Alt F4. I have to. Maybe it'll help.
My computer is hard locking. Am I still alive? Yep. Okay, I'm good. I just...
I have to steal the china. I have to steal the china. I can... I'll never let this down.
I have to get this. I have to go steal it. I have to go get this dumb fucking painting.
Can we get... Can we get china in the next German rumble? No. I don't... What? How would
that work? Like the whole... Like all... Like all the whole... The whole china? The whole thing?
Sprint. Sprint. Okay, I'm almost there. How do I save the game? Did it. Okay, it's time.
It's time. Give me... Let's give me one second. Just give me one minute here.
I'm going to just use the bathroom. I'll be right back. Get yourself a little snack.
I'll see you in two seconds. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal the china.
Oh shit, I fucked it up.
God damn it.
I was gonna have this blast while I was doing it with like scary music. Oh well. Well, that's
ruined. But I didn't go anywhere, by the way. I've been here the whole time. You can still do
it. I won't tell anyone. I was gonna... I need like more time. I was gonna start screaming on
it and stuff. All right. Where... I don't even know where we're going. 107, right?
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Don't you dare joke around with us.
Just hurry up and steal the china, okay? That's all that matters. Do as fast as you possibly can.
Okay, where is it? I don't even care. It's up there. Steal. That was the right one.
That was the right painting. Do you understand? That... This is the... This is the china.
That's the china. That's it. That's the china. I was right the first time. I had china.
I picked up china. That was china. I stole it. I stole china.
That was what it was pointing at. I had it the whole time.
That's daisy. But why is it... What happened? It was clearly... That was where it was.
Where'd it go? All right. So it explains to me, right? The marker was upstairs
around that corner. The daisy is the thing that's highlighted. The thing behind it is
the flower. Where's the china? Where is the china? Bottom floor? Why is it pointing me upstairs?
Like, this is... This is... This is not down here. It's very clearly like,
go up there and steal china. There it is. That's it. Is that it? Is it? Is there it is?
The china. How do you get out of your fucked up house? Get out of here. I need the light. Oh!
Get in there. The garage door? I... There's no garage door opener here. Yes, there is.
He got it. He caught the china. Yeah! Yes! D plus. Level up. Block picking four.
Block picking four. Open safe. Use glass knife. I only need two skill points. What? Who else?
What can I do now? All right. Where's the china on here? Candle holder, candle holder,
triple vase, flower vase, glass cup, the china. Where is it? I mean, I have it.
Do I need to steal it? I've got the china right here. This is correct, right? Welcome back.
Here. Four hundred bucks. Thank you. I had it right the whole time. Everybody was screaming at
me. I was being screamed at. That it was the daisy. No, no. It was a joke and I'm glad it...
Say we're fine. That's pretty... It's perfectly fine. Steal the china. Steal the china. Steal
the china. Steal the china. Get it. Okay. Got it. Stole the daisy. No, it was the china.
That was the china. I knew I wasn't crazy. I knew that I wasn't crazy, you know? New hints.
Uh, I can't do the skills. I want to... I need to wait till the next level.
I got new notes. Jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs,
jobs, jobs. I don't have any jobs. There's no jobs. I don't have any jobs.
Where are the jobs? Spencer just came in and gave five community subs here. Spencer Twitch
chat. Did I say Twitch chat? Twitch chat? I have no idea what the fuck's wrong with me,
but thank you, Spencer. And thanks for... See, there aren't... Look it. This is a bunch of
neighborhoods you can go to. But thanks a lot, man. I got nothing else to do. Do I just have
to go break into people's houses and steal stuff? Just get to level four? Man, I guess.
Steal for the pleasure of it. Well, I need... Okay, now I'm going to go to one of the
bigger houses now. Steal the china to farm XP. I'm not going to steal china to farm XP.
That would be a bad, bad idea. Because China does not have very much profit. It's only worth
like $15 or something. Or what was it? $40? I'd be better off stealing money from people's
houses. Like these people. It was $400. Well, is it? Should I just go do that again?
Okay, it was $400. Why did I think it was like $40? Maybe it's because of all the other little
ones. I'm sorry, guys. This is another slide. Nice. I'm gonna do it again. This is costing
me too much money. Last one, I promise. Last one. I want to like feel the thing go down.
You know, I want to I want to feel it like underneath my carriage here.
In first person. It's better to ride a roller coaster like this. Oh god, we're at the top
of Splash Mountain. Come on, back into this. Am I gonna get the car towed?
The car is gonna get towed with me in it. How does that work?
Hold on, I need to know how this works. He's calling the cops right now.
The police will tow your car. Okay, let's wait for the tow truck. He's waiting his turn on
the slide. Yeah. Well, I was too fat. I was a big fat guy and got stuck on it.
Yeah, I can't open the door. I'm kind of stuck on this right now. But here it comes. Yeah,
here comes the police to help me. Here it comes. How the hell are you gonna figure
out how to get here? He's gonna have a lot of trouble trying to get over here.
No, he's gonna he's gonna come back because he's gonna come over here and he's gonna
he's gonna screw the whole thing up. Well, I'm blocking both sides. So you can't walk up
here and oh, if I could only just go down right now. If I could only just drive straight down.
All the NPCs are coming over here. I don't know why they're so drawn to this place.
I'm like a NPC magnet. What are you doing? No, why is it? It really is a line for the slide.
He can't figure it out. He has no idea where to go. Can I how do you beep? Q? No.
Q opens up this wheel. There was another person. The police will tow your car. The
cop is gone. All great thieves honk their horn. I kind of want to see if every NPC in the whole
town comes over here. Look at this. Did you bind M3 to eat yet? I don't know what the hell
I was talking about. What was I even talking about? Just come over here. Please, police officer,
just drive over here. I'm very clearly causing a problem. Just drive down here.
You know where I am. Turn in here. Come on. Turn in here. Turn in here. Turn! Turn! Oh,
he's gonna drive by us every time. The star is just fading. Come on, there's gotta be something
I can do about this here. I can't go forward. I can't go backwards. I can't. Nobody can do
anything. I'm just gonna try to hold it. What about this way? There's another person.
Damn it. I can't at least climb out of the side. Well, hold on. Last chance. Come on. Turn
down here. You can see me. I'm right here. I'm waving. I'll wave to you. No, he can't
do it. He's not gonna do it. He'll never figure it out. I wonder if I can do like a
series of... Oh, well. We tried. Stop stalling. What do you want me to do? I'm trying to go.
Making noise? Hold on. I'm gonna get the actual police over here. I was just making
noise apparently. Making noise. Because if they get the actual police over here,
this could get interesting. I need to... Come on. Just get the cops over here. Like
the actual... Like two stars. This could get interesting. I'm gonna give this like 10 more
seconds and then I'll stop. I wish there was a horn. I'm pressing every button to try to beep.
I just don't think it exists. Alt shift. I can't hit the brakes. Oh, well. That's too bad.
Too bad. Nah, I can't get up. I was trying to do the... Look at how funny this is to go
down the slide. All right. What do I go? Just... I was gonna steal stuff. Do it again.
I didn't sell my paintings, you're right. Your bag is full. Welcome back. Sell them all.
All right. Let's go. Sell the china. Sell the china. Sell the china. Sell the china.
I'm gonna be hearing that in my sleep tonight. Buy the china back?
Why would I want to buy the china back? I got $400 for it. All right. Let's make this easy.
I'm gonna go to... I want to go to the bigger houses over here. I didn't... Oh, I stuck again.
I was just trying to go the other way. I can't move. I'm stuck again. At least I can get out
of that goddamn car. How would I get stuck there? That's impossible. All right. I'm just
gonna steal from... I have the thing to open the doors here. I'm gonna get a bunch of money
from 113 because I know that they're both not home. Well, they're both not be home,
which is Barbara now. And we steal literally all their stuff. Does this explode?
Okay. They're both gone at this point. Yes, they are. Okay. Just give me your stuff. I'm
looking for expensive stuff. These are two bucks a pop. Too heavy. Get the double alarm
clock. I don't want it. I don't want the dumb alarm clock. I'll take cash. Cash is easy.
50 bucks. There it is. Clown ball. Don't want it. Okay. Expensive guitar. $70 days.
Nothing there. I don't want the alarm clock. Check for more money. No, these things are
both $12. Don't want them. I can't pick up the clown ball. So why would I be able to steal it?
Look, I can't take the clown ball. Oops. I leave another 50 bucks. $5. Worthless. Ooh,
$50 phone. Pretty nice. I don't these cabinets open. $90 for a microwave,
but I can't carry it. It's too heavy. Tea box. Couple of wines. I think I'm out of room.
Let's like find some. Wait, how much is this worth? $40? Worthless. $18? Even more worthless.
This receiver is, I can't even pick it up. Who's looking? Does somebody see me?
This thing's $40. Just take it. Let's go the way we came. Baptism. No, this one's more
expensive. Okay, I can go with the front door. All right. Let's just, can I just run with the
painting in my hands? Just to the end? Will I still have it? Walk it right to the pawn shop.
Let's see if this works. It says a nice, no, I don't have it. Trunk? No. Oh well. All right.
Welcome back. So, guitar, lemon, razor, tea box, wine, wine. All right. I can do
lockpicking four now, right? No, not yet. Damn. Carry big items faster. More backpack
space. Disamble jewelry. Remove security from decks. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Climb on the house
gutters. Well, I'll give it a shot. Everything gives the same XP, so just steal a ton of small
stuff. Thanks for the tip. That's a good idea. All right. 101 is a big house. It's time to go
for the big shit. 101 is gigantic. Plenty of points of entry. What's with the indicator here?
Camera in front? Okay. Camera in front. Power switch will turn off the cameras.
Well, here's the electrical. Open it up. The electricity will be fixed in 237. Does the
guy actually come fix it? What's that way? Now, there's people walking around out here.
Is there no one for me to jump the fence? I'm going to go for it when this guy passes here.
Ready? One, two, three. Did you see me? I probably have expensive shit in here.
Come on, give me some intel. I can't get intel. I'm looking right at you.
What? Okay. The only two people that live here already got a guitar. Shit. Really? You'll never
get me on the roof. You'll never get me. Let's see. They're going to get out. Are you kidding
me? Come on. Damn it. Stop right there. All right. We're going to go. We're going to go
with a, we're going to go with a new tactic. It's called find a brick because I have not
seen one in this almost five and a half hours that this game has been played. Has
anybody seen a brick? Even one? Where the hell are they? On the sidewalks? You see
one right in front of the computer screen, do you? On the ground. Yeah, I know they're
on the ground, but whereabouts on the ground? Down alleys? There's one at the bus stop.
Well, there's not one at the bus stop, but over here. This kind of park bench area.
Some houses are made out of them. You know, you're right. They are. They are made out of
bricks. The first brick I find, we have to get some great shots. Sidewalks near houses.
Brick. Was it worth it? No, but that doesn't mean I can't get it through a window and
brick. I used to see in red bricks, not the cement looking cinder block bricks,
but I'm going to try and get it in windows. We'll play basketball from now on.
Now I'm going to go through that. I'm just going to throw bricks through windows. That's
pretty much the rest of the stream. I hope you guys are ready to play. I got to get some
good challenges here, but I can only get one brick. Try throwing it at a cop.
Laughing my ass off, poser. He's not going to get it through the window. Yes, I will.
If I could find one. I wish I had a brick right now. I wish I had a brick right now.
Oh shit. I need this. Hey, oh, I can't get out. I can't get out of here. Why would you do that?
Oh, thank you. What? I didn't get a chance. Why would you close the crazed psycho in the
garage with you? That's the last thing you'd want to do. Oh my God. This guy's going to
this guy's throwing bricks at me and he's running in here sprinting at me. It's scary.
Hey man, like you okay? What's up man? You like okay being locked in here with me?
Damn it. Let's sit right here. Let's see what that is. Way too low. Oh, that was close.
I just want them back. A new house. I have to get that. What? Throw a brick at the police.
I have to get a brick aimed in the right direction in the first place and not have one
spawn on top of me. You just had to throw them at the house with a security camera.
Bastard. I'll show this asshole. You're gonna throw bricks at my neighbor. Okay, this is
actually easier to find bricks to go faster like this. All right, we've got four bricks
here. You thought you could stop me? You think your security cameras are gonna stop me?
Next time come to the PTA meeting motherfucker. Oh, it was so close. Just restart it.
I know what that is. Store bricks in your vehicle. Hold on. Can I put bricks in the car and just
have a never-ending rain bricks on somebody? What the fuck is he doing in the house already?
Jesus. Oh, is your husband the cop? My guy the call came. He got that inside the house.
He was getting ready for work. Perfect place to store these. Perfect place. Perfect checkpoint.
All right, we're gonna go for the we're gonna get a bunch of bricks in here.
Oops. I don't think you can do this.
I hate this car. Car's giving me nothing but trouble.
So bad. No, what are you doing? I didn't even cross the line. So, okay, you can't,
so you can't put the bricks in the cars. I have to break a window with a brick before
I turn the stream off. I'm sorry, I have to. I mean, I'm pretty much got my fill of the
game. This game's pretty fun. If there's more content here, that'd be, it'd be better.
There's more like neighborhoods. I'm sure there probably is, but I mean, I need to end this
with a brick throw through a window. This is gonna keep needing to happen. What was that
spot? It was back in front of the 101, right? Right here. Bricks. Aren't they like
right here? I can't, you can't steal cars in this game. They're usually like right here.
Where do my bricks go? Oh, they're right there. Okay. All right. I have to get this.
That window right there. The same guy every day comes and tries to throw a
fucking brick through your window. Yes! I did it!
Underneath.
What time is it? Let me just have a couple sips of coffee here.
That's a nice, bold, rich flavor. Honey, what are you doing? Are you going to work? Okay.
Goodbye, kids. I'll see you later. Okay, have a great day. All right, now I'll do what I do
every day. Let's sound good in the newspaper there. Mr. Jordan, nice to see you. Line it up
here. Right there. A little too high. A little too much. I'm gonna go over the bathroom window
tonight. See if I can maybe hit one of them. Got one. Have a nice day. See you tomorrow. Same
time. How much does he get paid? Nothing. He won the scratch off lottery 25 years ago.
Dude, hit the mega millions. We've got nothing else to do. This time, let's go for somebody's
head. Oh, we got an open door. Open, open, open, open. Throwing bricks into the house
at this point. Anybody up there? Oh my god! It would have been right in his head.
Me! Hold on. Hold on. Stay there. Come here. I need to ask you a very important question.
You have to stand right in front of me. Right here. Don't move. That was too far to the left.
I have to do it. I ran out of stuff to do in the game, but for some reason,
I'm not leaving the game. I'm still here. I haven't left yet. I'm done. They ran that
lady over. That's fine. I have to get it. It's gonna happen. You'll see it. We can all go,
what the heck? Oh my god, he did it! Perfect. Oh my god. Oh my god. Fucking Jesus Christ.
Right there. Stop. Stop. Why are you getting so close? Some of them keep moving.
I think that my computer lagged, but yeah. Do they have a hurtbox? Yeah, they do. Oh,
fuck me. All right, the last attempt. I'm gonna try this one more time. I can't go
to sleep until you do this. I can't go to sleep until I do this. That looks good. No!
Oh my god. I can't believe it. I got a better idea. Block him with the car? That's not a
bad idea. Which way are you gonna go? I think I can get this though. You just go right there
like that. It should be it right here. Did it land? All right, I'm gonna block him with the
car. Did anybody hear it? No landing sound means hit. All right, well, we're gonna have
to block this. I'm sorry, guys. Like if you thought you were gonna see something here.
Stream's been over for 10-20 minutes. I'm just like kind of winding down. This is like just
like a me time right now. You know what I mean? It's just a little me time. All right,
where are they? We'll put that away. Why am I losing my place right now? I'm losing my
place. Right here. All right, stay there. Stay there. Don't move. It's like right here.
Oh my god. Why? That's as close as you could possibly be without a heading.
That wasn't even funny. It was only funny because his facial expression didn't change
at all. Uh, what am I doing still? Why am I still here? I haven't, I can't leave.
I don't think I can leave. Oh, all right. I got, I'm out of here. I'm done. Hey,
thanks for coming to the stream, everybody. That was fun. Can you crush, no, you, you,
you can, you, look, you can like hurt people. It's not the way you think. People, uh, there's
no, nobody dies. Nobody gets hurt. The admission ends. But that was fun. Thanks everybody for
sticking around. By the way, if you didn't know, uh, there's a poll that is hanging
around here. I talked about it in the first, uh, probably five minutes of the stream, but
this, if you could please vote on this poll, pick your favorite one for the green screen.
One of these actions, you got to pick one for your favorite because there was a lot of meme
shit. There was a lot of meme responses and of the hundred and like 75 different actions,
uh, the top three here are going to be included as well. So I put the memes in one thing. I
don't know when it happened. I mean, I know what some of this stuff does. I mean,
I know what like the Macarena is. I don't know what Jojo poses are. I know what the
sunglasses is and how the Sonic run is. The John Travolta thing, Dark Souls,
the bee video. I know what these are, but the date for the green screen has changed to Friday.
So Friday, I figured more people will be able to hang out. We could just relax. So it's
not on a week night. Well, Friday is technically a week night, but it's right before the
weekend. So I figured a lot of you guys would have a little bit easier of a time to
hang out and go if you wanted to. Uh, what time Friday? That is the real question. It's
probably going to be around, I would say three or four PM Eastern. That's the thought.
I don't know the exact time that I'll be in the studio because they're still
kind of working that out. So I, it's probably going to be in the afternoon,
but thank you everybody for hanging out. That was, I didn't expect to play six hours of
Thief Simulator. I was really under the impression that I was going to do that and
then like go play Hitman or go play like Delta Rune or something. But, uh, Hitman is out.
I will see you guys tomorrow. So tomorrow, which is Wednesday, we will be playing,
uh, Hitman 2 or Delta Rune, one of those two. Thief Simulator over Delta Rune. Well,
I did a vote before the stream started and people wanted to see this game.
I hope you had fun. Thanks for sticking around. It's getting late. I know for a lot of you guys, so
take care. Much love to you. Uh, but tomorrow I'll be in the chat hanging out. We'll figure
out if I'm going to do Hitman or Delta Rune because once I start Hitman, I kind of,
I'm kind of going to play it for at least three or four streams in a row, I would assume,
because I loved the first one so much. So maybe, I don't know, maybe we'll do Delta
Rune tomorrow and then Hitman after the green screen stream or Hitman on Thursday and then,
but we'll see. I got to figure that out because I don't have a schedule yet really.
But, uh, we'll see. Vote on that poll. I have tons of suggestions. It's going to be a lot
of fun. The green screen stream is set to go on Friday and I will see you guys later.
And for that, let's go back to earlier today and let's go through the bits. Take care,
everybody. And let's start with the outro, which should have been on already, but it wasn't.
All right. Thank you, Benny Toe for the two dollars. Hey, Jerma, I know this is a weird
question, but, uh, when you and italics wake up, does it happen that both of you guys,
uh, have, uh, brush our teeth? We do. We do brush our teeth every morning,
Benny. Thanks for the two bucks. Uh, Flubba Gut, thanks for the one dollar
gun. Interview for an apprenticeship in IT tomorrow at 10 AM. Got to get my Jerma fix
if I'm going to be confident. Good luck to you, Flubba Gut. Take care. Hope it goes well.
If you're not here anymore, well, we wish you the best. MostlyLost, thanks for the one dollar.
To be honest, I only donated to this channel to help italics pay for his house.
That doesn't make any sense. Thank you MostlyLost for the one dollar, though. Thank you too.
Bake me home for the two bucks. What games are you looking forward to in 2019?
Um, I mean, Smash Brothers comes out in 2018. Uh, February or March, what was it, uh,
the From Software game launches in March or February, right?
Shadows Die Twice should be awesome. Yeah, yes, you can absolutely expect streams of that game.
Sekiro, yeah, there it is. Looking forward to that one, but besides that, I'm not really
too sure. I'd have to take a look at what's coming out. Thank you Devakitty for the one
dollar. Jojo poses aren't a stupid meme thing. It's just that Jojo poses are awesome and it
would be fun. Well, that's up to you guys. I'm not going to give an opinion on them,
but thank you. Uh, HasNain, thanks for the 15 bucks HasNain. 15 dollars from HasNain and
they say Zoworldo. Zoworldo. Zoworldo. Thank you. Uh, that's a lot of money. Thanks a lot.
Thank you to Good Sir Reginald for the one dollar. That's it. Just one dollar. Thank you.
Manboy, thanks for the one dollar. These are some Jojo poses. Have fun making them.
I'm not going to do all of these. There's like a hundred of these. How many of these do I
have to do? I'm not going to do them. I'll pick out like a few of them maybe, but I'm not,
that's not even certain that that's what I'm doing by the way. The poll is not even done,
but anyways, thank you Manboy. Uh, that's an interesting thing that I'm about to do in a
few days. Uh, Darkstar, thanks for the one dollar Darkstar. Can we send you meme videos
to watch during bit readings outside of the movie night? No. I'm going to make that really,
really clear that because of the amount of footage and the amount of random stuff,
there is way I can't like pre-screen that stuff unless it's going to be for a specific movie night.
So outside of that movie night, I'm not going to click on like green screen, Jerma,
me in something because I can't pre-screen them and there could be some awful shit that I
don't want to like show or watch. You know what I mean? So unfortunately outside of the
maybe one or two movie nights that we do, it, that's going to be kind of, that's going
to be it. How often will movie night be? Um, I don't have like a set time or, you know,
duration. It's just something I wanted to do. We'll see how the first one goes. If there's a
lot of great submissions, then obviously we'll do it over the course of, you know, a couple
of streams, maybe if it takes that long. But yeah, thank you Darkstar, 700,000 games.
Thank you SinisterCorn for the five dollars. SinisterCorn, thanks a lot. Hey Jerma,
I'm shit-faced. I hope you're not shit-faced. Enjoy streaming. Uh, not tonight though. No wine
tonight, but hopefully you enjoyed your night. Thanks a lot for the five dollars SinisterCorn.
Googly-Garrett, thanks for the five dollars. Hey Jerma, I missed the labo bit train,
but I just wanted to say thank you again for being the wonderful goof ball you are.
Was super happy you enjoyed my animation and had it put on the second Jerma channel. Here's
some bits for being so humble. Also, I am at a drawing that Snoozing Copter made. I thought
you would enjoy it. Here it is. Thanks again for the years of entertainment.
Uh, thank you Googly-Garrett. Uh, your animation was fucking hilarious, so absolutely.
And let's take a look at this. Oh, it's a gift. It's a gift cat. Oh, that's awesome.
Have I seen this before? I think I feel like I've seen this.
If I haven't, then I'm mistaken, but it's awesome. The cat police. Yeah, the wrong clip.
Yep. That's that. Very, very good animation. But thank you Googly-Garrett. Thanks for sticking
around and thanks for being a very talented animator. So, because a lot of people enjoyed
that. I'm one of them. Thank you FlubbaGut for the one dollar. Who the hell leaves stacks of
dollars lying around in shelving units? Whose house is this? DivUSP, thanks for three
dollars. No message. Thank you Div. Again, Div, you give pretty much every single stream
and although you don't necessarily write messages every single time, thank you. I see your name
pop up very frequently, so sometimes I see you do write stuff, but thank you. It means a lot.
LSG Icarus, thanks for the two bucks. Wait, so pots and pans are worth a normal amount
of money in this game, but a laptop costs fifty two thousand dollars. Well, that's a
hacking laptop. It means it has special hacking software built into it. So that's,
you're paying for the brand. You know, it's like Apple. It's the same computer,
but are you paying fifty two thousand dollars more money? That says the guy that has an iPhone
and an iPad. Kind of a hypocrite if you ask me. Talking about this guy. Thank you
Superintendent Chalmers for the one dollar. I ever think of enabling the better twitch.tv
animated emotes like clap so we can applaud when you do cool things. I don't even have
better twitch.tv. I have just regular, not even night mode twitch. I can't see Sour Please. No,
I don't even know what it is. I know it's like a guy dancing. That's all I know.
You don't use, no I don't use night mode and I don't have better twitch.tv.
Guys, remember, this is important. Listen, I didn't have a custom HUD in Team Fortress.
I played with just the default minimal HUD. I didn't have a custom HUD in World of Warcraft
either. I think maybe I had one small change, but I do. I just go default, man. Yeah, really,
that's for real. I think I only had a custom HUD in any of these games maybe one time over
the course of a few, maybe like a month maybe. You can't see my name in light mode. I actually
can't. I can't see that. Let me see. I can't see your name. I have no idea who you are.
You're just a mystery person. I don't know who you are. I can't even
uh select and scroll.
There are people that told me that I had like pixels on some of my emotes that weren't erased
and I can't see them because I have light mode on. But anyways, thank you super seal
for the one dollar. Sorry to ruin the good mood, but because you live in Las Vegas,
I really should know this. Remember to lock all of your doors and windows.
And uh call the police when you see this man. It's just like a claymation thing. What is this?
I don't understand what it's just like. It's like a claymation thing. Thank you super seal.
I'll be sure to take care of myself. Thank you. It's sir. Thank you. It's Ross Garra.
Thank you. Oh, that was whoops. My bad. I'm gonna make mistakes. Thank you. Extra
cheesy for the ten dollars. Extra cheesy. Swiss is piss and cheddar is better. Use this money
to get some real cheese. I didn't say I hated cheddar. What? When did I? What did I say I hated
cheddar? I like cheddar, okay? I like cheddar. I just like Swiss a lot. But thank you for the
ten bucks. Extra cheesy. Fifteen actually. He says did you kill them? Who did I kill?
I don't know, but thanks for the fifteen dollars uh extra cheesy. It's a lot of money.
Enraged grandpa also gives ten bucks as well. Thanks for keeping the drunk me entertained.
But thank you drunk you for hanging out for the night. Hope you had a good time. Thank you so
much for the ten bucks. Uh good sir Reginald again thanks for the one dollar. They definitely
took a dump in your drywall. What? Enraged grandpa thank you for the five dollars again
here. Fifteen. Also take this because drunk me wants you to have it. So many people are
drunk on a Tuesday. Well uh you what? You want me to like oh how could they do something like
that? I was drunk on like a Thursday. What was that? That was like a Wednesday. When was that?
Was that Thursday? Hey it's five o'clock somewhere in the world. As long as you're
taking care of yourself and you're good to go and you have a few drinks that's all right.
There's nothing wrong with that. Just like I said know your limits. Know when it's like
time to be done and like make sure that you take care of yourself you know. It's not a big deal.
And look remember some people have different schedules right? So like oh well I'm drunk
on a Tuesday. Well what if that person has Tuesday, Thursday, then Friday off? You know
what if they have Tuesday? What if they have Tuesday and Wednesday off? That you know and
you want to hang out have a few drinks. You know it could be a different schedule. You know
but thank you. Thank you enraged grandpa. Hope you had a good time.
Hasnain, thanks for the five bucks. Need to keep that number one medal.
You currently are there at $30 Hasnain. Number one for the week. Thank you. It is not a competition
but that makes you happy. There it is. Number one. Thank you so much dude. Enraged grandpa
again gave one dollar no message. Thank you enraged grandpa. Eefs thanks Eefs for the one
dollar here. Love you Jeremy. Let me just tell you how fucking stoked I am to get to
see you do Jojo poses but that's not that's not confirmed yet. I mean it's it's currently
doing all right in the standings. I mean I wouldn't call it great but it's it's doing
all right. It's not hasn't hasn't won yet. It hasn't you know it's still competition is still
going. Uh but I'm gonna meme the fuck out of you if you do these poses. Some prime real
estate poses that I need to do. Oh god it's not I mean it could lose but if it wins
you know if it if it does or it might not you know probably not why not but if it does then
absolutely I'll take a look at some good ones. Uh thank thank you CK Luck for the one dollar.
I'd like to imagine this game is just you and Vinesauce high drinks when you are not
streaming. Just Vinnie telling you to break toilets and steal toasters and paper plates
from people's homes. Anyway my point is how many bits do I need to pay for you and Vinnie to
rob me? Uh not none. Okay I don't want to rob anybody. Do I know face cam? Oh I just I don't
really play with face cam. I have it when it's I find it to be necessary or when I have something
I want to say or something I want to do but I don't know. I typically do not play with face cam.
You'll see my face plenty though. He'll rob you for free.
Is it safe to say that you love cox communications? Um no I mean if if we have
this just liquid lightning liquid internet and we have like no problems really ever again then
I would I would have be okay with it but it depends because it's I didn't drop any
frames tonight at all over six plus hours so that's great that's bad and remember because
italics is also streaming we'll be like he he's we stream at the same time
so you got two six thousand uh k bit rates going at the same time and it's been pretty
solid so if it stays like this then we're good so that's good good good but thank you
flank tank thank you were wood for the one dollar germa come to my house and steal my
heart germa disgust did you smell your savory dog today well that was that was like
two completely different statements um well first of all second of all I have no comment
I have no comments on on this anymore I've made my case I've said my piece you can either agree
or disagree that the dog a dog has like a smelly sleepy dog smell that just like fills
the room when the dog wakes up or moves around and that's that's on you too if you want to
be on the you know understand it the people know what I'm talking about it doesn't matter
you've said your piece and smelled your dog yeah I have oh god thank you ck uh luck again
for one dollar please explain the savory dog smell I don't I already did it I've already done
it a few times go back into like the fucking history and find it find me talking about
no I was like drunk but like drunk me tried to explain what sober me was trying to
when your dog forget it thanks for the one dollar thank you unconquerable uh for the one
dollar break all the windows on a house and run don't bother stealing anything just be a
nuisance well I can't even like talk about it because if I if I start to talk about it
people are gonna clip it and it's gonna be like holy shit he really is insane he wasn't
just drinking wine give you dog a bath yeah I get my dog baths all the time but thank you thank
you unconquerable thank you extra cheesy for the two bucks you killed an innocent sink I'm sorry
uh ck luck another one dollar break the sink crunk wrong sink uh linear linera thanks for
the two dollars that was so worth it cheer thank you thank you so much onyx blaze thanks
for one dollar never stop being awesome please I'm just me I uh I don't have an opinion on it
either way I just like to have fun if you are enjoying yourself and you think it's fun
good then we're both happy uh Ben Jitsu thanks for the seven dollars and 75 cents
they just say kill me I don't I don't think it will no thank you for the seven dollars
and 75 cents but um no I'm not gonna do that why would I want to do that you seem like such
a swell man thank you has name for the 10 bucks you're gonna kill me with this music
okay now I understand now I get it see Ben with the seven dollars has name with the
ten dollars they're talking about the music okay I get it I get it thank you guys
thank you has name for the 10 bucks thank you Ben for the seven dollars 75 cents
sorry about the music sorry about the music guys I'll turn it down the cops came and knocked on
the door and I gotta turn the music down for the party imagine hearing that blast from your
neighbor's house like spongebob or fucking house remix uh thank you the green goo
sell your shirt uh no Tavares thanks Tavares for the one dollar someone stop him
thank you sticks renegade for the two dollars and 24 cents this song might ruin
your childhood the original Willy Wonka was trash anyway 2005 Willy Wonka for life
oh man that's just that's just not I that's just that's just not correct you know I just
don't think that's correct is that correct that's not correct right you would get a
red x on that problem if it was in the school or something right it'd be like x and minus 10
points I don't I just don't think that's correct but thank you I mean appreciate the
two dollars and 25 cents and I you know obviously respect your opinion on the matter but I just
don't I don't think it is I don't think it's correct hey son of Janoba thanks for the one
dollar thanks to you I developed a new kind of paranoia I now can't listen to any music
without fearing it would suddenly turn into dubstep I'm sorry that I had something to do
with that mostly lost thanks for the one dollar that autoplay was the greatest 10
minutes of streaming history I don't know I don't know it was fun but I don't know about that
the greatest 10 minutes of streaming history I think on this I think is when the dog was
rolling around in pee and the guy was walking a dog in his own house for the sims I I mean I
was that that was the most I've ever of my whole body hurt after that just the way that
he was walking he was on drugs walking his dog in his house and the dog was like rolling
around in pee I don't think I'll ever be able to laugh that hard at anything I really
don't think so that may have been one of the funniest things I've ever seen I don't know
that's tricky I'm thinking about it right now just like drugs mod but thank you thank you
bet three for the five dollars bet three doom ost or riot I already played it but thank you
for the feedback Dino Dan thanks for the one dollar this dream was the hardest I've
laughed in quite some time thanks for always cheering me up thank you I'm happy you think
that I'm glad you have fun I had fun too son of jenova thanks for the one dollar after that
shit show I feel like we need to cleanse ourselves so here's some uh some what is this
yeah this is cowboy bebop this is yoko panel oh I know this song aren't they doing like a
cowboy bebop again aren't they redoing it or something they're remaking cowboy bebop aren't
they for a movie or I what are they doing they're doing something thank you son of jenova
thank you bet three again for the five dollars thank you germa this is perfect germa heart
thank you bet three I hope not on netflix is that what it was that'd be weird I guess
thank you bet three thank you cj the dog for the one dollar germ I just want you to
know that the autoplay music bit was one of the funniest things I've ever would legit cry
laughing even well my brain I want you to know that the autoplay music bit was one of if not
the funniest things that everyone ever I was legit cry laughing thank you so much for being
an amazing entertainer I mean you can thank like the random autoplay because I had nothing
to do with that it just was playing them I've clicked on one pink panther remix so
that's all like google's computers but thank you appreciate that I had a lot of fun
bet three thanks for the five dollars in all seriousness thanks for such a fun stream tiptoe
through the tulips and live in the sunlight germa will do thank you bet three tusk or thank you
for the dollar 25 uh you should stream this game during december and face kim
and a full 800 dollar grinch costume uh thank you gaming hash for the two dollars and 70
cents love you streams but don't have much time to watch them keep up the good work
thank you for the nearly three dollars gaming hash man thanks for stopping in
good to see you thank you thank you drosophilia for the one dollar up cup sup pup jup no but
you don't you don't understand it's not it that's not how that word is said it's not
up jupiter jupiter jupiter jupiter jupiter jupiter just because another word has up doesn't mean it's
pronounced the same way jupiter jupiter jupiter steel jupiter steel jupiter jupiter jupiter
steal jupiter steal china steal china steal jupiter just say it a few times you'll get
It smackles more. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey German. Thanks for all the great streams
This one in particular left me violently cry laughing several times
Also, the lockpicking in this game is pretty realistic. I know because I had to do it when I got trapped in a walk-in oven
Sorry to hear that. Thank you. Smackles more for the one dollar. Thank you. Devokitty for the one dollar
jokes aside
Finder keepers has no legal merit legally speaking any stone or lost object you find if a judge deems that you didn't go
Through reasonable steps to find the owner
It's theft by finding of course if you find $20 on the ground
I hardly doubt the people will call the cops on you
But otherwise, you'll have committed a crime finders keepers has no legal merit
But okay legally speaking if you steal a knob
If you find an object on the ground and you didn't reasonably try to find the owner
So if you find a briefcase on the side of the road with ten grand in it
We are you gonna put up flyers on the highway found ten grand. Please call me
Hey, you found ten grand it's my ten grand what how you gonna do that your phones gonna ring off the hook all day
Hey, I heard you found ten grand. Oh, yeah, I was driving on the road. I fell out of my pocket
Oh shit, how can I come get it?
You have to ask him how much money it is
You can't just put all the cards out right at the beginning to say lost briefcase
Lost briefcase
Yeah, but okay. So on that flyer you just gonna write I found a lost briefcase
You know how many people lose their briefcases every day people that fly on
Airlines right now lost their briefcase today of like the
50,000 people that lost their luggage this afternoon who's gonna call you but on the side of a highway
Yeah, but I mean you could just
Take away the side of the highway when they call you ask what's in it. What if they guess
Like what if it was ten grand and something else and the guys like oh, yeah
I feel like you I've seen you you may have found my briefcase
Well, I had ten thousand dollars in that briefcase and a Mega Man sticker and he's just taking a wild fucking guess
And there's a Mega Man sticker in there, but he it's like fuck man. What could he could he just guessed?
Then it's his
No, I'd be the guy I'd be the guy opening the door even with like even with the most
Even like the most fucking evidence when that doorbell rings
You bet your ass. I'm gonna be the guy going like this
like
Here like I'm holding the briefcase right here. Ready? So like I'm gonna answer the door. It's gonna be like
I'm gonna answer the door the briefcase like this like
Hey tough man. Are you sure this is yours like I'm gonna be fucking holding cuz I don't know
Maybe he's gonna like try to rip it out of my fucking hands
Like I'm gonna hold it tight like this like that like hey, what's up, dude? No, I'm gonna go under this shirt
It's gonna be like like this like hey man, what's up, but I'm gonna be holding it like with two hands
Hey, what's up, dude? Yeah, so you look at me. Yeah. What are you looking for again? Oh my briefcase briefcase
Well, what is sticker in there? What's the sticker?
I'm like, I'm gonna make sure he doesn't fucking just grab it
What's better somebody just come ring your doorbell and fucking come punch you in the face and run out with it
Hey ever heard of a razor? You have to write your name on every single dollar
Handcuff it to your wrist
I'm gonna do an experiment. I'm gonna know never mind. I can't like say this but like
Wouldn't it be funny if all?
Joking here, but wouldn't it be funny if this joke I'm about to say
like if I just put like a thousand dollars in a briefcase and
put it on the side of a road and
Just say what happened. I mean put flyers up and shit. That's a social experiment. Yeah, I'm not gonna do one of those
We get stolen
We'd be like we'd be like like staked out like camped out while watching it like oh shit here comes a car
He's pulled up. Oh, man. What's he gonna do that? There's a grant in that brief. He has a fucking cash
Oh, wait, hold me. He's like, oh, he's looking at it. He's opening it up
Okay, man. He's he's scooping out all the cash
Yeah, I think he's got probably he's gonna go he's going in his crate through the briefcase as hard as he could into the woods
All the money just went into his pocket
Okay, but like hold on. Hey, hello ahead. He's in the car. He's stepping on the gas
Then anybody gets played he's gone. That guy's gone
And that would be it. That'd be the whole thing. Why won't you take the case with you?
Because like you don't want the evidence
How do I know he's stepping on the gas because his car peels out and he fucking goes 80 miles per hour on the highway
I wonder what happened. You would just lose a grant
Oh
Put a GPS in it. Yeah, but then like yeah, I guess
Funny just like a skit
We're gonna do a social experiment. We try to find out what happens if somebody finds
$10,000 in a briefcase and they just fucking take it and that's it
But moving on no country for old men
Thank you to Sperg S Ferg for the three bucks
Don't forget to report this
Wait, what don't forget to report this? What am I important? Oh, oh, right, right. Sorry
Thank you. I got to remember the things I said four hours ago
Thank you to genie boy for the one dollar my boy, Jerma
Likes lo-fi
Lo-fi like Wi-Fi
Like Wi-Fi, but not Wi-Fi like the like the shitty version of Wi-Fi. It's music. Oh
Oh
Boomer my life is completing itself one brick at a time. German knows what? Thank you
Thank you smelly boy for the one dollar. Hey, can you make a separate channel on discord for?
history and philosophical talk
No
No, you know how how fast that would get derailed in like 30 minutes
Why that would just I would just get derailed the history channel
Fuck it. Oh
Fuck
God damn it
No, no, it's not gonna be about the history discussion
philosophical channel
Make an IQ test so certain people wouldn't be able to get in the channel
Well, I would I would probably not be able to get it. They're my own channel on my own like officially Cindy like
done discord
Perfect. Thank you superintendent Chalmers for the one dollar. Hey Jerma
It is of most importance that you and chat watch this video
If it's a gnome, I'm going to turn off the string just checking
What is going on here, it's his wedding video so it's wedding video it's like a I don't know that is
Thank you for the cat video. We need a Garfield emote. No, we do not need a Garfield emote
Thank you for real though for the one dollar. I highly recommend you do a stream of the you testament
It's a game where you can make a character and fuck around in
Jesus's time now. So watch this video. Don't you know the rules?
What is it? This is this is this is a tiny URL link. It's ain't like a YouTube video
virus virus virus virus
Thank you for real though for the
Fun dollar
It's more of a compact URL
Hey, thank you Evan the newbie for the one dollar steal the frame rate. That was really weird
I know exactly what you're talking about
Dark star. Thanks for the one dollar dark star 700,000 games for good full grocery list burglar
For next Jerma rumble you will see a Jerma rumble here before the end of the year
I can promise you that I'm gonna try to make as many characters ever that I've ever made
It's gonna be the most characters ever made
Everyone is here. You know I'm saying
Everyone is here
Just kidding though, cuz I'm not making like a hundred and fifty characters. That'll take me like six weeks
Thank you card mom for the one dollar. I wish this was a movie. It's a reddit post Jerma place thief simulator
steal the China
November 13th, that's
The best the pink panther. Thank you card about thank you Garfield the Monday killer
It's long. So no Garfield graph just a Jerma mustard
It's the Garfield with those other. I don't know those those are those are not Garfield
Garf's coming in here with the bits and a Garfa graph. I paid the toll. It's time to troll
Good evening ladies and germs looking good
spectag
Somebody hit him in the head with and he's bleeding
Somebody fucking threw a rock at his head and it fucking collapsed his skull
What's next here?
Derms playing thief simulator, huh? Why not play a good game and play some of that sly Cooper action, huh?
Little custard pie too bad. My favorite flavor is mustard pie
It's just a rowing shit. Anyways folks. You've got plenty of funny Garfa graphs in store
There's no shortage of my Garf-tastic bits be sure not to od on them though. Yes. Yes
I snuck in a bit of PG-13 there. I was naughty. All right. See you around chat
You've been a great crowd
So Garfield I assume tonight was actually one of your better Garfa graphs. It went fantastically
They didn't even break out the firearms and pitchforks this time
You should like send these to
Garfield enterprises. See if you can be good the Garfield writer burn in hell cat
Thank you. Thank you Garfield the Monday killer for your your your
Jesus oh
You guys are fucking hilarious
Thank You Darkstar for the $1 Darkstar 700,000 games enough
even though the cough absolutely idiotic cough Jojo poses are going to
Potentially not there. It could be up in the air the pole. I would like to see a more elaborate bee snap
That's on the pole. I mean this few things on the pole. This Garfield steal the China
I don't think Garfield steals the China. It's not yet
Not women not yet. That's not like a movie. That's not a thing. Why am I like trying just that's not a thing
No, not yet. Thank you unconquerable for the $1 German 95. Hey, I don't need it before but I'm doing so again
I'm really impressed with how interactive you are with your stream. I can't wait to see what's next. Have a great night ugly streamer
Also, while I'm here take some more of my money with a sub. Thanks a lot unconquer a bee
Thank you
Look something sometimes chat, you know chat gives it to me. I give it to chat. We go back and forth
We talk a little shit. We have a little fun. We fucking do stuff
It go at these streams. I love them as long as you're having fun
I'm having fun. Then we're all having fun
Why are you talking shit to you chat?
No, I'm not like that. I'm just saying we'd be like we go back and forth. We have a little bit of fun
You know, some people call me ugly, you know, somebody will call me ugly. I know they're just messing around with me
Yeah, I did have it right
You are but you've said okay, so I so you could call me ugly, but I can't be like
My GPI sucks
What has nothing to do with you? This is that's me complaining about my mouse
I never like say anything mean to you guys what but thank you. Hey, honey chain
Thanks for the four dollars and thirty cents, honey chain
You've read my one dollar bit message in the middle of the stream the other day
Which was just a jump story that was only partially true. So here's a little to make up for that
Well, thank you honey chain for your four dollars and thirty cents. He just said I should burn in hell
I didn't say that I saw it pop up in the chat and my
Fucking cat person brain decided just to say it my squirrel brain decided it was gonna say it. So I didn't say it
But thank you. Honey chain for the four dollars and thirty cents
Hey night fang. Thanks for one dollar. If you need help with Jojo poses watch this video
well
Jojo everyone just is already assuming the Jojo
I'm not gonna stop saying the word Jojo. I'm gonna start calling it like
I'm gonna start calling it Doki Doki
People so badly think that Doki Doki is gonna win
Not so sure still another day. Hey, Valukey. Thanks Valukey for the one dollar
Yo germ our DND session was Sunday and basically the Castle Griffin Steed arc takes 20 years after Carl went in
No one has heard from him ever since and Elvin Woods next champion is a brute named Trog
He yells his own name when he's hurt and runs into battle. We ended up going by the abandoned wagon
That was a big mistake and had to fight a giant rat deeper in the dungeon. We got to Al Goro
He was a real boss instead of a one-shot and Trog ended up dying because he ran in headfirst
Like he always does we'll keep you updated
Well, they gotta stay away from that wagon. Did you touch the wagon? That's probably what happened, but I'm glad your session went well
That sounds like a lot of fun
Thank You Valukey and
Docs and thanks to the one dollar boy. Oh boy
I just got robbed 12 times in a week and some asshole threw bricks through my window three times
I'm giving you this money. So maybe it'll be a good some good karma to make him go away
I heard from Paul that he was screaming about China and interrupted his midnight work twice
Who the fuck even is this guy golly good gracious? I sure do hope the wacky police stop him. Thank you and Docs and
Thank You thievious for the two bucks. This is for the upcoming grand reveal of your
Stand up power
Stando power during a green screen and he goes
Rye why
Rye
Wr. I don't get it. I don't understand. I'm sorry. I meant the elephant green screen. Anyway, look elephant
Elephant green screen. There's no elephant on there. I'm like I don't like it
$12,000 animal surprise for you guys. They're looking of right under like into the studio on an elephant
Thank you. The orange pyro ranger for the one dollar. I hope you're not too overwhelmed by the Jojo poses
You know, maybe I'll just veto the Jojo poses and put dab back on the list
Everyone's so convinced
Now I already I already made already did my veto choices can't go back on them
No, just as long as I don't have to do the gnome video. I
would rather
Like I would rather think get a bad burn
Then recreate the gnome video
But I would rather like fall off a bike
Going like 15 miles per hour then recreate the gnome video
just do that if I had the option you can either recreate the whole gnome video or
Hold the handlebars and let the wheels spin downhill and intentionally fall over on the bike
I'd be like, oh
Well, I thought be okay in a few days like it would probably take like maybe a week or two of recovery
That I had my bones would heal
But I would never be able to get rid of
People making me a gnome in the gnome video that would last forever. That would last for life
Bones heal man. Haha. Jeremy fell off a bike, but thank you. Thank you extra cheesy again for one dollar here
Jeremy you are the first person I ever gave virtual currency to is
Steal the China the new toy boat
Well, steal the China is not a tongue twister
Steal the China is a painting steal the China is what you
Chant when you're breaking into a person's house that has that painting. That's the only time it's useful
Thank you. Hey bro. Look, thanks for the five dollars. Hey mate feeling pretty hungry
But only had like ten bucks left in my bank account. Have it. Why would you give me half of that?
Go get like food
Hey mate feeling pretty hungry, but only had ten dollars left my bank account. Have it you have
You can eat go you can eat something don't
Take care of yourself first
But thank you
Devakati, thanks for the one dollar. They say you w you
glumps
Within there's two asterisks next to it. Thank you
Cosmic Moses, thanks for the one dollar. Thank you for attempting to reenact this scene for almost an hour
We're recreating this scene
It's funny. You mentioned that because me and my brother
That's from home alone
Me and my brother used to rewind the VHS and watch that part over and over again because it thought was the funniest part
in the whole movie
He just whips as hard as he can. It's the only time in any of the two movies
That there's ever a real violent retaliation
to Kevin McCallister who is you know, the main character the only point in the whole movie and
He's trying to hit him with a brick in the fucking head as hard as he can
He throws it down as hard as he can like he's trying to kill Kevin McCallister here
Like if that he would have just killed Kevin
That brick would have hit him right in the fucking face. They say they're gonna kill him the whole movie
Yeah, they go like
But never is there any real violent retaliation like there is here
If you haven't seen that movie in a long time count the amount of times that Joe Pesci Joe Pesci says razza frazza
Marv is the real psycho
Just like the cartoon gibberish that Yosemite Sam used to do
But yes that cosmic mosaic that that is that is a great scene
Well, hold on like all right. That's a that's a great movie. It's a very funny movie
That's a great scene
Never mind
Thank you to
Brolok again gave $10 total Brolok. What the heck man. I'd like to have a laid-back chat
But the obvious plyer no racism or bigotry don't talk about politics and just try not to be a psycho
Yeah, copy and paste that for the rules of the green screen stream. Those are the rules there
Garfield the Monday killer click here to find out with one dollar sniff sniff. That's odd. Okay, there is a savory dog smell
Sorry, I ever doubted you right?
Well, what I what you didn't know was that all dogs are actually eldritch horrors with hypnotic sense
Make humans succumb to their will anyways, where's my ten bucks? I
Hope he does the meme dances from tick-tock. I'm not doing any I'm not doing any meme dances
They've already been taken off the table completely
They've already been vetoed. They've been pre vetoed even before I pre vetoed them. They were deleted
I don't know what that is, but I'm not gonna not doing it and finally Elizabeth
Thank you for the one dollar suck a brick out of my ass
It sounds like it would be very very uncomfortable
Thank you for the one dollar though. And now we're gonna go through the credits
Let's see the
Bunch of people tonight that subbed and resubbed. It was a gifted subs to all of you are fucking incredible
Thank you. All of you if you don't know yes green screen is happening on Friday not Thursday one of more people to be able to participate
Tomorrow Delta rune or hitman one of those two things
Thursday Delta rune or hitman whatever we don't do on Wednesday will do on Thursday Friday green screen stream
Saturday nothing
Sunday nothing Monday. We're back. We'll see. Oh, maybe I'll maybe I'll stream on Sunday
Maybe we'll continue hitman on Sunday
German you're literally the last of my gaming channel subs that I consistently watch
That I'm glad you're here
I'm happy that you've been able to watch for this long. I can't keep up with all the vods. I know I've been streaming a lot
And these these friends have been going a long time, too
But I told you guys I
Came back I wasn't able to stream for three straight weeks, and I wanted to go
we've been doing a lot of seven eight nine hour streams the last couple weeks here and
I'm all for it. I'm having a great time
It's good to be back here on a scale of one to ten. How many apples have you eaten in the past two years?
Probably like 80. No, that's not even true. We'd be like two
No, no, no, no more than that. I'm gonna say like 15. No like 25
Ask about the dreamcast. I still have it. I still have the dreamcast. It'll have the PlayStation 2 back here
I make sure I made sure that they got to Vegas. So they're still here
Once the dust settles and all these brand new holiday releases. We will go back
We'll do a ton of dreamcast stuff. We'll finish the PlayStation 2 stuff
Because there's a lot
But we're in that mode right now where red dead hitman smash brothers
Delta rune, that's not enough. But let's say it was like a lot of games that are coming up
Am I gonna play Smash Brothers with fans? It is Nintendo's online policy
Hey, can you just jump into random lobbies or do you still need to give people like a 500-digit friend code?
Because I'll do whatever I can. I mean I was planning on playing it with as many people I wanted to
What are you guys doing? Why are you guys spelling quest?
But that is it. Thank you. There was a lot of subs
Thank you so much everybody for you continued
Monetary support of the channel. You guys are fucking amazing
We had two more. We had Tingy came in with a dollar. This is one more
It's this one. It's me on a bike. It's actually actually pretty relevant. So I'll give that one to you. That's pretty good and
Elizabeth thanks for the one dollar Vinnie talked about you landing in Vegas. Did you see this? Yeah. No, I saw that
He was cute. He was confused
Spent a little time in his dryer. We've talked about that, too
But yeah, that's it. I will see you guys
Roll up. Thank you for the one dollar. Good night. Good night to you, too
See you guys tomorrow. We'll figure it out pre stream in the chat what we're gonna do
See they're gonna be Delta rune or hitman. We'll see if you know, it could beat my people off. Who knows
See you tomorrow. Have a great rest of your night. Take care. Sleep well
Same time ish. Yeah starting from around the same time around probably
3 p.m. Pacific 2 to 3 p.m. Pacific is we're gonna try to start every stream. See you guys soon