That title sucks. I forgot to change the title. Hold on, one second. I'm drawing a blank.
The VOD is permanently titled this? I don't know. What should I make it? I'm drawing a blank.
Call it Saints Row Poo. That's worse than this one. I got my iced coffee. I'm ready to go.
Sorry about that. I had to take a phone call. The easiest fucking way to get out of anything.
What could that phone call be? Was that phone call important?
Was that phone call somebody you had to talk to? Immediately? You don't know. You have no idea.
No, I'm not. I'm fucking around. I've got my wasabi soy sauce. Almond here. Just in case I need a
snack. What's wrong? I'm fine. Soy sauce. I actually don't like soy sauce. Okay. Let's go over what's
going on today. In the next couple, maybe a couple weeks. So hold on. I gotta move stuff around. I
just was not fucking prepared at all. But like I said, I'm not like all these other streamers.
Okay. It's time for the defense here. You ready for the defense? I've said it a thousand times.
So when, when, when, when all the other streamers turn their streams on, they usually have like at
least 15 to 30 minute countdown before the stream actually starts. See, I get here. I just turn it
on and fucking I'm not even ready. You know, I am the countdown. This is the countdown right now.
It's me. I am such an egomaniac and I'm so full of myself that even when I'm not supposed to have
the stream on, I'm streaming here talking to you as the waiting room. All right, we're gonna play
Saints Row 2 today. I've never played any of the Saints Row games with a asterisk on it.
Aster and I played Saints Row 2 for like an hour or two hours or something. We got through the
character creator and then we just kind of stopped like an hour or two later. So I've never played
any of these all the way through or even halfway through or even a third of the way through.
I remember that video. Yeah, we also have a mod. I have the gentleman of the row mod installed,
which I guess fixes the whole game somehow. You're a fake fan. What do you mean?
Saints Row 2 is literally the best game ever. Okay, well, find out. I didn't even tweet this.
Give me one second. I hope everybody had a good Thanksgiving. Did you celebrate it? I did. I made
a 25 pound turkey because I wanted to make sure I had leftovers for two or three months
because I freeze essentially more than two-thirds of the entire bird.
What is that sound? What's going on? Am I getting played off the stage?
What's playing? What's playing me off the stage right now? What's going on? Oh,
shit. This is DMCA music. Hold on. Why? Hold on. Why was this not playing earlier?
This was not playing earlier. I've had Saints Row 2 open for 12 straight minutes. Audio, music,
volume. Should I turn music volume to zero? That's so boring though. Well, that's not boring.
That's how I live my life. All right, let me turn my fan down. It's going pretty hard here,
but something really important to know is... I didn't even know this is coming out this soon,
I guess. Monster Rancher 1 and 2 remake is out in less than two weeks. I hope you guys understand
that whatever you followed this channel for, whether it was for... Oh, I like when he does
like the big stream stuff. That's never happening ever again. Once Monster Rancher 1 and 2 comes out,
I'm only going to play that game. I will fill that category for the rest of the time I stream.
It's a lie, by the way. I have plenty of shit planned. It's based. Yeah, I know. All right.
No more fucking around. No more stalling. Let's go. Let me tweet. Saints Row 2. But honestly,
no, all jokes aside, I'm going to play that game a lot. I played it a lot when
we did the PlayStation 1 stuff, but I'm very curious how they're going to handle the CD thing.
I didn't... Did anybody know? What are they going to do? You know what I said, and unfortunately,
nobody listened to me. They have a built-in database. It should have been URLs. Somebody
steal that from me, please. Like, but give me 5% of all the revenue of every... of the whole project.
URLs would have been fucking hilarious, wouldn't it have? The link here.
Okay. All right. I'm ready. You're ready to sit in, like, for an hour in the character creator?
Because you know we're going to. Because part of this mod increases the body sliders by, like, 500%.
So, well, welcome to the stream. All right. I'm ready to go. Okay. Here we go. New game.
Is there a... There's probably a... I'm assuming there's probably a opening cutscene. I think there
is. All right. Hopefully this is not too loud. If it's not, let me know. If it is, then don't,
then don't tell me. Okay. Go. I'm not playing on hardcore. Why would you play, like, a GTA game
on hardcore? Oh, that was... That hurt my head. It's way too dank.
You know, I just found out what that was two days ago.
I know. I'll fix it in a minute.
Do you think it's going to kill the framerate?
I have the Gentleman of the Road mod, which can fix a lot of problems.
We can't even hear you.
Not yet. But I'm about to take the... I know my audio. I know. I'm... Okay. Every time I try to
fix my audio system, it fucks up. All right. Hold on. You understand? I always hear... I'm looking
over at my OBS right now, and I see the microphone. I see, like, the... the waveform, right? That,
right now, is bright fucking red. And if it goes any louder, it's gonna... So I don't understand how
to fix it. Everybody talks about how quiet I am, but according to my... my computer, it's fucking,
like, barely... If I talk any... If this goes any louder, it's gonna be like... It's gonna blow out
your ears. It's gonna peak. I don't get it. I don't understand why. I think it's this microphone. I
think this... this microphone is a really good mic. But I don't think it was ever designed to be
plugged in to, like, do what I'm doing. Clip that noise. Don't do that. Idiot. You idiot. Okay,
hold on. Let me turn the game down a little. This should be a bit of right there. Okay.
So, we have to figure out... What do I want to do with this? Okay. Uh, I'm gonna try to make me.
No, not exit. Holy shit, there's a... There's a dick. No, it's not. Oh my god. Right. Right. Okay.
We're fine. Okay. Hold on. So, the sliders have been increased by about two to three hundred percent.
This is current German. Yeah. All right. Wait a minute. How come it's giving me these... Okay.
Why the... Where's the button prompts? All right. Body shape. Okay. I feel... This is just... I feel
like I'm in a Ninja Turtle costume. I don't know why. Why am I seeing that? I don't get it.
Why did I just say that? How much age should we have? All right. I don't want to go too overboard
because we have to live with this for the whole rest of the entire time I played this game.
You just made E. Honda. Should we be jacked fat? No. I can't just put all the sliders to the right.
That's so easy. Oh no. I can't. This is the back of the head? I'm just gonna make, like, a fucking
banana split head. Tyler won. I can't. Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me. What you meant to say is...
You didn't mean to say Tyler won. What you meant to say was one of the greatest Twitch
interactive entertainers on the platform is what you meant to say. Make sure you get it right next
time. Oh my goodness. That's the... That's not my hair. That's my head. Where's the brain? I don't
know. I don't think it exists. This is the neck? Hold on. It looks like somebody's cutting down a
tree. It's on the trunk. I don't know if I like that. I'm gonna have to change that, I think.
All right. Should I make his head a serving platter? Like a gravy boat? Because that's
what's happening. I mean, it just was Thanksgiving. Oh my god. He's wearing a baseball bat. A baseball
hat of his own head. A baseball bat? He's wearing a baseball hat of his own head. I said that wrong,
but you know what I mean. Somebody can ride his head? How wide? Should be not that wide.
I like it like this. At least for now. I might have to go back and fix it, though.
This is just Peter Pettigrew. He's so mad. Well, now he is. I kind of like it like this.
This is a beer. Maybe it will reduce the weight. Maybe it will reduce the fatness.
Oh, I like that. It's scary. Big and bushy or small and scary, what do you think?
It's the guy that can survive the car crash. It is. What was that guy's name? It was... What was it?
What was that guy's name? It was the... It was the thing they made in the CG program that could
actually survive a car crash. It had like a gram. That's right. Hold on. Yeah, I can't alt-tab this
game because it breaks. Look up gram. Car crash. I like that. I think angry is better, though.
I want to see the eyes. I don't want to lose the eyes. Real tragedy. No, I'm not saying look...
I'm not saying look up this person that... Whatever. It actually is Peter Pettigrew now.
Well, it would make sense to make that person because I'm probably going to get a bunch of
car crashes. No, I didn't say look up car crash on Google. I said look up car crash gram. It's a
very specific thing to look up. All right, that's okay. Eyes. This is important. I can't.
He looks like he could survive. Hmm. Randomize. I don't want to randomize it. He has a part in his
hair. Yeah, the part is a little bit further back on his skull. That's so weird. Okay, we'll keep
that. No, we won't. How about this? No. Really deep eyes. I have eyes like this. I kind of like it.
Not that low, though. I want to be able to see all those features. I do? Yeah, I have really deep
set eyes. They go really far back. Yeah, my eyes are so far back set into my head that they're
kind of close to my brain. So if I kind of push in my eyes very gently, like the last episode of
SpongeBob plays, it's just like... Like weird shit happens. Like I'm pushing on like the frontal lobe
of my brain when I do it. Like, okay, I'm going to do it. Someone was just speaking French. There
was a guy just speaking French holding like a big dinner plate. He was like serving it. I don't know.
Let me work on my guy, please. This is what you look like. Why do you... You don't think I know
that? Oh, boy. No, I want to see the eyes. Maybe not that big. Like this. Even anime eyes. Yeah.
Stop being rude. Oh, you're talking about other people, not me. Okay, ears. Should you just not
have ears? Maybe you just shouldn't have them. All right, those ears are where a fish's ears are.
No, that's where a bird's ears are. That's fine. I like it. Ears are cringe anyways. Get rid of them.
What? That's fine. No, that's all right. Like that. Ear openness. That's weird. Ear roll?
No, I don't want to mess with the ears too much because mess with the hair. Just really huge lobes.
No. An elf. Make him an elven. I kind of like the elven. Maybe not that extreme. It's a wood elf.
Okay. Cheekbones. Maybe not that much. How about temple depth? What is that doing? Temple height.
I like it higher. That's not bad. No, no, no, no. It's definitely going to be over here somewhere
like here. Cheekbone depth. No, way too. Put them in. That's not bad. Maybe a little bit out. That's
fine. Eye cheekbones are low. That's all right. Why does he look like Cartman? It does look like
Eric Cartman. Yeah, just wait for when South Park does all grown up like the Rugrats did. And this
is what they're going to get. They just did that. They did? Oh, shit. I did not know that. They're
literally doing that right now. They just did that. They did that literally, literally in the
new special. Does he look like this? I don't want these to be that. No, no, no. Pull these back.
That's like way too comical. You know what I mean? Like, oh, that's so funny. No, no, no. That's
too comical. It needs to be a little bit dialed back here. The chin is messed up too. That's got
to get fixed. Nose. Big or small nose? Probably small. We want the other features in the face to
really, really pop. Yeah, small. No, no, no. Not big. He has extra nostrils. No, that's too comical.
I think like right, right where it was is good. I like that. All right. Now imagine if I could take
this guy into Dark Souls. That would be great. I feel like that's what I'm doing. Put it up high?
No, no, no, no. Not high. It looks like the imprint of somebody's shoe is on the front of his face.
Like this guy had a normal face and then like in a Tom and Jerry cartoon, somebody with a boot came
and kicked him in the face as hard as they could. That's the imprint of a shoe from the forehead to
the chin. We don't got to get too finicky with the nose. Looks like Trump. It looks like a Trump
caricature. No, I don't like what that just did. No, I don't like what that did either. Right here
in the middle. Keep it in the middle. His nose is way too pushed in to have any of these other
settings mean anything at all. All right, that's fine. Mouth. He just doesn't have any teeth.
He just have no teeth. I like it. That's okay. It's his grandma. It's like an open mouth. Not that.
No, no, no. Not like this. Like this. Just the two lips. That's okay. A little bit lower down is fine.
That's right. It's just a fish. I feel like I didn't touch anything but I feel like they're
having trouble standing. Are they like swaying and moving weirdly to anybody else? I feel like
they're having trouble here. I didn't have- were they doing this the whole time? I don't think so.
Okay, that's fine. Oh wait, they're not supposed to have teeth. This is the- I don't have teeth
mouth but they're showing teeth. That doesn't make any sense anymore. Hey! Over the other way.
Oh no. This is slowly becoming a sus image, isn't it? No, it's got to be like that. Pissed.
With a big underbite. All right, this is fucked up because I feel like this person, if they- if
like their boogers just go right into their mouth, that's fucked up. If this person's asleep on the
train and they have a runny nose, they're just pooling the runny nose directly into their mouth.
Okay, I think that's fine. Is that- maybe not that extreme? Maybe. That's too extreme, you think?
That's fine. Like that. Oh, I don't want to look at that for the next like six hours. No, like this.
I don't hate that. This is hard to look at. Yeah, I- that's why I don't want it to be that extreme
because we have to look at this for a long time. We have to look at this for a while. Double chin?
There- I mean, there is no double chin. There's one single bullfrog chin. It's not double. We've-
we're past the point where there's a double. All right, almost done. Should we just make
him a beanbag chair? I don't know. Jaw height? Oh, he can pull it up. Yeah, but his- his head,
his chin is going into his body. Leave the poor- leave this poor man alone. Is that too much?
Because it's- I don't know. I feel like that's too much. We made Patrick Star
unavailable. All right, hold on. What about the hair? Wait, hold on. Oh no. It can't be Patrick Star
though. That's not gonna- it's gonna be- that's funny for right now. You think it's funny right
now. Let's make him Grimace instead. I like Grimace better than Patrick Star. It's Majin
Boo. I know, but we all think this is like funny for like the next 10 minutes. After- after he's
purple Grimace for four hours, I don't- I don't think we're gonna think it's funny anymore. It's
like a one- it's a one minute joke. It's funny right now. Like Mr. Greens? No, they can't keep
Grimace. Oh, okay. Fine. I'll keep it as Grimace. I like Grimace the most out of all of these.
But he- I- it's gonna be so distracting. If it's Grimace, he has to lose the hair. Hold on. I am
not committing yet. Facial hair? No. Okay, here we go. First Lady? That's just on- on this guy.
It's Elvis. I don't think. Half of these just look like coral reefs on him. They're so all- look at
this. This looks like a coral reef. This doesn't even look like hair. This looks like underwater
sea creature. Okay, if- like if- okay, if I showed you this image right here, and I told you- and I
asked you, what is this? What is this image? I don't- what would you say? You'd probably say
some deep sea thing. Okay, I think we found it. This is a sea cucumber. This is a cabbage? It
actually kind of does look like cabbage, you're right. There's so many. This one's good. But if
we have- if we're gonna commit to Grimace, it can't- Grimace doesn't have hair. I mean, technically
Grimace is covered in hair. There's so many options. Wait, we- let's go back to the top.
We started in the middle. He looks like a geode. I mean, this is the easy one if it's Grimace,
but it can't be. I'm going back. He's not gonna be Grimace. Beehive? Oh, oh, oh, okay.
I like this one. I like this one. We're keeping this one. None of the facial hair is gonna show
up. No, no facial hair. Oh, I feel like he's about to start singing the Smash Mouth song. Yeah,
like, right now. No, no facial hair. Sideburns? I actually like that. Yep. It's Elvis. It's Elvis.
It's Elvis. It's Elvis. It's Elvis. It's Elvis. I made- I'm done. It's gonna be Elvis. Austin
Powers? Okay, hold on. Evil scientist. I'll take full. All right, hold on. I need- I gotta get this
right. Let me see what it looks like when he's not purple Grimace. We'll fix the hair. It's just fat
bastard from Austin Powers. Fuck, it has to be Grimace now. But that's- no, I can't do just- look,
he's purple. I don't want it to be purple. No, no. We're going back. I'll get sick of the Grimace
joke in 20 minutes. I'm gonna fix this. I actually don't hate this. I don't hate this. Wait,
why does he have, like, a purple fade? Why does he have a- is there purple, like, highlights?
Oh, it's because the secondary color. No, this doesn't look like- oh my god, this does not-
somebody said this looks like Adam Driver. What are you talking about? How do you see Adam Driver?
Adam Driver is like a handsome, like, dashing man. What are you talking about?
Oh, I don't see it. I don't. I like this though because we're gonna keep it like this. I think
it's perfect. That's not Adam Driver. It's not at all. I don't even know where you're getting
that from. I don't know how so many people are- I don't know how many- so many people are agreeing
with you. So many people are saying Jay Leno, Dan Schneider. No, this is not Gabe Newell, Orson Welles.
Okay, this is- everyone has- all right, let's keep this for now, I think. I need to keep this.
All right, I think we're gonna- British accent?
Keep making British.
It's Snape. It is Snape. I like Snape the best. Oh, what the fuck?
Everybody stop talking. All right, we have, like, the soy face. I'm just gonna put this
on top of me reviewing, like, the new PS5 controller. These are all just thumbnail faces.
See, what you guys don't know is most YouTubers just sit there in front of their webcam and go
like this in about maybe two to three minutes, and that's what they've been using on every thumbnail
for the last five to ten straight fucking years. They've never edited them. They've never updated
them. Are you re- can I really be, you know, inclined to think that you're, like, very,
very scared of something? If that's an image that you were scared- is this the same,
I was scared of this game or this movie or this TV show or this thing, like, seven years ago?
How do I know that you're scared? You may have been scared when you made this, but not- you're
just pasting it on everything else. Oh, no, no, no, sorry, that's not accurate. They don't have the
looking up towards the ceiling with your eyes with your finger on your chin thinking about something.
Isn't that interesting? They forgot that one. I think blank is the best. This is taking shots.
No, no, I'm not- who- okay, taking shots. I'm the guy that's standing outside screaming. Like,
okay, you know when you go to, like, a convention where you go to something and there's, like,
a person that's, like, screaming about God outside? It's just like, what's the- what's the- who's this
person? Like, I am that person. Everybody else is looking at me like, what the fuck are you talking
about, dude? Everybody does this shit. Do Dopey, please. Fine. Oh, nice. Okay. Oh, this- I love the-
this one's really bouncy. This one's very bouncy. What was that? I think we may have found it.
Not quite, though. Zombie? He looks like a big baby. This is a big baby. I don't like this at all.
I have to move on now. Oh! Gangsta lean. O2 tank pull? Wasted? Slow and steady. Oh, yeah. Yep. I
don't need to see anymore. No, I don't have to see any other ones at all. Read the news. Carry books?
Carry clipboard? Metal detector? Do you actually walk around like this? Out shopping? Keeping dry?
Or laundry day? Um, I- I think we- it has to be this one. Or this one. No, no. This- I like-
I'm not gonna- do I move- how do I do this? Okay. No, I like this one. This one's better. You do
understand that there's so much opportunity for, like, me to make, like, a- like, a laugh-out-loud
joke where there's, like, a car coming and I do this into the road and get hit? Are you serious?
You don't think I'm gonna pick this one? This is the easy one. Combat style. There's only one.
Compliment? Slow kisses? Oh! Guitar? There's no music.
Photo? Oh, I see, okay.
This one's probably-
Okay. Um. Oh, the harmonica. The jig is good too. Okay, I guess we're gonna use the harmonica.
Yeah, blues is more dynamic. Haunt. Okay, what do we got? Bring the voodoo. Test bump. Come get some.
Eat takeout. I mean, this one works for this character, but eat the dead? Oh!
What, I can eat them on the ground?
I like this one a lot, but I don't- I don't think it fits.
Sword? Oh! Wait, it doesn't actually wrap?
Nope. Nope. Wait, that was Harry Potter. That's Voldemort.
That's a pretty good Voldemort scream. Just smoking? Is that a cigarette? Okay, it's a cigarette.
How about the wanker? Oh, okay. What the fuck? Oh! Look at the belly button.
What? It either has to be vomit or- or the fire breather.
No, I'm not gonna do the default taunt from GTA Online, please. I think we're ready. Okay,
we did everything right. Let me make sure this is right, okay. Body. I don't think anything else
needs to happen. All right. Are you guys ready to play the game? I am. Eat takeout. I don't even
know how to do any of these things. Time to go. Wait. No, okay, no, no. Yeah. Three, two, one, go.
That looks like it healed nicely. Be careful, doctor. This patient's dangerous. You got anything
you want to say to the judge? You better start thinking of it now. You're wasting your time.
Let's get ahold of Troy. Oh my god. Hey, is it really you? This is why I couldn't be Patrick.
My brother was in the Saints and he told me all about you. Listen, we gotta get you out of here.
Well, I'm sure if we ask nicely. I know a way out. Yeah? Then why are you still- I feel like
I'm watching Gumball. Like these two are from different animation styles and different complete
art styles. You really expect me to trust some guy I don't even know? Come on. I just got myself
shanked so I could get a chance to talk to you. Doesn't that show I'm loyal? It shows that you're
dumb enough to let yourself get stabbed. I'm trying to help you. You know what I got the last time I
trusted someone? Blown the fuck up. You need me. The hell I do. I got the Saints. Sure you do.
What's that supposed to mean? How long do you think you've been out? I don't know,
mate. Two to three weeks. Look, I know you think you're a badass, but do you even know where you're
at? Without me, you'll be wandering around the prison for hours. Even if you manage to hide from
the guards that long, and if you actually figure out how to make it outside these walls, you're
just gonna find out that you're sitting on a goddamn- Why does the voice fit him? I'm pretty
sure- It does. I don't know. It just does. You got a boat stashed here? No, but- I think that's by
design. All right, let's get out of here. Those little shoes. What? Why am I, um, why am I floating?
Okay, um, punch and block. Hold will- Okay, that's not correct. Three successful strikes will
devastate a combo. Alternate- Okay, I need to find out what that is. Okay, that's jump. Okay,
right trigger is punch. Left trigger is another kind of punch. Wait, what did I just do? I have
to kill the doctor first. Okay, play the tutorial, sure. Ow. All right, well, what's block? Okay,
holding- You can hold the button down, but what's block? There was a block. All right, that's like
my right bumper. E is kick door, but that's not what it is. Okay, it's, it's, uh, why?
Let's go! Punch, punch, punch! Holy shit. Get her! Get the fuck out of my way! Use R? What was R?
Oh, the weapon wheel. Okay. All right. I thought the mod, um, gave Xbox 360 controls. Maybe not
here. I know there's a sprint. What is it? All right, crouch. Okay, it's push in. What's sprint?
Left bumper? Right bumper? Okay, nice. Thank you. Thank you. This is your mini map. Uh, markers and
GPS navigation lines here will guide you to objectives. Set GPS waypoints. Okay, this is,
there's a map. Of course, there's a pause menu, right? Ooh, this is huge. Holy shit. Okay, let's
go. Kill the guard and take their gun. Is there a sneak? Okay, not really. Did they get the gun?
Okay, running over weapons you don't have automatically picks them up. Change your weapon,
press and hold Q. That don't need, that's easy. I already have that. Okay, melee bash or fire gun?
Okay, good. Good to know. All right, let's go. Oh my god, that was horrible. Was I not supposed to
do that? Was I not supposed to do that? I don't know. Why would I kick him like in the balls?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Wait, that's a new, that's a new gun. Use R. Don't shoot me. What? Oh,
wait. Dual wield? Can I? Is it Y? Oh shit. Oh well, it's okay. I'll figure it out. Oh, fuck.
We just gotta run. We just gotta get out of here. Okay, wait, wait, wait. Does it do, can you do
weld? I don't think you can do weld. R to do a weld. Yeah, but it's using the, it's not giving
me controller props. Fine aim is V, which is, I'm assuming it's probably, let's see. Okay, fine aim
is right on the stick. What the fuck? Why did, why would it explode? I might, okay. All right,
let's get to the dock. Sprint, yep. Thanks to Chad, I know how to do that. Oh, let's get to the docks.
How do you drive? Oh, fuck. It's, wait, it's A? It's A and that's, I think I have to change this.
I have to change this. Get out. I remember this happening. That's how Saint Root, Saint,
Saint's Row 2 works on console. Oh, fuck. Okay. Defend the boat. From what? Does this thing overheat?
Helicopter? I got it. Two pistol shots makes it smoke and explode, but I can't take this out
for the life of me. Oh, wait, I got to reload. Podler aim? It's hard on a controller. Give me a
break. Where's the music? I turned the music off because people said there was DMCA. Okay,
that's good. All right. There's nobody, what do you mean don't let them catch us? There's nobody here.
Oh, it's the helicopter. Okay. Well, I can't. Oh my God. I got it. Just put on Christmas music.
That's a really actually brilliant idea. Just put on like a royalty-free Christmas music playlist.
Jesus, when did this happen?
A very Kevin McLeod Christmas. Ludwig's Christmas album. Oh yeah.
I keep forgetting it looks like this.
Cops are looking for you and a lot's changed. I say you just go buy a beer and soak up as
much information as you can. Thanks Carlos. For a second, I thought he said go grow a beard and like
lay low. Like I'm not the most distinct looking person in the entire city. I could, guys, I could
grow a beard. I could wear like eight different like clothes. I could put five hats on. It doesn't
matter. 500 bucks. Save the game. Yeah. So games, I've heard do not even with the gentleman of the
row mod that it doesn't matter. Save every time you have an opportunity. Save game. Okay.
So how do I like, what am I trying to do here? All right. Pick up boxes. This is not like Donkey
Kong. What am I talking about? Wait, what's in here? Third Street Saints mission. Johnny
Bravo really let himself go. Okay. I need some new clothes. Why is everybody mad at me? Oh,
these are police. But wait, I need to get out of here. Wait, I can pick up the trash can. What?
How do I pick this up? No, fuck. I didn't want to do that. How do I pick it up? What's wrong with me?
Taunts? Is it, it's B? It's not B. I just took a shotgun out. It's not B. How do I pick up the
trash can? It's R? It's not. It's not. Don't hit that person. What are you doing? Leave me alone.
I'm not even trying to hurt you. Get away from me, please. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get
away from me. Get away from me. Wait, did you just bump? Leave me alone. I'm just hold A? Oh,
my God. Please leave me alone. They're going to start swarming me. Oh, my God. This lady is
relentless. I didn't. Okay. Where do I need to go? This way. You're not still following me, right?
No. All right. Good. Pick up trash can. Somebody said hold A. Okay. It is hold A. Oh, my God. That
guy. Go buy a lottery ticket. What the fuck? Imagine throwing a trash can at somebody. What
the fuck is happening right now? Oh, fuck. Okay. I'm going to go. I need a car. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. I should have done that. Give me that. Get on the bike and go. Go. Get on the bike. What
is she holding? What is that? Was that a drill? She's got a fucking power drill. Oh, she's drilling
that. Wait a minute. What? Oh, fuck. I didn't. Who are these people? Get away from me. Okay.
Hold on. I didn't stop. I have to stop. Wait a minute. Okay. I'm fine. I'm okay. If I let myself
go too hard there, I'm going to get hurt. I need to slow down. Oh, wait. I'm still holding a gun.
Put that away. Don't do stupid fucking tricks, you idiot. Just get to the thing. Okay. Buy clothes.
What? Clothing stores allow you to customize your character. By buying clothes, you can increase
your style rank. Oh, it's because I have a gun out. Okay. Purchase some clothes. We can get hats.
None of these are going to look right at all. This really is a bicycle seat.
Should I get the bicycle seat? I'm going to get this. No, no. Hold on. You can do different styles?
Arts. It's the Joker. Make him the Joker? Are those cops after me? I hear sirens. It's a shower cap.
Yeah, I don't want this. Actually, I'd rather have this. Okay. Oh, goodness. How much is this?
Okay. How about the... Keep the basic tee on for now. The tank top. Are you sure you don't want me
to have the bathing suit? The onesie bathing suit? Okay. What about... I don't want anything
underneath because I want it to be a bathing suit. Is there none? I guess I could do the jean shorts.
I have to be honest. There's no way that foot's coming out of that shoe ever again. Those
essentially have been surgically put on. They're not coming out. Roller skates? No way. Can I roller
skate around? Keep in the socks. Definitely. I want these. I just want tighty-whities on.
Okay. That was good. Should I have arm pads? No, no. Outfits? No. Okay. What else? Viscillaneous one?
No. A tool belt? Yes. Look at that hammer. Absolutely. I want the tool belt. I'm ready.
Okay. Switch to wardrobe. How do I switch to wardrobe? What space? No. What did I just buy?
Did I just buy the tool belt twice? What happened? No. What? Space is space. Okay. Well,
whatever. Why can I do that? Can I take the cash? Is there money in here? Oh my god. That lady. Is
there money in here? How do I get the money out? Why can I leave? Am I too big to leave the store?
How do I get? How do I? I want the money in this thing. Is there money? I already got it. Oh,
I got it. I got it. Yeah, I am in roller skates, but I'm not skating. Oh, damn it. That was so
close to hitting that guy in the head with trash. Save, save, save, save, save, save, save, save.
I need a car. Wrong button. I wish I could skate around. All right. What's reverse? Give me a break.
What the fuck? No. Get. Get. Leave me alone. Please. I thought that I just got struck by
lightning. I thought that was lightning that just hit right there. Leave me alone. You stole his car.
Is there a handbrake? What's the handbrake? Christmas music. All right. All right. All
on. All to having is going to be a disaster. I got to be careful. Let me save it right here.
Don't forget about Christmas music. I know I'm getting it. I hope it doesn't crash.
Will crash. It might. We'll find out. All right. Chris. Should I put on Ludwig's music? How many
songs did he do? Oh shit. He's got like a shitload of songs. No music. I'm putting it on. It's going
to be just low in the background. Pretty relaxed. Okay. Did it crash? I could do my own rendition
too, if you want. You can't even hear the music. It's drawn up by fucking rain. Hold on. This.
It actually works really well. I think this Christmas sucks. It's scary out here.
I have to pause it for this. I have to pause it.
Okay. I can't turn it off. I can't alt tab. Hey, Barry, turn this shit off. I can't.
Christmas is ruined.
Wait, what? Who's that? Oh, I don't know who that was. Why did I just do that?
No, how do I have to fight? Why are these people here? Is somebody up on the roof?
Where is this person? I don't know where this person is. I missed that whole cut scene. I was
laughing at the Christmas music. How do I get out of here? How do I get out of here?
Do I have to fight these people? They're on the mini-map. Are you on the mini-map?
I don't know. Are you on the mini-map? I think she's on the mini-map. Are you on the mini-map?
Are these people on the mini-map? I gotta get out of here. Let's get out of here. Who is this?
What are you doing? What are you gonna spray with? Pepper spray? A spray can? I don't even...
Just wait. Hold on. I don't want to shoot you, but I'm gonna...
All right. You're fucking dead, buddy. I'm sick of this shit. Get the fuck out of here. Get out of
here. Get off. Get off. I'm getting lightheaded now. Okay. Let's go to the... We only have three
minutes? What? The court. I gotta get to the courthouse. Who's behind me? Give me this car.
I gotta get to the courthouse in three minutes. Go. All right. This is good. Can we just take a
second to understand? This is good music. They did a fucking fantastic job. All right. Go.
I'm at the court. What am I doing here? Why am I here? Find the courtroom? What?
I don't know where this person is. I wasn't even listening. I wasn't paying any attention.
What room are they in? Which door is it? Oh, I need a break.
It's the most wonderful time of the year. With the kids jingle belling and everyone telling
you be of good cheer. What am I doing here? Mr. Gatt, you've been convicted of over 300 murders.
Do you really expect this appeal to work? I figured with the statute of limitations,
it really should be closer to two feet. There's no statute of limitations for murder.
Oh, fuck. Hold on. I gotta pause it. Jesus. I need a break. My fucking head's gonna explode.
Fuck just happened. Who is this? Is that me? What am I doing here?
Oh, I'm breaking him out. All right. Let's go. So I'm breaking out this criminal.
How do we leave? No, I'm gonna put the music back on. I promise. I need a break. My whole
fucking body hurts. Let's just fucking run. Who cares? I can't jump over that. Go, go,
go, go, go, go. Was this the judge? What the judge? It's a shotgun. All right. Get a soda.
Can I buy a soda? All right. Ready? Go. Oh my God. You guys cannot hit anything.
Fucking storm troopers. Oh, fuck. Don't talk shit. Hold on. Okay. Go. Go. Oh my God. Get us out. Get
us out. Get us out. Get us out. Get us out. Get us out. Get us out. Okay. That really just worked.
Yeah, it did. Oh, wait. No. No, no, no, no. I thought you were the guy. Where's the guy?
Where's the guy? Oh shit. Oh no. He's fucked. Oh no.
Get out of the way, please. How do I revive him?
Oh shit. Where am I? No. Damn it. Fuck. I thought he was going to get in the car.
I thought he was going to get in the car. Oh no. Did I crash? All right. All right. I got to focus.
Get away. Hold on. I just want to stop doing like modal combat moves. What do you mean abandon?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Where are you? What are you doing? What are you doing?
Okay. All right. Get up. All right. I got to remember what E is. Okay. E is triangle.
You good? Let's move. I didn't know he was going to get stuck back there.
Just run. Just run. Just run. Run. Run. Just run through. Run. Let's go. I'm not messing with
the judge with the shotgun. It's not going to happen. All right. Don't get stuck in the door
this time. I'm dual welding? I'm not. I am not dual welding. Okay. Here we go. Leave.
Somebody just said pacifist run. What? What? I just like I've killed like fifth. What are you
talking about? Let's go. Get out. Get in.
Troop behind us. Somebody behind us.
How do I shoot the gun? Wait till they get out. That's the strategy. Wait till they get out of
the car. That was uncalled for. Why did he do that? That was not what I did it for.
Forgive and forget allows you to remove all notoriety for a price.
I'm in a cop car. I'm still a cop car. Put the music back on. All right. Hold on.
What happened? Holy shit. What the fuck is going on here? Oh no. Oh no. Have you noticed that my
voice has been like, I don't know, I've turned into like an old library, like an old librarian
when I laugh. It's like, oh no. Oh my goodness. When did I become the librarian in the cinnamon
toast crunch commercial that gets mad at how loud the crunching is? I may have just made that
commercial, but I don't think I did. So that's a commercial, right? That's like, it's so crunchy.
Why did we do? What was that for? All right. You're good. 500 bucks. Oh, I have a red light
apartment crib now. Cool. This is your respect meter. Respect this game by completing activities
and diversions. Once you have enough respect, you can play missions. Oh, okay. It's like experience.
All right. Go to the previous map to view activity locations. Okay. You can set a waypoint
on the map. Okay. Very cool. Set a waypoint for an activity now. All right. So these are
just activities, vehicle dealer, unknown activity. Well, I feel like it has to be in this zone here,
right? It doesn't matter. All right. We're going to go here. Activity. This is my truck. It's not
your truck. Okay. Well, this is probably my bike. She's sitting on this. You're going to get on,
but she acts like she's going to get on. Okay. Save. Yep. All right. Let's get that music back
on. You thought I was going to run them all over, didn't you? Nope. All the rules. We're
listening to Christmas music. Oh, fuck the rules. Who cares? What's on that truck? Whoa.
I had to hold that to the end of the song. You know I did. Fuzz.
Don't turn it off. I'm keeping it on.
It's too loud. There. No, it's not.
Let's go wait. Impersonate one of Stillwater's finest and provide quality footage of the Fuzz
crew for cash and respect. Oh, shit. Wait, they have to catch the streaker? That's the
streaker right there. That's the streaker right there. What? We just killed him. That person's
streaking right now. Wait, are there more than one streaker? Why is it more than one person? What?
What? Oh, wait. That person. How is that person not naked? I need more footage. Why do we need
more footage? Get away from me. I'm trying to film something. I don't have enough footage.
How is this not footage? It's just zoomed in like. Wait, why is there a cop in the car?
Why did they get in the car?
Fucking turn the record button on. Turn the record button on. What are you doing?
Oh, apprehend. How do I apprehend him? What do you grab him? All right, get him. Don't kill him.
Apprehend him. What are you doing? What? How do we apprehend him? He's. What?
I get it. There's more. OK, there's more than one. Stop the lewd pedestrians.
I'll get it. I get it. I still have a minute. I first came out the window.
Have they been stopped? I don't understand what stops them. Don't run away. Get out of the way.
OK, wait, he already has enough camera footage of you running over perps.
Oh, god damn it. Really? I feel like that's what you guys say.
A chat sick of you like running people over and falling off ledges. Do something else, streamer.
Squid Game. Hit him. We did it. Don't give me a minus two for that. You all fucking love that show.
Oh, it's more level two. Oh, god. Do I have to do it again? I don't know. This is just an activity.
OK, I'll try it one more time. That's in the script. You can quit at any time. Yeah, I'll do
one more. How do I fly off the top of the screen? I don't know what that was. Was that him? Holy shit.
Oh, my god. Get out of my way. Oh, my please. I'm done. I'm not doing this anymore.
Activities. Turn it off. What is this? No. Turn it off. Activities. Can I turn it off?
Oh, down on the D-pad. Cool. OK, that's cool. No, don't. I just hit retry. Oh, my god. No,
get out of here. I wanted to exit it and not be like, oh, retry. Press A.
Meet me at Aisha's place. We got to figure out our next move.
What do I do? Where's the walker? There it is. Boomer. All right, the album's almost over,
so I got to make the best use of it. Come on. What the fuck?
I don't care about the presents under Christmas tree. I don't need to hang my stockings
Fuck you. Santa Claus won't make me happy. The toy on Christmas day.
Fuck all of you. Hit me already. Whatever. In the crosswalk. I'll turn it off. Ow, my eyes.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Perfect.
As for much this Christmas, I won't even wish for snow.
I'm just gonna keep on waiting underneath the mistletoe. I will make a list and send it
to the North Pole for Saint Nick. I will stay awake to hear those magic reindeer
Because I just want you here tonight, holding so tight. No! Christmas is over.
What the fuck? All the lights are shining so brightly everywhere.
The sound of children's laughter fills the air. Those sleigh bells ringing.
No!
It's not gonna happen. I'm trying to scare people. Oh, whatever. I'm done. We'll just go.
Just do it on the highway instead. Yeah, I know. Good idea. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh my god, fucking hit me already. You're ruining the whole joke.
Oh my god, dude, please. Wait, this one's not royalty-free.
What's this over here? What is that? This is a doctor's office?
Uh, what are you talking about? Can I buy stuff? You thought Ludwig's album was...
Holy goodness. Okay, let me try that again. Three, two, one.
You thought Ludwig's album was royalty-free? Omega-lul.
I want that. The person has a sword. I want it. Wait, I can't take the sword?
Oh, this is a costume. Hey, how do you pull the camera back when you're in the car?
I know this is the way to do it, right? Select? I want to go get a hamburger.
It's B? It's not B. Humper? It's not Y. Y's jump out.
Cruise control? Let's look behind. It's V. Not V. L3? Yeah. R2 and Y?
What the fuck? What the hell's going on? Is this a gang?
How would you ever bring a knife to a gunfight? Oh, hell yeah. Oh shit.
Oh my god, what happened? What just happened? Um, how do I pick up weapons? R? What's R on the...
I don't remember. R. I don't think I ever figured that out. Hold A. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
All right, just give me one of your motorcycles.
I'm just trying to go get a hamburger for god's sakes. Please don't. What? Are you kidding me?
Why can I do this? Enable the controller buttons in the settings? Is that in the options? Gamepad
controls? I think that's a mod thing. It should be enabled. I don't know why it's not enabled.
Graphics quality? Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, I don't think it's here. It should be just part of the mod.
Enable display. It's not in display. It's in audio. All right.
Yeah, it's in the mod configuration. I thought it was already there. It's okay. I'll be fine.
Fucking idiot. Save game. Yep. There it is. Can I not go in? Will you people leave me alone?
Leave me the fuck alone! Get out of here! I'm just trying to get food. What is that car?
It's like a transformer. It's too late? Oh, what time? Okay, what time is it?
Uh, this guy is still in the car. Why are they on my ass so bad? I want to get a hamburger.
Is there a drive-through? Look at the minimap. Oh, drive-through. It's a mission marker? Oh my
God. Hold on. I'm not ready yet. I'm just looking at your menu. You guys served breakfast this late?
Oh shit! Why are people swarming me? Leave me alone. Oh, what's this? This game is really fun.
It's very fun. There's too much to do. Okay, let's do a race. Three, two, one.
Oh, this is not accurate. Everybody crashes into each other in the first one second and only one
person's left doing the race. Oh, yeah. Are you fucking kidding me? I didn't know you had to
touch it. I'll make it up. I'll make the time up. Don't worry. Just what? What's handbrake on
controller? Somebody tell me. What is it? Is it Y? It's not Y. It's not B either. Is it B?
It's not B. You fucking liars. What is it? R1? I told you I could make the time up. It's not R1
either. I just turned on cruise control. Okay, left trigger. Thank you. Where's the person in
first place? Come on. There they are. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Crash into somebody.
Crash, crash, crash, crash, crash. Come on. Hit something. Hit anything. Hit somebody.
I had this too. Y is boost. Oh, really? That's pretty cool. Nice. Y is boost. That's cool.
That's a silver. I got the silver. Whatever. All right. Let's actually do a mission now.
What's this? There's a store. Oh, no. I want to see the store. That's pretty sick. I jumped over.
What store is it? What? Well, I got a bike. Oh, it's the doctor. Take that limo. No, I don't want
it. Can I fly with this? Does it push me up? No. Oh, well. All right. It's time to do a mission.
I've been doing nothing for like an hour and a half. No. Yeah. Okay. Here we go. Mission. Go.
I look like I'm asleep. I look like I was asleep. What the fuck is happening? What? Why is it on
fire? Oh, my fucking God. Let's go. How come this isn't on my minimap right now? Waypoint. There we
go. Quick before it explodes. Quick before it explodes. Map can be buggy in this game. Heads up.
Okay. Good to know. I just dove. He wasn't even paying attention either. Can I go in the restaurant
during operating hours? I need to find out. I'm very curious. Can I actually go in here or is it
only a drive-through? Oh, well. It's only drive-through. Oh, your voice makes my balls
ache. I don't I that could be I don't know what that even means. That could go in a bunch of
directions. What is that? Is that like liquor? What's this? Alcohol or something? Like drinks?
What is this? It's a pet store? Liquor store? Where's the entrance? When he said, yo, where's
the music? Can't do music. Wait, can I buy a car? Purchase more expensive vehicles at vehicle
dealerships. What a weird way to get off the bike. Oh, oh, come on. 15,000. Oh, compensator. Cool. Can
I hit this guy with the car? 70,000. I think there's extra cars in the mod. Are these extra?
The mod apparently adds a bunch of cards. Very cool. That's cool. What mod is this? This is
gentleman of the row. That's at a different shop. You just call me scrub? No, not worth it. What?
Let's do it. I'm like a melted action figure. You want a beer? Yeah, that'd be great. Juggles
the great. Yo, come to the living room. Don't do that. A bottle opener is like $1.50. You're
going to get hurt. You're going to break it. It's going to cut you. Don't do that. Don't be an idiot.
Or that you're talking. You're going to fuck up your table. We all thought you were dead.
I almost was. Well, for someone who was blown to hell, you look great. Did you do something
with your hair? Yeah, I've been getting that a lot. Yo, can we give it back to business?
What's the rush? I've been cooped up on death row and that bitch has been laid out in a coma.
We definitely need to remind motherfuckers who we are. And that can't wait until after dinner?
No. You two haven't changed at all. Well, you know, there's a saying about dogs and blowing shit up.
So what's the plan? We get our crew together. Once we got that, we can work on our taking back our
city. Sounds good. And where were you planning on having this little meeting? Right here. No.
Well, this place is pretty spacious. No. The color is very soothing. No. Come on,
this ain't no fucking gang clubhouse. Change of plans. We got to find a new place. Yeah.
He sounds like the Geico gecko. See what we do here is what I talk about. It's a commercial.
It's not a commercial though. I'm a real person. I'm treated like a real guy. Geico. I'm a real guy.
I'm not a fucking fake lizard. Did you know that I was me that came up with the idea?
Geico said 15% of all car insurance. I was me a lizard. I'm not real. Even though they treat me
like I'm a real person talking to a camera. Like it's like the ad people are there in the room
and the cameraman and shit. We got to find a new place. Stop making those.
Stop making those. We don't like them. And we're not staying in the mission.
Now check it out. Years ago, an earthquake dropped part of the city below sea level.
And rather than clearing out the rubble, the city just built over. There's an abandoned hotel below
the mission that'll work for us. All right. What's the catch? We got to evict the current tenants.
Sounds like fun. Make more. You're talking about them right now. Yeah, but advertising worked on
you. No, it didn't. I'm completely immune to advertising. See, I'm one of those people that
says no ads work on me, which usually means all ads work on me. And I can tell you that ads work
because the amount of times that I've seen stuffed crust pizza ads in my life,
when I was preparing stuffing for Thanksgiving, I wanted a stuffed crust pizza because the word
stuff. They fucked me up for life. For life. Why are you not eating stuffed crust right now?
That's a really good question. But hold on a second. He's okay. He's all right.
We can swim. We're fine. We made it. We don't have a car anymore, but we'll get there.
It was like a coin pusher game. They were right on the edge. I had to push them.
No. All right. I'm fine. Don't you think you wouldn't be wanting to walk over here?
All of you thought it was going to happen again. And I made sure that it wouldn't.
I made damn sure that it was not going to happen again. But I'll tell you right now,
I want this person's car because it's way better. Easy. Easy. No, they got away. What happened?
Okay, here we go. Let's do it. Make your way underground. Do I have enough weapons for this?
Ooh. I'm sorry. I had to do it. I haven't done it in a while. To go underground.
Resident Evil 4 graphics. That's a great game too. Let's flashbang the room first.
That didn't work. Never mind. Where is he? Down there? Hey, what the fuck?
Watch out. Don't run in my line of fire. What are you out of your mind?
How much ammo do I have? You all right? We didn't even get hurt. Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You all right? You okay? You okay? You okay? Get up. Get up. Get
up. Tagging? Oh, shit. Nice. Let's go. This is kind of hard with a controller. Shake the spray can?
You got this? Can you handle it? Oh, my God. What just happened? Gun. Nice. Okay. What? Oh,
it's a shotgun now. Wait. No, I want the other gun. Oh, fuck it. I'll use the shotgun. Who cares?
This is my weapon of choice anyways. I'll show you why. Just wait. I'll show you why in a minute.
What are these people? Oh. What was going on? Why did they all get out of there? What was that?
What's going on? Who are these people? They're not bad? I don't know. I saw them get up on
the grass and start running at me. I didn't know. I did not know. I'm sorry. You want to handle this
one? You take care of this one. You get it. I'll get it. You idiot. Oh, my God. Fuck off with this
bullshit. Got him. One more up here. All right. We did it. Destroy the shanties.
We get out of here? What do we have to do? Whoa. Use left control to take someone's human shield
to prevent you from getting hit by Moe's bullets. What? I don't know what that button is. I have no
idea what that button is. My God. How do I do that? Dude. That's no way to act. I'm going to
have to tell you right now. That's no way to act. That's no way to act. I'm sorry. It's not.
Why won't this break? That's no way to act. But how do I do this? Throw someone at it. Okay. I have
to figure out what that button that is. Come here. I'm going to test some stuff on you for a second.
It's not... Wait. You're not actually mad, right? Right bumper? Why? What is control? Left bumper?
Okay. It's left bumper. So hold on. Don't shoot this person. Don't shoot this person. Stop.
Do not. Oh my goodness gracious. Okay. Don't shoot that person. I'm going to fucking be pissed if you
do. Oops. I can't believe you can... It's not like... This is not... We're not playing. Okay.
I have to hold them. Why can't I just kick these? I don't... I can't. I just want to punch them down.
I don't want to throw people into them. You don't stop doing that or I'm actually going to hurt you.
I'll hurt you motherfucker. I will. Don't do that. I've seen too much. What happened? I put the
fucking gun down. Now. Why are we doing this? Is this like another gang? Holy shit. They have
fucking weapons. Hold on. I'm stun locked. Okay. Go. You are gangsters. They're in your hideout.
Oh, you get the safe house. Okay. I see. He studied the blade.
Star Wars kid. I forgot I had the skates on. Okay. Thousand bucks. I get five hundred bucks a day.
Oh, that's cool. Wait. I get to have my own gang? Oh shit. Okay. Seventeen hundred bucks.
Sorry. Let me go in here. Okay. All right. Fill up your respect bar to play this mission. Oh, I can't.
Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. This is a Nickelodeon Nicktoons MLB mod.
More extreme that you do things a better more respect. Okay. All right. So let's do an activity.
This one's the closest. We're going to do this one. Save the game. Yep.
Two percent of the game done. It's not actually right here, right? Oh, this is your garage.
Oh, okay. Oh, tagging mission. Walker comes up. What's that meter on the left?
It's like the boss health meter. What does that mean? Is that my health? That's enemy attention.
Oh, I. Oh, that would make sense then as to why they're coming over here now to kill me. Help me.
Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me. Help me. Thank you. What was that? I didn't even want to do that.
Wait. Now all of a sudden she cares. Get me the fuck out of here. Get me out of here.
Oh, don't get hurt from this. Oh, my God. You idiot. Oh, my God. You idiot twice.
Quick, quick, quick, quick. Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. What is this? What is this mission?
Thank God you're here. Every second we're talking is one more second of airtime that Zach Johnson
is stealing from me. Oh, you know, that nut job lawyer who gets hard at the idea of a lawsuit.
Lately, he's been crusading against media. He deems to be offensive.
They're gonna be dead when the mission starts. Not really. But the guy makes a big enough ass
out of himself that whenever he pulls some stunt, people listen.
And if people are watching him, they're not watching me. So what do you want me to do?
Get out there and give me something worth covering. The more damage you do,
the longer I can do a live broadcast.
The right way. Cause carnage. Okay. Wait. I have to like do a bunch of shit like for you to like
film it. Okay. I have to give you the fucking content. It doesn't matter what I do. Do I have
to just break stuff? I have to go to a specific area? Cause that crash game was probably at least
a hundred bucks. Uh, that was carnage. I mean, that was, I just broke a bunch of stuff. Do 50,000
property damage. All right. That was so easy. Do it. Get a bonus destroy luxury cards. Wait,
what about in here? Is it explode? Oh, that was not $50,000 in damage. What are you talking
about? That was an entire gas station. All right. Cool. Get new missions now, right? I still want
to figure out what this actually is. I see all these bottles. I need to investigate. What does
this mean? Okay. So it's a little store. Does that get me in trouble? Oh no. Who let the mayhem guy
in here? It does get me in trouble. Okay. I do get in trouble. I get in trouble. I didn't even
touch this guy. I'm trying to pick him up. How do I pick up people? You're a hippo that got into a
store. I didn't even rob the register. Oh, I can do another mission. Put that on the map. I can
go here or I can go down here. What's this stronghold mission? Uh, this one's closer to
this one. There's so much to do. This is ridiculous. No, I have three stars. How many stars can you get
max in this game? Six. Five. I can't. I hate. I don't want to do it, but you make me do it when
you say it. Holy shit. Scared me. Oops. Am I closer? Plus two dying joke. I know. Didn't you
yell about? I could hear you yell about from all the way over here. Door cut? Maybe. I think it's
up. Do I have to go on the highway? Come on, GPS. What the hell are you doing? Yeah. We'll take a
pee break in a minute. Doi, doi, doi, doi. Why is the GPS keep changing? Where is it? Stop. Why?
This GPS is not even on a road. What is this GPS telling me to do? What? I have to go underground.
Oh, hold on. Tag mission. Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake,
more Aaron. No, I don't. You want to see more Aaron, just go watch Attack on Titan dub. It
happens every other episode. I love it. Dub an entire episode. I don't know. That's not
happening. This is literally all the game just fucking crashed. Shit. What was the last time
I saved it? It was pretty, it was pretty recent. I'll go pee. Yeah. We'll take a pee break. This is
a good time to take a break right after the last mission. That's all right. I'll be fine.
Pee break. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. All right. Now I'm actually BRB. I want to make
sure I can load the game back in. Be right back. I'm telling you. Ever since I got this 3090,
this room is 10 degrees hotter than it was before. It just is. I could be playing minesweeper. It
doesn't matter. Bathroom break joke. Where were you? Oh, I'm just taking a break. I'm just taking
a break. Whatever. What? I was looking at my tweets and I don't know what the fuck was going
on in Thanksgiving. I really don't. I can read you some of the drafts if you'd like. I didn't post
any of these. I don't know why, but maybe I do know why. Okay. Let's see. The first one that's
in the drafts is, I accidentally threw away the wrapper to my little turkey breast I got.
Is it 30, 40 minutes in the microwave? I didn't post it. I don't know. I don't understand why.
An empty M&M's packet smells like someone shit in your bathroom 30 minutes ago. That's true,
but I don't know why I didn't post that one either. And then I put pumpkin pie in F tier
two weeks ago. I just had it for the first time in years. I want to travel back in time and snap
that motherfucker's neck. All these I wrote, but I didn't post. I don't know why. But wouldn't that
kill me? That would kill like future me. Okay. But yeah, I had pumpkin pie and it was unbelievably
good. And by the way, the empty M&M's packet thing, go do it. Go do it. We'll see. Eat a little
packet of M&M's and then wait. Smell the wrapper. Inside. It's as if somebody's shit in your fucking
house and like almost an hour has gone by, but it's still kind of there. Yeah. None of these,
none of these hit hard for me. I don't know why. No tweets ever do. I always write a tweet and I
go, nah, I don't care. I open up Twitter once every month or two to make a tweet. I write the
tweet and then before I post it, I say, I don't care about this shit and I delete it. The microwave
one is a banger. Well, I also maybe didn't want people to think that I was actually doing that.
Blow up my house, right? I don't want people that like, even though I fuck around a lot,
people still think that that I'm like serious classic, but it's funny. Yeah. Well, I just read
them to you. Now it's okay. We know you do that. Please read. This is very important.
I've sent one of your videos to a girl I've been talking to and she stopped talking to me. Is that
what you said? I can't scroll up, but what are you doing? Okay. Let's go. I'm ready. I hope this
captures the capturing. Customize your crib here to gain style points. Ooh. Oh shit. Okay.
2000. What about pimp pad? Ooh, I like this. It's 4,000. I'll save up for it.
You're my auto Lala. You don't even like that video. You hated that until I did it like three
times and then I somehow like brainwashed you all. I've like brainwashed all of you to think that
some of these things are funny. Isn't that weird how that happened? I said Aaron one time in that
voice and everyone freaked out and said, I don't fucking do that ever again. I did it like 35,000
more times and now everybody wants it every stream. I did the Lala dog thing and everyone was like,
stop doing that. It's cringe. It sucks. You probably watched the video and now you want me
to do it every stream. Doy, doy, doy. I did that once and people, I saw like the stop, stop,
nay, nay, no, no, no emotes. All right. Let's go. I'm just stirring up my iced coffee. Don't drop
that. This is a repeat episode. They're all repeats. Understand? It's these are all repeats.
I can do a home theater. I don't have any money to even care about this right now.
Don't leave. Okay. Missions didn't play zombie uprising. It's too much going on. Wait,
I want to play zombie uprising. No, I don't like this. Okay. Let me explain. Super Nintendo
switch. Nintendo is burned in my brain. The B button on Nintendo, the back button is where the
A button is on the Xbox. It's A on Xbox is like, yes, do this thing. But that's B on Nintendo. And
I, it's ever since I was 15, 12, 11, doesn't matter. 10. This is a, I, that's not, they gotta
get on something here. They gotta be on the same page. Cause I'm, I'm right now it's crossed up,
confirm and back because they're flipped on the different consoles. Who cares? Then I want that.
I don't want to see the person's name ever again. If I see it again, I'm going to fucking,
I'm going to throw, I'm just throwing up thinking about that person. Okay. No, let's go. No, I want
to stop the zombie assault. Is this part of the mod? I think this is the mod. Um, what's one,
which, what is one, what button on the controller is one. I don't know what button it is. Is there
a weapon? How do I get out? How do I leave the game? Just kill me. I don't care. This is fun,
but whatever. Also having to hit back and then confirm the back instead of pressing back twice.
You know what I mean? You get it. You guys get it. I know you do. Is your stash. Ooh,
take money. Should I put, should I put money in the stash and people steal from me or rob me or
something? All right. I need to do this mayhem mission again, because that's where we left off.
This one's a hundred thousand. I can definitely do it. That's passive income. Oh, that's cool.
Oh, shit. I forgot about this. Let me try a few in his drink. Not quite. Oh, come on. It's
right there. Let me just do this, please. Okay. Here we go. No, wait. I, this is for the video.
Am I asleep? I don't know. You might be. How do you type that if you're asleep? You make no sense.
Ban that person. No music. All right. Well, we need to have other music then. Cause I can't
play the one that's on here. I'm not playing Kevin McLeod. No thanks. He's really, really,
he's got, he's really talented, really great. Did awesome shit for the entire YouTube community.
When all the people were like, what are we going to do for music? It's great. It's awesome. But I
don't want to listen to it. Like what, what a hero. What an absolute fucking just may gave everybody
music to use. Wait, hold on. It's blocking me. Why is this bench that much stronger than the other
benches? This is the strap right here. They just respawn. No, they don't. My whole face is itchy.
Hold on. What the fuck is happening? Hey, good. I got two minutes to do this. I got it.
This is the slowest fucking car I could possibly use to do this. Come on, break it. Oh God,
whatever. Stop. Just get up here. I just have to get a car. Why did I even get out of that car?
Use grenades. I have grenades. Don't make any sudden moves. Oh my God. I have grenades. You're
right. Oh fuck. I'm down. That's your fault. I blame you for that shit. I blame you for that. I
don't know. I freaked out. I'm doing it again. I blame you for that. I really do. This is so much
easy. This is easy with just grenades. This is like too easy doing this. Just breaking stuff.
How am I so fat? I have a mod. Don't run into the grenade. You idiot. This is a cheap strategy.
Yeah, I just put in the cheat codes in GTA and just went to the rocket launcher and then I got
bored. You know what I mean? I got bored. Fuck. I did the cheat codes and I took out the rocket
launcher. The game's no longer fun anymore. Use the true meta. Drive over fences. I'll try that.
I don't want to throw this. I got two minutes to get to 10,000. Don't ever get on a motorcycle
ever again, Jeremy. Seriously, what are you doing? Let's try fence strat. I mean, fence strat is
perfect. That's actually a great strategy. I got it. Who is she shooting at? 250. That's it.
Okay. Save the game. Let's try this again. Hopefully it doesn't crash again.
I will be sad if this crashes again. That's literally right here. I don't think I've
blinked in two hours. Has that ever happened to you guys where you finally end up blinking
a couple times and your eyes are hurt and they're watery? Shake the can. Hurry up. Hurry up. Okay.
Game is saved. Don't crash. Please don't crash. Don't crash. Yes. We're good.
These guys are bad guys. These people are awful.
You said it yourself. Most of the old crew are either dead or busted by Troy.
We're going to have to start fresh. Yeah. Well, let's get on that because I'm done mopping up
blood. That's the point. Yeah, no shit. It seems all right, but we're going to need more. What's
you thinking? Yo, I met some people in jail who might work. Let me make some calls. Once I find
out where these bitches are, you're going to have to show them that you're the real deal though.
They won't just follow anybody. It won't be a problem. Hey, before you go, what sort of crew
are you looking for? I'm looking for people that are strong, smart, can work on the fly,
who know right from wrong, integrity, the ability to cook large meals,
feed everybody because how are we going to do that? I don't know how to cook. We're going to
have like 50 people in this. This is what happens when you just talk and you don't play video games.
Okay. But yeah, like seriously, we're going to have like 50 people in the crew in the same place.
We have to have like catering. One of the first people has to be a caterer in the group.
That's important. Like a tax attorney, right? These are all things you need. Pharmacy, a pharmacist.
Yeah, I would join the gang if it had a caterer. You need to have, if I was going to have a gang,
I'd want to have like a couple of teachers, two or three doctors. I'm not even describing
a gang at this point. I'm describing like your neighbor, like your neighbors, like a community.
It's not even, this is just like, oh yeah, that's just like a community of people.
We have like a few, we have doctors, we have nurses, we have workers, we have like,
this is just like houses. What am I talking about? I'm not even describing a gang. I'm describing
like, I'm describing like a YMCA. You know what I mean? Like, oh yeah, we've got like a gym,
we've got like people like, we've got doctors, we've got nurses, we've got a pool, play the game.
Fuck, I'm sorry. I know, I know, you know it. Oh, is he okay? Is he okay? Please get his money.
Where are you going? I don't know. I'm not paying attention. This is what happens. I just start
talking and I just drive in circles. Please bear with me. Well, I have to go to the one over here.
Just take your time. All right, I don't know what the mission is. Is the mission to kill this
person? Is the mission to recruit this person? Are you a caterer? You've experienced anything
like Italian Mediterranean food? Because that's what I want to have. You're not a chef. Do you
know any chefs? Oops. Do you want stuff to crust? I have to go off the jump? What jump?
Are you impressed? Are you impressed? That was pretty crazy, wasn't it? Well, what's with this
gigantic blob here? Well, how do I have to go? Okay, I get it. I'm just driving to the indicator.
Follow me. We'll do it on a motorcycle and then I guarantee you're going to die.
Just to make sure we're all aware of this. It's almost like I would put my arms around you to
hold on, but I can't. Where the fuck is this? I don't understand what I have to do here.
I have to jump that? Oh, is there a right there? Okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. We're good.
Get the fuck out of the way. Are we good? Do you care? Are we friends? We're still alive. That's
good. So there's three more jumps to hit. Follow me. What? Oh, wait. I don't know how much more
of this. Is she injured? Okay. Where's this next one? Just get it on the map. Here we finally.
Okay. What just happened? I don't know. All right. All right. All right. All right. It's right there.
Is it this mound? Did I count? It didn't count. Good times. Good times.
Oh, sorry. I was trying to kill her. I was just trying to dump her and now I have to do this
again. I'm so fucking sorry. I'm actually sorry. I didn't really, I did not think it was going to
kill me. I thought I was going to kill her. Oh fuck. Whatever. I'm sorry. It wasn't even worth it.
I thought it was going to just, the car is going to blow up or something. I don't know.
I'll get it really quick right now. I promise. Don't leave. Stay. If I don't finish this mission
in the next hour, like this one right here, to get the three jumps, like this, just with her to
jump over the three jumps, just this part of this mission here, an hour, I will give 500 trillion
community subs. Just this part here would just go to the three jumps. That's it. There's this, this,
section of this mission. I have an hour. God, I hope my power doesn't go up.
Why am I freaking out? I have an hour to do a mission that takes 10 seconds.
Oh, by the way, by the way, if, even if my power goes out, if I, if I do it,
it doesn't matter. Even if like the stream turns off, it doesn't fucking matter. I can do it here.
Just this part right here, this one, that's it. Just do the jumps. I didn't say it had to be on
screen, by the way. I just had to say I had to do it in an hour. By the way, I could literally,
I'm just going to, if my power goes out or something, I'm literally going to go download
this on the switch and play it in my bathroom and just do it and do it. So it counts. Get on. Quick.
I'm not fucking around. I can't right now, even if it's impossible to lose.
That counts. I did. Yep. Good. Cool. There's no reason for me to freak out about this. I have
plenty of time. And I know somebody probably going to say, no, I did not say an hour in dog years.
An hour in human years. There's two. Oh my God. All right. I'm done. I got it. Mission complete.
I did it. It's been completed. I can't redrive from checkpoint. I can't redrive.
It's done. She's good. We did it. It's over. I'm done. That section wasn't complete. Even if I died,
it doesn't matter. That section was already complete. Look, I told you just that section.
It was very clear. I would like a new weapon, special thrown flash bangs. That's so expensive.
Why don't I just buy that? That's stupid. I think it's 2000 too much. This is too expensive.
300 bucks. Dude. Double or nothing. Double or nothing. No, no double or nothing. It's over.
Oh, that cross sucks. Nevermind. Oh, what am I doing? Let's go. We'll go right here.
Double or nothing. That's stupid. There's so many old people here. Everybody's old. All right. What
do you want me to do? You got it. Get in the car. I made this very easy. Oh, hey, what the
fuck are you doing? Why did you? What would you do that for? Why would you do that? I don't want you
on the team. I don't want you. I don't want you part of the guild or whatever this is. I know
that was stupid. What you did was dumb and now we're in trouble. No, I'm kicking you from the
guild. Help me. You took the cop hostage. Who is this? No, no, no, no, no. Where's the crowbar?
How'd you get a crowbar? I want that. Where are you going? Okay. Let's get the fuck out of here.
Wait, it's over here. We're going to sneak up on them. Where are they? Where are they? What do
you think about that? What do you think about that one? Don't fall off. Although it'd be kind
of funny if you did. Is that going to kill him? He's blazed. What? Wait, hold on. Does this reset
the mission if he falls? Does it? I don't think it will. Oh my god, he's fine and he can't even
fall off this. Oh, whatever. I'm gone. Why do you guys think I'm zonked? What are you talking about?
How am I zonked? I told you I was drinking coffee. There's one more person this way.
What kind of coffee? An iced coffee. Let's go. An iced coffee. Busy. I made it myself.
Well, I couldn't let my boyfriend. You know, a guy from jail. You know, it's like 7 p.m. where I am.
It's 5 20. He's happy enough when he's killing somebody. You don't drink coffee up to 6 p.m.
Seriously. That's it. I got enough to go till 6. Brew your own coffee? Well, I mean, yeah.
Would you guys like to know the best beans of coffee to use for any occasion?
You want me to tell you? I will. It's nothing fancy. It's nothing like, oh wow, you got those
beans from some random plant. You imported them from a different country. No. The Illy coffee
beans are the best. They just are. Without a doubt. S plus tier. They do everything. Hot coffee.
Fantastic. They do iced coffee. Fantastic. Illy. It's in a little tin. A little tin can. That's the
best coffee beans you can possibly buy. If you're not drinking Illy, here's what's going to happen.
You're going to drink Illy for a little while and be like, oh, this is perfect. What a perfect cup
of fucking coffee. And then you're going to drink something else and go, oh, this is, this is good.
This is okay. You're going to pretend to like it. You're going to get like an expensive coffee
and pretend to enjoy it because you want to seem like you know what you're talking about.
Then you're going to eventually go back to Illy and say, yeah, why did I ever leave? There's no
reason to. All right. Back at the, oh, I have to tell this. It's just a really good, nice, smooth
cup of coffee. Illy. I-L-L-Y. I think. Coffee snob, Andy. You can get this at any grocery store.
How do I pick this up? I don't want to hurt this person. Oh my God. I'm running over stuff.
Left control. And what is it? I don't have no idea what those buttons are. There it is.
Okay. Hold until the vehicle is there.
Okay. Yeah, no, I'm not sponsored to say that. No. Illy coffee beans does not sponsor,
they don't sponsor people. I, I'm just telling you what I truly believe. That's it. How do you
grind the beans? Grinder. Freshest cup of coffee you can get is when you grind beans. Grind your
beans, put it right in after grinding. That was on purpose, but it wasn't somehow.
I didn't, I have, whatever. I'm using the car as a, what the fuck are you doing? I didn't press
that. I didn't press that. I promise I didn't press that button. What kind of roast is it?
I think it's just a, oh, the goddamn game crashed. God damn it. Are you kidding me? No. Oh no.
Wait, the timer? Wait, hold on. How long has it been? No, that counts because I did it and
you say it was completed on the stream. Uh, oh fuck. What? Are you kidding me? That's such
horse shit. All right. I have to start to save after every single thing I do now.
Now I'm actually concerned about this. Yes, it does count. You have 45 minutes left. Stop
fucking around and go. Hurry. Oh, please. Tap the game's FPS to 10. I don't think I want to do that.
Turn cheats on. No, I've never experienced this game before. I'm not going right to the cheats.
I'm enjoying Saints Row 2, the video game, as it was intended by the video game's development.
I think it's running pretty good. I mean, it's a little chunky sometimes, but I think it's fine.
I swear, what roast? Please. Um, I think it was just the just the standard roast. Just the
regular roast. It's the red can. Ili has like three or four different cans. It's the one that's the
red can. That's the red letters. No, it's not roast beef. It's just standard roast. I don't know
what that I don't know. How do you not know the can? It's your favorite coffee. I don't I don't
know. It's whatever it is. It's like breakfast roast, regular roast, yum roast, eat roast,
pork roast. It doesn't matter. The coffee is good. It's the red can. Just buy the red can.
You know what they do? They have an espresso blend too. And that's also good. I've had that
one before. Holy shit. Ili is owned by Folgers. Okay, wait a minute before. Oh, no, it's owned
by Folgers. It's a Folgers coffee. Oh, no. You mean the thing that you can go get a fucking tub of
it. It's literally like the cheapest like you can get a whole tub of Folgers for probably less than
10 bucks. It'll last you like three months. Sometimes coffee is just coffee. And that's all
you need. You don't have like, look, I Okay, oh, I'd like a cappuccino. I'll take a macchiato,
please. Yeah, but just a regular just cup of coffee in your coffee maker. Who cares? It's not
look, you can get some nice stuff if you want. But on a day to day basis, stop shooting at people.
Why? I actually like Folger. I don't think Folgers is bad. It's just regular just regular coffee,
just diner coffee. That's not a problem. Look, some coffees are kind of gross, even like the
really nice expensive ones. Get out of the car quick. Please get out of the car. Get out of the
car. Get away from for explodes. Thank you. Support your local coffee roasters. There's actually a few
that are really good out here. I've had but it's just in your cupboard. Just coffee. It's just you
can just it's always there. It's always available. By the way, I did it. See? Done. No, I didn't have
three more to do. Shit. Not sponsored by the way. I'm not why why would I be sponsored by a coffee
company? But I've what I'm just not going to announce that I have like a major new sponsorship.
I'm just gonna say bye. You need to buy Italy. When I have to disclose that for the fucking
FAA regulations or whatever. It's good times. Whenever you're getting everyone together. Let
me know. I'd love to roll with you guys. Okay, save it. You're safe. We're good. Now please get
out of the way so I don't hurt you. We're good. I love Italy. Yeah, it's very it's really good.
I've had a lot of coffee in my life. And it's probably the best one that I've had. That's just
a regular good cup of coffee. There's nothing else I need to say to you. I don't need to prove
that it's good coffee. Just get it. I have to prove it. I'm gonna run with you. I want to see
Well, what would you guys consider as good coffee to have is beans or ground? What do you buy?
If it's not illy? What is it? Folgers? What is it? Folgers? Yeah, what's wrong with that?
I'm seeing a lot of Folgers and a lot of you are Folgers haters for some reason.
Costco brand? That's good too. Trader Joe's? That's good too. Good. Starbucks? No, if I'm
going to buy coffee, it's not going to be Starbucks beans. It just isn't. Buying Starbucks beans is not
No, you can just go to Starbucks and get it. There's Starbucks in every fucking one mile.
It's not like special. You can't there's no like Folgers you can get.
Now like I'm going to go to the Folgers store and get a Folgers from the Folgers cafe.
No, I actually don't really even like Starbucks coffee that much. It's okay. Nice. Meet me at the
abandoned mission house. I'll be there. He's trying to dodge him. Thank you. Why buy Starbucks beans?
You can just go and get it from the store for 10 times more. Yeah, okay. I understand. I know. I
understand what you mean. But there is something to be said about having being somewhere out
somewhere. It's like, you know what? Yeah, I'll take a coffee. I'll take a nice iced coffee.
It's nice. Sometimes you just want to have like be holding around a coffee while you're walking
around just hanging out. Iced coffee is better from a cafe. It usually is. It's really difficult
to make an iced coffee at home that's actually as good as like a cafe. And I know I haven't figured
out why. I don't get it. I've tried everything. The iced coffee I make is really good. But it's
not the same. Get loads of sugar. No, I don't get. I don't put sugar in my coffee. Not usually. Maybe
like one. I don't put them in sugar in a coffee. I usually drink hot coffee black and iced coffee
with almond milk or oat milk and maybe like one pump of some syrup or something. But I can't
replicate it at home. That person went through the windshield. Holy shit. My brother's been looking
for a good recipe. I missed that. What did they say? My brother's looking for a good recipe?
I missed that. Somebody said my brother's looking for a good recipe for something. I
didn't see what it was. Oh my god. Damn it. Just fucking go. That guy walked into the car.
That was not even my fault. Where the fuck is the car?
Did you have a car on the back like a bicycle? Enough about coffee. Are we talking about this
too long? I'm really worried if you drive like this in real life. I don't drive like this. This
is a video game. You don't drive a car with an analog stick and in a cartoon video game universe.
The hell is about your Civic? Don't distract me right now. Do an IRL driving stream. No,
why would I do that? I don't want to do that. Why would I do that? This is getting ridiculous.
They... Okay, we're good. What the fuck? That scared the shit out of me. I was looking over
the chat. What the hell is going on? I had to do some canonizing. Hold up. You. You're next.
Wait, what? Sorry about that. When did you find these guys? Like I said, I made some calls.
Yeah, the character is a mod that makes the sliders much higher.
The gentleman of the row. It's been great so far.
Giving a speech?
Pierce, you're on the Ronin. I want to know who's calling the shots and what businesses
they're running. Done. Shandy, you got the sons of Shandy. It's gotta be them. Fuck you, sir.
Do you ever have kids? It's cool. I got this. No, I've shit my pants in the last year. Carlos.
I can't handle it. I wouldn't be able to do it. All right. Once we're done here,
talk to one of these guys. They'll have something for you to do. It's our time now.
Let's get this shit started. That means you must be good at changing diapers. Okay,
you now recruit a single saint follower. Press up to recruit nearby saints. Okay, cool. So I can have
a one-person crew. All right, so there are more symbols popping up here. What do these mean?
Start of Ronin mission? Start the sons of... Hello? Hey, hey, be cool. It's not so bad.
Mero asked to sit down and have a chat with you. He wants to work something out before things get
out of control. I got it. Okay, there's a lot going on here. What's that? A drink?
I wanted more of that. There are diverging quest lines. It's an RPG. Really?
That's actually pretty cool. I want to do this one. No, I want to do one of the
just random missions. This game's really fun. You know what sucks? We talked about...
Because this is THQ, right? Yeah. This is THQ, right? Here comes the THQ rant.
Well, you know what I'm going to say. Who saw that?
All right. Can you get arrested? What's going on? I'm looking over there.
I'm not paying attention to these two. Come on, do it. Oh my God. Fine. Never mind. The drip.
Stop. Everybody stop. I'm warning them. I'm trying to warn them.
How did I drive by it? What's the diamond? Oh, what's the... I want to go to the diamond.
No, I want to throw my head on the thing. I want to throw this person. Can I rob this place?
Jewelry stores allow you to customize your character. Oh, rob your weapon? I got to get the...
Okay. I guess I'll take... Do you have any silver? You guys have any silver? I'm looking for
sterling silver. Why can't I... She's got a knife. Why does this not work? This thing fucking sucks.
Why does this not work? She took a picture of me.
She thought if you have a knife, you're just going to take pictures. What are you doing?
Give me this register. No, I'm slowing down. I need to get back in the car. Give me the money
that's in there. How do I break it? How do I... Do I have to step on it? What the fuck? This thing's
not broken. It's not broken. What the fuck, dude? Is it... Can I... Tell me if I'm wrong or not. Can
I actually do this? You can't. Okay. Well, what the hell am I doing? All right. Get the cops off.
You have to do fine aim at the store clerk to do a robbery. Okay. No, don't play the fucking
harmonica. I want to eat the food. How do I eat the food? Eat it. Quick, quick, quick. No, fuck
around. They're outside. She just went through the window. She went through the passenger window.
What? Who is she shooting at? I'm very confused as to what just happened. Oh, it's this guy. I'm
going to see how this plays out. Here he comes. We're out. Oh, shit. It's here. What is this?
Car shop? Get that off the screen. I don't know. What is this? Go find a swindle. Oh, I found it.
Why are you going so fast? They're gone. No, don't. No, do not. No, don't. Shoot the gun.
Shoot the gun, you imbecile. You're the worst gamer alive. No, I'm not. I lost them. Where are they,
though? They show up randomly, don't they? Five of them were just on the screen. Come on, spawn one.
What am I doing? I'm looking for one of these cars. Sorry, I had to blink really hard. My eyes
are watering. Is there no other one of these cars? I was trying to bait the cop to go over
there and they didn't. Why won't one of these show up? They show up in different districts.
Here we go. This one is a million. What the hell? They desperately get out. Get out, please. I'm
not going to kill anybody. This thing is so slow. This is the slowest car ever. There's a lot of
extra weight in here. I just joined. Why is he an ogre? A thousand bucks. Nice. Oh, I can't wait
later on. I'm going to get takeout and watch Ernest Saves Christmas. An absolute fucking classic
movie. I can't wait. Let's go over here. Should I do one of the main missions? Yeah, if you don't
watch Ernest Saves Christmas in the next couple weeks, don't come back to this stream. I have to
be very, very realistic. If you do not watch Ernest Saves Christmas in the next three or four weeks,
don't come back here. What if you don't celebrate Christmas? All right. Well, let me rephrase that.
Let me rephrase that. I mean, if you celebrate Christmas, okay, then you don't watch Ernest
Saves Christmas. All right. I'm a fucking idiot. I'm an idiot. I'll take that loss. If you celebrate
Christmas, you don't watch Ernest Saves Christmas, then you're in deep shit if you come back here.
In fact, you know what? No, let's go even further. You got to go watch all the Ernest movies in the
next month or don't come back. By the way, you got to get started. There's like 15 of them.
You can do this. You can do it. You can do it. Come on, please. I know you're capable of doing this.
Come on, get the fuck out of here. Get up there. Get up there. You piece of shit. Did that kill me?
Here we go. What's this thing? This is my garage. Oh, it's a garage guy. Can I eat one of these?
All right. This mission is a brotherhood mission. What's the one behind it?
It's two. Is that inside? When are you going to do an Ernest tier list movie? Soon. I mean,
it's not going to be very long content because every single one of them is an S tier.
What in the name of God just happened in here? What the fuck? He was doing like,
this person has to be stopped, right? I have to stop this person. I'm trying to save you.
Gang strongholds are centers of operation for each gang. Find and wipe them all out
to deal hard blows to each gang. Okay. That person was on my team. He was red on the mini
map. I don't think so. Oh, we're doing this shit again. I don't want to do this.
No, I don't want to. I'm not killing anybody. No, I refuse. Except for these two. This is
Dark Souls area. It is. Yeah. This is like blight. This is like the entrance to blight town.
The bridges, the little corridors, the little ledges. Oh, I can't wait to play Elden Ring.
Do I have to even be hostile? Wait, that's not, I don't have to destroy that. All right. I'm not,
look, I'm just, let me go. Holy shit. There's so many people here. Are you kidding me?
There's like, there's like 500 people here. How am I going to do this?
I don't even want to be violent. I don't want, I don't, I want non-violence. I just need to get,
okay, hold on. I'm so fat. I can just run into them. Perfect. Nobody has to get hurt.
What the fuck? It didn't work on this one. Good. All right. We're done. We're done. We're done.
We're done. We're done. I don't have to do anything. We're good. Jim Varney's character,
Ernest P. Warrell, was created by the Nashville advertising agency and we used it. Oh yeah. He
did local commercials. The best one is when he has his hands on the windowsill and he's like,
hey, Vern. He leans in, he's talking about milk. He's like, I have for you the best creamiest yogurt
in all the world. And then Vern grabs it from his hand and the windowsill lands like flies down and
hits him in the hands. And he's like, entire Ernest advertising line is perfect. He's on a
ladder. At one point he gets pushed back and he falls off the roof. Immune to ads. I'm sorry. I
will buy whatever Ernest tells me to. I don't care what it is. I need to be more, have more respect
for this one. Okay. What about, what's this? Did I lose respect? I already know all this.
There's a train in the game. All right. We found a new thing to play with. Not yet. Which one's the
Get out of here. You're fucking dead. Excuse me. What was that for? Yeah. You know what? I can't
understand. Uh, look, you know how movies over the years, like they get like, oh, cult followings or
whatever. It, it, it is, it is insulting to me that most of the Ernest movies have like 20% on
Rotten Tomatoes. I can't, I honestly don't understand. I can't understand. That's unbelievable
to me because they're not good. That's what you just said is unbelievable to me. And what you just
said is very hurtful to me. What you just said is very hurtful to me. Stop. Don't say that.
I want that bike. Not that one. That one's dirty. I want the one that's clean and hasn't been used
or destroyed. Oh, this chop chop. You fucking idiot. No. Hold on. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up.
What's wrong with me? What am I doing? What am I doing on the ground? What's wrong with my character?
Uh, what you were busted a small amount of cash and they, the metal detector doesn't even work.
I like take it. Can I steal something? I'm not in trouble. Not yet. Move out of the way. I don't
want to hit you a little bit further. You kidding me? Fine. The chairs. I just like home alone to
this guy. This guy can't even move. He can't get up. I'm not in trouble for that. It's what
happened. What exploded at that? I didn't get in trouble. All right. I'm going to go do that.
One of the missions I can do. Oh, this is one of the chop chop. That was unbelievable that
that happened. Yeah. I even tried to break. That was actually unbelievable. That was unbelievable.
I thought I could go right through it. It's a fucking, it's a white picket fence.
It's not like concrete. There's 2000 bucks. Holy shit. I should just do this for a little while.
Oh shit. What can I, I need more respect. I guess I'm more close too. This one is trail blazing.
I'm curious what that is. That guy didn't even move. Holy shit. Where do you get the hamburger?
I want that. All right. Don't do that anymore. I bet you get points for riding a wheelie for
a long time though, right? If I were to take a guess. All right. What is this? Thanks for stopping
by. The brothers of Theta appreciate. The brothers of Theta better. If you do not take damage in the
next 10 minutes, we will take 200 million off the deck. So what's the problem? Okay.
Beat our step team. Now they think they hot shit. We need someone to knock them down to pay.
You got anything I can use. So they know you sent the message this year. We bought a flame suit for
pledge hazing. You think you can find a way to cares about the debt anymore. An old meme. Oh,
you know what I got? I got almonds right here. Let's go for it. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Those are
crunchy. Yep. I have to be careful because these have like wasabi and soy sauce on them, which means
you literally can't pick them up with your fucking hands. Like every other goddamn snack that prides
itself on having a bunch of shit all over it that gets all over you. Oh dude, you got to eat
Takis. Dude, they're the best. They're so good. No, fuck those things. You can't eat them. You cannot
eat Takis unless you use a fork or chopsticks or something. Why is there so much shit all of them?
Dude, just eat chopsticks. What if I don't have a pair of chopsticks with me? Am I just going to
carry chopsticks with me everywhere? Takis are one of the... Okay, seriously. If you... I put a tier
list of snacks in a place where if I eat one of them, I have to wash my hands. Like if you pick
up one Taki with your fingers, you have to wash your hands. I don't know. Fuck, they give me some
almonds. Baked Lay's don't do that. Baked Lay's are the best complete S++ tier snack. They're the
best. I don't have to do that with Baked Lay's. You know, they did a study where they took a bunch
of people and they did an IQ test to them. And they... I think the study was somewhere in
California. It had like 500 people in it. And they did an IQ test with everybody.
And then they asked what their favorite snack was. And most of the people that had over 120 IQ,
Baked Lay's were a top three in the rankings. It was maybe somewhere in California. It was
one of the LA institutes. Which is like, it's kind of interesting to think about that.
It's not real study. What are you talking about? Okay, let's go. Race to the finish for
cash and respect. I believe you. Yeah, why wouldn't you? Okay, bonus seconds earned from ramming
people and cars. Well, that's easy. I do that without trying anyways. Three, two, one.
This is fucked up. No, the study was a completely peer-reviewed independent third-party study.
I'm not running over enough people. Or cars for that matter. I didn't have to do anything. Oh!
How did that not hit everybody? There was a study in 2017 that did an IQ test on 5,000 people.
Then they asked them who their favorite Twitch streamer was. And anyone with under 70 IQ said
it was you. IQ doesn't fucking even matter. It's like a completely stupid outdated thing to have.
So whatever you say, who cares? That was fucking cool, but it didn't do anything for me.
Please just hit the dumb. There's too much smoke on the screen. I can't see anything.
But isn't it kind of weird though that when I'm walking around town and walking around the city,
I see these businessmen walking around with suits on. They're on the phone. I see doctors
walking around with stethoscopes around their necks walking around talking on the phone and stuff.
And they have like a bag of baked lays in their other hand. That's so surprising apparently.
Is it? Business man does not equal intelligence. What are you talking about? That guy has a tie-on.
I trust him. I feel like that's something Peter Griffin would say. I'm sorry.
All right, I got money. Let's use it. No, he had a tie-on, Loish. I trust him.
Do you guys remember? I completely forgot about this. Do you remember when I did like the
do the entire family guy thing with like the weird family guy piano thing in the background?
That I deleted that from my memory. I don't remember even what was happening.
What was I was I was reading like a script or something, right? Oh, I was reading
Germacraft as the different characters. Right. That was so fucking weird. I tried to do it with
every character. Oh, come on. I was at work laughing during that. Hopefully I didn't get
any in trouble. That was traumatizing. Now you have to do it as the Attack on Titan character.
What was like Attack on Titan music playing in the background?
Uh, I don't know about that. I'm not so sure about that. What does this want me to do?
Why does it want me to go down here? GPS is so fucked up right now. What?
It's just go in the ocean and swim there. What? That very clearly was go down the staircase.
It really was. You saw it wrap around the staircase. I'm not crazy. I followed it because
I don't know what is there's such a red marker over there. Oh my fucking God. Jeremy, please.
Look, it's on the staircase. There's not even a road here. What the fuck? They did this on the
office. I've never seen the office. Why is the character dressed as the guy from Happy Wheels?
This GPS is fucked. What is it talking about? Why does it want me to do this? I don't understand.
I'm just going to go this way. This doesn't make any sense. Dude, somebody's fucking with
me right now. The game is just messing with my head. What is this? Where is this telling me to
go? I'm going around in a circle. I'm just walking. This is where I wanted to go. It was here,
right? Where's the hamburger place? Yeah, it's the mall. Okay. I was right. Nobody here. All
right. So you said I could rob this place. Let me buy something first. I need some new clothes.
Game crashed. No. When was the last time I saved it? Shit. I think it was not that far away. I
wasn't in a mission or anything. God damn it. Why? I need the music again. Yeah, that's right here.
All right. We're good. You said you saved? I did. No, yeah. Six thousand. Yeah, this is fine.
I'm going to do this mission here. Either Ronin. What should I do? Does it matter? Ronin? Ronin's
the one with the bikes and the katanas. Let's see. I'm curious. What's up with the dollhouse?
Dollhouse my ass. This is how we're going to fuck up the Ronin. This'll be good. Trust me.
It is. The Ronin have a stake in Poseidon's palace. So I figure hitting their biggest money maker is
a good way to show them we're not fucking around. Okay. So what's the plan? You and I enter the
casino here. Once inside, we need to distract this security guard. I was thinking you could catch
me cheating or some shit like that. Anyway, while the guard's concerned with throwing me out, Gato
sneak in through this security door. Don't worry. I already got today's passcode from the blackjack
dealer Shandi's fucking. Now once inside, Gato had to sneak past the guards to cut the power.
And when that happens, we only have about 45 seconds before the backup generator turns on.
During the blackout though. He's eating Takis. No. But what if we just start here,
walk into the casino and just shoot all the motherfuckers that are between us and the money.
Well, I just think of the red dust being absorbed into my intestinal tract. I don't want that to
happen. You know what I mean? If you eat like a half a bag of Takis or whatever, like heavily
red food coloring stuff, I don't like want like red, like red dust absorbed into my fucking
intestines. I don't know. It just probably fine. I don't want to do that. Don't you like think of
like just like drinking? I don't know. Okay. Let me be, let me, I gotta make this clear.
I'm not saying that this is weird or gross. I mean it, but it is. Is my health going down?
How can I become like a Redditor like you? Hmm. Well, hold on. Okay. So listen,
anything that has a heavy amount of powder or like food coloring or like food dye,
you do understand. Now this is not, this is not me making it up. This is factual information. This
is just real shit. Red food dye comes from two distinct sources. One is bugs, like crushed up
bugs. They derive it from that. And the other one, I believe now correct me if I'm wrong,
is like petroleum. It's like from like gasoline or something. Isn't it? It's like a chemical they pull
out of it. So I'm telling you, I prefer the bugs. I would rather eat the bugs. I'd rather eat like
the red food coloring bugs. I don't want the other one. It's a, it's a petroleum byproduct.
Right. Okay. So if I have an opportunity to eat the bugs or the petroleum byproduct,
which one are you going to pick? Correct answer is grow your own food. God. Oh shit. I wasn't
looking. Bugs are a different byproduct. Oh my God. I've hit every car. Okay. But I don't know. I
just, I just feel something is so unnatural about, I know people love like flaming hot Cheetos and
stuff, but man, like I know there's like the blue Takis and shit. Why? Like, oh, I want the bright
blue fucking ecto cooler Takis. What's going on here? The Nelth flavoring is squeezed from a
beaver's anus. God, if you get like real for now, like a vanilla fucking plant, whatever it is,
what is vanilla? It's like a plant. It's a herb, but what is vanilla? It's a, it's a plant.
Oh shit. I just think I didn't know. It's a bean. Yeah. We just walk. What do we do here?
Take out. Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to be like the old like person at the casino.
Can I play? Can I play? What? I can't play. What the fuck did I just, what's going on?
It's the guy from casino. Get out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out. Get him out.
I get shocked so many times. What the fuck are you doing, dude? I don't want to, this, this,
Oh, I already got pasta. I don't want to shoot. Oh, they're up top.
Pasta. Italiano garden. Ooh. Well, he uses the, what? Oh my goodness. That hurts.
Oh, well, Larry, Larry, David. Oh, I love doing the Larry, David. I can do it really well.
You're taking a long time to do this. Hurry up. No, that was Jeff. Oh, what do you mean?
They both did the same thing. They both do that.
When are you going to put Christmas music on? We already did the Christmas music thing.
You get out of here with your fucking unbrushed teeth. You fucking idiot. All right. Should I
do a Kirby enthusiasm tier list? Cause, cause Susie's up at like S tier. We good? Um,
are we dead? Why does everything need a tier list? Because I'm, I don't know. I'm
trying to make the zoomers think I'm cool. Well, they call the cops. Big surprise there.
I already think you're cool. Oh, thanks. I don't have to try anymore. One of my favorite curb.
I'm watching the current season, right? One of my favorite jokes this season. If you haven't seen
it, but you know, spoilers hold yours close for a second. Uh, when they're talking about cheese
and they're talking about feta cheese and Leon's like, I don't even think mice like that shit.
He's like, you gotta be in a specific mood for cheese. And I don't think even mice like that
shit. The way it's delivery is fucking hilarious. Leon is, is absolutely S tier as well. Every
single thing that Leon says is just as hysterical. Are they going to leave us alone? Um, the person
sneaking back onto the car. Stop tearing shit. It's cringe. All right. I won't.
Don't question me. And we're in America. Speak English.
A little jumpy today. He's knocking on the door.
Over there. So rude. Sword. Listen, I know you're having a hard time adjusting to the way I run
things here. How about you let me deal with my father and you call whatever the fuck I tell you
to deal with. Um, of course. Excellent. Okay. All right. Ooh, $500 a day. All right. You guys said
that the Ronin missions are the best ones. Should I just do another one? Oh, I don't have enough
respect. What's your favorite curb episode? The entirety of season seven, which I mean, I count
that as one episode because I watched the whole season back to back. So I usually watch that in
one or two sittings. If I ever go back and rewatch, you can gamble in the casino. Really? Where is it?
Yes, you can. Is it just the Ronin stronghold? Don't tell him that. Who told him? Where is it?
It's not on the map. Really? Um, where is it? I want to go to it. Do you like Seinfeld?
I mean, I like Seinfeld. I think was our it was good. There's a lot of really like classic
episodes. But I think curb is funnier than Seinfeld. Somebody just wanted to punch me
in the face probably. But I think it's like a more fun show to me. I don't think it's by a whole lot.
It's not astronomically better. But I think it's I laughed more times at curb than I did at Seinfeld.
And you know, I have to be really, really honest with you guys. It's the laugh track.
I can't I can't take any show seriously with a laugh track. I just I just it ruins it.
Where's this casino? You guys are actually not going to tell me where it is. I'll find it.
Sidon's palace that on here. Oh, whatever. I don't care. I'm going to go do this mission down here.
The laugh track on the stream. No, not that one. Fucking God, I don't even want to be doing this.
I can't have a laugh track. I need to like cue it up and record it and stuff.
Um, yeah, and you can't just remove a laugh track either. Like, oh, what if they did a thing where
they remastered some of these old shows? It's like the weird awkward pauses that a lot of these shows
do when there's laughing. Kind of like when any celebrity doesn't matter how big or small they are
shows up on SNL, they walk onto the stage. And there's just the clapping and cheering while they
just go. Yeah. Okay. Yep. Yeah. And everybody just sits there and stares at nothing for like
20 to 30 straight seconds. It kind of takes me away. I didn't whose door is this? Find and take
out the individual listed on the hit list. Okay. Use the dossier to figure out how to find the
target. Then use your minimap to track and kill them. Listen up. Got some people that need to be
taken care of. You take them out and there's something in it for you. Okay. And then there's
a security guard for the trailer park. Okay. Orderly the downtown hospital is a lifetime
skeeters fan. Um, okay, we're going after the mascot. Buy one of each item from the the freckle
bitches menu and he'll show up to try and sell you on some franchise opportunity. I need to
pick up King's book. Okay. So we're gonna go get this guy. This is it. Where's this taking me?
Where is freckled bitches? Oh, right here. Okay. So order everything on the menu.
I got it. All right. Order one of each thing on the menu. Wait, it's a drive through order
one of everything. This is expensive. Okay. I ordered everything. Where is he? Because he shows
up. Oh, there he is. I thought they just fucking ran him over. Um, what? How do they know it's me?
How do they know it's I'm doing anything bad? You stupid game. What's this music place? Wait,
can I buy instruments? Oh my God. Can I buy instruments? Music stores. They sell songs.
Oh, nevermind. Well, can't listen to any of these. Casino is in the hotels in Marina district,
middle top island, middle top island. Oh shit. Look at that. Somebody said, sorry guys.
I'm going to turn this 10 grand into 50 grand and I'm buying one of those cool cars.
I can't be trusted. Play some Kevin. Oh, you know what I watched? And I could not believe what I
was watching. I watched home sweet home alone. Like the home alone sort of like sequel-y,
reboot-y, sequel-y thing. Um, the movie was awful. That whole movie, the whole point of
home alone was, look it, we're going to set up a bunch of like crazy things that happen in a house
and it's like traps and stuff. The first hour of that movie was just kind of like a,
a Will Ferrell movie where they didn't have Will Ferrell as the main character
and nothing happens for like an hour and 15 minutes. That's the first movie too.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on a minute here. The first home alone was a godly tier higher than that.
And where is this thing taking me? Oh, oh fuck. That person is going to be so pissed.
There was somebody in the chat like 10, 20 minutes ago that said,
stop doing tear shit. It's cringe. And I'm like, all right. And then I just did it again.
Oh, it's the way point. Okay. So where's the casino? Is the mall? The left? Having opinions
is not a tier list. I know, but we've recently did the tier list. So it's like in my mind.
Is this illegal? I guess not. Not really. Blackjack. Can I play slots? Oh, you can,
you can only play blackjack or poker. All right. Blackjack. Let's go. Oh yeah. Let's go.
What's the max bet? Oh no. What's the max bet? There is no max bet. No, I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't. Holy. I meant to hit back, but the stupid, the stupid switch thing where the,
I was back is a, you know what I'm saying? I wanted to hit B. I wanted to hit B. I'm going
to win this hand, I think, but I wanted to go back because I wanted to save. Stan, please. Oh,
thank fucking God. Okay. I wanted to save it before I did this. 17 versus eight. Stay.
That's too bad. It's this one, right? Is it this one? Which one is it? I don't remember.
What are you talking about? I just saved it inside of there. It doesn't save your location.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry. I'm freaked out. All right. I gotta get my respect up. How do I get, I gotta
like go find like a rival gang. Are you in a rival gang? I'll be honest. When we were walking
behind this guy, I thought he had like a, I thought he had like a rooster mask on.
It doesn't give me respect. Now he wants to fight. Okay. How much is in this can? How much is in the
can? He was faking it. He was faking it. I don't have any bullets. Do I get respect for that?
I don't need very much respect. Wait. Okay. Here we go. That wasn't enough. I'm going to go do
whatever this is. That's police activity. That's not respect. No, but the bar on the top right,
the purple one. You can surf a car. Can you really do a handstand? That's so stupid. Oh,
no. Oh, God. That person's going to fly off the cliff. Oh, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop. Holy shit. I'm going to just get, I'm going to do that again. Oh my God, dude.
Go get your car cleaned. What if he gets in an accident? Holy shit. Come on. Stay in it. Oh my
God. How much respect. This would be the most watched fucking TikTok video ever. How do I not
have the respect of the whole world right now? Who's screaming? Is the guy in the car? Drive.
Come on. We need the views. I've been doing this for so long. Oh fuck. That was close. Dude,
give me the respect for the love of God. Why is it taking so long? Okay. I did it. I did it. I did
it. Oh my God. He's gone crazy. How much respect did I even get for that? I do it again. Oh shit.
Okay. Ambulance mission. Let's go. I hit right bumper to do handbrake. I'm sorry.
It's my fault. That's my fault. I'll take that. What do I do? Move up and down to provide CPR.
Um, hello? Oh my God. No. How do I do it? Why won't this work? I can't fucking see now. Thanks.
Do you see that I'm trying to help somebody? Got him. Okay. That guy has the same truck.
Go run him over immediately. No, I'm trying to get respect. All right. What's going on here?
What do I do with these? Oh, I have the shock pads. Are you serious? Oh my God. Okay. Let's go.
Let's go. Hurry up. I'm on level three right now. Get out of the way. All right. You need to be.
All right. Here we go. Got it. I'm getting money for this. Holy shit. This is actually kind of good.
SpongeBob scream. What I keep hearing is I keep hearing every flash game scream. It's that one
that goes like hurry up. Come on. Police. What? Why is everybody freaking out? They don't think
I'm supposed to be here or something. First thing's going to run over level five. Let's go. Good call.
What's the max level of really itchy? I six. I'll get there. I work quick. Go to the casino. I'm
working on it. I need money to go to the casino. Don't you understand? And I'm going to get trapped
there. I can't go there. Oh shit. Easy. Come on. Do it. This person's. Wait, what? I can't bring
the person back to life. Level seven. Go to the casino. Don't worry. I will. Where is this up top?
First on the train tracks. EMT has 10. Okay. Well, I'm almost there. What's this like movie star one?
Dude, what is in the way? I thought the person was going to punch me. That's not what I wanted.
One more. Good. A thousand bucks. This is better than doing any missions. This is not the ambulance.
I thought this was the ambulance. I'm an idiot. I'm sorry. You're not getting any respect. I'm
getting a lot of money. Look, it's white and red. It was an easy mistake and has a huge back.
Are you high? No, bro. Are you? Do not run those people over. I can't light on fire, right? Come
on. There's only one more. I got five minutes to do this shit. I'll go this way. How come the number
of victims is increasing, but you don't have to save them? That's a good question. Nothing's wrong
with the car. It's dragging on the ground. Something's wrong with the back left tire.
Are you serious? Okay. Oh no. I'm going a really dumb way. Why would you shoot at an ambulance
here? Come on. Stop it. I'm being followed. Oh fuck. I'm being followed. No, not anymore.
Oh, hold on. Let me take care of you. Where are you? Where'd she go? Oh, okay. She's in the back.
Okay. Well, I'll just bring her to the hospital. That's fine. This thing is smoking though. I have
to be careful. There's only one more level after this. I can't screw this up. She's not even on
like a gurney or anything. Oh no. Oh no. Excuse me. They know she's in here. Oh, come on. Oh no.
This is bad. I don't have time for this shit. Fucking die. What? I did it to the car? I feel
like I'm making a specific YouTube video and like a first person shooter. Like only using the one
item that's like really hard to use. It's like a side item. And why would you ever use it? Oh my
God. I saw headlights. You. I've had enough of this shit. Move. Oh man. This thing is beat the
fuck up bad. This is bad. This is going to be horrible. Is she still in the car? Is that the
problem? This is not good. I have to take care of this now. I have to take care of this right now.
Come on. There's police here now. Were you helping me? I can't tell. I don't know.
Get away from me. They just don't stop. This is far cry. What's happening? No, my ambulance.
I need that. Game crashed. Fuck. No. Oh, all that money gone. Is there a quick save button?
I can't just like save it in the middle of every single thing. Every 15 seconds.
Oh, that's sad. Getting into the car animation crashed it. It may have auto saved. Ooh. Damn it.
Please tell me there was an auto save after I completed that. Come on. Please.
I don't think so. That's very sad. It's very sad. All right. Well, we're going to have to do the
thing where every five minutes you guys freak out and spam spam. This sucks. I had like 15 grand.
Damn it. I blame the like far cry six bullshit where it's just the enemies just spawn a never
ending on top of you. I need respect and I need to get I'm going to get it somehow. What is this?
Septic Avenger. I'm kind of I'm curious. I'm curious. This game is a lot of fun though. All
right. I'm going to take a quick poll in the chat. Do you want to see this again?
But I continue the playthrough of Saints Row 2. Is having a good time? I'm having a good time.
I think I'll do it again. So I got the community kind of gentleman of the row mod. Let's do a lot
of bug fixes and help with a lot of stuff. Is there anything else I should get to help make
this more stable? Listen, we have to make this quick. What do you think? Stefan is having another
one of this war race today. And I'm not his pool boy this year. Here's a few things. Okay.
I've been trying to sell real estate in this area for a month, but no one's buying because
the property value is too high. What do you want me to do about it? My cousin runs a septic company.
I figured you could borrow one of his trucks. There's nothing more than GOTR right now.
You know, you really think people are going to want to buy elections making an official patch
to fix it. It's really hard to find cheap housing and still what was what did you say?
Spray sewage all over your targets. What the fuck? Builder has exclusive rights to new homes
in Cuenbeca and new Henkei. Use space to stop the truck construction sites of business.
Oh my god, this is ridiculous. Those construction workers have a sense of humor.
Does it have to do damage? Safety rating on this thing. Why are the cops here?
This thing. Did I use all the. Oh, I have to wait. We haven't fun yet. Okay. You feel something.
Spraying somebody's house is a shit. I think my house looks shitty anyway.
This is disgusting. I wonder if they dented the truck picture of the grill for insurance.
This is shocking. Does it just stop after we get through? Okay. How much they're willing to
pay for that property now? Okay. Now we get a spray over here. Lesson to be learned here.
Don't stand in the way of a septic truck. You love this guy. That person went nuts.
Asshole. Power washing. I wish I could see the homeowner's face.
Code it. Hey, not that much more. There's no timer either. Wait, did I fail? What? Oh, come on.
There is a timer. Oh, what the fuck? Why didn't I. There has exclusive rights to new homes in
Cuenbeca and new Henkei. Let's pay their construction sites of business. Oh, that ought to make Javier
happy. I just didn't understand what was going on. How much they're willing to pay for that property
now? There's a route meter. You have to do it all before the route ends. Ah, okay. So that's the
time. I thought that was me increasing the amount of damage. I think I'm way ahead. It couldn't
break. It would have been unsafe. I just made that house. I wish I could see the homeowner's face.
The cars are almost worth doing more than the buildings. It would have taken too much time.
Reload it. What the fuck? Construction workers have a sense of humor. This hit and run thing
really does get easier the more you do it. All right, I'll get there. You okay, buddy?
You still pull this off, right? Is that reaching? It's not. Oh, I can't reach across the street with
this shit. Come on. Some people are just inconsiderate drivers, you know? All right, I got it. There we go.
All right, so what were you saying? They said they were making a patch for this game
like 10 years later. That's crazy. There we go. Now I can do the mission.
The developer making the patch recently died of cancer. Oh my God. That's terrible.
That's awful. Well, this is really cool. This was like really, really fun. That's very saddening.
Were they working on the patch too, like officially?
Well, this is really, really cool. And the fact that somebody was like, put this together.
That's really sad, though. He was the sole reason why they started patching the game.
Wow. It's still being worked on. Yeah, that is really sad because this is really cool.
And it's just like, it makes me hear about kind of stuff like that. It just,
I'm sitting here thinking like, oh, wow, what an awesome mod. Oh, this is so cool. Oh, that guy.
Why the fuck do we still have to have that shit in the world still?
Slow us down. This is just sober. It just angers me that like this cancer still is a fucking thing.
I really hope that whenever hundreds of years from now, maybe even less than that,
this shit is just gone. And it's just very easy to get rid of. You hope that it's sooner than that.
Much sooner. There's so much new shit that these medical companies are working on now.
Yeah, you got to hope that some of this stuff actually plays out.
I didn't do it. They did. They have the game. I will. I did. I wanted the extra respect.
All right, let's do it. I can finally do that Ronin mission, right?
I thought that was a spider. It's not. In fact, I don't know what the hell this thing is.
Pick up the stop sign. It said I could. Pick it up. I want to pick it up. Cool.
I just want to test the range. All right. Well, I've launched them. All right. Where do I?
Where am I going? That way? I need a car. Save. I got it. I saved it. This is very suspicious.
Why is there an indicator over here? On this roof? When you wash in the shower,
do you let the water run down your legs soapy or do you actually wash with your hands?
I rub my hands all over my legs. Most of the soap is so when I lather up, you get like a little bit
of the squeeze, get it in your hands. Most of it goes on the crotch, right? You just like get it
all over the crotch, all over like your balls and shit. And then like it really lathers up down there
and then it goes everywhere else from there. That's the central point outward. If you're
lathering and you're starting at chest or legs or baton, no, no, no, no. That's the central
location that can go up. There's an equal distance from like your crotch to everywhere else.
Arrest that guy. Arrest him. Jesus. All right. Arrest him. Do they cuff people that aren't
a playable character? Why is there another crew? Is there another? Oh, there's another.
I thought he shot at the other cop. Whoa. I can't get on the roof. All right. Get me out of here.
I'm stuck in this area. Get me out of here. What the fuck? Your crosshair was right on him. Yeah,
I know. It's a joke. What in God's name are you playing as? This is just the character in the
game. You don't remember. You had like nostalgic glasses on. You don't remember. This is what the
character looks like. This is what the main character looks like. All right. This is like
just like a battle going on out here. You suck. You are terrible. I need a car. Okay. I actually
need a car. Please give me a car. This is getting ridiculous. All right. Now you pissed me off.
Press R1 to drift. What was that noise? How's my chair? I turned my chair a little bit and it has
like a squeaky wheel. Don't you see that you don't take a turn if somebody's driving straight.
Nothing was squeaky about that. Don't change the subject. I'll listen to it. All right. Now
you pissed me off. I leaned back in the chair and it's the lumbar support goes back and it's
really, really it needs like WD-40. You guys are just over fucking reacting as usual, right?
It's okay though. Twitch chat, right? He's a liar. Maybe. Let's go. Technically,
legal called me up and said that a Ronan bachelor party was getting too touchy feely.
The bounces have all been paid not to do dick. So if anyone is going to teach those assholes a
lesson, it's going to have to be you. Okay. Oh, I'm here. All right. I don't have any weapons.
I have pepper spray and some pistol ammo. I don't know. Can I even do this? I don't think I even
give you the ATM. Can I pick up the ATM? I only have. Oh, I have plenty of shots. All right. Who's
bad in here? I assure you I'm holding left. Oh, fuck. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Watch out. What am I fucking firing at, dude? Why is it hitting the wall? You piece of shit.
I can't believe you shot that person. Wait a second. What are you doing? You don't. Oh, well.
I guess that did not register that was happening when I first got in here.
He paid. I paid for a lap dance. So I'm going to get a lap dance. Hey, didn't expect to see me
here, did you? Freeze. That's a TV. Freeze. Oh, no. All right. Freeze, scumbag. Oh, no. No,
don't. Don't make me do this. Don't make me do this. That guy. That guy was a super powered
person. Hands in the air, scumbag. Get over here. Get over here. Why can't I not grab you?
You all right? Oh, this is not good. I'm so sorry, but I have to do this.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I don't really. I don't want. I can't even pick this
person up. Oh, my God. No. God damn it. I was trying to throw you out here. You've ruined
everything. The game got stuck. You didn't think I was going to be fucking this small, did you?
You didn't think I was this small for that. Dude, really? Honest to God. Hold on. This is very
important. I'm trying to shoot him in the finger, just like in the finger. I just need. No, it
doesn't. They can't even be interacted with. Oh, no. I'm supposed to go to the roof. Stay where you
are. All NPCs don't move. Room back to A. Wait, did I go in here yet? Stairs. I got to get to the
roof. All right. Take him up from up here. Oh, a CD. How am I supposed to do this? CDs. Just shoot
them from. I don't know. I have a pistol. Is there a weapon up here I can get? Oh, my fucking God.
That hurts. Ouch. First try to talk to me. That was weird. Oh, you have a hostage. I'm really glad
I actually didn't shoot you. I can't hit them. They cannot be injured. Look at this. Oh, no.
Oh, cops are here. Does this count if I don't kill them? I can fall off this. I got to be careful.
Where is this person? Over there. Okay, I see. Oh, no. I'm on roller skates.
This is not the place to be on roller skates. I'm okay. Easy. Don't fall off. Oh, my goodness.
This person is so good. All jokes are writing themselves. I have not fallen off yet.
I can't even see this person. Is the tree shooting at me? I don't. Where are they?
That's it, right? Okay, I got it. Oh, don't do that. A thousand bucks. 500 bucks a day.
That's saved, right? That counts. Does that count? I got the screen, right? Okay. Good. Thank God.
Game did not crash. I'm fine. I need a little bit more respect. Let's do another race.
Let's try to get the gold medal here. It's hard to even see. I can try to screw with them.
I like to smash it on the brakes. I was trying to get somebody to fly out the windshield.
What a dummy. You're out. The person's attached to their car. I hit the rock. I'm the one person
that hits the rock. Get out of here. Excuse me. I had to kill the person back there. I should have
just killed that person and got on the road. All right. That's a gold medal. Nice. How much is that?
A thousand dollars. This person's right here. Who is this? Are they in this building in front of me?
Oh, they're in the hospital. Right. Is that person right there? Is this guy right here?
I got to get him alone, right? Shock paddles. I don't have shock paddles anymore. If I get the
plant. Take him out. Take him out. Did I get him? All right. I've had enough. He's spraying your own.
You fucking moron. Take a gun out. You fucking idiot. Like really? No. Don't you... Everybody
stay calm. That was a really bad guy. I'm an undercover agent. I'm an undercover police agent,
FBI officer. This guy was very bad. He was... I don't even know what he was doing. He was doing
something. Nobody paid me a lot of money to do that. Have a nice day. David again? What? All
right. Now... What should I do? What's this? Oh, this is for sale. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to spend some money. I want to get some new cool clothes. We're going to get some really like
snappy nice suits and stuff and maybe some weapons. Yeah. Brass knuckle. What's a good weapon shop?
Go to the casino. No, I'm not doing that. Go to the mall. The good clothes shop is near the bridge.
Something down here. I'll try it. Casino will sell you a suit. I don't think they have your size.
Hostage diversion? You drive at high speeds to evade the cops until your hostage breaks down
and pays you. What? There's so much shit to do in this game. I have two hostages? Drive really fast
for a minute. Where's this? I don't understand where... I want to go to the clothing store.
I don't care about that mission right now. Oh, it's because it's in the back. I think they got
away. Okay. I want to buy some nice clothes. No, I don't. I want eyes. Human eyes. Okay. Well,
I mean, I have to do that. That's so stupid. How about a knitted cap? This is not like suits.
These are different couch fabrics. Where'd you guys bring me to? Go to the suits category? Oh,
outfits. The game fucking crashed. Of course it did. He fell for it? Oh well. I don't know
what I just did. Hopefully it's the right one. 34. It's this one. Outfits always crash the game.
Suit category outright crashes your game every time when previewed. Oh well, that's good to know.
I can do the mission. For a second I didn't even know what that was on the couch. I didn't even
know it was me. I was trying to figure out what it was the first two seconds.
You're one of those deflated people from the anti-smoking ads? Musinex booger person.
Doesn't he have an English accent too? Isn't he like, oh Roy, I'm going to get under your
fucking toenails. Oh no, Musinex is there. I'm going to fuck up your lungs. Doesn't he have
a British accent? Buy an expensive car. Holy shit. Whatever. Whoa, that's cool.
Cool. How much is it? Except I only have $13,900 as a net worth total. So hopefully it's under that.
Did I buy it? I'm going a different route. See? They're coming down that road right now. Look
at that. 500 IQ play. Good stuff. Don't bait me with that bullshit. I'm not going that way.
Told you it was going to work. Eventually. Hello, I brought you a car.
The wheel's still spinning. Oh no. You idiot. You absolute idiot. And I'm talking about both
people on the screen right now. Because what that did, unfortunately, is it wedged it into the car.
I would have been able to go, but the bike is now here and that is a huge problem. This is very bad.
Hello? Settle down. All right. I got to knock that. Wait. Another one crashed. What are they doing?
Okay. You guys got to settle the fuck down. All right. I got back in the car. Good. Let's go.
Come on, dude. Why? Why did you have to do this? Get the fuck away from me, dude.
This is stuck now. I think I just made it worse somehow. How did I make this worse?
I'm like a different character that just came around. What?
Leave me alone. The game's going to crash. I know it. They're going to keep piling in here.
I can't even get up. Eventually, they'll do that enough times where I'll be able to get out of here,
I think. Can I use all their bodies and all their crushed rubble to drive over it? Oh no. I wonder
what's going to happen. I hear a motorcycle. I wonder if the motorcycle is coming this way.
Oh, that was a cop. Oh dear. How could it possibly still not be able to move?
This is not possible. Actually, it's impossible. Give me a car. Give me another car. Will you just
leave already? Get up. Can I please just get up and leave? There's no reason for you to be here.
Just get out of here. Go this way. Just go that way. I didn't even do anything illegal. Oh my god.
I did. Did I? Yes. What the fuck? There's so many motorcycles under here. It's going to be
impossible to get this to move. Idiots. This is not accomplishing anything. I'm just going to
be in... It's going to get this stuck. I need to take the L? Yeah, I think I do. Did somebody else
crash? Where did you come from? I don't know what else to do. Hold L2. Start with grenade. Nothing
is going to work. All right. Stop that. I have to restart the mission. Maybe it'll despawn. Get
out of the car. I think the wheels are touching something. The wheels are touching something.
Fuck this mission. I'll just redo it. What? Okay. Retry from... I don't know what that is. So,
I'm going to press backspace. Is it enter? Enter, right? Thank god. Let's go. I thought that was a
ramp.
Thank you. The special AR-50 fires grenades using right click. Very cool. That's really cool. What
is right click again? It's left trigger. It doesn't fail the mission, right? Don't even think about
going to that same spot. Thank god. Protect the... This blew the car up. I don't know why I did that.
I don't understand. I don't know what happened. I'm so childish. I just am fucking... I'm childish.
I'm a child and I have to agree. Jesus. You're a worse driver than I am. Look where my legs are.
My knees are so high. There's not much to protect us from. What am I protecting us from? One person?
Don't go that way. Okay. I tried to shoot the car in front of us.
We're traveling fast so it's going to go back and hit us. We drove into it. There's nothing to even
fire at so I'm just getting bored. There's nobody after us. I don't even know what they're talking
about. Oh my god. Were they all stacked in one spot? Did they all spawn there? Holy shit. Oh my
goodness. I don't think it's supposed to be like this. Jesus Christ. You think that has something
to do with the fact that they all were stuck in that little ravine and then it spawned them all
in the same place? If you crash anymore this is going to start to... It's not going to be my fault
if you do that. You crash again. This is on fire. No. It's gonna... Please be careful. We're very close.
Okay. Thank god. Remember my mom has a dog
with a sister? Shout out the dog. Shout out to your sister's dog. I think I misinterpreted that.
Somebody has an important question. How do I explain the word sus? No, that's not my thing.
Okay cool. 15 grand. Weapon time. How have I not tried to do this yet? This is incredibly
surprising that I haven't done this. It works. Holy shit. Okay that's really... Oh I need to go
get guns right? I don't want heat going in here. What the hell? Oh I thought I just shot electricity
out of the gun. What? You're good. All right. Why are people like dead in here? Okay you can purchase
melee weapons. Wait a minute. Oh no. Holy shit. Okay I definitely want this. I want the sludge
hammer. I want the baseball bat. Okay cool. How do I switch between them? You can only have one
melee weapon at a time. Can I trade this in? What a bad time to do that. What are you looking at?
Eat eat eat. Quick quick quick. Oh a titan. Right through. Perfect fit. There's no way you got
through that too. Three stars. Sorry I got three stars. I'll um damn it. Just go. Nobody is just
unloading the whole clip. Are they still shooting? Who's still firing? I can't tell who's shooting.
Who's still firing? Can I get in the bed? Leave me alone. I thought that was gonna hurt me. I need
to get some more respect. I need... Wait wait wait wait wait. Hold on a minute. I need to... That's a
store. Okay this place is called Friendly Fire. I want to go there. Nice iPad. I like iPads. Really
guys. All at once now right? You gotta go with the skid. Are you actually arresting me? Oh fine. I
don't care. No way. The Andes. I want to do the surf thing. Can I not do the surf thing here?
Get up there. It looks like I'm stuck in the windshield. Okay enough playing around. Next
person that runs me over. Freeze. I mean I have I have to do something with this right? Can I buy a
hot dog? I've just run. I didn't kill him. He's fine. All right we gotta get the hot dog to fight
somebody. Follow me. No don't run. Don't run. You just wanted to fight me. This is bullshit. I wanted
you to... You can be the hot dog if you want. Am I actually in trouble again? All right get me over
there. I need some weapons. Remember you're a big bully only in GTA games. I swear I'm a very sweet
sweet boy outside of Grand Theft Auto third-person games. I promise. I'm a nice young man outside of
this. I didn't even see those people. This is far away. Geez. You get respect for bailing out of the
car. Hi. Can I take the safe? Ooh all right. Pistols. SMG. Shotguns. Rifles. Special. Throne.
All right I want this thing. This is a 12 gauge. I'm buying it. Okay. You have this weapon. Shotgun
ammo. I have the... Okay I already have this. Holy shit. Hell yeah. Magnum. I want it. Bad.
I'm wasting so much money. Check the special weapon cache. What does that mean? Oh I think I'm
gonna do pistol. All right. I don't want to spend all my money. Wait. Weapon cache. Spacebar.
Bring to weapons cache. Oh I see what you mean. Okay. Dual 44 shepherds. Are you kidding me?
Wow. Okay. Double 12 gauge. I want the sledgehammer. This is insane. All right. I definitely want to
put this on. All right cool. Let's go. That's what I'm talking about. Oh that's sick. All right. Now
give me all the money in the register. Get to the safe. Thank you. Wait this is not the thing. I
didn't want to fucking kill that lady. Honest to god damn god. I didn't want to do that. I actually
didn't want to throw it at her and kill her. And now I don't know what I'm doing. I'm gonna test
this on you. It works. Why did I do that? Pick up the safe. No. And then I threw... I just wanted
to get rid of it. What a dumb ass. These things are powerful. Holy shit. Why is it telling me to go
this way? What the hell? There's only 30 seconds here. This is gonna be tricky. All right. The
first thing that somebody says is what I'm gonna eat tonight. What is it? I haven't. I didn't even
look at the chat. I have no idea what you wrote. Dude this one is really hard. I'm not sure I'm
gonna be able to do this one. Yeah I can't do this one. Holy shit. I got 25 more seconds. I'm an idiot.
All right. I saw a taco. Sounds pretty good. Don't follow the GPS you donkey. No. Stop it.
What are you doing? No. Not my Wellington. Three, two, one.
I got it. I'm not gonna make it. I wasn't getting seconds added. That was horseshit. Stuff cross
pizza. I'm just testing to see if it works. I have not had Popeyes yet. That's a good idea.
All right. Let's do a mission. What time is it? Oh shit. It's been a long time. I'm having a good
time. This is really fun. All right. I'm gonna go to the casino. This is a pretty long drive from
here. We'll play this again. I'll probably be live at some point in the middle of the week.
Like Wednesday or Thursday. Keep an eye on the sus. End of the stream voice? Almost. Not quite.
How do you feel about the asbestos allegations? That I've been like eating it? What are you talking
about? All right. Here we go. The rain makes the game lag so much. There were people waiting for
me down that alleyway. Don't let her get out. Did I get it? I got it. Okay. She just exploded I think.
Oh man. I didn't do it. Okay. I want to try this. I want to get this right.
I want to see how you do this. All right. Follow to the safe. Go to the safe. What's going on?
Keep your cursor on its head. Will you go to the safe? All right. There are raccoons in the trash
outside. They're gonna get me. Go to the safe. All right. Open it up. You all right? Okay. Thank
you. Is there money in there? Oh, this is a cheeseburger. All right. Oh, nope. Do I know you?
Oops. You're a psycho. This Saints Row 2. We're not playing Putt-Putt's Great Adventure.
I'm not playing like a math game. I thought I was going to fall through the middle.
Oh my god. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I gotta get the camera. Is there a camera? I swear to god there's a camera in this game.
Isn't there? Is there a camera? Is there a camera? Can I get in? Sure. I guess that is fine that it
happened like that. Who drove the car? A drift. Oh, MonkaW. I can do that one better, I think.
There's a better way to say that. Instead of like MonkaW. I get kind of caught up a little bit.
It should be like MonkaW. No, it's gotta be harder, right? Because MonkaW is much closer
and much more like holy shit. It'll be way more force behind it. I don't know why I thought I
could climb that. All right. Where's the casino? Let me in. Oh, that's not the entrance.
Wrong one. Is it this side? Yeah, save the game for sure. That sounds, yeah, MonkaW sounds too
forced. You're right. No, I completely agree. Where is this building? Where is it? Isn't it this one?
There it is. Oh, here's every single mukbang video you've ever watched in your entire life.
That's a lot. That's a lot of what the fuck, dude. Excellent. All right, it's fucking nine thousand
dollars. 10, 20. Oh, yo, yo. Something's wrong with me. I swear to God. 13, edit. Hey.
All right. Shut up. I've had enough of that behavior. It's like, just stop it. There's no
reason to be doing that. Like, why? This is so bad. Okay. Let me get this right here. 18. Oh,
it means you're going to have 20. You fucking idiot. How did I know? Anytime you play blackjack,
you always assume the dealer has a 10 underneath. So you just assume that that is a 10 that's not
shown. What a dog shit hit. I have zero dollars now. I lose. The game crashed. That's probably
a good place to stop, I think. Right at the exact pretty much six hour mark. That was really fun,
though. We'll do that again. Maybe we'll do that again at some point in the middle of the week.
Still trying to keep the twice a week thing going. You can always pretty much assume there'll be
something on the weekend and then something somewhere in the middle of the week. Somewhere
like Wednesday, Thursday, and like maybe Sunday. I was thinking about maybe doing Saturday, Sunday,
but I don't want that much time to pass. Because back three or four months ago, I was doing
Saturday to Saturday, essentially. I want to really try to get on that one stream every four
or five days rather than one stream every seven or eight days. We're going to play Saints Row 2
again because I'm very invested. That was a lot of fun. Hope you enjoyed yourselves. Thanks for
watching. Here are all the subs today. Thanks, everybody. I no longer call out that many subs
anymore, but I still really appreciate it. Yeah, we'll see what's going on in the middle of the
week. I'm either going to play this again or maybe we'll do some co-op stuff. We'll see. I just live
life by the wings or something. Whatever it is. I just wing it. We'll see you again. Keep an eye on
the sauce over the next few days. We are going to... Let's raid Ludwig. I want you to tell Ludwig
we listened to the Christmas album and I thought it was phenomenal. I want you to make sure you
tell Ludwig that it was really good. And don't... Yeah, don't be stupid. It actually was really good.
Like, I'm jealous at the musical talent. I really am. I didn't even know he could sing. They can
say... Like, that's cutie, right? As well. They can sing. Are you guys still... Are you grounded?
Yeah, you are, because I saw that first part when I raided Vinnie. And you still did it. You're
grounded. All of you. Every single person collectively. All right. I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching, as always. Go say the Christmas album is fire. And I will see you guys in
probably a few days. Keep an eye on the sauce. Take care of yourselves. Have a great night.
Get this to 8K. I want an 8K raid. Influencer Andy. You've got 10 seconds to do it. At least 7,500.
Come on. I know you guys can do it. Come on. I know you can. There's still so many of you that
haven't done it. I did my part. Yeah, thank you. Irma, you look kind of like Ernest.