You la. You lose. You laugh. You fuckin lose. You la. You lose. You laugh. You fuckin lose.
Ey, what's up. You really late? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll talk about it,
I'll explain what's going on here. Let me make a tweet, give me a sec. Okay. You laugh. You lose.
You laugh. You fuckin lose. You laugh. You lose. You laugh. You fuckin lose.
Sorry, something wrong with me. Hi
So you're probably looking for Monster Rancher 2. Sorry that that's not here today. I
Saw that house flipper had a major
update added a bunch of stuff in a while it's been a year I think since I've played it and
As you all know if you're been a watcher of the stream for a long time a house flipper DLC automatically turns the stream on
so
That's just what's gonna happen
But we can play it. It's called luxury DLC. I guess it's huge houses
I don't know how long is it gonna take me but
It's advertised to be some of the biggest houses. They've ever put in the game. I don't know
He hates Monster Rancher. What's your opinion on Alaska's beautiful landscape? Oh, well
Flawed watchers skip don't skip any of my content ever
Let's be busy. You know got something to do
Let me turn my fan on back here
By the way, I went through the VOD some of the clips and timestamps
Yeah, I've when I saw people randomly writing about my sweaty armpits. I
Didn't I was like, what are they? Why are they saying that?
That was some of the worst that I've ever seen
Somebody threw water at me. There's a you look what you say you laugh you lose. That was toxic
Humor is so subjective. I'm surprised that even five of you are here
It's one of those things where people just don't think certain things are funny
they think certain things are annoying or stupid and some people think things are
Dumb some people think those dumb things are funny. Some people think the funny thing is
childish
Vodwatchers skip everything you wouldn't open up a VOD if you were gonna skip everything
What you should say is VOD why I'm not gonna say that because people do it as a joke
Wait, all right. Let me let's talk about we're gonna do a content update here. It's content update part of the stream
first of all
Can you even say hi? I?
Invited you over for dinner and you you push the door open you did a little light knock
I open the door the door pushes with your hand
Where's Monster Rancher? How about like how are my two kids?
Yeah, you know Jason and Darcy, you're not gonna talk about my twins. You know, they're they're six
so
Monster Rancher, how could you say something like that? It's one of the best games ever made you have two kids
I thought that that was common knowledge
This is surprising to a lot of you somehow
Interesting. Okay, so let's do a content update
You haven't been paying attention. Wait, how do you you don't think what?
How do you not know this?
alright, so
Content update I got some stuff to talk to you about today. We play house slipper DLC luxury DLC. I'm in a weird mood today
It's a full moon one of those big orange moons
So we're gonna play that in a couple of days. I'm gonna do a Christmas Eve stream
That's right. The first time in a long time. I will be live on Christmas Eve and that stream is going to be a
compilation of itch EO games and I get a bunch of them if you have any of your favorites
Stuff that you've never played because I've never done that before
We're talking the weird creepy scary ones to the funny ones the weird ones
I'm gonna put together a little compilation and play them
so if you have
Recommendations put them in the recommended channel because I'm gonna go through that and I'm gonna just get a bunch of them
But make sure but the same rules apply to that recommended channel. Don't just go in there and just put bullshit in it
That's Christmas Eve a few days later after the holidays on the 27th. I hope you're writing these now
We're going to play organ trader
space
stocks game
It's got a long title. I'm gonna play the or that's been recommended so many times people just want to play it so bad
It's a game where you trade alien organs
And it's like a stock market simulator
People said I it I've got like 30 recommend as just about it and they're like you need to fucking play this game Jeremy
Please so we're gonna do that on the 27th and then on the 31st. I'm still hopeful
There will be the New Year's Eve stream with the awards and the rumble pretty cool sounds fun
You will have that poll to be able to start voting the nominees this year. There were so many
It's a process to narrow this all down
So once we do that and that's done with on Christmas Eve. I am hoping that after my stream
I will be able to tweet out or talk about on Christmas Eve
Go vote because the poll is ready and then obviously on New Year's we'll do the rumble and then
We're going back to VR the first couple weeks of January
Maybe the second or third week of January somewhere in there
I'm gonna set the whole VR head set up again, and we're gonna do a couple weeks of VR missed a lot of stuff
I know don't get concerned. I know a lot of people just went. Oh, but but what about I'm gonna be fine
I'm gonna do some seated VR
upstanding VR sprinkled in I promise I won't puke and
Then I don't have a hard date for you, but I want you all to be aware of it
There's a big stream coming at the end of January that last week of January keep your eye keep your eyes peeled
For me to announce a hard date. It is not baseball by the way, and then
Baseball is gonna be probably somewhere in March
But there is a big stream that I've not talked about that's at that same level. It's gonna be the end of January
I can't wait getting any hints. I can't fucking wait for that stream. So there's your
Content plan the next month or two and sprinkled in there sprinkled in there be a few more announcements
sprinkled in there
Still owe us a catboy stream you more concerned about the catboy costume not being put on or more concerned about like the
1.7 billion dollars I still owe you you got to pick priorities here. All right, let's play house flipper
Yeah, I just want to give it kind of an update on how things are gonna go
I'm very excited especially for this stream in January. I think it's gonna be fucking hilarious
I hope it is it sounds like it could be fun. I think it's gonna be funny
We'll see though because it's not for me to decide
Yeah, I might think that but that's for you to decide. So well, I hope that ends up being the case
All right, let's go house flipper. The DLC is here make a debt payment program
There you go. So if you have never played house flipper go get it right now
I had to kind of redo some stuff. You notice I have a half a million dollars
That's because I cheated as I haven't opened this game in a year and to do a lot of the luxury stuff
I think you need a lot of money. I also missing a tool
I don't know what it is. So I know you'd like to make this DLC fun
I believe you need to have some money because we did this one, but I don't have this saved
You can't even hear anything. There we go. You sound weird today
Okay, all right luxury flipper here we go
So apparently how this works is we have to do like jobs for luxury clients
It looks like the Sims and then I think I don't know. I think we can buy real estate out here
You sound fucked up. I was
Listen
Wiggle your treble in your bass on your computer. When's the last time you did that?
Why does everybody blame me for me sounding weird?
Have you ever changed the dial on the bass on your on your equalizer?
You might be like negative eight bass right now and be like everything sounds like shit
How come the whole world sounds like shit? All right, so this is the first client you sound the same. I know I'm just giving that person shit
I
Changed the bass on your vocal cords. Okay. I mean, you know what? I've never tried
Let me see how low I can actually get without making like a funny joke voice
Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey
Hey, everybody. How are you? Hey everybody. How are you doing? I'm doing really good. How are you? That's not I mean
That's kind of weird sounding it kind of got jokey there at the end. Yeah. Hey, hey
How do you do a low voice without being jokey it's impossible
Okay, I'm on a boat Jimmy took advantage of his father's absence and threw a huge party on the family's yacht
He had a great time with his friends which can be proved by the equally great mess
They left behind now the young social butterfly needs someone willing to clean it up before his father's return. Fortunately a world's a world tour
He's currently on will go for another week or so. We have to clean somebody's boat. Okay
Did these these freak me out by the way, I would never want to live on something like this
See the windows down there. Don't you feel like if like your PC was down there
You're just playing like fortnight and all of a sudden. Thank you. What if like water got in?
His voice acting
I feel like you'd open up the fucking window and a big wave would crash
And hit the window go in the window and like fry your computer and like electrocute you
Why is this voice actor
Am I timed
How much time do I have all pizza on the bed you must you must be 20 pizza on the bed
Why would anyone ever do that
I don't want to get in trouble. I know you can save my skin
I have kind of a messy desk and even back when I was like 18 19 20 21
Yeah, I had a kind of a messy room, but I would never put a cooked pizza out of the box in my bed
Who would do something like that? All right, dude, you got to do this. I have a thousand dollars. It's like a new area
Oh, I thought I could drive around. Okay, so I have to clean this boat. By the way, I have like the Santa pack
It was free. I think I don't know if that's accurate. All right, which I just clean the boat was a damage
Okay, why don't you take out containers a bunch of a bunch of the baby trays like to separate baby food
These are all fine bed between two pizzas is a calzone
Nobody does this and if you do no
Nobody has a party like this if I went to a party and it looked like wait
You can now change the stairs in some houses
What do you mean wrong? Would you sit at this fucking table? There's bird shit all over here. Somehow. I don't even know how
I'm not gonna sit at this table. I'm okay
Maybe I would come to this party, but I would be standing and I'm gonna wear
Those little booties that like the calm cast guy puts on his shoes before he comes in your house
I'm literally gonna wear those. All right, let's clean it up. It's done. Oh, it's Santa to calm cast guy
All right looks fine. Can I get the stain? All right, I got the stain
It's probably gonna take like 10 minutes. Not even I love this game
I I want to talk to like a psychologist because it has to be a reason it has to be I
Don't like doing this shit in real life. I hate it
Why do I think this is cool doing this in this pretend world? It doesn't matter thousand dollar budget
Does anybody and anybody like in chat kind of a psychologist? Let's get okay. I'll trash first just close
It's a good stream idea
No, I
Don't know. Ooh
Psychologists here. It's because I missed it the chat went too fast
You could have just like maybe internalize a lot of things, but it will it would just be real life
Those cans I love it. So relaxing. It's broken. All right, this shit's broken. All right, sell the electric cooker
Oh, I don't sell this too. Well, they want a glass mini fridge. Oh
Okay with the plates get these out of here sell the boat
I
Okay, do you can you do an open house on a boat do they do that?
I feel like that would be so interesting. No, it's a boat. But you know what I mean, though
I would just go to the boat open house because I've never really been on a boat before
Well, hold on. That's not true. I've been on a boat before I've been on
Okay, there's like the Boston Harbor cruise thing count
Does that count with like the tourist thing where you go go do the harbor cruise?
I guess it's it's like a 30 40 minute thing. I think it's huge though. It's not like this and I die
All right. This is almost done. That looks great. Get that dirt off that seat
What did you did? Did you partake in the Boston Tea Party? I don't know
Yeah, you dude. No, but like our collective like probably fucking how many people here?
13,000 people right now. I bet you're like if we mushed up like 5,000 of our DNA
It probably was like our great-great-great uncle or something. Can I sleep on this way to use?
Ah, this is kind of nice. You don't need a psychologist to realize that you are zonked
You're not gonna go to a psychologist and ask the psychologist if I'm high what a waste of time
All right, that looks good. There's some piece of dirt right here. Whatever it is. Whoa, you can open this see
I don't want windows. No, I don't like this if there's a high wave or something
It's gonna just crash in and ruin your fucking like
Mario Party session you're having I don't think I'd want to do that
Is it weird that I would want my whole boat to have no windows?
Whatever like wood or concrete or something. I wouldn't want any windows that you want a submarine
I think a submarine would be better. I want the whole thing in enclosed
I want an enclosed space. Look at all this shit. Did they eat up here for like three months?
I feel like they were shitting in these bags submarine Andy. Okay, I will
This is cool, right? This is cool, but it's like that only cool thing
I think about when I think about like a boat. I like I like the water. They're not paying me to redecorate. That's good
You're a fucking landlubber. What did you say? Say that again? You're a landlubber. Somebody said landlubber
Why is it called landlubber? Is that because it's landlubber? Is it actually what that is?
Because sailors wait, what what did I think it was? I don't landlubber
What was it? I don't know. I didn't think it was landlubber
I thought it meant like like dweller like land dweller like a lubber
They done to my father's anchor my friends must have played with it at the party and now it's ruined
Is this me but I have to renovate this thing you have some tools for that, right?
No, you're gonna bring this like a clog Smith. I can't do this
What here's a segment of the furniture to work on first of a renovation is always cleaning the surface of the furniture
Every material requires a specific tool. This is wood. Oh shit. Oh
Cool I like this it must be cleaned on every side. Why don't you do it?
Dad cannot notice any trace of those damages or I'm a goner
Is dad gonna notice that I have sanded this down to all the way where the stain is gone
I'm sure he's gonna notice like the the four or five centimeters thinner that this just got
Hold right mouse button to move the camera. I thought these things were made out of steel not wood wouldn't this thing just float
What good is a wooden anchor? Am I crazy? What does this made? Is this not made of wood? Oh, this is a decoration
Okay, I thought this is the anchor. I was like, what the fuck are you doing with this?
It's not gonna stop like a forty thousand pound boat. They didn't know here
Okay, first cue. Ooh
We got it. What happened to the color?
Can you fix it? Is it imply that he's standing right behind me?
All right, what color should do about how about blue?
Wait ocean deep. No, no. Ooh
one of these
Iroko no height and white no this one. It's kind of looks like Poseidon's deceptor now
It's not even an anchor
All right, spin it. It still works though. It could be whatever. It's a baby toy
It is a baby toy that looks good flip it this feels nice though
I could smell this paint you shouldn't be doing that. But you know what I mean that like fresh it just was painted smell
Did I miss anything this part? What is this? All right
This is like the part of the flute like the wood piece you put in your mouth
Because we could saliva and like soggy and dirty. It's one of the reasons why I never played an instrument
Especially one of the wood instrument no fucking way. These things are grosser than retainers. Yuck. Okay, so that part's blue
This kind of blue. No, I don't know just ocean blue
That's blue and brown looks good. You how was close
Looks like new to me now and my eyesight is way better than my dad
Thank you. It's your own saliva
Okay, I put the renovated furniture wherever it will present itself the best just put it like right here
I mean is this satanic if I do it like this is that bad to do this is like freaked me out
It's just anti Poseidonic, I kind of want it like this. No, it sucks over there. I have to put it here
I want to put it somewhere else like on the bar right in front of the bar and go here stupid
Replace comment on the bug you swallow. Does it taste better? I said that eight years ago. I said eight
Yeah, I didn't just didn't just happen last weekend. I don't even remember what you're talking about
Stop going back and ratioing old tweets of mine. I don't even know what the fuck you're talking about
You started about a tweet from like 2012. I think looks good there, but you remembered no
I didn't you know reason why I remembered is because I got ratioed last week from a tweet. I made in 2012
Okay, now what? Oh, we're gonna buy the mini fridge. Okay glass mini fridge. Let's do this one a
Lay out blacks good. She's the mini fridge go bro right here. Thanks to the captain's quarters
Is it weird that every time I just see a mini fridge all I can think about is Red Bull
The only thing I can think of is an oven. Oh, let's look. I don't care. It's not my house. It gives a shit
Okay, remove trash. Where's the trash? Oh, this job has to be a hundred percent
Alright, when do I get to have my mansion? Just try to get like I just want like seagulls to come in her and shit
All over their house. Uh, is it up? Where is this? I can't reach it. Okay, got it
Oh, it's in your probably in your dirty bedroom. Yeah, bro. Come on, man, bro
Really? Bro, what do you got under the bed? Come on. It's on the bed. Do I have to make the bed? No
Alright, that looks fine
Close this up. I don't think I've ever met anyone with more plastic bags than you get a canvas bag
It's way easier. You can put way more shit in it
You get one of those canvas bags that has like the kind of flat bottom
Instead of look here's that you want to here you go
You guys want here's a tactic ready for a tip when you go to the grocery store and you get like
12 plastic bags that you have to do like a fucking Olympic sport to take into your house
If you're strong enough to get you know what I'm saying like one bag on pinky one bag on ring finger one bag on middle finger
One bag on index finger if you can do that
Just get a canvas bag with the flat bottom
You can put all four bags worth of shit in that one bag and you can just carry that
I'm telling you don't you start doing that you don't have to do that weird awkward trip anywhere where
Some of the bags are heavier and you one of them is too heavy on the pinky and everything nice painting
Wait, this doesn't look right to me. I'm rearranging this. It's better make the bed. That was easy
Watch that watch they're gonna be a Bible in one of these. It's a broken mirror. I'm stuck
Fuck I stuck. All right, whatever who cares. Where's this broken mirror in here? What's broken? This is a mirror. What is this?
That's weird. I don't like that. Where's this broken mirror? So Oh sell it but it's not broken
You guys see I don't see a broken mirror. There's not even a mirror. This is like
Acoustic foam what that doesn't look like a mirror. All right now is this from done? Yeah, this one's done
How about this one? This is done. All right, close that up. This is done other side another staircase
There is do you give Otto forehead kisses? Yes, of course I do. Whoa, are you eating? What is that?
Was that what was that?
Vendor I was gonna throw this trophy out the window. There's the pizza didn't even eat one slice
Not one single slice has been eaten. All right, we're gonna get some voice acting here. He's gonna be like thanks, man
I mean if you got a home gym, you're an automatic asshole. I'm gonna have to say it. I'm sorry
I'm kidding. God
You're my hates healthy people. It's just it's coming with me. Do they care what I do with this
Let me put this out on the dock so people can watch me work out
Wasn't that you ten years ago? I didn't have a room in my house
That was my exercise room. My exercise room was my bedroom. My bedroom was my office
My office was my gaming den and my gaming dent was where I hung out with my friends and where I hung out with my friends
It was all the same room. It was very efficient that room fucking stinks. By the way, it smells in that room
I had to clean it once a week. All right, okay. I gotta stop like making stories up. All right, it's
Stupid why would I want you guys to think that I'm like disgusting? I don't know
It's some type of weird defense mechanism where if I tell you I'm gross and weird then like you can't do it
You can't say it has to be I what am I missing? Oh, these are is this dirty. Is that part of the art?
All right, this is clean. So what's left? There's nothing left
And if it's one bag of Fritos that I'm sorry, you can fuck right off
Oh was just the end of the movie where there's a there is the bag of Doritos on the ground and the door opens and it's
The mom and dad and it's the the car is coming down the road and they've almost got the whole house clean and right when
The door opens foot slides back under the couch and they always make a comment
I have really clean the houses and they kind of see they kind of see the kid or whatever
Slide the foot and they go, huh, let's wait for one of those movies for them to walk in be like, huh?
Whoa, wow, you really what is that? Is that lilac? We don't have lilac in this house. You motherfucker
We're all the kids
You're grounded. Wait Rick and Morty did that. Oh god. Damn it. Where's this last piece?
Diary of a wimpy kid did that? No, I'm late. You're a psycho or I would yeah
No, if I knew that that was happening, I would play along I'd walk up to shit, right? Yeah
Let me turn the camera for this. This is I I would walk up to like the windowsill
Just kind of be like, oh, like here's the windowsill. I'd be like, you know, I really have to clean this place
Where do I not really I'm not naked. I'm right here. I would walk around it like smell
I'd like I'd go to like the door handle and I'd be like, oh, yeah, that is clean
I did I remember cleaning that when I remember cleaning that son. Yeah, I did with fresh lemon
I wouldn't talk about it. I need to vacuum like weeks later
I would bring up stuff that I that I had cleaned in the house
Because in those they do really weird shit in those movies. They'll like power wash the barrels
I haven't done that in a long time. Oh you power wash the fucking barrels
Okay, I don't I've no idea this last piece dirt is trash barrels the barrels
How what do you guys call them the trash receptacles? What do you call them?
Where is this piece of dirt the bins the cans the barrels? I'm sorry. We're from different countries
Yes, there are different countries on earth and we call things different things. There's a booger on my hand
And I hope you didn't see it
There's a literal booger on my hand
I don't even know how it got there, but it's there and I it may have been on camera
That's why I have no idea why what happened where somebody just tell me so son
Where's that last piece of dirt that you're trying to hide from me? It's on the table. Yeah, I'd be like, honey
You know what?
The house is so clean. I remember cleaning this house before we left. Let's eat off the floor today
Yeah, I would sit down on the floor. Let's eat off the floor, right? Right son. Where is it?
The mini-map will show it. Yeah, I'm looking I can't see it
Dad dad to like make his point ends up like getting like a fucking bacterial infection from like eating a sandwich off the ground
It's the solo cups on the table
It's not dude, bro. Why would you get rid of the solo cups dude change the stairs?
I'm not buying this for this person. No. All right, let's go. I did it. I got 2900 bucks. Oh
Oh
Here I'm not watching the stream right now
You hold on do something funny so then somebody can clip it so I can see it nothing. Yeah, what changed?
It's still is a
The Sun went higher during the day. That's all that changed. This is my ass
Alright to be fair. I had to load a new save
Morning a mole has dug its way
I don't whatever complete each job to unlock new houses for purchase so I can buy the boat now
Let me see. How much is the boat?
$563,000
What why would I ever want that I could buy like a double cheeseburger at McDonald's for 563 years straight
Times wait, that's wrong. I get I've said that rung
I could buy a McDouble for McDonald's every single day for
563 hundred years or something like that. I don't know math is not my strong suit. Alright, what's the next one?
I'm not buying that. I don't want that fucking dumb thing
Okay, doesn't everybody say that owns a boat. It's just it's just a hole that you throw money into
If that's what people say about a boat and then people say oh when you own a home
I'll be aware when you own a home. You got all kinds of maintenance. You got to do a boat and a home combined
seems
Like a lot of money to just put in and throw away at that point
This should be like just a mechanic that lives in the house with you. Okay a new chapter
Moonrise Bay welcomes Hiroshi and Yuna with open arms this young couple of computer engineers
Who both got jobs in town had been looking for a place to make their own
Help came from friends in the area who offered to sell them their unprofitable printing studio
Now the newcomers just need a little more help with changing into a living space. All right, let me help you
I'll never forget when you pushed me off that cruise ship in 98 as a joke
I've heard you're just starting in Moonrise Bay, but it shouldn't be a problem. So are we hey
For $2,500 can you make a new house inside of the house? That's here now great
They're big fans of this game
More about it when you're done with the cleaning. Wait, so I have to clean and then I have to do a new chapter
What button do I press? I?
Get out of here. Oh, just walk. I'm at the wrong. Oh wait
Well, this person needs it. Does everybody need their whole house renovated? I'm at the wrong door
Well, I don't know. I'm not cleaning their door. Oh boy. All right, I have to change the stairs
Okay, you got a pretty good view change that window out. How much do I get for this? Oh my oh wait
My budget's $26,000. Never mind. I said three
They're paying they're paying. All right, I was jump the gun on that one. I apologize. I kind of want to dispose of this
All right
Do I hold on a minute are they gonna be mad that I'm gonna wipe the paint off?
Where's that like a don't touch that that adds to like the aesthetic of the apartment, right?
I feel like that could be like a point of contention
Who wants pain? I don't know like it's look look at all look though
It's like look at all the paint on the ground stuff. No, I don't know
What's this stuff? Why they're just gigantic filters here like water filters these pool filters. What are these?
All right, let me let me get the shit out of the way. Do you see the new fortnight item shop? I have
Never opened a fortnight. I don't I've not got that far something always comes up. That's more important
Isn't this all kind of trash liar? I mean, I've opened the
EXE file I've never actually gone into a game. I never looked at the store. This is kind of a this is a mess
This looks like when I close my eyes and put my hands on my eyes
Stream fortnight for 500k off the debt. The only way I will ever stream fortnight is if I do the fortnight joke
I'll tell it to you again because I
Just in case it ever happened. I'm gonna be in like a backwards hat with big sunglasses on in like a
Like a tank top. I'm gonna be in like a
Lit up room and in the room. I'm just gonna be sitting there with a vape pen
Like a big vapor and I'm just gonna vape and play fortnight and I'm gonna have I don't know
I don't know why I think this is kind of funny
But I'm gonna make my like I'm gonna put my voice changer on just like a tiny bit
And just like talk shit to people while I play and slowly over time
The whole room is gonna like in the face cam is gonna be like face cam at the bottom
Slowly over time you're gonna notice that it's just like you you can it's starting to get way too foggy in there
And it's gonna get to a point where you can't see me anymore
I'm covered in fucking fog and then you're gonna start to hear like the fire alarm and the stream is gonna end
When like a fireman breaks down the drywall behind me
I have I've talked about that making that joke for like four years and I've just never done it
You could probably go back to timestamps of me talking about this from like
2015 2016 actually this is kind of cool a little like why is there a break room in the apartment?
Well, cuz it's a I'm just selling all this stuff, right? Yeah, cuz it used to be a
It used to be an art studio. It's a kitchen. Wait, what? Is there no kitchen downstairs? That's kind of weird
So there's no the kitchens up. It's a room next to the bedroom. This is a bedroom. What is this? This is the closet
What's going on here? It was a printing press
Yeah, I gotta get let me get rid of all the trash first sell the tables to get rid of these fucking tables
What are these old doors? These are all messed up and out this window
When you're gonna play among us, I told you I'm gonna play among us when the among us VR comes out
They'll just sell everything. I don't know if I'm supposed to be doing this, but I did it
I take this wall down too. Oh, I can't it's already out. Well, I mean and I'm doing VR in January
Oh, you know, should I go over the content plans again? Cuz more people are here. Let's be nice room. Yeah, sure
All right house flipper today
Christmas Eve
Hey, okay house flipper today Christmas Eve Ichi Oh compilation night
And then 27th, we're gonna do organ trader
Simulator or whatever it is that gave me you trade organs like a stock market
after that on
New Year's Eve is gonna be the rumble and
the Awards on Christmas Eve
I'll make sure to let you know where the pole is so you can vote another doesn't actually another reason why I want to stream
Cuz I want to make sure people know it where it is and when it's there and then after that
We're gonna do VR for a couple weeks. So that's where among us VR will be
I'm just gonna go into a random lobby. I'm gonna announce myself as the sus guy
I'm gonna get roaring applause and then uninstall the game and never open it again. Then after that
There's a big stream, which you will not have any information on because I'm not gonna give you anything
Somewhere in like the third or fourth week January. I'll give you a hard date on that when I get it. There's a lot going on
Should be a lot of fun. And what about Monster Rancher? No Monster Rancher is not over
Yeah, you might see that on the 27th depending on how much fun I'm having in um that
Organ trader simulator. I still have to beat that game. I love that game to sell 41 objects in here
I just have an entire place. Oh jeez. What about this? All this stuff is it could be repurposed though
You could like spin this around connect the two pieces and make it a bed. It's called house flipper. I know what it's called
Oh, yeah, you're condescending little comment. I could never be like that with you guys
I really don't think I I don't think I could ever actually be like that
That like kind of makes me feel like bad and like odd I'm stuck in the window more stuff this all
What I make last time after like they'll do in a little bit of
Tutorial stuff. I did this saw house, right? I have no idea what I'm gonna do now
at some point it's gonna be like just improv yell out a few words and
a place
And an actor huh?
snow
Sheldon from Breaking Bad and
Doctor's office, okay
I'll break a big bang theory. All right, so new stairs. I don't know what they like
Whatever really quick question. Do you think Sheldon would be a meth user?
Character in Breaking Mad or a meth creator. That's a tricky one. It could go either way
I have to actually clean this user easy. No, this would scare this shit out of me
Do you have an idea what this sounds like? It's like that's like loud and scary at your door. Okay. Now we need to do
Okay, it's time to get some decoration in here sell object. What else?
But it's so cute hurt in the corner. Thank you. We should have sell the toilet
Oh, we're not this is not a custom job. I
What's the point of having a window this window has one purpose and that's to jump up here open it like this
Crouch lift and fart out of here because you don't want anyone in the house to know you did it this serves no other
purpose
It doesn't do anything else. That reminds me the windows that no, I don't why I need to open the whole window
It's not enough. You can't run away and fart somewhere in this house. It's just a big open room
There's not even a bathroom. Oh, there is never mind. What no you I don't know. I don't want to know
Now I'm going like this I'm opening this and I'm gonna stand up here brace my legs here push up and I'm gonna like
Bart out this corner. I'm gonna count to ten because don't ever count to three or four. It's not enough
I'm gonna close it and be like, hey, so what's uh, what's going on up here, man?
Yeah, I'm checking out downstairs pretty it's a pretty slick place. You got here. Wait. Why can't you do that with a regular window?
because
No, my point was it's this is the only thing you can do with this window
Doesn't do anything
You just sounded 50 years old there for a second. All right, stop distracting me. I've got things to do
Cell object. All right. We need to modify the walls. We're gonna paint the walls
I want what they want the walls painted white easy. That's it. Wait, that's all the paint you want on the walls. What?
That's very weird. Okay. Oh
All right, what do they want? They want this covered where's this even gonna go?
All right, if we're gonna go with the they got wood then let's just make it all wood
I'm so bad at this shit. We're sure this even go
Okay, standing set. This is where I should put this. This is a weird house. Okay Hubbard
I don't this I don't care about this is not my house. I don't care
Why can I ask me against a wall? I have like right here filing cabinet. I don't know. Well, this is the oven
All right, wouldn't isn't the kitchen supposed to be upstairs?
The oven right next to the door like this somebody opening up the door. It's just bang. There you are
I'm in straight to cooking. I actually don't hate it. None of this matters
We're just trying to blow through this so I can get to the big house so I can get I can actually make my dream house
It's gonna be a long one today guys. This is not gonna be like a three hour stream
There's gonna be a long one. Hope you're ready. What a dumb fridge. It looks like a school locker
What is that? Yeah, I don't care about any of this person shit who?
It's they can decorate it there you can they can do it their own way
I'm just putting the stuff they want in the house. This is tutorial Andy shit. I'm out of here
How many chairs do you want they want two or three of these two? I want a bench a green wall module
Oh, you want a nice moss wall it?
Whatever. All right. I'll put it up here two of these right this house sucks. I don't care how bad this sucks
I have to how many times I have to make it clear. This is not my house
I care nothing about it. Why would you look at all this? I don't wouldn't sliding door another wooden sliding door
Explain it two more times
You get it. All right, we need
Another one of these the ambient piano music. Yeah, it's nice. It's quite nice. It's quite nice. Okay double bed teddy
Where should I put the bed right here? Oh, come on. I can't it's just this just enough room for a bed
Where's the bed go up here? I feel like lying in this bed. That's fine lay floor tiles light oak mosaic
And that was already on the ground. This is uglier. He's a kitchen tiles
I'm just going by what the customer wants me to do
I I'm not what the customers said to do you and I might think this looks really weird
Somebody just said I have no confidence. This is not my house
I'm trying to speedrun this we get to go by the big house so that I can actually do what I want to do
I want to take down walls. I want to have like a dining room
I want to have a
showcase room I want to have a
Room where I like a game show room like a showcase like prices, right?
I said that's done up there think of someone else for once in your life people that are moving into this house
I'm not real. They're
Imaginated people that the developers made to teach you some of the new things that are in the new update
I don't care about these imaginary people all I care about is myself in my real imaginary world
Which is my fake house that I'm about to build because it's me making it got a little heated there. Oh TV
I put it up there. I can't put it. Oh, it has to be sitting on something
Oh like this kind of reminds me of the first house everybody makes in the sims
This big open square and the TV is far away from everything else
And there's just a big table in the middle and nobody knows shit about how to design cabinets
So everybody's house looks like this in the sims you guys can all sit there and criticize my choice of cabinets
Well, we all scroll over that we just scroll by it. What is this? Oh wardrobe? Okay, do these this is a fridge
No, let's get out. This is the wrong spot. Why is it so dark in here? Oh
This stuff is cool, but I really don't think I only have enough clothes to fit in the first three
Then not nothing else will ever be used. Oh get the paint bestie aided a mirror. Oh paint with white cool
It's dark and hey, how do I go get the paint?
Bestie is there no light switch to turn these lights on you're now manually breathing. You can't get me with that one
So dark turn. Oh, there we go shit was already white in here. Oh waste of money waste of money, but it's whiter
Now you're gonna tell me it's gonna brighten up the room. I don't want to be in a room
That's this bright white people will see how yellow my teeth are
Hey for all my friends of that that shave when you get the shaving cream on your face and you go
My teeth are fucking green. What is going on?
Y'all know that you look in the mirror you smile
Why am I teeth like fucking green and gray and shit? I'm telling you it's weird
I take good care of my teeth, please nobody shaves
What do you mean nobody shaves here you and what's it? What are you implying? You implying something? What's that supposed to mean?
I don't care. Oh, wow
It's important. Yeah, what a makeover. What's the next? Can I buy it now? I can't buy it
I can only why can I only buy this houseboat? All right. I think this is what we're gonna get a big house
There's one here. I was the contractors. There's another one somewhere. Well, what's this one business-as-usual?
Businessman with extraordinary taste wants to have an apartment close to his company headquarters
Therefore he purchased this one previously owned by a party-loving editor-in-chief of a famous angling magazine
Coincidentally, it turned out a very special girl officer works nearby
Christopher already has a list of ideas when it comes to necessary changes
All right bare minimum bare minimum where we gone the Walker family trusted the wrong people when it came to working on their new home
Okay, Benjamin a very gentle man didn't manage to keep them in check and his wife Naomi had to step in when she'd gotten back
From her business trip. She was astonished by the state of the house at this point
They need a true professional who'll be islanded this one. What happened? What did you would you hire the Tasmanian devil?
You don't understand he's just purple guy and he's got a big mouth
His mouth of this mouth is the size of his whole body and he spins and he was holding a hammer
Could you check if it's still fine? I hid in the bathroom for four hours
The kitchen it's such a mess all around it also looks like they finished nothing upstairs
Those will be our personal room
purple the Tasmanian devil's purple
Yeah, what what do you mean he's not purple what are you talking about?
Push the sofa off the ramp. Wait, who did I do this?
I think me and this guy work for the same company cuz I feel like I did that shit to people when I played this before
He's brown
No, the Tasmanian devil is not. What are you talking about?
Tasmanian devil. Oh, I'm thinking about his there's I'm thinking about his little fucking son. They're a little dizzy from Tiny Toons
Yeah, I'm thinking about his son
Yeah
Whatever wrong animal cares he's literally he's not alright
I'm gonna I have to shut everybody up cuz I need to put dizzy devil on stream right now
Is he devil is Tasmanian Tasmanian devil's bastard son or something? I have no idea. What do you mean fake? It's not fake
I'll show you right now. This is dizzy devil. No, I didn't come up with this in a dream
This is a character in Tiny Toons
See, that's who came through their house. This must this means the Tasmanian devil has had sex. Yes
So if two Tasmanian devil characters have it they did this
Scream at each other and run around the house and they spin around. How does that happen?
That's a question of not thought of new topic. Please. Please twitch ban him
He's the worst thing we talked about on the stream is this is how in quotes
How does the Tasmanian devil have sex? That's where you draw the line
The last time I played this game I put a sex swing upstairs. Give me a break
All right, so they like trash the place. This place is kind of swanky. I like it. Imagine the sounds he would make
I don't think they would be very different
It would be different
Would it be I'm curious
What does he sound like?
Hold on he's always home of loose
Okay, so that's what the Tasmanian devil just sounds like
So I'm gonna assume it would be a little slower it was a little bit slower it sounds something like this
Interesting he sounds like the drive-through guy from yesterday
Oh
Somebody said clear your history. It's just the Tasmanian devil screaming
All right for those folks at home if you want go ahead and do your own little fun little project
just what you do is you take you take what we just did and
You have you make two of those tracks and then you make pitch one of them up or pitch one of them down doesn't matter
There I'm not gonna do it here
Okay, let's let's continue what we're doing do the tutorial I was about to Tasmanian devil
I was about to scream Tasmanian devil on you. I was gonna drop that on the stream
I was about to drop right on the stream a full-on Tasmanian devil, but I've talked about it before and I'm not gonna
Yeah, no, we've done this routine before no, we'll not that last one exactly. But this one
You cannot do a Tasmanian devil impression
Unless you go 100% all-in as hard as you can you can't half-ass a Tasmanian devil
You go all-in or don't do it at all. I'm not doing it. No do it. You got to go all-in do it
No, I can't I don't have the confidence that I can go all-in right now
I really don't think I have the confidence to do it right this minute. All right, let's modify. Let's hold on so much trash everywhere
This is really pretty do it. We need to sample it. You're not sampling shit
by the way
Buddy, I mean enough to clean the windows anymore. I will just do the bathroom first. We're here
It's clean
Alright, they want to remove trash. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's fine
Alright, they want to do wall tiles at these wall tiles. What are these? Oh, I like this. This is smoky
I'm not your buddy. Alright pal
Okay, pal
Settle down. Hey friendo sans no
Wait, do you you actually have the clip you already? Alright, so how long ago is this?
This clip that you're about to hear was from like a year or two ago
A lot of you guys might not have heard it. This is me trying to do the Tasmanian devil going all-in
You can't do it and and I laughed at the end
Yeah, it's impossible I did it again after that I did you have a
Documented evidence of me doing it again. Why did I do it twice? What I have to do?
Alright snowy marble and oh they want both. Oh, I see what you're trying to do here. That one wasn't good
That was not the real attempt. What was that? That was it's inside the window. I
Thought I don't know why I just thought somebody shot me the gun. I don't know why it was weird
Big stream in January. Alright, there you go. There you go. You got it. It was two years ago. Wait, hold on
Are these different streams?
Wait, did I do this on two separate streams like more than like six months apart? I
Can't do it again, you need to slow this down. No, I hold on. Should I try it again?
Hold on. I have to let me hold on a bit. If I cheat I could probably get it. Let me let me cheat
I'll cheat. I'll see if I can get it
This other in the world of voice work. They they do this stuff. Okay, third time's a charm. Here we go
I
Not doing it with a face cam, are you kidding me? No
Mute this mute this because I want to be able to have this as a I don't want you to have any sound in the background
Okay, I'm gonna pass out
All right. I'm okay. I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm okay. How did that one sound?
That one's not okay
Was that one better than the other ones? I hear it. What do you mean fecal funny?
That's the Tasmanian devil sticks his tongue out at the end and goes with his tongue
Was that better than the last one was it unironically good? I know are you kidding me? No mute this
Mute this because I want to be able to have this as a I don't want you to have any sound in the background
Well, I have sound
No, I don't think that was really I don't think that was good. I don't think that was good
That was even close
Just the guy from Star Wars. That was the frog guy from Star Wars. That was not the Tasmanian devil
I was just shaking my face. That was not even close not even close
That's not even fucking close
Yeah from the Phantom Menace
Because listen to the other one the other one is so much better because the Tasmanian devil has a very distinct he goes like
Right and it's all over the place
See like the pitch changes and stuff. This is just me shaking my face and screaming play them together. It will be perfect
Oh my god, you're right. It actually would be I gotta get this cute up
Okay, I'm done. We're not doing this anymore
No, I'm not gonna you want to go all in you're arguing with yourself, okay, I
Do dizzy this time? Wait dizzy is different. Hold on. I'm curious. Don't leave. Please don't leave
Maybe I could do dizzy better. No, is he devil? Oh
Yeah, I can't go all the way
Is he devil sound I need to find a good one
Oh, why is there no audio of dizzy devil, but there's a million of Tasmanian devil dizzy devil
tornado
All there is it's like a wiki page
and just take the guy that all there is that I can find in like the video section is the
Tasmanian devil dizzy devil tornado and then the guy that does this with the tornado behind him this thing that like
You know what? I'm talking about. That's the only thing I can find
All right, I'm done. That was fun. I like cracked my back doing that. I like feels good. We're stream 2021
Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here
Get out of here and ban them. Let's put the bathroom in. All right, we need to put a
Delicate bathtub. Ooh
No, don't do it. There's already too many of those this thing's huge what this thing's weird. Very nice. Very nice
There's the walls you lunatic. No, I don't care. I'm just trying to unlock stuff. We're just getting for only 60%
That's it. It's banned people
Well, you don't have to okay
compact
What was that compact WC enu? Oh, it's a toilet. I might as well have it match
Mountable shower. How about this one? How am I supposed to put this? I might do this. Oh, okay
Let's get out of the way right in the corner. Oh, I would love to mount a shower here. I do this wrong
Oh put it together. Very nice. There might do a teehee for us. I already did. Ah, I'm good
Actually, I like the sounds this make sounds really nice. It'll like ring ring ring. This is on easy mode
You can actually put this on hard and I think it takes a lot longer
Cool. All right. Now they want a mirror a mirror and Lamont here
Mirror Lamont, I think a good beach finish. Sounds good. I want a TV. That's a pretty that would be like that'd be awesome
Just had a TV right here to me. Oh, there's mirrors, right?
So yeah, I wouldn't want this is not where I want that. What would the purpose of a mirror right here be still watch?
Yourself, where's the sink gonna go right here sink that not a sink. We're not doing a double sink
Are we he's wrong off-center? It's not my house. Okay, and this fit this mirror is not big enough
All right. Now we need to lay floor tiles
These ones sounds good. This is actually looking really nice
What happened it's the same
Minecraft power. This is a Minecraft bathroom. I do this wrong lay wall tiles
They don't want these on the ground. These are floor tiles. Did I do the wrong thing or is it just this ugly? No
It is like this. I don't know looks exactly the same five nights at Freddy's flashlight
It actually is how do you come up with that? That's so clever. It's just the unity light
Isn't five nights at Freddy's made in
Out of stone or something. It's not even made in regular game engine
I thought the original five nights at Freddy's was made in some weird game maker. Wasn't it? It's not made in unity
It was made in fusion. Yeah, this how this bathroom gives me anxiety. I don't like it
Hey, I'm bumpy. Hey, I'm bumping you know, I don't gotta live here. Hey, that's not I don't what all right bathrooms done
Wait hangar a little towel rack. I I want one of these I don't want like three of them Christmas is coming. That's right
I
Go you scared the shit out of me. Yep. Well the paper. Okay what this is that?
I was wondering what this was like a coat rack. I thought this was like a fireplace thing. This is for toilet paper
I'm gonna knock this over
You are going to reach for this and knock this over and get pissed cuz then the toilet paper hits the ground
Why that takes up so much space?
There's a backpack this looked like a backpack from here. The counter is not big enough
I just I just had to blink a few times did that freak anybody else out to that was weird like opening it with the door
Moving because I still had it selected. That was kind of odd looking wasn't it? All right, this
This room is done. I don't need to do any more
Just got to get to the progress and that's it this out of here the door isn't lined up idiot
The door is not lined up
Oh, no, I get no I don't get much more joy in life and watching a stadium full of 15,000 people
Think that something's wrong with me. All right
This looks nice sure cuz I'm not like this over this one. Why is it?
Hello, this must be inspiration bubbles. Why I don't get it. I guess looks all right. He's sitting on the stage. Wait, hold on
He's sitting on the stage with his PC set up with a spotlight on top of them
Oh 15,000 people just watch and throw popcorn at him. I think the more accurate thing would be
Half of you are on your phones
Watching someone else. I don't know why I sometimes I feel like you you're like the big grudging
You're like the begrudging husband that went to the show and you got to catch the game
You just like have me open the tab and you're doing something else
You got like the Golden Knights game on like in on your lap while you're at the show really cool. Okay, who's a wall finish?
Hmm, but this one not my house who cares remember likes hockey. No, I just pretend to to lift and uber drivers
Hey, I need more of these. Oh a big leather chair right here
What do you think's gonna win the English Premier League you had me tied down to a chair and you said hey Jeremy
Name one team in the English Premier League. I wouldn't be able to tell you and it's gonna matter
How many like teeth you pulled out? I wouldn't be able to die. I don't know. This looks nice
I'm gonna really like I'm a happy mood right now. Hope you guys are doing good. It's like the holiday season
I'm trying I'm just I'm in the crowd. I'm in the Christmas spirit. How are you? How are you actually you doing?
All right, hopefully you're doing okay
Alright, it's a room that you turn in and there's like the Resident Evil character that just sits there and watches you and has a few
Pieces of dialogue for you. Okay, this one's pretty good. Just gotta get to 65%
Chat and Jerma, I guess I just got the new Xbox hog. Nice. All right. Nice new Xbox in the chat
We got somebody with a new Xbox. All right, where there's got to be something
That's really awful to get a bunch of points here or the garage or something, right? Oh, yeah
Like this is what's bringing my score down. No good. Congratulations broken glass get it
I was like a great news my
Sandwich is toasted and it's buttery. It's flaky. Good melted cheese perfectly, dude. Perfect cheese melt
That's pogs. Let's see pogs and chaplains for perfect melted cheddar cheese on this turkey and cheese sandwich
Okay, I changed the stairs
Yeah, that's fine getting there upstairs. I haven't done anything. I've done a lot of things upstairs
It's down here that I haven't done anything rash under the stairs. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you
Okay, you need to do stuff down here. It was my birthday yesterday. Can you sing happy birthday?
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday dear chatter
Yeah, yeah, okay
Call it you want white already here try buy this house or should I wait and try to get the huge one?
I know there's a huge one over the huge one. All right, if I get the huge house
I'm just gonna make a gigantic comedy theater. I'm gonna it's gonna be a theater. Okay install panels
Okay, wait put the wrong thing in her shit. Oh, well, uh, it's fine
He's the kind of aisles you see on the floor where when you're doing the tour or if you're looking around and you see
Wow, these are beautiful. Wow. Look, I love that tile
You were you're gonna replace that the second you move in it's actually gonna be first on the list. That it
So panel I need to install new panels with a yonky splonky now. No, thanks put on some other music
Do you have anything to recommend? I think this is pleasant. It's pleasant. What's your best half-life to impersonation?
That my computer just crashed
Alright, this is not the impression hour. I'm gonna play the game. I'm just that I'm just the kid at lunch
I forgot I've talked about it about I'm this time the kid at lunch. Hey, Jeremy do do it. Can you do an owl?
And everybody laughs now do a wolf
And then I get detention I get in trouble
You don't get in trouble. I'm the one that has to take the the blow there. I have to hold the burden
Because mrs. Stephenson is going over the test results. I have to stay after kind of burnt. That's good enough
I'm not gonna fit a fridge in here. I'm just doing for the points. Trust me. I'm just trying to unlock
I'm gonna get to the point where I unlock the house that I want to use and
I'm gonna streams gonna be over. How close am I what's the next big game? You're looking forward to probably Elden Ring
That's the easy answer. I'm scared though, cuz that's every single person says that and
The more that people collectively in their brain internalize how excited they are about a thing that comes out
It usually increases the chance that it's gonna be bad
The universe does this weird thing the more that people care about something before it releases the worst they decide to make it
No, I'm not trying to get too excited about it
Cyberpunk yeah, although who knows this might be a no man's sky
scenario and
Two years from now cyberpunk is an amazing game. It could be do you believe in ghosts?
Um, I believe in radiators
Faulty hot water heaters add radio signals and
Wind that's strong enough to make the windows move around but that answers your question
All right, you want a vial damn right side shower and do that. I don't know about ghosts
No, I don't know about ghosts too. Too many people have died
All you would hear was the noise you hear at a baseball game
If there are people like our ghosts and they're just walking around just like kind of floating around they would be like
70 billion ghosts
70 billion ghosts just all talking over each other. I get rid of these you believe in the Power Rangers
Yes, I do because the Power Rangers are real even though there are a fictional group of characters
They're actually in the costumes and they're actually pretending to fight stuff
I've had an experience with a Power Ranger before right? I've seen a Power Ranger. I've never had an experience with a ghost and
I'm just realizing what I'm doing here. Okay, look Ben. That's about your experience with a Power Ranger. I don't like
I'm watching the show buying the toys
Going to Power Ranger con and buying tickets for every panel. See if ghosts had a comic con panels
I would probably believe more your theory of Power Rangers aren't real but ghosts aren't either then or something
I don't know. Do you believe in aliens that one's tougher because on one hand?
Yes, I do
Do I think that there is somewhere some a galaxy or something that has sentient life? Probably
I mean if we exist then other people could exist too
I follow by the we exist therefore theory if it happened once it can happen again
I don't know exactly how accurate that is, but you never know. I'm speedrunning trust me
But you don't want these down here. Yeah, you do. Okay
I'm just trying to get to the big big house as fast as I can. I want to do my own work
I don't want to work or someone else to do. I know I want to do my own work. It's close
All right
What room has not even been touched yet right here some work is the universe where you work a nine-to-five and you aren't insane
What do you think I'm insane you are? Yeah, say that to me in real life and I'll run bro. I'm running almost there
Now you said to me. I'm the coward
I I'm the guy and then beauty the beast that hides behind Gaston. I actually don't hate this room
Even though it sucks. Oh my god. Look at how depressing this is for me. Just hold on. Whoa, just think one day
Germa won't be popular. He'll just be another old guy in the supermarket
We might not even recognize him in the future. Holy shit Wow
That is that's a sad I just got like a weird image of me pushing a super like a cart
We get old just kind of looking at the sails and stuff and being like well
that's that's all those grapes are on sale and then I get to the counter and I'm just like
And my teeth like both my dentures fell out excuse me, we're almost there
I bet you the big house is next and I can't wait
What about in? All right. Yeah, I'll do this. She's got a paint after painting these walls. It should be good
Don't stop this is wicked sad. I know I'm this is sad and sad music playing too
Don't you see me holding the grapes which stringy hair with this music and on the front of the package
It's some motto. It's like and look at me. I guarantee these are freshest grapes
You'll ever see that's me holding and I smile a little bit and I look at me. Yeah. Yeah
Alright, this is actually kind of sad. I'm not gonna do this anymore. This is sad. No more of this. I'm crying
Don't cry almost at that threshold. Come on Gwyn. Let's see it. Come on. We'll be that old in 25 years
Yeah, 24 years is a long time. That's a long time
Think about years of your life and how much of it you've lived but how much of it have you actually lived how much
Have you truly been a sentient person that had decision-making skills?
I think under 10 years old you don't even know like you don't even really know you're a person under 5
Right, you don't really start making like actual kind of memories that you hold on to till you're over 5 to 10 years old
So your first 10 years you barely even have lived it
So I think about going from like 10 did like 15 10 to 20 15 to 30 and then like 30 to like 80
You've got a very long time of being like a sentient person and forget about all the other times sleeping
Yeah, but you need that you need that to live at what point do you stop being sentient?
I mean like what brain activity right continues?
What's the theory there? It kind of freaks me out. It's like your brain still has electrical impulse like activity after you you pass away
Doesn't it? So what it happens there because your brain slows down. Do you like live for like a
Hundred million years or something like in your slowed down slow low electrical impulse brain
So nobody knows that only lasts a couple hours. Well, that only lasts a couple hours to you
What does that feel like because think about it when you dream you only dream for like five seconds, right?
But sometimes those dreams feel like you're there for an hour or two. Oh, that's the freaks me out to a point
Well, like I kind of like the second that I'm dead
Smash my head with a cinder block crush my head with a cinder block
I don't want to like live for an eternity in my own weird like electrical impulse brain thing
Because like what if they do what if they're too cool?
What if okay in the ten seconds that it takes with like uncle Gary to come up with the cinder block and just crush my head
I may have lived for a hundred thousand years already in my slowed down electrical impulse kind of
Passing brain not to mention uncle Gary the people in there, you know, I've only told uncle Gary
I told this to me uncle Gary
Make sure would I die make sure I die the second that I have flatline you smash my head with a cinder block Gary
What are the doctors like? What are you doing? Put that down. That's another hundred thousand years. Yeah, I gotta do this
What if Gary doesn't finish the job?
I might live for 500 million years and I'll be sitting there after year number a million
I'm gonna be like, I don't I don't know what happened. Gary didn't fucking finish the job apparently
Well, Gary picks up the cinder block and like throws it and then it hits me like the groin
And it didn't even get the job done and they like they throw them out. Just enjoy eternity. It's a weird thought though
It really is everywhere at the end of time. I'm so close to being completed here
What what does house flipper do this to you do just paint the walls because okay, I go off
I pop the fuck off and I play house flipper. You know why?
Because it's one of the only times when my brain
Gets to this is just a background thing going on and it is occupying
It's occupying the part of my brain, right?
it's almost like my like the crazy part of my brain now can come out because the part that's that's keeping the
crazy Gary in there is now being occupied painting walls and
That's usually the defense please. Oh, right. I did. That's all right
Just can you imagine?
Okay, and here it there he drove there he goes
He's passed and like somebody's picks up a cinder block from behind like the table and it's just like holy shit, bro
Images insane. Oh, you don't understand. He told me he didn't want to stay stuck in a DMT flooded brain chemical dream
I had to
Look, I have it in writing. I sign it with like a blue Crayola crayon
Alright, what do you got? Just opened up another job. Is it in big house? Oh, come on. Where is it?
What is this crayon?
Dnr it's supposed to be three jobs here. Why can't I move? I'm an idiot. Where are these other missions the arrows?
Yeah, but I I see this one. I see this one this one here. So where's three is one two
I did that one one two a warehouse for memories. Oh, look at some of these. This is cool
Hey, this is now I don't want to be done on do this one
I want to unlock the mansion do the boathouse the boathouse is all I do
I can't even afford it. How much coke did you snort before this stream worsty? I do not do drugs that are not
cannabis or
Alcohol that up. All right. Let me just do one more job. I'll make a little bit
I need to make I'm not buying this stupid boat though, man. Let me do the apartment one
I feel like it's gonna be easy. I'm not buying the boat that boats boring my schedule Seth Rogen
I'm realizing right now that my Homer Simpson impression is just my Seth Rogen impression. Let's go listen to it
There's like a thousand clips
The helicopter is waiting and its engines are still hot. This place looks unacceptable
You need to clean it thoroughly for furnishings pick something stylish top class
Money is not an issue. Are we clear? We're clear. I need a room for my suits and ties
I want you to turn this area into a spacious wardrobe. I've left specific instructions in our contract
I'll pay you when you deliver your side of the agreement ways. This must be
What I trust my secret will be safe
All right, I'm taking the wall down and taking the door off. I'm gonna paint arrows on the ground
I'm sprinting to the secret room. What's in it? Why is everybody such a dirty motherfucker? I'll change it out
Yeah, I'll change up the music. Give me a sec. I'll change music
What do you want to put on something that's not gonna get this entire VOD muted, please do chrono trigger
About the block OST, that's a classic one. I'll put that on
Okay, it's like song is too good. It's distracting me. I love this SNES guitar sounds hold on
I need to listen to this and focus
You want to hear my favorite version of the SNES guitar sound
Let me put that on first. Here's my favorite version of what I'm describing. See who catches it. What is it? Turn it up
Mm-hmm
Send it nobody's got it
Really? Yeah
There it is
Killing it on stage
What a secret room I will I will I will I will
Hey, I saw you at PAX East one year
I was the one jumping up and down shouting your name not asking if you remember but I'm letting you know that I
Remember you being a chill dude. We were on the balcony. I remember walking into PAX East and
From the balcony. I had just gotten there. I wasn't really that popular or anything
I remember walking into the front door and somebody just going
From
From the balcony up at the convention center and I just was like hi
I think the channel what that was I wasn't that popular back then
It was terrifying not terrifying that you did it but terrifying that somebody recognized me
I was like, oh my how did that happen that I that's not possible
Terrifying like holy shit, dude, you are terrifying. No, like it was I was terrifying to me
I couldn't believe that somebody had recognized me
Immediately when I was at you when I walked right in the front door porn theater. Yes, it was. Yeah
No, oh, I remember that might be the first time I was ever recognized somewhere that was not
In the chat room of one of my streams. Hey there
For the 20 community subs, I appreciate that Santa. So what's the point of this is a discreet room?
Could why cuz it's like a porn theater
The cleanest room in this person's house the Tekken 4 beach theme
I just I'm gonna see if this is okay
If this is not a good song, I want that person to be timed up for an hour Tekken 4 beach stage
I'll be the judge of that
All right, and so far no
Okay. All right. That part's putting up. All right
All right. I like it. Can't why can I get rid of this? It's just dirty
No, no, there's like a shoe under here
double bed elegance
Christian dark bed. What is a Christian dark bed? This is way too big
Can't even be in the room still dirt in here where all right?
We need to give her some of the stuff or get get rid of everything actually turn the cool lights on
I do like that. Yeah
That's what it's high society is like mr. Top 1000 streamer up 100
As the last glass of wine that I had was from Trader Joe's. Okay, relax Trader Joe's wine is good
I know it is it is good. It's not
Thousand dollars a bottle everything at Trader Joe's is good coffee love and tea what I don't know what is in love
I don't okay weird. You don't want this stuff anymore. Do you let's do
Oh, all right. How about this? I'm gonna make your house
Get weird
Once LED stripes. All right, that was pretty good. You know to ban that person who else wants to risk getting banned for an hour
Well, let's see it if you if I don't like your song you've been for an hour a
Paint brawl. All right paint brawls
Music if I don't like this, I'm not even kidding. You're gone ain't brawl. There's like six songs
This reminds me of my first day in garage band, I actually don't hate this I think you're safe
Yeah, you're safe. This is so bizarre that I like it. What am I looking at here?
What is the moment to get rid of this upstairs? Okay, we need to sell the chandelier. Where is the chandelier?
Oh there. All right. Now you want you want this hanging cabinet bullshit?
Sure. Yeah, have your three microwaves. So whatever the hell these are webway chandelier rain clock
There's still trash where oh
I see trash. I
Can you see the trash? All right, you're safe. You're not banned. Congratulations
So to sell 28 items here what I can't what am I
Something here I can sell
Stairs, okay. I put a wall lamp on here console brushy
console Emmy
Hub extends ceiling lamp a cave story. Oh, it's tea. I will maybe
All right, you're gonna game down here. All right, you're safe. Let me look at what's next. Okay, okay, okay
Resident evil basement theme. All right here. That's an evil director's cup mansion basement. Okay
Get rid of that guy
Sucks banned for an hour. This is terrible. I'm about to get approached by the Radio Shack employee
Hey, hey, hey, hey, can I help you? Can I be find something? No, no, I'm just I'm just browsing
Okay. Yeah, I've been that guy for an hour. All right next iceberg from Kirby's dreamland 3. All right ice burg
Kirby 3. All right. Ooh that person wanted to get banned. This is good
All right. What do you want late? You want different tiles here? All right, pretty good. I like it
This looks that doesn't think a TV in the bathroom. I gotta sell the sink. It's kind of a weird sink
All right, you're safe next rug rats search for Raptor rug rats search for Reptor
Where is it? I missed it, right? It was rug rats search for and then it was a backyard theme rug rats
Search for Reptor
Backyard. I heard is I'm not saying it yet. I like it
You're safe definitely safe
Install wall tiles. Yeah, where are they ma'am? I used to love old rug rug rug rats
You'd love KK slider. Everybody loves KK slider though
Okay safe. Oh
Okay
Everhood feisty flowers theme ever hood feisty flowers theme
This one here, I think I don't think this is not a remix. I'm like I dig it so far good
painting emerald heart in a sofa
Okay, all right, okay, this is really good. What's this from ever hood? What is ever hood?
This is rare. This I like a lot. It's an undertale like RPG
It's a rhythm game. I play this
You got to play this, right? Hey check download this this looks like could be fun
Yes. Yes. Yes. All right. It's hard. Hey, does it go hard?
Can be hard. It's pretty hard. All right rhythm game as in
Like space channel or rhythm game rhythm heaven fever rhythm game guitar hero. What's it compared to something?
Guitar hero. Okay. Mm-hmm. I don't know about that. I'm not very good at that kind of stuff
It's different. Okay. All right, you're safe. I need another one. It's not that bad. Okay, maybe I'll try it
Alright, somebody said to put this on and I'm gonna tell you right now that it's just they're trying to be there was it was
They're making a funny joke here. I don't know. They just decided to tell me to put this on there
I want you to ban them. It's the Cantina a Star Wars song. Just ban the person for an hour
This thing Oh Cantina by Star Wars
All right ever is this band? Okay, how about?
Street Fighter 5 main menu music. All right, Street Fighter 5 main menu. Mm-hmm
It's all right, it's all right. Yeah, it's all right. All right
No, I don't be in that person, but it's close put on another one
Do you guys know what I thought the lyrics of this song was?
I thought I thought this song was saying I want to shake you boom boom by I want to shake you boom boom by
I had no idea what they were saying
Let us want to shake you boom boom by and when I found out it was take you for a ride. I was
Incredibly disappointed. All right time ban me. Do I get banned?
Ban me I get by to get banned
No, that's not that song goes so that song slaps kids. What are you talking about?
I can't get banned from my own stream. That song's awesome. No, I
That song's good. You all like that song. Who doesn't like that song? Okay, the little ships by
Jean Jack Perry the little ships the little ships
What game is this from the spongebob? It's from like rehydrated. Oh, it's just us. It's just a song. Oh
It's a maple story title maple story title theme. That's cool. I was about to ban you
All right, let me play the game for a while before I lose track. All right, last one last one last one last one
Fuck the music play the game. I know I know one more this song from
He's a jet jet set radio. Jack Graham radio
Doesn't the creator of that soundtrack want to punch me in the face or something?
It's just I have a distinct memory of him saying he was gonna like he wanted to fight me
Alright turtles in time. Yep, that's going on. Don't even ban that person. This is like one of my favorite OSTs ever
He said he could beat you in a fight. He said he's gonna like he's gonna like beep up like strangle me or something
I don't know. That's so funny. That's so fucking goddamn funny
Turn it up. You got it. All right. Now I'm gonna play the game
No more fucking around. I know all the people that want to see gameplay. I'm really sorry
I if I would do a tier list and rank the songs if this first one coming up Big Apple
Is probably up at s-plus I would say no not this not this not this Avengers theme shit. Not this one
Where's this last piece of trash? You don't want this
Here it is. Yeah. Oh, yeah, this is the good one. This is the one this s-plus
Don't care. Whatever. This just has the old Turtles vibe to it
I'm gonna set the end of this and then maybe I'll get to the actual big house
I've just been speedrunning this LED stripes, too. This is one of our monster rancher monsters
Another one of these what it is you want sell object. Where are these LED strips LED strips?
Where are they LED stripe?
Where the LEDs
stairs
LEDs on the wall
Okay
We're almost there. I want to buy a house. All right, so close. Come on another blizzard painting another one
Why do you want so many of these? What the hell are you doing?
Painting Blizzard of sorrow. Where do you want this fucking thing?
Gone. Hello. Ludwig is off twitch. Can you take his username? No, what?
What you you say you want me to squat on Ludwig's twitch username? What the hell are you talking about?
You should just redo your username and get the numbers off. No. No, they're just staying on. It's too late. I'm going on
11 plus years of the same name. I
At this point if you don't know if you know who I am, you know who I am
If you don't then you don't all right, I'm buying something. I'm buying. I'm not renovating other people's houses
What did I unlock? What the hell? Okay. Here we go. So I can get the loft or I can get that
This this swanky one, I'm thinking about probably the swanky one or it's a castle I get the castle
Five hundred and thirty five thousand dollars. Oh my god. This might have been a mistake make it into your fortress
Oh, yeah, I can make the comedy fortress. That's a good idea. All right, how do I get rid of these?
Yeah, this looks this is dreary and dark and no no no this big courtyard. Oh, I don't wait
This is the ticket office. Okay ticket office and then here's the main theater over here
No, is there a big room somewhere? Where's the biggest room in the house make a white castle? Oh
No, I'm not gonna make a white castle
I'm not gonna fast food restaurant man. All right. This is the ticket office clean this place up
Oh shit, is you playing phasmophobia now making a cinnamon twist relax. You don't even have you don't have my vision
You don't have my vision. I got this fucking thing now. Oh
Oh
Wait, I have a lawnmower. Let's clean this place up boys and girls. Oh, I got a new garden skill
Oh the game just kind of did not like it
It's okay. What did I get? I skilled up. I definitely want mowing speed regulated mowing speed
Whoops. Oh music. Yeah
Yep, only forty thousand dollars. How am I gonna buy anything old and some theme? It's a big house
I don't need to mow the back. No one's going back here. Oh shit. I just ran over a bunch of moles
That's not good. Oops. I'll lay out because I'm not
About the mischief makers OST bring it up. That's right. There is when the song goes
I need to remake this game. They've remade such dog shit in the past. Like why would you don't remake mischief makers?
Why because it sucks? No, it does not have you played it. You've probably never played it. It's already perfect
Well, it rerelease it give us some updated input commands and graphics and stuff would just update it
I'm almost done with the front at least treasure is basically dead
That's sad
You ever been to another country? I have not well just Canada count. I don't I don't count Canada. I just don't here comes
Here it comes. I'm to New Zealand. I'm not just gonna go to New Zealand. Just for no reason
New Zealand I'm sure is a beautiful place
That's too far for me to go. All right front yard looks pretty good. I
Would say so get out of your hobbit hole. Oh, it's warm and this grape jam Gandalf
I just want my books and my grape jam and my comfortable chair Gandalf. That's true
Now it's a little loud. Let me fix that. I got you need to come to your senses
This tree can stay
Come to Riven dare isn't that like Jughead Jones? All right, we're mode
Clean. No, we're not. Let's be perfect. You missed an inch wide strip. Who cares?
I've got a lot of internal work inside the castle to do the outside. I don't really care about
I just don't want to be look gross. You tell me right here. All right, you know the sledgehammer
I need to take down so what can you go upstairs into a theater? It was an Edgar Allan Poe or something
All right, what's up here if I take this wall down much outdoor space here to all this shit
Oh Gandalf my books. You don't need these anymore
Gandalf
All right, old people
You'll be dead in a few years. Oh
oh
Cigarette stains. This is we're gonna turn this around just you wait and see if you come up the stairs here
What is the whole of the steps we're selling that's not inviting we don't talk about how Gandalf was 80% sure that Bilbo was
dead on that journey
Didn't get enough just like smoke a bunch of crack and think that it was a good idea to send a hobbit into Mount
Doom it just worked somehow like lightning strikes once in a million chance, right?
I think Gandalf just got lucky. It's remarkable that that worked out
They even make a point to show Gandalf smoke a bunch of crack like smoke a pipe on camera
50 times and he sits back and it's like eyes like roll forward and he's just like, oh that scared me
I was like, oh yawn yawn. What's going this music sucks yawn
Here comes. All right. I'm I'm taking I think I'm gonna take this wall. Maybe not
I'm gonna play this game one day on stream. I
Will I've done it?
Paging paging everybody that works on the switch
N64 library put this on there
I don't have any more pogs left in my body to pretend to be excited about paper Mario. I put something else on there
It's a great game. It's a great game
It is it could be one of the greater games that was released on the console. I'm aware of that
You know what else I'm aware of corporate greed. That's right. Oh, I thought this is meat on here
Just it's gonna be the concession hall
You gave into that greed
Don't say that
Yeah, this is good shit. What soundtrack is this is mischief makers
Give it a listen. Go play the game if you can. This is ugly. No get rid of that. What's down here?
I'm not a person down here, right? Oh
What did that just make me feel so weird?
Why is it? Why is it in those weird? I don't like that
You're to all this this whole wall done get rid of the whole thing. Oh, here's my favorite song take this down to
And I not go outside
It's gonna be somebody buried in the wall probably
Let us keep the horror. It's here on the screen right now all the characters in the game too when you attack them they go
Okay, it looks good sell everything please help what what's wrong nobody said, please help what am I helping?
What did you do? What happened? He's not making money doing this, you know, it's statistically possible that somebody may have died right now
Don't tell me that maybe this could be the theater. I need a big open space
This is the wall to the outside of the property. You have many viewers
Thanks, is that a compliment or you mean? I mean if you want to talk about statistics
I would say if there's like a zero point zero zero zero one percent chance that somebody watching
You know, it could fall into that category. How many people are actually taking going to the bathroom right now?
Like they're on the toilet and they're holding like their phone in one hand. I gotta brighten this up a little bit
This is so ugly. I can't do anything with this space yet
Remind me it. Oh, I could I could put a bathroom right here. Oh
No, I could this could be the bathroom. Yeah, I think that's a good place for the restroom
It's also just am I gonna read what you said because I can put them against the wall. All right, let's let's start
Let's start the bathroom. I'm looking for floor. I want bathroom floor
floor tiles, oh
How about oh
No too much. How about these? I like it. Oh
This is gonna be a nice bathroom gonna be this the all the way through though. What the hell is in a public bathroom?
stalls
urinals
Sinks, maybe I should change it out halfway through here. Okay, which I need the walls to be different looking to
See the bathroom walls look like let me finish this first. It's literally $50 to do this. Who cares?
I can replace it if I want to
Do we have a consensus? How many are on the bathroom right now? All right, the walls need to change walls
Need bathroom walls wall tiles. Maybe some green some blue
Something that'll brighten up a little bit. This looks all right. Oh
What about the diamond tiles or these?
Let me see. Let's see what they look like. I hate that
Yeah, that looks awful. Just paint it. I'm gonna paint it. Just paint just paint. All right
I'm thinking that we'll do crystal. This looks like I need something more chill than this. This is too intense
What should I put on? There's 240 people
Right now that's so weird think about how many people
240 is how many people can fit in a movie theater? How many seats are in like an IMAX theater?
300 240. Yeah, imagine an entire IMAX theater full of people and you you know, they're all going to the bathroom right now
I'm gonna dress it up. Don't worry. That's gonna get this gaudy wallpaper off. I haven't peed all day either
So let's do that as well. This is not the main event. I'm just making the bathroom first. So don't forget it
All right, I'll be right back. I'm gonna go pee back in like two three minutes. Hello
So I was just downstairs and
I was walking and I heard a little ruffling. I heard like a little
What was that?
All of a sudden I get this wave of baked dog cookies
Those that savory like baked dog cookies just filled the air. I said, where is he?
I have no idea. I'm looking around like I get I where it's like somebody lit a
Savory dog candle down here. I don't know. I can't find him. I look over where he usually is
I look over in the corner and on his bed. No, look at the couch. There's nothing there
There's just a really really spun up
Crumpled up blanket that was on the couch and I go over it. Nobody wait a minute that it's dog shaped
I go over there and they wait it's I'm sitting right in front of where the smell is
He has wrapped himself up so much isn't been a blanket. I can't even tell there's a dog on the couch
I'm telling you it hit me in the face when I was far away from him
He's a little dog, but he has a big dog smell
It's so cute and then he let out this huge once he realized that I was in the room
He let out this just like you know what I'm talking about, right?
Yeah, he's so wonderful. Give him a bath. I he gets a bath all the time
He is very thoroughly cleaned on a very regular basis. All right, let's keep going Jerma
Can you read my diss verse you want me to what I mean your diss verse you made a diss verse
Where I don't see it dis first. Okay, let's go. Is it audio? Okay. Yeah, there's the way you posted it in chat
Yeah, you I do actually have to read this. Okay fine
Sure, I'm gonna get a good start here. All right, when do I come in? I want to come in
Yo, Jerma, you've read it or your rhymes are lackadaisical
You're not a real competitor your flow is so slow can't even keep tempo when it comes to delivering mediocre streams
You're so far on top. You're gonna forget vertigo
I thought you let the react any stuff on YouTube your IQ is so high can't suffer one by one Rubik's Cube
Give me another one. Give me another one. You got more anybody got any more diss tracks for me?
I'll do them. Let me see him. Give it to me. I have to diss him back
I have to write I can't put on the spot like this
Okay
I'm typing. I'm typing. I don't know. I don't okay. I don't know. Here's mine. I tried mine. All right, let's go
Oh
All right
Yo, officer your brain looks like it's made out of goo ain't nothing stopping me from hitting you with a shoe
People call me crazy. That shit's far too lazy open up the fridge. I serve up a plate of hazy. I'm dead. I'm gone
I'm getting rushed off the stage. I don't have any rap game
Hey, I don't know. I know I should have said I should have said after you
I get you the world's gonna go hazy like I'm gonna get you like after you get hit with the shoe
I fucked it up. I don't know why there was a fridge involved
Hazy
Alright, alright, let's go. How's this one? We got you got one for me. I'll do one more
Hey listen
What Jeremy you sure it is fuck you look like you pooped your pants. Yeah, Jeremy and getting dissed and that's on
All right, that one was bad. Give me something. Give me a real one. It was got no real scared of my diss
No, it wasn't even a real one
Cinnamon cinnamon, oh
Cinnamon
Feminine all venom. Ah hawk venom cinnamon. What is what is this? This is not even a rap. What are you writing? Is it real?
I just thought people were writing words
Okay
Shitting pissing and farting and shit and pissing and farting and shit. And alright, goodbye. Give me a real one
I'm doing one more real one. It's about drive. No, I gave you a real one. There was got no rap game
His streams are lame. He smoked crack cocaine like he didn't know what one to blame. Hey, I rap so fast
I eat ass like groceries and German at a five can't even spit shit close to me. All right, that was all right
All right. Nice. Nah, I'll give you another one
Uh
Some of them are
Don't know. Let me use some of them. Uh, I don't read. All right last one
Call me sanitizer cuz I'll wipe out the germa more sterilizing than a dose of Moderna. Yeah
The rhymes are on point here you get to read you get to write them
I have to come up with it so much slower than you do. Do I have to do this? What? Hey
Listen to me. You got no job streaming ain't work. Your paychecks like your height man
You're coming up short vomiting lines like this sleaze of Oreos. Why are you always single man? Where are your hose?
You're psycho and smelly. I'll call you a rat, but never have I seen a rodent so fucking fat. That was good
Okay, whoa
Boy boat toy boat toy boat. No soap
Just cope be smelling like a fart cloud German talking with his mouth too loud two foot too tall and never getting higher
Vocal cords sound like a swirling tire when I play house flipper. I think I
Gives me drugs. I don't know why I was making a bathroom
That's the last thing I remember sliding in the cringe streams when vids of the year were voted on recently
Yeah, I am invincible. I am unstoppable turn on auto-tune. Oh boy
You guys are fucking gonna derail this whole thing. Aren't you?
Hold on. Give me a second. Hello. Hello. Hello
Oh
Is it on? Oh shit. It's not even on fuck. I didn't even turn it on
That was really bad, I thought it was on I thought I was safe I thought I was so safe
Okay, here we go. Oh opster has another one. Okay, this is it after this cuz I'm we have to have to play the game
Before everybody leaves the like 14 of us to think this is funny. We'll stick around. All right, here we go
Last one it needs to be
It's gonna sound so weird. Okay. How about this one? This is officers response. I got a new monitor. So my shit
I can't really read it that well because everything is so small on the screen. So it's actually kind of hard for me to read it
I'm at like 144 P. No 114 40 P
Oh gee German the Worma cuz he's slimy. He calls his crew the Boston Beatles more like the Boston Ladybugs
My rhyme so sweet and variable
I call it Ebola Coca-Cola his flow so bad and sleeve of Oreos get thrown up all over the bed most crude thing to come
From Boston since the movie Ted I would say worse, but I'm scared
He's too hot would send him into his deathbed can't rap much longer ain't got the character count
But when it comes to rap battle victors, I don't think there's any doubt
Don't do that. I wonder how long would it take to be able to realize there was an auto-tune on you think like these people coming
To the stream. Okay, I'm gonna laugh and freak somebody out. Why does this sound so weird?
Does this sound weird you guys do the Tasman auto-tune the test? Oh my god
Okay, this is gonna put me out. This is it. Oh
It's the Tasmanian devil time with the fucking auto-tune on full blast full blast auto-tune Tasmanian devil turn your speakers down
I'm gonna tell you right now. I'm gonna be giving a little bit of a warning here
As many in devil I'm going for it here we go. You ready is it should I do this? Okay?
No, I just heard that in my head that hurt
This is the Tasmanian devil in the electric chair, okay, this is not doesn't sound right at all
This is like Tasmanian devils is it was tried is on death row for like the times that he's killed like fucking 50 people
With his tornado guilty
Auto-tune no, I have to get back to normal
It's the end of the year man, you can't nominate this shit anymore it's over I can do whatever I want at this point
You understand?
I'm safe. I'm free. I can do anything
Oh
It doesn't sound any different it actually doesn't that doesn't sound any different why okay, that's enough everybody relax
All right
People I'm gonna be known as the fucking guy that's on drugs every stream and I don't even do them
So we're done after this and how many times have I done this where I go?
Look at it. I can't I have to move on. Am I just the crack guy? I mean I might be
I just lean into it. Just be like the crack guy
whatever
Let me turn this off. I was doing no country for old men. I'm so goofy
He looked like earnest can't save Christmas by bars hop from the furnace
He really think his bar is all that but it sounds worse than a shitting rat his height dented got hit with a bat
He thinks he's a lion. Nah, he's just a cat in the hat that one. That one was alright. I should've done that one
Do it as saw. All right, if you give me a good one
I I need a good one to do as jigsaw and make a jigsaw themed
I'll put that freestyle thing in the background again. They'll do it or as as as Anton from no country old men
You give me a good one. I'm not gonna do a hundred gecks. That's a real song
Okay, say a hundred gecks a thousand times why I why you guys posting a hundred gecks. Oh my god. Okay, hold on
All right. Here's a message. This was okay. This auto mod held this one for bullying
I'm reading this one. This one is held by auto mod for bullying. Let's go
Kind of goofy
This one's like not even good it was held by auto mod for being bullying
Okay, here we go
You really get into these it's kind of fun who won who's next I don't know
This is what Jerma does to his friends on discord
Really does feel like that doesn't it get Freddy get Freddy to write something
Freddy if Freddy writes me a saw rap, I will do it
I I will do it in the saw voice. No pressure on Freddy
By the way, Freddy if you're like, no, I don't want to fucking do that Freddy. You write like a saw rap
I'll do it and I will release it on stream. You just ruined Freddy's DMS
No, turn off your DMS Freddy Freddy go private for like a week and then we'll talk post it to the main channel
No, nothing's to go into the main channel ever again. It has to be a music video
No, I can't do a music video
Yeah, January and February is gonna be so busy. I I can't oh
This is awful
Okay, I gotta turn the volume back up and we have to put on just some music just regular just kind of hangout music
No more freestyles. Okay. I'm gonna put like Animal Crossing
New leaf OST we got to come down from that. That's too. That was too much. I gotta relax held for auto mod for bullying
That's the like. Oh, yeah, send me your diss tracks
Excuse me. Don't bully the streamer. That's so funny
Well, at least I know it works. I'm not gonna put the music on times to speed just okay
Here's what you can do wait 20 minutes go open up the VOD and then watch this part in times to speed
You need to talk in half speed to match. Oh, come on
Don't give me more stupid routines to do now. I have to do this
So I was thinking of putting white up on the background here
and
You guys tell me if you think it's a good enough color
I think it's gonna look really nice
Maybe eventually we can put some
paintings up on the walls. I
Think that will come out good
Up stairs, however, I think we have to do something a little more
elaborate maybe a
couple of chairs here on either side
But what kind of chairs do you think we should put on here? Oh
Oh
This is not the chair
It's the paint menu
I
Think it's over here somewhere
Let me search for it
Chai
I
That's what I was saying to you earlier
This one with the green that's gonna look so good here
Okay, I think I have enough chairs there
Oh
Hey, does anybody see the new
Marvel movie is it any good? Oh wait, I think somebody's texting me
Feel a sneeze coming on
All right, all right, I need it clipped given me can somebody do that get that at times two and we I need to watch that right now
I want to see how close I was. I think I was pretty close
Can we get that section that like two-minute section there's to see if it was like a full minute of me of normal shit
You're a psycho. That's fine. You got the whole thing and I do this in times two. Okay speed times two
upstairs, however, I
Got it think it works
Think it works. Hold on. We got it. We got to confirm that this works. All right, it's time
I think I did a pretty good job that will okay. Let's see how I did that will come out good
Upstairs, however, I think we have to do something a little more elaborate
Maybe a couple of chairs here on either side
But what kind of chairs do you think we should put on here? Oh
This is not the chairs, it's the paint menu
I
Think it needs to be a little faster. I think it needs to be like two and a half or three
I need to see the three sounds like an AI generated voice. I need to see this at three
Upstairs, however, I alright somebody clip this. No. No, I need the whole thing
I need the whole thing. I need I need it at times three. Wait, hold on kid. It's too long
Clip this one and just do alright. Alright, get did you get that? Give it to me
Give me that what just happened right there and I'm gonna do times one make this. Okay. Here we go
Let me open this one because this would be times two. There's here on either side
Okay, so now let's do times times two on this one chairs here on either side. Oh my god. This is fucked
Okay, this is perfect. I
Eventually want this whole thing. This is now times four that will come out chairs here. Oh my god, dude
Are you kidding me? Okay times two
Chairs here on either side chairs here on either side
But what kind of chairs do you think we should put on here? Oh
This is not the chairs. It's the paint menu
Okay, that's a little too fast a little bit and needs to be 1.5
There's here on either side
But what kind of chairs do you think we should put on here? Oh
This is not the chairs, it's the paint menu
I
Think it needs to be a little faster. What I think it needs to be like two and a half or three
I'm too fast three. So wait AI generated voice. I
Want to see the whole thing? It's all right
See it at three
That's so stupid nobody all right, somebody download the
I don't know. It's time to do it in the reverse. Here we go
Ha ha. I think over here. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Right here. Right here. Here. Here. What should I do?
I did blue. Should I do this blue this blue right here? Good. Yep
That's not gonna work. It's too hard to go fast speed this one up chairs here on either side. Oh
Oh
This is not the chairs. That was so fucked up. Somebody said Vocaloid
All right. I'm no more derailing. It's time to play. All right, somebody
I know somebody on the subreddit in like an hour
We'll have that whole section sped up to the exact preferences that need to be to make it sound normal and then you'll see it
You'll see it there later in like an hour. I'm looking forward to it. All right
I just I was down doing the bathroom. I don't even know where the bathroom is
It was like underground somewhere. Oh, right. Okay. These are not the chairs
So I'm thinking
Hells why even do with this place? I was gonna make a theater, but it's the the castles like too big and weird
It's too it's like there's too many outdoor areas. You know, I mean
Just make a counter-strike map I
Made the FPS house already. I know this dude's actually playing the game. I know what happened. It's a user-made sawdust
All right
All right. I'll say this is too much. I'll do this later go back to the funny stuff. No more playing games
No, we can't it can't just all be
cartoon world
Oh music though. Yeah, let's put animal crossing back on
So now what I was thinking
Was singing you a little song
I'm done. I'm kidding. I'm kidding relax. I
Don't like this place. Yeah, I don't like this house. I want another one. What? Here we go. Here we go
Okay, I got my money back. Yeah, I don't like that place. Let me find no accept the offer. It's fine
Whoo? Ah
Whoo and the stream suit my family's making Christmas cookies. We'll go for like an hour or two
I'll be live in a day or two. Anyways, I'll be laughing Christmas Eve, but no, I'm not done
I want just one different house. I didn't like that one. I just say fuck it and buy the dumb boat
What can I even do with it though? I feel like I this might be just like the castle though
No, we already did the boat. This one was kind of cool
Yeah, I'm gonna buy this one. I did the moon house last time just make a big bird house
I did the moon one last time. All right now I'm gonna go for it
Actually gonna play I'm gonna do a regular house with a theater in the middle
Or maybe I'll just mow the lawn and then do a rap battle with the chat. I don't know. We'll find out
This is a nice house that I could decorate this to recreate your own house. I have a verse
I want you to rap. I'm not doing any more rap destroy your own house with a sledgehammer
All right. This is mowing speed. So I think this one's good
I'm going faster make a studio in the house and then just do rap battles in the house
What the hell are you doing? All right, whatever. Let's clean up. Ah
Leaning I'm gonna go room by room one by one just make a normal nice house
Should I actually try to show you guys what I think is a nice house what I think would be good instead of making malls
Comedy theaters ice cream shops best buys golf courses
Should I actually try to do a decent house for once in the three plus years? I've been playing this fucking game
Let's see what I can do. That's on the ground. No, it's a glass girl. Hi. This is the garage front window
All right, let's just let's let's settle down. Let's relax
Not the chill section of the stream here. Just relax with me. Take a deep breath
See don't you feel better what's going on with the ground what happened what happened you're in a really silly mood
I think that once every six to twelve months or so I let the goblin out and it just
Happens to coincide with house flipper updates. I give it all this now. Okay, I like this kitchen
It could use a little bit of work change these windows out. Don't let the goblin out. Ah
I will if I want to he's a broken. I need to redo this. Oh, right. Okay. Wait, okay
What TV is going there? So if this was my house? All right
Open the door a place my keys right here. What are my favorite colors? I want for house
I got a spray so dirty dad. Hey, what are you talking about? What are you talking about? I got it. There we go
Where is this other dirt? I don't see it on the ground. Where is it now? Whatever use Oh
Broken fuse. All right, it's kind of dirty. I clean this. Oh, it's the side entrance
Okay, find the same shelf that you have. What's your favorite Christmas song? My favorite Christmas song is
Grandma got run over by a reindeer
Walking home from our house Christmas Eve. You could say there's no such thing as Santa
But as for me and grandpa, we believe balcony auto-tune that what about the grandma got run off by a reindeer movie
Did not know they made a movie the sink has got to go a lot of this stuff's got to go
Bathroom needs it work. Is there a second floor a little bit of dirt left to get should be good though. Very cool
They take Santa to court sounds like a wild movie. He's scary for me. That's too scary for me. All right
I like this upstairs. You got to clean first
That's the most important thing and you just go one by one room by room and make your dream house
I've a lot of money
500,000 nice place this guy up here. I don't like the see-through door too many windows. I said shit
It's almost 4 a.m. Yeah, I'll be going for like another hour started a little bit late today
I had some stuff to get situated. Why is somebody saying fuck you chat? Hey, hey, what's your mouth?
Hey, all right. What room is gonna be my bedroom? Oh, no, where's monster rancher? I uninstalled it
I got to s-rank and I raged I threw my controller through the window
Exploded I was it was embarrassing and shitty. I can't get back in the house. No more dirt. I'm here. Come on
Get that balcony really?
Looks better. Where is it? It's not even on the map. This house is modernist trash
modernist trash
Modernist fucking sucks. No. No you guys with this
Into home design good. Okay, there's only one more room that I really need to clean this dirty one. Hey nice
Almost time to redecorate chat sees the new Pringles logo and thinks all modernist art sucks. What's the new Pringles logo?
What do you mean? What do they do? It's an iPad game. Um, I I mean, it's the new can it took they removed his hair
I didn't even know he had hair. Hold on. Wait, I didn't he has hair. He does have hair
All right
This looks like the episode of the Pringles TV show where he goes back to like the 30s and it's black and white
I mean who cares
Care
There you want my reaction who cares when they change the recipe of Pringles? That's when you'll hear me scream
They could put they could put clown makeup on him and give him like a big chef's hat
I don't whatever they taste the same
I'm just not looking forward if they ever make the Pringles guy a real guy in the commercials
Be like interesting and funny and shit and it's like a rich guy. I think everything's clean
I'm gonna go to the living room gonna start living room
Let's change the stairs to something that is way more tolerable than this. All right. I like a I
I'm not a big wood guy. I would ruin it. I think it it can be destroyed too easily. I'm like a vinyl
linoleum tile
You can just what is expensive and you can fuck it up really easily. Mmm. I don't hate the mahogany
I don't hate the mahogany and I don't like dark wood. Actually, that's not true. I like um, where's that?
Where's where's just like the right? All right, that doesn't look bad. This doesn't look bad either. This doesn't look bad
I'm going with the mahogany. It looks good living room time. What do I want my first of all?
I gotta get these walls taken care of cuz oh my goodness guys
What the heck's going on here ain't I like very neutral colors in my living spaces. I'm talking grays
I'm talking like kind of like olive off white not ever cigarette yellow though
I don't like a cream yellow. I think it looks like cigarettes like this. No cigarettes
Steel gray I would like on the wall. Probably. Let me say what it looks like
I like a neutral living room, although it could be an accent. I have an orange couch. No
No
No, it's too neutral. Let me just see what it looks like
And maybe like a blue. I love Navy really like nautical colors. I like blue white navy
This is too dark. Excuse me
Blue is a nice color. Yeah, I'm gonna have look I'll have a navy wall here. Let's try it nautical
No nonsense do something else recommend dark green. That's not a bad one either. That's a good one
Let me check this first though now reds too bold royal blue is I think too I'm thinking like a navy blue
gray fog
Moody cobalt. Yep, this might be the one live a little I love blue. I just I really like blue a lot
Now the question is should I just have that be blue I think so. Okay. Yeah, what's wrong with this?
Look at this is comfortable. You're making a restaurant. I beige. I'll give it a tester
White wall. These are not white walls. These are I don't remember. It's some kind of gray
I need to get my lighting in here. It's your dream house not chats. Do it. You want? Yeah
You want you want bright orange walls? Oh, just get the game. Why do you not have this game in the first place?
Why do you not have this game in the first place? This game is the most chill game ever that's ever existed
Oh, it's light. I think it's not wait. Is it on sale doesn't run on your operating system. It doesn't what how much is it?
I don't know. Let's find out how slippery guys. It's half off right now. It's ten dollars fifty percent off right now
I believe it's part of the winter sale. That's good
That's pretty good to me
All right, be careful over here
Ten bucks on switch to if you can't get it on PC. Oh, that's cool. It's no secret
This is one of my favorite games on Steam. I don't know if I want to do white over here
If this is too plain on the sides here, maybe something else here. What do you think? Maybe pistachio green?
Do I love it the last a little too green little a little too green
Lady gray
Hmm
My lab Mike fella into my pants like went down into my underwear and stuff I had to get it. Okay, I like that
Yeah, how does something fall into your underwear? We need some lighting in here. Ooh
Play it's gray that symmetrical. How are the windows? Sorry, you're gonna make you gonna hear some noise
I'm gonna make some noise. There we go. I have a half drank coffee that just sitting here
Hey when in Rome floor is now important and I'm gonna tell you don't like wooden floors down here don't like it
Don't want it. I want not carpet carpet. I will put carpet somewhere else floor panels though
I like that. I'd like
Yeah, I like this
Let me see. What does it look like?
Yeah, let me try the other ones. Yeah
I actually don't hate it. I gotta see the whole thing
I can't like this with this weird pattern on the ground is freaking me out. Okay, I need lights
I should put for lamps. It looks good with rugs. Yeah, it should be good lights. I
Don't like stuff like this too old. I don't hate this but I don't really like the wood
All this is too extra for me too extra way too extra. Okay, not bad too artsy
I feel like I have something I have something to prove. I have this the boring
Generic to streamer maybe no. No too old ugly. No
Ugly
Okay, I armin
armin armin
Now I don't want it
Way to futuristic extra weird shit and that too campy to fake sci-fi
To fake old sci-fi wedding no
There we there it is
There it is finally we made the shit that I think actually looks alright here we made it I like that
I don't like that ceiling fans. Yeah. Yeah, I don't hate that. Yeah, just do candles
All right. I'm gonna let's go this. Ooh
Here I like the gray like the gray this is gonna go right right there
Oh, look at that. Oh, I like that where it is. I might move it. See. Ooh, I like this too
Goldner. All right. Now we're talking now we need I need to get a couple more lamps. I hate
Ceiling fans, you know, I hate ceiling fans because most people that have a ceiling fan
I mean a lot of people have it fine
But when a ceiling fan is not mounted completely correctly, it's not maybe screwed in all the way on one side
When they have that weird
Wobble it just induces
Anxiety in my brain. I hate it if it's not perfect
And I don't like when a ceiling fan spins a lot something about it freaks me out the fact
If especially if you have a specific ceiling fan and you like, oh, yeah
I turn the ceiling fan on and this thing is a blender sitting above us on the couch
I don't know
I just feel like dude if that thing if it falls it's we're just literally chopped up like a fucking helicopter and like GTA
Especially when they're on high. This is you look up and you just see this
Helicopter blade just spinning. I don't like it mounted on the wall like a normal person and not sharp
It's something about how fast it moves. I don't like fast things. Let me name you some things that I don't like
I don't like when a car goes fast
Speeding and shit. I really don't like it anything that goes fast like more than 70 80 miles per hour is like
No, no, no. No, I don't like when cars go fast
I don't like the things spin really fast. You laugh at car accidents in video games
It's geared of ovens cars and fans. I don't like I don't like snakes
I love snake theoretically on paper as an animal
But I don't like how fast they are if they want to just be like
They can just go. It's I don't know what they couldn't move too fast
Spiders that can like sprint. I just don't like when things move fast. Yeah balloons
They fill up boom real fast air shoots out bomb like bomb explodes. I don't like it. I hate it
Okay, what was I doing? Yeah, I need the want the recessed lights anything with a lot of tension or that moves really fast
I do not like how's this one?
It's all right. I got a I'm gonna move these because I want to know what I'm gonna make sure I know where the couch is
You know what I'm saying suck. I'm just like poked a hole in my ceiling. You are a prey animal
So funny
Everybody's a lion, right? Oh, I'm a lion. I'm a tiger. I'm a wolf. No, you're not
Your horse no, you're not. It's 70% of people in this chat are frogs bugs
Smalls animals like my mice rats goldfish fucking aardvarks monkeys
You're a bunny. Yeah bunnies. This stream is all over the place. Should we tell them bear? Nope, actually, you know what?
I actually feel like a lot of you probably could be a bear like a grizzly bear
No, you don't want none of you lions lions the guy with the fucking ear pods on just blasting music in the gym
Like, you know, we're not we're not lions here. They look lizards. Yep. Oh, yeah
There's probably a lot of lizards here. Are we a lot of snakes was it looking up? Oh, yeah lights
I think some of you probably are lions. Some of you are probably tigers. These were my hyenas here than anything else
Why am I under doors lights? Okay, please ceiling. There we go. Just wanted to be I don't want anything fancy
Swanky, ooh
Look at that. Most of you are sheep. No, I don't believe that
I actually think they're probably more there are probably more anteaters here than sheeps really believe I think so
Let's get some furniture. No brick. I just think of bread
This looks like it hurts to sit on so it's like a coffin. This is a coffin. No, no
I like this one because it's like I don't know the couch is there another now
There's a million furniture living room sofa. Okay. I like that one. I like this one. Mmm, okay
This is okay, too. I actually kind of like this even though it's kind of weird. Oh, this one looks like a musical instrument
Too elaborate too many holes big too fancy weird a bed. Eh, uh
What was that on and I liked it? I like this one. It's kind of I like it
It's kind of weird a big corner. All right, what color do I want? It's comfy
I like black couch or a darker couch a lady. Oh
Now that's fancy. Oh, that's good, too. No we got
I
Want to move the window, I don't think I can hmm
Don't want the TV to be here. No, let's put you know what? No
I like a TV out on the wall the couch kind of needs to be here though
I don't I'm what I don't like the setup and then I'm stealing this and putting the TV here and you can't fucking stop me
No one's gonna say anything to stop me from doing this. No, but you're oh, no, don't close that off
Nope, nothing you can say that's gonna change my mind. Well, what do you think? Do you think it's okay?
You think it would look okay value your opinion very much. So, all right, where's the bathroom gonna go after wait
What's over here? So this is the garage?
No, what is this? I don't like that. I don't like that. Where's that? Where do you put the car?
Why is that there? I don't have a garage. Where's the front of the house? I can't find the front of the house
Where am I? Okay. This is the garage. All right, so it's not enclosed
You pull the car up here and you can get out. This is the front door
Where you get out and here's where you go in through the garage, but I say okay, so this is the bathroom
shit, I
Want this to be the bathroom does have a huge bathroom. Yeah, what else do I don't want anything else down here?
Oh shit, the kitchen. Yeah, the kitchen will
Oh shit, I supposed to watch TV on this wall. Oh, well, this house sucks for putting a TV anywhere
Does it someone the couch almost does it this house sucks?
It's got a couch has got to go this way then TV's got to go on this wall couch. Yeah
Fine, I'll get rid of my dream couch. I want to do this. That's weird
Is it weird though? I gotta open this up and see what this looks like because this this has to be the bathroom
Well, this could be the kitchen and this could be the bathroom
You understand because the kitchen I feel like needs to be here because this will be the kitchen
So you'll walk in and here's the little area. We put your keys whatever and then oh the kitchen
Yeah, you can put the groceries in the garage
Come on the kitchen in the bathroom. There's no privacy. Okay, that looks good. Yeah, cuz then I'll close this I'll close
No, I won't how come there are no walls. I just need to open it up and see how much space I actually have
Yeah, where's the load-bearing wall? There isn't one apparently
There's nothing keeping this house up. So if I walk in the front door, I got nice living room couch
TV let's get the TV up there right now. So I don't forget TV hanging 85 inch TV bingo beautiful a little bit. That's good
All right
This is nice my consoles in here. I look so cool. I put my consoles in there. Okay, I need sofa
So we can't we're gonna have to go with one of these which this is fine. I don't hate those
All right. What about one of these? No nut brown. I do black this house sucks. What's shitty wall placement?
I feel like this needs to be like here. It's couch is too big
It is it is too big one of these will do let's go with one of the ones I was gonna get up here
With this one here. I like that. This is where we go with a little bit of blue and orange maybe orange and
All right against the wall. That's comfy. I don't like this though. I want something else
Yeah, everyone's got a pretty good view of the TV. You can sleep right here. Yeah, I need like a media media console living room
shelves TV cabinet, uh
Whoa, I just yawned this music is putting me asleep. It is it's working. I'm like falling asleep here
I actually did a big yawn. I I'll stick with it. It's fine. I don't like the color some darker
I'm bad, you know fall asleep on stream. I need uh, ooh, I should like light shit. It's too close shit shit
It's too close. This thing is fucking huge different color. I like the black hitman gloves. Yeah. All right these few end tables
That's right. Just need a few end tables. Oh, those are cute. Oh, I like these I like those
Maybe not the color but you know, all right now I need a
Lamps standing lamps, although actually this is not even accurate
I hate having a lamp on a place where I can put drinks and shit. You know screw that
I'll put about a lamp and a plant and a decoration. You can't even use it. Not even worth it
I want like four sodas here. Those tables are too big. Yeah, they are. I'll get smaller ones living room tables
Oh my god, turn this off. Give me something else. It's not gonna put me to sleep. Why are these also sleepy?
These are all go to bed songs. Here we go. We need something else streets of rage to that's right
Sounds good. All right little end table. I don't like last tables. They freaked me out. They break perfect
I'm gonna lights I need a rug double color decorations
Is it would it be decorated pets with it is the pets expansion out the rug of decoration?
What the hell would you have this for what is this porn music? Oh
Yeah, I wanted a triple XL. Okay. All right. I'll get one over here, too
I want a square square. This one's got cool birds on it. Let's go. Oh, yeah
Rectangle I don't like solid colors
Forest animals like that. I'll change the pillow. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Hi. Yep. Can I edit this?
Hey, it does kind of look like a mouse pad. You're right. How do I edit this couch?
Need that kind of teal white green maybe green or is this up here?
All right. I want is this one here secondary color green. How does that look? I wonder too big
How can I put it here? What's going on? What's happening the wrong couch?
This one couch was it this one. That's cute. You need to move it a little bit though
That's soon in Miku big friend. This thing is dogshit. It's gotta go. I gotta do something lighter
I got it. I got it. No, I thought this is gonna be bigger
Miku dolls all over the place. What the why they are so small
Sorry, should I keep it that looks so bad? I'll fix it later in the meantime
I just have to get something in here to have enough be terrible
Well, this is gonna be the kitchen that means bathroom has to move. So let's get rid of all this crap
I can sell but wait, I thought the windows were permanent. Did they change that? That must have been an update. Oh
You could not touch the windows before I guess you can now
Interesting. Okay. Well that changes a lot then so I want this to be the kitchen. So you walk in
Bang kitchen bridge is gonna be get rid of these windows put them in later
I have to get my furniture in first before the windows gone. So
kitchen here that means I need what I need and you get the
Ground nice kitchen floor. I would say would be linoleum
vinyl big into vinyl and kitchens
You could dump a whole glass of wine on the ground and vinyl and just get it up easily
All right
No, I get that's the reason. Oh furniture
What is it? Oh, yeah
What do I want on the floor?
floor
Natural stone that sounds kind of cool. What does it look like?
Not very good. Okay. What about cream tiles? I don't hate cream tiles in a kitchen too bright. Mmm
I think it looks okay. Oh
Yeah, I think we're talking I think we're talking now we need a I need to put a wall up now because bathrooms gonna be here
I need to wall that off doors gonna go wish of the door. Yeah over here if he's over there bathrooms right here
I'll leave this open so I can put a door
Bathroom now, what am I one of the kitchen walls? That's a great question. What I put on the walls. How about like, uh,
Paint. I don't know. I feel like I'm doing too much paint wall tiles
Now it's too weird
carpet walls
What happened to the baby videos? Oh, you must have missed the the 12 minutes on stream yesterday where we did that
Hmm. Yeah, I'm feeling it. Um
Maybe
Horse mist horse mist. I think it's a I like it. I'm I'm digging it. It's not a vomit wall
It's a kitchen baby vomit. So now we have that done. I'm gonna put the let's get a fridge
I want a cool fridge. All right, here we go. Is it furniture electronic equipment was it was a classmate as well
These are kitchen accessories would be kitchen furniture
It would
Okay, so I need
This green I'm thinking the green would look kind of good. What do you think chat a chat? What do you guys think?
Hey chat, what do you think chat? This is a walk-in fridge steel
thing
stainless
Stainless steel. I think stainless steel looks good put it down. What's going on? Put this shit down. No, that's in a bad spot
And I'll put this because the lights hell what's going on dude. Why? Oh, it's this like thing on the ground
my fridge
Counters and then I'm thinking I like that. I like that, but I don't know what color I should do
It's green too powerful. Is that too much to go with like a
Whoo, what details I'll give that a look make it teal
Yeah, it's got to be darker either darker or just the old like just white goes white. That's good
There's no light in here now meltdown incoming. No, this house is too sterile and the fridge has to be white
It's like a cheap flipped Zillow house. I'm not a graphic designer. I don't know how to do this
We're hanging hanging cabinets
I don't that's not bad. We better. Okay. Now I need I got the oven. I've got the range
I need lights stove needs a hood. Otherwise all the gas is gonna go somewhere this sink
Wait, let me get let me get this stuff in here first. I need a functional
Yeah, let's get some sink shit in here
There's it in the right place. What the fuck is this thing? All right. All right, I think it's the oven
All these can open. This is a rest stop bathroom. I think it goes over in the over here though
It's a bar. That's how we what's wrong with that. It looks okay. I should get like a trash compactors functional cabinets
We go dishwasher dishwasher stove dishwasher
Little table. I'll come back to it. I don't know. I'll come back to it. I need some life in here crashing
I want those recessed cans. That doesn't look bad. Just get a huge piece of artwork right here and I'm done napkins
Knife forks. Yeah, put like little little gravy boats and shit everywhere. Look a bread box a bedpan
Okay, sure cutting board. This is cute. Look it's coming together. I like it about a big bowl of fruit
You guys
90% of house
Decorate like it's all just bullshit. That's all the counters who nobody cares about the cubes in the house
But the care about is what paintings on the wall and how many fruits you have in the fruit basket
I'm gonna give shit about anything else. It's all about detail work. Nothing else matters only detail work
You are the ultimate white guy. Why?
Why what he why what do you mean? What are you talking about? What what why?
Why is the corner empty because I'm gonna put something over there. I just haven't figured out what
Rome wasn't built in the day. It took them the whole of it long. The Bible took the right
All right. What am I getting right? Okay any table Rome wasn't written in the Bible
But what okay Rome wasn't built in the day
What did God do the Garden of Eden or something Garden of Eden wasn't built in the day?
There's another saying there's two of these the Garden of Eden was crafted after what is it?
God did a lot of things God made the world in seven days. All right. Yeah, that's what I mean
Rome wasn't built in the day. God took seven days to make the earth. So I've got some time
I can't it's not gonna say I've been here for an hour. God got seven days. Give me seven days
Rome one built in the day. I need a table even a little one. There'll be a dining room table
Oh, I like that. Is this weird to like open the door and this is the dining table
I don't think so. Where's it supposed to go?
Just wait till I finish this get all the detail work that all that that God has done, right?
Think about the detail work look at Mount Fiji, okay
I think God was really concerned that much about like the the pavement like the gravel on the ground
No, he's he was busy. He was busy crafting Mount Fiji in detail work. Here's your gravel on the ground
Just wait till I get to my Mount Fiji Mount Fuji. That's yes. That's the one I'm referring to
He's the water. Whatever. You know what I'm trying to say. I promise I like graduated college
Maybe just seeped out of me. Did it seep out?
Maybe there's like a hole in the back of my head and just like info is just slowly pissing out like a gas leak
I think I'm fine. I think I'm alright. Fiji is an island
Exactly what I'm talking about think about how much
Craftwork God had to go through to craft that island of Fiji all the all the foliage all the fawns and all that and all that
The all the stuff that's there somebody says lead exposure
Mount Fiji island. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right
Let's have a doorbell though. Nice apartment. No bread in there. All right. I need some paintings
I'm done like done streaming in like 10 minutes. Who cares? I mean I do I like I'm having fun this detail work out
Okay, put like flowers in nature shit and just colors all over the place. You're gonna be fine. It's too big
All right. Okay. Hold on. I'm gonna have some hanging on the wall. I've got a decoration. How would you have Medusa?
I'm gonna find an excuse to leave your house if you have this like I forgot to brush my teeth
I have to go home, you know, y'all are giving me shit for this
But I guarantee you you know
Somebody in your life that has this kind of shit everywhere
I bet you you've walked into somebody's kitchen and gone the hell is going on in here. It's like a weird bronze Greyhound
Statue in the corner in the kitchen. All right, let's put I'm done. See the bathroom table bothers me
It needs to be smaller. I agree with you. That's it floor. How about um stone white tiles? Let's see. How's this look?
Yeah, the tables not good. I know it needs to be in a smaller and different spot. Why is the bathroom so big?
I don't know ideas. I want room to shower and to bathe and go in the tub and stuff which reminds me
I think I'm doing a bath bomb tonight. I think so. All right ones in the chat if you want to do a bath bomb
Lush Andy, did you ever get one? Did you ever get Popeyes? No, I haven't I have not
Let's uh, let me put them. All right walls
something
Interesting in the bathroom here. Ooh, this is kind of cool. How does this look awful? Let's find out
It's not what I thought I picked up I'll buy surprise. Yep. What does this actually look like? Okay, pretty ocean
The ground could use a little bit of work get help. Why because you don't like my choices. This guy is on drugs
I am NOT on drugs. I'm on what God gave me oxygen life. Maybe pick up the Bible once in a while
Okay, why does it look this shitty? Is it the light? It's a light. Alright, so now I need a I want a tub
Whoa, are you shitting me? Yep. How do I put this in? I need a fixture. I need a tub fixture
How do I do it? Okay, we get fixtures need plumbing urine. Oh, I actually want one of these people think I'm messing around
But I would I want a urinal the amount of time and the I just want one so bad
Why does it it's just you know, it just have to piss into this thing. It's just so convenient shower. Okay, I need
Toilet washer bathtub plumbing system. Here we go. It counts as a bathtub, right? Oh, hell. Yeah way
I need a shower
Don't even tell me you wouldn't want one of these you had access to this just 24-7 just in your house in your bathroom
All right. Now I need a toilet. You wouldn't use it. Yeah, you would all the time
Was this a toilet? Is that a right toilet?
suspended toilet plumbing system
Suspended toilet. I mean that's kind of that's kind of swanky. Well, it kind of looks like a baby potty
But whatever I always see these in hotels and stuff and I always think they look cool. Yeah, I want one why it's so low
Like a lay down where you
It really is a potty how would you use this? Oh my god
And the urinals too high
I'm trying to see what with this would look like you'd have to be legs would have to be wide and
You'd have to just squat you don't have anything to hold on to it's not even a toilet seat
What is this thing? Why do they hit? What's this for sale for? I can't even move it. Whatever. I need a sink fixture
Even this sink what's happening?
I
Am I 30 feet tall? I'm so confused
Okay. No, do you see how low this was? Okay. I think it's fine. No, that's normal. That's normal
Oh my god, this is this is just where you just spit the mouthwash. That's that little thing
The dentist has next to the chair. I don't know. I didn't mean to put it
I didn't realize I'm gonna be this slab was gonna be so huge. I just need a mirror
That toilet is freaking me out. Why is it so low to the ground? Why?
Okay, I don't like the gold I think it's way too big. This is okay. This is all right. It's pretty modern
I don't get it. All right. All right. I don't care. Whatever. It's give me a door
And then I'm probably gonna call it another another twisted
Why doesn't say Hell's Kitchen stream another twisted? What is the name of the game house flipper? Not Hell's Kitchen?
What another twisted I
Why don't I want to say Hell's Kitchen another twisted house slipper stream? Okay. There you go. It's Christmas Eve
I can't even get in here. I don't think yeah, I can why is this so weird looking?
Why is it just barely too small? I love these colors though
I really do fucking happen in here the front door bro. This is the front door. No, oh you motherfucker. Just come here
Why can't I pick it up? I just I didn't mean to do that. No, I'm done. It's pretty good apartment
Okay, that's fun open bathroom no, I was gonna I'm trying to put a door there. All right
I will see you guys on Christmas Eve
We're gonna play some itch EO games if you have any games that you want me to play itch EO little horror ones
weird entertaining
quirky ones
I'm gonna play them then I
Should on Christmas Eve be able to give you guys a link to take the end of the New Year's Eve stream
The words so you should be the vote for what you want to vote for
Hopefully as of New Year's Eve if I can't get it ready by New Year's Eve
I can't get the poll ready and I'm probably gonna have to delay the New Year's Eve stream
Should be more like a New Year's first week of New Year's stream, but I
Very confident I can get it ready by 24th with that. We're gonna say goodbye. I think six hours is perfect here
Thanks for watching. It was fun house flipper is always an adventure
Didn't really get to build anything weird this time, but it's just fun to hang out and fuck around you guys
So as always yeah, the rumble would be on the same day. This was a crack stream
It was sometimes you have just sometimes you have one you just sober up
I've had a bag of peanuts a light breakfast and a coffee this game just does it to me. I don't know what it is
That was a nightmare. I think it was no I don't think it was a nightmare. I thought it was a
That was a daymare
Go eat something yeah, I'll figure out what I'm gonna eat was a good time. It was a really good time
I had a lot of fun yesterday, too
I'll see you guys on Christmas Eve if you're not gonna be out obviously people have stuff with their families people are doing things
people potentially moving around maybe you're going to
Families houses and stuff or friends. I don't see on Christmas Eve
I've ever have a really good Christmas a really good holiday whatever holiday you're celebrating if you want to spend it here
Elise Christmas Eve, maybe we'll see you good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. We'll see you soon
Have a wonderful rest of your day and have a wonderful holiday if we don't see you see you soon