Guys, it's very easy to be early when the stream starts normally four hours ago.
It's easy to be early when you're four hours late.
How are you guys doing? Doing well? Hope your day's going well.
My day's going real well. I got out of physical therapy.
Got some info. I'm a little tight. It's all right. We did a nice consultation.
Find out what we're gonna do going forward. Now I'm gonna go two plus days a week.
Let's go. Today, we're gonna be playing Incredible Crisis for the PlayStation 1.
The reason why we're gonna do this is because this game is a short,
albeit incredibly interesting experience from what I've told.
It's kind of a rhythm game, but not... I think the whole game is just fucking weird.
Because we're starting so late, this stream is gonna be only probably a few hours long,
so we don't go until like 12, 1 a.m. Pacific, and we'll be back tomorrow.
I did want to get something in here. I didn't want to just not stream today.
I wanted to stream because I like streaming. I like streaming. Quick, do a funny grandma voice.
That was perfect for what you're asking me to do. We got a wink.
That was a left funny grandma voice. I can do a funny grandma voice,
but that's not what you asked me to do. I had specific instructions. Wink for us already.
Hold on a second. I'm getting there. Just wait. Let's wait. Let people trickle in.
Hurry up. You're a con artist. Hold on. I'm doing fine.
But you didn't ask me how I was doing. Hurry up. How was your day? I'm doing good.
All right. You want me to quell this whole thing for you? Do you care more about wink
or do you care more about dog on screen? It's me being like, chewing on my tongue.
We're getting angry. I tell you, this thing's gonna get me in trouble.
I was like, more blink than wink. Hold on. I got you. Hold on. There. Use it. Print it.
Edit it. All right. You guys ready? I want to say, what's the MOBA? What's the MOBA that they made
and they patched it like 10 times and it got to a point where it was 1.0 and then they closed it?
Incredible Crisis. What was Infinite Crisis? Yes, that's the one.
Yes. Infinite Crisis is the game that got into 1.0 finally and then they closed the servers.
The family guy online. What the heck? What are you talking about?
All right. You guys ready? You can make a move around. This is awesome.
Here comes Incredible Crisis against the dog bones. Presents what? They present, but like
it's developed by Polygon Magic. Music by Tokyo Ska Paradise Orchestra. This is on PlayStation 1,
by the way. Is there a voiceover or anything? Please have a face. Two moons when I was Earth.
Here comes the ant. You all know it's my birthday today. What? Birthday? Yeah, that's right.
I'll make your favorite dinner. It really is that family. It's 3D movie making. Not again.
It's the same family. Not again. Of course. Brad movie's free. That's my reason for living.
Happy birthday, grandma. I want everyone home early today. Who just opened that?
Who just closed that? Take an ice cream. Michael got old. Story of Taneo chapter 1. Goodbye. I
missed it. Whatever it said. Where's this? Okay. What are they doing with another Earth?
Daydreaming? Time to exercise. Wait, the office is. I mean time to. Taneo dance fever. Okay. Okay.
Hold on. Okay, everybody. Let's do some exercise to relieve the day's stress.
Let's dance. Press buttons and direction buttons as shown. Make a mistake. You're
fired. Your skill level goes down. Perfect dance. Your skill level goes up. This
game cannot be paused. Push what? Push what? What is that? Oh, what was that wrong? I did it wrong.
That's good, Taneo. Good job. This is why it takes so long for somebody at Comcast to answer
the phone. Is this what people do at the office? Holy shit. Hang in there, Taneo. How am I doing
this wrong? What? You're doing great. What's on your resume? You know, I got my master's in
business engineering. I sold brick. What? I already love this game. Okay, now I'm killing it.
All right, so when does the trap door open underneath the person that did the worst?
You've pleased me. Back to work. Hey, well, that was fun. They do this every day. What? What the
fuck? Holy shit. Bowling inferno? What? I thought we were dancing. Avoid the iron ball. In the
distance, meter turns red. Run with X. Make sure you have enough energy drink. When running, use up
and down directional buttons to avoid obstacles. What? I'm going to be being followed by a ball?
Wait, what do I have to do? I'm tapping, right? I'm tapping. I'm tapping. How much do I have to
tap? I didn't... Avoid the iron ball. If the distance meter turns red, run with X button.
So don't do anything until it's red. Okay, let's go. I have to have enough energy drink.
All right, I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. Oh shit, I have to pay attention to that too.
All right, we're good. All right, same deal. Oh, fuck. It's going to hit me. All right, we're good.
Got it. That was interesting. Elevator of doom. First try. I made it. Phew.
Wouldn't the... Is it going to open and the ball's going to be there? Excellent. Is this an emulator?
No. Oh, it's like trying to get me. It's following me around. Why is it doing this? Stop the elevator.
Break it with X button. Stop it before the counter hits zero. Use directional buttons to avoid
falling objects. Blue meter indicates breaking power. I'm confused. Stop when it gets to zero.
Use directional button. Oh, okay. I get it. Stop it at zero? Mash A? Wait, stop it now?
Who's dropping bots and fans at me? The people have thrown rocks at me. I can't laugh. Hold on.
I can't laugh and play this. Oh, it's too many. Hold on. I got to get the... Hold on. I know what
to do now. Okay. There's a lot going on. Stop it. Break it with X. Stop it before it hits zero.
When it hits zero. This is not a superhero movie. Okay. Here we go. I'll get this right now. You
ready? Why is it not registering these? I'm doing it too fast again. There we go. I'm literally
pressing it too fast for it to register. I was going like... Like, you know, I can do it if the
game wouldn't register it. Am I dead? Again? We don't want to register this shit. It's still
following me. It's still trying to kill me. What the fuck is going on, man? Am I going to be all
right? Nerd. Nerd. Nerd on a wire? Okay. Now what? Cross to safety. Press and hold X button to move
towards the green zone. If you lose balance, recover with directional buttons. Pull will snap
when the time is up. What? I'm already gone. Oh, I get it. Okay. 40 milliseconds? 50 milliseconds?
What's this milliseconds? What? Get in the middle. All right. I'm good. Oh, God damn it. I try. You
have to hold... Oh, fuck. It's going to happen again. Okay. Fine. I'm fine. It's the Tony Hawk
manual. Except sideways. We're good. I feel like I'm letting that go when it's supposed to.
Don't get over it. This thing's going to snap, isn't it? Now what? What the fuck? He's trying...
He's holding. He's trying to hold it. Come on. Hold it for like another one more time.
That's a lot harder than it looks. Trust me. Trust me. I'm really good at Tiger Woods golf.
Holy shit. Okay. That's harder than you think it is. Guys, I get a perfect drive in Tiger Woods
every time. Trust me. This is much harder than you think it is. Am I good? Hey, no. What? Is there
gust of wind? I'm fucking trying. I didn't get it once. No, I didn't because it's really weird.
It's either too much or too little. This game's running... It's like 20 FPS. I'm not getting all
the exact frames that I need. All right. We're good. Nope. Look at that mocap acting. All right.
That was pretty cool. All right. That was... Oh no. I got an A in bowling, an A in dancing,
and a C in an elevator, and a D on nerd on a wire. That's not good. Oh, this is a PlayStation 2
memory card. Right. My PS1... I don't know where it is. This game's like three hours long. Don't
worry. We're going to beat it. Story of Teneo Chapter 2. Five seconds to what?
I'll check it. Paramedics, the A team. Hold on. Just answer the questions. Press X for yes or
O for no. 10 correct answers are needed to clear the stage. Two wrong answers in a row will trigger
an electric shock. Hey, listen closely. Is 47,326 an even number? Yeah. What? Yes. What?
Hey, are you okay? Did Nightingale take an active role during World War II? What? You have to give
a heart massage. Hey, I can't read the text. Is one centimeter 10 millimeters? No, it's not. What?
I pressed no. Are you still alive? Is one kilometer 100,000 millimeters? No. What?
I'm pressing the right buttons. Wait. X is yes, right? X is yes?
Four play by six people per team. Yeah. Okay. I got it. I got it backwards. X is no. Oh my
fucking God. I thought X was yes. Okay. I got it wrong. X is, I thought X was yes. X is no.
No. Press X for yes. I had it right. What? X is yes. You got, you're freaking me out. I live in
America. I'm an American. When they start asking me about like 10,000 milliliters, I'm going to
get it wrong. Okay. Here we go. Is Maine the northernmost state in the U.S.? It's not. I
saw, I thought it was. Listen. What is it? Michigan? Is 21 an even number? No. He's American.
Is soccer played by 11 people per team? Yes. Are the reindeer pulling Santa's sleigh all female?
No. No. No. I'm okay. Is soccer played by 15 people per team? No. You just asked me,
that's the question. Is four hundred and three hundred times two? No. Um, I don't know.
There's two. I couldn't do it. Can you hear me? Is 30,000 equals five? I don't know. Yes.
I don't know. I can't read the fucking numbers. Is 218 times 2576? No. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. Is basketball a sport played by five people per team? Yes. Is one times one two? No.
Can you hear me? Is 68 times nine 610? I don't know. No. I can't do that. I seriously can't do
the writing in two seconds. What? How many hoes are there? Ten. I don't know. Point A is three to
be north of the tower. Point B is one to be north of the tower. Is point A five meters south of point
zero D? No. I'm dead. I'm still alive. Is one plus one, that's one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven twelve. Shit. I thought, I thought they were going to throw something in
the end where it was like is one plus one plus one plus one plus two plus three minus ten ten.
You know what I mean? I thought they were going to do a minus on me. Is Maine? No. I already know
this because I've, guys, I've died three times. I can come back to life and get the same questions.
We rewind. Is the currency of Japan yen? Yes. Hey, you're still alive. Is California the western
most state in the U.S.? No, it's not. No, it's not. It's probably, I think it's Washington.
Or Alaska. Is basketball or sport played by five people? Yes. Or Hawaii. Hawaii. Hawaii is all the
way over there. Are the reindeer pulling this leg all female? No. By the way, yes. I don't know. Hey,
you okay? Is soccer played by 11 people per team? Oh, I don't, I don't watch soccer. I've never
watched one full game in my entire life. It's 96. Yes. Hey, are you okay? An even number. No.
You hear me? I have no idea. I would need, I would need to write that down and do long division.
It's 300 north of power and point B, one of east. I don't fucking, I can't even read the question.
I gotta get these right. Point A is, is point, fuck. West of B and D is 200. Is the west tower,
is the tower? I can't read that fast. I can't even read. No, yes it is. No, it's not. I'm dead.
I'm gonna lose again. Point A is, it's point A, point A at point. I'm gonna suck her for a while.
What's it, what's it? One plus one plus one. Is that, no, what's, no, no, no, no, no. What, what is,
was that a two? I couldn't, it's a, it's like the blurry fucking line. I can't even read it.
Just do it again. Start over. I thought it was a plus. No, it's not. No, they're not. No,
they're not. Oh my god. Oh my god, I hate this one. They keep changing the questions.
I think I haven't memorized, but they haven't, fuck it, they changed it a little bit.
I think I haven't memorized. No, they're not all female. It just said are they all male. I thought
it was the same question and that's why I didn't read the other. Yes, it's yen. Is the currency of
Japan? No. Yes. Hey, can you hear me? No. Three, no, no. It's 100 minutes past 11,
15, 12, 15. What? What do you mean, what are you talking about? 100, no, it's not. Is the tower,
Haidotokyo tower 330, what, how am I supposed to know how tall the tower is? What is that?
How many sets is it? Oh, it's incentive. I don't know. There could be a small miniature tower in
Tokyo. That could be like a small welcome to like the miniature tiny Tokyo tower. I don't know
what's going on. I've never been there. Oh shit. Oh shit. I got to do that again. I can do the
whole thing again. All right, hold on. I can blow, I can do this one very easily, but I need to get
that memory card right now. Oh shit. Shit. Why is he being here? He's Yorika. This game, no.
Tokyo tower is? How do I know it could be? It's under a lot of stress. They can electrocute me.
Just when they think, I think I got the answer. All right, let me check this. Make sure it's
actually going to read this. Me and my friend beat this with no memory cards.
I don't care. I'm going to use one. What the fuck, dude? Easy. Oh, we had big bits come in.
I know how these ones work now though. Don't you'll see. You'll see. I'm interested though.
Now you got me interested. A phylactery lich gave $55, 5550 bits. Hey, Jerma, I bought the ring.
I'm going to use to propose to my girlfriend today and it's in part thanks to you. Thanks for
always putting on a good show and keeping us laughing. You're our special boy. Another marriage.
Another marriage proposal. That's two in a row. Oh, congratulations on the proposal, right? Hope
it goes well for you. Hope you guys are happy. And I'm not going to say anything to potentially
ruin it because that's what happened yesterday. Thanks for the huge amount of money. I'm happy to
be your special boy. Well, no, no, that's weird. That's kind of weird to say out loud.
All right, here we go. Dance fever. I'm going to get, I'm going to get A's on all this.
Let's do some exercising. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Fuck. Oh, did they change the song too?
Or is it the same? Good job. Can you please ask my wife to marry me? Well, I do like that you can't
pause these. It makes it more interesting. I'm Han Solo.
Impressing those at the right time. The dude on the right looks like Jerma.
Pretty cool suit. No, I don't. I need to get a new suit. What color? What should I get for a suit?
What color should I get? Should I get like a pink suit? No, no, no, no. Yellow? Wait, what's
someone in Dumb and Dumber? Pinstripe? I don't know. I don't know if I would. Pinstripe would
work here. I would, I would, a light. No, you just, I have people saying that because of the
Joker. I get it. Um, I'd like light purple maybe. Red or green? Just trying to get to grandma's.
That's all I care about. Turn the brightness down. You think so? Too bright? Is it too bright?
Maybe a little? Well, we'll take a look. We'll see. What do you think about this? Better? Look a
little better? Oh, this part. This part kind of sucks. Here we go. Take it nice and easy. I know
how to play it. Fucking TV. Look out. Turn off the pixels. Uh, I can't do that because this is a
video game that was developed in 2002 or something. Cover that TV. All right. That was much cleaner
than last time. I'm much happier with the outcome on this one. Do it. Come on. Do the line.
Get me back in that ambulance. Get these questions right. Oh no, I forgot. I have to do nerd on a
wire. Shit. All right. Let me try to get this at least once. I can't get a D on every single one
of these. Here we go. Dude, I'm telling you, this is fucking hard. It's, it's very, it's got to be
that. It's hard. Get in there. Finally. All right. Got it. It went faster that time. It
fucks with you. Shit. Come on. All right. It's going to be faster. Yep. It's faster again.
Come on. Hit. Oh, good recovery. Immediate recovery. Oh my God. That's hard. I can't imagine
getting that every time. Whoa. Oh my God. You can do it. I know you can. I know you're capable
of it. There you are. Here we go. Okay. Would it be easier just to, yeah, these are just wrap
around the thing and shimmy up. All right. It's time to save the game and let's get back in that
ambulance. In Alaska, the Western most state. What is the Western most state then? Why for
a lot? Is it how it's Alaska? No. So what is it? Why? How far over is Hawaii?
Like data data one. All right. Here we go. Five seconds. I'm going to get this. I will do this.
That doesn't matter. It takes me three hours. Why is also East? That's what I mean. They,
that muck ass, you know, it could be it's East and West. It's the East most and West most state
potentially. Right. It's one kilometer, 10,000 liters. No, it's not liters. I couldn't even
get it's hard to read. It's California. The Western most state. No, it's one centimeter,
10 millimeters. It's not no 10 centimeters is one. No, an odd number. Did it say liters again?
I get hard to read. I thought of millimeters. Yes. It said milliliters.
Is soccer played by 15 people? No, it's 11. It's 8, 57 times 9, 7. No. Yes.
We got a wink. I know. Hold on. I don't, I have no idea. How the fuck am I supposed to know?
Hold on. That's a lot of subs. That's a lot of subs. Harrow is heavier than Hanoka.
Pierre is heavier than Harrow. Hanoka is, is Pierre heavier than? Yes.
Yes. Uh, Freddie Dredd. Freddie. Freddie. Hold on. No, Freddie. Freddie, did you go to,
did you go to Hash House or Go-Go? It's 93, 60 times 21. Not. Yes. I'm alive. I'm alive.
A hundred community subs from Freddie Dredd. Did you go to Hash House or Go-Go? And was it
your favorite restaurant you've ever been to in your whole life? Thanks for the fucking
100 community subs, Freddie. That's ridiculous. Insane. I, I, I need confirmation of that because
you said you were going. Well, we didn't get the verdict. Ride the stretcher. Use left and
right directional buttons to steer. Avoid cars and motorbikes. If you hit construction signs,
you'll lose control. For a while you're done when the distance meter reaches zero.
All right. Don't hit any cars.
All right. Why does his voice get lower? Can I jump? Is there a jump? Jesus. Why are they on
this? I have a long way to go. Come on. Stay good. Stay good. Oh my God. How many times
am I going to get a hit? I can't. All right. Settle down. Settle down.
I'm not, I'm not doing this. I hit one and it fucked up forever. I'm not pressing these buttons.
Now I can press. Dude, how have I not failed? I can't. I just read the funniest comment.
I just read it. And it's going to stick with me for like two weeks.
Somebody said, why? What's with the America's funniest home video music?
Or any show on Animal Planet? Oh, God damn it. That was fucking funny. Oh,
look at me. Oh, Freddy. Freddy says something again. I went twice. I got the blue cheese burger
the first time. It was great. And then the chicken and waffles the next time. My girlfriend loved it
as well. Thank you for that wonderful suggestion. I didn't get to see Betty White's slot machine
though. Unfortunate. Unfortunate, but that place is awesome. I'm glad they took care of you.
Wait, what? Don't I have a wife? Wait, am I going to like, Taneo? That's not, Taneo, what the fuck
are you doing, man? What? Did we just go? Love fireworks and Ferris wheel. He just waved at the
stream. Hold on. Find the pressure points. The lady wants a back massage. She will guide you.
Find the points with X. Press X repeatedly to fill up the massage meter.
Okay, I don't. What? What does that mean? I don't know what that means.
Oh, God damn it. Fuck. Okay. I get to put on like fucking animal planet music again.
Okay. All right. All right. All right. So that's not what you think it is. That's like a remix of
a famous song. I just don't want it to tone. Hold on. I don't want to turn it off. Just wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'll do it with all the audio. You don't need to hear this.
I'll pass you bedtime anyways, you kids. Okay. What? Okay. I'm going to get Twitch arrested if
I keep doing this. Okay. Hold on. I don't. Okay. Oh, God damn it. All right. I'm going to get
through this. Let's get through this. I'll get through this. Yeah, I got to get some fucking
background music to make sure like people, whatever.
You don't need to hear anything.
This is uncomfortable. This is uncomfortable. Is the song still going? I can't even hear it.
I can't. Is it still going? I have no audio. I have to do it. Dun dun dun. Okay. I'm glad this
is muted because this is a lot of, this is a lot of fucked up stuff going on right now.
The other one. This is the new one.
I didn't play the new one. Make it stop. I'm trying.
All right. Let's go. Anybody in the chat, over the age of 18, stay.
She's happy that there's a back massage going on.
This is not the way I'm going out. This is not the way I'm going out on
Twitch. This is not the way I'm going out on Twitch. This ain't the way I'm going out on Twitch.
No. Not going to happen. Let's get to that.
This is a strange of things.
This is too hard.
I'm gonna fucking pee my pants.
Alright, come on.
Oh my god, man, this is so hard.
Do you understand how hard this is?
Look, this is fucking impossible.
This is impossible.
Alright, no, no, no, no.
Fucking god, I can't un-
What is this?
Stranger Things-
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
Is this like fucking spoilers?
I just saw season three fucking tease, and I just had to-
I can't hear what's happening.
I don't have audio for my desktop.
I saw season three tease, and I'm like, oh fuck, is it like-
Are they talking about the season three?
God almighty.
No, I don't want any more Stranger Things.
The boys of Stranger Things on fucking like Conan O'Brien.
Get this off.
Come on, I have to get this.
Why?
Why is it on this?
I just went- I went and hit the back button like six times.
Why is it on Stranger Things announcements?
I'm paying attention to the game, and I look over at chat, and I see-
Fucking change it, dude, change it.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
I got it, this is gonna be it.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh my god, man.
Okay, I got it, this is gonna be it.
Done.
Okay, we'll be back.
Alright.
Jesus Christ.
I can't believe my fucking legs.
Did I?
Alright, be real with me.
Did I like spoil fucking strange things like all three seasons?
Did I?
Like, I hope I didn't.
Did that actually happen?
No?
No, did I?
Yes?
No?
No, did I?
No, seriously?
Don't fucking tell me that.
How do we get from America's Funniest Home Videos theme to Stranger Things announcements
to-
You played music.
Oh.
Why did she leave a bomb with me?
I only got a C.
God damn it.
Dirty old man.
For that one to be under review.
We had $50 come in.
Twice.
One from Vimthral and one from DesoidCatchfuck.
You got an A.
Do you permit override?
Yes.
Vimthral, thanks for the 5000 bits.
Fat bits for a very funny man.
Please read this as it's important and this person needs to hear it.
Okay.
If you're out there.
Ignis Scientia.
Please let me put your beautiful aqua line nose in my mouth.
What is that?
What did I just do?
Also, chat, you better be making the away noises each time Teniro makes them in the
game.
Thanks for the huge amount of money.
It's a Final Fantasy character.
Now what the fuck is going on?
What is going on in this game?
Thank you, Vimthral.
Independence Debate?
Independence 3A?
Hello?
Oh, Rurika.
It's me, Dad.
Don't let them attack.
That's the...
What are you all talking about?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
That's the what?
That's terrible.
Okay.
Protect the UFO.
But first, I want to say thank you to, uh, Desoid.
Another $5000.
It's 5000 bits.
5000 bit currency dollars.
Uh, thanks for the 50 bucks.
It's my birthday today and I had to go to three important meetings.
It's the hardest I've laughed today.
Thanks for making today a little less stressful.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Thanks for the 5000 bits.
Thanks for sticking around.
Hope your meetings went well.
Alright, so shoot down the missiles attacking the UFO.
Directional buttons to aim and X to shoot.
Why are we siding with the aliens?
Again?
Why, why does it...
Did I shoot the planes?
Someone's there.
Oh, it's coming right at me.
Oh!
Even in...
Oh, this is kind of hard.
Okay.
He just...
Come on.
I did it, right?
150.
15.
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Good.
That's not a UFO.
That's a Simon Says.
It does kind of look like that.
Titanic away.
Not every day you see a middle-aged man falling out of the sky.
Thank you so much.
That's okay.
No big deal.
Um...
Oh!
Why did you...
What have you done?
Bail water out of the boat.
Press X button repeatedly to scoop up water with a bucket-press triangle to empty it.
Avoid falling objects with an umbrella.
The directional buttons.
Reach the goal before it sinks.
Do I have to help him?
Wait, he...
Oh, he's gone.
Sorry, Captain.
I hope I don't lose points for that.
What?
How did I not get points for that?
Come on, help.
Faster and faster and faster.
Oh, here it comes, right?
I tried to press it.
It didn't do anything.
Uh-oh.
We're not moving.
If he goes in the air again, I'm doing it.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, that...
Yeah, an umbrella wouldn't stop a guy not hitting you.
Just get out.
Come on, move.
I don't care.
Just go.
No, it's gonna sink.
He's trying to kill me?
I get it now.
Can you hear the fucking furious tapping?
Dodge, right?
How do I dodge?
I just left, right?
You don't?
Wait, I'm just supposed to get hit by it?
I don't think I can dodge it.
I'm sure I can.
Fuck, I thought that was him.
Stop trying to fill it up all the way.
All right, let's...
No, I can't go forward.
I can't go left or right.
Maybe that's scripted.
Oh, come on.
Felt good.
Throw it.
All right, dodge, dodge, dodge.
No, come on, come on.
50, 50, 50, 50, 50, 50, 50, 50.
37, 36, 35, 40, 15, 10.
Give me a D, I don't care.
Great Canadian FK Club.
Another $50, 5,000 more bits from another person
that's been like fucking seven of them.
Thanks for the huge amount of money.
I cut the brake lines.
What's wrong with this lady?
What the hell was that?
Did we just get like a Hideo Kojima?
What was that?
That was like a please unplug your things turning off, right?
Okay, you just killed a dog.
No, you didn't, thank God.
I was gonna say, worst game ever.
Honey, I'm home.
I made it to Grandma's.
I did it.
Great Canadian says,
Is this like one of those flash games
where you need to shake your mouse back and forth
to make the story advance?
That was an A.
I got an A+.
I did it right during the...
I'm never gonna be able to hear this song ever again
and think.
It's always gonna bring back memories.
B and A equals an A+.
Yeah, but I got extra credit.
Story of Etsuko, Chapter One.
Etsuko's errands.
New character unlocked.
This is Mom?
Okay.
Afternoon of the Wolves.
Wolf robbery?
Oh dear.
Get to the exit.
Press X repeatedly to move forward.
If the robbers are around,
step back with Triangle.
This is Five Nights at Freddy's.
Step back with Triangle.
Use the security cameras to detect their location.
Be alert when the robber indicator turns yellow.
So where am I?
Oh, it's coming.
Okay.
Hurry, hurry.
Get to something.
Go, go, go.
Hide, hide, hide, hide, hide.
Hide.
Okay.
Um.
No, no, no.
Stay, stay, stay.
So he goes left,
and then he,
was he turned left again?
It's probably gonna walk down this way.
All right.
I'm gonna wait till he goes,
walks this way.
Is this,
that guy's permanently looking this way though,
isn't he?
Okay, I'm right there.
Why'd the guy,
okay, hold on.
Go.
Who saw me?
Top left.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I'm the next best.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hurry up.
Hurry the fuck up.
He's so slow.
Okay.
He's gonna see me every time.
Go.
What?
I'm trying to hide in the other bush.
Get in there.
What?
Okay, I made it.
So now I gotta go across to the couch.
So I'm not safe here.
I'll be safe when he comes this way.
So here we go.
Bang.
Safe.
Here we are.
Now we got a scenario.
We got red, top left.
Goes back and forth,
and then he goes that way.
Red comes back down.
When he turns this way,
it's time to go now.
What?
No, I was,
I thought it was gonna turn green.
Fuck.
I thought the one on the left was gonna turn green.
I thought,
cause he was green,
I thought they was gonna turn green
right when I stood up.
I'm gonna get caught.
Ma, just break a window and dive.
No, do it again.
Do it again.
Get there.
Am I there?
All right, here we go.
Two, three, and go.
Okay.
Now.
I got,
I'm right there.
He's now red.
He's yellow up there.
He's green.
He's still yellow.
Now he's red coming down.
Now I can go.
Not yet.
No.
What's the scenario where they're all green?
Right there?
Right there.
One, two.
All right.
It's when,
holy shit.
Okay.
It's when he walks down.
When he comes down,
I get an opportunity right now.
No.
It's gonna be,
I should know that.
I would have been caught.
One, two, three, and comes again.
Here he comes.
Here we go.
This is the part where we go.
And here it comes.
I'm spamming it.
Settle down.
Jesus, Cherubi.
Wait.
I have to steal the diamond pig.
Oh my God.
Okay.
That was, I was about to say that's not,
that was very ridiculous.
Okay.
You didn't,
pound for pound.
Balance the weights.
Move items from shopping basket into plastic bag
so weight of bag and pig become equal.
Use L1 and R1 to switch between basket and bag.
Use the X button to select items
and the square button to compare weights.
You can select up to six items.
Okay.
There's Paw.
Snapper.
Okay.
I'm gonna say,
we'll put a snapper over on this side
snapper and a okay let's go to the now let's go to the plastic bag okay these
way am I trying to get them to both way the same
yeah oh my god this is gonna be fucking hell okay five six seven that's seven
thousand on the left four five five seventy seventy five eighty five ninety
put this in the put this in plastic over here this is three five eight nine
ten this is ten it's ten thousand over here so we got four thousand fifty five
hundred seventy five hundred eighty five hundred forty eighty five hundred
ninety eighty eight hundred eighty you don't he doesn't get it he doesn't get
it what are you talking about I mean I don't get it I don't get it I do not
wrong that's the prices I thought I was supposed to making the bags equal thirty
three thirty four over wait so I have to get rid of I'm thirteen hundred and
thirty four I get it okay I understand I get it okay all right thirteen hundred
thirty four over let's get rid of this one thirteen hundred thirty four so I
need oh I need now I need 1666 short so let's go 16 got like 15 15 15 what do we
got 33 anymore 33 we got a couple 33 right 33 1144 all right now I know it's
gonna happen sorry I'll just take I'll take the spike in the head I get it so
you the left bag has to weigh the same as a pig let's go all right anything in
now no all right let's go with let's go with two snappers what we got two
snappers I need 26 I need 2666 let's get this in here where is it 59 get it in
there it's a fucking weird number I can make it work this is a weird number to
let's say let's check it out 2227 all right let's get like another fucking
weird number in there 27 now that okay what we got like tissues put it in a
weird-ass number 2172 all right let's get like get this radish in there what
oh I can only have this row only six items okay hold on let's get this weird
item in there 1592 okay what do we got in there 1592
92 take out take get this shit out of here what do I know 136 I just do the
math that's 36 this is 230 all right give me one of these tomatoes I'm gonna
take out 94 what's this what's the odd no what's the odd number in here 2000
2000 380 650 15 and 230 if there is no odd number it's just that the under the
weight is I need the odd I need the word I need the 59 okay I mean I need the odd
numbers I need to make the I need to use the odd numbers make me I get it I got
I'm gonna try to make the number even first so we got so what am I what do I
need 7010 all right well there's nothing here for 10 let's do the 44 all the low
ones maybe let me see if the no no no 33 carrot no 140 44 what there's a weird
one here 933 is there a 33 here there's an 11 is there 11 and a 22 it's an 11
11 the herb 30 the herb is not 33 so hold on this is 33 I'm gonna back in
22 but get rid of the hold on wait wait wait wait get rid of this
what does that make it I want to press the other button get over here get rid of
it all that's fucking game over omega well what's wrong with you I don't do
math I don't know I don't know a goddamn fucking thing about addition or
subtraction I use my hands and I'm 34 guys I still I use my hands and I turn
35 this year now you give me an English paper to write and I'll get an A plus
you put a number in front of my face I will I will spit it out like cherry
I was like a fucking baby sitting at a high chair all right so where we need to
load let's load elementary school all right let's continue I have to do the
sneaking again god damn it your mouth which is you you write my English final
I can't do that all right now I know how this one works though how do you do your
taxes I don't I have a CPA that does my taxes I don't do my own taxes I do not
do my own taxes I have somebody that does that for me and they're a
professional and they're hired to do so I just come in with like an
encyclopedia size like binder or shit and I'm like this is all my stuff and
please do it and the guy he's he's I've been doing it ever since like 2012 it's
where the guys every time I go in there there's this I don't know if it's the
way I think it's the guy's offices made differently or strange or whatever but
there's a conveyor belt behind him of clothes that like and like people come
in behind there's public people they do in their taxes there too I don't know
I guess that's he keeps his clothes behind him I don't know what it's for
but and I always just leave that was that was a sneaky one that was a sneaky
one I'll tell you that was a sneaky one hope I get I'll get caught no go back
don't go back no I have a CPA so I don't I can't do my fucking do you think I'm
good I have to count on my fucking fingers
you guys think I'm capable doing my taxes 100 million years we'll make a lot
of a so funny thing I appreciate it I'm glad you thought so otherwise you would
have not laughed and you would have said that wasn't funny I didn't think that
joke was funny and I would have been like fuck I'm gonna try better next time
thanks for giving me the confidence I need to do more though all right why
doesn't he walk down here now here's the full reset all right we have the one
opportunity right not right now no is that on the next pass this turns red
this turns green right when he comes down it turns green green green here it
comes no this past year one two why are you playing weird shit from the 90s
again I don't feel like it oh you already see this cutscene all right I
gotta do math this game is 50 years old hey by the way not even from the 90s
two thousands just saying all right let's go let's go let's go let's go what
5,000 I need to do big first right let's go big big bear claw I need to make
some do somebody I need to always my CPA all right now I need three let's get the
what's with four should I do the two the two fishes or just go huge 3,000 what we
need 1355 do another fish 645 all right 645 whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait I need 645 that means I need what's 220 220
plus 320 220 plus 320 is 540 0 120 what do I need oh that's over oh shit you're
right okay fuck no no I want to take it out take the meat out take the meat out
come on two three five five to do enough fish is there even a nice there no fish
you can do the mackerel is already with the with the second fish is there two
fishes those two there's two meats where's the one that's 1,500 right now
this is 4,000 should I do one meat the 44 and 11 in here was that 11 like this
prison prison prison prison what was this like a little twig right okay dude is
this shit changing 2300 2300 okay wait I gotta remember this this is this is the
tissue and the weirdly fit 2300 I need another 2,000 another 2,000
2300 foot 650 fish out but take the fish out you guys have to help me with
this I can't do this shit not a hundred million years fish out horn in fish out
horn in all right 300 all right I need 220 and then all right bear paw bear
paw tissue leaf horn paw tissue leaf horn was the month for 140 was the one
for 140 was the one for 140 I know it's here where's the one that's 140 I know
it's in here oh done done done done done Bart Bart I'm fucking really really good
very good I went to a job interview the person at the job interview lies it's
so bright this is getting booed the job interviewer asked me to do something
basic like that like hey let me ask you a question I know you you you you have
the job I just want to tell you you know the perfect candidate you could
write an English paper so easily and look at these I can't believe what
you've done here look what you've done I mean just like for the sake is like the
guy at the counter over there the guy the guy that's in the front desk he can't
even fucking do 220 plus 140 plus 300 you know what I mean like what is it
isn't that fucking hilarious be like it's one two three yeah look I'm gonna
shit my pants I have to go I would pull that card I would pull the I'm gonna
shit my pants I have to leave thanks for the job I would just start going like
my chest hurts I don't know what's going on something my chest I would take like
I would go to the hospital for that like oh oh oh not have to do fucking an easy
math problem oh yeah we got the results back you will find what was wrong but
why'd you do that I'd be like oh look let me write you a check well you know
for all this nonsense that you've had to go through I guess we'll have three
checks here Jeremy you'll get the money if you can tell me what they add up to
the code the statue secret oh it's her and the golden pig play a tune repeat
the robbers tune by pressing O square and directional buttons to the golden
pig's secret message play eight times oh my god this is stupid no pausing no
sorry this is cute looks like OBS
why is it going what trying it's my directional working I almost got a
perfect shit a little sloppy but I got it do I get a cut of this money finally
it's awake the ultimate weapon Benjamin you watch out what did I kill it with
right on to a snowboard now that's that was unbelievable snowboarding with wolves
probably gonna dodge right snowboard escape avoid attacks with left and right
directional buttons you're safe when the distance meter becomes zero just dodge
how am I supposed to dodge gunfire awesome
golden eye insects of course I'm easy dodging these attacks just have left and
right
I don't have any like banana peels I can throw back I mean it's hard not at the
walls because if they hit me with a bullet I fly into the wall sweaty all
right can we be done it's the wall that's in the middle oh god damn it oh my god
what a disaster I'm getting no control of the character they do a lot of falling
sorry you can do me that's fine I'm not very good with this character I'm not
gonna map not very good at snowboarding all right I'll get an effort I'll get a
D in this class the enemy from without emergency all fighters rushed to the
Tokyo Bay area I have to cook dinner we're fighting aliens again wait why is
she going into that a fly a jet all right looks like the top gun little
bumpy fly the fighter avoid obstacles with directional buttons fly against why
the fighters safely to the exit this is a little bumpy all right is there up and
down there is up and down nice tilt that's not what would happen this would
explode okay I'm driving against traffic stay in the bottom so far so good I'm so
wide though Jesus all right stay up they're gonna go down now I have to
concentrate we're good all right down no they never go down just stay down the
whole time I mean if that's not a B I don't know what is number seven come in
huge monsters heading towards Tokyo attack immediately Rico what is she
doing here bear wars everyone is down number seven you're our only hope stop
the ferocious bear fighter is on auto flight mode use directional buttons to
aim X to launch missiles hit the switch on the back of the bear eight times to
clear the stage fuck you game okay got it hit it hit let it hit right into the
seven more times mom mom is kind of fucking badass apparently you more oh
yeah that was over here for a second turn it now wrong way this is a really
great ride at Disney Preston I got time check it out ready one two three got one
more two more oh
being over one more quickly turn it around quickly turn it around turn it
around come on is it oh no turn turn turn turn turn come on please
oh you're not in range turn shit bear it's time to start dinner nice work mom
the grandma's house menu is sukiyaki great shot kid one in a million it's
got the egg yeah I could have done I'm way more I got wait a hole in a B and a
C you get an egg there's no a to be found on that report card I believe
whoever is grading this is being paid a very very hefty sum of money to make
sure I do not get less than an egg the story of suyoshi chapter 1 oh it's the
it's one of the kids wait we just take care of this is a we going back it was
not very good for that kid all happening at the same time the Tarantino film wait
I'm tiny I got shrunk I thought that the bear was just drinking big-ass beers or
something and throwing them down yeah I didn't think I shrunk any of the hill
escape from the antlion climb up with X button while the meter is changing color
avoid mudslides with left and right directional buttons use directional
buttons if you get caught in a slide the game is over if you slide all the way
down why do I have this right it exponents in the middle preemptive jump
that was a preemptive that was like what oh shit
make me laugh right now
just me just somebody filming me from behind okay he's even got like that the
hair part walk yeah he's any very deliberate walk just turns into that
doesn't it spiderweb kiss of the spider-man I hope we get a royalty free
spider-man that would be amazing to move forward press and hold the X button
until the meter reaches the green zone be aware of the meter disappearing at a
set point if you lose balance recover with directional buttons the game's
over if the spider gets you hold and let go oh I get it it disappears okay I feel
like this is gonna turn into a real pain in the ass don't say it resist I'm not
gonna say it ah so close some of this should happen tomorrow 64 it's so slow
ah no fucking way am I gonna hit that he's shitting me stop he's turning stop
oh my god I have to get it use your finger and trace it over the screen now
that's brilliant too bad I didn't think to do that it's alright my parents are
not gonna be mad about that the only D I got is in visit you know I got really
really dog shit grades and visit when I was in middle school in high school you
know why because I never wanted to bring a change of clothes to school because it
was oh you change and then you get you change clothes and then you go to the
gym I don't want to do that I was painting so I just didn't change my just
I just like kind of just did things very slowly and it was like hey Jeremy you
gotta change clothes no I don't I don't want to put clothes in my locker okay
absent for the day okay what have you done wait didn't we do this already
they'd go nuts if you did they'd get there was a big problem if you didn't
change I'm not a smelly person guys and I didn't I alright we were playing if
we're playing like the pickleball or something I'm just gonna take it easy
I'm just gonna do it lightly I would be I was fine you guys don't know pickleball
the greatest sport ever invented but you guys didn't have pickleball everyone
should know pickleball yeah I agree I'm shocked at this that's like one of the
most fun it's like tennis and ping-pong mixed together into one sport yeah I
just made a bunch of new pickleball fans some of you guys right now what the
fuck is he doing a pickleball you're gonna go to watch a YouTube video and
it's gonna you're gonna you're gonna become like a pickleball champion you're
gonna love it trial you're gonna love it all right the same the same thing with
water we've got a clone minigame here it's a clone minigame who it's not it's
harder okay it's the same one that dad did except it's way harder of course they
get like this job to the kids I'll be honest though this is like an old man
would you rather have an old man or like an eight-year-old do this that's tricky
I don't know the old man or think what if the old man goes down and it goes like
and then he can't go any he's done but he throws his back up but he didn't
though yeah I guess that's true if if he's not getting hurt by getting thrown
out of the boat a thousand times we gotta move now we gotta move now come on
this boat's going great you motherfucker I kind of like just double tapped come on get this
fucking boat moving get this fucking boat move oh I got it dude but how do
you get away from this fucking guy dumping on you to it efficiency is more
important let's get three one two directional oh I don't think the
directional existed back in here one and land to go do it oh fine fine fine
fine fine throw it yeah maybe you should try getting a job I'm a fucking waiter
I've been waiting tables since I was like fucking 19 what the hell are we
talking about Mantis Park did you imagine being served by
imagine you just have to dinner and I walk up hello oh hello you two how are
I three of you how you doing welcome yep welcome to the cheesecake factory
that's that's me hi am I I'm gonna be Jeremy I'll be I'll be dealing with you
today and let me just tell you we have got quite a special today we've got an
eggs Benedict on top of a beef brisket that is smothered with the best gravy
we've cut this out of the Mississippi welcome again I can take care of you but
waters all three of you and then I'm like it was you you call me back over at
some point you like I think that's him hey dude I I know are you Cherma but
sorry about that no no I'm not no I'm not and then I get another job so I
don't see you again yes okay goodbye it's you leave a big one this a wink no
that wasn't what a fucking lie I have it up right here no there was holy shit
all right when running use up and down directional buttons to avoid obstacles
oh it's just it's just more of this but only it's the kid now I gotta dodge is
that a job is it a dive or a jump which I don't understand which one that is I
got hit by every single problem jumping over those how does that make any sense
huh all right I'm jumping over him and I'm just smashing it and I gave the
bill and I see that yeah you got you guys got you guys got like the two for
two deal whatever the two for the two for five meals deal whatever whatever
whatever the fuck they have that gross restaurant and you sit down and you say
okay okay yeah here's here's your tip and I get like like a like a 4% tip or
something I must have been terrible and I do I stop you and say did I do
something wrong I mean this is this is like the bill was like 80 bucks and you
gave me like two dollars is everything okay you made it you made it to
grandma's I love these freeze frames it looks like shit what's the last time you
guys had the Cheesecake Factory never never four years ago story of Rurika
this is the last family member okay oh I want to go what is it holy shit it's
well that's fucked up what sneak out of the classroom move the kids around to
reach the goal choose a kid with directional buttons and press X to
decide don't get hit by the flying chalk game over if Rurika gets hit wake up
dozing kids with X switch kids run run out of the class run wait what am I
supposed to be doing switching seats oh two one two two the ZZ one two what do
you mean why they all fall well I've the everybody's sleeping in this guy's
class this would be so infuriating if you were a teacher if you were fucking
it's teacher and you turned around and every single fucking student was asleep
it'd be like I get we're gonna check to see if there's like a gas leak this the
that's the only explanation is there a fucking carbon monoxide leak in the
school holy shit I gotta do this again holy fuck I actually might do it no the
person's knocked out oh I have to do it again what are you doing that many
people are sleeping you class man do that insta punch to the face okay let's
go oh shit oh my god oh so fucked up don't go wait why is it not doing go
go move move move I didn't what he's doing what's my indicator oh okay we're
fine come on hurry up dude is he gonna turn around every single time I hit the
button are you gonna wake up you gotta get up get up wait one two don't turn
okay wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up
got it go get out my not out I can't do anything they get out okay I have the
indicators that no indicator I can't move what the fuck just happened it has
to be bottom right it's does not I thought it had to be just the right side
here but I had to be the I have to be in the bottom right seat that goal could
very much be any of those see there those two seats oh my fucking god get up
wake up turn wake up X to wake up X to wake up it's not waking up X to wake up
it's not waking him up I don't peen what was that where's my indicator I have to
wait till it gets all the way to the end dude where's where's the where's the
cursor I don't care you know my cursor back I got out dude that punch in the
face it was unbelievable that's brutal I was fucked up
gives me you drop something oh lady what a beautiful lady the goods must be
crazy get the sale items select an item with directional buttons and press X to
decide if you forgot what you have no no no no no use l1r1 to toggle you need
four items to clear what do you want me to do limited time sale get the lipstick
alright press X to start I need to get the this one here this one that's the
one right wait what that was icon wait hold on splice sale items summer lips
peach I just got I got ring scammed in Diablo 2 my lips peach my lips peach
fucking fake stone of Jordan all right limited time lip gloss great great lip
gloss lip gloss every great skill call thanks for the five community sub thank
limited time sales current and special lotion oily skin dry skin body wash
lotion lotion oily skin got a body wash floral body wash vanilla here body wash
floral body wash floral floral floral floral where is it
body wash floral body wash floral body wash floral body wash floral where is
it really not that that much you know what's going on this mundane life
simulator now it's incredible crisis game is insane thinking don't remove
memory card and controller mundane the girl got her brains bashed in by her
teacher why am I in the bathroom what are you talking about I mean I'm in the
bathroom I've been in the bathroom over that robot what's with the robot oh it's
like the bill it's like build a bear workshop oh I look terrible oh now this
is where she makes the bear huge why is it bear alive you come and sing with us
why am I locked in the bathroom why does the person keep saying this are you on
drugs what are you doing huge UFO appeared over the Tokyo Bay this evening
its intention is still unknown mama that's your mama someone is on the
missile battery but oh it's dad ignorant encounter oh community crack
night Rika dad why is he there hello Oh Rika dad don't let them attack that's
the mothership oh it's all coming together don't worry about it just don't
attack don't let them attack but you want to make contact with her I'll help
you I'm supposed to sing all of the lights the colors of the UFOs lights
correspond to the respective colors of it it's gonna be Simon Says remember
the person that said that like two hours ago they said that's not a UFO that's a
huge Simon Says give that person a gold star twitch where's my gold star where's
my gold star this is the best feedback you're gonna get from any channel on
this entire website I want my gold star for somebody in chat that only lasts for
like 20 minutes it's like a little mini VIP it's a gold star and it pops up
next to the name and it's there for like 10 minutes I want that here we go they
were right when do we start we have already started green pink green pink
green but what is that green oh it's triangle it's the button okay five more
to go X X X X X X that I can do this one all dad you know how many times I
pressed that in the last two Lord of the Ring streams circle hit this guy off the
get cut away circle X triangle circle X triangle X circle X triangle X circle
circle X triangle X circle circle X triangle X circle triangle triangle X
triangle X circle triangle X circle triangle triangle X circle triangle
square triangle X circle triangle square triangle X circle triangle square
I was just fucking ruined everything saying it is the TV station getting a
phone call X square X square triangle X square triangle circle X square triangle
circle square X square triangle circle square circle X square triangle circle
circle square circle X circle triangle circle square circle X circle triangle
circle square circle triangle X circle triangle circle squares X circle triangle
X triangle circles triangle triangle X I fucking I lost it it's triangle X square
try
one more I don't know what it was what was it red I I don't know what it was I
don't know what it was I fucking if the screens that's gone the pixelation on
the screen is fucked it up I don't know what it was I don't know if it was right
let's go fuck shit these ones are easy blue blue blue red pink pink blue or
orange green green sorry blue green green pink blue green green pink red blue
green green pink red blue green green pink red yes red blue green blue red
blue green blue red blue green blue red red blue green blue red red blue green
blue red pink blue green pink red pink blue green pink red green blue come on
give out to see I'm that's played if it's fading it's fading pink blue great pink
blue green pink blue pink blue green pink red blue green green blue green blue
green green yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm shutting the fuck up for this
one green pink pink green pink pink blue pink green pink pink what it wasn't
pink blue blue blue blue green blue red blue blue green blue that's a good
sequence red blue blue green blue red blue blue green blue red pink red blue
blue green blue red pink red blue green blue red pink red blue green blue red
pink all right get me the fuck out of this he's crying no I'm laughing to
what else are you kidding me story of a Ricky chapter 3 there's no place home
what that was no place like home I got that wrong not another boat sequence
mr. let us get on your boat no more boat shit Titanic away one more time honest
oh it's not every day and I have a pretty girl on my boat thank you that's
okay no big deal you I wonder what's gonna happen hmm should I unplug this
like my entire fucking idiot family has done so far what have you done okay
thousand meters there's got to be a way that I can move pixel perfect good rhythm
got it up before you hit me time it come down one more I'm going for a big one
right now not gonna fucking hit me oh shit that was as a statue oh oh that
hurt better okay boats gonna sink okay major major major choke major choke
this is like dropping a ball in the end zone at the fucking bottom of the night
inning in the world series and getting a penalty on the kick holy shit let me get
on the boat oh that how you play pickleball it's one of the rules yes the
crane D crane wait rain thanks what's that if the killer crane press X and
triangle alternate alternately go forward directional buttons to go
sideways don't get run off by the crane it's hard this is hard is our X and
triangle oh I have to how do you do exit triangle I'll turn alternately I got a I
got a not just two hands but I have to push that to press this to move out of
the way use both hands and foot not gonna it's my chin I'm getting tired
it's tiring me the wheels broken turd turd I didn't want to do that one again
not again I want to do that one twice oh what ET song are you okay now great
goodbye I did it now we can have dinner as a family oh I do permit this is fun
wait hold on camera how come we didn't get to play as the dog that's not fair
funny some videos yeah this is when it's when grandma chugs the milk and then
somebody says something funny and it comes out her nose and they submit it
AFV and Bob Saget goes I'm gonna take the drink of this milk and now oh no
it's out my nose the original the original guy that does this voice it's
Bob Saget Bob Saget the original Elmo hey they do it every year
yeah nice cool
is there a secret level America's funny some videos I want to hear that I want
to hear the America's funny some videos so when Teneo cheated on his wife out of
the next slide please yeah this was incredible crisis it's an old
PlayStation one game and it's a little weird fun though I had a lot of fun
that was great and ladies and gentlemen that has been bite-sized Monday we'll
see you tomorrow no I'm just kidding we are not done there is something else I
want to put in here just to play for a little bit yeah that was that was a lie
is a game that I've had for a while and now is a great opportunity because the
PlayStation set up it is the original the original should I show it or should I
say it I wonder just say it or should I show it the original
pasta groove the originals very very very good oh yeah it's the game the
games are crazy nobody knows that game yes they doubt did you see how many
people just plug their faces off when I just showed that there is a rise actual
secret level boss to groove not bust a move bust a move is the matching game
must approve is the dancing game okay this actually is a secret part this is
often did a meteor hits their house welcome to incredible crisis actual
ending to the rat movie yeah all right let's put him bust a group for a little
bit we'll play until I guess I'm done playing it
let me just see what mini games there no what about hidden folks we can do that
we'll figure it whoa hold on there's a lot of DVDs Titanic away the tense
teacher what was your favorite mini game mine was probably was my favorite let's
go by stretcher the porn one about that one yeah sure I like the paramedics one
it was fun they really messed with you no I think we've seen it all I don't
think there's anything that we haven't seen all right let's take it up I mean
the streams gonna be short but it's not gonna be that the only reason why the
streams gonna be short is because it's obviously getting late already we
started late so here comes that your favorite sound