Alright, hello. We'll go for a little bit longer. We'll do some of the Blade and Sorcery update.
It should be opening now. You should see it on your screen in about five seconds.
One, two, three, four, five, six. Alright, Blade and Sorcery. I'm ready.
We probably will put the cap on. Maybe we'll go back another day on disassembly. It's so much fun.
It's just such a relaxing game. If you want a relaxing, just chill
and cry on the ground because a microwave won't open. It's fun. It's 30 bucks, so it's a little
one on the expensive side for a VR experience, but it's still good and there's a ton of content.
Why is everybody laughing? Did I brush my teeth? What? What are you guys talking about?
What the hell are you talking about? I can't even see. I gotta see what you guys are saying.
Back in the closet. Nope, no one's in there. You guys are fucking twisting me up. I have
to check every time now. Alright, so where are my hands? Well, there's one hand. Alright,
this is where I was before. Let's go. Next. Oh, whoops. Play. Calibrate. Blade and Sorcery.
It's been a while. I kind of forget how to play. We will continue. I believe it is right. Oh,
my god, that I'm running too fast. Oh, you have to move your hands, right? And then it's,
yep, it is the right trigger, the right grip. Already fucking shit up. Watch me take the tip
of the candle. Oh, it was a trash can. Either one. Alright, let's go. You can do two grip
at the same time. If I remember correctly, you can, right? Maybe not on this particular sword.
You got stuff in your pockets. You can dagger and then either holster over here.
So what we got? Canyon. Arena. Market. Unknown location. Work in progress.
Should we go check it out? What's new? Upstairs. Cool. So, god damn it.
It's getting worse, the amount of things I'm going to smash into. Honestly. Did my room get
smaller? I feel like the room got smaller. Take his arms. The room got smaller. It did.
Look at this. I'm already hitting shit. My room shrunk by like 45%. What's up there,
anything? Alright, let's test out, oops. I like the spears the most out of all the weapons.
These are my favorites because you can just go like this and just fucking charge. Right in the
face. Right in the face. Right in the face. Alright. How do you, what's the throw? Isn't
there a throw? Is it grip and then grip again? What is throw? Enable climbing?
They don't talk about the book so close to you. General climbing. Experimental. Player
invincibility. Physical climb. Physical climb. Alright, so what does that do? I can like use
your weapon to climb. Oh, this is really weird. Oh, there's a chest up here. What's in the
chest? There's nothing in here? Oh, okay. Alright, let's go fight. Alright, what's in
these areas new? This ruins arena. I feel like, is Canyon new? Let's go check it out.
Oh, wow. Alright, we're gonna do very easy because I'm gonna get back to playing.
One of the potions, right? This is cool looking though. I like this, like the stabby sword.
Okay, let's get the potions ready. At least one of them. Alright, here we go. This is
the snake technique. Let's just do wave one. Let's just do very easy. Let's just, because
I gotta remember how to play. Here we go. Always have to be moving around in snake
technique. What the hell happened? What? Why are they running away? Whoa! Already,
oh, that's brutal. Um, I already, I already lost my headphone. Come here. I'm trying
to cut her leg off. Get me. Oh, he got me. Get him in the face of the shop. You'll
be mine soon enough. We good? We did it. So you can cut people's arms and legs off.
Now I need to, I need to heal. Healing, please. Let's try, uh, something quick. Let's do two
of these. It's hard to get the grips. The grips are right here. I need to, I gotta
heal. Alright, let's do it again. Let's do wave three. Come here. Right in the neck.
Oh! There's a wall. What? Whoa! Whoa! Hey! I'm trapped in a dream.
I think I broke it. Just come over here. I, come on, get. Damn it. What? I have to,
what the hell? I can't pick anything up. Oh, now you gave me a sword and now you're in big trouble.
Get out of my fucking face. That's some good steam. That's some good steam. Climb with the
axe. Holy shit. Is this getting over it? I need another axe. Let's go check over here.
I wasn't prepared for that. Oh my god! Grabbed up! I just Super Mario'd a spear. Jesus Christ,
my hand is shaky right now. Oh shit. Not what was intended. Not the flourishing move that I
intended. I'm gonna put a fucking hole in my wall. VR is too dangerous. I swear.
Oh my god! I'm gonna throw it in my room. Get off my sword! Another one! Get off! Get off!
Oh, I just fucked up my hand. I just fucked up my hand, I think.
Yeah, I did. Seriously. Oh, there's some skin ripped off there.
There. It's brutal. Pogo stick with the spear. It's going through. Hold on. That's fun as hell.
That's fun as hell. All right, give me some healing. I'm gonna pogo stick for somebody's
head. I have to just goomba stomp somebody. So it's like up here. This is gonna be fucking
ridiculous. Here we go. Oh, it's close! I got hit. I got caught. You're ruining my fun.
Oh shit. Pogo, pogo, pogo, pogo, pogo, pogo. I gotta do that again. I feel
like I could get it. I'm gonna skewer somebody. Oh my god, my back. Okay, let's go.
But I need a lot of enemies. How do I track this down? There we go. Uh oh! Uh oh! Uh oh! Uh oh!
Uh oh! Uh oh! Yes! Oh shit. I got it. Use the axe on the zipline? Oh man,
that sounds like fun too. Axe on the zipline. All right, let's go for it. Um, haha! See you
in hell. One, two, three. What? We both did the same thing. We both did the same fucking move.
That was just Dark Souls PvP. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas.
I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. We got a raid came in. How's my hand? It's all right.
A little wounded, but it's fine. Kiwo. Hey, Kiwo. Kiwo coming in with a raid. Oh,
all right. Kiwo did come in with a raid. Hello, everybody. I'm currently in the uh at like 245
calories burned and I'm already done. Kind of winded right now. Uh, we're doing blade and
sorcery. Thank you so much, Kiwo. I hope you had a good stream and welcome everybody.
We're doing a pogo stick technique. I'm gonna try it again. Sorry, I'm a little sweaty.
That's what happens when you get in the virtual world. All right, let's try pogo one
more time with like 30 enemies. But again, welcome everybody. Thanks for the raid, Kiwo.
Fuck yeah. Thank you. Uh, I think I know what's wrong. All right, pogo stick time.
We're good. This is like the funnest thing I've ever done. I wonder how high can you actually
get? Oh shit. Okay, let's get back up there. Just run. Just run up there. You're too long.
There we go. Okay, I got my Garuva. Let's do it. It's just another heavy wave of monsters.
Here we go. This is hard. You can fall in a million different places.
I'm gonna go up. Can I get up there? This is a gap here. This is, this is tricky.
There you go. Oh dear. Oh dear. I'm good. Ducked. You duck. How did you duck that?
They're so good at dodging. Oh god. What happened? Oh, get it. Get it. Get it, guys.
Come on. Oh, you pulled me. Come here, you son of a bitch. I'm getting pretty good at this.
Stay down. Just like rowing a boat. Check this. Ready? We're gonna end this one with a
flourish. Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
He ducked. I just shot himself with an arrow. Oh god. Oh god, it's over. Oh, no.
Let go of this. What? Oh, fuck it. I got the double pogo. Oh, come on. What the hell?
What? How did I make two of you? How long is this fucking level? How many fucking enemies are
there? How many enemies are in the level? Did I beat it? I did it. That was hard.
That was on hard mode. Oh my goodness, I'm fucking exhausted. I actually fought
30 people in real life. And won. And I won. And I won. That was wave three, hard mode.
The local man goes crazy in VR. You're crazy. What the fuck? Why? What? It's a video game.
You're sick, man. I think it's time for me to wind down. Close the closet. Okay.
Drink some water. I'm made out of 75% water. I'll just drink myself.
I'll be fine. No, I'll be fine. Oh, yeah, I think I'm gonna have to call it there. I'm
fucking destroyed. What? The Dane Axe? Okay. He's gone. No, not this shit again.
What's the Dane Axe? This one over here? I'll go easy. I don't gotta prove myself anymore.
I just pogo stick through hard mode. Yeah. Clip that one. Why the Dane Axe? What's the
cool about the Dane Axe? Is this the thing they can chop off heads? Climb with it.
I'll give it a try. God, it really is getting over it. Just VR. This is hard. That's a lot
harder than it looks. I don't think I'm, okay, I'm not supposed to be up there. It's like,
it's a good wall. Because I'm clearly up here. That's the problem. See, look. Okay.
I'm, like, stuck on the edge. Bye! Okay, I'm fine. All right, let's do it. I'm just
gonna try to slaughter somebody with this. And then I gotta get out of here.
I'm past the point of tired at the moment. Burnt. All my fuel in my body has just turned into
burnt-out molecules. I'm gonna do an easy one. I wanna try to get somebody's head off.
Like, clean off. Oh, no! Hold on. Time out. Time out, please. Oh, my God. That's gotta
be nice and clean. Ah, come on. Close. I tried. Oh, that was perfect, too. Didn't
get the head off. Oh, no. That was an opportunity. Get back on the ground.
Pretty good technique. I thought that guy was, I thought he was undead. Got it. All right.
That's gonna be it. I'm gonna go get some water. I'll come back onto the bits. We'll
hang up a little bit. I am fucking exhausted. More blood. Not tonight. I'll be right back.
See you guys in a minute. That was weird. He was just still going, huh? They were
still fighting. Weirdly enough. Thanks, everybody, for watching. I'm fucking drained.
I gotta go take a shower. God, VR is so much fun. I wish I had the stamina to play it more.
I wish I wasn't such a boomer. But we're gonna do the bits. We're gonna hang up.
Shower stream. No. Think of it like getting really good exercise. Yeah, I know. It's
just spending four hours at the gym. Oh, Kiwo. Kiwo's still hanging around.
Kiwo, so what do you plan on the next few days? We were already talking.
And I'm not streaming tomorrow. I'm up in the air probably the next day or two. But
on tomorrow, today is Saturday, Sunday. On Monday or Tuesday, maybe we can figure
something out. Possibly. Wednesday? Thursday? You hurt your boyfriends and you abandoned him.
Oh, my. Oh, my. Why? What? That doesn't sound good. You're playing GTA RP? Oh, God.
I gotta stream. You gotta stream. RIP boyfriend. Yeah. Well, hopefully he understands.
Horrible girlfriend confirmed. But if you got time in the next week, I'll keep the VR
hooked up and we can do some shit. Should be fun. You're gonna have to give me a tour of
VR chat with extreme, with extreme limits put on it. I have to have like five people
with shields that walk in front of me. We made you a glue man avatar. That's fucking amazing.
Are you serious? I cannot wait to see that. That's unbelievable. Hit me up on Discord.
We'll talk more about it. But I'll be around Monday or Tuesday. Maybe we can set something up
for like Tuesday or something. Because when are you getting back? Give you a day to settle
whenever you're coming back. We have a rat related avatar. I cannot wait. It's just a
place to hang out and show off your expensive full body. That's fucking awesome. Surprise
avatar. I can't wait to see this. This is gonna be great. But yeah, thanks for the
raid again. Sorry we kind of stopped 2030 but it's after you came in. But I just I have no
stamina. Especially in this virtual world. The world that's in VR. No spoils. All right.
I'm looking forward to it. Whatever it is. But let's do the bits. Let's go back a few
hours ago. And we had five dollars coming from Afterlooksatrix. Thanks to the five
dollars. Hey Jerma, back in 2017 I sent a bit message saying I was going to France to meet
my boyfriend for the first time. Well this summer I'm moving in with him. Ain't that rad.
Anyway I've missed almost every live stream but I have watched every single VOD.
You have more fans than you realize. Say it with b-chat. Jerma Hart. And they say party party
party. That's awesome. That's amazing. What a perfect love story. Good shit. Thank you so
much for the five dollars. And I know it can be hard to catch every single stream. They
last a long time. So thanks for checking out the VODs and still hanging out. Being
part of the community. My first DM was an avatar and I never responded. No I just don't
even open up my Twitter. I opened my Twitter once to before my streams. To just say I'm
streaming. I don't ever write anything else. Kailer memeamoto thanks for the
three dollars here. They say Jerma loved your content ever since 2016. Don't know why but I
think your chat is too nice sometimes. It should be a little more mean to you.
Have you been here before? Are you sure you're in the right chat? It should be mean to me.
You know sometimes I've looked over here and saw like Jerma you suck. Fuck you.
It's happening right now. It's happening right now. It's happening right now.
Look over there and see it. But anyways. For real you've inspired me to make content of my own
and I'm blowing up on Instagram. The hellhole of all social media.
Earlier today I was talking to some girl on there and we met up at a local
you fucking had to do that. It was a walk-in. It was a walk-in open thing. But thank you
for three dollars. I appreciate it. Thank you lukewarm soda can for the two five
ten five ten fifteen. I guess we got some uh this is when I looked over it was like four out of
four right. Let's see. All right lukewarm soda can thank you for 250. I've got a story for
you about a weird dream I had. No joke. There's no punch line. It'll be four messages long.
So I'm at a wrestling event and as luck would have it I'm sitting next to Jerma.
I try talking to him. He can't hear me so I get closer. He can't hear me so I get closer.
He still can't hear me so I get closer until I'm right up against his face.
I say something along the lines of hey Jeremy did you see WrestleMania last week. It was
awesome. Um two two people died and Vince I'm cut off. What? As Jerma looks me in the eyes
stone-faced and tells me in a snobby voice I moved past that in my life then he turns to look at
his phone and says on it looking bored for the entire wrestling match. There's a girl with him
who some stripper name like Candy. What the fuck is this dream? Who is super into the event.
She keeps trying to get Jerma to watch but he refuses to look and looks pissed. A guy
walks down like in a baseball stadium selling concessions and asks Jerma if he'd like
anything with a. Jerma just repeats do you want anything back to him in a mocking voice
and keeps saying what did you what did you day aggressively at the concessions a guy
being a huge asshole and mocking the guy. I wouldn't be surprised if dream Jerma kicked.
What the fuck is going on here? Why do people have such strange dreams about me?
I'm not like this. I woke up after the main wrestler who is some weak useless shithead
and then finally I gotta do this all again. I need to know what the hell is going on here.
Talking about somebody's like head being exploded. I don't know anything about wrestling.
I've never even watched your streams for a few months because I've been busy at university.
I don't have the time to sit down and watch streams. What does my dream mean? I have no
idea. I have no idea what that means. I think that means that you just somehow put me into a
strange happenstance. I don't know why people have these weird dreams about me. This is like
number five in the last like two or three months but I appreciate it. Thank you for the
10 bucks here. Listen to Kiwo. Can we watch this? Yeah sure. What is this?
Hold on I gotta I gotta change my audio back to not the VR headset. Yeah super loud warning.
If this is this Titanic thing. Yeah lower the volume. This shit is loud. It's gonna hurt your
ears. I'm not kidding. Don't fuck around here. Okay let's go and watch this. I actually I
didn't get to really see this whole thing. Make it louder. All right let's look at it.
I've never watched this whole movie so I don't know exactly how the scene went down.
Oh it's beautiful Jack. It sure is.
All right let me put you down. Oh it's beautiful I know. Just watch out. Watch out for the railing.
The explosion.
The explosion when when the body lands. I was so fucking loud. Oh I probably killed somebody.
I'm so sorry. Imagine having that at full blast in a house with your TV on and speakers.
My goodness. But anyways let's uh move on to do the rest of the bits.
We had uh rain. Rage bow. Rage and bow. Thank you for the
bits here. The Titanic was so loud that my little sister came down to watch.
Sorry I said your name wrong. How would I mispronounce Tasty Turd? That's not possible.
It's very easy to say. It's a disgusting name. Why would I mispronounce that? Tasty Turd?
I know and you baited me but that's fine. I don't I know I was baited.
I had to screw up. I had to get that cleared up. Thank you Dorkcube for the 250. Man listens to
Celine Dion and loud sounds of rending metal. Well helping you with the rowing machine. The
sequel to man listening to loud farts and screams helps you lift weights. Oh VR is
fucking hilarious. It really is so much fun. Thank you Tom. Tom Cream for the five dollars
and one cent. No message just five bucks. Thank you Tom. Disinterest thanks for the five dollars.
Remember the Titanic chaos was the hardest I've laughed so far this year. Here's a few bits
as thanks. I'm glad you thought it was funny. It was fun to do so glad you liked it. Uh
Schwartzerade thanks for the five dollars. Screw that guy posting fan fiction. Smiley face.
What do you mean fan fiction? Thank you the five dollars though.
Oh did I just turn the stream off? No okay I just elbowed the I thought I just turned off the
stream. Thank you Lazy Luke for the three dollars twenty three cents. Last stream you talked a bit
about how you wanted that YouTube archive to keep the chat because people wanted to keep the
chat's reaction to the drunk VR stream. Disregarding the quality of the archive chat
extension is it fine for me to make my own stream archive website that displays chat
next to the video and is pretty much the same as if you had highlighted all your streams
and if the answer is yes then what's the difference to you actually highlighting all your streams?
Um I think the dip yeah I don't think the highlights don't keep uh chat do they? Do
highlights keep all of chat or is that only VODs? I don't think they do so that would be
the difference. Jeremy's too lazy to do that shit himself. No I mean they only keep chat
if the VOD still exists. Well yeah but I mean a VOD is deleted after 60 days so a highlight
of a VOD will always after 60 days not have chat. Okay so yeah but I think mostly that stream
archive channel on YouTube has everything there so I mean that's years of um highlights do keep
chat they do. I feel like it's like I'm going to be breaking it up into two places like if
you ever want to watch one of my VODs from a year ago you've got to go to another channel
you know what I mean? Oh but where do I watch that stream that you did? Oh we'll go to this
YouTube channel. What about this one? Oh it's here you know they're kind of in the same spot
so it's a little cleaner but if that if I can keep chat I really might have to just start
highlighting everything. It's probably time. Do I have the sorcery chat logs? No I do not.
Those that was years ago a long time ago. Well because remember that like three four
years ago I never I didn't think I was gonna want to save the chat I was just barely
streaming full time like more than three or four times a week. I had just started I didn't really
know the ins and outs completely. I still don't but let me look into that for real not just
like as the meme on the channel because if I can just keep them all here with chat
it's probably worth starting to do. Let me actually in super quotes like look into that
but thank you Lazy Luke and also for your 250 also sorry my last sorry for my last
message. What's wrong with your last message? It's a good thing to bring up obviously. I know
that's cool man don't worry. It's never gonna happen. No don't say that. You don't know that.
Thank you bop beep for the three bucks. Some empty cans of booze might have something to
do with that. I posted the wrong link. Anyways this puke talk has reminded me of this great
clip. Is this somebody puking? Hold on let me screen this. Yeah this is this is this is
somebody puking. This is the this is Vince McMahon. I don't think I want to play this
but I want to play this line here. I'm not gonna play that though because that made people
I don't think one have to see or hear that right now. Vince McMahon was fucking crazy.
Thank you though. Thank you to Jess you got it for the 250. Here we go guys Jess you got it.
Made lemon basil ice cream and they just tried it and we're gonna get a review. All right here's
the ice cream. It's really weird but I don't hate it. I think it's only as good as my ability
to make ice cream is. I'll probably make it again. That looks delicious. What's wrong with
that? It's good shit. It's good stuff. What you meant to say was my palette just was
enlightened. I could see colors after after I took a bite of this. I could see colors on
the spectrum we can't see for 10 seconds and then I had to take another bite to get to see
it again. Looks good though. It's got a lemon zest. Come on. Oh that's not a good thing.
Yeah I just like describe. I feel like that's what happens if you drink mercury.
I can see the whole other spectrum and then you die. So don't do that. Anyway C4G thanks
for the five dollars. Adorama you handsome little lad. Fuck it up and go get them.
And it's a bisexual pride. Handsome little lad. I'll take it. Thank you. Fuck it up and go get
them. I appreciate that. Thank you. Thanks for the five dollars. I missed community subs from
cure cure or cur. Thank you for the five community subs. I missed it an hour ago.
I was probably sprinting in place. So sorry I missed it. I also missed a 50 dollar donation.
What a bad streamer. Terrible streamer. Cat's beanie gave 5000 bits 50 bucks about an hour ago.
I'm not sure if you still here. I hope you are. You're the best fucking streamer. Also PS
be aware of your surroundings. I hit my wall playing my VR and snapped my controller in half.
Don't be like me. I I'm not even concerned about the controller as much as I am about
my desk. There are two big dents in this. This is a nice desk. I just got this when I moved to
Vegas. It's a beautiful walnut desk and I have smashed it as if I was hitting it with a hammer
like four times. There's at least two or three big big dents here. I fucked it all up. It's a
walnut desk and it cost a lot of money. It was at least at least like 180 bucks and at
most like five grand. It's somewhere in the middle. You'll figure it out.
It's not even close to five grand. I gave you a huge average potential.
It's not $5,000. I'm kidding. You think I'm I'm not gonna buy a $5,000 desk. I've ruined it.
Hey, Wince Ryan, thanks for three bucks. You may have been asked this already,
but are you planning on doing Labo VR? Reviews are saying it surprisingly does not
suck. Yes, I will. I will be doing Labo VR. Just not now. Probably in like a week or two.
I mean, if it's Labo, I have to do it. I'm gonna be the only streamer that's ever done all the
Labos. No one else can say that. Somebody might do one. I'm gonna do the car just the
car one. I'm talking one in the from the box. I'm the only goddamn person on this whole
website that did them all except for the submarine. Find me somebody else that can say
that. We're doing them all, but thank you. Uh, smelly boy, thanks for the $250. Can somebody
make an edit of Jerma killing people in Sword and Sorcery to Beware? The song Beware by
Death Grips. I'm sure somebody's capable of it, but thank you. Uh, Wild. Thank you Wild
Hike for the $245. Ah, I'm not supposed to be reading this, but you hit a growth spurt.
Room's not bigger. Shader! Thank you though. Pika Banana, thanks for the $5. Thank you Pika
Banana. I had to work today early in the morning and I've been pretty tired all day,
but then I saw you were online and watching your high-energy VR antics brightened me up.
You never fail to make me laugh, Jerma Hart. I appreciate that, thank you. I do burn myself
out in these VR streams though. It's like a 50% faster drain. If I'm not doing VR,
streams are six to eight hours long. I get, it's like a 100% increase, sometimes longer. Yeah,
it's just, it's draining. You gotta find the right VR games. Yeah, I mean sometimes I can do
it for a while. It's just when you get into room scaling, you start moving around and
like running around in place and crouching and standing up and moving. It's like you're doing
yoga for four hours. People don't even do yoga for like 40 minutes before they stop,
but I still love it though. It's a lot of fun. Jerma lied about Fruity Loops thanks to the $2.50.
If you aren't going to play Fruity Loops, then you should at least play Google Earth VR.
I'm gonna gotta play Fruity Loops, so don't worry. It'll look like a year. I don't know,
maybe. Let's get the credits rolling. Thank you everybody for your subs and thanks guys.
I mean when I get really tired, I do that. Okay guys, so let's have a look and
it's filler for my brain to make up a sentence or get a word out,
but let's get the credits rolling. Here come all the new subs and all the old subs and everybody.
Thank you for your support. Wait, when was Joel here? Did Joel show up at some point
that I missed it? Oh well, apparently I missed it. Was it gifted? Oh he's very sneaky, very
sneaky about that. No, he was one of the gifted subs. That's awesome. A few more bits have come
in here the last 10-15 minutes as we watch the credits roll. Maxi Kaspersky thanks for the
three dollars. I was listening to this in the background as I got some work done, but I had
to put it on the main screen after I heard the sound of your knuckles impacting on your walls.
Great as always. And they say Kiwo stream hype. When's the Germa V Joel gamer challenge? We
actually talked about it. Joel is apparently very busy, so we might do something a little
different. We might come together and collaborate on something soon. He was busy
working on a lot of stuff, so we're going to come together and probably collab on something
special. So he admits you're the better gamer. Something like that. All that trash talk.
Now we've talked about it a couple times. He's out, he has a lot of projects that he's
working on right now, so we're gonna do something. When is it? I haven't, I'm not
sure. I have to get that information from him, but thank you. Thank you Freudian Weapon
for the floor at all. This VR looks like a hell of a workout. Kudos on playing it for
so long. If that were me, I'd be done in 20 minutes. Yeah, I mean, it got close. I was
sitting there when I was doing in the chair VR and moving around and tilting my head around,
but being completely still in the chair, I had only been streaming for like an hour and 40
minutes. I thought I had, I was, I almost had to stop. If I didn't stand up and just take
the headset off and move around for a little bit, I was gonna have to stop streaming.
So thankfully I was able to go for longer, you know? But it is a workout, but it's a
lot of fun. And that juicy bit has an incredibly nice message. They say,
Jeremy, you're seriously the biggest inspiration in my life. You don't know it as we never have,
literally never spoken, but you've shaped me into the person I have become today.
You're hilarious, intelligent, handsome, and everything I strive to be.
I speak for myself and everyone here when I say that I love you and I wish you a long
and prosperous life and career. That's a shitload of incredibly fucking wonderful things
to hear. I'm honored and humbled. I can't believe that somebody would say something like
that. So thank you. I hope you can take something fun from the streams. I hope
if I do inspire somebody, I hope it's for good, you know? So thank you. I really appreciate
that. But that is my time. I am going to go take a bath, like the hottest bath I've ever
taken. I am not going to be live tomorrow and depending on a few factors, I'm going
to get in touch with Kiwo. Kiwo, if you're still here. Looking at possibly like Monday
or Tuesday, right? Not going to be a lot. No, not going to be live tomorrow,
but we're going to figure it out. I'll get sus updated when I got, I'm making a mind show
clip. Wait, what do you mean? Please tell me you didn't see the mind show stuff that I was
doing at the end. I'm going to give you a key word here. Did you or did you not see
QRS? QRS. That is fucking embarrassing. Oh, I got to do it. I got to do it, right?
QRS. Every single one of them. Watch their fucking arms. I'm fucking insane. He's still
drunk. I want to do another mind show stream. I just had a bunch of technical problems with
it. I got like some kind of sinking issues. I got soft locked on the table. So I think
I'm just going to come back to it because it was a lot of fun, but I will see you guys
soon. Wait, Kim check. Oh no, Kim's not in there. Don't worry. Hopefully you've
enjoyed the VR recently, the last three streams here in a row. All right. I'm going
to leave you a mind show clip. You can respond for our collaboration. You mean like
right now on stream or you mean like in discord? If you got it, I'll watch it now.
You got it now? No. Okay. Okay. Well send me that clip. I'm drunk off my ass. Hey,
well I was there like two days ago, three days ago. Drunk VR is worst VR or best VR,
depending on who you ask. I'll see you guys soon. I'll see, if not on Monday,
we'll see you Tuesday. Take care of yourselves. Have a great rest of your weekend.
Thanks for watching as always. See you soon.