Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Fistful of Frags on a gameplay commentary.
I screwed that one up. It's actually a gameplay commentary on Fistful of Frags.
I screw I went backwards on it. I haven't had my coffee this morning. So forgive me. But hi, how are you guys?
Welcome to this video. It's been a little while since I made a just talking to the microphone video like you're watching right now.
Where I just discuss something that's on my mind or something that's sort of relevant to
The gaming world or even just my life in general. This is just gonna be kind of an update one of those update-y
I ramble and rant for like five to ten minutes and that's it. So Fistful of Frags in the background
This is my game of the year for 2014
If you were curious at what my game of the years are for 2014
We're gonna get those out of the way because I haven't really talked about it
I talked about it like once in star stream a week or so ago, but here you go
Here are my games of the year for 2014 in no particular order
Okay, Fistful of Frags, Finding of Isaac Rebirth, Shadow of Mordor, Smite, and Lethal League.
So there you go. Those are my top five games that came out in 2014 and technically Fistful of Frags
Was a mod from a long time ago, but it released on steam in 2014
So if you don't want to count Fistful of Frags
Then it's Tactical Intervention again because Tactical Intervention is game of the year every fucking year no matter what year it is
Okay, so just you can replace that wherever you want and now that that's out of the way
We're gonna actually talk about
One of them in particular the one that you're watching right now Fistful of Frags
and how I really wish there were more games like this because I'm just I I need fresh ideas
And I'm not saying that as like oh, I'm so smart. I'm so intelligent
I need something that can fill my brain with all kinds of wonderful knowledge. No, no, it's I need something. That's just interesting
If something doesn't interest me, I can't do it. I can't play it the same thing with this youtube channel guys
If something doesn't interest me enough to make a video, I'm not gonna make a video
I'm not gonna press a button to record and force myself to upload a video because I have to be interested in something
It has to be something that I go
You know what? Okay that I want to do that and if you take a look at some of the recent first-person shooters
That you know when I say recent I mean the last 10 years or five years. That's not recent at all
Sorry, if you take a look at the most recent first-person shooters in the last fucking decade, that's a stupid thing to say
But in my recent memory of gaming I gravitate towards games that have interesting ideas
Strange stuff crazy weird mechanics style. I don't like to play
The kind of run-of-the-mill shooters i'm not saying they're bad games. I just have trouble. I have such attention deficit hyperactivity disorder guys
I have adhd if I don't immediately like get hold on a second. There's a squirrel at my window
If I don't get locked into something within the first hour or so of playing the game
I'm not really going to put that much time into it. It has to be pretty colors
It has to be interesting gameplay. It's got to be something to make my brain click and that doesn't happen that frequently
And that's my transition to talking about overwatch
Overwatch is the new blizzard game that's coming out in the next
Maybe within the next year or so there'll be a beta. I think eventually coming up here soon
I don't know
I don't want to get so hyped up about overwatch for one very specific reason
It might not be that fun. I'm not going to say it isn't going to be fun
I'm just saying that there's a possibility
With the track record of the last five years or so from all these triple a companies releasing games
And a lot of them being not that great
I don't I just don't want to get hyped up about a game anymore
Now this is not a shot at blizzard because this game might be fantastic overwatch might be a fantastic game
Which I will dump a ton of time into but I just don't know that yet
And I really wish the overwatch team the absolute best of luck
And I hope you guys come up with something great
I hope it's interesting and I hope it's really fun because I really want to enjoy it
and hopefully the name of the game is still overwatch by the time you're watching this video because
They just got like a trademark problem
So the game the name of the game could be like fusion core
All right
So when fusion core comes out in whatever beta it's going to come out in
I'll take a look at it and we'll talk again there
But I need to be very very careful and I can't stress this enough at how careful I need to be
When overwatch comes into beta because beta means it's a beta
And the same exact scenario I do not want to have play out
What happened to me when I played smite one of my other 2014 games of the year when smite was in very very early closed beta
I played a shitload of it. I was so into it. I was making videos on it
It was I go this game is so much fun
This is such an awesome game
But it was so early in the game's development and it wasn't even close to being ready yet
There was a lot of unbalanced gods
There was a lot of broken stuff in the game and it was frustrating and I really burnt myself out
In that year or so that I put into that closed beta because it was such a fun idea
It was such a great fun concept and it wasn't done
It just wasn't done and I put all my energy into it when it wasn't done
So I don't want to do the same thing with overwatch. I'm looking into a crystal ball right now
And i'm seeing the same scenario play out. It's a game that looks really fun
Really interesting
And i'm gonna put time into it when it's not done
So I again want to stress to myself and to you guys out there
When you're playing a new game that you're hyped up for and this is like hype in general
Just let it play out a little bit
Don't just dump all your eggs in one basket and like and spend a huge amount of time in something
Knowing that when you're done putting all the time into it
You might not care anymore when it's actually a finished product and potentially a way better product
Than the one that you put all the time in two years ago
So that's gonna wrap up this video guys. That's all I really wanted to say
Um the wrap one more thing my book i'm still working on the book books are hard. Uh, don't expect it's gonna suck
um and
Eat your vegetables because there's all kinds of calcium and there's all kinds
You know, there's vitamin k in that broccoli there. There's vitamin k in that broccoli
You want to eat that broccoli?
Make sure you're taking a little bit of protein too because protein is the building block of all cells and that's it
That's the end of the video