Hello. Hey guys, welcome to stream. Welcome to my first ever stream. I've been waiting to try something like that. I don't know. I got a headache. That's why I'm doing this.
Oh, he's doing the Sans voice. Hey guys, how are you? Hold on. Hold on a second here. Yeah, sorry we're starting a lot later than usual.
But the reason for that... Ooh, let me move you over here. The reason for that is I woke up this morning and just had a really annoying headache.
It didn't really hurt that much, but it was just... it just was there. It just wouldn't go away.
It was a pressure headache, so it was just messing with my ability to talk and think and like right in the front of my forehead, you know what I mean?
It's called a hangover? I didn't drink anything last night. What? The last time I drank is on this stream. Like last week.
I only drink... I really only drink probably like two or three times a month. Maybe. If that.
Shoot, what do you mean sure? Every time I drink, you guys see it. Boxed wine? Yeah, but I was building a labo for that. I had to do that.
What about that time that I drank toilet water? Well, I mean, I didn't drink actual toilet water. I was drinking water out of a sink.
But tonight, I'll give you a rundown of what we're doing here. So tonight and possibly tomorrow, we're going to stream two days in a row.
So Katamari Damacy Reroll, the remake remastering of the original Katamari game just came out.
So obviously that was one of my favorite games ever. And what are we even waiting for here? You know what I'm saying?
What are we even waiting for? Here it is. All the original music, all the original levels. I played this game as shit.
This is my childhood. And here's the thing, those of you guys who don't know what the fucking title means, sing it with me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ruined. All right. All right. All right. You know what we're doing. Yeah, this is my childhood, guys.
When I grew up, I was probably, I don't know, maybe like probably 20, 22 when this game came out, 23 maybe.
And yeah, I grew up with it. I was just a kid. I remember riding my bike around the neighborhood, hanging out with the neighborhood kids.
I had a backwards ball cap on, a cool vest with Marty McFly on it. I was like 24.
Me and all the other like neighborhood college kids, you know what I mean?
Well, how old, what, when do you guys think that you get old? I'm just barely right now. I'm barely like turning into, I'm barely an adult.
You don't really become an adult till you're like 38. I'm not there yet. I'm still just a kid.
I saw the song from the TV commercials and they told me when I was younger, this is not my fault.
Okay. Blame Toys R Us because I don't want to grow up on the Toys R Us kid was what was on TV every fucking day.
And they they were brainwashing me to say, don't ever be an adult. Don't be an adult. Be a kid forever.
And I'm like, fuck, man. All right. I guess you barely become an adult when you're 30. I'm just kidding.
But we're going to play Katamari tonight and tomorrow. And then we're going to take a day off on what is today.
So Monday, Tuesday, we'll take we'll take Wednesday off and maybe Thursday because Friday is going to be the Birdhouse stream.
I'm building a birdhouse. Why don't we just listen to it again? No, we don't need to see it again.
Turn it up louder. Here it comes again. What if I just did this for like three hours?
Do you agree to these terms and conditions? They weren't terms and conditions in the original game.
This is like, this is absolutely a remake. Privacy policy. Didn't have to agree to this shit last time.
There he is. Hello, Prince. This is the King. Long time no see.
We thought today would be a good day for rolling the Katamari. The Prince.
You want me to read this correctly?
Where the first rolls, the second follows. Roll, roll, roll.
For that purpose, all alone, we went to the bother, the bother of making this space.
The King of all cosmos going to the bother. Just for, I can't read this.
It's like too fucking cryptic and all over the place.
We went to the bother. They would like for you to start the rolling.
But, but, first things first.
But, first things first. Does the Prince like vibration?
Meaning the moving and the shaking.
No, no, no, no. I hate it.
Plane is best. I love going on natural.
If that's what you say, what you declare.
Then you can turn the vibration on and off with the...
All clear, good. We shall see you later.
That's slower than I remember. Did the text come on screen that slowly before?
This is a remake.
All right, Katamari. If you don't know what Katamari is, it's a game where you roll around a little
never-lasting gobstopper and you have to pick up shit. It sticks to the ball as a sticky ball.
You use the analogs to turn around, back and forward. You have to roll over everything, pick up stuff.
And you got to make your Katamari huge or as big as the King desires.
Vibration on? I'm not going to put vibration on. I hate vibration. I'm with the King on this one.
Vibration sucks.
It's a feature that we somehow put on all consoles after its intended purpose was used and done.
You guys, listen.
Rumble was the VR from like 1993.
Well, I'm in the game. Oh, my car just got hit. Whoa, my hands. It was revolutionary. It was insane.
It's not necessary anymore.
Dazzling. We feel a swoon coming over.
Vibration? Yeah, it was a peripheral you had to attach to the back of your controller.
Phones have vibration too, Boomer.
Yeah, but your phone vibrates to alert you of something. It doesn't vibrate so you're not like walking around
and each step the phone vibrates to pretend like you're walking around somewhere.
Like, oh, dude, this is pretty, this is pretty, uh, ooh, I can feel, I'm walking.
I actually am because I vibrate every single time I step. I know I'm walking.
Did somebody just say turn off the music? Wait.
That's like one of the best parts of the whole game.
Please turn off the music.
Look is L.
R is jump.
Okay, quick turn is...
Okay, so you gotta go up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Let's just charge and roll. Click it to spin around.
Very useful and they're using this a lot.
Don't turn it off, beatbox to the scratches.
I've mastered the controls.
If you've actually never played this game before, it really is like a wonderful experience.
That's why we're doing it on stream.
You wanna talk about like a DLC character for Smash?
Don't put Sora in the fucking game.
Everyone's like, oh, Sora for DLC? No, put the king of the cosmos in the game.
What a great character that would be.
It's indeed not a dream. We really didn't. The king of all cosmos has really done it.
A sky full of stars.
We broke it.
Yes, we were naughty, completely naughty.
So, so, so very sorry.
But just between you and us, it feels quite good.
Not that we can remember very clearly, but we were in all nature's embrace.
We felt the beauty of all things and felt love for all. That's how it was.
Did you see? We smiled a genuine smile. Did you see it?
The stars splintering in perfect beauty.
So many, there used to be almost a nuisance, but there's nothing but darkness.
He. E. He. It is but a dream. E. He.
But a beautiful one.
B. But. Beauty.
That miraculous, fabulous moment has passed. It's over.
We came to and found everyone furious.
Even the king of all cosmos was not spared their wrath. Really, everybody was irate.
Anyway, Pee Wee Prince.
Hurry up and bring back the glorious starry sky.
Our problem, your problem. Yeah, you owe us your existence.
We collect on the debt. Pee Wee German.
Hand in hand, always there. Yes, the very definition of the father-son bond.
Alright then, let's get cracking. Sending things to Earth.
The Prince is already in Smash. What? Really?
But not the king of the cosmos.
Here we are, Earth. This is the game. Full of things as usual.
So, so small, you're as small as ever.
We didn't notice not one jot with what the stars at all.
What is that? That body? That physique? Could you really be our son?
E. He. I've got it.
Build yourself up while you roll the Katamari. Work out and get bigger.
Yes indeed.
Don't presume to take the escalator up to the throne just because you're the Prince.
Wow. Tangent. Wild tangent.
We didn't go there last time, but that's alright.
First time on Earth means no worrying about time.
We think we'll come and pick you up when that Katamari is ten centimeters.
Just remember, many things live here, scurrying around and generally getting in the way.
When one of these sneaks up behind you, an alert comes up on the lower left.
I love this name. Try not to bump into anything alive.
But don't worry about it too much. It won't end the game or anything, so just relax and roll.
Good luck, inchling Prince.
So, there we go, here we go.
The best part. Ooh, that same thing.
This was the very first thing we ever rolled up.
This dice.
Oh, we feel a little emotional.
We should put this in the diary.
Oh, I bumped into the snail.
I'm going to get the blocks of cheese.
Oh, it's all coming back to me, the memories.
Get the sandwiches. Oh!
You guys know the Reddit subreddit, like, oddly satisfying?
They actually got all their inspiration from this game.
This whole game is just one giant, oddly satisfying Reddit thread.
Just inherently satisfying. What about the cell phones?
No, not big enough for those yet.
Not big enough for the cell phones.
The phone text hurt. Get the jello.
Ah, what? It's alive?
The same thing. This was the very first thing we ever collided with.
Why can I not pick up the little mounds of jelly?
I'm just nailing it.
Let's make it roll fast.
Almost there. Ten centimeters and that's it.
Get the blocks.
Eventually you can pick up the biggest stuff in the hole in the room on Earth.
How goes it?
How was Earth, huh?
We made a ten centimeter Katamari. How fabulous.
We'd forgotten all about that, so you're mostly clearing everything else we see.
Everyone on Earth is very nice, so they'll be very helpful.
They'll let you roll everything up with a smile, yes, possibly also a wave.
Anyway, let's go home for now.
Oh yes, I almost forgot. Completely slipped the mind.
When rolling on Earth, there are a few more things to be careful of.
You cannot roll up objects larger than your Katamari.
Scratching into larger objects and walls will break things of the Katamari and reduce its size.
Things fall off.
Oddly shaped objects will make your Katamari lopsided.
And fuck it all up.
What? No.
Loud game.
There, is that better?
I'm not doing the... I know how to play the game.
It was the first goal, but it's not the very exciting one, is it?
Next time, we want a much bigger one.
The thing that you collected the most of is...
Snacks, stationery, and games.
My Earth is really full of things.
We will now release it into the sky.
Yeah, you're essentially making stars for the cosmos.
Ten centimeters, one millimeter.
Here's the menu. You forgot your own planet.
Really, are you serious? So you're just not just small, but a bit slow too.
I can already see the clips that are coming out from this.
You know?
Like, how many clips have been done in the stream so far?
You guys have already clipped 13 things in the tutorial.
We cannot feel but partly responsible.
Sai, this is your home planet.
The planet where you live.
Here you can look at stars and save the game and do lots of other things.
You can even visit Earth and the space mushroom.
Just by pressing the L and R button.
Roll your Katamari around on Earth, visit the space mushroom to complete against your cousins.
And that's about it. Your smallness to get a grip.
Oh, there's another clip!
Your absent-mindedness.
There's another one!
All right, make sure to save.
Make sure you remind me to do that.
All right, let's save the game right now.
So you guys want the music up or the sound down?
How does that sound?
Is that more tolerable for your ears?
Maybe?
Uh, data.
Collection.
Control, config.
Presence.
View, constellations.
All right, let me go save it.
Select a file.
Uh, how about right in the middle?
Louder.
Not louder.
No, don't quit the game.
So, is there anything else I can do in here?
I remember somebody was saying that the graphic settings are actually somehow in here.
But I'm playing on the Switch.
I don't think there are any graphic settings.
All right, let's go.
So, let's take a look at the map.
We've got this one.
This is, uh, our first ever roll.
It's Castella.
And I think now it's time to go to Earth.
Here's your world map.
Make a star 2.
Make a star 1.
Here's the second level.
Make a star 2.
What's this?
I wish I could play the piano.
I would put it on, like, the weird dum-dum chorus thing and just play all day.
Because this is just a keyboard with a setting on it.
All right.
Um.
Dang, dang, dang.
Have you ever been to the Philippines?
We stopped in the day before yesterday.
We hope you can visit during the day's rolling like that's possible.
Oh, yes.
A royal present for the hard-working prince.
That's what we were thinking.
While playing catch with your present.
And it went down to Earth.
It just fell to Earth.
Must be around somewhere, so roll it up while you're at it.
Sending things to Earth.
Movies.
Programs.
Elephants.
Giraffes.
Sheep.
Alligators.
Here we are.
Today you'll be rolling inside the house.
The catamari should be, let's see, around a full 20 centimeters.
We can believe in you for seven minutes.
This is the amount of time you have to do it.
But any longer than that, and even the king of all cosmos can't be expected to wait.
We look forward to a nice catamari, mini prince.
Look at the little rats with the cheese balls.
Here we go.
Why did it, come on.
I'm trying to like do like an interesting intro to the game.
Can't get these.
Oh, I can.
I can get the toothpaste.
Got to get the small shit first.
Taffy.
Get the candy.
I can't get the taffy yet.
Not for the love of God, really.
No orange slices?
Not big enough.
I can get the little marbles.
What about these?
Fuck.
Come on.
Nail polish.
No.
Matchsticks.
I have to get bigger.
Get up.
There we go.
Okay.
Take your own.
Now it's time to roll over everything here.
I'm going to take out the Legos.
And the chocolate cookies.
Can't get the big ones.
Was it one?
20?
20 centimeters?
Oh.
Okay.
I can get the nail polish.
I'm going to go up.
We did not go up at all.
No!
I fell off.
Shit.
This momentum.
It's all right.
I got six minutes.
Careful.
All right.
There's a game board here.
What's going on?
Hmm.
Ten centimeters.
Just get it bigger.
I know.
I know I'm going to do 20.
What do you think I'm doing?
I can get the candy.
Oh, I can get the tapes.
These things are huge.
Get them.
All of them.
Every single birthday tape.
Get it.
Oh, my God.
I just ruined everything.
I'm going to go up here.
Pick up the entire breakfast.
House of cards?
No!
I fell off.
Shit.
Oh.
No.
That was about to be so satisfying.
Get me up there.
Come on, man.
Ah.
I can go to sleep tonight.
Okay.
Good.
Reset.
What am I bumping into?
Frogs?
Oh.
Come on.
I can still pick shit up up here.
Oh.
Watch out.
I'm not going to get out.
I don't know why I think that's funny now.
Anything in the bathroom?
Oh, mousetraps.
I'm getting hit by the mousetraps.
Right here.
Racer's got them.
All right.
I'm good.
Anything else over here that I didn't get?
Can I get the whole dinner?
Yeah, I can.
18.4.
We got it.
That's fine.
Everything's fine.
I want to get up there.
How do I jump with this?
Can you jump with this?
What is left that I didn't get?
I can't go outside.
Oh, my God.
I can go outside.
Basket of apples.
Got it.
Just jump.
Oh, what a nice tatamari.
Substantially, it goes down smoothly.
But actually, we would love to have a much bigger, nicer tatamari.
We'll leave you to your work.
All right.
I've got to get up there.
Oh.
But actually, we would love to have a much bigger, nicer tatamari.
We'll leave you to your work.
All right.
I've got to just...
I beat it.
I just have to get as many socks as I can.
Get the knives.
I know people are going to get really upset that I didn't get every sock.
And there's going to be a lot of opportunity where you can scream at me.
Pikachu sock.
Yeah, that's what they were.
Get the sock.
All right.
Now, because I have an opportunity to, I'll get it.
It's back here, right?
Right there.
I got it.
Everybody can relax.
I got the sock.
I'm not big enough to pick up a fence.
I love the PogChamp for picking up the sock.
Is that it?
Is that all it takes?
I just have to pick up a sock?
I'm not tall enough to get this.
Eventually, you can pick up...
I'm tiny right now.
You guys think this is the whole game right here?
Just wait until I'm as big as the buildings.
Everybody clip that one.
Oh, I got the present.
Clip list rose.
Every time he says the word tall, small, or not big enough, make sure you get like five clips in it and then string them all together.
So it's like small.
Not tall enough.
I'm small.
I'm too small.
I'm short.
I'm too short for this.
I'm too small for this.
God, not tall, short, inch.
I just gave it to you.
You don't even have to do the work.
Nobody has to even do the work now.
You just got it for free.
You don't even have to do the clip compilation.
There we go.
I can get the fence.
What?
I thought I was...
I couldn't just get the fence right there?
30 seconds.
Come on.
Fast.
I can't make it up here.
Into the lady's face.
Steal all of the shit that's on her desk.
Time's up.
It was boring to watch this all the time.
Come on, man.
This game is really fun.
I love this game.
Let me have this.
King of the Cosmos is a chat.
34 centimeters.
It's pretty big.
We imagine it like a pretty star.
If it were ours, we'd make it much bigger.
Here.
This is our royal present.
What is it?
Guess what?
Guess what it is.
The thing that you collected the most of is stationary.
Earth is really full of things.
We will not release it into the sky.
Oh, I forgot about these little...
Wait.
Everybody quiet.
We're about to leave.
Okay.
They're watching General Robo.
There's a story here, guys.
I didn't think it was an elaborate storyline.
I want to see what the present is.
Winter scarf.
Nice.
I'm not even saving it.
Let's just fucking go wild and not even save it.
Yeah, now I have a scarf.
Let's go back to Earth.
What about the secret mushroom?
Here's all the friends.
Another cousin has arrived.
Here they are.
All right, who do I want to...
You can be...
This is a character.
Who's your character?
So let's see.
Who do I want to be?
I fucked it up.
I couldn't even get the strength to even say anything afterwards.
I was trying to do...
I was going to say, Olimar!
But I missed?
Who do I be?
I kind of like the picnic table guy.
Or Longhead.
What about this guy?
Oh, here, I was Marcy.
All right, fine.
I'm Marcy.
Come over here.
Why can't I select you?
What the hell?
Select.
Okay, got it.
No, no, select.
Can I not use usual control?
Okay, what the hell?
I can't play with Marcy?
Yeah, I'm pressing A. A's not doing anything.
Can I just...
This is for multiplayer only.
What?
I can't play as those characters?
Whatever.
Everyone just get ready for the next meteor restart.
Boatar Day.
Have you ever been to Portugal?
We were there yesterday.
We hope you can visit during the day's rolling.
Like, that's possible.
Oh, yes, I almost forgot.
Oh, yes.
A royal present for the Powered Working Prince is a present on here.
That's all I care about.
I don't even care if I fucking lose.
I don't care if I lose.
Give me the present.
That's what we were thinking.
But we sort of tossed it down to Earth.
We had an issue and just sort of pitched it away.
Must be around somewhere.
So roll it up while you're at it.
Will you guys leave?
No, not to leave.
I was going to say leave the king alone.
You guys leave.
No.
Like, I'm just going to do this by myself.
He'll be rolling around the town.
The Katovari should be, let's see, 50.
50 centimeters.
We can believe you can do it in nine minutes.
Any longer than that and even the king and the cosmos can't wait for you.
We look forward to a nice Katamari.
Loser Prince.
This is my favorite song in the entire album.
Get out of the way.
Silverware first.
And a blue toothbrush.
It can even be about a blue toothbrush.
All right.
This got real though.
I have to be, I have to actually focus.
Look at all the little animals.
What are they collecting?
What are these little mushroom popovers?
What are these things called?
The appetizer with the mushroom?
What are they called?
The stuffed mushroom?
What is it called?
A stuffed mushroom.
Let's roll.
Let's roll, baby.
I am not, look at the pizza wheel.
Oh, I love this game.
I don't think I'm, I can't get these.
Collect bird.
I can't, I'm not big enough.
I can't get these yet.
Shit, I got to go back.
I'm not big enough.
Damn it.
I did the wrong route.
No, it's okay.
I got plenty of time.
Get out of the way.
All these.
Watch this.
Ready?
Oh, this feels so good to pick them up.
Oh, we want some chocolate.
What?
Oh shit, there's a cat behind me.
When am I going to get chocolate?
What's wrong with me?
Is this, no, this is tape.
Am I big enough to get these?
The cylinders?
Yep.
Okay, chocolate.
And we need to find a present too.
Get up there.
I know you can.
Really?
All right.
We have an edible arrangement.
Now I'm lopsided.
I need some bigger stuff otherwise this is not going to work.
Give me the spatulas.
And the clock.
Oh, it's 50.
50 milliliters, okay.
Get the clock.
Take out food.
What?
I'm stuck.
I have to jump it.
Get up there.
Forget about the cat.
Just go.
Where's the clock?
Get clock.
There it is.
I can't get the clock.
Watch out for the dung beetle.
It's stuck.
I cannot get the clock.
This dude, you're doing your own Katamari with shit.
Get out of the way.
I got it.
I got the clock.
Everybody can relax.
No, I didn't.
I can't get the clock.
Sorry.
You can get it.
Well, let me just make sure.
Let me come back when I'm a little able to get, when I'm able to pick that up.
Back down, okay?
I'm just stealing the muffins.
Ooh, too late.
What are you doing?
If anything, scamper is what we call it.
All right.
I'm now bigger.
I can't get the clock, everybody.
It's not going to happen.
It's glitched out underneath.
I only have four minutes.
I've got to stop listening to you guys about clocks.
I have to go up here.
Where have you not gone?
All right, fish.
Here we go.
This will make me 50.
Oh, no.
This is not good.
Not good.
I got to get these trees.
I can't even pick these up.
I'm not big enough.
Soda?
Okay.
I don't even know the name of this song.
Do yourself a huge favor and just type in Katamari Damacy OST.
It looks like a whole damn thing.
Ooh.
Found the water jugs.
Three minutes, I can do it.
Just get on top.
Come on.
Look at all those utensils over here.
No.
Don't get stuck back here.
48.
I got it.
We want clock.
You guys don't really want the clock.
Plus, I don't even remember where the hell it even is.
Where's the clock?
Clock.
What a nice Katamari.
Kind of bratty.
Kind of shy.
See?
Flower clock.
I already got it.
Now that you've come this far, we would love to have a much bigger and nicer
one.
Let's go.
All right.
Let's see if I can figure out where that clock was.
I got two minutes to figure it out.
Clock or no stream?
Wasn't it up?
It was up here to the right, right?
It's over here.
Okay.
Clock.
Line it up.
Oh, okay.
Everybody can calm down.
See?
Now you can all hang out.
Everything's fine.
I got the clock.
Clocked.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
That was an ooh right there.
You have one minute left.
I can't go through there.
I'm too jacked.
I forget the broom.
No.
I get the dust fans.
This is the best part.
When you get big enough, you can just rush and roll over everything.
When I get to 70, can I jump that?
Come on.
Jump it.
Fire extinguishers.
Time for a fireworks display.
What?
What is he talking about?
Get all the birds.
I have 10 seconds to get the birds and the cow.
I got the cow.
Or dog.
Whatever it was.
71.
It comes and gets to the bunker.
I didn't get the present.
Royal Rainbow.
Take us back.
24 kill streak.
It's pretty big.
We imagine it'll make a pretty good start.
What even is this game?
I'm so glad that you don't know what this is.
It makes me very happy that you don't know because this is an old game from
PlayStation 2 that they just recently redid, reimagined and remastered.
I know it's a remake and remastered, but still.
It's on the Switch.
It's on Steam.
Is it on Steam?
Am I lying?
Is that a fucking incorrect statement?
It is.
Okay.
Yeah.
How much is this game?
This game's like 20, 30 bucks, right?
I picked up a lot of cooking for this.
30 bucks?
30 bucks.
That's not bad for a game like this.
There's a lot of content in this game.
A 30 dollar jug?
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet.
I really told you, didn't I?
Didn't I?
Am I saying this was made in Unity?
I can just bait it here.
That sounds like it could be real though.
Ported to Unity.
Okay.
So it's ported to Unity.
But Unity is one of those...
It's one of those things that...
Oh hey, wow, interesting.
This was made in Unity.
My mic is fucked up. Wow, I got it. What? What? I can't hear you. What? I didn't get any
presents that round so, unfortunately. Pick a star 3. So we have some options here. We're gonna do
make cancer or make a star 4. Is there anything else? Peek the mic or riot? Why would I do that?
Yeah. So, 1, 2, listen, this is 3 so let's just stay, no, 1, make a star 2, make a star 3. So 4, 5.
Peek mic or riot? I'm not gonna peek my mic! What? Why do you want me to do that? Do it. Peek
the mic. What the fuck is wrong with you guys? What? The game is super loud compared to me.
That's better. When is the yes? Have you ever been to Spain? It's our other homeland. Peek it.
I'll do it. Hold on. This is the only time you're gonna get me to do this. I can't do it. I
can't. I'm trying to capture it on my webcam. I was gonna break the webcam microphone but I
can't do that right now because I can't. I have my mic on the switch. I have to go
into my audio device settings. It's not like, hold on. Tell me if this changes anything. What
is this doing? What is this doing? Is this the same? Is this the same? Do it. Oh, god damn it.
Just, hold on. No, it's not gonna happen. It's not gonna happen. No. That's not gonna
happen because I can't, I have to like restock my computer for it to recognize the microphone
here. No, everybody relax. I'm not gonna peek my microphone. It's not recognizing the
other audio device which is the webcam mic. I'm not gonna peek this one. I'm not gonna
break my fucking $6,700 of mic, okay? It's not gonna happen. Alright, let's go back to what
we're doing. Wallet, keys, rings, hopes, and dreams are lost at all. Roll it up while
you're at it. Break your stuff. I can't believe I just wasted like six straight minutes trying
to find a way to break the microphone that I have over here. Now, alright, if you stick
around for the whole stream, I will break this mic over here. I will peek this mic
until it doesn't work. Not this one, the webcam one. No, no, don't do that.
Okay, Stakatomari should be one, around one meter. We can believe in you, it's ten minutes,
one meter. But any longer than that of the king of all cosmos, I can't. We look forward
to a nice Katomari bite-sized prince. Let's go. There's another great song, too. This
whole soundtrack. What do the kids say? What do the kids say now, right? Light it
up, right? This contract is light it up. It's that good. It's like, it causes a fire,
right? Man, this soundtrack is so good. It's causing a fire in here. Who lit that fire,
right? No, this is not satisfying to me. I need to, I need this to be satisfying
to me. Okay, that was that. That was satisfying to me. I can't leave here until I get
all the erasers. I don't think I'm gonna be, I don't think I'm gonna be able to
get it, though. I have to go across. Oh, no! There's too much momentum, I had to do
it. Get out of the way, mouse. There's a bear with a sweater on it. Sing it with
me now. I'm up here. Get the cones. Not big enough. Fuck. Roll it. I know you
can do it. I know you can. I've seen you do it before. Come on, you're wasting
time. You're wasting time. Up, down, up, down, up, down, up, down. Why are you
wasting time? Come in here. There we go. Get all the erasers. You can't marry as
big as 24 lipsticks. Get it bigger already. Just get it bigger. Forehead. Okay.
Is that all the erasers? I think that's all the erasers. You see? No, just a bit more.
Oh, erasers. Sing it with me now. I'm not even singing it. Why do I keep saying sing it with me now?
Oh, sing it with me now! Okay, can I break through the window? I'll be
eventually big enough to go through here. I'm missing, but I didn't get. Get the whole line of rats.
What am I missing here? The pencils? Orange peels? There we go. Nice roll-up. So
eristic from it. We are dazzled. Let's just roll it up before it runs off.
Why do you want me to roll up the animal? Right through, straight through. Here we go.
Get them all. Get all the cigarette packs. Don't smoke, but just pick them up if they're on the
ground. Don't pick cigarettes up if they're on the ground. Throw them in the trash when you do
that. 20 centimeters. Not a long, long way to go, but it really does exponentially. Light bulb?
Is this a sentient light bulb? What? If you can't make the Kazamari bigger, you can't get to the
next stage. I'm working on it. It's not my fault this house is so fucked up. Little birds. I'll be back for those bears.
Really? Watermelon? That's not gonna make me grow? Just a baby. Just a very strong baby. Putting
the square peg into the circle hole. And he does it. That's a strong baby. That was
Santa hat. At least I'm big enough to get these. This whole area, I think I can get. I'm losing so much
because I keep running into things I'm not supposed to be. The whole fridge worth of stuff. Here we go.
This is where, now we exponentially get marked. All the tuna cans. Mustard. Ketchup. Relish.
Bananas. Toast. Cheeseburger. Can I get it? I just want the milk. All right. It's back to
come out here. Let's see. Steal all their toys. How can I not get those? Santa hat? Santa? Where?
Did I miss the Santa hat? Here's the worst part about this game being that somebody's watching and you
play this. There are items that I just miss and you're like, oh! Get it! Oh! Bathtub. Uh oh.
Oh no. No, no, no. Get me out of here. Because I'm losing a centimeter a second. Get me out of the
corner. Out of the corner. Jump. Oh shit. No, that was pizza pizza I think. I want to keep
that. No, that's my dog bone. Oh! Oh thank god. I need to be a meter. Under the sink. I can. I
can get all of both of them. Just be careful. Wedged in under the sink. Don't hit the gas line.
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna make it. I'm not gonna make it. I'm not gonna make it, am I?
Fuck. There we go. Hold on. It's possible now. Only 50 still. I got half way to go.
Exponential. Come on. This is where you exponentially grow. Do it. Come on. Get in here.
No, no, no. The bathtub. The bathtub ruined the whole thing. Try to get up there. 60. Almost 60.
Come on. Grow another. 67. Oh, I gotta get to 100. When's the next big growth period here?
When do I get my new growth spurt? Is it TV? 75. One minute left. Back outside. 50 seconds.
Go! Get everything. Just dash everywhere. Pick up the cat. Pick up the shopping cart.
I can't. Fuck the cat. Fuck that cat. Come on! I get it. What a nice cat to borrow.
Tough get with a soft feel. Now that you've come this far, we'd like to have it a little
bigger. Okay, let's see how I can get it. I can't. I don't even know where I am.
I can't go back in the house. Oh, I'm in the house! Oh! I made it to the house. Damn it.
I can't believe it. I got in the house and I would have just sucked up everything.
It's a coarse goal, but it's not very exciting. We want a bigger one next time.
The thing you can collect at the most is play time. I don't even know what that even
means. Play time? Earth really is full of them. Time to release it into the sky.
What's this one called? Toys is the name of the star.
To be, why does it say to be continued every time? To be continued. Say the game? No,
don't think so. That's not even funny. Like, it's not funny. Because if for some reason
the game crashes or the console crashes or something, that's not even funny.
Oh, it's funny. We have to restart the whole game. Isn't that funny?
Like, no, that's not funny. That would be a waste of time. Santa? Wait, Santa hat?
I didn't get any presents. Oh, this is annoying. I had one present. All right, back to Earth.
Santa hat. All right, we've opened up more things. Here is,
uh, star five. We have to make constellations here. Okay, let's go.
They can't. What is it? Something's not quite there. Oh, yes, we get it. It just doesn't look
delicious. The sky does not seem yummy at all. Everyone is still hungry, yes? Can't you see that,
silly? Speaking of delicious, we must say, most certainly, we say crab. Most certainly crab.
What a delightfully weird fucking dude. It's just what? I can't even read that.
What the fuck? I didn't even do it. Looks yummy. But no, no, not yet. Patience is a virtue. Focus,
we must focus. To make the yummiest... Okay, we need crabs. All you have to do is roll up as
many crabs as you can find. Let's see. You have seven minutes to roll up as many crabs as
possible. We look forward to a mouth-watering catamari, callow prince. Go. Crabs. Oh! Oh,
I can't. I hate them. Why is a crab on the spider web? Why is a crab hanging from a spider
web? What the fuck? Doesn't make any sense. I wish it was like that. I would love if spiders
weren't spiders. They were just crabs. I would love them. They would be so fun.
Crabs are spiders with armor. No, crabs are fun and funny and spiders are evil. I know this because
they're holding the toothbrushes. That's so... I love this. You know how I know this? Because
every television show and movie I've ever seen in my whole life, spider was evil and goes like
and every crab is a funny character that likes money or the dances and shit. That's all I've
ever been told. So of course I'm going to be scared of spiders and not crabs because of that
stupid monster noise that I just made. Oh! Me money! Me money, SpongeBob! That's not like...
Why would I be scared of that? There's never been one spider in the history of media
that wasn't evil and had foam coming out of their mouth. I think it was like Charlotte's
Web. That's the only one. Crabs foam at the mouth? Oh, they don't. Spider-Man? But Spider-Man is a
man that was bit by a spider. That's not the same thing. And the spider that bit him was
terrifying because for some reason he got superpowers by being bit by a black widow
radioactive fucking spider. That's scary. Oh yeah, but be careful. There's the
black widow that'll bite you with radioactive poison in its fangs. Oh, but like it's Spider-Man.
The spider that bit Spider-Man, it was too small for you to hear it, but right before it bit him
it definitely went like... just didn't pick up on the microphone. I need more crab. I can't get
the funny crab with shoes on. The shrimp looks good too. I hate this shrimp. I have to get
the super crab. Crabs literally foam at the mouth to breathe. Yeah, but I see that as like
flavored foam at the mouth, like Starburst, not like evil's venom foam. Am I not big enough to
get you? You know what I mean. Laughing at his own joke? No, I'm laughing at the interpretation
of the thing that I said, which on second revelation it sounds pretty fucking dumb.
The crabs? There's no more. I've ran out. The only crabs over here and I'm too big to
get in there. There's some up. How do I go up? Can I climb? Jump? I can't. I don't have a jump.
There's nowhere else I can go. Can I get up there? No, I can't. I can like go like this,
but that doesn't do anything. There's an elevator? Where's there an elevator?
That's not an elevator. This is not an elevator. Those are two chess pieces. Oh,
come on. Really? All right, I got 90. Can I make it up? I need 100. Come on. There's
one right there. Got him. 97. Come on. 98, 99. How did I not get the one in the corner?
I need 100. I need 100 or I'm going to turn off this ring. What? What the fuck? I got it.
I got it. I got 100. If you Starburst is reminding you of foaming at the mouth,
then no. By the way, I'm just fucking pissed about Starburst. Can I tell you?
I bought and I realized why there was a there was a box of Starburst, like a big box
that was on sale. I was like, holy shit, I like Starburst. Starburst are awesome.
I bought the box. The thing was on sale and Starburst don't have a fucking expiration date on
them. Can Starburst even expire? They made it a plastic rubber and they did take a droplet
and drop a little bit of flavoring juice on them. You just chew out the flavoring and then
you spit it out. You're not supposed to swallow Starburst guys. It stays in your stomach
for like eight years. You chew it up until it's like a pale transparent color and then you just
spit it out. You don't want to be ingesting that. Have you seen the ingredient list?
Oh shit, I've been eating them wrong. That actually does look kind of delicious. No,
it doesn't. Yeah, every Starburst you've ever eaten. Oh, hold on. I'll tell you in a minute.
Teapot. I love how that's the one thing you got out of that entire sequence
and how delightfully odd that whole thing was. The teapot is the thing. Whoa, I can't believe
there was a teapot there. But just be careful when you eat Starburst guys because the stage
is done for 10 years. So let's say you have like 200 Starbursts over the course of like
four years or something. Eventually you're gonna, you know, 10 years from now you'll be
like in your late 50s and you're just you're gonna shit out a gigantic flavored size
like basketball. Crap, loud. What do we got? We unlocked a Star, let's do Starfire.
Yeah, you're gonna shit out a giant rubber flavored basketball. What are you gonna do
with that? Ever been to the Netherlands? We stopped in the day before yesterday.
We hope you can visit during the day's rolling like that's possible. Oh yes,
I mean why does he keep saying like that's possible? There's another present down here.
I want to get another present. I'm gonna work my ass off for this present. Hey Jerma,
I just made the math. I have 150 hours of old streams to watch. So can you please stop
streaming for 150 days? I don't think I could do that. Sorry that you're gonna be forever
catching up. Okay, today you'll be rolling around the town. The Katamari should be,
let's see, around 15, 1.5 meters. There's a point there. 13 minutes for 1.5. Any longer,
and you'll be very angry. There's a gift here too. Tell me, okay, if you see the gift,
tell me the location of it. Because my eyes aren't so good anymore. You know, I'm gonna
take this one slow because I want to be sure I don't crash into everything, pick up all the
eggs. Quail chick. Not big enough for that. Ha ha, it's there. I'll know when I look over
the chat and see 500 million people all writing the same thing with like fail fish.
Because I would have passed it three or four times by then. Use your eyes, fail fish. Use
your eyes. Is he this bad on purpose? Like, once I start seeing that, is when I know
that I'm close. Pretending. I'm not big enough for the milk. I need to drink more of that to
get bigger. Well, I don't. But whatever, just clip it and fucking use it in your video or
whatever the hell you're making. Get it! I need to get to 15. I think I grow a little more.
Super glue? It's not 15. What is it? I'm getting all the little teeny tiny stuff first.
It's always the hardest part. The trees. Parsley. Reminds me of Jetset Radio song.
Both with good soundtrack. This soundtrack is so good. I remember having this on a CD
that I would play in my car. Oh, look at this. Perfect. And I remember specifically stopping
at red lights with the windows down and blasting the title theme with all the windows
down. I remember there was one time. Okay, so listen, hear me out on this. This is like
really embarrassing, but whatever, who cares? It's not even though, but it is. So one time
I was driving some co-workers at the time home and I had a CD that was a lot of video
game music on the CD. And you know when you turn your car off when you're listening to
music and you're blasting something just like, Oh yeah, this is like my alone me time music.
Well, that's what it was. It was like a bunch of video game shit on it. And
my co-workers at the time, when they weren't like into video games, they didn't really.
This is also probably like, this is like 15 years ago. So anyways, I'm driving them home
and as we get in the car and I turn the car on and we start, Oh, there's music in here.
Oh, wait a minute. And the battle sequence theme from Lost Odyssey is playing loud.
It was just like, what is this? And I had to cover my tracks. You know what I mean?
Cause it's like a symphony orchestra is what's playing. And I remember just going,
Oh, I love classical music. I'm like, I listen to classical music sometimes when I drive.
I bet he was beat red. It probably was. That's even worse. I have to,
I had to cover my tracks. Ah, yes. Mozart. Yeah. So I had to look like the guy driving around
listening to fucking Mozart. And honestly, I'm, let me tell you something about classical
music. And now I'm going to, a lot of people are probably going to disagree with me here,
but the only time I ever hear classical music ever is when you were at the dentist getting
surgery. So I don't want to be the guy listening to classical music. Like when you're getting
like your teeth pulled, the guys listening to classical music, I don't want to listen to that.
And there's nothing wrong with classical music. It's really, you know, very expertly crafted.
It's amazing pieces and they work so well and there's so much wonderful, wonderful music.
That has come out of full orchestras and classical instruments. But I don't, I don't,
I'm not listening to it in my car, like hanging out with friends. Like, oh, what do you,
what do you got, man? What's on your, what's on your playlist? Oh, well, you know, I've got,
you know, Eminem, I guess, I think. And then like, it'd be like, dude, what the fuck is
this? It's like, ah, nothing. There's a play, where's the present? No one has seen it yet.
But I love listening to classical music. I do. But for some reason, I don't know why this is,
but classical music really is just, you don't, you don't want people to know that you're
listening to it. I don't know why. If everyone can agree that classical music is so wonderful,
well, we're not allowed to play it in our cars. What is this? I love in the middle of
that. Is he this bad on purpose? So there's a way through here. I just get it. Okay.
No, I love, I love classical music, but I also don't listen to like really any music.
You guys all know that because you're wondering why everyone's like, what are you talking about?
Question mark. Because I'm a fucking idiot. Like I'm an imbecile. And for some reason,
when I have music on, it's the only thing I can do. I can't put music on in the
background. I can't, I can't have a conversation while music's playing. It's just like,
I can hear it. I just think though, okay, I'm here, the lyrics and talking and there's the
beat and I'm talking too, but I can't cause I have to hear, but what are you doing now?
Yeah. But this is different because this has to be on here because this is the whole, this is
like 70. This is 0.70. No, this is seven. This is like 50% of the reason why you play
the game. No, that's like 30% because this, this is not, you know what I'm saying? It's
a fucking amazing sound. Okay. Case in point. I couldn't just talk to you there
because I heard like the construction music in the background.
Where's that entrance? Up here somewhere? I did actually go past it. This has to be 1.5 meters,
right? I gotta be kind of on the ball here. Not pretending. Let me get home. Let me,
let me get the Jenga thumb. I can't get that. Really? Fail, fail, fail. Yeah. I
don't listen to music. I'm such a fucking strange person, man. I listen to music alone
in my office sitting here and I put on stuff like Pac-Man's theme from Smash Brothers.
Like the cool one. And I listen to it like 17 times in a row. Is that weird? And then
you get to the one part of the, holy shit, I'm going fast. Oh, do it again. Do it again.
Have to do that again. So you pick like the one part in the song that you want to hear
over and over again. You get to that part of the song where it's like the big breakdown
and you listen to it like 87 times. And then you wonder silently to yourself,
what like the, the YouTube data algorithm on your profile looks like and where you've
clicked on this same video, like 185 times. Get out of the way. I need to get a strike.
All right, here we go. I can't see. Oh, close enough. I just got wrecked by a cat.
You listen to music on YouTube. See? I told you. I knew there was something wrong with it.
I knew there was something wrong with what I was doing. I don't have very much time left.
I got to focus here. The radishes, what you do with music. Who's on this bike?
What you do with music is normal. Everybody does that. So are people just pretending they
don't do that? I don't know, because I know a lot of people that have Spotify open and they
don't, I don't think they've heard the same song twice. Like, oh, I have a Spotify on the
discover mode. Yeah. I've probably listened to 14,000 songs in the last like five years.
The same clip. Wait, I can pick up the water? No, those are rookie numbers. I'm going to lose
1.5. Come on, dogs. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no. Get out. Out, out, out, out, out.
Oh, fuck. Into the supermarket. Oh no, I'm going to lose. Why are there so many people
in the way? Get out of the fucking way. No. We were talking about fucking starbursts
and shitting out basketballs. I was going to pay attention. Everything you do is kind of lame.
Nobody wears sharp horns like that anymore. And why is your head so wide? For the record,
there's nothing here. Well, you get your stardust today. I'll do a better job next time.
Do it again. Was I really loud right there? I don't want to be like the loud guy.
Have you been to the Netherlands? Yeah, it's the same one. I'll get it this time. Fast.
You waste the time going back up the hill for the bowling joke. You
dare. But we were talking about how crabs aren't spiders. I had to pay attention to that. That
was more important. All right, 1.5. Let's do it. In the very beginning, I was like,
I'm going to take my time. Be very careful. No, just go. Are lobsters spiders? Well, no,
because lobsters look like, really, they just look like lobsters. There's no other
animal or crustacean that even looked remotely similar. When I look at crab, I think, okay,
that's a spider. When I see lobster, I say that's a lobster. That's it. There's nothing
you can even compare a lobster to. A shrimp? Yeah. Yeah, that's just like a big shrimp.
Nothing compares to you. Am I accidentally, purposely avoiding all the shit I need to pick
up right now? Oh yeah, there's a scorpion in the house today. That was different. I've never
seen one before. I have not seen a scorpion in real life ever until two hours ago, like an hour
ago. Finally, a game that punishes stalling. Well, that's why we're not stalling anymore.
Did I freak out? No, because it was already dead. I talked to Talix about it. I was like,
did you kill a scorpion down here? No. Oh, it was really weird. And we don't think that
the dogs had anything to do with it. Maybe one of the dogs went after it and got it.
You got to be careful there, though, because a dog can get actually very seriously injured
from a scorpion or a large insect. So we have a little talk about what we need to do.
And we need to start this kind of thing. It's weird. It's December. A scorpion in December.
I thought all bugs go to hell. Well, I mean, all bugs go to hell, but they disappear
for the winter months. That's why it was inside. All bugs go to Valhalla. No, are you kidding me?
It's like if a scorpion was in, like crawled in front of Odin, no, he's so strong.
That's me, Odin. I'm the most powerful. Oh, it's a scorpion. Get it out of here. Thor.
Thor, help me, Thor. And Thor comes in. What is it, father? Ew, ew. And then Thor is like,
don't worry, I will use my hammer. And oh, it grows.
And then somebody finally, like, throws a grom at it and kills it.
Could you miss any more items? I was supposed to be paying attention. All right, no more fucking
around. Could you miss any more items? You know, you're right. They do have a coin.
I can't just leave it up to the last 10 seconds. You know what I mean? I got to
get big now. You know, turn on the infomercial. I used to look like you.
Scrawny, small. And then I started drinking Jack's juice. Oh, by the way,
all this is is just maltodextrin. A shitload of it. And some chocolate powder.
I can't get up there. Fuck. He's dodging items. I need to just shut up and play, man.
Did my brain subconsciously think this was an avoid the object game?
I'm sitting here talking, and I'm, oh, watch out, I don't want to run into anything.
All right, I got bigger. All right, eight minutes. I got enough time.
Pick up, I want to pick up this shit on your car, man. Get all the envelopes,
get the Nintendo. I can't pick up the Nintendo? All right, I need to go,
I need to change locations. Only 35 centimeters. All right, this is where we pick up
the whole world. I'm just gonna get to 50, pick up all the soda bottles.
There's a lot more soda bottles over here. Good. I could go for one of those tees.
Yeah, playing Katamari, you really do need to have snacks available.
And now it wants me to go through here. There's a way through there.
So I'm gonna, I'm gonna wrap around. I'm gonna get a little bit bigger first.
Get all the crabs. At least most of them. Now it's hiding.
Don't even worry about it. Nintendo. Can I pick up the Nintendo?
Now I can. Okay. Katamari is about hitting the wall and stalling.
How dare you say that. What? I'm not big enough to go through there?
Stop. Don't make me laugh. Don't make me laugh. Not when I'm playing Katamari Damacy.
Strike. Doing way better than I did last time. So, wait. I can't pick up the full
watermelons? I can only pick up half watermelons. What kind of video game
do you think you are? This is where I'm gonna have a lot of time to exponentially take out
everything in here. Solar panels? Please move. Can I pick these up yet?
I feel like I did the same stupid shit last time. I definitely did.
This is the guy that runs into walls and stalls playing Katamari.
The melons germo. I couldn't get them. I could get them now.
I couldn't get them. I couldn't do it. All right. Let's take a trip over here.
Try to pick up as many radishes as I can because they're pretty large.
I'm gonna go up here again. Back to the street.
Anything else that I missed over here? There's a guy lying down.
Okay. Didn't do anything I thought that was gonna do.
Wait...I'm almost there. 150. Did I get the sign? Did I have the barber?
Can't get the sign. I'm going back up because there's a
lot of shit that I can get over here now that I couldn't previously.
He's too fat. I mean, am I? I'm not really though.
That's good. I want to be huge down these halls so I can just
accidentally pick up everything. Yeah, take down this whole wall.
I got the phone. This may have actually been a terrible idea, you're right.
I gotta stay on the road. This was a very bad idea.
This was a very bad idea. Oh no, this was a terrible fucking idea.
Get back down here. Down. Back down. Back down. Forget about everything here. Go.
Oh shit. Shit. What have I done? Get the cat. What the fuck have I done?
Oh, I'm so mad. What was I fucking talking? I said Thor's name and it's angering me.
I'm actually fucked here. I think I can fit. I can't jump. I can't fit through this at...
Oh, I'm so mad at myself. You have no idea. I'm fucking furious with myself.
I am furious with myself because I went back up here and now I can't go back down. I am
absolutely livid. Why did I come back up here? Why? What was the purpose of coming up here?
Why can I... Why could I even... Okay, here's what I don't understand. Why could I fit back
through there the first time? And then when I lost like 25 centimeters, I couldn't go back down.
Really? Like I told... I don't even pay attention this time. Let's talk about Thor like throwing
darts at a scorpion. It's a pretty try-hard time. It is. I'm not gonna lose this one.
We want some grace back in the sky, but the swans don't seem to have hatched yet.
Pick up eggs. Don't... Nobody talk about any other topics besides Katamari.
Get as many as you can and make as... Okay, gotta pick up as many eggs as I can.
Seven minutes. I'm not talking about anything else. Look at Katamari eggs. Where's... Where
do I go from here? To the left. Pick up more of these eggs. Cool. All right. Eggs.
Make sure I get them all. Am I big enough? Yes, I am. I can get these ones. Focus on them.
Watch out. You don't... Well, it's going to happen every time I do this.
I'm trying to get seven. I ate like fucking 30 eggs. Okay, I got four. Four. Wait,
they can't be broken. Oh shit. Why does that one not count? They have to be swans.
You know what they say? You don't make eggs without what? Yeah, this is a beautiful song.
Don't fall off. Get them off. Cool. How many swans do I need? Just as many as I can get.
There's a lot up here.
Some of them are not going to be swans. I'm going to try to get 50 swans.
That's a number that's way too high.
There's another one. Just a regular egg.
They're hitting eggs with a golf club? What a sick fuck.
Just sit here for a second. Get them all.
What is a swan anyway? No, don't get me talking. Do not get me to talk.
I can't be trusted when I start speaking. It's a silent stream. I'm going to go underneath
because I'm still small enough to get these. If I got stuck under there, I would have just
swallowed the switch. I would have been the first person to ever eat a switch.
Oh, you momentum. Come on. You can't get angry. Yes, you can. Oh yes, you can. I was
going to say with the soundtrack playing in the background.
All right. We suspect. All right, I got 24. What do I want? 50? I'm probably only going to get
25. Oh, I haven't got up here. Can I get up there? All right. Duckling, duckling, swan. 25.
Can I make it up this way? Say something. No, not yet. This one is very specific.
I got to get to 30. You know what I'm saying? I got to get to 30. I mean, I don't understand.
30. 29. 30. I'm going to climb up on a shoe to get up here. Get up there, dude. What?
What are you doing? What are you doing? It can't be a weird number like 31.
It's got to be like 45 or something, right?
How many characters were in the last Smash Brothers game?
42. 43. That's how much we need. I can't live with this if it's 36.
Here we go. I'll get some here. You have one minute left. 38. 39. No, don't do 39.
It's going to be 41. I'm going to stop playing after I get to 40.
45. 45. Get it. 50. I can get 50. Don't sell yourself
under what you would assume. No, not 46. Oh, 46. Very graceful and a bit disturbing.
Tweet, tweet, tweet. Noisy things will take the graceful rainbow back. Restart. 46 is not bad.
That's 65 percent. That's a D. All you have to do is pass. 46 smalls. Commonplace grace.
Skin deep grace. Fake grace. Grace and light. It'll be a counterfeit constellation.
It will be a pale imitation of a swan in the sky. All righty, let's just release it into the
sky. He's mad at me for getting a D on my report card. You need a 70 to pass. Since when?
What are you guys on about? Since when do you need a 70? A 70 is a C minus.
Did they change the way the grading is done? What do you mean yes? A 60 is a D minus.
70 is now a D minus. So what's 80? That doesn't make any sense. 70 is a D minus. 80 is a C
minus. 90 is a B minus. And 100 is what? An A minus? How do you get an A plus? 80 is a B
minus. What are you guys talking about? Anything below 80 is an F. D is a fair. I'm
doing this wrong. It's not 10% per letter. I'm being fucked with here. 60 to 69 is a D.
60 is a D minus. 69 is a D plus. 70 is a C minus. 79 is a C plus. What am I? Are people
just making me feel? Talk about anything besides school. All right, I'm going to do
this one now. 70 is a B. No. No, it's not. Whatever. It's not a- whatever. I- I used- I
was- I was a teacher. I was a substitute teacher, guys. I know how to grade papers.
I didn't do any grading, by the way. I talked with a fake English accent and would draw
pictures on the board and stuff. Why am I trying to pay attention? What's with this
leveling causing my brain to turn off? Lore, you've no- oh yeah, I've talked about that
many times before. I'm staying over with the fruits. This is a different route this time.
This is the fruit route. Missed gift. No, I didn't. No, I didn't. You can't prove that.
Golden fruit split. What a joy of a video game. Can I just- let's be real.
You know what I mean? Does anybody else think that? I'm so glad that they remade this.
It deserved it. First crash of the evening of this level, I mean. First crash of the evening.
That's not true at all. Watch out for the goats. I know you're gonna say that's a dog.
That is- those are goats. That is a goat face. Much better than last time. Nobody brought up
any comic book characters. I didn't talk about, like, orchestras. There's no reference
to shitting. And look at how good I'm doing. Let me take a look. Anything else over here
I can do? Is this a sponsored stream? Is that even happening? Why would they sponsor people to
play this? Why else would I play this? No, don't start. Don't start it. You're in the
middle of doing very well. See? I controlled myself. No, if you're new to the- if you're
new to the channel here on Twitch, I do not do sponsored content on the channel. That is a-
that is a guarantee. We're all new. That's not to say I never will for any reason, but I probably
won't. I cannot see a scenario where I ever would. Is that a money back guarantee? Covering
his tracks again? Okay, hold on. When was the last sponsored thing you saw on this stream?
Time's up, because the answer is it's never happened. That's never happened. It's been
like three years. Sponsored by JetBlue. No, I just said that JetBlue is a fantastic fucking
airplane company that's quality and I've never had a problem with them. That's not me- that's
not a sponsorship. That's me talking about a service that I've purchased that I liked.
Brain fluid. Yeah, but they didn't even pay me. The guy that- the guy that made the company
fucking- I got like a bunch of weird emails. They were all broken up and it almost like
there's a lot of typos and shit. He said that the check- it was- it was for 40 grand.
That's why I did it. And he said it was- it'd be- I would get it within two business days of doing
the sponsorship. And I- he- I got- it was a little weird because I had to send money to him
first to like prove that my bank account was be- could be linked to his. So I- I mean,
I'm still kind of waiting. I sent to get it to work. All right, we've got eight minutes.
Yeah, I mean, it was two business days and that was, um, was it like a year ago now? So,
I mean, maybe I got like stuck or lost in the mail or something. And it's weird because every
time I send a message to that email address, I get back the the mailer like daemon thing,
whatever it is, the Matt Damon mailer that says the address doesn't exist or something,
which is weird. I'm trying to get him to send me his new email. I'm sure he will.
Nintendo, give me it. Oh no, he's getting distracted again.
Get the cap. Car. All right, this time when I go down, I'm not going back up. Not going down
there yet. Let me get a couple more things in here because this place I didn't go right over
here. Okay, now I'm going down. Watch out for the people that are blocking my path. That's
the only reason why they're up here is just to walk back and forth and be annoying.
See? All right, no one's. I've got over five minutes to do this. More than halfway there.
Make sure I don't miss anything. Get the pineapple. Jerma, get the pineapple. Jerma,
the pineapple. The pineapple. Get the pineapple, Jerma. Jerma, get the pineapple.
Jerma, get the pineapple. Okay. Jesus Christ. Jesus. Choose. All right. Almost at one meter
and then it gets easier. What are you? Why do the people have to be just in a fucking way?
Get away from me. I'm going to get all the radishes and all the fruits here.
It's just free and it's a lot of space. It gets a lot of space.
Takes up a lot of space on the actual Katamari. It's very heavy. That's why it takes a while
to roll it. It's a heavy piece of equipment. Okay. Now we're going to cross this way.
Pick up a couple of these baskets. Up and across. Here we go. I beat the level. I won.
Now nobody can pull back this VOD and be like. That's what a lot of you guys do.
I get to a certain part of the game that I have trouble with and then you just sit there
and go. Get on stage. Take all this guy's stuff. This is a huge. Come on. 1.5. Almost there.
This is done. Now it begins. This is the guy that died to Pinwheel on stream. I did.
It was really bad. I lost like 30 times in a row. I think that evening I think I lost
six or seven hundred subscribers to the channel because I died to Pinwheel on like
the 20th or 30th attempt that I remember just like. Chat was. We got a huge argument.
It was like, dude, you are so fucking terrible. And I went off. Let me tell you something, chat.
I was talking about like how Pinwheel is hard and like I think the word I used was like
dumb idiots or something like that. It was like a thousand subs that left overnight.
It was really bad for the channel. Can I get two? What is your cat? What is Duck Hunt
Dog doing up there? Yes, I'm going to make references to Spanish Brothers because I've been
playing it recently. Well, I can't move from here, so a good thing I beat it.
Still not two meters. Give me the two. Come on. I'm going to grow a little bit higher.
And then, no, not another level. I got to be close to getting a little bigger.
You all laughed at me when I was small. And look at you now. What about this guy? Let's
rip him off the pole. Now I know why Jerma likes this game. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's
really, really funny. That's very funny. That's going to be when Twitch finally does their awards,
right? You know, you see like the gamer awards. It's like the one. No, eventually,
I'm going to predict this is the timestamp. And like the next year or two,
Twitch is going to have its own award show for a bunch of different Twitch related awards.
It's going to be the Twitch Awards and there'll be a whole thing. It'll do to probably
TwitchCon. It's going to happen. And when they do that, they're going to pull back.
They'll be like, best chat joke. And there'll be nominees on screen and you'll get to go.
You'll be sitting there next to the guy that said resident sleeper. Like he spammed it
during a boring part of a video game. That one will probably be nominated.
I don't understand. Santa hat. Santa hat. Ice cube. I don't know. What is this?
If it were ours, we'd make it much bigger. The thing that you collected the most of is
vegetables. Oh, I got lots of vegetables. I don't have a better TV and I'm never going to have it.
I'm never going to download it. I have a bright white background and default emotes.
I saw him. I saw him outside. He was just standing there.
King of the cosmos should be in Smash Brothers. Shouldn't he?
Too big. Oh, that was the Ridley excuse. And we got Ridley. So I don't buy, I don't buy that
one anymore. Make Corona Warialis. Any other ones we have so far? Make a star six. Let's do the
Corona. What is it? It still needs something. Is it our royal present? No, something more.
Oh yes. It's not gorgeous. The sky is not gorgeous at all. A starry sky and it still
manages to look shabby. It has gone. It has none of the beauteous maximal gorgeousness of our
crown. What do you mean year? What are you talking about? Can somebody describe what the Santa hat
emote is? Describe what it is. Oh, it's balding. Amazing, amazing. The earth looks amazing today.
What's this? Crowns everywhere. It's just a Santa hat. But what does it look like? Is it on
somebody? It puts a hat on an emote. So it's just, it's a Santa hat that looks like it's
on top of the emote. Okay. All right, I gotta pick up crowns. Let's roll them all up before
somebody shows up. Get as many as you can. Super fab gorgeous sky. These crowns must belong to
someone. There are just too many. If a likely person shows up, we'll make a getaway to the
great cosmos. In the meantime, we have nine minutes. Hurry pilfering prince. That one felt
real fucking good. That was a cheeseburger. That was the Burger King. I missed something
up there. Fuck it. Who cares? We need crowns. Not like baking soda.
I love the dogs driving the car sharing a crown. What are they moving? What are they
rolling? They're pushing a can. Why does this have to exist? They're looking for crowns.
This is going to be annoying. I'm sorry, guys. Hello. Hello. This is the king. Hello.
Yes, this is Doug. He should have said that. How funny would that have been? Get all the
swords. I gotta get bigger. Forget about the crowns right now. I have one more. I gotta
level up. What even is this game? This is Katamari Damacy Rerolled. It's a game where
you start small and have to roll up any object you can possibly roll up. That's right. You
can even roll up anything. Everything is roll up-able eventually. You progress through the game
and you have to make stars. It is a one of a kind. You have never experienced it before.
Oh, is there a treat waiting for you? Cloud was confirmed. That's cool, right?
Santa please Santa hat. What? No. Sour please Santa hat. Sponsored stream.
Next person that says sponsored stream. You are getting free tickets to Disneyland.
No, you're not. That's a joke. I'm kidding. Oh, did I say Disneyland? Oh, I'm sorry. What
I meant to say was we're going to go to the website Disneyland. You get free tickets for me
to show you the website Disneyland. We get to go on a virtual Disneyland tour together.
That's what I meant. I didn't say you physically were getting tickets to physically
go to Disneyland. You get tickets to go to the virtual tour of Disneyland on my stream.
Now I have to do that. I need so many more crowns. Go to the dark house. Scam. I wonder,
okay, how much would that actually cost? Were there 4200 people here?
Isn't a Disneyland ticket like fucking 400 bucks? What's 400 times 4200? And what's
4200 times all the money that would have to be paid for plane tickets? That's like 20
million dollars. I need crowns now that I've gotten large enough. Go to Disneyland if you see
a crown, okay? Anybody that sees a crown can scream Disneyland and then they'll, you know,
you know what I mean. Disneyland. I'm not big enough for that one. I'll get one of the
guys bumped. I'm not falling off. There are a lot of crowns down here though. But I'm not,
I can't get up on these. I can barely get them. I believe you owe me some tickets. Get
bigger. I'm trying. Free tickets to Disneyland. Just get bigger already. Just go to Disneyland
already. I'm kidding. I know the present is there. What's in it? One of our royal presents.
It's tickets to Disneyland. Free tickets to Disneyland. When was the last time you guys went
to Disneyland? Overused joke. We just made it five minutes ago. We just brought that up
like not even 10 minutes ago. Old joke. When was the last time Disneyland went to you?
Does it count if you hire like a Mickey Mouse mascot to dance at a Christmas party?
Not a Christmas party. A birthday party. I only have 30 of these. I need more crowns.
How did I miss all of them? Christmas party. What kind of fucked up Christmas party is that?
Can I get these? Ah! Yes! Big crown. That's a huge crown right there and I can't touch it. I hate
this. I want that. I can't pick that one up. You have one minute left to get. I've got to get
to 50 right? Or you can't get through there. Why? It's all ruined again. No it's okay.
He's sponsored by Disney. No. No I'm not sponsored by Disney. No one gets Disneyland
tickets. It was a reference to a tv show. I was watching a tv show where the host gave out tickets
to Disneyland to everybody in the audience. It may have been Oprah. 43. It can't be a number
like that. I will restart the whole fucking level if it's 43. It's got to be like even 45 or
something. Oh thank god. Someone's coming. Oh we can't open our eyes. It's too dazzling.
Let's take a look at our rainbow. 45 is not even 44 is. Boy we failed that one. It's all right.
Well it's 44 crowns. Only a measly 44 so it'll be a bland constellation. Here this is our
royal present. It's a crown. Guess what? Guess what this is. Alrighty let's just release it
into the sky. We're still on the same level from an hour ago? I mean that was the same
area. Different mission. That looked like shit. He said crap. I don't know why I turned
it into a swear. There was no reason for me to do that. I just transferred what you said.
They said this looks like crap and I said shit. Thank you Cuman. Cuman gave 10 community
subs earlier. Thank you Cuman. Appreciate it. 10 community subs. I missed them. I didn't see
them. But we have to crown them. We can't have the scarf on. That's kind of... Give us
more slots Valve. What the hell? Yeah we'll keep the crown on. Looks good. Sponsored by Valve.
Mega Star 6. Let's see what we've opened up. Is that the only one? I think that's the only one.
This is the end of the game. Level 6. So when are you going to go back to beat Dark Souls 3
without taking damage? I wouldn't be able to do that for a million dollars. Like for literally
a million dollars. I wouldn't be able to do it. Have you ever been to the Arabian Peninsula?
We haven't either. We hope you can visit during the day's rolling. Really? Could you?
Okay. Could you right now if somebody sat down with a briefcase and said there's a million dollars
in cash here and it's just ready for you to take it and it's been taxed. It's been pre-taxed.
So you're fine. Like that's it. It's just cash. But you have to beat Dark Souls 3 without taking
one hit. Like right there in front of like right there right now in front of this guy.
That would be easy. Yes that would be dumb not to do it. But how you wouldn't be able
to do it? It would be impossible. You gave your present away to somebody on earth.
Must be around somewhere. Roll it up while you're at it. Whoa you guys got real fucking dark.
It's not impossible. It is not impossible. But what's gonna happen is you're gonna because
you haven't played Dark Souls 3 in like seven months. You're gonna load it up. Be like I'm
gonna try. I'm gonna at least give it my first attempt. And you're gonna get a hit by like
the third enemy. You're gonna be in the graveyard and you're gonna fuck up a dodge because you
haven't played in a while and you're gonna take the hit. And he's gonna go
ha ha ha grab the briefcase close it up like see you later fucking loser
and he walks out it's but it was so close it was right there in front of you
all right we need a crisp three meters just tackle him i'm sorry about that there are
30 bodyguards with him like like i'm sorry oh just like steal it i'll take it from him
okay good luck and these 30 bodyguards are so big that they can barely fit in your
bedroom like only two of them can fit in your room they're like seven feet tall
and they weigh at least like a like 290 like to like 350 pounds each and just for just
because like you lost so you like quickly one of the huge bodyguards just fucking karate
chops your destiny it crumbles in half why would he do that i don't know you invited
these guys here you'd say you let you let these guys come into your house okay
you have to be ready to take the potential like desk chop let me know we didn't well what do we
know we did the guy just comes in your house hey doorbell rings oh it's fucking like seven
o'clock in the morning until i'm like tired i haven't even had coffee who's at the door
here's a million dollars in this briefcase think you can beat dark souls three
hold on the telephone's over here turn off slow mode no i can't turn off slow mode there's
too many there's so many people here there's over 4 000 people here well look at this guys
i just got like five million dollars coward i want to be able to read what people are saying
it gets hard i don't i don't want it to be a situation where
you kind of have to it's a series of weird compromises right because i don't want slow
mode to be impossible to talk but then i don't want the chat just to be like
it's hard it's hard okay stack of bears i'll go get them over here right
look at these bears i can't even pick them up why did you tell me to do that
come on let's clear the chat thank you that's the way
what the fuck is going on over here all right all right what can i go i just want to like
explore i don't care about picking things up anymore eventually i'll get out there pick
up these at least yes holy shit sour please that's the emo that's the emo where the
guy's doing like a fortnight dance right so this is a fortnight emo you can't get those
yet there we go this is what i'm talking about get me growing get me growing i can't
pick up the merry-go-round halfway there there we go all right here it comes this is what you
came to scream for never mind never mind whatever i figure the fences did you get 3.0 can i pick
up the people i can can i pick up the bears i can i can't pick up the bunny for some strange
reason he's too tall what guy on the yep there you go got him go get the bear stack
that's gonna have to be a final thing let me just make sure i get to three first
how is he still bigger than boxes there's a bear okay where are they there they are
got them i think i might have accidentally killed one but i did get them right now i have
to go get the guy doing the that the thing the guy doing the thing down here we will
eventually pick up the chicken sheep all right let's get him i can't pick him up guy on the no i
can't pick up the lifeguard what about these people yep what would you do in this situation
does it be i think this is scarier than godzilla i really do because godzilla is a huge scary
monster and you know exactly what's going on all right scary huge monster came out
of the ocean and is just breathing fire on us and killing us right
but this you don't have an explanation for this one
and that's more terrifying like i can explain king kong somebody if they ask me i can't explain
the katamari like trash ball nice katamari very airy and exciting but now that you've come this
far let's do it even more oh you can get you actually get the bushes now signs trees
nothing is going to stop me now it's a stupid light post just messing everything up
keep going i'm wanting i want to pick up a house can i get the boat now for the dispense
nice again that's gonna be a huge amount of girth here still three minutes anything else
can i get an island get the captain at least i got the captain all right back up into the
town uh just kidding i mean never go back to the town again i can't pick up the trees
oh that's not cool let's just go this way light house is there any way to get back up there
this way maybe there we are you have one minute get it all everything
uh this is the best part of the game and i hate that i only have a minute to enjoy it
get bigger get all the cows another one of these guys no what the fuck is happening over
here i just ruined it like a gymnastics competition i don't think i can get to five
no i don't think so four point seven eight it's like a it's like a thief right there
four point eight ah that's big enough we have a piano lesson now so we'll go back to space
royal rainbow go he actually won yeah there's only one level where i spent more than
an hour on but i'm in no rush it's kata maria you can do better well since you're the prince
you should do much better you did that fast you hit the goal awfully fast that was fantastic
that was so speedy and so smart it will be a shooting star like boom the thing that
you feel like the most of is i got flowers is the most interesting okay speedy and smart
streamer floral but that makes sense flower party
i can't talk during the cut scenes it's not nice it just wouldn't be right if i talked to
the cut scene safe complete and we must have unlocked some more anymore like cousins
yeah but i want to be i want to be this guy why am i not allowed to be that guy
that's not fun okay make racy species dude shroom laughing my ass off laughing my
hour i'd say that hello uh there's something missing we have it it's not fresh the sky is
spoiled already it's not fresh at all it's very ripe this is not acceptable quickly find
some fresh fish on earth rolling up fish no it's not right it's fucking raw up here
can't even cook a fucking scallop hurry prince the sky is looking a little tired much like
your eyes and clouded like something you see on last week's fish oh feeling a bit more
at home on earth and starting to get a little complacent are we getting a swelled head
terrible get as many as you can and make as fishy a katamari as you can
for a beautiful pisces for a super fab fresh sky we order you to look at rolling with a
fresh eye rediscover it we plan to rediscover waiting around for six minutes perk up loser
prince oh i got a cat i'm getting every fish look at all oh this is so cool look at how many
there are so many fish over there get it these sharks can i pick these guys up
oh they move around i gotta be bigger for that now i gotta know my battles
yeah know my battles because i can't run these guys down can't go this way i need
some more little fish move over to the flowers flags
okay can i pick up the flowers no it's a texture on the ground
too small for these yeah damn it come on i only have a few more minutes i grow even
one more meter and this whole thing is mine stingray okay skipped all the fish i couldn't
pick them up they're in too awkward of a spot they run away stingray is not a fish
i was actually gonna ask that but i felt scared that somebody you know people would be like wow
you don't think stingray is a fish and i knew i was probably correct that stingray is not a fish
but you know i didn't want to get ridiculed the same he did this who flattened this like a
pancake i'm talking about uh not big enough for these can i get them yet no i gotta be much
bigger kind of sand cap is over here can i get the trash actually so much larger than this
just get out you can't go under that man who did this i actually can't go up here
what the fuck man all right i'm not even going to attempt to do it again
i'm stuck on barbed wire of all things still can't fucking get these random things i can
pick up down here from monster truck get up there all right i'm big enough to get these
that's what i was waiting for i can't get these ones though i gotta go back up where
those at the hunt of them are over here penguins penguins are fish right no they're not a penguin
is not a fish penguins are not fish i thought it was gonna count them as fish for some reason
all right i got a bunch of those i need to go to that area where they will all line around
and they have two minutes to get it there's that spot there's that area with all the
random ones just lying on the ground it's like up here there it is you have a minute left
i think i can get on it back this way 86 all right just wait they're right here just wait
until they're gonna dive back over this way just get them 88 89 90 91 92 94 i'm huge now
95 96 i got plenty of time and there's 101 don't give me a weird number 120 120 not 118 120 120
are you feeling livelier too we'll take the fresh rainbow back uninstalled again
that's not even 70 that's like a neighborhood fishing champ
get out there and challenge yourself on the open sea forget the dinky neighborhood you can do
better yes you have more than this yes we'll force it into a constellation but do it fresher
next time all righty let's just release it into the sky i will get every fish i will get 68
percent of every fish so fresh i still have any new presents okay let's see what else we opened
we got make a star seven make gemini and i believe uh make ursa major uh let's make
it ursa let's make the bear ursa major
it got away to tell you the truth i skipped it ursa major to be exact the parent that leaves
all the work to the child that looks bad dead to be yes so we we were finally done and then
the last one gets away shoot stupid bear we are sick of it so just roll me up one bear and roll
up the present too i just have to give one this game teaches you that the constellations are
made up of trash fish rats and people in their houses and movies programs and alligators
bear family oh i smell a bear bad bears bad hurry up and start rolling just one that's all
we need one bear we're just missing one last bear give us the largest bear you can find
we'll be patient for 10 minutes what the fuck i don't remember those two guys doing this
uh leave you to work so i need the biggest bear i can find uh you got a bear we can calm
down now what the what is that it's small we didn't lose a small little bear like this
fine we'll somehow scrape up an ursa major from this but next time get a much bigger bear
rolled up so you actually can't touch any bears holy shit that's gonna be hard how did i pass
that then strangely enough on the right side that's the fastest i've ever completed a mission
well let's do it again where was it was ursa major okay i know what to do now we're also
making a constellation ursa major yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep so i'm already big enough
where i can pick up most things already so i need a big bear that's a big bear right there
right that bear is singing into a microphone and people are watching why are those people
stacked up stadium seating with benches all right well that i'm going for that one so
i need to get a little bigger just make sure i don't run over any fears i got 10 minutes
so i can just chill that one's pretty big too is that a bear or is that a person in a bear costume
does that count look at that bear what the fuck has happened to humanity what time place
is this when does this take place okay um he's wasting time i'm just look there bears in the
water i just got i gotta be slow about this because i don't want to pick up anything
accidentally bear no champion felt there's a bear in here don't touch that bear the
costume counts as a bear so you're sure about that watch out don't go so fast i got a lot of
time elephant is not a bear but just walking around on the street
come on
holy shit that's a bear that's a very big bear and it just tried to kill me okay i'm gonna try
to look at that bear look at all these bears they're everywhere that one's huge too floating
balloons what the fuck is going on in here why they all just want a bear on
what are they what's he standing on just a ball they're playing baseball with watermelons
slow down slow down slow i will i'll slow down you're right you're right i gotta slow down i
want to roll up any cubs that guy don't drop that bear on me what was a bear where what
what bear what where's the bear what bear that's a sign of a bear that counts as a bear
a sign of a bear what the hell that's even smaller than the last one but that's not a
cover it back i'm gonna go i'm gonna take a piss and get water
all right why are you guys screaming what is there a reason why everyone's yelling
oh the music all right well whatever so snowy what does that one look like explain it to me
all right we'll go back to that one later because i can't even roll up a sign of a bear
make a star sign do the bear no we'll go back to the bear later what am i eating a little
like meal bar thing i've been to poland did we go there often hope you can visit during the
day's rolling stop being a boomer and download the plugin couldn't help but throw it towards
earth we suppose it was too much to expect the dog to go fetch that far must be around
somewhere i'm not a boomer if anything i would be i'm i'm late millennial no early millennial
that's not a boomer a boomer is like 60 the katamari should be six meters that's pretty
big all right next person that says boomer is getting free oh i fucked it up already
ba na na banana turn the music up hold on just one little second they go there's your music
here it comes i have to get every banana why am i such a psycho just don't have to get
every single banana i have to i have to follow the trail and it's so awkward to control going
don't say banana again i guess i'm collecting all the bananas and i got them all no i didn't
how many more bananas i got that has to be all
what was it six meters
i can do that
let's go back up to oh i guess i have to go this way
can i collect that's all
more fruits get them all you can't even grow one meter in real life
yeah what do you mean yes you can it happens from age eight to 15
oh you're talking about oh you're saying i and this is what happens when i look at the
fucking chapter i look at the chat room somebody calling me smaller than your average
bear you know what i mean and i get stuck on a plate what the hell is money is watching tv
not loud enough turn it up turn it up turn it up you say the for space w h a two question mark
i'm gonna say it ironically now i'm gonna say it ironically trying to get back to civilization
i'm wasting so much time down here there we go chickens
wasn't there we go there we go there we go now we can get there
follow the simple rules birthday cakes gasoline hey birthday cake and gasoline what a combination
i'm not gonna turn it up it's already already very loud it's too it it is too loud that's
people have been giving me shit it's way too loud i need to turn it down if anything
okay who was just gtaing off the side there me apparently it's not big enough to get these
why no don't hit me with the duck boat almost there it is stop sandwiching me
all right i can actually pick up people that's good don't touch the bear right i'm not seeing
very many large objects to pick up which is concerning me just a little there are a lot
of people down here though can i get the bikes i can't good why are you so weird
three penguins just watching the whole thing don't think i can pick these up but i hope i can
no i think people have on with it not the actual bikes themselves
this is gonna be tough turn your voice down
turn your voice down now there are people sleeping
up
only five minutes i gotta get so huge i'm not even close even close
just gonna say how good that can be all right three meters still just a baby
there's a way through here all right quickly start picking shit up turn it down all right
it's going down it's too big to control it's too big to control it it's so big i can't handle it
i really can't i can't even pick up these bikes can i open these doors yes all right new area
this might have just saved the whole area the whole run may have been just been saved from this
if i can grow another level here it should be okay 4.4 not enough there it is all right
come on exponential exponential growth what else is out here can't get the cars yet back into the
town huge rocks anymore big rocks get out of my fucking way 5.3 this fucking music is
gonna give me a nightmare i can't get through that yes i can only six not even six i don't
think there's gonna be enough time oh get over there please i can get cars now i can do it i
can do it i can do it i can do it i can do it i can do it i can do it i can do it i can
do it i can pick up cars tractor i can't get the fucking tractor almost there i thought it
was eight not big enough to pick up the i have way too much momentum though there's no way i can
actually control this anymore i just have to let it go wherever it's gonna go
not big enough to pick up a house and get almost everything else
can i get up this way yet
can't get up that yes you can yes you can there's so much stuff here to get
i only have 40 seconds at least get to seven there it's 7.7 7.2
no can i get to eight i'm stuck 7.7 maybe if i roll off let me get the tractor nope see you
later 7.43 that feels so great is the audio out of sync let's test it did it just happen
let's try most thing i thought it was fruit and then teenagers okay vitamins
all right let's let's test it ready so i'm gonna i'm gonna make noise when i move
it should be syncing up ready
do we sing hold on with this ready one three four we got it all right how much longer am i
gonna play for yeah i mean two hours a couple hours we'll see when we get to like
five or six hours in well let's see taurus star eight gemini
there we're also making a constellation taurus apparently this is the same thing you have to get
one bull stupid cow one cow sorry i'm like eating i bought these specifically for streams
because sometimes i get real hungry i'm one of those people that after like three or four
hours of sitting in the same place i have to eat so i got these little bars that they're
like protein meal replacements and they're actually pretty good they're okay it's a cookie
flavor we smell a cow always mooing noisy things hurry up and start rolling all right
hold on i'm ready one biggest cow you can find all right there it is that's what we have to get
that's the one we have to find we have to pick up with that one keep that one on your
radar these cooked chickens all right actually i'm gonna be very careful here no cow signs
if i pick up milk does that count it better not that's not gonna count is it taking my
sweet time with this don't hit the fucking cow
the car phases through the barrels what are you waiting in line for
what are you doing there's some big cows up here a sheep is not a cow right it's not
but does the game think it is almost touched a cow that was a cow sign wasn't it whoa whoa whoa
where's the cow cow cow cow cow cow cow's coming don't touch the sign this is minefield i can't
go through this i'm so nervous right now these are so difficult it's so hard just to ram into
things so easy to ram in things it's not hard the trees in the way are really starting
to give me like a panic attack i need to get out of the trees head down this way i can
get people wait it's a couch up it fell out of the tree oh these are so hard
outplayed oh how is this possible the cow is gonna fall out of the tree
time next time get a bigger one i was being so careful too what the hell not scouting i
didn't know the bumping into the tree was gonna drop cow coconuts no presents either
what kind of christmas is this star eight gemini okay how is this gonna work how can this be
there's something missing ah yes that's it we get it now it has no mystery the sky has no
mystery it's so straightforward and easy to understand that's important of course
which is so boring it'll tell you what's mysterious twins what is with that connection
is it telepathy do they have esp for god's sake visit and switch cousins i thought i couldn't
do that unless it was multiplayer but i can't you're talking about the mushroom right is
there a different spot to do that eek identical mind-bending uncanny come to think of it didn't
you have a twin a lot of them uh at least it's 62 i believe is my number that i've been
given really so not true well that's boring no surprises there at all well your deficiencies aside
get as many twins as you can and make as twin pack the katamari as you can twins super fab
wonderful sky i gotta pick up twins since it's all about the twins you'll have 11 minutes
devil the usual we'll look forward to the results solitary prince twin boots we see
oh it could be twin anything how does the game determine that you picked up double of something
if you pick up like a thousand of them frog give me the other frog i didn't get the other
bat all right two dogs oh look at all the bowling pins two four six eight two birds got
them i accidentally got them okay twin pineapples how is that not right what get out of here
you just have to pick up everything apparently i didn't get cleansed 15 16 don't fall off
thank you for listening i don't think i'm big enough to get those animals let's go to beach
don't hit me yeah whatever how did you roll over i thought i avoided it i don't know what it
is that's not twins i just got three uh that's triplets not that it matters right jellyfish
aren't twins why is that turn your cam off i did i just looked over to and i had a small
panic attack i don't know why i did because i'm i'm i'm naked i don't wear clothes i speak
get over there give me up on the mountain thing you're all going so fast stop going this
fast birds no twin vision hello they're triplets why something wrong with that
get this what a loser say i don't know plenty of bats here
cabbage cabbage how's that not twin carrot carrot no get the cat cats on a twin now the cat
doesn't have a twin to eat so look at all these telephone twins that apparently doesn't count
grab twins somewhere called older and younger i see interesting can you get the rabbits
got the two dogs oh i didn't pick up the phone pick up the goddamn phone older brother
but it's not they're not twins okay those telephones are twins twin cats
oh now i understand why everybody was like pick up cat pick up cat
they don't have to be next to each other to be twins i see
i get it frying pans what about the two pizza boxes i can't even pick them up okay telephone
let's go back to the beach wait wait wait wait i see twins these are actually twins right here
you can't pick up the i'm down there there are cows down here get all of them these guys
twins get out of the way a watermelon is stronger than a car 40 he's 241 still not big
enough i just killed the other one there bear twins how can a log be a twin
streamer gets bullied by watermelon can't pick it up can't pick these up what about
down with these people down here these two mermaids twins how did they get you
but not the other one 46 down here i got another guy's rolling around still not big enough
so
none of you are directly related that came out at the same time fire and you guys twins
tuplets are not the same thing there are twins here on twin bikes got it those guys don't count
as twins the one on the front is in charge how does that make them not related skateboard
come here just come here i just need to i need you for research just come here
oh fuck me this guy playing golf i can't even pick them up i have to get to 50
those guys are not twins can i get you guys now nope shit funny twins 29
50 guys odd numbering incoming it sucks no maybe not so fast odd numbering coming
yeah no it's we got lost one i feel better it's still a mystery beyond comprehension a
thing of wonder we'll take the mystery rainbow to drink this like that 46 percent
real mystery is how you manage to get so few oh quite the critic became the cause pose
that is actually an f just like clockwork i look over here just tease all i see are
tees all right so somebody was saying go do the cousin's thing but i can't select these
guys this is only for multiplayer another cousin has arrived okay i wish i could just pick one
i want to be this guy there's so many interesting characters so one guy said that
but that doesn't matter it's still i know i know you could be them in some of the sequels
names objects location size chart somewhat large press x to jump no you said press x to juke
all right what have we unlocked star eight i think that's the last one here that is we have
to do this one star number literally just select one by pressing a and then you can't
do anything after that after you select somebody it just says okay then it waits for
another player to connect can't do it you've been to russia we were there yesterday hope you can
visit yeah we tried a royal present for the hard-working prince i've not picked up a present
in two to three hours we didn't bother to actually get one but we're sure there's
something down there's something that looks like a present it's earth after all they have
everything why is my chat whatever i don't i don't even what do you what am i supposed
to say i don't know oh rash today you'll be rolling around the town catamari should be
12 meters we can believe 18 minutes this is a long one this is a full raid boss guys
i gotta be on my a game any longer and yeah all right a game i'm gonna bring the tryhard
here i'm not even kidding you know i'm not getting around i'm not even kidding smack
crackers cookie sandwiches level up already don't let it get to your head don't let it get to your
head just keep the fundamentals up roll spin roll spin pick up the clips
desync we're hearing noises before he picks it up is that for real you're hearing noises
before i pick it up how about now next was one guy but i want to make sure that that
one guy has a fun experience you know i'm saying if that one guy goes no no no no no
no and then leaves i then i lost a one guy there may be four thousand people here well
not anymore i think i lost like 300 people when i talked about like shitting starburst
i think i lost a few people there but there are there are 4001 of news you know what i'm
saying and it makes a collective four thousand one guy you know what i mean
the grilled cheese sure yeah how we doing we're okay not great but not bad either
can i get the fence not quite but i do we need to go this way you're almost you have
200 000 followers where are they all where where are all the people that have ever
followed by stream i don't know where are they how dare those people have things to potentially
do and how they need to be here watch me roll up stuff so you guys are here to be fair i'm
not even following see so then yeah that's all that's all good you have to follow the channel
if you don't want to but i mean i'm only down i'm only taking followers to uh virtual
disney world so what was that noise i've rolled over something and it went
i don't know this person's body get out of the way all right don't lose it here come on get up
don't let this be the reason why this ends because i got stuck over a fucking fence
how does this happen why can i not just go back over this why why can i go over there
in the first place what is it why i could go over it i can't go back over it
it's an incline do i really have to restart this we started off well and i got stuck in
this one one tiny little place that i cannot get out of jesus mother of okay i'm gonna have
to pick up the pigs all right i gotta make this last few minutes count uh 45 we're sure you
can go further i need to i have to otherwise i lose look at these huge trucks this is might
have been a bad idea to go down this way and how does he do it every time
i really need to be more than a meter right now i can't pick these up either
i might be completely fucked right now yeah i'm fucked this is i don't think this is
possible anymore everything here is way too big yeah the game game over because i went down the
hill no not not not yet don't say that yet you can use your one reset why do i only get one reset
i'm stuck hell one reset thanks lady you really made this easy for me
why is that guy holding a gun i gotta get on these this fireworks
well it's not even worth doing this these are too small hands hurt
something about holding up and down on the analogs but permanently it's giving me the arthritis
really am boomer man my hands are like a hurting this is all too far way too far in between i was
not supposed to come down here when i did it's gonna be close but i might still be able to do
it chat every time if there was some way i could let you guys collectively control this
i would that'd be so funny here we go i also might after this level like i'm gonna grab the uh
the actual controller thing that this thing the little watermelon slices go into
i'm holding these little ice cream sandwiches in either hand i think it's part of the problem
don't go in the water god please all right talking in riddles no i'm talking about the
switch controllers i know the switch is a great console and it's so wonderful there's a lot of
great games on it but the if you don't have like the pro controller you can put your thumb
over every single face button and be able to press them all at the same time it's it's like
a it's the youth my thumb can cover every single button i really just need to go get
the uh actual controller because that's a little bigger right it's a huge alligator all
right i gotta focus focus focus focus don't block my path there i gotta go to the baseball
game no i'm not supposed to be here all right can i please pick these up now yes
can't pick up people yet i can't i can i can't i can hurt them but i can't pick them up okay
i guess i stole a pizza from this lady that's all i can do i don't really don't know where to
go i'm in like the worst possible place to be in right now i have i can i'm even make it
back up here god oh i'm gonna scream what is preventing me from going over here this lip
that lip right there is what's that's preventing me from going over huh why is that preventing me
from going over somebody just died okay he's peeking the mic no am i why couldn't i go
over that lip why was i banned from going back where i was before please tell me that helps
me here just pick up everything i can down every hall the printers there's so many corridors in
this level there's little tiny corridors everywhere just probably pick up the entire bench right
give me all of them people are shooting at me now
i tell you this is scarier than godzilla this is scarier than king kong go north
huh which way is north i missed the present oh well i need to beat this this is a long level
the length of this one i'm not gonna have to get the playground stuff
if you get to 12 here's the baseball game i don't want to go to the floor five beaters
finally this was not as big as we thought don't worry i'm still working on it they get cars
oh not yet shit why did i pick up these cars and not the other one
that car is bigger than the one that's on the road right there gas station
just getting stuck on everything i'm too big for my own good
i'm too big but not big enough to matter up here all the stationary cars get them all all
of them this is such a great place to be if i could just get this construction equipment
pick it up come on i need this so bad i'm almost there oh stop being so slow
just go roll over the whole town now i need that momentum not bringing up for a house
oh my god i don't even know where i am i'm on top of the buildings
11.4 come on get it get it i don't even know what's happening anymore i made it
16 minutes all right i'm getting houses for the first time ever yes it feels so good it feels
fantastic all the build-up to pick up the monopoly houses 17 meters can i get 20 one minute left
there's another little area right here come on run them over every person here is dead
but well it's possible but i don't know even bigger
in case you were wondering now i'm in the clouds now i'm too big to even understand
and this is not even close to as big as you can get my game 21 like what else is it for me
to pick up 22.46 glad we got that one though it's pretty big we imagine it'll
make a pretty good store if it were ours we'd make it much bigger the most thing you got was
plants well that makes sense i'm running over dirt green that's it
i'm gonna mute my mic
i mean that was that was disgusting i'm trying to drink this is a straw supposed
to go in this cup but i don't have the straw so i have to suck it out of the top
i have to drain i have to bite into this like a snake vergo vergo or let's make sure
you overfill the drink no the drink has a lid on it that a straw is supposed to go through
like through the little hole but i don't have the straw and i don't have a straw
so i have to have to drain it through the top it's lacking a certain something
is it our royal present no that's not it oh yes we get it
prettiness the sky is not pretty at all it's rough and masculine possibly sweaty what we want is
pure girlish prettiness there should be loads of maidens like those on earth take the top off
and drink it like a cup why didn't i do that though i just could i could just take off the
lid but but hold on hold on let me let me give me i could have some defense here
i didn't touch anything somebody kicked me down the stairs
okay listen a couple of days ago i dumped a full entire coffee on my desk 16 ounces didn't even
take a sip it dumped on the whole thing it ruined this whole entire room it took me like
an hour and a half to clean it up and i said i will never i'm gonna i'm gonna close
drinks i don't want to knock anything over and have it spill not never again so
subconsciously that's why i was doing this rat movie is about to hit a million views
that's a that's quite an achievement i never thought that i didn't even
that had that many to begin with took you an hour and a half to clean it up spencer you
have no idea man it was fucking ridiculous the earth is full of maidens this is another lucky
day for the prince uh roll up as many as you can and make as maiden rich a catamari as you
can super fab pretty sky most earth maidens are easily bored so you only have 11 minutes
we look forward to it frisky prince okay 11 minutes how have i already oh the dolls
it's a trail of dolls what are you saying oh i need to change that i'd rather just
shake the controls hold on a minute can i do that from here no going up down up down up down
on the joysticks is kind of a pain in the ass i'd rather just do the i'd rather just
shake the wemo i'm just literally a cop what is this laugh what is this laugh i need to get up
some speed is this the whole area is the pool over there the lady with a cat coming out of
her stomach i need to go into the pool but i need to be bigger than this i can't take
anything it's supposed to be like a school i don't understand with a field trip no idea
outdoor school there was a door but no walls and roof it was very odd pick any of this stuff up no
i feel like i may have missed a lot of things in the beginning picnic basket
i grow one more time i think or i can actually bear carving in this way
now should get it in the second here there we go okay i've reached the level of largeness
that i need to pick people up for the most part you could pick them up really good i ran
right into them last time remember i went through there and i bumped into the desk and the person
of death whoa present a present okay i need to remember where this is because when i get big
enough to collect that present i want to come back all right i got a feeling up there
sliding door why there's only sliding doors up here
all right over to the wrestling ring not quite large enough no all right is that really going
to block me that one tiny little thing in the way i need 100 i'll pick it up for the
present right not yet although it might be able to reach it not quite come on no
camera crews out here is there everybody is everybody filming a tv show in this town
i don't know what i just picked up it's the truman show get present get present i'll get it
if people even that person's filming this person playing the piano on the back of a truck
where is this re-roll this is re-roll this is re-roll all right where was there
they had to have been a lot more i'm missing a lot of people in six
for a second here i need to get up still can't make it in here oh yeah i can 90 93 94
look at chat look at chat what do you mean what what what what what what what what what what
what's the matter dropped the present what do you mean i dropped the present
what are you talking about where where did i drop it what where is it holy shit there's a lot of
people here it's in the water water water water water water water hold on all right all right
i'll get it wrecked the annual physical okay where in the water water burger what do you
water burger i didn't drop the present am i getting people just am i getting baited umbrella
wait why did it fall off why did it fall off in the first place royal present okay i have it now
120 this is hanging upside down back back what do you mean back what are you talking about
what why is it on the ground over here this thing what can this thing stay on now please
no it fell off again i'm just not going to do anything in two minutes the present is more
important to me than getting a high score you have one minute left present still on it is uh
bomb with has a few more people please tell me if that present drops again chat can breathe
did it fall no i see it it's still there i'm gonna put my i'm gonna take my hands off the
controller there's tons of people here wrestling ring last attempt straight in
no nothing no need a number on the we must hurry or the maidens will be bored
quickly quickly or go go go is that all there is 65 131 maidens it's not that many and it's
not that few as far as maidens go these are about average too gee what get out there and
risk it more what the hell is going on next time we want a plethora and i got the royal present
the t-shirt do i get to wear the t-shirt too or do i just i don't get it take it easy up quark
thanks for sticking around yeah you got a lot of guys have finals don't you i keep seeing the
finals stop saying finals how do you pronounce plethora plethora end of stream voice what i'm
not ending the stream what are you talking about end of the stream no we'll have a stream for like
four hours don't you know new germa doesn't stream for like three and a half hours anymore
vegas germa streams for like six to seven hours i want boston germa back i i there's
nothing wrong with boston germa but vegas germa streams for longer as it's the only
thing on the menu here i believe so star nine change goal thank you for reminding me i gotta
get the controller i'll be right back it's gonna go get the little thing that you slide
the controls into it'll take me like 30 all right we're back let me just slide these
p i didn't even i didn't p i got that little carrying thing you can hear the satisfying
clicks that's in now if i actually have a place to put my fingers that's that was a
problem holding those little wedges oh just nowhere for all your index fingers to go
that feels better you've been to mongolia we were there yesterday
there's a present down here as well
yeah your hand is index finger index index index thumb you have four index fingers
today you'll be rolling around the world the katamari should be 30 30 meters that is more
than twice what it was supposed to be last time 20 minutes here we go all right 30 20
minutes let's go big bounce i can't pick up those fucking heat lamps i am very small i can't
spend very much time i really have to just kind of pick up as much as i can those sausages
i love the little mini hot dogs when was the last time you guys had a mini hot dog
yesterday i don't quite believe you
down here telephones lots of telephones
i'm gonna make a pass back it's like mowing the lawn guys you don't get the whole lawn
mode in the first go-through
these ones move around i can just stay kind of in this no come on you don't mow the whole
lawn in a single you don't mow the whole one all right we can move on can't get them all
what we needed got it got it early too that first level up is the most important thing
you got to get that early otherwise you can do what i did up to four and just
get stuck in a fucking wall somewhere let's go back to where we were in the beginning here
i see that clip you look i can't see that i can it pops up in the chat room i could see it
every clip you make i see it i actually got somebody telling me this is fucking idiot in
the bear costume fazbear pizza fucking idiot i don't think it was possible to even do what
i just did he's an idiot roast on a bone that sounds pretty good all right freddy back to like
your seventh game i can't pick you up why isn't freddy fazbear in the smash brothers that's what
i want to know i'm gonna do my best attempt to remember what the names of the freddy fazbear
pizzeria people are freddy i mean that's his name it's like that's like not knowing that
mario his name's on the fucking cover uh chicky bun bun rocko foxy and um mecha a mecha bunny
there's like a mecha bunny right and there's the balloon kid and there's the other uh wolf
thing all right i'm just going back and forth over and over again fucking get over
how'd you put watermelons in a boat like this i need to see the map i can't see anything
what about sans um sans is not in five nights at freddy's so here's my prediction you want
to hear what i have to say about five nights at freddy's i will bet any amount of money
talking like 10 bucks five bucks up to even like 15 bucks that five nights at freddy's is
gonna get the slenderman treatment and like five years from now there's gonna be a five
nights at freddy's movie that's gonna get 17% on rotten tomato god she said to get stuck in
every object i still can't pick up the guy and his like 10 sons on his head it's gotta be
exactly 17 or i lose three meters still a baby oh all right how big am i now they already
did it but they threw out the first script yeah it's gonna take him decades to figure out
what to do all i know is it better start with oh hello oh hello if that doesn't it's not that
that's not the first 10 minutes of the movie i'm going to walk out of the fucking city
can't really go that way anymore this dude is still can't be picked up the question is
where the fuck am i supposed to even go right now i need to get back up there
i gotta go back this way somehow back up on the street can i even get over here
i get up there came all the way down and i just don't know how to get up
let's go am i back here um goes
how do i get up there is there is there one way for me to get up there
where the hell is it down this way
i'm not big enough to roll over this yet and what fucking messed up reality are you talking
about here what reality is this problem though how am i gonna fit through that
oh oh oh that's that's thank god i'm not five meters bigger this is where it starts
nothing's seriously wrong with this building trees oh i can't get the trees yet shit
six seven no playground equipment
nice good time to beep all right what about this way is there anything up here kind of
bulls this might have been a bad idea but i could probably get the fence yeah i kept good
fence adds a lot of height i get you bulls okay i got it i can pick up the bulls am i big
enough to take down the whole barn i gotta get down there again let's go right off the edge
momentum and all right well like apparently that didn't want to work ask me why
trees yet why these guys driving around in this parking lot is this like a driving test
all right where from here though over there all the mushrooms all right i'm going that way
wait i don't think i can even get in there i don't think i can roll in there yet
oh it's so awkward to control it's too big
fuck how are you supposed to hit the brakes on that where am i going right now have had
i've ruined everything by trying to dumb jump when nothing is even over there there's nothing
even over there worth picking up there's a handful of solar panels i've just lost weight
doing what i did what is coming what all right trees are now able to be picked up
at least the smaller ones that's good because that's how i'm going to get the height necessary
to keep going i only have six minutes left good still in diapers says you exponential let's go
a single star in the sky i'm supposed to get over there what oh my god i can't even see
i'm not going to be able to do this
hold on slow down what's that what's that over there i don't have time for this i don't have
time to do this no oh we're going this way why do i who cares about that it's just a dumb
little gamer achievement i don't know i don't care about gamer achievements i want to beat the
level it seems like a good place to get some weight it sure is all right there's apparently
a big battle going on what do we need 20 now it's 30 nice okay can i get the cylinders up
here nope not yet i gotta go back all the tractors are here and all these freight containers
i can't pick those up what money i one is kind of giraffe over here here we go trees
can't pick up the whole circus yet here are the mushrooms i wanted this is gonna be
fucking close houses need them come on i need more 24 25 26 switch it come on oh no
get the barn the silo two minutes i should get it unless something really really bad happens
29 um trees up here yeah i got it you get stuck here oh getting stuck
you cannot be serious right now just slow down hit the brakes why can't you climb up this
oh nice katamari you did it go somewhere else i'm fine that lighthouse mine giant fish
got it swordfish take it all get it yeah i stole your spitball too present present on the
island i think no whatever get some boats get all and the giants quick come on i need to get
it all nice come on get up very good like a bunch of shit quick more more more i need more
is your mode with no timer i believe there is all right stop what you're doing we have plans
to get together with your cousin so we'll go back to space if i'm not mistaken i think you
can actually roll up the entire world first goal but it's not very exciting is it we want
a bigger one next time plants how is luggage in third place have to pick up houses the whole
universe man
and the moon is gone can i get a new present no i'm already wearing it why do you need a
telescope for that oh change the spin move right the game controls sound constellations
control type motion controls i want to play with motion control i just controls check
so this is okay this is motion controls both uh no thanks i just want that bottom left one
that's all i want what is simple simple uh oh charge and roll look at that quick turn is
okay hold on this might be better no i like the usual controls i like because essentially
looks like you pretend you have two hands on the ball so your thumbs are your two hands and
you have to do the motion that with your hands is what you'd be like in real life
you want to spin the ball to the left you hold off on the right one you spin with your you
know your left hand you push with your left hand the charging rules the only thing that
sucks on here yeah the jump is the it's not the uh it's the prince you just jump in the
air and look down well i guess we can't really change it so it's all right um make
the moon is what is remaining nice and that's it make the moon
i'm using shit controls what are you talking about uh do you know esperanto maybe we'll
invent a cosmic esperanto oh yes almost forgot oh yes a royal present for the hard-working
prince but we felt bashful about handing it to you so we left it on earth you can roll
it up when you're making the moon movies programs elephants wraps the whole thing
today you'll be rolling around the world the catamari should be let's see around 300 meters
300 you have 25 minutes 300 okay here we go and it's the it's the song and it's the song
oh whoops whoops whoops whoops whoops oh no no no no no i went the wrong way
all right here it comes he's coming oh come on i don't like i have this is a 25 minute
encounter i every every second counts here not i get oh whatever i fell off the earth
and it's gonna be five minutes to get up there don't worry the song will play again
you just killed the momentum it's gonna be fine and here we go
you know i tried to learn how to play this on the drums did i tell you that before
i used to play the drums and i wanted to learn how to play this exact beat here
and i did it all right perfect score here i gotta get the giant squid to end the game
up here i should just i should put the song on my gym playlist is that inspiring
i can't fuck with the momentum of the song they're doing it too and they're better than me
oh yeah
yeah
all the cows
i'm gonna back up the civilization here
that's pretty that's a pretty good start
all right i'm not trying to itch my neck at the same time i just think i just get like a fart
with my neck did anybody hear that what is happening with this why is people copy pasting
i think it's hilarious and you got some shit to me right here i'll go school good level up
still just a baby back it up come on go up why would there be a school on an incline
i was going crazy
i can't be here all right i gotta move on next area
wait you're not quite gonna get these trees yet
from here so far so good back out here
here
the office i can't get them yet i think i have to get this shit in here now
let's hit battle royale this seems like i'm stuck in this one spot
how do i get out of this little quadrant i can't see up there
do
20 minutes to get to 300 not even close but it's all right back this way
i thought the song was over it's not
so many people on the road
can't pick anything up here no i just fell off five minutes that's not true it's 18
i can get these though that thing right there says well i don't think i can go over there
i'm gonna go to the beach or a lot of her
there we go all right back into the town trees
little trees
then once you get able to pick up trees it's pretty much game over
well there's a look at this shit look at all these cars come on walk the cars down
get rid of me barely hear your voice well now you can
hydrate what do you mean hydrate i don't have time to drink water right now almost is he
gonna go for it again why would he do this why would he do it again why would he do that again
why would you do that again i want a fucking five page essay tomorrow why you just did that a
second time all right i gotta get something main town center but i need to be big enough
to get over there i got trees trees trees trees it's time i gotta be 12 i can go up this
way i probably can yeah i can here we go i make it 12 meters get over that let's do it
why is there a floating house freeze i just keep losing all momentum by running into one
thing that i can't pick up i wish i could see higher that way
i love every time i get actually angry at a game i do gonzo flies out of a cannon sound
oh fucking idiot come on why would that stop there and why can't i pick up these trees
somebody shoot me out of a cannon
i wish i could pick those up but i can't all right stop i need to see what i'm going that way
all right i have to pay attention this is an important level
i can't concentrate oh god damn it if this makes me lose it i'm gonna fucking watch
first season of the symptoms houses can i get these yet yes yes all right let's go get out of
my fucking way i'm getting very angry i'm getting marge simpson level of angry like why
can i pick these up i need to get to 300 meters squid is almost attainable yes it is
it's getting close we got 12 minutes back down here all right squid is not attainable yet
it's not for another minute or two down towards this the buildings over here
telling me i can't pick that up am i gonna get marge simpson over here to fucking yell at you
up there you can do it i know you can i've seen you do it before i watched you do it
yes getting stuck i have too many things on me
oh me 40 almost at 60 and i can go that way speaking of that way let's go this way
get it all get it all go get like the wii sports with the mes playing fucking basketball
holy shit i can just got i can get the wind turbines now you can definitely make it
over all right back to the other side oh god 16 meters still just a toddler
not for long though this is going to get out of control here in a minute i gotta go the
other way i can't even physically go this way 300 get missing me back over to the wind turbines
are the biggest things i can get so far a floating circus over there all right giant squid
got him what the hell is that what is that thing i can't even look at it yet
once i get to 100 i can start to pick up actual islands robot person i'm going to keep
going this way i'm just going to try to get as much as i can here i get nine minutes
airplanes i can get the little islands right yep and up there oh forget it even bigger
wow i'm too big to fit through this little area
over 100 meters there's another squid over there hold on i gotta go to that other area down there
this one's got a field goal all right islands netting cage i can't get the big ones quite yet
oh fucking hell yes i can 150 this way giant squid two is too big
can't get them yet holy shit oh my god i i'm so big i don't know what else i can even pick
up from here this whole town right here the whole stadium seven minutes giant mushroom squid back
here i can get the weird like what is this a raptor mogran all right back to the main
town here giant squids are taking over the whole world all right 200 meters still just a
preschooler oh this is getting a little out of control what is down here what is that
is it a monster oni rock oni island that was a living island can i get the giant mushroom
no not yet that's really important i gotta get that i gotta get the monsters over here
quit being stuck on this place i picked up a giant turtle somehow another giant squid and
another town giant octopus uh come on i can't i'm passing through the rainbow oh that's the
that's the plane that's the rocket i just picked up the rocket ship 275 who the hell am i
hello picking up islands windmill still not big enough to get that tower here wow look at that
that's probably i think that's the biggest building in the game oh i'm picking up what
a nice katamari so pleasant and dreamy i did it and i'm about to start picking up a whole
entire like sections of a board game the bridge is what's gonna stop me here
shit i got it i got the runway i can't pick that i give you the stadium stadium quick
got it i'm picking up clouds mushroom i can't get the mushroom yet what how is that possible
got the tower that destroyed pretty much the whole world except for right here
got it the only thing that's left are i gotta get the rainbow oh look at that a whole civilization
over here gone the volcano fuck can i get the rainbow yep give me this airport
i have to get this volcano there's nothing left i've destroyed the whole universe clouds
tornadoes there's an island over here i didn't get pigeon town there are things on the screen
well yeah but i'm talking about major things i mean you can get all the mushrooms i'm talking
about landmarks all the cities are all gone there's one sad there's a giant cruise ship
right here all right i got the cruise ship go get the hurricane hurricane where is it here i
just got married get the mushrooms get the mushrooms mushroom xx xl i'm picking up like
the whole antarctic right now this is fucking crazy mushroom mushroom i'm at 800 meters why
what what what's the angels flying around before got them all no i didn't all right got all the
mushrooms everything else is just icing on the cake now scallop island 823 there's nothing left
i've eaten the whole world i picked up a cake
it's floating but it's not a dream 824 meters how supple this silhouette this substantial heft
this mellifluous mood and the rising tide of familial love we are moved when it gets this
big it's hard to tell what you have the most of plants still plants is not vulnerable
and somehow i still did not get the present is that what i'm understanding here the moon is
returned let's see the conclusion of the story the moon is back in the sky welcome back this
time we the king worked hard we think we worked hard we're pretty sure we did
oh it's you yes what what is it oh i got it maybe the prince grew a teeny bit
ha ha you did yes you did at least a full one centimeter taller this is also thanks to us yes
that makes me five eight we are the champion yes so all we need to do is put the rest of the
stars back get cracking on prince of ouija king of osama queen of oh he's doing the sour
thank you total ob just collected 11 71 824 meters wait we're missing somebody
what who are we missing there did i not get somebody oh it's me okay here we go
you thought it was over not quite
every country on earth
is this is the real challenge now and you can't spin i have to go slow
one piece of time
quite yet not yet can we get anywhere in i don't think we can no we can't get uh america
america is safe for now
can't pick up that canada's not going to fall oh yes it will all right i need to go
okay pretty much all of africa
i want to miss any countries
whoever's left has to redo the whole earth
okay no i'm not big enough for this one come on give me australia no it's actually easier
to go this way so i can actually see the country forever all right all right canada
uh canada gone canada gone u.s gone china gone still here australia has to go down
there it goes and there goes it was anartica what country's left right here come on get it
got it there goes russia few more here what is this cg what's left
no this what country's left produced by namco no i gotta get every single one man
barbedos i see a couple right here
hey the sky isn't finished yet well that is the base uh game you might say it looks a little
short the main little story little little cute story there oh that's because this is a
playstation 2 game but it's not over it's not over because you can do this as many times as
you want there's a lot to do and get high scores and this is just the first one so i do have
to try i have to do this is there identical levels oh yeah but i mean you can redo them
and that eternal mode is i think you can just do it as long as you want
um it's a fun game there are a ton of sequels and the sequels are much larger and way more
going on especially in some of the later ones
how many catamari games are there i missed one new one
all right let me try to get a decent beer there are like five new ones what what did i
miss five new levels a couple games too because i would really love i mean i know they did this
and this is this is cool but they went back i just fucking uh whatever a bear carving of a
bear it doesn't even look like a bear on the ground whatever that's the smallest one i've
picked up so far that is tiny that is the smallest one that's i'm not gonna go
i buy food and eat it the same day all right let me see what you're talking about
because i don't think there isn't is this up here the new levels are oh oh what would you look at
that would you look at that there's a there is a new level i told you the game wasn't over
make the north star for some reason for some reason i don't feel comfortable at all
is it because our royal present is missing no that's not oh well that's it we get there's
no center there is no belly button there is nothing solid in the center of the sky
that's why it's unstable off kilter undignified and preposterous but we remember now it's the
north star this level sucks who knows why but make it exactly 10 meters the closer it is to
10 meters the brighter a north star will be but there's a catch or maybe two how big the
katamari is to start with nobody knows but we will show you what 10 meters looks like
ready 10 meters very very simple what when you think your katamari is 10 meters summon us with
the y button much is expected of you prince of wait what oh shit okay i have to guess
when it's 10 meters i still have no idea well how wait wait wait how big am i now i'm big
enough to pick up people so i'm definitely at least two meters right that circle up there
in the top left is how big i need to look okay how tall a car is three meters three feet so
three six nine twelve fifteen twenty thirty feet like once i get to what seven eight meters
every tree close already too much shit once i'm as big as a tree
hold on too fast come on wait am i i'm pretty big i'm probably five or probably six meters
right now easy easy easy slow down don't go so fast you're like two meters sure i gotta stay
next to a tree all right and right now i'm like as big as a tree right now i'm gonna go
way way too small go away and start over 10 meters 30 feet so i don't really have a
kilometer to how tall these things are double the size i'm pretty big right now oh shit okay
i'm definitely 10 meters now how tall is the normal telephone pole because a house that's
30 feet yeah i know how tall is your house whose house is that that house is like eight
feet tall i'll kind of turn off the rails here i'm picking up the trees is this size
contemporary okay yes we're not certain we are not at all sure that's almost eight meters
rushed it 7.7 that's almost eight that's eight meters oh that's close compact north star
at least we did it seven meters equals trees that reference image was shitty
yeah but we probably shouldn't have been going by that image then huh that's c plus yeah you're
right it is we are exhausted the sky is done the sky is complete we are tired
rolling the category is very hard right prince wasn't it hard wasn't it well it was hard for
us as well to wash it from the cosmos was very hard so so boring half asleep we were
ah we can finally go home finally sleep in bed today would be a party day especially since
the prince is finally two centimeters we must celebrate mother we need cake yeah we talked
about how that you get that was chat before we get them another party sequence where i roll
pick up again party sequence two we beat the game beat the game no no this is not credits
this is an actual party it's the dinosaur you tell me that that guy wouldn't be a perfect fit
for smash brothers dlc yes i see told you here we go again why is it giving me a credit
sequence again i did one extra level uh now they're all there everybody's there now okay
i've completed it for real skip this please i have to get every country somebody look it up
right now how many countries are on earth uh 324 or something right 380 it's like 340
five or something i think it's more than that 365 yeah this 365 countries in a year
okay 195 okay we're already almost there i'll get it this time 21 40
okay now i get the big ones 155 157 167 172 what did you say that was 195 175
all right i gotta i gotta come down on it so i can see 179 come on right here
there's at least like four or five right here 183 185 come on no 188 191 192 we're the last
three last three countries in the world one two two last country where's the final country
where's the final country oh no does anybody see it i see it i see it i see it i see it
no i didn't see it there's only 194 countries on earth guys that's it there's 194 countries
there actually are 210 i think that is it for this game i don't think there's any
secret levels we just did one secret level okay uh so all right so what's the ending
oh fuck no we already did this is it okay that's the arrows the ending end of the stream boys
yeah i think that's a i think this is a good place to call it tonight six hours
that's a that's a good so that's i think that's a perfect length i thought this was
cool vegas drama what do you mean wait to the moon memorial opening movie chapters
staff credits now this is just oh let's see what's all right can you just pick from here too
oh it's just these cool drama would go eight hours well we're doing the bits so we'll
probably go for i don't know only six and a half hours tonight and then tomorrow i didn't know
how long this is going to take us so tomorrow is going to be something different and then
we're building a bird house on either thursday or friday probably friday oh yeah edf right is
edf come out tomorrow oh that i know what we're doing tomorrow earth defense force five edf five
comes up tomorrow so you promised to peek your mic no but i immediately said i'm not doing it
i immediately corrected myself uh so tomorrow if all internet goes to plan and the servers work
and everything right uh i think i think me star and italics are gonna try to play it
at least that's the i mean i gotta ask those people you know what i mean i'm pretty sure
that's the plan check out the sound library why not all right these are all the songs
here is the ost very good yeah so edf tomorrow and then the bird house building stream
uh day or two after that lonely rolling star okay all right i'll just have this in the background
instead of my usual song thank you everybody for coming see you tomorrow probably around
3 p.m pacific something like that between like two and four because anytime you play
with other people you do have to essentially go with uh you know you got to change
schedules and stuff around everybody piano play at the same time so
so let's do the bits go back a few hours ago here six hours ago now uh thank you to
thank you to snuggly for the one dollar please do a goofy impression like a goofy impression
or an impression of the character goofy from disney like the goof a goofy or like oh i'm
like wow look at me whoa look at me yeah i just did it thank you uh snuggly for the one dollar
snuggly again thanks for the two dollars it's an imgur link oh dear uh the the tag on this
thing the message says i will make more i will make more is that is that is that like a
supposed is that like a threat i'm gonna make more of these you better believe it here they
come you understand dab yep look at how fucking jacked i look thank you snuggly uh snuggly again
there's another imgur link and i think they did it again no it's it's it's like a garfield
post it's me in a garfield costume i get it's all right well you did make more that's true
thank you for your three four four five dollars here thank you snuggly sticks renegade
thanks for the one dollar this intro song is more painful than the abscess i had what
everybody loves katamari the katamari theme song is the opening intro is one of the most iconic
well-liked video game song in history what are you talking about it was the song that
wouldn't beat boop beat boop thank you those sticks thank you divas p divas thanks for three
bucks every single stream you've given three dollars every time thank you no messages you
never write a message but i do appreciate it uh snuggly again has another uh imgur link uh
what the hell is this what does this have to do with anything it's shaggy that shaggy just
beat up superman seems you've forgotten what the s stands for in your suit do you need me
to remind you no please it stands for shaggy don't hurt me i'll do anything don't unleash
your wrath what what does this have to do with anything i don't i don't understand what this
means what the fuck is that i don't understand i'm too old uh thank you just langford for the
dollar 85 derma you're a bit inspiration to me since i watched man versus machine wave 666
back in like 2012 i don't remember it's been so long thanks for making life fun thank you for
hanging up and i miss man versus machine i really wish that they would do it more of it i wish
somebody would just make a man versus machine video game with just a ton of items and and
make it difficult and not just have it all ready to go and not monetized like crazy
i just want a 60 dollar man versus machine game isn't that edf it kind of is now i'm starting to
understand why i like edf so much that's what base fortnight is no but base no i don't want
to build any bases it's i don't want to build a fucking minecraft house and then shoot plants
versus zombies enemies it is a game mode that i think is a lot of fun but thank you uh
just langford thank you also to son of janova for the one dollar you said september and then
your laugh sounded like september from earth wind and fire huh what do you mean september
of this year i'm sorry i just fucking smashed your head all right what is this i said september
september of this year what you've got to be kidding me september of this year do you
remember how did you pick up on that that's fucking crazy timber of this year
the 21st night of september well yeah that's that's kind of insane but thank you for that
son of janova i don't i can't even how do i even respond to that
thank you though thank you dark star 700,000 games for the one dollar this first semester
away from home has been a wild one for me with the hurricane destroying my dorm and all
but through all of it i've had your wonderful streams to help me unwind i sincerely mean this
i love you keep it rolling prince of all comedy i am honored to even be mentioned as a prince
of comedy thank you so much dark star it's great to have you around thank you for
being part of this community for as long as you have prince of comedy master of comedy
that's not me though that's a different person but thank you so much dark star
take care of yourself all the best garfield the monday killer thanks for the one dollar alert
alert incoming garphagraph race for impact hey jerma i had a dream that batman went nuts
and was played by jim carrey don't know why i felt the need to mention that but i can't
watch the whole stream jerm macaroni i'm busy studying for my world history final wish me
luck i gotta learn about what the capital of the byzantine empire is anyway i always liked
the feel of katamari he'd be such a cute smash character oh yeah are you looking forward to
avengers 4 yeah i mean everybody's looking forward to avengers 4 it's it's gonna just be the it's
gonna be the next movie in the marvel series and it's a big movie who's not excited to see
that movie it's something you're not excited to see that no okay i mean if you're not
then you know that's all right i think it's gonna be a pretty fun movie but yeah thank
you garfield has name thanks for the one dollar my roommate is questioning why he's hearing a grown
man moan from my room thanks jerma what did you tell him that i was playing katamari tamasi
rerolled and trying to go over uh trying to get the ball to go up with physics is hard and it's
like makes you have to grunt a little why yeah what i people tell me hey man like you you
like screamed and you like screamed something crazy and woke up my dog you just got me like
full blast in your living room you got me how many bars do you have you know like the tv
volume bars you don't have me like 80 of the way up do you who doesn't do that xbox record
that but uh sorry about that has name and maybe drop the volume like two notches maybe i do
actually i'm in my living room well all right hey anyway anyway you can watch the stream that's
fine by me right hey flying trolley thanks for the one dollar have you considered the
possibility of stealing star's mic and peeking it that way you won't have to damage your microphone
also that song well it would be very hard for me to steal uh star's microphone because
we live in different states so that would be very difficult to do that it would take a
long time for me to to pull that off steal it steal his mic i how do you want me to do
that just get a plane ticket no anyways thank you flying trolley thank you extra cheesy for
the one dollar man picking up all those erasers sure was inherently satisfying wouldn't you say
i would it was great picking up the rubber the ice creams it's a very satisfying experience
uh moist in tidy whiteys what five dollars thank you thank you thank you for the five
dollars thank you smelly boy for the one dollar thank you i have a final exam tomorrow morning
that i may do very poorly on thank goodness instead of studying i'm watching this fantastic
stream thanks jeremy um just do as good as you can get a good night's sleep make sure you have
breakfast in the morning and remember it's not about getting an a on the final it's about
passing the class it's about getting a good enough grade where you get the diploma where
you pass you know you don't got to get an a plus on everything don't feel that kind of
pressure i would say you should you should strive to get my twitch social blade grade
which is a b minus if you're able to reach and get to my level of b minus on twitch my social
blade then you don't have to go any higher than why would you have to go higher than that
humble brag no but that gives me it that's a b minus means you did it and you're good enough
but you're not getting like an a plus you know nobody you don't have to get an a plus
and if you do great i'm glad you did you're a b plus when did i become a b plus
holy shit b plus now guys oh boy so you really should be looking for a b plus is what you
should be getting anything under that and it's like i don't know maybe don't do that
you don't need an a minus b plus that's that means you tried enough and you did a good
enough job and you did that really that's a pretty that's a great job actually b means great
b plus is great below b plus b and b minus stay away from that i was a b minus like yesterday
i literally looked at that like two days ago b plus umar streamer boomer streamer no do
your best for real if your best is a b then that's your best and that's fucking fine you
don't have to get an a plus if a plus is your best then congratulations you're a smart
smart person and you're really good at what you do you need to get a c c minus i was like a c and
a b student in college it's don't worry about it i have like a 2.7 or 2.8 gpa in college
and look at me now i ate a half of a sandwich out of the trash three days ago
and i still have trouble tying my shoes and wiping my ass so i mean look at what look at
where i've come you what giving terrible advice i'm forgive i'm just i'm just fucking
around hope you guys understand that but good luck on your finals those of you that have them
hope you do well hey extra cheesy thanks to the one dollar local streamer is creates
now that's not very nice that's not a very nice thing to say i've already bombed my finals
and ate trash sandwiches are you going to do any more green screen nights
why don't why don't you just work at the trash yard like your dad well because because
i'm not my dad okay i'm gonna do i'm my own person we're all our own person work at the trash
you and your dad's have switched jobs for a day
that'd be pretty hard to do thank you though thank you and doxen for the one dollar and 50
cents that flash game stream is one of the funniest i've laughed in a long time i had to
tune out near the end of the balloons game but i hope everyone had a great time ps i'm really
surprised the chat never tried to make a dick hey love you that will you left prematurely
because they they did multiple times and they did and they put something bad in the the germ
germa mouth over here and i'm not gonna have that happen yeah that was awful and i'm not
gonna have that happen again you lost privileges forever you lost your privileges forever it'll
come back in like a week one more for the road oh yeah i forgot about that but thank you
to a and doxen thank you marvish mcgally for the one dollar hey germ boy i just made the math
oh that what you said you talked about 150 hours of old streams were
to catch up with they said can you stop streaming for 150 days it's a reasonable
request i'm giving you a dollar to do it thanks in advance well we're streaming tomorrow
and then we're streaming a day or two after that and then making a birdhouse
but thank you marvish mcgally snuggly again for one dollar hey germa please audition to play
a plastic man in the upcoming plastic man movie what i what is that a superhero
i don't understand i don't know i really don't know half of these references
i must look like such a fucking idiot when i say oh yeah plastic man and do a dog head tilt
and then the people are just laughing like
he said he's doing it and then i'm like holding my hands up to i would
thank you for the dollar and the reference that i don't understand tk reapers thanks for
the five bucks five dollars you've ever tried stand up germa and if so tell us how hard you
bombed i've never done stand up i already told you guys about the idea of me going
to an open mic night and streaming it getting permission to stream it and just seeing what
happened i'm gonna try to come up with a bunch of material and see what happens when i try to
entertain a real actual crowd of comedy goers and see how badly i get booed or who knows
that would be very stressful to watch what if i just did what if i went in there unprepared
and just tried to make stuff up on the spot now that would be really really hard to watch
the chat will laugh all the crowd booze we aren't real enough to you no no i mean like comedy goers
like people in the audience at the comedy club no that's not what i meant that's not what i
meant you guys know what i meant we're not comedy goers no you're not we're not all
sitting in a like we kind of are no but we're not at a comedy club and i'm not on stage
with a mic yes i am there's a mic right here i'm in a digital stage fuck i guess i'm
wrong i guess that was incorrect just stream comedy night no because comedy night is
when that came out i was like oh that might be interesting to do and then i saw a couple of
videos of people just like getting in close to their mics like you get like a one minute
turn and then you have to watch like eight fucking dickheads come up and be like
and then it's like all right it was what's happening with the next guy
then you get your turn again in like a minute and then you try to come up with a
funny joke and then you get booed he did not peek he did peek the mic did i know i didn't i
turned it down so no no comedy night maybe at real comedy club comedy night if i ever want
to publicly embarrass myself for like an hour and no it wouldn't even be an hour that's why
how would i stream that that would be like a 12 minute stream you only get like six or seven
minutes when you go on stage for an open mic night you don't get like an hour it's not like
presenting germa 985 and it's like oh yeah there he is and i come out and get an hour and a half on
the stage no i get like three minutes i'm gonna go up there and tell like three awful jokes and
no one's gonna think it's funny and then i'm gonna turn the stream off just put on disguises
and go more than once and then i'll get thrown out of this comedy club and that would be
that would be even more embarrassing because then i can never go back there it'll be funny
all right well sure i'll go get banned from a comedy club on stream that sounds like a great
time to me i'll get like thrown out and then we can sit on the sidewalk and chat for like
10 minutes before i get in my uber anywho uh we've got some more bits to go through
thank you too oh that was tk reaper by the way that with that the stand-up question thank
you for five dollars uh drosophilia thanks for the one dollar king of the cosmos for germania
2019 one stream one like six hour stream is that enough to be on uh is that enough to be on
the rumble i'm not so sure it'd be hard to make maybe quiet man made it in the quiet man
was i mean that was like a four hour stream but that felt like 40 hours of streams so it
was it's like how i it's like how i feel right that could have been like a 36 hour stream
maybe he's a great character i think he's hilarious i think he's fun and interesting
captain worgen thanks for the one dollar why do you call your gamer room an office
because it's not it's not a gamer room my gamer room no i have because i don't do i
do other things in here besides play games i sit in this chair and i open up other things
that are not video games here like like for instance like for instance like editing and
discord and you're that is i you are taking this in the wrong direction
like communicating and setting up the streams and cleaning you don't edit anymore yes i do
yes i do he doesn't edit wait oh whoa where do you think where do you think the balloon
video came from so it's your gamer room it was live it was live where do you think that
feed came from who plugged in the feed into the computer in the middle of the desert i didn't
somebody else did i hired somebody to set up a which followed me landing in las vegas it was
like 65 it was 6700 dollars to get that person to follow that balloon as it came into nevada
and then they had to plug in like a bunch of microphones and a bunch of streaming equipment
and they had to get one of those super 5g bricks that person's still paying like 400
dollars a month for that i demanded that they get that so they you could see it
because you've got like four three g in the middle of the desert are you serious
why does everything cost 6700 just does thank you too okay the captain worgen says it's not
it's a gamer room it's not it's not an office i do office work in here i did i went over taxes
in here do you go over taxes in your gamer room tap my taxes you don't do taxes in your
gamer room i sing in here sometimes when i gotta make sure i make sure nobody's in the house
and i sing did you sing in your gamer room do you open up frody loops and get a track ready
and sing i love how somebody just wrote stfu like shut the fuck up anyways why would i ban
why would i ban them uh thank you jess for the one dollar what do you think of that what
do you think of that super volcano under yellowstone that could erupt any day now
i don't know what you mean but you just i'm scared now this is a super volcano
is that for that happening holy shit red shell just gave 20 community subs
it's true uh red shell thank you for your 20 subs thank you so much that's a huge amount
of money huge amount of subs in one second almost at 200 000 followers how close are we
how close are we to 250 199 383 the yellowstone thing is a meme thank goodness well i don't know
guys memes have done lots and lots of damage before just look at the gnome video and the
irreparable damage that that video has caused this is all those tim allen's meme volcano
erupts i don't even know i don't even want to know what's inside of that volcano i hope that
that never happens but congrats all the people that just got subs and thank you for the extreme
generosity of red shell thank you sweetie swanky thanks for the one dollar were you one of those
substitute teachers who would not give everyone homework and just played movies for them that's
what mine did and got to see some amazing rated r films i didn't go grow up quite normally
after that why would it why would you substitute teacher be showing you r rated movies
that's like a call the superintendent scenario cool teacher no you get you pick up the phone
you dial your superintendent like hello this is superintendent hey what's going on i just
uh first of all uh i mean i'm a local resident and the first thing i have to say is man wish
you would cancel uh school when we get all that snow and for some reason when we have like
four or five six inches of snow on the ground and you don't want to close the schools
and i have to sit there and watch the local news as every fucking school in the entire district
goes by alphabetically and see there's that one there's that one and mine gets skipped
and it's not up there and i have to go to fucking school second of all uh actually
i forget why i called you why did i call the superintendent oh right a guy is showing
r rated movies in this class that's just not okay cancel more fucking classes because
it's snowing you fucking bye fucking dick what happened to the music is it still playing the
same song is it playing any song it's just been playing lonely star on repeat oh goodness
now how about uh how about this one this one no this one no how about this one yeah this is
a good one this is perfect anyway so thank you to uh swiggity swanky for the one dollar
thank you hands beats for the free bucks what do you think about all this article 13 stuff
that law passes no one in the eu will be able to watch the stream anymore uh it's that's fucking
stupid i don't know why everyone's so why is everybody so afraid of the internet you know
what i mean that's what's been around for so long at this point like are we why are people
so scared of the internet it's like what what's the problem here it's because they saw the
spay video now i don't know the the complete and total ins and outs of article 13 but there's
been shit like that before and this the stuff is already like happening where it's like no no no
nobody can have the internet right hold on a second somebody hold on a second somebody
hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait you were in you were inside of a mall
and the mall was playing a song over the radio and in that song somebody said there was a
sample or there was a there was a fucking sample from a tv show everybody in the mall is under
arrest well how do i don't understand how are they gonna do that hold on there's an internet
person on here that just played a song that they don't have the rights to you're all going to
jail like you know when you're walking around in walmart and they're just playing fucking
music they're playing like ads and shit you know they think they think walmart has the
rights to play fucking whatever local radio station is blasting songs through the the pa
they do they do they actually do i hear like radio stations so mr walmart gets the rights
to like 10 000 radio stations i mean i i understand people and you know companies wanting
to be paid for services and stuff and but i don't i don't think blocking and banning is
the the right way to do it because how are you supposed to share things with people you know
what i mean like how like you see hey hey dude come here i found this really cool song that
i want you to listen to take a listen oh hey but uh you gotta pay me first though
but how you supposed to like share stuff you know what i mean like if you think about it it's
very core it's people used to sit around and listen to like a record player right
and now we've gotten so connected that the new record player where everyone's hanging out
in the room listening to like 30 people all at a party listening to a record you know you people
are streaming or listening to the radio or playing music or it's a new world it's a different you
know it's hard to i understand the difficulty in trying to figure out how to go about
policing it and figuring it out but it's almost impossible where's my money but there's
i think there's a difference between you know obviously like this dmca takedowns and stuff
but outright banning websites is just don't we already have systems in place that do this
shit already don't we already have systems that will take things down or monetize for
whoever the creator is or do we have to ban entire websites boomers like germa ruin everything
germa no i don't want to get political here or go any further than that but i think there's i
think there's a different way you can go about doing that and outright it was it's the same ship
with like the net neutrality stuff is well uh if you have verizon uh you can't go to netflix
anymore if you have comcast or you can go to netflix it's just why why does that even have
to be a thing why could why would that even be a possibility because money i guess i just
feel like there's a better way oh because of big bits germa isn't even a good boomer he's a left
for dead 2 boomer a good boomer a left for dead boomer what are you talking about fat
but talking about stuff like this is a whole can it's a can of worms that when it's opened
is just there's so much to even discuss there's too much to discuss and i mean we
could sit here all night and talk about this kind of shit but i hope that uh sensible hope
there are sensible things that are done and that people don't just jump right to conclusions
immediately it's just like almost like hey we gotta get to it right now we're gonna do
it right now we have to change the internet now tonight tomorrow hurry hurry do it do it
do it we're gonna just go come on it's like this is one of the most important mediums
in history i think it needs to be treated with a little more let's talk let's figure this shit
out you know what i mean like the the probably most important thing that's happened in the last
30 years 40 at least 50 years in regards to technology right the internet especially where
it is now technologically is just i mean you're talking about like the invention of the
fucking wheel back in the caveman times as an important politician i'd like to know what
this internet thing is this is nice background music for political discussion
i wasn't even listening to it
yeah this is like didn't fit oh well
the fact that we are watching this stream right now would blow people's minds back in the 90s
oh that's what i mean it's such an insane stepping stone for humanity that it needs to be done
in i think a lot slower a lot different and a lot more people need to be part of the equation
you know it can't just be like three guys that are like i think this is what it should be
no you gotta get every more people gotta be fucking involved with that shit but regardless
of any of this you need to have at least four guys in that room we're gonna we're
gonna implant memes into our dna but we'll see what happens by all i can say is what i've just
previously said and again i'm i'm coming from a place of somewhat ignorance because i don't
really know that much about how it is in the eu i mean because i don't live there
so i don't know how your day-to-day goes with stuff like that i know there's a lot
of different rules in different countries so i get all i can say is i hope that it's not
i hope that it doesn't do what it's what it says that people are afraid is going to happen you
know what i mean because that's a whole can of worms you don't live in the eu
it would be really weird if i did i'd be streaming at some weird fucking time
oh can't it's a real can of worms but anyhow thank you to thank you to hans beats
hans beats for the three dollars and getting us on that topic is obviously a very important
topic to talk about so i'm happy to share uh share some of the opinions that i have so thank
you dr clay thanks for the one dollar virtual tour of disneyland stream when
yeah probably like probably now soon something like that somewhat soon thank you though thank
you swiggity swanky again for the one dollar what is the scariest film or show you've ever
seen mine is current tv news uh it was the scariest film or show i've ever seen
i'm gonna sneeze and i'm gonna mute them am i gonna make it i just cut it off i just stopped
sneezing i just forced my yeah i'm good scariest film or show you've ever seen
movies don't really scare me because a lot of scary movies at least that are made in the
last 10 years are guy with like a mask on or something and flashing lights and and they're
in the script right in front of the screen and it doesn't like scare me it's just like oh
okay that was like annoying all right i wouldn't even classify it as a jump scare because you
are it's you know what's gonna happen so far away so i don't know a truly scary um actually
i will tell you the the first uh hereditary was actually really fucked up that movie was
just unsettling so i don't know but like it didn't scare me but it was unsettling
so i mean maybe that i put that in that category of scary that means scared unsettled
disturbing yeah if you've never seen hereditary it's it's quite a strange wild ride have i seen the
sonic movie poster yes i have i don't know they're going but i don't know what they're
even gonna do with that i have no opinion because i don't know what it is they showed
a poster uh timmy tim tan thanks for the three bucks my dog had to be put down today
use your twitch money to take auto for a checkup thanks for cheering me up slightly
today i'm really sorry to hear that timmy tim tam i'm terribly sorry to hear about your dog
that's an it's a difficult thing to do it's not easy and it won't be for a while i just
hope that your dog had a great life that you loved him every day because that is losing that
is losing a that's losing a close friend our animals our dogs cats whatever they are
they're they're like your best friends auto is like my like one of my best friends
it just is but and it's it's devastating and incredibly difficult i wish you all the best
and again i'm sorry to hear about your dog but thank you for the three dollars
i really appreciate it thank you to blue comet for the six dollars no message just six dollars
thank you banjo boy thanks for the one dollar hey germa it's my birthday today and i couldn't
be happier that my name is the actual name in the rat's birthday song which is michael it's
also great sharing birthdays with uh emily dickinson and raven simone anyway just wanted
to say that i've loved you since loved you and your content for like six years now and i've been
waiting for years for you to stream on my actual birthday so having you read this on
today is a dream come true thanks for everything well happy birthday mike if you're still here
if you're still watching uh that was banjo boy 88 happy birthday mike hope it was a good one
take care of yourself much love to you here here flying trolley thanks for the one dollar that is
so offensive and they they spelled it off dash fence dash i've i think i ran over a fence
thank you kumo for the one dollar germa be honest how many followers are just your mother
making new accounts um zero i don't my mother does not follow this channel so uh zero so
my mother doesn't like know how to do that she's watched streams before but she does my mother
doesn't have like a twitch account guilty uh thanks mom thank you uh zeno or zeno for the
five dollars germa does star have any pets asking for a friend hope you have a good stream
uh i believe i believe i believe they have a dog i believe so yes they do i think he i think
he's talked about this dog like a dozen times hasn't he yeah let's get a dog mystery solved
they i will talk about star and ashley why are you asking me
i don't i don't know hey hey does your friend have a dog uh yeah all right nice
that's just all i wanted to know but thank you for the five dollars zeno thank you one
eyed thank you one eyed ninja for the one dollar i just got out of the hospital two weeks ago
uh i'm sorry to hear that just got out of the hospital hopefully for nothing serious
hopefully you're doing well um stay healthy hopefully you're doing well thank you for the
one dollar that's a good thing no i'm so i'm like i'm sorry that he was in the hospital
to begin with that's great that you're out of the hospital it's amazing thank you weighted
gucci for the five dollars no message thank you smelly boy again thanks for a dollar watch rat movie
to commemorate one million it's worth it okay i will watch rat movie one on stream when it
hits a million views but it's not in a million views yet so not tonight up quark thank you
for the ten dollars up quark getting off of the night it was a good way to clear my head
for the finals uh we touched upon the finals before like i said i think i actually caught
you right when you left but good luck on your finals also the present catastrophe was
great i didn't even know it was possible i thought it was you collected it just saves the fact that
you collected it i need a uh there but thank you up quark for the ten bucks have a good one good
luck on the finals it's russ thanks for the one dollar you are a mini hot dog kaira toby
thanks for the one dollar hey germa what movies are you looking forward to recently
uh the new avengers movie and i would have said venom like a couple months ago but i
did see venom and i loved that movie i loved that movie i thought it was great i thought it was
one of the best movies i've seen in like the last couple years 17 on rotten tomatoes
no all right let me tell you let me tell you the truth here though that movie was
really really it was really like stupid but i think people were a little too hard on it i
thought i think they marketed that movie completely incorrectly i don't think that
movie should have been marketed as oh it's venom spider-man and it's a venom movie no
you market that movie as like a shitty buddy cop that why would you market that as anything
else yeah i i mean it was it a good movie in quotes no that wasn't a good movie but i had a
good i had a good time watching it i think a lot of people were expecting something and yes
yes i know the movie was supposed to be rated r and then they pulled it to pg-13 and there
was a lot of scenes that they cut and yeah that's i mean come on are you gonna whatever
they're trying to appeal to as broad of an audience as they can what wait what's going on
no stop what what's going on here sony shill what i just told you that the movie was bad
i just told you it was not a good movie but that the bad movies that are not good
does not disqualify them from being entertaining you know what i'm saying that you don't a movie
doesn't have to be good to be worth watching i love watching bad movies yeah i mean like you
just if if you like venom you liked venom if you didn't like venom then you didn't because
i mean obviously we can all probably agree the movie wasn't very good so you're correct but
the guy that liked venom is is not wrong no neither oh no don't spill another thing i
that's why i had the lid on that's why this fucking lid was on that's why i was drinking
out of it out of the top like a child fuck venom the movie was stupid but i liked it i
thought it was funny all right hold on all right it wasn't that bad i'm fine it was just like
a lot it was a little bit that's why i had the top on in this fucking thing there wasn't
that much left in it so it went in a very easy blood splat pattern for me to clean up but
it was still aggravating all right what the hell were we just talking about dude dude drinks
blood no i don't yes no i didn't mean to say yes i don't drink blood
that's like my body and brain were fighting my brain was so desperately saying yes and my
body was like shut the fuck up dude uh all right let's keep going anyways thank you
kairatobi thank you to chug chuggy for the ten dollars thank you chug uh i forgot to leave a
message when i sent you bits earlier so here's some more thanks for making me laugh since the
tf2 days love you jeremy thank you thank you for the ten dollars thanks for being here that
long you guys are fucking awesome thank you sticks renegade thanks for the one dollar this
song right here reminds me of the grubble gum katamari song from the show chowder oh that was
two hours ago so we need to talk about this song but thank you sticks for the one dollar
thank you up quark again two more dollars i guess i should get the most bits you are in
that top spot as of monday today new week thank you for the immense contributions thank you
kenderman thanks for the one dollar dear fast food franchise i hope this letter reaches you
the burger i ordered got cold after i got home replace it for me um like i will dial them
immediately uh thank you thank you honey chain for the three dollars i wanted to make a donation
to the spies are we but the website redirected me to your twitch channel so i guess i'll just
give the money to you thank you for the three dollars i appreciate it three bucks from
honey chain thank you to elizabeth for the one dollar i feel the cosmos we all do uh up
quark again thanks for three more dollars and he's just linked to the rat movie so this is the best
movie ever everyone should watch it he's currently at 999 838 views are you serious
thank you up quark thank you fh gregory for the one dollar hey there jerry jerry actric you
mentioned having substitute teach before and as someone who might get into teaching do you have
anything that resembling advice for me planning to start with something before i earn my degree
and i'll probably be at a high school or a middle school thanks to keep up the hard
work it pays off more than you could imagine um i really don't have i really don't have that
much advice because i wasn't i wasn't going into teaching i don't have a teaching degree
i wasn't getting my degree in education i was doing it because it was um it was easy
because it was being a sub is you just it's not it's it's easy but it does give you good
experience but i mean easy in the sense that you do still have to you still have to have
control of the room you know you can't just be like okay kids welcome to class
i don't care what you do go for it you play fortnight on your fucking ipad for all i care
no you have to at least have order but i can't i'm not advice for teaching i don't know if i'm
in a position to give that to you just because i don't really have very much because i don't
have that much experience but like i said just make sure you still control the room
you are the teacher it you are the authority in there no and it if somebody like throws an m&m
at you confiscate it don't take that shit pick up you pick up that office phone pick
up the fucking phone that every phone for some reason and that's connected to the office
or just you know pretend somebody does something like bad like hey shut up stupid idiot teacher
everyone laughs and you go okay and you walk over and you hold the fucking receiver down
you pick the phone up yeah i've got a i've got a uh i've got a student here that's starting
to act up a little bit here do you have any room down there in the office and they're
like oh shit he's picking up the you just picked up the phone and then you let me put
it back and you let go and yeah that's right everybody sit down but then be careful because
if you accidentally lift your finger up you do call the office and then you the phone you'll
get a phone call some they'll call you back and be like what happened oh i was uh i was trying
to do a thing where i made the students be careful only use that tactic when completely
necessary you were one of those subs no i was very very professional i'm just fucking around
be professional take care of your students and have order in the room best advice i can give
but thank you fh gregory best of luck to you uh dinky dinky duper thanks for the one dollar
hey germa i saw you at uh walmart yesterday i was too afraid to come up to you and say hi
since you seem so distracted by the ongoing xbox deals since you're something of a microsoft
gamer on it yourself uh on a more serious note though i hope you have a great night what
the echo is distracted by the xbox deals how would you get distracted by a sign that tells
you how much percent off the xbox is you go oh like 10 off okay what do you have to examine
sign thank you dinky duper thank you um mizu thank you mizu for the 10 dollars
thanks for all the streams and jukes well thank you for the juice you guys that make them all
right i don't i i've never had a full jupiter in my own chat ever i've never done it i can't
do it you guys are the guys making you guys are the guys you guys are the ones doing the
jupiter's one thank you thank you sage did you buy the Pikachu socks and the whale lord
plushie you'll find out in like a week arch woody thanks for the one dollar hey germa please say take
care everyone at the end of the stream and play bloom bombs i would we already did that though
we did that like we already did that bit i'll say take care of everyone because i do say that
there i'll put it on i'll put it on at the end now let's get away from that music and put
on the original music it's a good bit to repeat maybe i will uh king comrade thanks
for the one dollar uh host someone playing smash brothers or dark souls um end of the stream boys
yeah i mean this is the end of the stream now i'll play smash brothers you'll see my stream
i'm just kidding grandma doesn't host people i hosted vinnie like four days ago i hosted italics
like a week before that i host people one host per week he's a selfish maniac
uh he's doing the bell don't break me don't make me do it do you forget about this one
i'll bring it back if you can't come down oh shit he's bane posting there's still people
that are on the peak mic this stream has been going for seven hours and within 12 minutes
we were talking about peaking the microphone and it's at seven hours later peak mic almost
a whole day has gone by please break you a mic why you guys want me to break stuff
thank you up quark for the one dollar i forgot to tell you this stream is sponsored by flex tape
flex tape can punch poncil okay i don't do i don't i don't do sponsored ads thank you
shoosh room for the one dollar just one guy for germa rumble they will be there you the
one you might have your chance to be the one guy to be in the rumble red shell thank you for
the 20 subs we talked about it already but thank you so much for 20 community subs that
was amazing thank you dr stein thanks for the one dollar if it erupts half of the united
states will be gone the other half will be struggling in an ice age why have i never
heard about this old god that's underneath the fucking earth what all right that's i'm
gonna have to look this up after the stream uh ala thank you ala for the one dollar first
dono here longtime fan just found out that the fairly odd parents intro song sounds like
gin and tonic and red roses from the katamari ost and the song after it is called wanda wanda
this changes everything also the beep boop song is angel's gift let's listen to it this is
let's see fairly odd parents
it is kind of similar you said blues uh all right turn it off that's pretty interesting so
thank you uh thanks for the coming in and uh donating for the first time it's never required
but thank you nonetheless dr stein again for the one dollar do an improv stream form an improv
group and do an hour-long show in a comedy club no up quark again with another dollar
what do you think about having a workout stream where you lead a workout session
embarrassing maybe four or five years ago i would have killed it if this was 2012 i would
have been that guy on twitch that everyone's like holy shit dude this guy's sick this guy
knows exactly what the fuck he's doing he's exactly what he's talking about and look at him
oh it would have been awesome but no sorry i got i got like gross i i peeked over 31 32
years old and i got i got gross so i can't well i can't do a workout stream now it'll
be i'll run out of breath and i'll struggle to lift weights that i could have thrown over
my head five six seven years ago but thank you thank you to sticks renegade for the one
dollar you know what movie is unsettling final destination every time i watch clips of those
movies i refuse to leave the house all day yeah that is a really weird that is a strain that
stays with you final destination does stay with you because you all of a sudden you start
looking around you're like hold on there's a plug right there oh but i've i've got a i've got
a plug on my iphone but what happens if like today what if i did i like cheat death if i
plug my iphone charger in am i gonna get like electrocuted i don't know somebody else can do
it i thought they were too cheesy well they are but the thought of it is still scary it's a bad
smash map you mean it's the only smash map sorry one of like three no that's not i don't
know if that's true anymore this is probably a good solid like eight to ten commuter uh
community maps i was gonna say competitive maps items on all items on on high community
stuff so there's some really good community steps on there but thank you sticks renegade
thank you clueless sniper for two dollars no message but thank you elizabeth thanks for
one dollar soon your death is coming up derma and by that i mean in your bio inc death make
sure to go to church january 23rd that's that is coming up 23rd was january 19th january 23rd
which what day was it that came up quick okay now you got the final destination shit okay
this is weird to me man somebody talking about final destination and then another person talking
about hey that date's coming up i'm gonna weigh oven mitts on january 19th and through the 23rd
i'm just gonna wear oven mitts and a hockey pads just sit in my room and pikachu socks yeah
that's true but thank you for the reminder thank you uh risky xd for the one dollar hey
first time on your actual stream from youtube and watching for a long time i was a big fan of your
content welcome welcome to uh your first actual stream hope you enjoy yourself hope you stick
around thanks for coming on thank you to dragon breath for the one dollar derma i can't believe
you lied to us before the stream about having bttv you betrayed my trust and i'll never
forgive you for this by the way cool stream man i love catamaria have a spunky night i did
i did say in the chat pre stream chat that i got better twitch tv i think i've said that like five
different times don't you like you gotta remember something the pre-stream me in the chat i just
write anything i'm like a weirdo when i just have like a text i could just i'm writing
whatever the hell is happening i have no idea i could i write just random shit in the chat
i don't know why i do it it's i just i don't know if you give me a text box and a
keyboard it's just i don't even know what's going to happen what was that in the background
i'm looking to see how many views the rat movie has it has 99 999 873 so still a little bit off
you barely tweet yeah but that's not a text box that's my phone i i need like a text box with
a keyboard oh yeah the the that move that's it may be at a million views it's probably
going to take a few hours to update but until it shows sorry and finally thank you up quark
for the one dollar thanks for putting up with me tonight see you another day love you now i
don't put up with you guys you guys are fucking awesome you guys you know i saw you know i saw
i saw a message i'm gonna be real with you for a second here let's kill the music because
this is important there was a clip of one of the green screen streams one of the green
screen videos and that had a lot of upvotes and one of the things in the thread what people were
talking about wow what like is is his whole community like content creators these are all
fucking awesome and there was a bunch of like upvotes and threads but like oh wow yeah what
a bunch of like talented funny fucking people i'm just like holy shit man like that's fucking
awesome like that's that that's more than i could ever i seeing that was like oh look
at that yes because i do believe so i believe that a shitload of you guys are very funny very
talented interesting people so is there something playing in the background yes it's it's coming
through my headphones there there yeah i know that i saw that message and it made me really
happy you mean all of us yeah yeah i don't want to put pressure on people like whoa hold
on well i'm not a content creator oh i didn't make a video he's not talking about me
no i i told you all the time i look over here and shit that i see doesn't need to be a video
whole entire fucking ideas have propped up from something that somebody wrote in this chat room
whole characters were created from something that somebody said or something that's like
like look at fireman fireman was just a drawing that that killcode did like i didn't
do that you guys surprise me every day with how funny and interesting you are so it went
up two views well it's only two of you watched and yeah so i put thanks for putting up with me
no no no no you got it all wrong i should be saying that to you thanks for putting up with
me so thank you for being here and we're gonna play the credits all the new subs there was a
shitload of gifted subs and i'll see you guys tomorrow for probably edf if there's some kind
of problem or something that changes i'll be the first to let you know so take care everybody
see you soon have a wonderful rest of your night and i'll see you tomorrow as this plays out
what's edf edf is earth's defense force it's a game where you are attacked by thousands of
insects on the screen at the same time and the latest iteration it releases tomorrow
and try to get a couple of friends to play it might be fun and then on on thursday or
friday is the bird house we're going to be building some gamer bird houses oh katamari
right okay sorry you've been playing it while watching the stream is it any good
all right darzy we need a three second review yeah a review in 10 words or less yes it's good
three seconds all right cool good oh let me go get the real outro that everybody wanted
let's get it on there hey remember this one this is blordow again by the way musician artist
animator scream your mic peek your mic by saying take care everybody crank it it's late
it's like 1 a.m for a lot of guys 2 a.m being on pacific time i always forget that i
oh yeah it's not late yes it is i'm like one of the only places in the world where it's not
late right now pacific time it's only 2 a.m yeah but that's still late for a lot of people
start of a new week you know monday people have work to do school to go to it's it's
late for a little for a lot of people there are all the subs and debris subs thanks a lot
thanks for your extreme support i'll see you guys tomorrow take care of yourselves
and i fucked it up uh take take that uh take hold on all right see you guys tomorrow
have a great rest of your night see you soon take care everybody take it take it there
take that take that see you tomorrow