Hey, what's up? How you doing? Welcome to a fun little afternoon. Today we are going to be playing
Warhammer 40,000 Dark Tide. It is a sponsored stream, so thank you Warhammer for the sponsor.
Drops are on if you want to participate. Drops are on for the game. This is currently the beta.
You pre-order the game right now. You'll get access to the beta before the game comes out on the 30th.
We got some friends in here. We've got Vinny, we've got Kraiken, and we've got Charborg.
I think it's gonna be a pretty fun time. But again, thank you Warhammer for the sponsor. Let's get
started pulling up the YouTube voice. You know, let's see how they're doing. And then like us
calling the meeting exactly at the moment you were about to die and you run into the room.
Yeah. How the fuck did that even happen? I have no idea, dude. That was such a fun session. I
really like want to play more. What, the, the, the Among Us section? Yeah. Yeah, we were just
talking about it. It was so good. It was really fun. But like, I don't know, I, dude, I put,
I put all my VR away. I, I just like, no, I just like put it away. Salvation Army. It just, it
takes up so much space. It's just such a huge thing. It just like, it turns your whole room
into a different room. Right. That's the rule. Yeah. All right. Well, me and Kraik and we'll
just do Among Us again, I guess. That's fine. You guys can watch it on their streams. It'd be fun.
Snot has requested to join. It's not one of you guys. This might know. I don't think that's any of
us. Did I get an invite? I did invite ice cream. I think you could also right click and join too.
Oh, can I just, is it from like the mission terminal?
Escape menu. Oh, in this team, your friend, your friend, please. Oh, there it is. Okay.
Snot Fondler has joined the match. Well, we're gonna have to, uh, we're gonna have to,
I don't, it says I don't have any invites. You have social invites, friends, even, oh, there you are.
Okay. So let me just join. Invite to now join your team. Right. Are you Snot? No, not Snot,
right? No, I am not Snot. It's not keeps trying to join. Maybe it's, maybe it's Charbord. Is it
Charbord? Charbord would unmute, right? I mean, and I see you. Yeah. No, no, no. I haven't joined.
Oh, there we go. Okay. Wait, somebody just randomly invite me or is that you? That was me. All
right. Okay. Who's Spush? That's, that's you, Charb? Yes, that's me. I'm Spush. Okay. All right.
There we go. How'd you get to level four? I'm level, am I level four? Yeah. Oh, no, that's
actually a visual bug. I think it's level one. Oh, it says you're all level 25 for me. What the
fuck? You want to see my character? We're all level four. Oh, I see. It's a visual bug. Yeah,
you're right. Yeah. So, um, we, is there anything we can do for a few minutes? Cause I don't know.
We might have to wait. We might have to wait. We can wait like 10 minutes if you want. Okay. Um,
so how much do you know about this game? Yeah. Maybe give it, give it, give it a quick. I mean,
I used to, believe it or not, I was a huge, huge, uh, Warhammer 40k RTS fan. Really? Oh, massive.
Um, I played as the Tao. Uh, I thought they were, I liked the, uh, what's the hero for the Tao?
It's, uh, XV. What's his name? I actually don't know. The guy with the flamethrower.
My chat's about to explode with the answer though. And then I also played, uh, what was the, the
chaos? Not the chaos. There was a different, like the K88. Yes. That's it. XV88. What was the other
one? There was another one in that expansion, the chaos elves or something. Oh, the, uh, Eldar.
Yeah. It was like the new expansion one. Yeah. The dark Eldar. Dark Eldar. Yep. Yep. That was
the other one. That's cool guys. Did you, did you play? Are you a huge, uh, Warhammer nerd?
Yeah. Oh yeah. What's your, what's your favorite army? It's definitely, I mean, knowing you, it's
um, the Blimpticus. Oh yeah. Blimpticus. Yeah. The boy, the Blimpticus. Oh, you made that up. Okay.
I was like, what the hell is the Blimpticus? He's flipping through his little handbook. Hold on.
I don't see that in, in, in my CTA. The Blimpticus. But yeah. So you get four classes,
right? I guess we can, let's go over it for real. Um, there's four classes and yeah, this is the,
what's, what's the, um, the, the Ogre or the, the Ogren, right? There's also, so this is like a
melee short range focus character, right? Yeah. He's like kind of the tank. You get shields later
on. You get like explosive weapons and a big old, like you have a dagger. That's the size of like
our entire body that you just swing around. So it's cool. You just kind of wait into the battle and
hold the line for everyone. Oh, I probably have some cosmetics, don't I? Let's see. Oh, I just
have a green t-shirt. Yeah. I don't have any cosmetics. I'm in my pajamas at level one.
So wait a minute. The thing dropped at, uh, in 15 minutes, right?
The thing? Uh, in exactly like probably, I think 15 minutes.
No, do we have to start exactly at that time? Yes. Okay. Then we, we need, we need to start a
mission. We need to be available at exactly 14 minutes. We're, we're all good. Mental. We're at
the, at the mission board. Uh, Trevor, what's your character's name? Um, my character's name or, uh,
my steam game? Uh, well, I, I believe I have you on steam unless you changed it. Turn your
eyes up. My character's name is snot. And before you make fun of it. We, it was him. We, we were
like, we were trying to kick you over and over again. Oh really? We don't know snot. No. We were
like, who's this snot guy? Oh, on the lower of my planet, that means it, I know it probably means
something else for you guys, but for me, it means something entirely different. Oh, please do tell.
Uh, it means runny boogers. Oh, no. Thanks for the info. That makes a lot of sense. Everybody
have a good sound quality now. I think I had to turn some of you guys up. I, I always, every,
every time I play a game on discord, I always have to go through and just individually do all the
bars. Yeah. Everyone. Oh, maybe I should do the advanced training just so people can see what it
looks like. Yeah. My training would take you like five minutes. It's, it's good to learn a lot.
I want to meet up with you guys. I want to see you. I'm at the big little, uh, I'm so excited.
The mission terminal. I'm at the meat grinder, just practicing, uh, my weaponing. Yeah. Where
is the, uh, the training area? Left. It's like a big old, there's like a lady in a tube in like a
circular room. It's called the psych, psychinium. There's a lady in a tube. Okay. Yeah. No, that's a
barber. Wait. Okay. The guns are a little loud. Yeah. That's what guns do chat.
Is your hair. Don't tell Brian, don't tell German where the meat grinder is.
Well, that's where the training is. Your personality trim.
Should I use, should I get the bugle berry? Whatever. Is there a map? No. Um, I haven't found
one. You just kind of learn. Oh wait, I found the barber. Yeah. You can get it. It's pretty damn
good in this. I have to say I was playing last night and I was like, Oh, like, Ooh, that music.
Yeah. Kind of surprised at how much I enjoyed it. Yeah. I, uh, so I've been playing this game
a lot over the last week or so that it's been available. And like two nights ago, I was in bed
just listening to Spotify and chilling out, like getting ready to sleep. And so the, the
soundtrack for this game is on Spotify and it auto really started playing the soundtrack from this
game. After I'd just gotten done playing this game and my eyes literally went wide up like,
like a Wokage emote. I was like, and I like got up out of bed and went back to my computer and
played for two hours because I was like, so moved by the, it felt like it made, it was like,
I got to play this now. Yeah. It was, it just, you know, the emperor called me and I had to,
yeah, to respond to the call. Yeah. At that point you had to, I'm very excited. I've, I've
in the prologue and there was some, there was some music that was just,
it seemed like I was swinging to the beat and it seemed like it was cool. Right.
So I'm very excited and I'm very excited as to potentially happening here. And
were you a big left for dead guy at all? I was, I, I actually, I loved it left for dead, but
you'll love this. Yeah. I mean, I, I played Vermintide. Vermintide was a lot of fun.
Yeah. See, I had never played Vermintide. So this was my first experience of this
series aside from Dawn of War. That's the only other 40 K I've ever played. Yeah. So,
so when I played this last night, I was like, oh, this is, this is good.
Dawn of War was, I was obsessed with it. Yeah. That was awesome.
Yeah. So Vermintide in this game, both have like really, I think, well-tuned both gun and
like melee combat. So just the pacing of like fighting through hordes and pushing things back
and then dodging out of the way of like stuff. It's all very readable. Is there any, anything,
where's the least amount of info in the screen? Top right, top left, bottom right was like the,
where's there like no info? Are you looking for a cam spot? Yeah. I need a cam spot here. You
should do a direct middle. Yeah. They always want the middle for me too. I think top right has been
the least amount that I've seen. Okay. Yeah. Or top left is just like the watermark. The beta
test. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm, I'm ready. So you played the tabletop, Jerma, back in your... No,
I played on like the RTS, the Warhammer 40 K. Oh, the RTS one. Okay. Okay. Yeah. I,
I started playing through Vermintide. That's my first exposure to the Warhammer universe. And then
I played the Total War Warhammer franchise, which I fell in love with. I love the voice work. So this
is like my first big 40 K one. The voice acting is always like 10 out of 10 in these games.
I love it too. Oh, are we doing voices? Please. Can we do voices? I love role play. Just guys,
lads. Okay. I'll be my guy that I picked. What does that sound like? My character sounds exactly
like me. It's really weird. It is kind of weird. Yeah. I thought like this kind of like salt spire
from Vermintide. I was going to say, yep. Yep. That's it. That's the classic. The Pernicus,
the Zealot. Vinny, why are you on the news again? Because I saw that game. I saw that. I
saw you on the news again, Vinny. What are you doing? What happened? You want to explain?
Yeah, I'll explain. Uh, the reporter interviewed me for Trombone Champ. And then I explained it
while I was playing Placid Plastic Duck Simulator. It's just a plastic duck game. And I said, I dare
an interview viewer to interview me about this. I was like, come on news. We can, we can do something
like this, um, about this game where you just watch ducks fall into a pool. And then the interviewer
from the previous segment emailed me and said, challenge accepted. And then he interviewed me
with my alien on the couch next to me about this plastic duck game. And that's literally all I was
on the news for. You know what's kind of nonsense? Yeah. You as it goes, as it's going right now,
you are potentially going to potentially be interviewed on the news more than like
Ninja. You know what I mean? If it keeps going this way. Yeah. Just keeps, just keep telling people
to do it and they'll keep doing it. All right. I challenge, I challenge anyone to interview me
about this right now, this moment, just me talking to my friends here in this call.
It's starting to realize he was going to be the next face of gaming.
Yeah. You're, you're, you're going to turn into like the, the, the face of, okay, who's the gamer?
All right. There he is. Let's interview him. There he is. He played that duck falling game.
I played the duck falling game and other meme streamer bait games. Um, and then I'm going to
start getting people to floss on New Year's Eve. It's going to be great. Yeah. But you'll actually
be able to do it. I mean, you live in New York, right? So, you know, the, the, the energy,
I know the people first to have to go, Hey, I'm walking. They know you. Yeah. They're like, Hey,
this is what's up, boy. Hey, I'll fly for you. New York. I just came from Katz's deli. How you
doing? Let's do a little dance. Is that, is, is the hub world? Hold on being too weird. Is the
procedural? Oh, no, no. Is the hub world have just other players just kind of hanging out? That's
what I meant. And I said procedural. Yes, it does. Random. Oh, just the wrong word.
Procedurally generated hub world. It sounded good at the moment, but it was completely wrong.
Sorry. Think of how absolutely fucking annoying that would be. Yeah. Procedurally generated hub
world. And it's always someplace new. Hey, I can't find you. It's because hub worlds are different,
dude. Yeah. Like, Oh yeah. I can't move past it. Blacksmith is like on a whole nother level. You
have to go in an elevator and go up this time. That'd be such, that would be so annoying. Okay.
Let's see. We have like five minutes, right? We've got, we've gotten just about five minutes
and that you guys know about to be excited about this. The lore of like this game or like hive
worlds in general. No, tell me. I could tell you. I'm actually quite the, uh, go on. It's not then
let's hear it. Let's hear it. Yeah. In the year 300, there was, there was the main character named
snot. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, sweating pressures on now. I don't even know. I can't even begin to fake my
way through it guys. I don't know a single thing about Warhammer. Yeah. That's the word really
raised his hand in class and well, there were night elves, there were orcs and they were undead.
That's always the worst. They fought in storm wind. Wait, is the year 40,000 Warhammer 40,000. It
means we are, what is the 40,000 is the, the amount of time Pat, somebody know this?
No, I think it's 40,000 years later, right? It was like desperately reading his chat for
someone to save him with this. No, no, no, no, no. I, I used to play a shitload of Warhammer 40k.
Okay. Please let me, let me do this. The Warhammer 40k takes place in the timeline of Warhammer,
right? Okay. It's the four milky way galaxy from human prehistory up through the 41st millennium
in the Warhammer 40,000 setting throughout. Yeah. Preparative references to present dates
will be made with respect to the original Imperial calendar used before the birth of the great rift.
That sounds like you're reading off of Wikipedia. I think he just accessed the
deep annals of his brain, dude. That was like, I just had to pull it up. Yeah. I said, I like the
kind of, um, one of my favorite, uh, I love the orcs. They were awesome. Yeah. The orcs are great.
They are pretty cool. What are they? What was the, uh, the, the main orc? What was his name?
Gork. His name is Gork. No, no, no, no. His name, Grim Skull, Grim Skull. Yep. He had the chainsaw
and like this. See, I know. Yeah. I know the song. When I did the orc massage video game,
I included the song. I went orcs, orcs, orcs, orcs. Oh yeah. That's the song. Oh, that's right. You
do really get around with the games you play between plastic duck game and everything in
between from orc massage to 40 K. It's a duck game. Yeah. I have, you know, I think here's everything.
I am actually like very excited to play this. I'm so happy. I am like, this is my first level
I'm ever going to queue up for. Okay. This is going to be fun. It's going to be fun. Do I have
to meet you guys somewhere? Uh, I think we just get pulled in, right? I think. Yeah. Once the,
once I queue up. Yeah. We just, we had literally three minutes. Are you guys ready? Three minutes.
I'm excited. I don't know what is going to happen. And I actually kind of, I actually kind of don't
know either. I know that something is a, something is about to happen. Now, is this something
appropriate for level one players? I don't know. We will find out. Oh, that's a good question.
I'm sure we can handle it. Well, I don't, I don't think they would have, I don't think,
I think the part would have made that clear. I have this little prison jumpsuit. I think I can
handle anything. Yeah. So they've been dropping new maps every few days because of a, it's like
rolling out into, you know, the full launch. Yep. So we'll see what happens in two minutes.
Well, chat, this is the mission board. It's not quite like left for dead in the sense that you
just kind of go through a campaign. You just choose missions. They're like bounties. They're
timed and then you get money and experience. It's pretty neat. It's actually a very addictive loop.
Yeah. And they have different modifiers that can randomly get rolled on them. So for example,
like endless hoard. Another one I saw in the other beta was like lights out where all the
lights in the map are out and you basically need to bring flashlights to find your way everywhere.
It's like a horror version. Yeah, that's pretty cool. Here we go. You said that. Here it comes.
We have 60 seconds remaining. Oh, oh shit. Okay. Uh, I'm on the edge of my seat.
Is there drops enabled? I want drops. How do I get drops? New war zone conditions in 47 seconds.
Alert global condition alert. New war zone conditions in 40 seconds. I just repeated what
you just said. Yeah. There's going to be a meteor that hits tomato town.
It got wiped out. All right. So give me a quick little tutorial here. What's the, all right.
I know F is charge. I know that I can do an uppercut tutorial with 20 seconds left. Yeah.
Yeah. Look, it's time for everyone to get, by the way, I'm having a little bit of trouble looking
in the chat here. I don't see anybody spamming. Let's go. I mean, what the heck's going on here?
Maybe I'm being, I just, my glasses a little bit here. I don't really see it. I did that
tutorial. And the second they gave me like a fourth ability I can do, I just started
just kind of pushing buttons randomly. I got a little overwhelmed. Oh, it's happening. Should
I be seeing something? It's still pretty, all the missions went away. Yeah. The missions are
gone and it's just quick play. Why do we quick play? Uh, I don't know. I don't know what happened.
Is that Disney castle? Yeah, that's the magic kingdom, dude. So do we just do a quick play?
The missions are rebooting. I think maybe we'll give it a second because it's a very specific
mission name. Okay. I put it in the chat. So we have 239 hours we have to wait. That's enough
time to talk about the lore of the game, I think. Maybe not. Actually not. Yeah. There's so much
lore in this stupid game. Let's see. I'm a huge lore nerd though. So I will talk as long as you let
me. Are you actually like a big Warhammer like Ben? You are, right? Yeah. I only found it. Oh,
it just popped back up. Oh, power supply interruption. That's the one. Okay. There's
it go. It's going to go at level two. Hold on one sec. Oh, no. Okay. Magistrate Obelette. All right.
Let's go. Oh, it is lights out. Holy shit. Lights out. Wait, is it? Wait, is it the power supply
place? Yeah. Power supply interruption. Wait, I'm freaked out. Oh, it's going to be freaky.
We need to bring a flashlight. I just have this terrible little sword that I found in the trash.
I don't have anything. I don't have a flashlight. You'll have something, Snot, if you just.
I'm like babysitting these pajama kids. I'm ready. This Lays gun has a flashlight,
so I'll bring this. All right. Let's see if I got a flashlight. Oh, that'll be good.
Wait, do we need flashlights? It's going to be dark, man. Power supply interruption. Press I,
and then click on your weapon, and you'll see an icon that looks like a flashlight.
It's three icons on your weapon, and the right one should be a flashlight. Mine's a knife. Well. Oh,
no. Well, shit. Augren's are traditionally stupid. I don't know if you could know how to function
a flashlight. Very good. What is your weapon? I have the default stuff. Just a cudgel of some kind.
It's like, but it's like a makeshift club, it looks like. Did we naturally all pick
a different class out of the four? That's cool. That's actually pretty remarkable.
That's the first time I've seen that. All right. Here it is. This is the big moment.
Oh, my Lord. You're massive. Look, he's counting his fingers. He's not like his iPhone.
It's the Ork massage guy. Stop bringing up Ork massage so that I don't have to say it in the call
anymore. That's going to be your next interview. One hundred percent. This is us. This is us. This
is OK. Calm down. How cool are we? Yeah, we look great. Thought I just crashed the game. All right.
Here we go. It's time to play. This is definitely darker than it usually is. Smoosh, Copernicus,
and Vine. Dark time. Four of us. Are there Fortnite emotes? Before we begin, guys. Not entirely.
Sorry, I don't have somebody to be flashlight lead. I got. Can you see my flashlight? I can.
Yes. OK. Oh, I love the acting. That's a Tom T. I don't know. It's like a numpty.
What's the flashlight button in case they get separated? Mouse five on your.
We already are separated. Oh, Chris. Oops. Oh, what happened?
There's some zombie friends down here infected. Oh, it's fucking dark. This is really dark.
Are these guys confirmed bad or are we just killing like. Oh, they're heretics.
They're they're heretics. And aren't they infected with like worms? Yeah, they're infected with.
I can't see anything. If you look closely, they got like postules all over them, postules,
whatever. Yeah. And when you hit them with a shovel, maggots fall out of their face.
Really? That's gross. That's why you brought the shovel. I knew there was some meta reason.
What's this thing? That's the only one I have. The only melee I have, but sure.
All right. You want to see some cool shit? Let's go. Oh, I like. He's got a flamethrower. What? Yeah.
Yeah. I came to purge some freaking heretics.
Feels pretty good. It is so dark. This is usually well lit.
I haven't done a sewer level at all. Have you? Yeah, you have. So.
Did I kill it? Oh, it's not. Help me. I think a dog pushed me. That wasn't intentional.
I think it's been the only one that brought a flashlight. I think so. Oh, my God. Oh,
you can see them glowing in the dark over there. That's so cool. Look at that. Oh,
that's terrifying. Throw a grenade. Grenade out. Let's go. I'm chopping them up. I'm chopping them
up. Ow. Oh, my God. I keep shooting you guys. I'm sorry. Is there friendly fire, right? I don't
think so. There actually isn't friendly fire. They could just get upset. Like the characters
are like, oh, watch what you're doing, mate. So good. I'm too much of an impact to sound like.
Hey, why are you targeting me? Ammo if anyone needs it. I don't mix in some like
Warhammer space terminology. Would you hit me with the blast the end of the of this of this laser
laser gun? Oh, my God. I threw a box in that guy's head. What's the curse word that replaces
fucking this groggin? What is it? That does not have the same punch to it.
So one of my chat just said dirty sci fi is so cool. It is literally a great way to describe it.
Yeah. Oh, my God. I just I have a brick as a grenade. It doesn't explode.
So the Ogryn just throw off the whole box of grenades. They can't figure out.
That's so funny. Individual ones. I think there's a sniper over there.
It's my mouth. I tried, but I've got this mush. Do we got to find some more flashlights? I can't
see it. Oh, no, I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble. Help. Also, they're suppressing us right now.
You have to like get out of the way of suppressing fire. Otherwise, your aim
gets all screwed up. Are we going to hear that ticking sound? That's an explosive guy, like a
boomer. Oh, but do you need grenades? He's just going to run out. Actually, yeah, I do. I threw
a grab those. It is a lot scarier when you can't see them. Just listen. There is that light.
OK, got him near us. I got you. You look like a monster on the ground. Just try to keep my
flashlight active, which means melee is not a good option because then it gets. What does that sound?
It sounds like a sword. Why are there so many people down here? What are they doing? Oh, my
goodness. It was a rave. It was a Matrix Revolutions rave. That seems like the best time of your life
coming down here. It's been a weekend getting sweaty. Oh, music, guys. Music just started.
I'm going to die. I can't see, guys. I think I'm falling. What the hell happened to you, Snot?
I think these guys pushed me. They picked me up and gave me a wedgie.
Fucking walked off. What did I do? Oh, my God. Wait, where did Smoosh go?
Smoosh is dead. It's dark. We are in trouble. Everyone just walk off the ledges.
I seriously think I did walk just straight off. It's dark. We can get you back. We just need to
find you. OK. He's the only one with a flashlight. His entire job is to just keep it trained on the
way forward. Yeah, this is actually pretty cool, though. So this is going to do more arson. Does
this level exist in the game? Like just the game right now? But this is like a wow. Now you can't
see pretty much. Yeah. All right. I think I think they just wanted us to be like scared. They were
like, yeah, we're going to make sure I'm scared. Yeah. Have a dark environment for him. I
accidentally ran off the cliff. Yeah, we'll get you back. It's OK. Oh, my God. What the fuck is
this? What is it? What is it? What is it? I have never seen this before. I've never seen this.
What is that? We're so screwed. We are so screwed. I don't have a hemo. That was actually terrifying.
Smoosh, are you OK? You're not OK. I'm just observing. Holy fuck. OK. Help someone. He's
killing me so bad. I don't even know who to attack. Sorry. He's just annihilating you.
Help me. Help. Just fucking sweat. Oh, he's so close. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead. You got
him? He's dead. But we're going to get snot up. Oh, my God. Just leave me. There's another special.
There's another special infected. What the hell is happening? That was insane. That was a real
fucking demon. We just all got downed. That was terrifying. Wow. All right. That was cool.
Do we need to go back to the lobby and buy some things? I've got I've got a couple ideas for
supplies. Yeah, I'm going to bring a flashlight. We need flashlights. Yeah, for real. I don't I
don't think you can actually afford flashlights at the moment. Damn. You just really said that.
I said that. There's a leveling system, too. Oh, yeah. Yeah. That's how you unlock more weapon
classes and, you know, stuff in the hub. Full four player co-op, by the way. That's the view,
obviously. You can play it alone if you want to as well. You don't have to be with four people.
That was very intense. The music kicked in, too. And that got my I got my blood pumping.
I I've been playing this game for like 30 hours now over the last week. And I did not I've never
seen that entity. That was the first they just added them. I think right now. Maybe that's what
they wanted us to wait for. Yeah, I think that's what they wanted to close my eyes. I'm not going
to lie. I believe that it was just like too scary lapsed on this floor with like this hallowed
frosty ground around it. And then I walked up to it and it just animated and went after my freaking
neck. It was terrifying. That thing was doing like 10 attacks a second, by the way. Yeah. Yeah. I
no idea how to deal with that. And then show me where you buy flashlights so that maybe one day
when I find a pretty little thing, I think you need to be level two. Unbelievable. All right.
It's all right. We'll manage. We'll manage. We should do a level one mission now and then maybe
come back to that one since it's there. Yeah. Let's let's we're going to the goal of this whole
thing is to beat that mission. Well, let's start with like an easy one, right? Like somebody to
get us. Yeah, we got this consignment yard HL 1736 mission, which we could probably do that way.
You guys can level up and buy another weapon. Yeah, that was crazy, though. All right.
I was with this one. This is also a new map that just came out today. I think the relay station
TRS 150. I do that. What difficulty level is this one? Yeah, we could do that one. That's cool.
You can crack in. Someone said you can upgrade your health or like vigor. Can you do that? Yeah.
So if you press I and then go to feats every five levels, you unlock basically a new perk
for your class. And that's how you kind of build a you can build like a build for your
your how your play style is. We got you. And that includes like, you know, more tanky damage.
OK, I see. Yeah, I didn't see that before. But no, I can't do it anyway right now. But yeah,
drops. There are drops enabled. You guys have drops on yours, too. Yeah. How do you do that?
You've got to connect your which to the Warhammer thing in game or out game. It's on the on Twitch's
like dashboard. I'll do it another time. Can I get some of your drops? Yeah. Open one of our
streams and leave it on. Actually, I'll do that. I'll do that for myself. That's a good idea.
Wait, you just leave the stream on? Yes. Leave it on the background.
Get free items. But I have to connect, though. No, you can connect later. It tracks your watch
time first. All right. Looks like I'm watching Jerma while we're doing this. All right. Hey,
welcome. Hey, Jerma, I'm watching you right now. What's up, buddy?
All right, we can see. Chad, I'll enable drops if I ever play this again on stream,
and I probably will. But next time, this is much less scary. I think I just tried to shoot this
innocent guy coming. What a hero guy. I like that the door. Look at the look at the door handle.
It's just a skull. Yeah, I need to get one of these from my house. So it's not just the skull.
Apparently, the four key universals are called servitors, and they're actually
somewhat conscious humans. Really? Brains still intact that, you know, they're basically programmed
their brains to function for their purpose, like opening the door to be a servitor. That would be
just a pleasant existence. You wouldn't have a whole lot to worry about. I know. Yeah, you can
find them like there's like one for like drying your hands in the bathroom. There's like a hand
drying servitor. Are we all here? Your AI in this universe? Yeah. Well, so it's like doing a little
bit. Yeah, there's a lot of really weird, dark, like grim dark shit in the 40k universe. I know
there's a god emperor, which is also very dune. Game looks really nice. Yeah. Oh, Dave in my chat.
I don't know why I said that. Dave, what option do I turn off for better performance if I need to
ray tracing? You want to turn that off? That's just wondering. Just wanted to make sure they
were dead. I'm just checking the work there. Smush. Oh, Adam, you have a flame thrower.
I got a freaking flame thrower. That's pretty sick. The guy here. Every class gets a couple
weapons that are unique to them. I have a slap. Are you kidding me? Big meaty slap. What? Wait,
what's mine? Do you know what mine are? Should be if you have a button on your mouse.
Oh, yeah, I've got a force push. I'm basically basically like in Star Wars.
So this happens a lot where the ogren of the team gets shot a lot. Yep.
Because doing my job in the melee and then I end up shooting them a ton.
He's so big. He's like a door. He's like a door. I am like a big door. You say there's not friendly
fire. They just get mad at you. It doesn't feel like you wait. Watch out. Be careful.
You shot me in the back. I keep shooting German. Oh, my God. I knew me green fire.
Oh, look at this. It's wildfire. The world looks so cool. This is beautiful. Guys,
we need to unbolt this thing and take it home. This thing's probably worth a lot.
Probably 40. Who's crying? The zealots, man.
Heretics. They picked the wrong God and they're just salty about it. Yeah.
It's nice to know that things in the future are still very. Oh, we're going outside.
Wait, this is the first time we've gone outside in this game.
Reloading. Oh, my God. I haven't yet. I haven't seen this either.
Hang on. Let me just grab some. Got him. Look at that beautiful, beautiful skyline. Breathe in
that fresh air. More discipline would not go amiss. Is it not the measure by which warriors are
judged? I just have been following you around and hitting the thing that you hit again after it's
dead. OK, you know, you can. What happened? Oh, dude, the lights are on. What is your
Falcon? Pick me up and a fucking Falcon. Yeah, I look like I tried to peek over.
I tried to peek over the edge and look down there, but it did not work.
I keep forgetting there's a dodge. The dodge is so much fun.
It's just what's the dodge again? In a direction. Oh, yeah. Was the space.
There are difficulties on the levels, too. Oh, yeah. That's awesome. So this is a level one.
One way we tried first was to it goes all the way up to five. So by the time you get this
five ones, you got to be like, no, the highest level of that chart before.
And they're they're pretty damn difficult,
but really satisfying. Just makes you like work as a team really carefully.
But you also get better weapons as you go. Mm hmm. You have tried to five?
Well, no way. Oh, you haven't. OK, a lock. Everybody in here? OK, good. Yeah.
I want to get some new weapons. So this is also a medical station, which we don't need right now
because we're only on an easy difficulty, but you can heal on these. And every time you go down,
you get this like purple bar on your health and that just reduces your max health.
And whenever you feel these, it gets very, very. Yeah. Oh, ammo and stuff.
And this guy's still alive. This is a server. This guy's still alive. Yeah.
Look, he looks so uncomfortable. Oh, that's right. I forgot about that.
Just ask us to take him with us because he's fucking lonely and does nothing better to do.
That's sad. What's happening over here? We get to run for you guys.
Oh, my God. That was Jerma. I thought Jerma had picked you up.
It was smacking you, dude. Yeah, I was outside looking looking at the cool stuff.
And then I see fucking a giant ochre. Yeah, they're all just staring at
the medical station while it's getting. Damn, look at this.
I'm getting overwhelmed like sensory overload. It looks like Mad Max.
Do you love it? When are we going to when are we going to get the go get us?
Well, I don't know what that is when I'm wait.
Is that like those the blimpkins or whatever I called them before them?
Oh, yeah. Then the good because you'll know.
This guy's played 40K. You can tell. Oh, we've got a whole.
By the way, go get a time, I think. Oh, my God. That dog scared the shit out of me.
Help me. It's not what we're going to do with you.
I need to stay in the background. Jess, I think we're good.
I'll get out of here. Heretic gather thermoelectric cells.
OK, we have to find thermoelectric cells. All right.
It should be near the good guys. I don't know what that is.
Still hold on. You'll know in just about five seconds.
Two, three, four, five, six, maybe. Hold on.
Maybe another five seconds or so. What are you looking for?
There's no payoff for this. There's no out for this bit.
There is, but I don't know if it's going to happen.
I got one of the power supplies. You did?
Yeah. Nice. Where did you find it? It was up top over here.
No, I'll just look over here and hope for the best.
Oh, that one was on my map. Oh, over here. I got another one.
Oh, you know, you got it. Wow.
Let's wait. I see one.
I see one neighbor. Don't let him up.
You guys get the other one. It's here.
It's here. You guys are beating my ass.
I'm coming, snot. Oh, I'm coming.
Did we ever resolve that go good a bit?
Not yet. Maybe. Oh, we got a lot.
There's a lot. There's a lot. Go long, dog.
My grandfather used to call zucchini go boots.
It's not a zucchini. No, I know.
But yeah, now the thing that we're that I'm waiting for is not a zucchini,
but that's you door. That's a zucchini.
Is that what you said?
Dog help dog.
It's like door dashing one single Gatorade. It's like, come on, man.
You drink the whole thing.
I do open the door and grab it and small thing in front of them.
There's no size chuggy cheese pizza once for my birthday.
Last ones over here. That's nice.
Yeah, I got to customize what was on it and they put every topping and it cost $80.
What? Wait, what?
That's clown pizza at that point.
Yeah, it was a little they put little diamonds on it.
All right, we got sardines and they put
the rest of the toppings.
We go through this even eat sardines.
Yeah, let me go through it now.
Oh, behind us. What?
Throwing a grenade.
Started back up. Grind them up.
Yeah, seriously. Oh, that wasn't so bad.
Don't forget that you can tag special enemies to make it easier for everyone to see.
Oh, good job, Charlie implemented it.
I love that overhead.
I mean, it's not sorry.
It's not please.
We use our names here.
All right.
It's the same for the untested soul.
So you say we're playing on easy right now?
Yeah, this is the easiest.
Wow. All right.
This is this has got some.
I think difficulty is actually dependent on each person.
I think I set mine a little higher, which is why I'm dying so much.
So I see that explains it.
Who has the flame thrower?
That's awesome.
That's me. The results bastard here.
Another. Whoa.
OK. I mean, you know, there are all baskets.
No, not quite.
Oh, my goodness.
Milly range is much longer than you think, says a chat member.
OK. Oh, yeah.
Dodging and blocking is your friend.
Yeah, it is.
You can also hold right click and then left click to push.
Oh, yeah. And then you get a special attack after that, too.
Yeah. They told me all this.
I just can't remember it all.
Yes. I mean, it's a heck of a game.
To write this down on the like, the palm of my hand.
So I can do you guys see this?
What is it the like one of them is just stretchy.
It looks like Pokemon pilot.
Well, we just killed like 50 of them.
Yeah, but one of them got real stretchy.
That's all right.
It's fine.
It's the chaos.
Chaos. Yeah.
We'll crouch.
Oh, I'm here to stay together.
Low hanging Pokemon joke.
I don't think it does anything.
There's a lot of view.
Distance can we click this? I don't think this is a button. I could have just declared. I have found a switch
All right, enter
Plastil is what's plastic is that just money to buy some flamer and they have the best sound effect in the game in my
Opinion it's the sound of like a fucking gas stove turning on like the
Right before they fire. Oh, that's a cool
Do we have to bring sound design in this are incredible is incredible?
Maybe class steel is current in this level for so I wonder if there's a I guess we have to do if you kill
Anything or maybe it's bugged
It says enters station. It's probably just one of these side paths
Maybe up. Oh
Also, I called I called the psycher a freak a freeze. Yeah, I heard that. Yeah, so that was
It's not just very nice to be working on a team where people just are shitty with each other. Oh, here we go
Yeah
I'll take care of that
Yeah, it's interesting because I was playing this yesterday. I was like, oh man, there's no map button
I've gotten so used to having map buttons that I'm always opening and yet I had almost no problem navigating the levels
I feel like they're they're pretty
They seem vast, but you know where to go
They also have a little
Like weenies here like this freakin little arrow that goes aiming at you and then he pulled a sword out instead
See where to go
So snot and me could use this
One spot left. Yes, the purple is that your max health reduced because they've been at times you've gone down
It'll fix it so this fixes
You didn't think the the medical station man, which is a little rude he hasn't taught he hasn't spoken to somebody in like six years
Behind you Johnny cab
God there's a lot of detail. Yeah, I was gonna say this is
But immense if I say immensely detailed I like all the clutter it really just feels so
claustrophobic and this is the level that's outside like every level you're like
constantly indoors
Kind of want to see maybe this is not a good idea
I kind of want to see what this looks like with ray tracing on high for a second. I go in here
I love the slap. Hello the sound of it's so good to write
Can you guys hear me yeah ray tracing on my game crashed? Oh, no. Yeah, see that ray tracing man. I've tried to warn me
You can reconnect yeah
That's good, thankfully
Guy
Someone said what the fuck did he expect?
expected ray tracing to turn on
Dude if you turn one of the known bugs, I think is ray tracing
if you turn ray tracing on in general like in the middle of any game you get your computer just kind of goes like
Should I should have known it's not like it's the first time in the first game. But yeah
Aren't they doing a bunch of stability patches too. Yeah
Yeah, this is this is still the beta by the way, so it's what the 30th is when the game actually launches, right?
If you pre-order it you get access to the beta and comes out on the 30th
Wait, get away from the barrel. I accidentally hit that. Oh
Well, this is a bot oh wait, this is who Vinny was okay
This guy with the hair, this is me. I'm the pernick. I know I turned on
I saw like a funny haircut and I was like I have to hit this person
You look like count Olaf
Okay
Who's count Olaf?
Count Olaf from a bad time bad luck
Lemony Snicket presents bad luck bad time
Jiminy cricket. Hey, I'm back everyone. Hey, welcome back
You didn't miss much
Okay, did these explode? I'm not gonna try it you're do this. Oh, damn. You look great. Hey
Oh, wait, are we leaving without Vinny? You ever do this?
This make look like it's made of rubber. Yep. Yeah, I've done that. Yeah. Oh, yeah
You know, we're doing it. I people used to think I was a warlock in second grade when I figured that one out
Yeah, I got all the ladies with
Do you remember the origami or not origami but you'd make like a thing where you could tell fortunes where you'd open it up
Yeah, now, how about this rubber pencil origami paper and you draw the crazy ass on it
Yeah, oh
God was that oh my god
This thing's like coming out of the wall. I
Thought that was the character very close in my character's ear when you just did that
Thanks, I guess I was actually that was phenomenal
Well, this thing has a face
Look into these dudes do this is freaky. What is this thing?
What I just do
Look the eye and now I'm gonna use that fridge more bro. Oh the music's gonna kick it now. It's sick. I
Think this is the song that woke me up from bed. I was in this song came on and my eyes went wide open
Yeah, if this does not have no choice, but they give up and play too well dog
Oh
Dog it went through a wall dog
Okay, it came from a these we got to be careful up here these like holes in the walls up there
Those vents they spawn. Oh god. It's a little sus, but they spawn and what is this? Yeah, it's gross
Oh, look at this face. This is so cool. I mean, where's heresy but
In the face
I would take a piece of this off and I love what you're using a shovel
It's like black mold but actual sentient chaos God
It looks so friendly though. This on the hard difficulties would probably be very very difficult
It is so fun on the hard difficulties man. It's not we got to try it communicate constantly. Yeah, we should really try it
Grab that when you can your health. There's a health thing. I tagged
Bridges I
Look a little laser gun you got you might get one. You might be able to unlock one. I want out here
Do you not have any guns German? No, I have I have one gun. It's one. It's a one-shot shotgun. Oh
Gotcha. How did you get up there? I
walked
There a staircase or ladder. It's a staircase. Oh, I see ya
evil carnival music
Maybe a little bit
Sort of carnivals you go to I don't know like demonic ones that church
Yeah, the now now it's like church carnival
That's what I'm waiting for
There's actually a song in the
Identical to that. It's like do you guys remember one of my favorite parts of vermin tide?
Which is the other the other game like this right was when the rats would spawn it would be like rap rap rap rap
And then they would start charging. Yeah, I was awesome. You can like hear them chanting this part of it
Not that
It's kind was actually kind of like that. It's a kind of like that. Yeah, it's cool. I
Like your memes your community's memes have infected my community's memes
Like plus two minus two rats. It's it's yeah gas
They've got a lot of good ones from you
gas
Like that, that's fun. What's the lore on these statues Copernicus?
I'm gonna start answering and you're gonna interrupt me or something or like you're actually on me. I'm just curious
Statues, oh well, that's actually the god ember which we all serve in our every waking moment. How's the audio audio good?
anybody
What?
Hey guy here everybody
Hi here
Guy hey
Can that big guy pick up our big gun? Oh, yeah, just pinned up to the ground. Oh, yeah, he got me
That's freaky
Guys ammo here anyone need some I think on easy, it's probably pretty I am in need of ammo
So, oh, it's full. It's a good good stash you got here. It's a good animal. Yeah
Oh, there goes dead
There's no safety hazard signs on this I would stick my hand in that
It would be snot sausage that would be dangerous yo, this guy's mad chillin look
Hi, I knew I wasn't gonna do it I wasn't gonna do it somebody else I had to I had to
Took his head off. So I the thing is I'm kind of confused is like I on the map
It's giving us directions, but I don't know which way this is trying to get us to go. I'm having this like a bug
Wait, how do you see the man? We just started? I don't think there's
It's just up he's gonna go up this looks amazing. Look at this. Oh
No hazard signs
This is an OSHA violation. He's a guy weird guy
Bad hair
That machinery is like I would lose a hand to that. I would lose probably one or two
Everything here looks so dangerous
Meaty and dangerous. Yeah, there's the face
Data relay, I love the combos you can do like I can slap light swing heavy swing. It's fun. Yeah
some of the other weapons to like I'm using like a knife for example, and it's just incredibly fast swinging and you can like mix it up with
The overhead and a sweeping attack
There's something
What are they called chain swords in this universe? Yeah
There was one that they gave me in the tutorial and I was like, yeah, I need that. All right, we're gonna turn this off
Why was it doing? I don't know. It's a turn it off
Out of transition, I think it's over here. This is a reticle transmission
Hate that. Oh
Hold for signal. Oh, all right. We got let's group up on the way behind you. Oh, this is bad. All right
That's it. Let's turn out the flame up
Posted a good night. Hey lad. We got a weird guy over here
weird guy
It's this thing is just screaming
You know, you know, I'll tell you let me tell you about this game
There's a lot of activity going on like this is very deep a lot of activity
stimulation
It's kind of uh, it's kind of sick
but you get into the swing of it like I um last night I was like
Really just I hit like a weird flow state. Yeah, where my mind left my body and I just like
100% I think that's my favorite part of this game. It's like let's see hit that
Somebody just sniped me in the head. There's a sniper over there
So you can you can actually dodge their bullets because right before they fire you hear a sound
Your scope and then if you dodge left or right you won't get hit
Music sounds like rocks or the rock and roll clown. Oh
Oh
What is it I think that's my character I picked a voice that was really like
Oh, it's you. Okay over here. Oh, all right. Let's get out of maybe wait, maybe it's not me
No, you think the flame is my talks flamer
I
Might be the same actor
We need to Google this
In this universe, I don't want to I want to be more you're gonna use a skull. It'll fly off
I'm playing guys
You're so big
My hand is really sweaty
All right. Now you do unlock the store. So now we get some items
Yes, you can now purchase a weapon of choice
Perfect. This is a big decision. I got a hellbore Lays gun
2,500 bucks game looks cool game is cool. Actually
Actually, very cool. We got confirmation that it's not the voice of Rox. Oh, okay. Oh
I don't want to play this anymore
What do I go for this flashlight
We definitely need flashlights. Yeah, we all go go buy flashlights. So it's certain weapons have them the last gun
I think is the main one but there's also others that have it. So where's the story? We unlock it right now
All right, so follow me
Like it's just to the right over here I looked a super imposed
Yeah to the left. Sorry, not right
Which one?
Requisition weapons and curios. Oh god my damn headset
When you click the weapon look on the at the three icons and you'll see the one all the way on the right will look
like a flashlight
Well, this is my
Again, I want to just want to say thanks again to Warhammer for sponsoring the stream
Games really fun. That's obviously the first mission, but let's keep going
This is beta right now you can pre-order it right now the beta
Game launches on the 30th, but go on access to the beta. You can pre-order it right now
Game is pretty sick. I
Go I look at myself in the mirror for two hours every day
Oh, wow, how I warm up or should I get the axe instead check? I
Like your hair too. Thanks. Apparently I made
Hi Chachi, I gotta reckon with the armor out this way over here smell the revolver seems fun
You really do look like count Olaf
So embarrassing
What's the difference between these knives and sword for wards acts for single target? I like your tattoo. What's it mean?
Emperor these are these like not are these different rarities or something? Well, there's different rare numbers are level this like
Yeah, I get but you'll basically gonna level up every mission you do and so you'll be able to get new stuff in the shop
Every time what do I have? Yeah, what do I have right now?
All right, so damage is a little bit lower, but mobility is higher range is higher stopping powers higher reload speed is lower
I love this one. Oh, okay, tiny range tons more damage tons more real. Okay. I don't know get the shovel
Oh, wow. I don't look like I'm wearing pajamas anymore
Did you get pants are still my pants are still pajamas. Never mind a lot of crowd control
What does night get a knife? I want to cleave damage
What everyone has the most cleaved evan just one good bringing the thunder hammer
But if you want I would kind of recommend maybe a range weapon too, especially one with a flashlight
I don't think any of these have a flash. I do. I know I don't think Ogren gets flashlights. Unfortunately
All right, I'm going with super cleave damage I'm bringing a flashlight though, so we'll have some more
Do I look cool walking slow like this you look sick my friend?
You can inspect it too, are we doing the dark mission again right after this or are we doing something else?
I'm gonna do a dark mission. Let's do the dark mission. Yeah, okay. Let's do the one that power supply one
Well, it's gonna be really I think funny for your guys first experience in all these levels to be with no lights on
Nice. All right, cool. You have two options for dark missions
Yeah, let's do let's do the put the power supply one is the one that they just added right let's do that one
Yes, but we it's a power supply. It's the dark mission with two different main objectives
So two different levels that oh dark mission on it. So
either do one where we're going after assassinating a target or
We're trying to repair
Like a train assassinate. Let's do that way and do it. Let's do it on normal. Let's actually let's let's let's turn it up a little
Yeah, I don't difficultly too. Yeah, it'll be it'll be too difficult. Yeah. All right ready when you guys are I'm ready
I'm ready, too
So if you when you guys accept just double check that you you got the same the weapons you want
Yeah, open your inventory. Make sure it's in. Yeah, you got it. Yeah, so I'm doing a beer
Oh pistol, um, I didn't have a beard for you before. Yeah, dude. Wait, did he I should about it?
Yeah, it looks like your head's on upside down kind of
I love your knife
Yeah, I know what you mean it's one of those like illusion photos and yeah
I bet if we flip that over if we got some Photoshop specialist to somehow flip that
Yeah, I bet the beer you just got Mandela affected yeah, I had like selective memory and removed his beard and Photoshop my eyes
Yeah, chat my pistol has a flashlight
That's good, so did we at least one or two of us have light right yeah, we'll be
Flashlight. Oh, yeah, that's been all my money on a flashlight. I'm just swinging a knife in the dark. Whatever
Well, you guys look cool a cannon. You guys got different clothes, too. Yeah, Vinny's got a shirt
Basically wearing what I'm wearing
Able flashlight
Yeah, it's like your secondary mouse button. Oh, no, never mind. I don't have a light. Oh, no
All right, not you got one though, right? No, we've got one. Okay
Is this like a like a glow stick I think I got lost no, no, we're good I
Can't I can't light them put way up for you guys cuz Germans so damn big
Yeah, I should be in the very back. I'm gonna just go I'll be in the back
I'll be in the back charges in for
Well, I realized I don't have any weapons that can shoot more than 10 feet in front of it
It's like oh god, it's so creepy when they activate
This is so much scarier without being able to see
We can all take my guns with my gun if we need I
Keep forgetting that I'm one of the flashlight guys
It's like I switched to melee. I'm like why'd it get dark? Oh
There's a person. Oh
You're so quiet, too
What was that how?
Probably just a puppy
All right step
Watch out yo
Oh
You just sniped his head off
We stay together we have to stay together because we have the regeneration right? Yeah, it'll believe you
Oh
My god, I'm dead
Shit. Oh my god. I'm down
Ogre was very powerful. That guy is hitting one hit kill. Holy shit
I got you
All right, we're good we're good already needs a medic station
Yeah, guys. It's crazy. These guys are targeting me
Did they're they're all they're toxic. I mean, they probably read the lore right? He's the main character you guys doing good on ammo
Yeah
Did we slay the bomber or did the bomber explode on you we got him from a distance I think yeah, he's right here
This is a tiny skull. This is a child skull
You know what that checks out for the Warhammer universe, yeah
So dark good our dark dream is lagging a bit. No
That's a possibility
How did you get up here
You know, honestly, these are these are voice lines you say in the mirror
Weird guy over here. Yeah big guy. I definitely need something like that like I'm down
Wow, that's gonna be coming. That's gonna be using a lot
In your everyday life, there's that ammo. Yeah
Yeah, that that's got some. Oh my god sniper
Yeah, I can't snipe them anymore
How many of you guys walked around saying Thanos lines from Infinity War after Infinity War came up?
Come on a little bit not as much as the Joker when Dark Knight came out
Was that and more at we're just like
We were the annoying guys
But I did reduce to Adams was a bit of a favorite of mine
This is kind of scary. What's the sound? This is this is the talks person. It's the one that explodes and it gets too close
Keep an eye out. Oh
I don't know where he is. I don't see it. I'm quiet. Oh my god. I see the health station guys
I'm gonna make a run for it
Careful easy
Watch out
explosive barrel if anyone needs it, there's there's a
little bit of ammo
Just like clunking him in the head. Oh
The melee is better for the armored guys know I'm trying to hit him directly in the face
If you have like an axe that's our piercing if you have like yeah, my axe is probably pretty good for that
So this healing station is should I take this?
Yeah, yeah for sure. This is you you'll recover that. Oh my god. It's him again. Oh god
All right, we gotta fight fight fight fight fight
I'm taking up my cube. It's going for me going for me going for me. I missed
You throw a box for me. Oh my god. What's he doing? He's sucking you see he's sucking out your soul. Oh god
Stop it. Leave him alone. He gave me put him down
Oh my goodness, I can't believe I'm dead. I can't believe you he's almost dead
Oh
There's a chat member that said that this thing is like the witch from left for dead and you should avoid
Yeah, we got it
Coming snot
Nothing's over here. Um, you want the honest truth? I think I think that was unrelated to the enemies
Tired that was actually that was a great voice line if I die here, I'll haunt you forever
Anyone that went down should uh, what is that guy doing? I'm totally like eliminated, but you guys will find me at some point
I'll find you soon. Should I do this down someone? He just literally sucks the life out of me like that's insane. All right
All right. I can't see what did you say?
That's tragic there he is
He'll I I couldn't could I have healed right there I
Didn't have an indicator
The medical station. Yeah, you did it. You saved me. Thank you. Oh guys. Look at all this crap
That's good crap. There's lights that turn on. Oh, I got good. I
Like this place it's got lights take them grenades I could definitely use some health
Oh, there's a health kit thing. Somebody picked one up
Well, you know what we can does it recover a criken do help kits recover purple health? No, they recover
Oh, I feel so much safer around her buddy
Ouch. Oh my god that freaking
Did we start the thing I think it's going in my accident
Well, I say by accident, but I didn't know what it did. Oh my god, that hurts
All right, might have to use cover here because there's a lot of range guys. Yeah, there's a lot shot at things
Unless you're smushed then you're you're shadow luck. I'm gonna try to wrap around
Step up turn music. Okay
All right. I got the ones that were over here. Oh
My god
Talks flamer
somewhere
I found him. I think I found him. Did you get him?
So Trevor your class has like a head-popping ability you use that yet
Yeah, so if it reaches like a hundred then you blow up but if you use your ultimate then it vents it and also
Thanks guys
Yeah, I keep forgetting to use my ability I'll try to remember chat I just
This this voice sounds like beep oh from Mario and Rabbids chat
Is those good those games fun I loved Mario and Rabbids it's just you know, it's it's like XCOM light
I'm in real time. It's really
Yeah, I had no idea what the gameplay was like for that game. Especially the new one
It's dope. I don't know why I'm saying sick and dope so much. I feel like it's the 90s part two for me lately, but
But really no, it's awesome. I really enjoy the Mario Rabbids games. Oh
Boy, I went down
All right, watch that watch that fire. I'm getting into this
Oh, yeah
Kraken that does sound exactly like you when you do that. That's actually unbelievable
the voice
Sometimes I actually think it's you doing it and now we fight for the emperor
Yeah, that's oh my god. There's too many of them perfect. That looked like it was a like a body waterfall
Yeah, good drop in like water. That was creepy
Doesn't matter if I can't see
Yeah, I'm out of ammo guys, that's gotta go away for now
Corruption I should have let snot get that ammo. All right
We got to find some ammo for snot for flashlight purposes, right?
I think I found something this looks like promising over here. You want to see this guys? It's ammo. Good news. Get it. Oh, yeah
Especially when it's this dark another one
Oh god help oh fire what
Trying to do big slashes. Oh my god. You just feel it bowling. I love that move
You want to go
Parking lot press 3 to deploy ammo. Oh fuck. I have ammo this whole time
Snot could have used that
It's not my fault
We do reaction
What it's over that direction, I think it's it's the demonic hosts corruption
Don't go in there man, we can avoid it we can avoid it telling you don't go in there man
Oh fuck we can't avoid it. All right
This way and I'm not gonna I'm just gonna okay follow me everybody
Cuz I bit my tongue damn it
No, you didn't even land it
Oh, I thought you were screaming you threw the grenade Oh
Oh creepy
It's here if anyone needs extra actually I do
Just don't know where I am
Anyone need grenades? Yeah, I'll take him my box of grenades. All right
This backwards
It's yeah, there's no way this is for us. Oh, no, I do you know what does is the heart inside of the outline based on?
Is the heart is this guy is the heart based on your health the outline I
Guess so maybe you can start seeing their little skeletons whenever they're hurt. Oh, yeah, like the thing through the the
Yeah, I see your skeleton right now. Yeah, I think it's the color of your heart is how much healthy you've got
That's actually pretty cool
All right. We have to go back in the room with the weird guy. I think so when we stuck the wrong direction
Yeah, we gotta go this way here come come this way follow me
Don't look just don't look. They can't see you. Okay. It's okay
All right, we're good Copernicus you're probably gonna want this
Okay
What's up there?
Probably there's one more
Some good stuff use of it. Well, I'm smush. How'd you take that?
I'll take it. I
Know what I want. I want a big shield. I wonder if they have it in this game. You're gonna get one
Yeah, thank the ones that get it. Oh, yeah, I want it bad
Yeah, you can like right here you could just put the shield down and no one will be able to get past us cool
We just hold fire past
They did
This is somebody dames game
Like I like that. It's not just all the lights are off like the you know
One's in the level like the torches the stuff is still on so as a school. Yeah. Yeah, it's cool looking
Lighting I love that that voice
Okay, so wait
Find magistrati. Oh, okay. I thought now was the time we were gonna assassinate that dude. Oh
Wait, is it a boss? All right. Oh, there's another fucking bitch thing
Just three of them in this level
Right here we activated
It's activated. It's activated. It's activated. Are you sure wait? No, what's that stuff coming out?
It's lasers that the enemies are shooting but oh like if as long as we don't shoot it I
Don't want to miss in here. I'll be so embarrassed. Oh, there's a med kit over here. I'm gonna grab it. Oh
There's somebody sniping. Oh
Ah
Jesus I
Think we have to just just rush in there. I'm going around it. I wonder what the aggro range is on it
It's the other way. It sucks like you get hit. Oh
on that
Yeah, I was getting hit while crushed behind cover
All right. I think we're all right. Keep an eye on it. I think we're okay
It might just be the like the icy ground that activates it when you stand on top of it. That's true or attacking it. Yeah
That doesn't sound good
Yeah, either there's like there's something going on behind us. Oh, that's scary
All right, it's time to use the axe
There are too many people down here, dude. There are
This is a fire hazard and my axe
My bum and my bum
I'm on solo. Oh wait wrong wrong song. Is that that the cranberries?
Zombie I don't know where I'm going. There's a healing thing here if anyone needs it. Oh between you and
Salve salve
Creepy church. No. Oh, I feel like this game is just metal and creepy churches
Oh, no, what do you pull me up? I
Keep trying to jump on top of stuff and it vaults me over it. Somebody keeps throwing grenades at us
This place is giving me real creepy vibes everyone. I love how you said the barrel explodes and not even a second later it exploded
I hear somebody big weird guy weird guy
We got a weird guy. I
Said swatch to do that
There's an eye on his arm. Is it that an eyeball? Oh, no. Oh, yeah, that's chaos corruption
That's why we're gonna you just described all of warhammer 40k. What metal and religion? Yes
Pretty much yes and dirt a little dirt. It's cool, though. I
Really hope they're gonna add a tech freeze later the ones that like literally just pray to the machine spirit and they're like
my gun works because
I'm getting zapped by this thing
Now are there any giant sand worms in the dune in the sorry
What are you applying him in the wrong universe? Sorry about that
Group up ammo here. I get one stick with a knife
What is your watch get that that's large rafting later on crafting?
Yeah, then you get to like
Craft weapons and stuff. I think cranking is that correct you craft weapons or you re craft them or something?
Yeah, you don't both you get like
if you think of every weapon you get is like a template and then
Create your own and try like reroll to get specific modifiers for it
That's okay. My knife has like bleed on hit and so I build this like if I hit a bleeding enemy
I get higher crit chance
So the stuff happens when I crit so then I just have like a crit
Well, what's that? Oh, dude
It's similar to vermin tide a bunch of lads over here
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was a rat extermination game
I didn't know it was warhammer related for like a while because everybody's been you need to play vermin hide
No, thanks
Hope I'm all right big guy
Tyranids have giant sandworms
Said oh
Sorry guys, she's dead over here. We gotta help them. Oh
Stop actually hoping around electrocuted. Did you not hear it in my voice?
But I'm not smush is gonna do it. I got smush
The cleave on this is actually huge. It's funny
I'll tank I'll tank I'll tank taunting taunting taunting. I think I think he picks one person in
Down here
One of us is definitely gonna be
Yeah, I'm out I'm dead fuck I missed I'm about to go down to
My cost us the mission
I'm gonna smush this guy man. He pushed me down here on this ledge. I'm sure I'm doing that. Leave me
Oh
I get him just in time. Yeah. Oh
Oh down here. It's too dark. Oh Vinny. I'm sorry
Sorry, it's my fault. I didn't know that's what I was shooting
I thought I was shooting like some regular like dude in the distance. Oh a med crate. I got a med crate
Should we use it right now?
I'm kind of hurting
Did it work? Yeah, sure. Yeah, you just gotta stand in the smelly air
I bet this would feel so excellent
Right, can you imagine having that air would feel like throwing one of these down? It's like a
Future vix vapor rub. I've had enough
I'm out of ammo guys. We're going dark. All right. Well, there's Vinny. Oh, yeah. I'm yeah. I'm in there somewhere
Somebody said you're button mashing. Yeah, I am I have arrived to provide light
Oh, thank goodness
Oh
That's a guy with a that's a guy with a gatling gun yeah, we got gatling gun gatling guy
Let's see if I can get to him. Yeah
I'm gonna try to infiltrate his mind with my powers
All right, we're good. Look I I want to switch to melee more but then everything gets dark
Okay, I need to be the team light
It's very very helpful. I was about to say I don't know how much it's helping
It's helping. Is it like pretty visible? Oh, yeah. No, it's great
It's actually when I turn my light off and I just look around at yours. I can it's tremendously helpful
All right. Here's the way out and also a medical station and ammunition. I don't know why I said like that
All right, i'll take me some of their medical hey guys medical crate over here. Oh, that's good to have
I did that for you guys not for you guys on the call
Oh
I did I did like a I did like a thing to include chat for a little bit
Oh, yeah, I i'm sorry chat. I have to apologize to my chat too. I forgot about them for a bit
It's very easy to just get like tunnel vision in this game
When we were playing among us vr
like
You're a you're in vr b you're being terrorized by charborg
right like
So much going on it was hard to imagine chat was even there
Yeah, if there's too much going on I just my brain shuts down and I can't
This is just ignore chat night
unfortunate
Yeah chat is the the uh
The odd man out so to speak
It's all right chat
All right time for me to say my next line
Never mind. Does the boss
captain america
Captain ander
under anderson
Yeah, i'm seeing and he's got a shield
Ow
We have to pop the bubble. Yeah pop the bubble and then we do damage. That's which one's him. I light it up
Oh shit watch out back it up back it up
Hey, um, he's hiding heels on me heels on me heels on me. Oh, okay
I was gonna say the heels would be awesome. Yeah
Oh, this is the music
Yeah, this music is also awesome
This is the one that does the thing german was doing
It sounds like they're saying this is halloween
Reload the gun
Reload the i'm gonna put healing down on the boss
I had a version of that halloween song for statin island. It went like this
This is parker said this is parker said parker said parker said
There was a bit of a parker set problem here like 10 years ago. So
Shields down. I thought it was being funny. It was mean
Oh fuck you want to go blow for blow, let's go everyone make a scream make a scream
Keep keep killing them everybody do a voice line from your character
We did it good job everyone
Thank you. Was that good enough? Oh, that was good. All right, good. Let's wrap up
Oh my god, that guy turned into just gibs
Grub hubba salami
on me
That was cool. That was fun
That was you just got possessed
That looks so good do higher difficulty
Well, we we need to get our our levels up a little and unlock a few weapons
I wouldn't try it the next difficulty until like at least level five. Yeah
I got a level five unlock like skills and stuff
All right, that thing looks pretty amazing
The calm chatter doesn't meet e3 quality standards
Oh, we can do an e3 freaking calm chatter. We could easily now. We absolutely could for sure. We're all very very familiar
Copernicus i've got a tango on my six. I'm gonna go look at this new weapon
And i'm also gonna make sure to tell you guys that again warhammer sponsored this stream
uh
Games actually really goddamn fun
Um, it's available if you pre-order it, uh, this is the beta the game comes out on the 30th
Four player co-op played vermintide. It's it's kind of in that same world
Also warhammer and let's keep going. It's been pretty fun so far
Pants are like this gold standard of like this game's economy
All right, I want to see that gun
Oh my god, you're you're right. They're so expensive
I want to look at that thing
If yeah 15 000, i'm gonna look like a dweeb forever. Yeah 20 000
Wait, where did you buy your shirt from?
It was just in the character creator. Well, you can change your shirt in the character creator
Yeah, also the character creator has a bunch of personality questions that I was not prepared for
I can't I don't think it does that matter. Does that add anything to your character? Uh, it's your voice
uh lines
Really?
That that's actually pretty cool because honestly it's like a 10 question survey that you take when you make your character
I definitely needed a gun
How often should you uh buy better?
guns and all that
um
I'd say like every other level
At this point is probably good good or if you literally just want to try a new type of weapon
I'd say like just buy buy it. It's never a bad idea
Yeah, I have a nice variety now. I'm pretty happy with that because eventually you're gonna start buying them to craft them into better gear
Will you break them down?
Yes, you can you can break them down to get money or you can use them as raw materials to craft a better
Version of whatever that weapon is
I have like three different knives because knives are my favorite
So I was like i'll buy a bunch so that I have options when i'm upgrading them. How do you?
How do you break the old one down?
If you go into your inventory and then click on it and then hold x it'll discard
I should yeah, this is the slowest reload ever
Oh, that's how you get a gun actually shoots through look at that. It actually hits more than one target
Cool
Go to the training area. Oh, that's where you guys are, right? Right? Where are you?
Yeah, i'm in the training area
Where is that at compared to the little the walt disneyland place?
um
Oh god, I don't even know how to explain it
I've got a good imagination. I'll probably just imagine how my gun would shoot shrine of the
Om nissiah, what is this?
need to be level four
His dude's name is how do I play this game?
He's level 10. He seems to have a pretty good grasp trust him. Yes. Trust that chat member that viewer that uh player. Oh my god
I'm fine. It's the mini stroke. It's an upgrade station. Oh, that's when you get to do that. All right, so right here
Yeah, this revolver is fucking awesome r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 r1
I can do like one more
If you guys are okay with one more. Oh, yeah, i'm i'm i'm gonna play this for at least the next hour
Yeah, okay, because I I have a I have an engagement. I must go to congratulations
No, no, it's just a
It's a friends giving
Um, oh cool. Also, there's my my other friends are doing a charity stream today. So i'm gonna be
Throwing them the host after this but oh, yeah, very cool. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Only an hour. No, i'm i'm i'm down to play
Um, you guys okay finding a replacement after I leave we can also just maybe do randoms
It doesn't really matter right? No, probably not. Yeah, I got some people that are down to play I think
Yeah, everyone to just come on in that's easy
Should I get
What's uh, what's the mission that we should do?
Uh, I can do you want to keep doing dark ones or do you want to do one?
That let's do let's do a normal. Let's do a normal one. Yeah, I want to see for a little bit
Yeah, uh chat member I meant raid I forgot the um, I say host still because i've been saying it for like years
But uh, yeah, they got rid of that feature. So i'll raid let's start gone. Is there another one with the boss? The bosses are fun
There's there's weird. What's that weird slug thing? Criken, you know that that like slug boss that showed the beast of miracle
Yeah, I love that thing. So the lore of that thing is he uh,
He just wants a hug like he's just friendly and like wants that like, you know, like a golden retriever, you know
Like he just wants to hug you i'll give him a hug
But he's incredibly poisonous and also eats you accent something else that i'm realizing right now, too
Which is interesting. So these missions up here
They reset or refresh every 10 to 15 minutes or something. Yeah
Interesting, so you'll always have new things
Huh?
Oh one just it's literally just happened. I saw that. Yeah. Yeah, it just happened. What so we could do
Uh, I don't think we've done this mission yet. What's the what's a raid?
That's a difficulty one, but that one's a fun level. So unfortunately, I don't have it on two right now, but okay
Let's do another one place in like a pleasant location
Not really pleasant
One takes place in a chuck-e-cheese ball pit
This is a huge ball pit. It's the whole level which is to say that it's a pit of disease
Which is what this game is about. I was about to say make sure you uh equip your weapons. Thanks
Yeah, I got my revolver somebody said why am I playing as the amish hulk?
I love you. I love every weapon. I've seen you have I love it. Look at this big giant knife
Yeah, it's like it's like the hulk's brother, right? They like they went like separate ways in life. Yeah the hulk
And they have to go
They have to go convince the amish hulk to like come on man. We need you
And he's like he's like putting a wheelbarrow with butter in it. He doesn't want anything to do with it
He refuses to ride the train to get out of retirement
He walks there
We need you amish hulk credible hulk
The credible hulk
I just borrowed that from a chat member. Um, apparently the hulk are a real thing in 40k
So I accidentally what chat when you have lore the size of 45 bibles
There's going to be something for anything. You just save something and you know, what is this? It's probably true
Everything's make-believe words guys. Oh I can stab
The blimpticus are real
I'm so glad I can see
My god this environment
Although those people
What was oh those are on our side. They're like the ones sending us in or basically the suicide squad, right? So
They're like, oh, okay
That's right. Yeah, because you yeah, I know the prologue, right?
And you can appreciate the level with all the lights in it, I guess I can hit fire
I don't have to just stabilize it
It's nice that I can like switch to a weapon that doesn't have a flashlight now
This thing is so much better than the thing. I just was using
By a long shot
No, is that the three round burst one? It is. Yep. Yeah, I like that one
Maybe i'm just not using the other one correctly
Actually shouldn't even be using it right now
Oh, your voice is terrifying. I love it. I need I need a little help guys. What's up, buddy?
um
There's just some dudes that were just I I don't know one guy this guy giving me trouble they hurt
All right, i'm good now, thank you
You need to block and shove occasionally. Yeah
I don't block and shove and i'm doing just fine
This thing is sec
Oh criken, do you like um, do you like city builders?
city builder
I don't know builder d's nuts like any city builder type game. Oh my god. He got me you're right
Uh, oh you mean like um, just the genre of games in general. Yeah that genre
Uh, yeah, I I played uh, let's go
Okay
I don't know if I got a game. I got a game recommend my channel. Oh god. Here we go
Well, I got a good game recommendation. It's a city building rogue light that I think you might like
Shit, they're too fast city building rogue light. Yeah, it's really cool. It's my favorite game of the year so far
Aside from elden ring
Really?
Yeah
What is it called?
Um, I don't want to seem like a shill
I'm not a shill
I got a movie recommendation for you, but i'm not gonna tell you I can't tell you my chat will get angry. It's so awesome
No, it's called against the storm. I love it. I've been playing like every day. It's really good. Nice
Yeah, i'll uh, I just want to see more people succumb to the addiction of that game
I think there's so many games that not recently i'm like struggling to keep up i've been playing this so much
It's like the first hour and a half of a sim city game
And then you just keep doing that and it gets more complex and it's wonderful. I love it
Uh, can you guys do my favorite talk about this game? Oh, yeah
Um, excuse me about this one
Man
It's funny because you really have you've been like you've been playing this a lot, you know everything
Look, this servitor was turned into a typewriter
Yes, yes
Hey, don't shoot that. This is my new favorite. I like this game because in it you get to shoot
That's true
I like this game because it seems like hold on a minute. We've got an issue
Handle this
Our servitors by choice, uh turn into typewriters. No
Okay
It's usually if you've done a crime like stealing apple
or
You know
Bump into the wrong person
Oh my god
So in the warhammer universe like every minor thing
Like not like overly minor crimes, but you can get turned into a typewriter. Yes, that's so ridiculous
like the
You know, like when you're doing that personality quiz to fill out for your character
Those were like how you ended up in this situation, right? That's no one for mine was like
I
Complained about the taste of corpse starch, which is what everyone's given to eat is literally like melted down people
And I was like the corpse starch is kind of bad today and someone overheard me
And then you got arrested. Yeah, that's how I run my
Colonies people just throw a fit about their bedroom and I just don't like give them peg legs
Yeah, and uh, not to talk about another game for too long
but in rimworld my chat kept wanting me to get the the
The one where you could make people into like
Milkable like colonists mod. Did you ever use that mod?
Uh warhammers takes place actually guys
in
4100 millennia the textures are great in this area and
The boss we're about to fight here is who is it again? I would probably just do I don't know but is he milkable?
Probably um, hey snot you might want this
Yeah, I just feel bad the server the server doesn't want to be here
So if we complete the level finding all these scriptures, then they get bonus exp and money
There's a lot of people over there and i'm in trouble
Can I use this? What?
It's like three stop shooting our hulk
Can't count the on three though, I guess that's
Makes sense
This thing is so fun
Can I press it? Oh, wait, I don't think I should have pressed it that
Prested that
I'll press the button. Why I should have should have pressed it that why am I turning english?
No, you're role playing you're fine
That's the credible hurt
I know i'm the same boat as you
Who's gonna get it first you can have it. No, you can have it
You know, do you take it take it
Okay, fine
Yep
Yeah, I guess I think you you need it more than I do because you have more suppressing fire than I do
I like that because even when i'm missing i'm still suppressing and i'm missing the most of them
Oh meta bullets pressing fire machine
behind you
Behind you flame
Yikes. Oh god, i'm running behind you. You got a tox flame. I'm the tank. Why am I running flank?
That's another horde criken. Why is the fire green?
Bokeys on your sex
Because it's a tox flamer not an actual flamer
Are you using toxic flame?
Oh, you're toxic get off the server
I'm chasing this freaking guy talk more about warhammer
What's the lore of this symbol above the door
Why is the symbol of the emperor?
Why do they have chainsaws on swords?
That didn't kill him
chainsaw swords
I'm down
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming
Ask criken about the arco flagellants for a good time
I think your chat may assume I know more than I actually do
Oh, no, you can just make it up and i'll yeah, you're right. You're right. I'll make it up. Uh, ask me then
Well, um, tell tell me about the arco flagellants. Oh
The arco flagellants. Yeah, so that's actually
a sect of
purple
inquisitors that
slap each other
in the arctic and
That's why they're called arco flagellants
It's nuts. I think we have to be in here, right? Yeah
Is the up human more than beast or mutant train
Somebody said why do I keep making the bat chest face? I haven't made the bat chest face once this whole entire day
He's just having a great time criken my audience one of my chat members said that you were 50 right? Hell yeah
You got that close
Are there clowns in this universe
Actually, yes
Insane machines by implement implanted weapons who constantly feel pain and regret in combat. There's there's like a
an assassination like
Order of clown masquerade elf people that like are an army that fight chaos don't don't they're gonna be don't the dark eldar
The dark eldar like torture each other right or something. They're they're like the most bad guy bad guys. Yeah
They torture each other
Do they want to be tortured? I I don't know maybe
After a certain point, maybe you start to like it
I don't I have no I all I know is I remember they were just like torturing each other and like tortures and shit
I wouldn't like that
Uh-oh
What's that sound?
Oh, you're about to find out what?
Oh
What does that mean? I keep getting like
It sounds bad though, doesn't it? Yeah, what's this?
Uh, what's that sound?
What i'm waiting for the game to do the real
Oh, no
Kind of reminds me of that movie event horizon, which is also not warhammer 40k
What is it you hyping this up for no reason what oh my god
The guy with two saw blades for hands
Oh my god disgusting i'll shoot on the back
Oh
Give him a purple nergal
On the back the puss the pustule on the back just puked on me
I like his hair. Oh my god. He's eating
What
Um, okay that happened that just happened there we go there we go interesting
Cool
Now we should eat him
Yeah, that's sort of like a payback
I'm pretty sure you would have every infection by now. Yeah
Oh my god, that just happened
God damn it. You said that unironically
I did say that unironically. I like that. That's what I was talking about before. I love that, dude
That's the thing about you man. You're just a walk in marvel script
I
Weird guy another weird guy. I need ammo. Oh my god. He's breaking every bone in my body
I remember your ammo. I don't have scripture right now. I've got some ammo here guys
Hey, thanks. Thank you. You just saved us that actually is saves us. No problem guys. Oh, that's so much ammo that I needed
I'm just happy to home. I think smush should
I've been you should probably take this I have more I think so. Yeah, I have two and a half bars
Okay, thank you. I just don't even ask anymore. I guess I can I can do it right? How many times can you use this thing twice?
uh, it's the amount of hips you see like a little uh, oh
Yo, I just so
I just so you look at I just healed and look at my health
Because somebody just ate a shot from a slaver because we keep getting eaten in the head. You know what?
I just killed a sniper
I was a level one player in any br game
I just was like, oh, I just picked up an item
Oh, that's really interesting. I wonder what it does and if you stand still you're dead. I really just got sniped in pub g
Watch out behind you
What's that?
Flamer somewhere. I don't know if we got him but oh, he's still here. Is he oh lord have mercy
You're good
Don't worry guys
He won't be burning anybody alive anymore
Last deal, but you take it
Well, that just happened
Uh, does anyone else see this?
Uh, you're gonna want to see this. What are we looking at? What are we looking? What are we? What are you doing?
I don't know. I was a bit
They really should hire me for the e3 things man. You can't say shut up and then do plus two
That's not how it works
Uh, we could do it. You guys want to do an e3 segment? Yeah. All right
We got a shotgunner
good shot
tagging
Reloading we're all clear. Maybe not. That's a little much. I mean, that's not quite e3. That's like just the game generic
I'm an npc in the video game. I thought that was in the game cover me convincing. All right
Okay
We're going through
Once this opens on the other side of that portal. I don't know
It's looking a little scary though
one guy right there
Nice shot. Nice
We got another one coming 12 o'clock. Nice job at 12 o'clock there
Two healing station as well
Nice work. German 985. Thanks a lot. Fine sauce. You need the healing station
That's okay. I'll take it
Now you're going to take it. I think you need a little bit more than we do
Oh, that's better
I might need it too
That was close, wasn't it?
was
On your left
Thanks. I'm imagining a horde's gonna come out here soon guys. Just be ready. Make sure you have enough ammo
I'm ready. It moves right here
We need one more scripture lads and then we get them
Experience i'm thinking of throwing a grenade down here, but let's uh, i'm gonna do somebody cover me before I do it
on your back
Watching your six
Thank you. That was a close one
Uh, I got a pizza in the oven
All right, you want to take five
I bet you'll enjoy that when we're done with our match of warhammer 40k
Hey, hey come back with that pizza man. There's a lot of freaking zombies here
This is not part of the script
He actually left he's uh, oh he's he's actually it's all right guys
What is he
He's doing some kind of joke. It's not done yet. It's not quite done yet
Of all times. Well, welcome back german 985. Thanks, man. Appreciate it. I got a uh,
I got 70 ammo so i'm good to go on that front more ammo here
Big guy coming through here big guy coming through
i'm unloading
All right
Six o'clock and 12 o'clock. Thank you. Nice job down
On your six group on the left. Could that be a sniper?
could be
Also, also, I know that we're recording for the e3 segment
but like don't fucking talk about that shit like I was hungry like
They'll edit this part out. But like seriously guys like if i'm hungry i haven't eaten all day
So just shut the fuck up about it
I haven't eaten since fucking like eight o'clock shut the fuck up
so fucking annoying
Yeah, I mean just
All right. So we'll just get back into it. They'll cut and go come back here for this part. Hey got some ammo
Sorry, can we start over to start over to start from actually it's probably it would be better if you walked from the red room
Over there. I thought you wanted us to start the sponsorship stream over
Uh
Come on this boy you got this e3 gig coming up. Come on get it together
Game awards are coming up lads. We got to practice for it. All right, three two one
All right, we're in the elevator
Uh guys, I need some help
Yeah, we'll find some in a second here, man
Nice shot real chat member. Nice shot. Thank you
Trying to stick together guys. We shouldn't get split up here group up
It's a good call the closer we are the better cohesion we have
That's right. And that's how you recover your toughness. Yeah, we've recovered our energy that way watch out over this way on the left
Group up gunner down
Did you know you can nice shot? You were always the best shooter in crouch. You were always the best shooter of the group
Are we talking to you? You can do a tactical crouch if you run and crouch and
All right, that's enough i've had enough of this
I started getting tense in there. I've never seen e3. I don't know
Wait, hold on. You've never seen e3
Yeah, what do you know what e3 is?
Is it like a movie? What does e3 stand for?
Charborg were you just actually playing the game and talking to us? Yeah, I thought that's what we were doing
That made that whole routine 10 times better. That's so awesome
That's amazing for entertainment entertainment entertainment
Oh, it's like e to the power of three. Yeah. Yeah, what does it stand for entertainment expo or something?
Electronic entertainment excellent excellent party time party time
Entertainment entertainment entertainment. Well, if it was e to the third power wouldn't it be like
Entertainment like times like 50 or something entertainment three
So wait, what is that? That's nine entertainments that we know I had it wrong three
Yeah, I was not a math person. I don't know math neither. Neither was I
Guys, I have a book. Can someone tell me what to do with this?
Oh, yeah, we need to if we get all the books to the end of the level then we all get a bonus experience
Yeah, so, um, it's like noam chomsky. Yeah
Wait, there's an actual gnome
in uh in left 4 dead
I did the environments actually are really cool
it's very very
Well made I would say the music in this uh, like oh
We only have two of the three books though, like just yeah
Do you still get um, we get partial credit you do
All right. Sorry. I need this again, but my dude just likes to die. It's his favorite hobby
Oh, I can only carry one of these. Oh, I need actually anybody need ammo
As I kind of do
Yeah, it may as well throw it down
Oh my goodness
Wait, um, the the music in this part is very good. Is it is it hype? Yeah
I heard a hype dog
I thought that was the beginning of the song
Was the dog I thought it was like like I thought it was like barking. Yeah, it's actually who let the dogs out but
Uh
Was it like rasta boy or something I don't know who was that
Some good boys
The bahaman
Was the one bahaman or multiple? Oh, we have to get rid of the gross probably lost the time
Yeah, we gotta go down here now. It's it's unknowable. Let the dogs out
Ah, it's fine. Oh my god
What what is this thing? I'm too big
genuinely
We should group up for cohesion. Yeah, we need to we actually need to group up for cohesion
Across the map this side
Oh
They never did figure out to let the dogs out did they?
No, it's a real shame
Ah, all right. I gotta take care of these guys. I'm going in
Where are they?
What did you guys say? I don't know
That dog was fast
Whoa, just dodge. Oh, yeah, that's right
Oh my god, throw his grenade into on the big eyes for a free shirt
But I was reading chat and I got the freaking grab. Can you can you get your head in the game language?
Excuse me
Copernicus
Don't you have something to invent? It's pronounced copernicus
Did copernicus invent something or was he just like a physics guy? Like what did he do copernicus?
Did he discover the apple? I think he was the one that was like, hey guys, we're in a solar system
They're like you fucking liar
Yeah, yeah, they called him a jerk. Yeah, we need to kill the we didn't hit this thing in the face
All right. I'm getting hurt here
He was yeah sun is the center guy and they're like, you know, you know, it's in the warhammer universe
Now is the sun the center of the no because they're they're like a galactic civilization
The emperor is the center the moon's center of the universe. Good answer. Good answer. Good answer
Number eight everyone there are that's a lot of people
I know where I know where like a little health thing is i'm going on a mission real quick. I'll be right back. Oh, no
What are you we getting a pizza?
Yeah, guys, I smell a pizza coming from down this hallway. He's he is fucking so dead
Is he gonna make it
I got the cysts. Oh
Oh
Oh, sorry, we'll be there in a second. I was just killing some cysts
Um that scripture dropped
Yeah, I want to go back and grab it
Does this heal? Oh, it is healing who did this?
We did this
You're awesome
I'm gonna just tactical slide into it
Oh, we stopped doing that bit
Um, yeah, where'd the scripture go smelting?
Yeah, where is it? I don't see it. I grabbed the scripture. Oh, I grabbed it. I grabbed it
Oh, okay. I see
I can't wait to get out of here and read this book guys
Yeah
Whoa
Gotta push your way to the other side
This guy's got my shot a lot of health
Thanks, man
I might pick up the organ. Do you see how fucking cool this looks?
Is this molten like steel? Oh, this is gonna get hairy though
What just said me after taco bell?
Can you push it? Oh, you can push him in you can shove them in
That's a good play. Well, yeah, I think it's the uh, you want me to walk into it. No, i'm not doing that
Wait, it might heal you
I almost did for the bit then I realized I had a scripture. I'm not doing that
Thank you
There's a lot of people right now
I need a sword for better crowd control. I want like a big axe
The axe is really good for like, um bosses and like powerful targets, but there are weapons that are more designed for like crowds
Yeah
nice
Nice, how many books what's our book status?
Does it show how many kills you had because I definitely was number one and I want to prove it and see it
I don't think they've added that yet, but apparently it's on the way
Oh dang. Yeah, I was probably up there
Too bad we can't find out i'm just kidding forgetting. I used my ability one time that entire match
Really?
Yeah, I need to I
I just keep forgetting
Oh, it does show kills now. It does total for everyone. I think yeah. Oh cool. We had exactly 100 a thousand exactly 1000
Oh, wait. No, it was a thousand. I missed a zero. That's pretty rare
It's got to be rare
That's got to be rare. That's a good omen
Oh my god, I have a grenade
gauntlet
Oh, yeah, those are fun
That sounds fun
Ah, sweet. Just got some fresh loot my drops aren't loading. Um
Uh, maybe refresh maybe you have to reconnect your uh account or something
This should be on can we confirm that the drops actually have been on and working they're working. Okay
Yeah, mine was only working on mine. Cool. I really I would like to get your drops as well. I got two drops
Cool. Oh, I have a cutscene. We're back. Ooh, I don't have a cutscene
But i'll be right back in one minute
Yeah, so this is um
This is fun. I like it
I have a cutscene, too
I already saw this one
Executed for less this unit will request permission to do so
The recruit is expected to achieve competence in regard to technical apparatus
I'm curious about this
In order to perform their duties at the maximum level of efficiency
Because I think i'm level four, right?
Will most likely cause the recruit to die
Do check your pizza
It's all right
All right. You've started to make a name for yourself reach trust level eight
You've unlocked the shrine of okay, so there's the shrine
Actually, let me come back and say
20 of 163 on the oh god. That's a that's a very small amount. So idea
I just unlocked the ability to upgrade or do whatever this is
the shrine
Oh, I have this too, I don't maybe I don't want any of these i'm just gonna
You know, i'll just wait. I'll earn more money and i'll buy a different weapon when they refresh
Oh, because wait, what's consequent?
So it basically with this thing. It's like once you find a weapon you like
Uh, you can theoretically just keep upgrading it
Oh and it uses this, uh this currency
Where's that person? It's over. It's kind of right out the
See if we can find you
It's literally if you go to the big, um green room
And just if it is a hallway you just turn. Um, it's like it's literally like two feet away
Oh here. Okay. I see. It's like a robot this five or six slots. Yep
I don't think I want to do anything
Yeah, i'm worried to lock into something and start upgrading if I find something better. Yeah
You unfortunately kind of just have to level a bunch to get more options before you start spending the resources. So
I imagine you probably just get resources and it's not too terrible, right?
Yeah, they probably only added resources like a few days ago. Oh, wow. Okay. Yeah, that's still like that whole grind is new
What is this?
New perk i'll get i'll upgrade this
But if you guys want to learn how to get new cosmetics
I can explain that real quick
How do you inching ever so close to buying that grenade?
How may I serve plus five percent you want to buy the pants you can also earn them by doing achievements, um
And every class has their own achievements. So if you go to penances, yeah penances press escape go to penances
Uh class and then pick your class
And it'll give like a little description. So for me, it was like while dashing kill a mutant with a melee attack
And I got a shirt for that
Oh, I just unlocked a weapon, but I don't see it here
Kill three enemies with a frag grenade without it bouncing interesting and you unlock shirt for that
Yeah
I see
During a single use of volley fire hit the weak spot of four enemies with a weapon secondary action without missing a shot
Damn, oh some of these are gonna take me a while. Wait
It's I unlocked a weapon but
I don't have it and it's not at the store
So you unlocked a weapon class?
Oh, it's just meaning you can now buy it
But it won't be in the store all the time. I think because the weapons refresh. Oh, okay
But I think germa at level four or five. I think four you get a free weapon
Also, the shop refreshes in one minute. So if it's not in there now, it might be in one minute
Your pizza is ready
I'll go get it. Oh, hold on. I don't know if this pizza is real. Yeah, I just yeah
Yeah, I don't know either. Let me see it real quick
It's gonna eat the little bits real quick
Oh god
He did it. Oh hot fuck. He did it off camera
German scared of his own oven, huh? How was the za?
Um, it's frozen on the bottom and the top was burning hot that I've managed
I don't know. I have this little oven over here. It's only heats from the top and I don't know
I just put it in there. It's like an easy big oven. Vinny if you get the right components you can build
the
chevalma
Why do I think that's something like ligma?
Like are you tricking me into saying something chat member? Okay, so the weapon should probably be refreshed, right?
Oh 25 seconds
Make your final purchases
Ding ding ding if you see a rare in there, should you just get it or no there's gonna
It eventually becomes much higher chance for rares and purples and stuff. So so there are they like legendaries? Yeah, there's legendaries
Now you just haven't yet. You just started speaking my language here. Oh, yeah
Where are the new weapons gonna be? Oh what I see I see
one second
zero seconds
Oh new weapons different. Okay. Ooh
What does it mean that if it's on the black market? I don't know which one
ranged weak spot or ranged probably this one although the
ammo is
Terrible for this one. What do you guys think?
What I think wait, are these gonna be different for all of us? Yeah
Hey
chat
Autoguns are a trap really besides the brace braced autogun. Oh, okay
So maybe wait a little longer
I'm gonna save my money
Should I get a new flamer?
Or hammer? Oh shit. Oh wait, it's like a punch gauntlet like an explosive gauntlet or something. Very cool
How you guys doing you uh, you still around for another one video are you gonna take off? No, I I'm I gotta take off
I'm sorry. No, it's all good
Thanks for playing. It's been a very busy day. No, thank you for the invite man. I I like this game
I was probably gonna get it anyway, so i'm just yeah, it's awesome to play with you. This is cool. Um, yeah
Yeah, so have fun jerma. Um, i'll catch you later criken
Charborg you guys are great too. I hope to see you again in some sus sus among us
You got man, all right. Bye have fun. Bye guys
Uh, so do we have another fourth or are we gonna just do matchmaking or uh, I can pick some people
We can also uh, we might have I think I criken are these staffs cool?
Uh, yeah, they're like four staff. It sounds badass
I think they're like you can channel like a lightning or fire. I haven't tried it myself yet, but they look fun
Uh, how do I invite somebody? Can I just do it just from what you have to be later? Yeah
Anyone can invite within the group. Okay, cool, because I think
Uh, I think I got a yeah, I got I got one of my mods. The vr. Josh is done
So just go I can just invite him from here. Okay, so
um
Invite I think I just did it. All right, it'd be here in a second. Let me um, actually drag him into this call
There we go. Where did you save the little place to test the weapon is?
Yo, uh the meat grinder. What's up? What's up? Hello. Hello
Yeah, this is uh vr. Josh. Hello vr. Josh. Hello. I think i've met cracking before yeah in vr. Yeah
Yeah, I know vr. Josh. Did you get the invite? Josh? Yeah, I just uh got to get the game
Sweet i've already done the tutorial and everything. So oh so you're you're a seasoned player. I think then right?
Well, I mean I got the first tutorial round and then the first match they throw you into but yeah
Okay, cool. This is you i'm assuming right this uh virtuous
Yeah, okay. All right. So what mission should we do?
Well
I'd say once you guys get level five then we could start a or a tier three mission
It will be difficult at five, but if it's doable people are saying that
Mod busy we can do whatever we want
Uh, this is not just that's not how it works. There's not just one mod here
I can't find this training arena. Is there a refresher? Is it? Oh, okay. Prepare repair
Assassination was kind of cool. Yeah
Uh, we got depends if you want one with lights on or lights off. Um, I think lights on I don't think we're uh,
skilled enough as new players to handle the
Yeah, it also sucks because you can't use the like you can't use other weapons
Like just having to use the one gun with the flashlight. Yeah, I will say though
That is actually really cool mechanic to put in the game because they can just keep doing weird shit like that
Like oh today, um, uh grenades just uh fall from the sky every five seconds
Like they can do cool wacky shit like that. I think that's pretty cool because you said those missions are playable just normally, right?
Uh, yeah
No, I think there's definitely the potential for like a whole bunch of modifiers later on that's cool. Oh
Wait, oh wait, I didn't do I put my weapon on no you're in here. Oh, they're on here
Oh, yeah looks like it you can also put your weapon on if you press i and then you can equip it
Oh my god. I look so cool
If you don't look any different
What wait, where's my sword or my oh my god wait till we get in there guys you I if you didn't have a crush on
Me before you might just have one boy. I as soon as we get in there. I look so cool
And it's just like you have the same shirt and pants on you just have like a
A different weapon here. You'll see when we get in game. You'll see rest assured god
I can't wait to get some better clothing options though. I look kind of dweebish. Yeah cracking it. Did you buy that costume?
No, I did the achievements for it, which is like just doing special, you know challenges in the level
Are you learning to count
Learning to count by his fingers the servitors just like insulting the ogre
Yeah
So apparently in lore the smartest ogren can count to four
That's
That's really that's literally the smartest ogren out there can get to four
I understand what that fifth finger is. Yeah, he's working. He's working
Wow
Oh, he can only count to four on his fingers. Yeah. He just like your mouth
Oh my goodness guys. This is
Whoa, i'm like a wizard now look up at the skybox in this one. All right, that's pretty cool
This is the best weapon in the game. Yeah, unfortunately guys
Unfortunately, you guys aren't me. All right
Let me see, what do you got? Yeah, there's a there's a a space marine statue down that way
I'll go take a look
All right. Sorry chat the smartest ogren can write his name and count to 10. I was off by six
Look up
We're inside of a motherboard
I've said yeah
Yeah, so this is what the rat in my pc
They basically build cities on top of cities in this universe because there's just too many people and over time it expands too much
So that's just like another city up there
It's upside down or something. It is it feels like it's upside down. Yeah
Mirrored or something. That's weird
I would hate to live here, dude. I would get so bullied
This would be tough. I would get so bullied
I mean you you fucking go into school with your like staff and pajamas
I got my stupid little onesie on my my yellow onesie
Me
Yeah, I would yeah, they would instantly turn me into one of those servitor toilets
This thing is so cool. All right, and also it's also it's a melee weapon
What you're oh the oh, that's cool. You can just club them with it. Yeah
What I think that's so cool. You like the reason it's hand mounted is so that you don't misplace it
I remember hearing the lore. Oh, so it's like attached to me. So I don't yeah
You don't accidentally drop it someplace
I think i'm gonna be uh, i'm gonna upgrade andy on this one. I think
Yeah
Oh, it's got a forward punch as well. What's the charge?
It feels so good when you find a weapon that you like mesh well with, you know, yeah, that's how I feel about this staff
The game is changed. There's other staffs too. So like if you start using this one and then you try other ones later
Oh
Geez the call out of barrel
All the uh, the magic looks awesome from the staff cool
But I really feel like i'm doing nothing for the team here. I think it like leaves a burning area on the ground
That yeah, yeah
Yeah, that just happened. I
I didn't quite finish that part, but I did kind of say that you're right
Yeah, that
Just happened
God damn it. I think it's cool though. Just get a bunch of those and then just rotate the pool. You hear that. What's that?
Is one of the uh, the slime slug people. Oh, yeah, holy
Uh, we got a big one guys we got a you're gonna want to see this
He's slug now. He's coming for me
Why is he coming for me? Get him away from me
Leave me alone
You see that charlotte I didn't see it but I heard you scream, okay, where am I? No, he's
It's like when your dog gets a hold of something
We are hurt oh god what I wouldn't give to inhale some of this
Wait, what? Uh, yeah
I've been experimentally vaping. I just i'll just vape whatever i'm experimentally vaping
Vaping nergal gas i'm testing the limits of my body
That's so great
That's a very weird way to say I started smoking i'm experimentally vaping, you know just an experiment
Yeah, he's saying that he's vaping
Not like vapes though. He's like smoke. Whatever too. He's juicing. He's juicing. Whatever cricket
Oh, yeah, gross you ever vape a cricket
I saw a dude in a video who vaped like uh, like a chili pepper
He's still uh, okay. I don't know how I don't know how he's doing, but he did not seem to be liking it
Too much. I didn't like it. Okay
You're gonna blow some fat clouds, man
Let's go probably how he talked the rest of his life. Yeah, it just permanently ruined his vocal cords
It just kind of seeps out of you
Just your sweat becomes spicy anyone around you just starts like crying like an onion a walking onion
an onion
I can't wait to start
Doing body augmentations and stuff. Yeah, dude. Have you have you baked an onion yet?
No, I haven't I haven't yet
one day
How oh i'm in trouble?
Oh, uh tank i'm in trouble i'm in trouble i'm in trouble that's not a tank this isn't left for dead
Well, it's it's a
tanky character
There you go
Thank you character over here. Thank you character
Thank you. Oh my god the staff. I was born for this staff
Salt the same names, but in latin, right?
Different potato chip flavors salt and vinegar of vape
When they tried to
Barbecue vape barbecue
Sour cream and onion vape gross. Do you think you could like in your last will and testament be turned into a vape juice and have like
That's so weird smoke you yeah, they like juice me and then
I'm like concentrate roasted turkey vape
Dude, yeah, they're really missing out on doing a whole line of like thanksgiving themed vapes
It makes like holiday vapes like christmas vape partridge in a pear tree vape
Wow, I can really taste the partridge
I don't know what a partridge is. Is that a bird?
It's a bird dude if they made if they made a thanksgiving day vape it would be like let me try that one
Have some of it around the table. Oh
Your friend want to play and he's like no
I've got this and it's just a nasty thanksgiving turkey vape. Oh dude. That was that one was intense
Everyone's eating and enjoying their time and he's blowing fat clouds over the table
Is there enough for me?
Anyone got health i'm hurting there's literally a station right here snot
I really feel bad taking it from them though, because I because they're being tortured nothing else to do
Your devil was so gross and it's like add to cart like plus plus plus plus plus plus plus plus plus
I might I might go down this avenue. Do hardcore vapers like like the dank like
the stankiest
Vapes like what what's a good vape? That's actually a good question vape that stuff
Is it like green?
Robust oh you want to vape a tox flame? Yeah, all right. That's actually perfect
That's unbelievably funny plus plus a thousand to the person in chat that just said this
harry potter jelly bean vape
Oh where it's so gross. You never know what you're gonna get. Oh you wax gross
Is there some marshmallow or stinky stock vape?
stinky sock juice
That's so stupid
Black mold vape. What did you get man?
It just gives you like a terminal illness. Yeah, this one's either like like a licorice or
Black mold and then you try it and you just die about it
That's gonna that's gonna show up on snl now. We just yeah
a lot of people are
This thing actually is everything I wanted. It's awesome
I love the sound it makes
A little grenade. Oh, it's like a cannon. Yeah
It's fun to use
oh, so for this one, uh the
The thing is gonna go down and one of us has to use it to start a mini game turn it back on again
because right now
so
Uh, I got to do or let's have one of you guys do it and then I will try to wait
What the hell is this so you gotta click when it's highlighting over the glowy bit, right? Oh, okay
Guys i'm getting hurt real bad. Should we have let the person that can't count to four do this
Technically augerins are the slowest at doing it than ever anyone. Oh, are you really?
It's not there's literally one guy here. What happened? Yeah. Yeah. Well, there were plenty more but I managed to take them out
Oh
What is this get out of here? All right, i'm gonna i'll do it somebody protect me protecting
There's no one even here anymore
They got tired of us. I promise i'm not doing this wrong. It is really slow
Dude, I love this stuff
You may have any ammo when you were
Thank you guys think you can learn magic when you were younger
I would really practice telekinetic stuff
Do you tell me like real magic you wanted to move stuff? Yeah when I was little I really wanted to be magic
You ever get close?
I've been that same world
You did what in that same world when I was younger? I wanted to be a magic wand maker
Only like the all-even-under guy
But this is this is way before that though before he existed. You're like you invented the concept
Well, by the way, this is not like harry potter style magic this is I think magicians on stage magic
You know what I mean? It's probably a pretty big market for that
What is involved with making the wand like I don't know
I wish I could ask my former self little handkerchiefs out of it. There's got to be a secret compartment or two
Yeah, I need to brush up on like magic
Just like you wanted to be a magician you wanted to provide a service to magicians
Despite not knowing how the magic works itself. Yeah, I didn't know the first step of making it
Not to provide it not at all
Oh, yeah, I I just figured I wanted to be a magic wand maker not a magician
That's how you make the money in the magic world, right? So that's good business sense smart kid
Like the uh, the people who made it rich in the gold rush for the ones selling the mining supplies
Yeah
Very low, please
nice
Oh also looking for grim wars. I totally forgot to even mention that they're like little flowy books
Oh, that's where like extra. Yeah, that's for extra experience at the end probably already missed one, but
It's okay
No, I feel like we'll get all three this time. We're capable
All three out of two
Let's get some uh, I want more um
I want my ammo on this thing. I'm definitely going to upgrade it
It's addicting oh, here's that ammo right here
Just don't go shooting navigators or sanctioned psychers you get in trouble for that shut up
Geez, okay
Look at this. So a little
Uh
Like an embroidered pillow, yeah throw pillow
That would not be a bad existence
Unless it's painful
I'm sure it's very painful, you know, yeah, probably having your nerves bound to like metal would
Probably suck. I think like the process like most
Lose consciousness and like aren't sentient anymore, but some retain it somehow
and they're just like
Like I would be just I would still feel it probably yeah with your luck. Yeah
Hey
Where are you?
Who this guy shooting across the balcony over there?
Ammo here. Yeah, I think I got enough
I can't use ammo anymore. I'm now a spiritual being I cast I cast magic
That just seems like kind of a fun character
That seems like a fun character actually
It is it's pretty cool. I love this little spell
Oh, uh, is this healed? No, never mind just computer this way
I don't know we're down where they're at. Oh
Are we going the right way or you guys are going the right way? Uh, it's down here where snot knees
Uh, why am I the only one that gets snagged by this little bug zapper net? Oh, there's fire. Goodbye
This is the worst oh
I'm fine. I'll be fine. Wait, how did I get back up? I think you can help you can uh press e
grenade
But there's something green back here. Was that a tome? I think I got one of the
Oh you did nice
So if you die with it it goes
But there's healing over here
Or snot down. Oh down there. Yeah, what's that thing on the map? It's like a icon. What's that? Oh, yeah snot
You should get this too
Uh, what I can
Oh, it's the heal icon. Okay
Like I didn't even know he died
Everything you've told me so far makes me want to learn about the lore of warhammer
Yeah, right it's it's addicting once you like learn a little bit
uh, my two favorite concepts in warhammer are
like
Hive cities, which is where we are and then uh,
Just like how distance works and like time is really actually original and you can hit by the train
so like go through the warp and like
Come out years later. Sometimes like
Yeah, it's like inconsistent. Yeah
I don't want to waste em. I'm definitely falling down the uh, it's a servitor radio
Wait, let me talk to him
Nothing in there
Dude what a funny idea just like punishing people by turning them into shit
That is so funny. I want to be a little dude
I need to make an entire game about being a servitor
And you just stand around
Yeah
You just watch people go and have fun
I have no i'm not I can't hit anybody. Come on, man
It would be like prop hunt
But like you don't move
You're so so bad. No, you you wouldn't have said anything unless I said that first
I saw that
That person was running behind you
If i'm rushing ahead too much just let me know
Just like playing a speedy nice guy. No. No, you're good. Oh boy
Oh that hurts
There's ammo back here if you want
Watch that
I kind of I want to place the flavor guy eventually. Yeah, seems fun. He plays like the augering kind of like he charges in
deals with words really well
What am I doing?
Oh my god, I almost blew myself up. That's a lot of people
Holy shit, just shove them off
Oh, yeah, I can get there's a challenge for my character to shove a bunch of people off
Yeah, i'm gonna try that. I completely forgot about the challenge. Is it that's how you unlock pants and stuff?
Yeah, i'm gonna get a nice little pair of like a lincey aga belt
This music listen to this
I need that that's not very much ammo though. What the heck what the heck
success is
Warm
Yeah, I feel like that i'm like so worried i'm missing it
Yeah, the one I saw
It was glowing green like it was behind the boxes the other one
So as soon as we get out of here, we should gather around a little campfire and read the grim war
Oh, there's a lot of dorks over here help
A lot of dorks. Yeah, I bet you were a bully in high school. I think you're a high school bully
The guy the guy the guy that wanted to make magicians ones, yeah
Yeah, oh yeah, that's such I was such a young I was such a bully, you know the guy that wanted to make the match
What the fuck just happened?
We're all pretty freaked up, huh? Yeah, we need some healing does anyone have a box a cavernicus you do
I do but we might want to find an actual heal station
I gather around everyone box. Oh, that's helpful
Nice does that box not heal if you've got purple? Yeah, only these stations heal the purple. Oh lark
I'm taking all the ammo. I feel bad
I like using this one because I don't need ammo. I just i'm just channeling like energy
Careful, sorry. Sorry cavernicus. What am I actually doing?
Oh, I was running it
I thought you were getting mad because I was butchering the lord call it the right thing snot
It's called garbly chokes
My garbly chokes levels are low
Eat shit, you know what fucking i'm going in
I'll try and
Ammo never mind, there's no ammo here. I didn't find any your character said ammo time
Ammo time am I insane? I straight up think he said ammo time
I must have been a fucking glitch with your computer dude
That's weird
Does the does the bloom get more intense if you're very low on health?
I don't know
It's like my guy's like under a bar. It's uh
A little fuzzy around the edges now
Yeah, I feel like I just smoked a pepper
It's a big chest over here
All right, we can all heal here now
Guys they're trying to break in it's not heel is that them actually trying to break in
I don't know. Maybe they're like striking a table or just looking over here. They're doing something out here
It's a lot of really cool environmental. Yeah, this is the drum class
Yes
They're down there playing bongos
There's a lot going on if that's that's what I mean earlier when I said this just stopped going on
Let's see. Yeah, see no one was there
Oh, i'm gonna use this
All right, so for this one
We want to go to each of these trains right left and right?
Yeah, and then we open it and we transport the ammunition on it to the
Okay, this is gonna get it's gonna get weird
I think they're dead
What other kind of staffs and stuff are there coming from the other side? No
The face is so itchy
Get away from him
Uh-oh, I got netted. Oh, no
Good boy. They're taking us out one by one. They're netting us all I can't move
Oh, I see him. He's like trying to clear the space. Oh no
Thank you
Oh fire
All right, so oh we gotta open the rest of these up. Yeah, we open these up and then just throw them out again
What do I throw this brother? Uh, we're just gonna carry them in the
I'm gonna get this net guy. He's being a problem. Anybody have any ammo? Uh, no, I've got a book. Oh, here's something right up here
All right. I got this thingy damn copernicus
I just see you telling they're chasing some poor guy down. That was the netter dude
Oh, there's a couple more containers down here if we need them
Oh
Oh, I see what to take him down here. Oh stop
Yeah, so it's like up the platform like the landing platform. All right
So we're gonna get as many as we can over there, right? Whatever just
How can I?
I'm walking the stairs
How many do you need for that's all? Uh, it's just all of them
We have a couple here and then we have to get a get them to that
Yeah, so the augurans carry them faster than others so i'll pick it up is there be you want to drop it for me?
I'll take it
Ow
I gotta find a pit to push some people off and this goes up in the middle. Yep. Yep right to that pod up there
Why do you keep swinging to dead bodies because they make sure they're dead
Ha ha
I mean when you knock them over as an augurian, that's when you knock them. Yeah, sometimes they don't know
The flamer
Oh, all right, it's not got you
My life flash before my eyes
jeez
What's this? Oh
That guy threw the grenade and then his head was gone another swarm coming behind us lots of I think this is ammunition
All right
Oh, wait, is this the stuff we're supposed to be delivering? Yeah, it's me to find
He's gonna throw a grenade in here. Absolutely. Oh shit
Get out of this run through it. Yep. Got him. You got one here
I'll take it angle it up and chuck it further. Yeah, it's fucking all right. I'm gonna go get this grenade guy
You don't want to see copernicus when he's mad they won't
Don't even there's like three of them that's why
It's just I thought I could beat him over here another flamer
how
Put this out
Put this out. Are you blowing on it? Seriously? It was there for too long
Augur never learned to stop dropping the roll
Yeah
Oh you got that? Okay tunnel
I'm too weak. You got it. You have to do it
All right, i'll check it out there. Yeah, if you throw them over here, I can i'll grab it. Can I get it up?
Oh, wait, there we go. I think I got it. Yeah
I think that's the last one
Uh, we need one more
You're holding a big guy. Oh, I thought there was two slots. Okay, so we're good. We're good
So trouble if you shove people off this bridge, yeah
Oh, i'm gonna do that. Oh my god, this is gonna be so epic
Get to the helicopter
What's the lore name for it
Uh, that's a helicopter in the lung. Yeah, they just call it
Let's go. All right, i'm gonna bump them. Did I do it? That didn't work
All right, wait, we gotta be careful
Oh, they hurt they hit hard
Get in get in i've got to get on 20. I can't get on the platform
Can I jump the jump? Okay, there we go
No
Nice I got I probably got at least 60 or 70 there. I'm tired. You see me all tuckered out
Cool so we're gonna be level five
Yeah, you'll definitely hit the five
I just unlocked a dueling sword
Oh, wait, that one's super fun
It's like uh, you're basically holding it's like a you look a pirate. You have like a little cutlass
Oh really? Yeah, it looks so goofy. I unlocked um traits. That's like a skill points, right? Yeah, so those
Every five levels you can allocate you can change them whenever so you don't have to like respect or anything really and yeah, and they
Are like really good buffs for your class based on how you like to play them
Let's take a look
Do you guys want uh another fourth to jump in or?
Um, good either way, but yeah, i'm totally down for either. I I know uh stripping is available. Uh, germa if you want to see
Stripping's got a level 30 augren. It's really cool like the full
The full power of the eventual augren is oh my goodness. I just unlocked a new shirt
I kind of want to see that too. So i'll back out and let's trip enjoy and then we can see like what high level stuff
Looks like
Um, whatever. Yeah, I mean you want you want to do you want to just do one more and then we'll get stripping it
Oh, yeah, that's fine. If you want to do another one. Yeah, we'll do one more
You kind of want to see what like the high level unlocks look like
I only knocked five people off the ledge back there guys
Out of how many 70 I have to get 20
Okay
Well, what's this? I have to pick one of these two hit four. I don't know what that unlocks
Wait, I can change my can I change this?
Wait, there we go the feed if you just click on it, it'll equip the different one
Oh, I thought I could do something up here, too
Oh, no, those are that's just default. Those are default. I think for now
But eventually there's like gonna be other subclasses. I think so like i'm a zealot preacher and eventually you can be like a zealot
I don't know
Matic or something. So I gotta pick between these three. Yeah, I think i'm gonna keep my current staff
I feel like it's this one. I feel like it's the this one here
Just 100 toughness replenishment
That seems just great. What are the uh, there's little icons on weapons. I don't know what each one means
Yeah
See the oh inspect maybe inspect shows what they mean. No. Oh it does. There we go
If you inspect it shows on the right side what each of those icons mean
Flushed right down
Did I unlock any other clothes?
I got just a shirt on my guy and I look even stupider when I don't have the full
little onesie
People saying that I have a this is a dad shirt
Is that your new shirt that tank top? Yeah, it's just like a dirty tank top. I think it looks good
I think it's like you yeah
Oh everybody, let's go check the weapons because it could be new
Actually, hold on same weapons
20 minutes
For you carry with you martial tokens of the omniscience blessings
Got a new axe
Oh
So is the only way for me to get that little sword we're talking about kraken is if it just
Is in the shop like when it refreshes?
um
Yes, unless did it say emperor's gift and
the end of the match
Um, I don't really read I don't do that
So if you check your you might have it because sometimes at the end of the match you just get a free weapon from
the emperor
Because he's very generous amazing. Yeah, I don't think i'm gonna buy anything. I just keep what I have
What the?
Family reunion. All right that that was a 3d movie. I've had 3d glasses. That'd be crazy
Yeah, I think are you guys gonna go?
Yeah, i'm ready. I believe so we could do a lights out one
I don't have a flashlight anymore. I sold the gun with the flashlight. Okay, that'd be the only one maybe
My guy's so ugly
Does the barber let you do like full cosmetic change or just hair?
uh
This this haircut just makes me look like such like a goofball
That's like your mom gave you that haircut
Have you seen where the barber is?
Yeah, I I had something else before maybe you can get one similar to mine
Yeah, somebody said I have the mo the three stooges cut. Yeah
Uh, i'll keep it. I'll keep it. So what's this one? Uh, this is the normal one. Oh no lights out
Oh, look at that new shirt
Okay
And there's snot
Hi
Hi folks. I wonder if eventually you can get
Big armor pieces or something. Sorry. I didn't do my feets guys. Give me a second
You guys you guys fan of feet you got 35 seconds. Oh brother
Um, you better check stuff. Exactly
Are these passives or do I have to do something?
They're passives
You just have to select one of the three and it just will be on you permanently. Oh my god
There's too like there's too many words, dude. I thought I'd just pick one at random
We said just remember do you dye your hair? No, I don't this is
Weirdly enough and this is actually a good thing. But you know, obviously knock on wood
um
I don't have any gray hair
And that's a little concerning because i'm getting a little older
I'm not looking forward to when I look in the mirror and there's just white hairs here. We'll see
Yeah
Let's move. We look so cool
We did just look really cool
So it'll be the same kind of layout, but will the mission be the same every time we'll change it up
Yeah, usually the things that change are the secondary objectives and
Whatever other modifiers around the level
You end up doing the same mission a lot
So I guess like any of those other modifiers, well, I think after this we can probably try a level three
Especially if sam's joining
Well, it's also I mean the levels are they're supposed to be played over and over again. That would be yeah very different
I feel like a dark modifier from two to three is very dramatic. Yeah
Change a lot of it. Yeah. All right. No, i'm not gonna waste any ammo not like last time
Wait, are we looking for grimoires again in this one?
See the mission thing it's just the last time it appeared I think under the main objective
No
Kraken, can I get a lore update on what i'm looking at here?
Did I miss his I punched what?
disco ball
Oh, no, wait a second. There's a skull on it. This is a sever
Test in past
Right in the teeth
Already ammo
cool
So kraken, do you have any do you have any blues?
Uh, yeah, so you have blue right now
I have one purple
You have a purple
Yeah
You can
I mean at the level you're at you start getting purples
Oh like purple weapons. Yeah
It didn't hit oh my god, what's your favorite bit of warhammer war?
uh
oh
I
What's that sound?
Okay, cool
I like just the concept of like
so the the empire
you know colonizes thousands and thousands of planets and then
Some shit goes down and they basically can't travel for like a few thousand years
And so these planets these colonies just don't hear back from
You know the emperor for thousands of years
And then they show up one day and they're like, all right time to pay back the back taxes that you owe
Everyone's like no, fuck that and then they just burn their planet and take it back. They're like, no, fuck you. This is our planet
Oh the empire
Exactly. Sorry. I forgot I was streaming
I was just like blocking in playing
This game does that man. I just like
How are you still alive shit, uh, there's a lot of people over here
with the actual
Too much magic. Oh, right. That's the thing. I forgot to pace myself
Thanks for the help fellas
I actually need that
Sorry, uh, you get the next one
Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, you probably needed to do though. We have to share it to find a big uh, ammo case somewhere
I think that's like a full ammo refill for everyone. Yeah, here's you know
Oh
Oops, you're a person
Did you just shoot? Oh, there's a tried over there
grenades anybody grenades
Ammo here for you smush
That's a good question are there any dances in the game not that I've found
We could come up with one like this. Oh, yeah
Oh, wait, there is actually hold on. Is there ready? Yeah, look at me
Wait, I did it wrong
Oh, it's a slide can I do that if you run and slide and then spin around looks freaking sick. Yeah
Cool that was pretty cool
Oh, oh, he actually calls out who has the lowest ammo. I guess
Yeah, that's cool. Oh, if you actually look uh next to all of our names, there's a little ammunition
Yeah, it's fine based on the color of it is how much ammunition. Oh like the game automatically like called out big man
Dog just hit a front flip
All right, don't waste ammo. Let's stop it. Okay. I just love shooting the grenade. Wait, can I heal on that thing?
Yeah
I don't know if there's any left. Yeah
I'll get it
What the hell was that?
He just got his head shot almost all the way off
He shot me through the wall. That was so that was sad. Prykin? I'm gonna take care of him
Prykin? What? You all right? Yeah
Okay. All right
Wow, it hit me too. Be careful. Where is he? I'll shoot him if I can find him. Oh, there he is. Got him
These guys are jerks
This guy I managed it on hard and harder whatever those things will kill you in one hit
That's probably sad
Okay
Let's go
Oh, yeah, maybe modifiers in general make more of the uh hard enemies
Oh
Oh boy
Oh, okay. Uh, no, come here, please
I thank you for killing that guy because I couldn't yeah, I definitely should not do that. It's way too slow
What are you doing the hacking there's a little mini game in
In this fight that you have to do. I bet snot would be pretty good at it
Yeah, you should get it. That's nice
Does that actually affect the speed of the little bar like your class? Uh, the auger does. Yeah, it's just slower in general
Oh guys, i'm not gonna lie I tried to do it but I didn't know how to
All right. I'm guarding you snot go for it. Okay, big guy. Hey guy. Oh, yeah, we've got a just a typical hack here
Yeah, we got the uh motherboard might be fried on this one guys
What's wrong with it? Uh, oh
Yeah, it just needs some. Oh, there we go. Need a little tweaking. I got it guys. It's one of those 4090s with the uh
High voltage pin, right? It catches on fire. Yeah. Yeah, exactly that you nailed it
Isn't the 4090 like as big as uh, like five bricks laid on top of each other basically, yeah
As much power as a typical household
That's what they use to wipe the cold winters to warm the winters in this universe
4090s. Yeah
It's mr. Krabs
Right into the fire
Uh snot more uh more hacking up for you if you want. All right, let's see what I can do
Game is fun as fuck
Yeah, I like this like especially what you said after getting a weapon. That's more your play style. Yeah
That changes so much
Okay, getting this uh axe versus the shovel like i'm actually killing people with melee now, which is nice
Oh snot need some gatorade i'm getting hurt
My electrolytes are all screwed up. Mr. Krabs is my favorite warhammer character
They're actually the slaneshi demons all have like crab claws and tentacles and shit do they yeah guy's throwing a grenade
Is he still alive oops
Don't help him let him think about what he's done. Yeah, he's got to learn the hard way
I start pinching his fingers. Yeah, just start like stepping on my fingers
Yeah, it's been like three oh
Oh, I thought it was only when the power was out. I thought it was the powers up. I'm gonna break them. I'm gonna break them
This is bad guys. This is very this is very bad. I would say
Oh snot's down too. I put down healing
Uh, what no he's choking you. Yeah
I don't know if we can kill him in time. Where's the healing?
No more shouty
Where'd he go? Oh, he's gone. It's like a witch. I guess
Other than that dark mission I guess where you have to kill it
Wait, I disturbed him
No, I did buddy. Oh, we lost two. He's dead, too
He died separately he died unrelated cut we have to rescue
Natural
Wow that fucking hurts
I'm gonna pass you a note. We're gonna go rescue
All right, we're good. Yep. We just gotta keep up keep ourselves alive until we just run it
Where are they down here up ahead? Yeah, they're both down there each other
Oh, we got a swarm of dudes. Oh my goodness. All right grenade
Don't yeah, i'll get him. Oh, that was a lot of bodies
I should need you. Glad you were close
Does anyone need ammo right now? Uh, I do
But if you need it more than me, I can use the knife. I have a I have an ammo box
So I can the bag. Oh cool. Yeah, I definitely need it then
Let's find a good spot where we can all get something
Right here
Oh, wait, do it. Did I I thought I did maybe I guess that wasn't what I thought it was. Is it healing?
No, I guess it was just like a big bag of ammo
Like yeah, still not familiar with what all the pickups look like like that. What is that?
What's happening giant raid is a raid who raided what happened
big raid
Huge raid. All right. Who was it?
Somebody said there was like 40 000 people. Are you serious? Who did it?
Thank you. Whoever it was
Who raided me with 40 000 people?
Oh, you're just bullshit. This was where I saw the book last time, but I don't think we have that mission, right?
No, we don't have any
You got a
Medical thing here. Oh bag. Yeah
Ow
I can do that too
I missed oh my god, that fucking hurts so bad
So is there a sound right before they fire? I I need to i'm not dodging them. I really need to dodge them
I need to remember the dodge even exists
I got one of the dodge
Excuse me, who's shooting me? There's another sniper. I think you got him
Never mind, I thought there was an outside area. There's just this giant lit up area
sanctuary
Okay, we do have an ammo box. I think we need it, right? Yeah
You missed them all they were here
It would be kind of sad. I want to push these guys off one sec to watch this
Sorry
doggy
Where are they pretty good in this game? Yeah
Oh my god, why can't we kill this dog?
Are you trying to get the push thing? Oh you're trying to do the shove. All right
Dar that's that would be so sad if 40 000 people rated and the view count did not go up by one viewer
They all left immediately. They didn't like that. That would be very sad actually
Dude 40 000 people raid. All right, here it comes. My view count goes down
That would be sad
That was a really bad idea and i'm i'm muted in the comms right now. So they're probably like what is he doing?
I'm stuck
Okay, I gotta mute. Sorry. I was muted. Oh, no, they left too
Hello
Oh, that was weird. Oh wait, did it sound like we left?
That was very funny because everyone just said that a raid of 40 000 people came in
And they would I mean there was chat was just full of shit
They were just like oh huge raid like 50 000 people i'm like who the fuck is doing that who's live right now?
And then you guys weren't like they were like, oh they all left and then like that was bull bullshit
I come back here and you guys aren't here
So it was like weird going for like an hour. Yeah, you looked over and you're streaming
Just to a party of zero and you've just been alone
That would be terrifying
Do you guys have stress dreams about streaming? Yep
worse
The classic the you i'm i'm live while i'm lying in bed and I didn't need to be entertaining you want to go around
Let's go around the uh, let's go around the table here. What's what's your what's your like nightmare stream dream?
I was actually the other day
I was thinking about how lucky I was because I have stress dreams about like school stuff
Like i'm trying to like find my class
But I was like, you know what? I was telling my chat. I don't have
Stress dreams about streaming that's I feel like I should have by now and then like that night
I had a dream that my camera was on
And I like was basically face revealing on accident
But I was trying to cover my like I was trying to cover my face
I couldn't move from in front of the camera. So I was just covering up my different facial features, but I only
Oh really?
Yeah, it was like I was covering like only my mouth. Oh my god. No, they can still see my eyes
It's like a thousand people just spawned
What the hell
Whoa
Get off him
Dude, I keep having the same stream nightmare stress stream. Really? Yeah, and it's it's happened like at least four times
I keep having it
so
I'm I'm naked from the waist down with a webcam on
And I stand up and I realize oh shit. I'm naked people probably see my you know, you know
And I freak out and nobody in the chat says anything
And then I go fuck normal
Well, no, it's just like because i'm like did I show my did I did that just happen because i'm naked right now
And like I stand up a little too far and i'm like, wait a minute
Is that what that was that on in frame in my webcam view?
And then I I don't and one or two people in the chat will say oh my god
Did anybody see that and i'm like fuck
And I go back and look at the vod
And I go wicked slow frame by frame and I see that I just barely get it in in frame
You just barely get your dick in frame. Well, hey, come on. This is where the spawn's free, man. Oh, sorry. Sorry
We can't say that
Anyways the warhammer lore. Well, can we go over that again? I haven't having a lot of dreams about warhammer
Yeah, dude. I had so many dreams about warhammer. I especially the uh
the
unbelievable down in warhammer
I wonder does the streaming exist on hyper worlds?
Yeah, there's a streamer
I don't know imagine the freaking impression. What is the entertainment like in the 40k universe? You don't really get that
Yeah, true. I guess no
Too grim dark for fun
I was naked in warhammer. I took both the crafting materials fight me for them
Well, they're shared so thanks. Oh, oh there's a health attack here and
Uh, i'm gonna hold on to it. What's your streaming stress stream cracking?
um
I so I talk in my sleep sometimes and
I have been told that when i've had a streaming stress stream
I'll like just randomly
Talk like i'm on stream like there's a certain cadence to your voice when you're on stream
You know and i'll just like be rolling around and then i'll just be like
Like hey, what's going on?
really
You do like you do like the youtuber voice in like you to sleep talk
Just while under the covers in the dark
Because i'm convinced that i'm on stream. That's I need to say something entertaining. It's really horrible
That's so yeah, that's so scary. That's so like stress inducing. Yeah, there's gonna be so many studies on on us
I'm sure like, you know years for now like this is done to our collective brains. How did a dog get in here?
That's how we doing man, i'm not a big sleep talker, but I did uh wake myself up with a fart the other night
Oh my god
And it was really embarrassing
I feel like my my farts aren't loud enough to do that
Oh your weak farther
I mean kind I mean, it's just like this. It's just
I can't get this guy off
Deficiencies in your diet. I think
This guy won't leave me alone
Leave me the fuck alone
Okay
Oh this part was actually kind of tricky oh shit i'm in trouble actually
So obviously the game the game looks kind of easy well we are not playing on any hard difficulty right now
This is the second one, but yeah
After this mission, we're gonna bump it up the level. I think
Sniper. Oh that hits hard. Yeah that where where is it?
I see him across the way. I got him. Oh nice shot
And I that was not an e3 presentation. I really mean it
The net gun uh trapper or whatever
That guy live
All right, i'm gonna take it
You idiot throw them up from up here if you want to come upstairs here you might uh, actually never mind
No, don't throw it over there. I can move pretty quickly with it. Right? That's one of my perks. Yeah. Yeah
Do we have any more inside this train? No, I guess that's all okay
So, uh, oh you're okay. I don't know
I don't know
I I was looking at chat and then I heard a drop he was just carrying the thing
Correctly, it drops it turns around winds up a big knife attack on my neck
Uh, I was startling
You guys are in trouble, all right
All right, we're good
All right, that's all them from this area
You're alive right now. I was gonna say that's why I always check people when they're dumb
I'm getting the rest of my push kills after this
Look at this guy's tummy
Anyone want to look at the tummy? I would love to
What the hell is wrong with you brody that's gross
Large enemy incoming wave. You know what? I'll say it screw these guys
Whoa
No, I agree hate all heresy in all forms
I think my guy got arrested for heresy, but it was like
Just like heresy. Yeah, like just a little bit of lighting arrest him again
Turn him into curtains
Curtain turn him into a nintendo 64. I want to have tons of fun playing mario
Who determines what they get turned into? Yeah, it'll be the most fun job
Just coming up this thing strikes me as a curtain the curtain rot. Let's make it the curtain
Okay, here we go
You guys are torn on that one
You should do a uh, they should do like an online quiz like personality quiz for which type of server you'd become
Yes, dude
That's what's up people need I think we're almost done, right?
I'm trying to get him guys
I can't believe I didn't hit him
All right, i'm putting the last one in
Watch out that sniper might still be up there. We got him. I got him. All right, we're good
Everybody make it to the extraction
You need to shove people again i'll try a little bit but I don't think the worst servitor options are
Maybe a bidet bidet. Yeah, good. I'm telling you toilet servitor would be awful just going
like blowing the fucking
Listen, I think the point was clear. I don't think you needed to make a fart noise
Oh guys, you're gonna have to go on without me. I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you
I got netted
Gotcha now we're split up watch out. There's fire. Oh wait, that's set up fire. Goodbye
Nice
Someone said imagine having to call the tech priest to fix your toilet
I don't know anything about war hammer lore, but is there a dude who just
Who deals with all the servitors? Yeah, the mechanics are basically priests in this so they just pray to fix it. Yeah pray to fix it
Oh, what a weird job. Oh, I got a foe rend mkv ripper gun
sword class unlocked
You know some might consider we have a weird job so we can't really be judging. It's true
I got ten thousand almost
Oh, no, that's just current. That's not currency
Hey, you guys feel you want to do another one?
Hell, yeah, let's get up
Yeah, he said he's around. Yeah, what's this dragon? That was fun though. Thank you. Yeah. No, thanks for joining josh. That's vr josh mod
He's gonna go back to uh
banning and timing out a lot of you fucking weirdos
I look over and she's like message deleted message deleted ban ban ban like he's just back in it. He's back in it back in the chair
I love how i'm getting defaced for that, but you guys called me a weirdo 20 minutes ago. It's not fair
They can dish it but they can't take it. I know it's not fair
That's really the chat experience in a nutshell, isn't it? They can dish but they can't take
It's different because ours is true. And well
You should start training them to like
like take abuse better
Just have like streams dedicated to
Just getting them used to getting roasted a little
We all have the same clothes
I'm going to the barber. I need okay. I'm gonna make a different haircut or something
I think you can rock it if you have confidence
Maybe a different beard. Where's the barber? It's over here somewhere. I just I just think I crashed my game
I think I exited this menu too quick
Where's the barber?
He's on the left side if you're looking at the green disney world thing. Does this cost money or no?
Barb is free
Oh, man
I think this is pretty good. Actually
I think that's I love it
Do they have many mohawk options?
They do actually I think they might yeah
All right. I like this so far
Kraken, can you invite me again on this night? This one actually I think is it
That's that one I made my decision you said your guy is good. I think so. I'm just doing some scars. Yeah
I thought about adding some scars, but am I in your game? I think you just joined it
Let me tell what maybe I can find some cool. Maybe I can get a new mustache
I was gonna have no tattoos
It's not as too iconic. Actually, I don't think I could change them
Oh wait, because the way he is I I have I can make my eye color different because of the
The home world i'm from oh you're from katia, huh?
Oh, okay. Where are you at? Let me see your new hair
Everyone loves katia
Kraken, how do you get the little gems the little gemstones to level up your weapons specifically the ones
That are like blue font. They look like a little cube
uh
Those are just rare the rare ones, but you can find them
Out in the world katia. Yeah
Oh
I got blues now. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, it's important
You have blue eyes
I got blue weapons available
to buy
Why this thing's just better? Oh, yeah, me too. I've got a little blue sword. Is this worth eight like all my money
It's a little bit. This is almost every cent that I have
That's the vicious cycle of this game. Hey
Hey, hello
Hello, i'm doing it. It's my buddy stripping. He
Is plays this game even more than me and has the giga chad augren
I want to see so bad. Do you know the lore stripping? I do know lore
All right
That's all that matters. How's the test? It's cool, man. I want to see uh, i'm also playing augren
And I I love augren and i've heard that you have a really cool augren
I'm very excited. He could be cooler. I've been trying to get this achievement done for some really cool armor, but
Uh, it is just too hard in the dark. I think
But the new stuff is uh is awesome
That they added today. Yeah. Yeah the power station
The witch like encounter freaked me the fuck out when I first saw it
I've only managed to kill it once dude
There yeah, especially in harder difficulties. I cannot imagine how hard it gets
So are we five are we gonna do the hard difficulties that we're about to do? I think we should do a three
Yeah, okay, we could totally do a three. Yeah
Uh, i'm gonna i've escorted these guys to the boss room. I'm gonna pretend i've dc'd good luck
Uh little small children, they're so dead and uh, let's go
Surely it's gonna go well
Hey, I think we're gonna be fine
I got my new weapon
Where are you at drama? What kind of weapons you uh you rocking?
I I got
i'm into the uh, the gauntlet the
Grenader gauntlet. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah with the special
Explosive punch thing. Yeah, that's pretty sweet
Uh, I just got this new knife, which is pretty cool
I'm just standing in front of the uh, the mission thing if you want to come look at me. Um
Charlie, I think you were saying it
You're at what i'm just in front of the mission thing the big um green
I like the fresh cut dude
You're rocking it. You think it's good. Yeah
I think it looks pretty good
I would definitely uh uncheck the box show helm if I had this kind of a hairstyle
Yeah, i'm not wearing no
Wait, where are in front of the missions?
Oh, where are you? No, we don't do it lights out tier three. That might be a little rough. That might be scary
That'll be great. Come on
We don't have many flashlights we found. Wait, what level what level uh, what level are these two we got? Yeah
Six or seven years. Yeah. Yeah, I'm like a 20 on my main. So uh
Okay, well it's not though. Yeah, it's not six
Uh, okay
Yeah, nice posture
Okay, we could do a three with no
Uh modifiers or we could try and do like a light
I think it lights out to you because you get extra xp if you do lights out. That's why it's good. But
I think they haven't done a three before we should try. Okay. Yeah, let's do a three in daylight if we can
Yeah, where it's a little intimidating because we've never we're very new
You guys will do fine
Okay. All right. I've been struggling. I will say
Maybe you got your new staff. Yeah, I got the staff and the new knife
And i've gotten a lot of confidence the first missions. Look at that shield. Where'd you get that shield?
Soon, you will have a shield of your own. Oh damn smush
Looking good. Yeah, I cleaned up a little
I just took the clippers and just went like this
Um a few times a bit. Yeah as well grew up about 25 years
You like you guys like my sword that last mission was that bad, huh? That you aged significantly
We've been all look at these two lads. Oh my god
I feel like we're pissed to be in the same room together here
I want to see a full auger and team in this hill thing. It just crashes in the low
Doesn't even make it to the mission
I've been in the full auger team and it was a hot mess. No, it's the boys
Yeah, we're gonna do the boys here. Do you have to be balanced like an overwatch team?
Uh, it helps it helps but you don't have to like for example, we don't
We need someone that can kind of take out snipers and I don't really see in this group
Oh, i'll i'll handle that
Okay
Wait, i brought the flamers. Oops. Yeah, I don't have anything to deal with them either. Jeremy if you want to take a look at my gun
Yeah, what do you got like this one
What is that oh my goodness
Wow
I got a cool grenade launcher on my arm. I actually enjoy that. Oh, those are our friends
This new map is also really cool
It's pretty
So this is this is on hard this is on uh, yeah three out of five
So what's after hard? Is it just four and five?
Four and five, uh, no one
in within the dev team
Has beaten five really? Oh my goodness. I don't know if any players have beaten five, but
Five is just insane. Okay. Well
We're on a three
If you get threes down, this is like the juicy
I feel like I should be hanging out with snot. This shit is busting. All right, cool
Yeah, you know what? I don't know what's I don't know what's I don't know what's going on with snob. I kind of want to kiss him
Yeah, i'm
Kind of known as the cutest one in the group has a kissable face
Are these enemies or?
Yes, it's a safe bet
We can try to make friends with them i'm sure they listen for reason
I knew you weren't dead. I that's why I always check. Yeah, so on this difficulty we get more specials in general. So
Oh
Are these the bad guys? Yep, this is my time
This is going to be perfect. I'm I can't wait to watch this
I'm not used to seeing another big another big dude. Yeah, it's actually I like it
You feel safer. Does it make you safer? I actually kind of do I do feel safer
Wait till he throws down that shield
Oh sniper i'll get help guys. I'll take care of this
Oh
Oh this look at oh my god, there's a lot of people here
Oh guys, i'm gonna blow up. I'm sorry
I was every time I play with a psycher. I hear that exact quote and it's like they already know it's too low. Oh my goodness
Oh shit, I got dog on me
Oh, this is no joke level three
Yeah, there's a big difficulty spike
From two to three
Was that flaming?
I
Didn't kill that guy
All right. We're okay
On level four you need at least one augren to even survive
Really?
Would you guys agree with that?
Yeah
I made a mistake, but you know what the like special ability the augren is. Oh, sorry
I didn't see i'm gonna tank this. Oh, no, he's in someone else
He's on he's on me he's on me he's on me
I'm gonna die
Maybe he'll be okay. Let's pick him up
No, he's dead
Okay, let's we need him to focus me
Guys i'm gonna blow up again
All right, i'll push myself too hard he's killing stop just gonna kill himself. Okay. All right. Yeah, that's fine. It's fine
shit
Oh my nerves
So he leaves after two, right?
Yeah
That was incredible it's not just gave himself as a fucking sacrifice
Yeah, it was almost wait. What just happened
So snot blew up because of his own mechanic like he overheated. Yeah while he was on the ground. Oh god
I'm stuck between two augren
Okay, okay. That's all right. Things are fine. I'm gonna throw a grenade
It didn't work for another grenade. This is a mess
Yeah
All right auger down
Sorry, I got us some more experience. I got us more xp for that
Yeah, we get for the kill
Oh boy, I love that shield. All right, there's two healing things
All right, you ready? I'm ready
The guy running that he was not really running to get away. That was very funny
Yeah, I think certain weapons like actually causes fear and they just flee
Like if you have a really explosive weapon or something
You're right. That gun is amazing. Is that purple or blue or any or what is it?
Uh, this one's a purple but you'll get this pretty soon, I think
Looks cool
That was very funny
Wait, that's me
That's you bud
Here you go
Oh my god. Thank you. It's good to be back. Nice
nice job
Yeah, this this difficulty feels
so much more like
uh intense
Somebody just called me washed up
What warranted and that person permanently jokes on them ogren's don't wash
true
More like unwashed up
Is there like a class that can heal?
No, it'd be fun to just be a little healer, dude
Get like self-heal stuff kind of as a zealot
But can't help it
Yeah, ban ban
We're doing great
life
Mods, can we dox this guy ban him for life?
Look how chilled this guy is
Oh my god
What sort of unfortunate situation occurred that led to this thing?
Why am I just shooting up here
I'm so I am so obsessed with how this looks
All the the game
Yeah, it's just like it's it's so far away
It's amazing
If you needed healing there's healing back there
Access is unpowered. I guess you don't know a if I say lifetime then it means 15 seconds. Oh my god
They're just throwing me like a little rag doll
Oh guys i'm blowing up again get away from me got him
Wait, oh shit. Oh shit. I'm sorry
I'm gonna give you a little tip here
If you're about to blow up save your ultimate if you use your ultimate when you're about to blow up it will discharge it
Is it for higher difficulties do you blow up easier this was not happening until just now
Um, did you only just put on that stuff?
I upgraded it recently
Like I don't know
Maybe i'm just paying less attention to it. Yeah, I think enemies are harder to kill so you might just be like i'm so fucking locked in
Basing it off of how many enemies I kill or something
Probably gonna happen again. I got like so locked in that I didn't even I was just like sitting here
The last like 10 straight minutes you just stopped talking to the chatter
Anything i'm just like i'm just I just I'm just like in my own head here. Just playing the video game you become an ogre
Yeah, that's what happens to me too
Yeah, dude when we started playing this like stripping first made chug
I I don't think you streamed anything else since then right sam like you've just been no just
chugged
Simple life like my uh, my wife
She pointed out that my sentences have become shorter
Just becoming an ogre everything has to be one syllable all words. Yeah, let's go grab the next one
Maybe ammo anybody need health. I kind of do i'm gonna put healing down over here. I need it
What causes the purple build up again?
going down, uh in certain
Enemies like dogs do when a mutant grabs you when a dog grabs you any of those kind of things
foxbusters
That guy. Oh
We're good
I didn't I didn't know that guy was gonna blow up on you. I just saw he was red
Yeah, i'm a bit of a i'm a bit of a too difficult
So do do you have that charge move as ogre or do you have something else?
I have that charge move. Yeah, that's um
When they add new subclasses that move will be different cool, but mine's like, um, I have an improved version from like my feets
But you use your bare feet
You know like the skill you got when you get hit five
Yeah
Yeah, so I have one of those at 30 that lets me uh charge twice as far and I can't be interrupted no matter what
That's cool
It's like i'm like, yeah, i'm gonna knock down all the big stuff. Oh, come on now they're all in
This new knife is pretty good
Oh, I need to try mine
What the heck is this?
Oh, it's a circuit breaker. Oh
I just splattered like a dead
Um, is that heel stick now I dropped it already
I got another one if you want
I saw that uh
You were pretty low
Yeah, we're we are gaming right now. I mean you guys want to see this. Oh, yeah big gaming
Keep getting extremely
Hi everyone. Sorry
Oh, no
Sniper yeah
Thanks mush
You're very welcome
So we get extra money and extra experience for doing it on hard
Yes, yeah more money more experience and then if you do the modifiers you get even more money and experience
Why did I do what am I doing?
I want to be on this side
Somebody said he keeps doing the great stomp lady noise. Yeah, that's me
Oh, that is what that is
I started doing that like when I was like
17 I thought the video was so funny. So whenever I got hurt I would make that sound now. It just took second nature
Whoops, well i'm down here
That's my marvel script moment, you know
That hurts
Just keeps going up and down
Ow, don't shoot me
Oh my god, don't shoot me. I'm in trouble
Oh, i'm in big trouble here. Oh, there's a lot of a lot of shotgunners here. This is the most i've ever seen
What the fuck?
What do I do?
Okay, most of them are dead
Never not even
All right. All right. Good job. I'm gonna get inside this guy's mind watch this
The only way is forward
Stop does anybody
I need I need like a I need a little help guys. Stop it
I need we need a healing station or something
Oh, no
Oh
It's ready out of the way
Oh, actually, i'm good. Thanks
Well something in here
Please be ammo, please be ammo
Why would there be nothing in a box? Why would you ever close a box lock a box and have nothing inside of it?
Who put that box here? Why is this box even here?
Why do you think they're uh, you know
Something a heretic would do really
It's not what happened bud. You want to talk about it?
Well, i'm opening boxes and there's no ammo in in here. We are again
gosh
What is there anything in this one?
There we go. This one's got
Oh, they have a little like a little team guarding me
That's anybody need it or can I take it no no, you're good. Oh my god, that is a big one. Ah, oh
Oh my god, I think that explosion saved me
That's a lot of health. Look at this. Look at this little captive
I don't deserve to join the team
Not until I get some cool swag like our mascot
Ooh
Yeah, there's a hill here
Um, wait, oh these the little three things tell you how many people can use it. I see
Yeah
um
I guess people with purple should get prioritized, right? Yeah, you can grab it. That's it. That's good
Okay
I'll take it first
Yeah, next time you're about to blow up. It's not try using your old uh f
All right, i'll give it a shot. It should save you
It's not
Little snot
Where are we going?
Did it go down or up?
up
Oh, I got netted
I can't wreck it. Oh my god. Watch out. There's a big dude
He's just walking over to snot
That would did that sound weird that was I have felt headphones in and i'm like really locked in
I feel like I just sounded very weird
It was a very natural laugh. Was it though?
Yeah
You're having a good time, man
self-conscious
That poses a bigger question though, uh when you're aware of your
Love
Self-conscious andy
You know when you have two headphones in and you're really just gaming and you kind of like a speech jamming yourself
Wait, do you not usually have two headphones in this? I dude I usually
Right ear only always 100% really 100%
that's like uh
Things going on around you that you require the other info or does it just happen?
I need to be able to hear myself in a natural environment
and
Okay, hold on put it back in
No, i'm kind of with you on that because I had these headphones that were two noise canceling
And I had to like figure out how to get a live feedback so that I could like think straight
Yeah, it was weird. It feels like you're like in a sensory deprivation
Yeah, I know this like the opening but it's not even just the fact that it's
Covering my ears and the sound in both ears. It's it is
It's happening right now
Um, i'm dead
It's because of the speech jamming
Okay, this is sniper. Where's the sniper?
If you're in the corner, you're good. Just stay in the corner. Yeah. Oh what I'll help you one second
I gotta deal with
Oh my god, we're coming for you guys. I almost just blew guys
i'm getting better at managing my uh
All right. Here you go. Oh, thank you. Come here smush. Let's get you up
Thanks
nice work
Uh smush. Thanks you. Oh good good good
It's not appreciate it plus one plus one
Uh smush says that he's very grateful for all of your contributions
All right, maybe just do a voice, you know, you don't have to
freaking like i think
I think my computer just crashed my whole computer
He's walking into the wall
Is am I live? Oh my god
Oh shit the lore behind this. Why did he just disappear the warp took him am I live still?
It yeah
There's a crash that you can rejoin. Oh, okay. I don't think it shuts off your obs, but it does stutter for a second
Oh, okay. All right. I'm coming. We've had that happen
Dude, literally all my windows turned off at the same time too. It was weird now. We have darlin
I'm coming. At least I think i'm on my way if I just open the game. I'll put me right back in
Yeah, yeah. Oh cool. All right. Good. Let's go
Just waiting here
Yeah, no, you guys are good. Keep keep going. I'm joined. You don't see darlin's giving me a dirty look cool level design
We did this level once already. It's wednesday
But anyways, i'm having a
A speech jammer going on in both ears. That's why I always have to be able to hear
myself in reality
without any
Um, like filter on it. So, you know what that might help me. You have a filter on usually
Well, what I mean by filter is i'm hearing my voice
with a little bit of um,
Like dilution like diluted because i'm not getting my actual voice. I have headphones in both ears
Does that make sense? Yeah, you're hearing a muted version. Yeah, and it just messes with me so bad
something that I've never actually heard my voice when I try to start talking i'll be like
Like repeating myself when i'm trying to start talking maybe that's what it is. Maybe I have like a speech jammer thing going on
Yeah, putting one headphone in usually works
but it just
If there's any positional audio at all, you just don't get it
I have streamed before where I had the left earphone out
I usually do the left earphone out always permanently and I will not hear something coming down the left hall
And i'll turn and get hit by it and people will be like, how did you not know that was coming?
Like well because I physically don't have any knowledge into your into your right ear. Just put them both in the right ear
Squeeze both headphones into one ear
So you still get the visual cues
That's actually really funny
All right, i'm back. Oh wait, I heard that little the flamethrower guy
Yeah, right a little bunsen burning just go mono in one ear
I don't think you could even set it up that way. Can you even do that?
I think maybe I should try it. Yeah, because if you're if you're
I hope I get credit for beating the mission, right?
Yeah, you'll get credit
Back you tentacle beat. Ow
You guys see ammo could use it. Oh, I have a box I can put down. Ooh
Yeah, if you want to get at the stairs once we get this growth
I think i'm gonna train myself to deal with loud noises
I'm gonna start putting a distortion effect on my computer and turning it up to like 300
Yeah, it's like while you're watching tv
Yeah, any particular, you know end game for that or just to make myself stronger
Oh cool, you can do you can do sub alerts. They're just screaming you
Yeah, tell you enough to it
I bet there's no, uh downsides to that either. Yeah, there's no way you'd develop like
Some canon tonight is behavioral induced
It's like uh taking a little bit of poison every day to become immune dude
I actually blew out my left eardrum when I was sick like a couple of years ago
I blew my nose too hard
And it was like boom and I could feel it and it hurt
And I you know, this is for real
and now
Uh, now I have like a little tiny ear ringing in my left ear. Oh, it's horrible. Yeah, it sucks
It's not that bad. It's just have to be in a dead silent room
With no sound effects, but I I hear it
It's annoying
I feel like you think you could like blow it back, you know
Yeah, like go the other way. Yeah
I bet we could put you in a big microwave for a minute and it might fix some problems
Not even like a minute like micro dosing a microwave like put you in there for like a second another second
You grow immune to radiation
Yeah, that's how you could become immune
Yeah, that's what uh the hope did right? It is important
The chopper is full of really cool great ideas. He takes off himself in a microwave
He tick talks
Keep yawning
Uh back then I went to the I actually went to like an ent about it and
It's kind of weird because they were just like, yeah
That's it
Your ears are gonna ring
Just like is there anything I can do about it?
No
Oh, I paid for this. Okay, I paid for this advice
Well, they look they checked
There was no like real damage to my ear, but it was just like yeah, it's just the way it is
Like okay
Listen, you let me give you medical advice and I think we could probably get that here
There was this uh supplement
That had I forget what the actual supplement was but it sometimes
Maybe works for some people, but I don't know if there's even any evidence that it works
Um, what's it called? I got a specific name like an herb
All right. Oh, wow. Yeah, just eat extra just put oregano on your pizza and it'll be better
I just got hurt a lot
Oh my god, it's like an amino acid or something. I figure what it was
You just saved my life
Hey anytime
You guys look like you need a med kit
I could use I could use a med kit
Wait, there's a skull and wait
Is this a severie or what are we sharing it or are you gonna guys gonna drink most of it?
Because we I we and chug literally only got like a one sniff of that
I think like maybe there's a finite amount of healing it can do because we just yeah there is
Oh cool. He started doing any character. He's like, I can't
He takes over
Oh wait smush I got a thing for you to do you do what should I do over here? Yep. Do you have any grenades? Um, no
Grenade
If you throw a grenade at the eyeball, really
They don't want me to stand up, um, what's happening to me? What was that?
That was very weird
You did it there's more than that
Oh shit
Thanks chug
Chug you might need to follow me this way and get ready to pick me up. Okay
Don't don't don't don't a lot of talks versus I hear
I actually just killed by a default shitty guy
I'm actually pissed off. I got beat by a default guy with a hammer in his hand
Thank you
What who's this
Things just keep happening to me. All right, let's go home guys. Come on. You did it. I'm proud of you
Oh, we've got a big group coming from our anatomical web
How's that that was my phone, sorry
Copernicus
Enemy enemy, uh
Where did they all come from?
I am dead
Sorry, you guys get up. Are we able to rescue him this way? I don't think so
Yes, we are
I'm just dead
Oh, I did respond oh my elbow
Thank you
So grateful
Oh, right. Sorry. I forgot to roleplay
Thank you
It's amazing
All right, we're in the prison
Hey, we did it. Oh, hey
The camera pan overdue we're good easy. Yeah, you guys should get a bunch a lot of experience for that
That's a lot
Holy shit. That's an entire level. All right
Oh, I unlocked a new weapon
This day just keeps getting better
rumbler
I think I got roman for one more
One more and one let's do one more hard one. I think we're I think we're ready for a five
Oh god
Just skip four altogether
Also, again, this is sponsored. I really do appreciate it. Um playing a little bit extra
Games really fun. I'll be playing it again
Uh, but yeah warhammer. Thanks a lot for the sponsor. This is it's been a lot of fun game is available for free order
The beta is currently ongoing right now
Uh, it is free order available
Get you access to the beta game comes out on the 30th as you see pre-order beta test november 17th and 29th
Game releases in full on the 30th
Seems like they are they're working pretty much double time here
Uh, it seems like to get some stability patches. I think and some stuff ready for the actual launch
So I will definitely be playing this again
And we'll go from there, but it's been a blast
Uh, let's keep going. We'll do one more. This should be a level where you go get slimed like nickelodeon
They put you in a big chair. Is there a map we haven't done yet. Yes
this one
this one is
rank three lights out and scriptures
so
So pretend the scriptures isn't that because you're not going to find them in the dark. Yeah in the dark
I've got quite the keen eye. Let's do lights out. I think we can do it
You want to do lights out? All right, let's do lights out
Uh also, let me clarify that when I say working double time
I don't I just mean that they're like
Dedicated to making sure the launch is good. I think they already have plans for like patches and stuff. So
Uh, I don't mean like oh they're working triple time or something. So I want to clear that up
It's called a trauma force staff. Oh, that's kind of sad. What do you need flashlights if it's dark? How are we gonna see?
Yeah, can do the do the arbons not ever get a flashlight. That's so weird. You can't just use your flame up
I don't know if the flames give off light. I think they might just be listen to what you just said
Yeah, but you know video game limitations and all that man that big bright thing coming out of your gun
It doesn't yeah, it doesn't seem to damage. Yeah, I can try it
But if it doesn't work, then i'm letting the way with holy fire. It's gonna be a little difficult
Okay, are there any new any new weapons? Did it tell you that you unlocked any when you love it up?
I yeah, I did. Let me see if I can upgrade one. Oh my god. I can afford pants
No, I shouldn't though
Also wait three minutes for a different mission. Oh, yeah, the weapon shop upgrades in three minutes, too. It refreshes my service
You want to just chill for a couple minutes and just redo all this? Okay. Okay. Sure
Want to take a look at this anyways?
Did I get any
I've done multiple missions now and I still haven't gotten this blue currency
in the shrine of all my mama's nasha
They they look like little squares in the level
This club I the only the reason why i'm not trying to buy it is because it was what I started with
But that's not how this works
Just because the you started with the default weapon does not mean oh, yeah, that's the default weapon
You don't want that thing. It's just a weapon. Should I get it? Yeah, so you can get like a really good club leader
What do you think the the way the game determines the gear you get in the shop is it takes the
Highest level piece of gear in your bag or on your person
So if you buy something even if you don't want to use it if it's like a big upgrade
It means that when your shop refreshes next time you'll have like better stuff in there. Oh, okay
That's good to know. Well, I don't know. I have enough money. You can also sell old stuff
I don't know if you've done that but if you
That's right
Press i and then hover over your items you can hold x to sell them and that's easy cash
That's actually a great I don't want to sell everything but just the stuff I probably won't use yeah, just like your old stuff
Is it bad to sell greens? No. No. No, I'll just sell get more based on the rarity too
one minute remaining
See we got up at 10k
Shouldn't have sold
Yeah, it's all right though. Watch me regret not buying this right now. It's gonna be all greens. It's been fun, but I can go over
Um, let's go over what's going on next week
I will be back on tuesday. That's something interesting going on on tuesday
i'm gonna be playing
Something I don't want to spoil it but uh stir maybe somebody else. I don't want to spoil it. I don't want to spoil it
I'm playing a fun game on the 29th
uh
We'll be playing this again on launch
So i'm actually happy about that because that's gonna be a lot of fun because they think the game's really good
and then on the first something
very
Interesting and unusual is happening not on my stream. You'll you'll hear about it very soon
So that should be fun, too
That's the plan for next week. Did did stir already talk about it? Did stir talk about it? Yeah. Oh, okay
I had the hiccups for
Like an hour straight the other day and I was almost in tears by the end of that hour
I don't think you can survive a full year. I'm telling you no no mortal man. That's too much
Okay, is this better?
Hello. Hello. Sorry. I was muted just you think you could survive a whole year of hiccuping germa
How often does it happen?
Like as on on the normal it's like every having hiccups every like 30 seconds to minute two minutes. Yeah
Yeah, no, no, I don't think so. That's what i'm saying people keep saying they could survive it
Is the money involved? Yeah, you you would get a sum of money, but that's not too important
Well, now it is very important. How much I don't know 100 a million dollars
I was gonna say a hundred away a hundred dollars
For a hundred million dollars, I think the answer is yes, but your mile your life might be at stake
No, it would just be really annoying for a year
But then you have a hundred million dollars for the rest of your life. Think about the anatomy of the human
I don't know about you guys, but sometimes my hiccups like hurt really bad
Yeah, that's what i'm saying
Like you you get the hiccups after like dude after two days of hiccuping straight even in your sleep
You're gonna be like you're gonna be on your knees like begging for someone to just like cancel the deal
You wouldn't be able to sleep. You'd like die of sleep deprivation
Well, do you but hold on but do you hiccup in do you hiccup in your sleep?
Yeah, it'll be a year straight of just hiccupping. So you wouldn't you would wake up every that wouldn't make any sense
You wouldn't be able to that's why I say it's considerate carefully. Criken doesn't want to think about it
He just thinks he can do it. You you would sign yourself up and you would just be in agony
So all the lights out ones just went away and turned into endless horde
So just back in the endless horde zone great for new mission
I don't think we've done this your body would get used to it
I think your body I think it probably would I don't know if it would happen in your rem sleep
I don't think it's possible your body like shuts down a bunch of features, doesn't it?
Yeah, but you also accepted a curse man. I don't think the curse cares about you your body's features
That's true. You're hiccupping every every 30 seconds for a year. I wonder if that muscle would get pretty buff
Oh, you would be so buff like that hiccup muscle. I wonder if you could like medically induce sleep though just hiccup through it
Yeah, definitely. You get used to it. I think your body would adapt going to crypto sleep for a year
Yeah, this is uh, this is my last one. Are you guys gonna keep playing after this?
I think we'll play a little more at least I will uh, I know I think tomato might be joining us
I don't know if i'm gonna play pizza just got here
Pizza if you think you're still going i'll uh, i'll raid you after it's over. Thanks
I mean you can just eat the pizza while playing try work like germa did remember it was good to eat on stream
What if I get the hiccups?
All right, let's make it a good one
Is that my character talking
Yes
I told you actually I picked the one that's sort of
You can see how I was mistaken for rocko the rock and roll frown. I just want like a score a mad scientist
I want four of the character that you're playing to all harmonize at the same time
Yeah, you can have multiple people all have the same voice
And just oh, yeah
Wait, so this big dude can have that little tiny voice
Uh, no, it it's classic
Didn't lie you misunderstood me
Blue this knife is good
What should I eat tonight? What do you guys think?
Any recommendations yesterday?
Uh
Thanksgiving dinner
Come on you got you you got enough to eat for like three or four days. I could just eat that some mayonnaise sandwiches
And do you want something light something?
The opposite of thanksgiving or you want to keep riding the thanksgiving train? I actually might just ride the thanksgiving wave. I think
But if it wasn't that then what what do you think?
If it wasn't that yeah, what are you guys favorite foods? Like yeah, what do you guys would say?
I feel like maybe a nice pasta dish would be like the opposite of a thanksgiving
I like it. It's a comfy one. Yeah
You know, i'll be honest ever since we went to that, uh chicken katsu place in vegas
I started ordering chicken katsu because it was so fucking good. I've been chasing the high ever since
Yeah, it's just it's just unbeatable
It was so good. It's a it's like a japanese curry
like breaded chicken
But it's like this kind of deep spice unlike other curries. It's a really interesting. Yeah, it is fantastic
That's actually not a bad idea
Is it like my favorite places to go in la was coca?
The curry was so good. Oh, I don't know if i've been there
What?
Did we go there together? Where's the sniper?
We must have we went one time for like ramen. I remember
You haven't been I don't know if you live there
Yeah, that was a big city just tell me to eat shit it can't be that big what do I do
Get some ammo pal
I got a healing crate
Well, next time you go out to eat, you know where to go
Cocoa. Oh shit. I'm having like with you guys. I'm just being a big line of gunmen
I hear a dog
Thank goodness
I would have probably died. I've been to sugarfish. Yeah sugarfish is
amazing
There's a staple out here
I'm having a really bad day a really good day. Then I'll order sugarfish. What is sugarfish? It's like sushi
Yeah, it's usually places. It's really high quality
You know, I have not had sushi in a long time
It fell off real bad for me though. I kind of stopped like wanting it off. Oh, I fell off help
Oh, oh my god. You did copernicus. Come here
Mike stuck
Uh-oh
Oh, that's a lot of people
Uh, uh, I just panicked
I probably shouldn't have done what I just did
Oh my god, I just ran in he really should have done that
One open into oh my goodness
This feels like a slipknot concert or something. Shit. I'm done. You chugged us ran in there to save your ass
That's some real ogan friendship
Yeah, I mean, come on. We're gotta
Be on uh, get each other's backs
What is happening there you just gave me the hiccups by the way, yeah, I have them now check your bank account
100 million
Is that 50% uh up front or after it has to be yeah if you survive the year you'll get the other half
I'm telling you dude. I had the hiccups for like an hour the other day and I was like almost in tears
Oh my god, you came i'm fine now wait, that's still a lot of money though. It's like what maybe 10 000
We got company we do
You're gonna want to see this. It's slugsworth
Oh
There's another boss. It's the slime
The beast we've seen
Have you guys killed the demon yet the new one? Yeah
Somebody's shooting us from below who is to what are you?
Excuse me
Why?
Slugging all over me. He's slugging on my do you see I just eat one of the soldiers? Yeah, I saw that
She's eating me dog
Help he's leaving
They're eating her and then they're going to eat me I remember that oh my god
I watched that again recently. Really? Yeah
Terrible movie. I hope he's doing well
Oh come on
But i'm in a i'm in a pickle right now
Behind you snot. Oh, no, I go. It's not as in me or
No, it's not as in how did I miss shooting the dog off of you? I should quit the game right now
I need to quit the video game
There's too much going on should watch some documentary they made about the oh my god guy
Do they really dogs fucking me up?
Call the animal control they have to say
About the oh my god guy. Yeah
That movie is so weird
It it genuinely makes
Like no sense, dude
I want to go to I want to go to no, it's uh, troll two troll two. Okay, that's close
I bet life and no bog would be pretty good
We're trying to find a power supply for this healing thing. I'm not gonna lie. I'm kind of kind of getting cracked out here
I just popped off right there
Let me crack your mama
The germa pop-up 2022
Uh, yeah, we're looking for a battery, right? I found it you did. Okay, you got it
Oh down here, okay
Oh, it's a dog
Oh no, oh, i'm so sorry. I didn't know what I did. There's another one. What the heck
Is he dead?
Do you ever come here come here?
That was scabby
Keep going that way straight to the end this way. Oh here. Yeah. Yep. I will try and find our friend
Oops, i'm gonna press g
There he is. I see him. Hey guys
Thanks chug
He's here
You go back and get that healing snot. You hear me big guy. All right, i'm on it. Which way?
Uh that way then left. Oh, you're not kidding
Straight through the door in front of you. He's fucking broke box that up. I hit him twice
There's where all those guys are coming from. That's the way
I'm gonna try to deal with these guys first
These guys aren't playing around
That's what happens when you play the game on fucking hard kid. All right
It's not straight down that corridor just all the way to the end
On it. Oh my god. I've been
Oh my god, he's dying we
It's okay. It's just one enemy. I can handle them
I just saw you miss four times. Yeah, it was actually more like eight
You just happened to come in at the last four
All right, a hound dog has found me. Oh, no, he's gonna die. I got i'm fine guys. I'm fine
Do you have people running into that room you guys are in by the way?
We're never leaving this place
Oh my god, I almost blew myself up where are they even coming from that's what i'm saying. There's too many people in these places
Wait, how many people live in a hive city again? Do you know 90 billion?
90 billion 90 around in a billion
And it has 90 billion what happened
Because i'm panicking there's like too much shit going on 10. All right, we're good
I have a heal. I'm not I don't think we need it right now though, right? I think we're okay. It's 11 I guess
dog
This shit is just exploding
Yeah, so the the current augment we have is endless horde
Oh, that's what's going on. Okay
Oh that guy goes yeah, he's got the slime
Does a slime is that like a boomer where it sucks up the I mean it attracts the horde?
Uh, no, no, they just hurt he's just out here to us
Thank goodness
Why did they call it the boomer? Huh?
Did you guys boom?
It was probably the most brilliant name
in gaming history
They probably named it before like the boomer stuff
Kind of come on
Oh before like okay boomer. Yeah
It would have been if they capitalized on that though and had like a bubble flossing or something. Oh, yeah
They were a trillion dollars. Oh, I didn't even know what that was. Sorry without even having a hiccup for a year
That little oh
There was a little a little bit of fire. Wait. Oh, you're here with me. You saw it. I did it actually accidentally
What are those goofballs doing over there? Oh, right. Sorry
Just having a little conversation. Where the hell are we don't say that because then they think we're bad gamers
Oh here. Uh, germa don't forget to buff with this thing
Fight my fucking heart out over here
Fuck tons of them. Yeah, there's a lot of them over here guys. We're holding them off. They're trying to get to you
Drop down that big hole
Thanks
Hey, we did most of the heavy lifting back there
Just glad you guys are all right, you know
it's
Could I push one of the like, uh, one of the special infected off the map?
Rehealing for everyone
I guess get topped off right that reason not to yeah. All right
That guy really you got that guy it goes running up to you and just quietly put up your knife like
Oh my god, what the fuck right after we did what what happened he's gonna hurt me
Fucked on a fucking compressed air container and flew. I'm stuck. I'm dead. I'm gone forever
I can't move
I'm dead
Can you break the thing? What happened? Oh he he must I think the boss knocked me back. I was stuck on pixels
It's up to you to find this
He can handle this i've been farming the boston accent a little first might be the best one
Oh god
This does not look good. Did we just lose?
Bounce me over
Oh, that's
That's the end
Fucking muck
Yeah, I went I went off the whole map it actually launched me into the sky box i'm not kidding
I was dead instantly. Yeah, that
Could not have done worse. There were like 10 snipers that instantly shot me all at the same time. That's what happened with me
And it was nothing I could have done
That's fat
That was fun
I did get some more currency. We still get paid for losing a little bit. Yeah, that's good
Get a portion doesn't just take the whole thing from you
The payee payment
But yeah, that's gonna be it for me
Thanks for playing guys. Seriously much easier to it was fun. Have a good one. Yeah, it's uh
It's much more fun to jump in with obviously people you have spoken to previously or just to get in the call and have fun
Hey, man, you did great
No, no, seriously, thanks guys i'll uh, i'll talk to you guys soon have a good rest of your night
You craig and you said you're still streaming. Yep, look i'm more of this. Yeah, i'll just raid you. Thank you
Have a great night guys. Thanks for sticking around
Have a good night, buddy. Hey, don't be strangers either. Okay, sure sealer. Bye. See you
So yeah, that's going to conclude the stream
Uh, that was warhammer
40 000
That was a lot of fun
Uh again warhammer, uh sponsoring the streams i'll be playing it on the 30th at launch as well
Actually, really really great game. I'm into it
We're planning to get on the 30th and then there's also a bunch of other stuff going on next week
I will see you guys fresh
on
Tuesday and then i will do tuesday wednesday thursday a couple of events going on. Yeah, that is going to be it again
It's available for pre-order
It is there
and what how uh
Take a look. How much is the game? I think it's actually not
The music on sorry about that. It's like it's 40 for the game. Yeah, I mean it's 40 bucks
You get the base game
Um, it seems like there's a lot to do seems like they're adding probably going to be adding a lot of stuff
That was fun. Oh, you can't even hear it. Sorry
Good night. Goodbye
Can you give us a clue on the december 1st stream?
Nope, because it is not my stream to announce
Let's put it that way
But once that is very clear, it's been announced then i'll talk about it should be fun
It's going to be very interesting. I don't know how I feel about it. I don't it's actually
Something I have never even remotely considered ever trying in my whole life ever
Um, it's going to be very interesting. I can assure you that thanks for the support though. Thanks for sticking around
He sponsors streams
Games have been actually really really fun. So i'm really happy with them so far
Have a great night. Oh, uh, kraken's gonna keep playing it if you want to keep watching
And i'll see you guys soon
Have a good rest of your weekend. See you guys on tuesday. I think starting early on tuesday somewhere around like 12 noon pacific
1 pm pacific somewhere between 12 and 1 because we're gonna be hanging out with stir. Let's go ahead and get that going
See you guys later. Good night. Goodbye. Go say hi to kraken even though he was just here
See you later. Oh, yeah. Yeah, of course
Calling your mother