Good afternoon. Hi, welcome back. Sorry, yesterday, but welcome.
Okay, good to see you again. Oh, MonkaS clown detected.
Today, we are going to play WarioWare for the Nintendo GameCube.
And you're probably wondering, Jeremy, you said that we're probably gonna be playing Casino Inc. today.
And I wouldn't even be saying that. That was last night Jeremy saying that.
It's a different person.
So, the reason is because I think that game's gonna take more than a few streams,
or maybe like more than one to two full streams to do.
And I'm not gonna be around tomorrow, or the next day, or the next day.
Over the next four plus days, I've got a lot of stuff going on in my personal life.
Those of you that don't know, I am moving, staying in Vegas, but moving over the next week or two.
And gotta get a lot of shit done. Gotta get a lot of stuff in order,
especially considering the circumstances as of right now.
All the stuff with the coronavirus. I gotta get my shit together.
So, he's moving to Vegas. That's right, I am.
But, so I didn't want to start Casino Inc. because I want to give it at least the necessary time,
because it looks like a really, really fun, interesting game.
So, I was like, what can we do today for a little while over the next X amount of hours?
And well, WarioWare is one of them. And obviously, Animal Crossing as well.
So, the plan is we're gonna play WarioWare until we have eaten our full.
And then we're gonna move on to Animal Crossing because I want to play it again.
We're on first party Nintendo mode today and yesterday.
Las Vegas, here we come. That's the plan.
He's gonna be demonetized. Where are you moving to?
Las Vegas. Staying in Las Vegas. Just a different place.
Yeah, but where? Oh, well, you guys have. You guys have.
Fuck. Anyways, let's play.
Let's play WarioWare. How many WarioWares are there?
How many games? This is the GameCube WarioWare, right?
Because they like renamed it. This is WarioWare Mega Party Games.
But the original game was called Mega Micro Games.
It was renamed or something for some reason. I don't know. It's weird.
But here you go. We have to do a test here because I don't know.
It looks like there is a full four or five second delay when this is coming through my capture device.
So we're going to do a test. I would like for you to all to participate in this test.
Are you ready? Because it might. I got to get this right before I play.
One. How off is that? I need to know. It's probably very off.
One, two, one, two. It's off by like, yeah, it's going to be off by like two full seconds.
When I move, let's say I hit left and I say, oh, I look over on my other screen.
It takes three or four full seconds to happen.
All right, here we go. Let's try this. Ready? Tell me how this sounds.
Do I actually have to delay my voice by two thousand milliseconds for this to work?
Holy shit. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Better?
Now that's too much. It's close. So I'm early.
So you hear my voice first, right? All right, here we go.
Time to go to twenty. I feel like I'm in the fucking like past.
I'm like I'm in like the future. One, two, one, two, one.
Hey, the video is early. How's this sound? Hey, what do you know about that?
What do you know? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I don't know. Nothing changed. It's worse.
Fuck. This whole thing is fucked up. I need to like hear this, but I can't.
All right, hold on. I was trying to get in my room. He was like, let me in.
OK, why is this such a huge delay? OK, here we go. Ready?
One. Two hours of fixing delay.
Why would it take like five full fucking seconds? It's close.
One, two, one, two. All right, what are you hearing?
Video first or audio first or me first? Voice is slightly early. OK, hold on.
I'll get it. This is this is this is it. This is the one you're at.
Hey, are you ready to go? Are you ready?
One, two, three, one. Now the game's further behind.
Now this is making me. No, that's way too much.
I just added so much more time. Hey, how are you?
Two, three, four, five, one, two, three, four, four, five, five. Good. Yes.
Who are you? I'm me. Oh, God. It's not good. Should I do it a little more?
You tell me. Ready? I'll do the whole alphabet.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P.
It's good. OK, I stopped right at the far at the point everybody wanted me to do.
All right, P, Q, R, S. That's fine. All right, here we go.
Stage clear games. Beat all other games.
Why is it a Game Boy Advance up there? You owe us a QRS.
No, I'm not going to do it. Grab. How do I grab?
Well, I don't know. What do you mean? I just got that wrong.
Oh, OK. All right. All right. Where's the fucking storyline?
Isn't there like a storyline? Oh, this is the first one.
God. All right. You got it. The screen is cut off.
Wait, why is the screen cut off? This is fucked up.
That's happening to me, too. That's not just happening to you guys.
That's happening to me. Hold on. Yeah, that's happening to me, too.
Should have done the QRS. Oh, fuck. I got it.
Got it. How many of these do I have to do? Is there a boss?
Oh, fuck. I could put clothes on. I'm good.
That's what I look like right now. Oh, bar. Oh, shit.
OK, it swings all the way. How do I? OK, I got it.
Is he playing party game? No, they renamed this game.
This is the original one for the GameCube. All right, I got the one up. Let's go.
This is a face game game. Do I really have to go put on clothes?
What? Fuck, I'm going to lose. Should have clothes on.
No, I don't have to put on clothes. I don't have to wear clothes if I don't want to.
Easy. Done. I'm in my own room. I'm in my own house.
I'm not in your house. I'm in my house. Oh, fuck, I lost.
Do I actually have to? All right. How about this?
This is not my beautiful house. Holy fuck, there's a lot.
Wait, wait. Intro. Wait, it's supposed to be zoomed in.
Oh, all right. I get it. So, yeah, the game's not cut off.
It's supposed to look like this. I had everything was correct.
Now I have to redo that. I need to go get on naked.
All right, I promise I'll put a face cam on in like 40 minutes.
I can't. This is just an intro. There's a story. All right, speed up.
Fuck. Okay. Excellent. Hello, his voice.
He's going to turn into a clickbait face cam streamer.
Jeremy, you should get a mustache. You want me to get a fucking mustache?
No. You think you get like serial killer vibes from me now?
If I grow a mustache, I increase that by like 50%.
You don't have to look at fucking reddit threads and I get to see like,
all right, is this guy like a serial killer?
Now imagine me with a huge ass mustache instead of is this guy a serial killer?
It turns into this guy's a serial killer.
Balance. Oh, shit. Okay, I got it. Got the pieces.
Curl. What? Oh, shit. Damn it. I didn't understand what it meant.
Spike the ball. Jump. Oh, I love this character. Look at that guy.
Swim. What? Did I get it? Shoot. Yes. Got it.
The audio is bad. I'll try. I'll fix it in a minute.
This is for some reason this game in particular is like so fucked up when it got captured.
And I was trying to figure it out, but I couldn't figure it out.
Jump. Oh, fuck. I got a jumping. Did I get it?
Oh, fuck. I have to press up. Shit. All right.
Shoot. Shoot what? Oh, my God. I got it.
No. Fuck. I thought I was moving me. I thought I was moving the guy, not the trampoline.
Shit. All right. I'll put on clothes. I'll be back.
You know what's funny? Me turning on my face cam just made syncing this whole thing up
exponentially more difficult because now I have to sync the webcam too.
There's like three different things that need to be delayed. This is going to be,
well, this is going to be, well, we're here for a while. All right. If I turn the webcam on,
you're not going to see like a naked body, right? Because sometimes this fucking camera
takes the frame, the last frame that it saw, and it might be my naked body.
So I need to make sure that's not going to happen. Okay. I think we're good.
Let me make sure this is right. Nope. See what I mean? You see what I'm saying?
Did you see that? Like that, that could have been a naked person.
Are you guys ready for a like, look, I get it. Look, it's so weird. This is so delayed.
This is such a joke. I can't even monitor what I'm doing. I'm pointing and talking at you,
but the guy over here is doing the same thing like three seconds later.
It's fucking freaking me out. Okay. You ready? Here we go. Let's test it.
I need my audio. Holy shit. Look at, look at how many different
fucking mini game levels there are. This is going to be sick.
All right. Where's my fucking audio device? Half screen face cam. Well, it has to be that
so we can get this synced up. I got another thing to sync. Welcome to the sync stream.
Okay. Here we go. How bad was that? Why is his jacket zipped up all the way?
Well, I don't know. I wonder why is this jacket zipped up all the way?
It doesn't have anything to do with the fact that there's nothing else underneath this.
And I put it on out of desperation because there's nothing fucking, there's nothing under here.
It's just nudity under this zip up. I'm not going to stand up. I'm not standing up.
All right. We have a very specific task to do. Are you ready? I have to go back.
So when the door opens, I'm going to move myself over here.
Let's get this open. This is going to be so fucked up. Oh, fuck. I messed it up. Hold on.
Wait, this is going to help. Holy shit. This is going to help. I can see it over here. I
can see it like five seconds. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Ready? Okay. It's going to be longer.
Longer. Ready? Check. This section is going to help. I can get this right. Hold on. Wait.
No, I didn't press the button. Fuck. Close. Oh, it's close. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Here we go.
Ready? Do you have the time, sir? Get the fuck out of here. Let's go. Let's go. We're good.
Wait, I have to fix the, nevermind. I just realized I just was fucking like pointing.
Holy shit. There's a lot of people here that just watched me do that. There's a lot of people that
just watched that happen. Like I would do that on my own. I tried, but it was, why is your forehead
shining? I don't know. Cause I have an oily T-zone. Here, here's your gold star. It's your T-zone.
God. Here's that. Just take a shower. It doesn't, that's a plastic surgeon terminology. No,
it's a skincare terminology. Well, that's like, that's, that's what that is called.
Okay. And that's how you can tell. And those of you, you saw it in real time. You saw it in real time.
You watched it in real time. You watched me look at another monitor. So there was five community subs
came in and I looked over at the other monitor and there we go. I fell down and I got fucking hurt.
Saw it in real time. So those of you that just like, that asked the question all the time,
what the fuck did he miss that? It's because somebody, I just looked over here because
something happened over here. I looked over here. I was looking over there. I was looking over here.
See something. I should do face cave every day. Uh, germa sucks. Thanks to the five community subs.
All right, I'll get it here. God gave you two eyes for a reason.
What are you, are you implying that I need to frog eyes both monitors?
All right, here we go. Let's go. Jimmy T. Holy fuck. How do you defend? Got it. Catch. I don't
know. Okay. You can just like this. Got it. Hurdle. Just jump. Whoa. That was a lot quicker
than I thought it was going to be. Balance. Swim. Did I get it? Yeah. Jump. I love these fucking
micro games. Here comes QRS. I'll get this one this time. Bounce. Right. I'm not moving him.
I'm moving the trampoline. Got it. That's what the, that's where the hiccup was last time.
Good. Yeah. What are you talking about? I pressed A. Dead. Oh, fuck. Got it. Nice. All right. I only
have two lives. I don't want to fuck this up. Speed up. But got it. Ooh, got it. Got it. Got it.
Got it. Loser. Whoa, that's close. I almost didn't get it. All right. Finish. Got it. Welcome to the
commentary of this game. I have to pay attention so much that all I can say is what happened at
the end. Knockout. Get him. I did. I beat it. Chill, baby. Chill. Got it. Do we keep, do we keep
going? Sci-fi. Dribble and splits. Wait, I just have to keep going. Land the jump. Holy shit.
Frost. Oh, fuck. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. Got it. I got it. I said it a lot of times
there. Assemble. Holy fuck. Okay. This game is more serious and more speedy. What do you mean blast
off? I just did. I held, I held the A button down. I think I actually dodged it somehow.
Side step. Got it. Dodge. Who's that? I thought it was shooting me. Wait, who's shooting who?
Who's shooting who? Didn't got it. Oh, I see. We go from, we start it. Okay. Sci-fi. Here we go.
Started sci-fi. This, this one's much quicker than the last one. Well, the future one, right?
Twitch plays WarioWare. Dude, rare minigames. I know. This is the one, this is not, I know it's
not the original one, but this is the one, this is the one that came out of the GameCube.
And I've heard great things. Pretty rare. I am not looking forward to when it gets to like
times 10 speed. That's going to be kind of all over the place. Beam. Oh, you have to do it. It's
actually like Street Fighter. That's fun. This one sucks. No story. This is just pure gameplay.
This one is just pure hyper gameplay. Repeat, repel, repel. I don't know what,
do I have to push him, punch him? Chop. Fuck. Where the hell is my 40 minute unskippable?
I'm not going to read that one out loud. This dude fucking sucks at this game.
Strike. Strike who? Get five. Got five. Hit Mars. Red one. Shoot? Okay. Cool. Cross. Oh,
that was close. It's four. Are you even actually doing anything? I did it. Yeah,
pressing, just sitting here watching. 22. Shit. Okay, we're good. Dodge. Escape.
Oh, got it. Got it. Complete what? Oh, yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. I'm super good at games
like this. That's why I got the spreader. You always want to get the spreader in these games.
Do I go in that? I don't understand what I do. Go in this? Oh, now that's a real penis music.
Got it. Off duty time. We have to keep going. Oh, no. Here comes Mona. Got you. Got you.
Got it. Got it. I don't understand. Twirl the spaghetti. Twirl the spaghetti. Oh,
that was, that was, that was stupid. Sorry. I'm going to start right there at strange.
Strange. No story. Can't play hands. He's so bad at video games. Steer. Oh, my God. I didn't even
know what the fuck. Mark page 10. Shine. Post. Got it. Squirt. I thought I was supposed to do it
in the mouth. I thought, I thought it was like food. Look out. All right. No, no more mistakes.
There's the, there it is. There's the, that's the Wario wear that I know.
God, I love micro gaming. Come on. What, was he not supposed to cut all his hair off?
Catch the toast. Deploy. I say, oh, I got it. Sniff. Okay. It's a bad parking job, but I,
but I still got it. Oh, that was close. Oh, you little fuck. He didn't like come up high
enough for me to grab him. All right. I'll get it. I'll, I'll get it. This is literally pre-recorded.
I mean, it technically is because I've pre-recorded the sound. Almost missed it.
You guys can see, right? When I'm like with my big ugly mug in the way. Speed up. That's what,
that was really easy. You just have to press A. Well, you just have to press A on all of these.
Got it. Got it. Ooh, did I do it? No, I got it. No, I got it. Got it. Got it. All right. I gotta
get this one now. Brush those fucking teeth. I got it. Okay. Got it. Fucking YouTube thumbnail
face. I didn't mean to. You're so good at this. Thanks. I appreciate that. You think so? I can't
say that now. I can't say that I did something. Like I can't say the word got it now because I've
said it too many times and I've recorded it too many times. You're good at parking. Oh my God.
I got it again. I was like dropping fucking flavor drops in that person's mouth. I don't know what
the fuck I'm doing. Pound? Watch out for the hand. Hit the nail. Hit the nail. Hit the nail,
Jeremy. Hit the nail. All right. Good. One up. Next game. Nine volt coming up.
Everyone can do that. It's just level one Mario. Throw? Oh, he's all the way in the back.
I didn't know. Vacuum. Shoot. That's a pretty cool gun. Oh, he didn't know. Dodge.
I should play that and beat it on screen. Punch. Nine volt. Connect. I don't know how to play
Dr. Mario. I've never played it. I don't know how the game even works. I have fucking no idea.
You know what I know about Dr. Mario? It's his side B as he throws a pill in Smash Brothers. I've
never played the game. I don't even know what happens. It's Candy Crush, but it's different.
That's his new way. That's not even right. That's incorrect. That's how much I know
about Mario Dr. Mario MD. Here we go. I love balloon fight. I don't know if you just want to
play Mario Brothers 1. Oops, sorry. It just told me to shoot. It didn't say to shoot. Enter.
Was it star drop? I have forever a sour face after that one. I love Game Boy. He looks so
ugly in that E mode. Guys, you want to do something? Sure. You know how easy it is to make yourself
look ugly? You go like this. Wait, hold on. That's looking where that is. That's bullshit.
It's very easy to make yourself ugly. This is what I normally look like. Like this. This is a
fucking normal person. If you scrunch your face up and press your lips into your jaw and pull your
nose back and close your eyes and scrunch your head, you can make yourself look ugly. Look at
all these emotes of me doing. Look, I'll show you. Ready? This is normal. Then see what happens to
my nose. I don't know how to play Dr. Mario. Did I do it? Is it four or is it? I just spoiled all
the Metroid. I'm not going to play it anymore. 6,500 people have watched you do that. I had a full
diaper of fucking slime. You think anything is going to embarrass me at this point? Think about
that. I was in a fucking diaper on stream with slime in my ass. You think that me making a face
on camera is going to make me embarrassed that 6,500 people saw that? At this point, it's over.
You were wearing clothes. Oh, what's this? Got it. Got it. What's the matter, Otto? What do you want?
What's going on? What's the matter? What are you doing? He's giving me the look. Got him. Oh,
okay. I get to tap it really fast. Pretty good Atari game. Joe Dog. Hold on. I'm in the middle
of a fucking micro game. Is that game good? That's F-Zero, right? Joe Dog for best of 2020.
Let me beat this first. Look out. Oh, it's Mr. Game and Watch. Game. Type two. Type one? What?
I don't understand. Shoot it. What the fuck? I don't even know. All right. Hold on.
What's the matter? What do you need? You want to go out? He wants to do something. Hold on.
Give me Otto. Yeah, he wants to go out. You want to say hi first, Otto? Say hello. Otto! He's like,
get me out of this room. All right. I'll be right back. Let me take him out. He's going to come.
Kim's going to take care of it. Joe Kim. Hey, everybody get in here. Everybody get in my room.
That one's just thick. Wait, I failed it? I thought it said don't. Wasn't it just don't get hit?
My face game is fucking huge. It's shrinking. That's way too big. That's so big. That's
obnoxiously huge. I got to kind of focus. Hello? Microscopic. Make it bigger. No.
Put the game in your mouth. Don't. The things I fucking do. Can you see? Can you guys see?
Can you guys? I can't. It's hard for me to do this. You shouldn't be able to still hear it.
That was fun. Oh, sorry. Sorry. I can't play the game like that. It's impossible.
That's physically not possible. Smaller. No. Am I bad at that? What, bad at pretending to
put the video game in my mouth and play micro games that are on another screen? Stop whining.
That's all I do. You look more naked with this jacket on. That doesn't make any fucking sense
at all. It's got clothes on. If I had a t-shirt on, you know, I'm naked under the t-shirt.
You know, with a t-shirt on, I'm naked under the t-shirt. This is just a shirt.
How am I more naked with this with this zip up on? He's blushing. All right, here we go. Speed up.
I'm going to beat this one now. I don't want any more people making fun of me,
but they're going to get the band. Shoot it. Just shoot any of them. All right. Shoot it.
So you admit you're naked. No, you got three lives. I'm going to, I'm going to knock this
one out of the park. I fucking don't like it. Speed up again. Damn. This is hard. Hit six.
Oh, it's body. Where the fuck did that even go? You can't say the F word on the internet. You
can't say the fuck word on the internet. Yes, I can. P Q R S. What? Oh, I beat it. I love this guy.
Match. Okay. That took me a little while. I didn't know what I wanted to be doing.
Shoes. I don't care. Who cares about pressing the button? Decide. Decide what? What am I deciding on?
What am I deciding on? That was cute. That was really cute. Oh, right. Because they spin.
I thought it was going to like just press A. Oh, you're going to, okay. You press them.
Search. What am I looking for? I got it right there. I just found them. Remember. Right down.
Hey, what the hell was going on there? Three. That's it. Just only three. Yeah. I got it. Yeah.
It's a three. Oh, fuck. The extra hand, the extra finger there. I was why it was like this.
And it was like that. And I just, I, you know what I'm saying? It was like that.
And I just picked them up with a three. I Q. I clicked before the thing got heavier. This one,
it's bigger turtles, right? Three picks four. I know. I don't like that one. Most wins.
What do you mean most wins? Oh, I see. Okay. Whoever has more. Choo. Are you hiding poop line?
Yes. It's in a cup. It's not see through because I've got sick and tired of people making fun of my
fucking shit line. There's a teddy bear. That's just a regular cup now. Dribble is. Dribble is.
Inspect. I don't know what the fuck it was. I think it was the guy's face.
Oh, I'm deciding which one doesn't belong. I get it. Dribble is Dribble. Dribble is Dribble.
Okay. You just have to Dribble is phrase search or what? I don't know. What the hell was that even
asking me to do? Or leap forward while holding a press. That's it. Okay. I did it right. Watch out.
Oh, I was trying to stay there. I held it down for too long. I was trying to stay in that spot.
Match. All right. It's got to flip. It can only be this one. Hey, I did it a little too far. I
Super Mario panic jumped. Like he went over there. Count. Oh, inspect it. Q. What the fuck are you
talking about? Right left. Right left. Right left. What the fuck? I did right left. I did right.
Right was wrong apparently. What the fuck happened? Right left. That's what I did. All right. It's an
apple or a tomato. Either one. What was wrong with that one? Okay. There was like small little ice
cubes in there and it's freaking me out. Three. Stop squishing him. He'll be fine. She still has
the microphone attachment on. Why didn't why would I take it off? What if I need it? It's a piece of
plastic that just clicks on right down. I got it. You guys act like it's just like surgically
implanted on here. Look, it's off. It was very difficult to take off. Dude, it only works with
five games. I know. What a catastrophic failure that a Repro was. Save him. I don't understand.
God. Is it orange? Yep. I can do shapes. Thankfully, that one's very easy. Ah,
heavier. Widen the webcam. Why? Can we wide screen? What are we looking for? Which cat? Which cat?
Which cat? Where is it? Where? Where? Where? Where? All right. I almost got this one done.
Boss time. Speed up again. There's four. That one. The coffee bean. Praise. This game is cool. This
bat is cool. This game is cool. Oh, that dribble was a character's name. That's okay. I thought
dribble was a character. Out wit. Oh, it's Hungra. You can attack now. What will you do?
Left jab. That hurt it a bit. Hungra is attacking. What will you do?
Crouch. Try using magic. What will you use? Curse. Curse. Last chance. Time it and press A.
Okay, success. I almost just pressed A on failure. That would have been very bad.
You failed. Hungra. Get it. Want to dance? Nothing in there anymore. All right. Dr.
Prigor. Wait, do I have to press A when pinched? One. Okay. Cut. Eat. Oh, I want a T. How do I get a
T? What a strange game. All right. Let me get this one without even having to stop. Oh, look at this.
I love that. I'm going to do like the JPEG with the face and stuff. Eat. Pray. Now the little dog
ones. When they make the ears like a little animation. Fight. Build up. I don't. Okay.
Build up. Does this only play with one button? It's played with a couple. Like two. A. Up,
down, left, right. That's typically how it works. This one's called reality. Oh, fuck.
Can I restart? Connect. That was easy. I'm looking forward to the super insane
times 10 speed one. Pick a hand. Wait, is that assuming that the other one? Pick a hand?
Hunt. Probably A. Smash two. Eat. All right. This is where we have to pay attention. Get it.
Did I get it? Okay. Oh, just barely. It's okay. He's still edible.
Bidet. Level up. What does that mean? What does that mean I'm doing too good? Oh, it means I'm
doing good. Nice. Oh, got it. Repel. I don't even know what the fuck he's talking about. A, left,
right, move. I can't even. The day means doing good. Plate. All right. Almost there. Watch out.
There are only five buttons. A lot if you think about it. Yes. The devil. I only need to get one.
Okay. That's the one I had to get. Here we go. Boss fight. Defend. I'm a vase? Oh, shit. Holy fuck.
Don't move. I did it. Cell tower noise. Must. Take. Break. Cat and Ana. Wow, there's no video game
with the slug. Oh, the snail. I want that game. Cover. Press A during cutscene. Yeah, I want. Oh,
okay. He has to press a button when it comes up. Shoot. I want more picture games. Remember that
game Africa? It was so fun. That game was so much fun. Just taking photos and getting raided on them
and stuff. I so badly want to play another one of those. Borrow. Oh. Get in the water?
This one's not that bad. Scare him. Pokemon Snap. Yeah, we can do that. What does it want me to do?
Clear? Oh, like hit it in the wood? I'll play Pokemon Snap. It's not that fun. Oh, you gotta
hit it right in the center. Good day job, dude. Got it. Mad because bad. He's mad because bad.
Mad because bad. Mad because bad. Catch. Oh, what? He caught it. He caught it. I'm trying to. He's
the analog. No more analog. Bad because mad. Mad because analog. Analog. Analog. We're good. Nice.
Got it. He's molding. Why do you? How do you? Where do you get that idea?
I'd love that creature. I want it. That one was tricky. Speed up. Micro-malled.
Get off my fucking screen. Finish. Oh, there's another classic turbo web stream. Which one
I'm supposed to lick? Which one was I supposed to lick? I'll get it. I'll get it this time. This is
the one. This is the one. I thought the other one. I thought the one in the middle was going to move.
Why does it keep doing Game Boy Advance? Is this a port? No, it's not. This one came out for the
GameCube. Exclusively for the GameCube. It is. It is. It is literally a Game Boy Advance game.
Wasn't it literally made for every other console? The GBA version is better.
Well, we're playing this one. Catch Fruit. What does the bottom of the screen say? It says
Game Boy Advance. It says Game Boy Advance at the bottom. Yeah, but it's pretending to be a Game Boy
flying rat. I know. Stop pretending. I almost fucked that up. All right, I got it. No, fuck
ups. Here we go. Got to get a ball. Fight. Oh, that was risky, but I did it. Here we go. Jump.
I'm not going for more than one at a time. That's a mistake. All right. Don't call me a coward.
All right. Is this the end of the game here? Is this the final level? Am I about to beat the game?
I'm about to beat the game. Am I? Anything goes Wario. Anything goes Wario. Oh, okay.
People have nightmares about that shit. Catch. That's a broken fucking nose. Oh.
Wrestle. What? I don't know. I was supposed to go for it. Crush it. We're going to have to restart
this one. Never thumb wrestled. Anything goes. Compete. Munch. You're going to lost a pinball.
Of course I did. Create. All right. He's just going to throw a bunch of shit on his face.
Raze. All right. Speed up. Oh, he's a beetle. That's disgusting. Wrestle. Be nice to beetles.
I like beetles. They're cool. They're fine. What's wrong with beetles?
Hide. Oh, hide your fucking stomach. Level up. Oh, I thought I had to tap A to go faster or left or
I don't know. Dude. Did I get it? You got to get Wario's eyes. That's correct. I'm going to get 25
and then I'm doing the super 100. What? If you do it too much or fast his belly button shoots out.
I'm doing super 100 after this for sure. It's going a little too fast. Literally can't beat it.
Got him. Got him. Get all those cherries. You fucking idiot. What am I grabbing? I don't even
know what the fuck I'm supposed to grab. This is the one. You notice how pinball and pinwheel
are related. It's full of the word pin in the product. Thank you. Thank you. What am I producing
egg salad for? Egg salad. What is that? What are you talking about? Egg salad. Say it. Egg salad.
I suck. I almost messed that one up. He said it. Who said it? I said it? Egg salad. Egg salad. Wait.
Okay. He's talking. I know. Didn't fuck that one up. What? I had to do both. Smash. What am I?
I got it. Fuck it. Wait for me. Tuber face. Yeah. I did the like. Fuck. Close it. Egg salad.
It's Wario going. Egg salad. Okay. I see you. Weirdos. He still hasn't beat it. It's the final
level of the game. Of course it's going to be challenging. What does his face look like?
I almost jumped over it. Fuck. Weirdos. Weirdos. Weirdos. My whole body. My whole body is itching.
He hates us. What are you talking about? Take the jacket off. Yeah. It must be this jacket.
Should I take the jacket off? I don't understand this one at all. It says smash. But this is like
a. I don't know. Can I move forward? Nice. Excellent. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's funny.
Take the jacket off. I'm not taking the jacket off. I'm not going to take the jacket off.
I'm not going to. I'm not taking the jacket off. I don't get it. I don't. I don't get it. I can
move. It's smash. Take it off. I'll do anything. He fucking flew by level up. What website do you
think you're on? What do you think? What do you think you are right now? All right. Almost there.
Come on. Sixteen. You gotta get. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. I fucked it up.
Take off your prosthetic mask. I'm not messing this one up again. Take the wig off.
I hit the button at the wrong fucking time. At the wrong time. I'm trying not to hit the wrong time.
That's not rock, paper, scissors. That's one, two, three, four, five. Remove your glass eye.
What if I just like pulled a fucking prosthetic neck and shit? Like seven of my teeth came out.
One of my fucking eyes comes out. The wig comes off and like my jaw. Like I've just got a ton
of stuff on. I don't get it. I don't get it. I get it out. Fucking analog. You're really
fucking me up here. Speed up again. All right. Let's go. One shot for this. Go. Dodge. Watch out.
My eyes. Heck. My eyes. My eyes are burning. Why? Okay. We're good. I'm fine. Wrong dummy.
Is there a cut scene? Oh, his TV reception. Finally, his TV is back. The coffee looks good.
I want one. There's no fucking water in here. Are there harder levels? Are there secret levels
in this one? Are there not? There's no like secret hard levels? There's no like super 100?
At least I'm not even gonna leave it out loud. Every micro game has three levels of difficulty.
Can I start at level three? What the hell is going on in this cut scene? Oh shit. Stage clear.
Character intros. Movie matters. Thrilling. Hard. All mixed up. Thrilling. Let's try thrilling.
Okay. Why is it starting at 81? Oh man. He's gonna get us all.
On a Ritz cracker. Oh my god. The link. Which is what's up. It's a sandwich. A sandwich. A sandwich.
A sandwich. A sandwich. A sandwich. A sandwich. A sandwich. A sandwich. This one. You gotta do
more than one? What the fuck? Oh my god. Okay. You gotta do more than one. What's what's what?
What do you want to click on? Yeah. I know. Yes. Sure. You took a photo and you like did the the
smudge tool and you smudged my eye over there by like 5%. All right. That's fine.
On to the scan. That's a tiny little spot. Look at the clip. It's real. It's not fucking real.
You took you took the smudge tool and you smudged my left eye by like 40% the other direction.
It's not real. It's not real. I know it's not real. Put on the clip. I will in a minute.
Look at the clip. Look at the clip. Holy shit. That's fucked up. That's fucked up.
It's not real. This only works one time. Okay. This only works once before I catch on to the
bullshit. That's not real. Watch the clip. All right. I'll watch the clip. Give me the clip.
Where is it? You got this. You got this clip to prove that this is real. Where is the clip then?
I don't see you clip it in my office. I don't want to click on that one. That one's got like
a fucked up title. What's with the title on that one? Why is that one so fucking weird?
I don't want to click. That one's freaking me out. You're freaking me out. How to make
yourself look ugly. There is no clip. You guys are a bunch of liars. All right.
I can't do those. Am I using the filter to make your eyes look more blue?
What? I'm not like a fucking psycho. I'm going to put a filter on today to make my eyes look
wicked fucking blue. What are you talking about? I got bullied into putting the cam on in the first
place. Perfect. Guys, this is not a purple twitch hoodie. This is a blue twitch hoodie.
They made different colors. Excuse me. This is blue. It's not purple. It's a deep blue.
What game is it though? What game is it though? I hope it's fucking, I don't know. Six. Count them.
Jack, it's going to be unzipped. Hey, you know, they're getting rid of it. Oh, they go.
Ooh, that was close. Shoot. It's such a tiny little area. The pig is cute. Yeah. What are those
noises from? What are those noises from? That like, what is that from? No, no, it's from like,
it's from a, what game is it from? No, no, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not. Give me the right one.
This is not from this one. Those noises. I can, I can, I can, I can smell those noises.
I've heard them a million times before in like an NES game. Bubble Bobble? Yeah, maybe. Not Yoshi.
No, no, no, no, no. Bubble Bobble? Yeah, definitely. Pugs Bunny and Crazy Castle.
Check that shit out. Pipe E. Ooh. Pipe E? I don't know. I don't know. I don't, I don't know what it
wants me to do. I know it's the ones, the ones that are spinning. And so when you do this,
what you're trying to do is you're trying to spread it up. Blue shadow will make it so
it'll accentuate your eyes. And then what you're going to do is you're going to take the blush
brush right here and you're going to add it to this part and you're going to give yourself a
nice little shine here. Fucking damn it. I want to beat this. Oh my fucking God. And
this is a celebrity meltdown. I'm not a celebrity. Where do you get this idea of a celebrity?
Celebrity? He's an E-celebrity. Just press every button. It doesn't matter. You're a top 10
Twitch streamer. Is that even accurate? You have 7,000 people watch you several times a week.
Well, I'm glad you think I'm a celebrity. Which way do I go?
There was no way to go. He's dead no matter what. He's just fucking dead.
Let me try hard. Don't inflate his ego. I have to get at least 25. Otherwise I
refuse to stop playing until I get to 25. I have to. If you're a celebrity, why did you ignore me?
Why didn't you ignore me at the grocery store? Wait, what are you talking about?
Is this this this this this this this thing again? All like you're doing now? Yeah. Right.
Something. Whatever. Something. Whatever the fuck you. Whatever. You know the thing.
The coffee pasta. Yes. Electrical interference. Yeah.
Excellent.
25. Here it is. Thank you. Whoa. Eating BLT right now. Tish is like.
I like actually. I like actually. Actually timed that person out for like 30 minutes. That was
fucking outrageous. But I give that person like at least 10 minutes to think about what they've said.
Like you've got to think about what you've said there. I'd like for you to press like tab up
and see the last thing that you wrote. I'd like you to sit there in your 10 minutes of
silence and solitude here to say yeah I think this is this is worth other people reading this.
I want you to read. I want you to really sit there and process each word and then come back to us
with your assessment after we after you're back from the band. What did he say? Something. Something
fucking heinous. Just so disgusting and heinous that like they we have to they have to be you
have to be punished. Where did it go? What do you think about what you've done?
Nobody knows what you're talking about. Only one person needs to know and it's the person
that said the naughty thing. A perv abandon. What the fuck do you think is going to happen?
What do you think is going to happen? Hold on. I'm bad at these.
Slow mode. Slow mode. Slow mode. Help us. Slow mode. Help us. Did I lose? Hey Bowser. Get the
heck out of here. Perfect pixel. Nobody said slow mode. I did. Double finger in the nose.
That's hard. Watch it you PG-13 ass. Yep. He's never going to get to 25. Yes he is. All right.
No. Get the fuck out of here. Where is this one? Oh look at you. Oh look at you. Oh look at you
guys. I'm eating. What are you eating? What do you want to say? I think you're eating a bacon,
lettuce, and fucking tomato sandwich. Hey look at you Lindsay. Look at me. This game is
intriguing. Can I just be very clear about something? The BLT is a dog shit sandwich.
It's just a condiment fucking sandwich. It's just where's the thing that goes underneath all that?
Lettuce, tomato, and bacon with bread. Where's the thing that goes underneath it?
That's what a scam of a sandwich. Like imagine if you went to like a sub shop and you paid eight
dollars for a large BLT and eight dollars for like a large chicken palm. You're getting way more
fucking food telecommunicated down into your esophagus. BLT. And then people do what? BMT is
what people do. This game is groovy. Bacon, meat, and tomato. It's like just call it a fucking
regular sandwich. Oh my god that's hard. If you put egg on there that's no that's a substantial
addition then but why would you know but lettuce, tomato, and on a lettuce on an egg sandwich.
I wouldn't eat a lettuce egg sandwich. I wouldn't eat lettuce eggs. An egg like a bacon, egg, and
cheese sandwich with lettuce on it. I'm not gonna eat a bacon, tomato, and lettuce, cheese, and egg
sandwich on like a croissant. Starbucks sandwich. Oh Starbucks sandwich. No Starbucks sandwich is
like an egg white tomato paste wrap with feta cheese, spinach, and avocado oil in it. What's
wrong with feta? Nothing. Spinach feta wrap is 10 out of 10. I'm not I don't understand the egg
white thing. I want I want I want the fucking I want the B vitamins and I want the I want the
fun part. Did I really not get it? High cholesterol. Yeah yeah yeah oh high cholesterol yeah you got
a high cholesterol. It's and that's in so many studies proving that the cholesterol in the egg
yolks is really not even a big fucking deal and all the vitamins and all the nutrients you get from
the egg yolk are are so much better than you deleting it from your life. You know you know
how many studies there have been to prove what I'm saying correct? Am I ever gonna get 25?
Return. Webcam is desynced. I'm sure it is.
I'm trying. One guy said that. I thought we synced it up alright well. Chat stop you are killing
Jerma. Quick stretch of webcam. I got eaten by the ground. What the fuck? Alright I'm gonna
do this three more times. This one doesn't count. This one doesn't count. This one doesn't count.
That didn't count. That one didn't count. Have I done anything on thrilling mode?
Um I think this isn't this is thrilling mode. Where we are now. Still on the pig level. Omega
lol. Let me get to 25. Praise. Great. Decide. Yeah okay they're doing it's going the other way.
That's where it's like that the battle of rain thing when you're looking at logging up it goes
the other way. Break. Holy shit that was absolutely pogfix. Which one? All the way to the right.
Settle down. Settle down. And go.
Shit. No emotion for five minutes. Where is it? Where is it? Square. Square. Square. Square.
It's got a resting gamer face. Figured if I maybe I just didn't move. What do you mean? I just did
it. I pressed up. It was up up down. I pressed up first. What the hell? I don't understand. I
pressed up. I pressed up. I did press up. I pressed it. Go back in the bottom. Look. I said I pressed
it. That means I pressed it. I said it. If you look at the bot I said it right after I did it.
He's still going. I'm trying. I'm interested. This is the hard. This is insane mode. This is
thrilling mode. I gotta get to at least 25. I have to. Streaming for 2,000 more years.
That was tricky. I don't know. This side. Yeah. That went in an extra medium turtle. All right. 10.
Oh. I thought he was gonna hurt me if I touched him. I thought he was gonna hurt me if I touched
him. I don't know. Okay. I'm choking. I know. But it's hard. Not a leaf. That's a butterfly.
Eight. Damn. That's fucking hard. Come on. That one's hard to determine. That one's hard to
determine. I did it right. You just have a whole wheelie. But I got the 19s the highest. Give me
some easy ones in a row. The poop. That guy's back. What'd he say? What'd they say? They came
back and just said poop. That's it? That's okay. Just don't fucking do that. Don't do that again.
He mocked you. You don't. All right. You don't want to come into the king's court with a stick
this big. It's this small. It's like a twig that you broke off fucking like a tree. You came before
into coming into my court and you're gonna be like hey I've got something to say to you and
you're talking about the king that has like a plus 200 damage like lightning enchanted great sword
that is as tall as the ceiling and it's as light as a small baseball bat and I just literally have
to go like this and I fucking cast lightning down like Legend of Zelda on you and and I don't think
you want to do that. I've got an incredibly powerful sword versus your less powerful twig.
He's what? He's a king? Ego maniac. What? What? That's overcompensating. How so? I got what?
Because I have this huge fucking gigantic sword that's bigger than everybody else's and I can
okay that might be all right so the sword is the sword is not as high as tall as the ceiling. The
sword is like this big. No fuck the sword. It's a it's a fucking magician's wand. It's a magician's
wand. It's this big. It's small and it can fit in my hand. It's like a Harry Potter's wand. You
know what I mean? And I can just be like I could fuck it you disintegrate you. Yeah I just disintegrate
you. You don't want to come to the king's court with a fucking Harry Potter wand. They can
disintegrate you in less than 10 seconds. I don't think you want to do that. You got a fucking tree
off a branch outside. Moving on. Moving on. You don't want to don't you don't want to come fight
the king with the twig when the king's got a fucking great sword. Big bits. Oh I don't have to
I'm gonna I'm gonna I did we just play D&D? Yeah and I've had my D&D character for 30 fucking years.
You just spilled out the character sheet an hour ago. You want to throw the dice over at me? Good
luck. Core monster thanks for the 50 dollars. Thanks for the 5,000 bits and they have a very
important message. The important message is peepee poo poo. Very important for us to know. Thanks
for the 50 dollars. That's insane amount of money. That's a lot of money. Thank you core
monster for the peepee poo poo. I have no idea. Gotcha. Idiot. I don't know what the fuck that's
supposed to mean. I think I have to come to terms with the fact that I'm not gonna be able to beat
WarioWare smooth moves game cube edition. He's so rude. Oh yeah. I'm dealing with with with some
okay uh all right so i'm the i'm the rude guy now i'm the rude guy when this whole conversation
stemmed from somebody talking about of them they were going to eat a blt sandwich and and they
it was something about i'm gonna paraphrase here something about how they were like going to eat
it was it was they tasted i'm not even why would i even say it out loud again but i'm the weird
guy i'm dealing with something i'm not saying it that's it's absolutely fucking heinous why would
i ever say it we're all psychos he hates blt's yeah i've already went over it blt's are stupid
just remove the bread and you have a cob salad what's the point of the bread the bread just
makes no sense just okay if you're gonna eat a blt just remove the bread and add like some
ceasar dressing and maybe a little bit of romaine done eating a salad with bread blt's don't have
corn he's popping off he's popping off this is so based i'm glad cool whatever
i wonder in there all right that shit's hard they can let us corn and tomato why would they be corn
in a blt who's putting corn on their blt what it sounds like the fucking hit them a corn blt
corn bacon and tomato all right we already talked about this before but i really i really did think
that cbt was a time zone i thought it was like central british time or something we already went
over it that's the one all right i got i'm i'm done with this game i like one more round and
that's it i'm admitting defeat i'm gonna admit defeat here in about a moment or two
okay it's orange it's got buttons and it's orange it's got the buttons and it could be i don't know
very odd gamer gives up on easiest game i think this is the easiest game i don't agree with you
all right we haven't been this far in a while all right all right all right last one
you don't he's getting mad i'm not i'm really i'm really not
i'm really not i'm not i'm not no i'm not no i'm not i'm saying that they're saying it they keep
saying it they keep saying it stop saying it not absolutely seething he's boiling
i still don't fucking get it i'm doing this one more time and that's it and then we're going to
move on to another game this is the final the actual true final the final time i'm going to
do this the final one here it comes the true final moment final i'll be silent for a little bit i'm
going to focus only on the video game and not on you guys my eyes are going to be over here
there
i don't fucking even know what he looks like he's a funny guy with a mustache there's like
seven of them in this universe i don't know exactly what he holy shit that's fucking hard
you got one square adam sandler i thought i was the hand i thought i was the hand hey
friend i thought i was there buddy you weren't the hand what are you stupid
sorry friend i just thought i was the hand buddy if you don't shut the fuck up okay let's
i can't even put his clothes on right stop playing no no no i refuse i can't even get past level one
okay i'm done i'm done for this one uh i gotta i can take it out of the system what am i gonna
play instead of this animal crossing is not happening for a little bit longer i'm gonna
take it out let's see what's up that's it what else i got like some other shit for like the game cube
i could play what else can i put in here what am i gonna put in but um
i got the game cube set up taped it holy shit that's i got a shitload of wii games and uh and
game cube games over here so we're gonna do it one more time when do i get to play my god
why is it me i don't know why i felt like a clip of me was just playing going like oh oh i oh oh
uh that freaked me the fuck out no no no all right all right let me i'm gonna go i said we're
i'm sorry i got cut off because i'm delayed by like three full seconds i said i'm gonna go pee
i'm gonna play another game i'll be right back it's probably gonna be for the wii or the game cube