Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerba here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and today I'm going to be playing as the Soldier, and I don't know what the loadout is, forgive me.
I'm probably just going to show it on the screen right now for you to check it out, but this video is not going to be about much of the gameplay.
I'm going to talk about a very, very, very specific topic, and it does have to do with Team Fortress 2.
There are some things you could say about this topic that will fall into Team Fortress, and we'll talk about them.
So first of all, the title of the video is probably like, what is game balance or how difficult is game balance, and I will explain this title.
And pretty much what I mean by this is, how hard is it really to balance a video game?
And this is going to be one of those discussion videos where I open it up to the comments, I want to hear what you guys have to say, get something going, get some type of fight going.
Actually, don't start a fight, please don't do that.
You know, can we just talk about this for a second?
I hate when fights break out in my comment section, because I always feel like I can't pick a side.
You can never pick a side in these heated fights that happen in comment sections, because you'll piss off half the people that potentially agreed or disagreed with that particular person.
So I always like to play a referee when stuff like that happens, but I never remove comments.
One of the big things about this channel and about how I feel as a person is if somebody has an opinion, whether it be good or bad, if somebody hates my guts and wants to say Jerma, you're ugly.
I'm not going to remove that comment only because at that point you start to censor what you deem as worthy for your comment section, and it starts to get a hold of you.
You start to remove more comments, you don't like what that guy says, you don't, shut up, I don't like what you said.
I like to keep my comment section completely open, except for blatantly offensive things.
Like if somebody just starts slinging around incredibly offensive language, then I will probably remove it.
But regardless of that, we're going to move on, we're going to start talking about the actual topic of this video.
So first of all, the reason why I'm making this video is because I was hanging out in a Skype call, like I typically do with friends.
I do it pretty much every day, and we were talking specifically about one particular game.
I'm not going to throw the game under the bus, I'm not going to say, oh, it's Doom 3, it's not Doom 3.
But we were talking about a game, and we were saying, man, this is not how I would do this.
This game has a lot of broken stuff in it, as fun and as good as it is.
There's some things that are really wrong with this game.
And unfortunately, here's the real predicament when you start talking that type of language with people, is we don't know as gamers what happens behind the scenes.
None of us have any type of crystal ball that can show us what happens in these development studios on a typical workday.
We just don't know that.
But what we do know is passion, and a lot of us are core gamers.
I consider myself a pretty core gamer, and we get very invested in the games that we are currently playing,
enough so that we start to see problems that developers might not even see because they are just working on these games
and sort of going through the motions when they go to work.
Now, I am not saying that all these development studios that could have potentially unbalanced or imbalanced things in their game,
they don't just go to work and like, I'm done, let's go get shit-faced.
No, obviously, if you work in the gaming industry and you work in the art field, you work in the balance field, you are passionate.
You don't go into gaming, you don't go to work for a gaming company not caring about the games that you make.
But I really do feel like there is a disconnect between development companies and communities.
And I've talked about communities in a video before where the more invested in the community
and what the community has to say that a game company is, the game will turn out 10,000 times better,
and people are more willing to throw money at it.
That's why Team Fortress 2 has done so well and why people support it so much.
Sure, I could probably name you like a couple things in Team Fortress 2 that I think are just dumb.
But really though, if you look at the big picture and how much support that Valve has shown the community
and how much they've actually listened over the years,
and Valve's motto, Valve's motto over the last at least few three or four or five years has been games as a service, in quotes.
And what that means is instead of just releasing a video game and saying,
it's done, it sucks, you know what?
Screw it. If you don't like it, then we'll try better next time.
We already got you $60. I don't care. I'm the CEO of this big company and I have like two jets.
That's the disconnect I'm talking about.
But how hard is it, how difficult is in reality is it to balance a video game?
Because when we were talking in the Skype call that I mentioned,
we were mentioning things that seemed like they were very basic mathematical changes
that you could do to completely fix the game.
And it really got me thinking. It's like there has to be a reason why some of these things do not get changed.
There has to be a reason behind it, even with community outcry,
even with people saying, man, there's something really wrong with that, dude.
Are you going to do anything about that?
And it happens across the board in a lot of different games.
And who is ultimately responsible for the final decision of a game change?
Is it a one dude? Is it a team of people that come together and they say,
okay, we're going to do this, we're going to change X, Y, and Z.
And then they hand that off to some guy and he can like veto it if he really wants to.
Anybody in the comments that has any type of game development experience
or if you know something about this or if you actually have real world experience with this,
please let me know because that's a question I've been asking myself for a very long time.
All the way back to my like Diablo days when I would see something that just really in my mind didn't make sense.
Why don't things get changed when they very evidently should?
And I guess I'm going to end the video there. That's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Keep the discussion going in the comments. I'll be chiming in a little bit as well.
And thank you so much for watching. I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.