Let's open it up. There it is. Let me just make this different.
So I have a confession to make here, and I'm sorry to all the people that were
expecting it. Zero playing off stream. I played a little bit off stream. I did
some side stuff, because it was just, I just couldn't stream with my internet,
obviously. And I'm not sure how much longer we're going to get of being
green. So by the way, just want to make sure I say this.
See you soon. Thanks for watching everybody. It's been
pretty fun stream so far, but this might just go to zero because it just does
that at like seven o'clock. So I did do some stuff off the
camera here. Let's go ahead and get it on the screen. There it is.
And I can go like this. All right, so where were we? I did one
mission where I unlocked the fence. I'm an idiot. Let me just update
this. RdRd2. RdR2. I can't, what do I think? A title for this.
What should I title? It takes me like the amount of time to create a
character in a game. To make a title in a game. Just do the boring
stuff off stream. That was kind of the idea.
Was to make a little bit of money, do some hunting, and trade some stuff,
make some money, pay off my bounties, and now here we are ready to play.
Okay, how about RdRd, how about just Red Dead Redemption gameplay?
Red Dead Redemption 2 gameplay only. 480p. Am I trying to get people to
not come here? I don't understand. Am I trying to just lose everybody?
How about Red Dead, how about RdR2? No gameplay. Only commentary.
That's worse. How about, I'm just doing RdRd2 continue. Done.
Horseball stream. Oh Red Dead Redemption, okay.
I got it. Boring title. Whatever. Don't you guys know, don't ever judge a
book by its cover. Open up the first chapter and read it.
The Reddit Redemption. Alright, so here we go. Let's uh,
let's open her up. Wait, hold on a minute. My microphone is
synced up. Okay. Just making sure I was synced.
Make sure the audio here is telling me. Make sure we do this now.
You should be hearing Lethal League ball hit every time I go
duh duh duh. Okay, I'm ready. I did get another horse too by the way.
Just go, just go. I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Those of you that were here for Lethal League and you are, don't want to be
spoiled, you don't want to see anymore. Every streamer plays Red Dead
Redemption 2, every single one, I understand.
Thanks for coming. See you soon. Uh, where's my horse over here?
Toy Story Woody's Adventure. Oh, I can't.
I can't take him to camp, that's right. Let me figure out what I want to do.
Let's go. There's a loan shark mission over here.
This looks like a, let's go to Maryland. That sounds like a plan. Oh
no. Hmm. Don't ask that you get Micah out of
the gym. Yeah, we've been on this one. Let's go to this one.
Just do it. We were, that was a story mission
like six hours ago. I think it's time to do it.
This is a different horse. Yes, it's because I stabled the other one because
I didn't want to get too fatigued. Those of you that can see what
happened when a gamer or a horse, it doesn't matter if you're a
human, everybody gets gamer fatigue. It happens.
What's this horse's name? The horse's name is Thunder.
I don't know, I was eating. I had fucking like a bowl of spaghetti in one
hand. I just did the easiest thing I can think of.
Whisper's still fine, yeah. Whisper's around still.
Just stabled. Oh my god, we got an event over here.
Please, anyone. Okay, what's what's up? You all right?
Medicine or a siphon? Suck out the venom.
That's an option. Then you know what? This doesn't work. This doesn't work.
No, it doesn't. I saw I saw like a clickbait YouTube video that said it
didn't work. You saved my life. You're gonna give me
money or something? All right, money. Treasure map. Family
platinum jewel. That's it. Keep your eyes on the ground.
Let's go. That's it. All right, fine.
Fine. I saved, yeah I know I saved him, but doesn't he like give me
something in return? You gotta have like something in your
pocket, man. All right, yeah, he'll show up later.
We're good. Greedy streamer wants... oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
we got a loan shark mission right here.
I gotta collect the debt from somebody. First of all,
put the bow away? Give me like the shotgun. No no no no no no no no no
listen. Okay, give me the double-barred
shotgun. Don't bark. Don't bark. Don't bark.
These loan sharking missions you have to go collect. What why would you
put... what are you doing? What the hell was that?
I didn't do that. Okay, let's find him. Usually they've run.
I'm here to collect. Hey, looking for someone?
I am actually. Ah, who's this then? These cards is the only world team
we're likely to meet. You're asking the wrong feller.
Okay, the outside? They're just playing poker. Where's the
actual dude? Let's explore the area. Eventually we'll find him.
There you are. Do you smoke sir? This is not a loan shark.
Not as much as you. Oh no no don't worry about these. Actually
let me take some. Smoking and other hobbies. Oh thank you.
What are all the cigarettes for? Were you heading on a long journey or
something? No no no nothing like that at all.
I'm just interested in the cards. Okay. Cigarette cards.
Oh you got me? Yeah. Oh this is okay. Let me take a look. Come on. I actually have
quite a few of these, don't I? Yeah, I'll pay a good price.
Okay. Ah, nothing I haven't got. Oh bullshit. The value isn't
completing the debt. Sometimes I'll smoke up to 200 cigarettes in one day
just so I can keep opening the packs. I wish I could explain to you the
pleasure and the pain I get out of collecting these babies.
Sure, well it sounds thrilling. Yeah it is. Not to mention the vast
amounts of life-reaffirming cigarettes I get to smoke.
Oh. Sucking poison doesn't work. You get it on your mouth and it goes in
your bloodstream, see?
Meow meows.
There's so much side content in this game.
It's insane. There's so much to do.
All this stuff just, you don't even have to do any of this.
It's wild. Collect all the cigarette cards and mail the completed sets to
Phineas. Well, so we're out of this way.
We're still, yeah, yeah, yeah. 12 cards, that's that.
Still on the trek to go to see Micah. Good, good, good, good. Don't run into the
train. That would be bad. It's nothing
impressive. It's still fun though. You've been
hunting in Red Dead Redemption 2 for the past week and hardly done any
story stuff. Yeah, it's a wild west is such a
great setting. There's so much cool shit in this
time period that like it's surprising that not more
people try to do it. I definitely have to try to like
road rage somewhere. Well, we actually have to go this
way. We could use a BAP too. The horse is
kind of dirty. Wild West VR game. That actually
might get my attention. You would actually probably sit me
down for 45 minutes straight. What the fuck are you doing?
These pigs? These dogs? Oh boy!
Oh dogs everywhere!
Is there another one? There's another one! Oh, what the fuck was that for?
Okay, one hit and I was dead there. Damn. Leave him alone. Rip horse.
Horses. The horse is fine. Poor. Well, these are going to be worth nothing.
It's because I ran into a rock. Oh, I have the pelt on me. Come here.
The car is dead. Stop running into shit and come over here.
It's definitely not even worth taking these. I've shot so many holes in them.
No, forget it. I mean, maybe it's worth it for the meat.
Okay, I can cook the meat. I'll take it. Why did I kill the wild autos?
Because the wild auto is all ganged up on me
and tried to kill me at the same time. The game meat.
I can sell that. I use it. What's this guy's problem?
Oh, is he mad about the wolves?
Where the hell is this? Is this the same road, man? What, I'm not allowed to
take the same highway as you? Good morning. All right, let's go.
Let me first want to drop and gets the gold. Why?
Why is this happening? It's an ambush. Okay, are these guys in the wolves
working together? Seriously, do they send their like
World of Warcraft fucking pets at me first? I don't understand.
Everybody wants to be dead. I paid off on my bounties too. What's up with
this? You're good. Let's get some free stuff.
Probably old Drew. That guy had five dollars. Damn.
Okay, this is a witness, right? He doesn't care. Good.
Sometimes they stop and they get very upset at you.
These guys have a decent amount of money. Gold wedding ring.
Where's this dead horse? These are random dudes. Five bucks.
Where's the dead horse? The horse is back there.
Let me feed mine. Up on the hill here.
I don't see it on the minimap. Where are you horse?
Where the hell feed your house? Well, oh well.
It's back where you parked it. No, I didn't go. Did I go that far?
Let's just take a look back here because they were chasing me from like
over here. Okay, there they are. Are these the wolves?
Are these the wolves? Are you a horse? No, you're a wolf.
Well, well, let's go. I ain't gonna search around for it.
It's up on the hill where the horse was standing.
Wouldn't have to show up on the minimap. So many random things.
So many random things. Come on, man. Hey, what's up?
You scared me. Boiled Satan? Yeah, I get that a lot.
What? What do you mean? What's that you got there?
You ain't interested in no scrap paper. It's nothing.
Just something for wiping. He'll freak out. He doesn't know where I am.
Well, I guess to go now. What? Hey, why the hurry?
Animal cruelty? What? This guy's an animal?
What? Hold on. I got his map. Animal cruelty. You've acquired a map
leading to a treasure that is rumored to be cursed. Many have died looking
for it. Who's the witness to animal cruelty?
Crime reported. Oh, hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait.
They don't know the whole story there. That's absolute bullshit.
I was wildly, rabidly attacked by animals and I had to save myself.
I was going to be killed. This is actually a pretty good horse.
He's okay, right? Okay. New horse. I'm gonna get out of here now.
How far away are they? They're not gonna find me. I'm 50 miles ahead of you.
I shot a horse during a fight with bandits? Well, what am I supposed to
do about that? I'm getting bombarded by all sides.
Thunder's fine. Thunder's coming behind us. I need to claim this is my own, though.
I'm gonna go to Stables. Is there a stable down here?
Cruelty. Well, at least I got the map here.
I tried to be nice to him. He just didn't even have any of it.
Sometimes not just changing the mask. Gotta change clothes, too.
That would make sense. Another random encounter.
These guys don't care. I'm in bad sorts here. I took
a little jolt and have managed to get myself hopelessly lost.
I am staying in strawberry. If you could just guide me back.
You need to ride to strawberry. Okay. I think of a good reason to say no.
Lead the man to strawberry. Oh, thank you. Thank you, sir. You need a horse?
Well, after you. What possessed me to come out here, I'll never know.
Wait, I have to lead him? So this guy is just a guy following me now.
I have a horse he can get on. Natural. I'm just visiting.
He can borrow it. I'm from New York City, actually.
You don't say? Oh, yes. There was some talk at the country club about this
burgeoning little resort town called strawberry.
So I thought it might be quite the trip to see what all the fuss was.
Just an escort mission. I have to make a few investments while it was still undervalued.
Turns out I was made the fool. It's a town of splinters.
If you could call it much of a town at all, I'd hardly stepped off the carriage
and I'd taken an old place. Should I get off the horse?
I suppose some might call it charming. Let me tell you,
charm is not worth much these days. You show me a timber frame, Jack,
and I'll show you Broadway. Meanwhile, you have this mayor, a
quite intolerable blowhard. He doesn't usually do that.
The man's completely deluded. Well, I should give him some credit.
He must be quite the salesman. He didn't get me out here after all.
More fool me. Now I'm tromping through the leaves and the muck was up.
This horse likes me. Cowboy. No offense.
This horse bonded me faster than anybody else.
Please kill this guy. Why? I have no reason to kill this guy yet.
For what reason? Look, I'm not just a maniac.
I don't kill people for no reason. There has to be a reason behind it
every time. A lot of people coming out of here. I had no reason to kill the
map that he didn't give me when I asked it for.
What do you mean there wasn't a reason? I want your map. Give it to me.
I don't have anything. This guy's not going to hold out on me.
He has a nice hat. I don't like that hat. I don't think it would look good on me.
I don't think that hat would look good. He's got nice shoes.
Not nice enough. Why couldn't he just walk here by
himself? You seem quite the resourceful
sort, sir. I don't get it. If for some reason you couldn't just walk half a
mile. You may want to look into that
gabbing mayor. Something is definitely off with him.
Ask? Talk to the mayor. All right. Keep that in mind.
Got some intel on the mayor. Maybe stay in town for now.
I've been to Hard Place. Thanks anyway. This looks like a Skyrim town. This
looks like the first Skyrim town. Is that all we done? I think that's
Yeah, this is the very first Skyrim town. I don't need to follow him still, but I'm
kind of... I just kind of want to hear his
whole story. Hey, this is the whole town. It's probably stable here.
It actually is. Press O. No. Somebody already got me with that. I do have
stuff to sell with Butcher. This guy's done.
Congratulations. You win. Let me sell some of this shit.
All right, we got, we got... Not bad. Big game meat. I'll sell it all. Maybe not
all of it, because I can cook this. Get rid of the shitty
bird meat. Shitty rabbit pelt. Turkey feather. I'll keep the turkey
feather. I'll keep like five turkey feathers.
Big game meat. I need a stable. Is there a stable in this town?
There is no stable here. Well, that's just not good, is it?
Dammit. No stable? Well, here's one. A little outside of town. I was looking
in the town. I was just looking. I'm sorry. I was
paying attention to this.
Don't run him over, boys. What are you doing? Don't get up here.
I gotta talk to him like the freaks and geeks. Freak and weirdo.
To bring you the great news. The great news that you are saved today.
This even happens in that first level in Skyrim.
You guys are in the same spot. So we can spend eternity together.
They did. Hello, sir. Do you want to be saved?
Sure. Yes, desperately. Well, that's
wonderful news. You are. Come on. That's really all there is to it.
Just do more good things and less bad ones
and we can be together for all of eternity. What's wrong with this guy?
You and me. Am I gonna get married to these guys?
What? Great. Okay. I think that's all I can do with this guy.
Married now. Appreciate a little more room here. Rejoice. Push him. No,
I can't. I just cleared all my bounties. It was so expensive.
Together we shall light up paradise with a whole
Wait, that's not the horse I want. That's a great light
that shines from within about the great glories of life. Yes,
glories that I embody. You all thought I was gonna run right into him.
You thought I was gonna ram right into that guy, didn't you?
There's a time for living and there's a time
for dying and your time has come. Hey, I want a new horse. This one.
I'll stable you. Need a new name though, right?
All right, let's saddle this one up and I want to
change the name. Horse care package. Let's rename the horse.
What does the horse look like? We got like kind of navy blue.
Could be old navy. Old navy. What the fuck are these suggestions?
Bean bag sonic? It can't be bean bag sonic. That's to be like a horse
bag sonic. Why would it be bean bag? There. Okay. Upgrade. I got 320 bucks.
Let's see what's big. Saddles. What's on the back of sonic the hedgehog?
Is it red? Red spikes? What? White? It's white, right? It's blue. It's just, is it
blue? All blue. That's pretty close. Okay.
Got it on. I already own it. You have this item equipped already. Okay.
Saddle bags. Upgraded. Here's blue. 40 fucking dollars, man.
It's worth it. I know. That's what I just said.
Stirrups. Try to give them red shoes. I'll, I don't know if you can.
Corge rain rate. Bell stirrup. Any of these any better?
I mean, I already have. The bell stirrup does a better job. Yeah, just put the bell one on.
It's already equipped. Corge rain rate. It's higher, but
that's fine. Horns. This is the, this is the joystick.
Sock puppet? I think I want the sock puppet.
Diablo. Hmm. Yeah. We're going with sock puppet.
Blankets. I don't even need any of these. It's the one that I already have.
It's fine. Bedrolls. I don't think, can you do shoes?
No, this one's fine. All right. Grooming.
Main. We need long spikes. I mean, that's not even close. I get, that's
as close as it's gonna be though. Yeah, it has to be the white ones.
What? You guys don't have mobile? Why are you saying that?
Does he, the Sonic doesn't have a tail. No, he just, he's just blue.
That's fine. Okay, anything else that we can do?
No, I can't do anything with the shoes, right? Grooming. No.
Services. You could just do a care package.
Yeah, let's just like, let's care package to the horse. What's with the
blue mohawk? Then it's like, what? Yeah, what's
up with that? That's weird. Okay. All right, here's
Horsebag Sonic. A little bit slower than, uh,
no, at the moment it's a little faster than Thunder. I mean, Whisper's just too
good, but that's, that's like kind of cheating.
This is the, this is the you spent $20 horse. No.
All right, let's go. That's not even a white main.
Oh, it's the wrong lighting. All right, let's see how fast you can go.
Pretty fast, actually. Pretty fast. Back to, okay,
Micah. We were trying to get to Micah. Come on. Micah.
Hold down P. What do you mean P? Crazy fool. See, that was pretty cool.
All right, Micah. Time for a mission. Break Micah out of this prison, right?
Micah. In here? Horse hybrid. Hello, sir. I've, uh, I've come from
Blackwater. I'm on the trail of a dangerous gang,
Tomo Drisco. Heard you had some sort of incident.
No deal with bounty hunters around here, son. I was just wondering if I could
get a description. Well, they weren't friends. They got
in a fight, two men got killed. Now one of them's an idiot, the other's
some kind of dumb mix, so maybe them's your boys.
Can I get my bounty back? I already paid for it.
Thank you, Sheriff. I do need another outfit. I've been doing this same
outfit's been here for a while. Okay, locate and speak to Micah.
Do I have to sneak? Am I allowed back here? Arthur, Arthur.
Hello, old friend. Had a good time. Tagged on.
You going to get me out of here? I ain't decided yet.
Real fucking- Am I clean shaded? I've lost her out of your mouth these
last six months, and now the opportunity to watch you be
silent. Well, you gotta do something. I always looked up to you, Arthur.
You can pull this card. Listen, there's one little problem.
A town full of people wanting to see you swing.
You got to do something, Arthur. I do. So we have to find a way to free
Micah. Do I have to blow this building?
All right, hold on. Stand back. This wall just needs some good force.
Might want to step back.
I did it. Let's get out of here. Come on.
What the fuck is this guy? He wasn't O'Driscoll. What?
It worked. I'm just standing right here.
Out. Just driving around. What am I doing, man? I just used them.
Right? What the fuck would I do that for? There wasn't anybody- I just lit
another one. Throw it. Get it out of here quick. Get it out of here.
Wait, no. Wrong button. Okay, those of you that need to know,
if you press L2, it lights it. It lights it when you press L2.
Oh, fuck. Easy.
I didn't know that when you press L2, it just lights it up.
I got some deadeye here. Should I use it? Might as well. Was that just random
person? That might have been just random.
I want to loot all these people so bad.
All right, back to the shotgun here.
I got that- wait, I got this guy? How did I get that guy?
I think that camcorder fell down. I got cocaine?
All right, we don't need to clear this room. Do we need to clear the room?
Wanted. Slice. What the fuck is happening?
Oh my god, he just killed somebody in there.
We're wanted right now, we gotta go.
Oh, on the top? Nope, we're good. Hold on, just wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to pick it- just wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm gonna get at least like two
cigarettes off this guy. These are our horses. Nice. All right,
let's go. Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Okay, we're good. I can't shoot this guy. And I got off
the fucking horse. That's just wonderful, that wasn't it.
The horse is fucked up. The horse is injured. The horse is-
I'm on a fucking bonko. I'm on a fucking bronco.
Oh Jesus. Wait, wait, the horse- my horse is hurt.
I need to feed the horse. Drink this. Drink it. Drink. Have some.
Okay, you're good. That's a gun. Drink it.
No, I need something that's gonna refill your core here.
More stamina, of course health. I need some cores here.
There we go. Just eat it. There we go.
All right, we're good.
We have some gifted subs here from Kazzy, thank you Kazzy101.
For your five gifted subs. Thanks a lot man.
Thanks for your generosity.
Lightning.
I like the storm skyshift, it's pretty cool.
Kinda need to do this, right? With that stormy sky, looks good.
I think we finally lost them. I hope so.
I'm giving you a holster. My way of saying thank you.
And thank you. A holster? There I was having a dull day only for you.
To liven it up by letting me help you shoot up half a town.
You're a funny fella, Arthur. Real funny.
Why you act all sour all the time. Yeah well, you ain't funny at all. So why
you gotta act like the court jester? Right, listen.
I'm sorry, but we're family now. Arthur,
you and me. Son of a... I don't know about this guy. Makes us brothers.
Sometimes, brothers make mistakes. Now I'm heading back to my little camp
where I'm back a strawberry. Come see me. Can you get struck by
lightning in Red Dead Redemption 2? You ain't heading back to Dutch? No.
That would be hysterical. I ain't seeing Dutch
till I can bring him a peace offering. No, you cannot.
Are you kidding me? I mean, are they trying to make this the best game ever?
You can now own the offhand holster. This allows you to carry two sidearms at
once and dual wield them. Okay.
How are we doing? Sawed-off shotgun. So this is
dual wield. Oh man, that's cool. What does aiming do then? Is it both
of them at the same time? Committing serious crimes will cause
towns to go into lockdowns. This is shown by a red area in the pause
map. So we killed everybody in this town so
we can no longer use this town. Hold on, wait, wait, wait. I have a
bounty in here? $85. Well, that wasn't even my fault.
That's bullshit. Let's go. You dual wield.
Oh right, I forgot. I'm aiming the gun at people.
That guy doesn't have a face anymore. You can't just do that. Well, I was
checking the dual wield. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop. You didn't see shit.
My aim is so bad. It kicked him off. Okay,
I gotta get out of here. I have to leave right now.
Horse revival. It's my horse now. Okay, you're fine. You're good.
What kind of horse is it? Ooh, nice. Not bad.
Everyone told me the horse sucked. I looked over. I revived it and was like,
horse sucks, bad horse, shitty speed. I just, I was trying to get off of
him. Sort of dealt by decision making. I
didn't, hey, he ran. I didn't. I just, I just got off of him.
All right. I just got off. That made me sad.
I'm sorry. No, you're not. I'm not gonna jump off.
Just, I got a telephone pole. Can I get down there from here? No, I
probably can't. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Hold on a second here. I think we may have found a little campsite.
Let's hitch the horse. Put some backpacks and everything. There's
probably something over here. This is why this game's so cool,
because this is just random shit everywhere.
It's gotta be something, right? All this stuff over here and there's not anything
here for me to take. This is really cool. Nothing? Yeah,
there's a box right here. So I didn't show up when I walked into it
before. Apparently, I can't do anything with
this. No, I don't. I opened it up. All right. What's in it?
Stand on the other side. That doesn't matter. There's nothing in here.
There's clearly a fucking apple in here though, guys. I mean, for real.
No, crouch. I'm doing it. I broke somebody's lunchbox. Well, you
shouldn't have left it there if you cared about it.
There's something over here. In the well. Let's go.
Too blurry. Wait, I could actually go down this way, can I?
Yeah, I can go down here. Why is this GPS telling me to go
this way? I definitely cannot make it down here.
Thanks a lot, fucking Google Maps. We're both over here.
I think I can get down here. We made it. We're good.
It's all right. You're fine. You're fine. You're good. You're good.
It's fine. Come on. How deep is this?
I gotta test the depth. It's pretty deep.
That's really deep. I don't know if it's gonna make it.
See, look at how deep this is. You become blunted if you're seen in this area.
I'm not going back there, am I? I mean, how...
This whole area is on lockdown. I can't even go over here.
Be careful. I gotta sneak around. The entire side of the map over here is
on lockdown. Holy shit. I just don't be seen by anybody
in the law. Dead Eye Core is empty.
Oh, let's see. I can eat something, right? Let's drink some brandy.
And let's also drink another one. Why not? Just gin. Yeah, drink some gin too.
All right, we're good. So I just need to sneak over here.
The person I need to talk to is right here.
Oh, we're supposed to be over here. Look, I'm here, guys.
I made it. Sorry it took me so long. I was busy.
I ghost-rid a horse off a cliff. I killed a whole town worth of people.
And that's where it's going to remain for now. I think he's bait.
Well, I want to trial him publicly. Gentlemen,
Sean is being moved up the up. You're going to hear too. I started this
mission as well. I was drinking at a bar and
punching people. Sorry. We need to rescue him now.
Moose? Of course not. Ike's Skeletons, boys.
I'm moving him to a camp nearby before handing him over to them.
One person thought that was me. So I guess we need to stop them before they
get to camp. Charles, why don't you head up on the
north side and we'll head up on the other side of the valley and meet you.
That way we have them in either direction.
Javier, Josiah, come on. Let's go see.
Come on. You know, Ike. I was gonna throw dynamite down there, but that's too easy.
Angry. Sure. Rescue Sean and then we'll get ourselves lost good and proper.
It's a big country. I hope so. Okay, get on your horse. So we got
Sonic, Tails, and Shadow.
Find the boat. Let's do it. Let's see if we can track down this boat.
Keep your eyes open. Knuckles is red. They got patrols out all over this area.
Yes, south of the river West Elizabeth isn't a very welcoming place right now.
It's definitely as bad as we feared over here.
I keep hearing about this woman, Heidi McCourt.
Hold up here. Hold up. Reckon those might be our boys.
All right gentlemen. Gotta intercept the boat.
Nice and easy. Let's make sure it's him first before you go starting
another war. They're already looking at us.
Do you think they can see us? If they can, we're just three fellas out on
the trail. Act natural. We'll be fine.
So, you've been gone for a while. Much as I love charging the law and
sleeping in the dirt with you derelicts, I do have a lot of business to attend to.
This is never a straight road anywhere. Especially with you.
Nice guy. He's coming out of an old record player.
People to rob.
He hasn't stopped talking since we left you in Valentine.
Fog is riding my life. Cute, dear boy.
Hey, cute. Have you ever heard of radio?
No, I don't think so. Pick up the pace a bit.
Well, you're leading. All right, you want me to lead? Fine. Get out of the
way then. Apparently there's a camp somewhere
around. bounty hunters and transfer before continuing out West.
He's turning back yelling at me to go faster.
You're the guy in the lead. I'm just kind of following the boat.
Cinematic mode. Let's just keep it in sight, right?
I don't really have any control here. Well, do I?
They've stopped. All right, let's take a closer look.
All right, the boat's stopped. This gentleman. So who are these bounty hunters?
There he is. I don't know too much about arch-skeletons, boys.
They're a big crew, wild, built some reputation in the last year or two.
That looks like Sean to me. Certainly kicking up enough of a fuss.
So they execute him out here? Yep, that's definitely Sean.
Oh, they're giving him a decent kicking. Well, you can only imagine the
shit he's been giving them. Oh yes, they're taking him up the
canyon. Is it gallows up here or something?
Why am I... I thought that was somebody else that we didn't know.
That wasn't connected to us doing the same thing.
Just waving at us. We're just tourists on either side of the attraction.
This is gonna be stealth mission, right? Turn up the volume?
How's that? Better? We should do this quietly if we can.
Leave it to me, gentlemen. I'll go around and create a distraction.
Then you two sneak across and do the dirty on them.
Okay? Distraction. Crouch down out of...
All right, so give me my knife. Take out your knife.
Wait. Okay, I have the knife out. It's TMS.
You take the one and keep down. Slow down, slow up a little bit, man.
Slow up a little bit. You're gonna do it before I get there. Dude, come on.
Let's get up there.
Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Cattleman revolver. I have one of those.
Never mind. I don't want that. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I don't have a horse. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Where'd they go?
Oh, wait. I'm in the water. I gotta go up this way. Hurry, hurry.
I was too busy fucking looking at this loot.
Halfway up the canyon to deal with.
To clean this gun. Looks good, right? Come on. Take out the bounty hunters.
Stealthy. No sound.
To get back home again. Me neither. I get. Just travel.
What?
There! Look out!
They turned around like that. I have a plan, R.
Oh, man. He's dead. Oh, no. This guy.
I see Charles up there.
Which one's Charles? I don't know which one's the bad guy. He's using the Lux.
I just aimed at him and he died.
Oh, good. Wouldn't go that far.
The camp's up this way. Come on.
Truck guns. I have a bow.
I'll take the left side, Charles. You go right, okay?
I guess.
Follow him, boy.
Let's take these easy we putas.
God damn army.
Oh, right in the throat. Oh, I only have one shot left.
This is fun to use, though.
What the hell was that? Oh, I'm gonna die.
All right. Is that happening or am I crazy?
During the middle of a fight, does this happen automatically once I actually drink it?
Let's get Sean.
I got my arrow back.
Rescue Sean. What do you got down here?
Is this the button for healing items?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to. There's so much stuff.
Are you gonna get me down from here?
Oh, right. Okay.
Shoot, bro.
No, I ain't doing that all over again.
You know, you're a lot less ugly from that other angle, Arthur.
Come on.
Do we get a hug, Arthur? A warm embrace for a lost brother now found.
New character.
You know, nothing means more to me than this gang, the bond we share.
It's the most real thing to me.
I would kill for it, I would happily die for it.
But in spite of all of that,
I would have easily left you here to rot if Charles hadn't stopped me.
I don't believe a word of that, Arthur.
Get him out of here.
You're a great man, Arthur Morgan.
The kind of young whipper snapper I can really admire.
Oh, shut up.
Right. We should split up.
Javier, will you escort Mr. McGuire back to camp?
That was a trailer moment.
Charles, best you ride separately.
Be careful. There's patrols everywhere.
What about you?
I'm gonna see what's worth taking here.
I'll meet you back there as soon as I can.
All right.
Okay, come on.
Have I got stories for you?
Yeah. I can't wait.
Well, imagine y'all missed me a lot.
But fear not.
The joy's back in your lives now.
Bronze.
I'm getting hungry.
Actually, in human world hungry.
Not in video game world.
Again, let me, I want to make sure I reiterate this again.
Tonight, this is the, the suggestions of the,
the green screen suggestion channel is going to be locked tonight.
So if you have some, something great that you'd like me to see,
you got to get it there before like four hours from now.
How long?
Chest up here, maybe?
What?
Crime reported.
What? Did somebody call the police?
I don't understand.
Where? Who reported the crime?
Nothing up here.
Somebody's investigating.
I gotta go now.
Get off.
I ain't going that way.
Is there a date for the green screen?
There is not a date yet.
Are they gonna hit a bird in mid-air?
That was weird.
The date is probably going to be this coming next weekend.
All right, let's see.
What do I want to do now?
What's this?
Trapper.
Okay.
This whole side of the map is in lockdown.
I have to go back over here.
I don't really have anything I can do.
I gotta like go to bed.
I'm gonna go back to my town here.
I'm gonna go to sleep.
But yeah, I'm gonna hope for this coming weekend.
That should be, it should give me enough time to
to buy all the props, have the props all get shipped
to the necessary.
I think I need to, hold on.
I think I have an achievement or something I can do
to shoot rabbits on horseback.
I kind of lost my opportunity there, didn't I?
Easy now.
Maybe not.
I'm very smelly.
Yeah, I know.
Okay, doesn't, I don't think this is rabbits.
What the hell were those?
What is that?
I'm dying.
No.
Yuck.
He did the voice.
And yeah.
Wait, what?
One of those is a raccoon?
Oh wait, how is one of those?
Okay.
I guess.
Any more?
I need rabbits.
Oh well.
Let's take a look.
What do I got?
Challenges.
Find a treasure.
Win blackjack five times.
Eat.
Throw different berries.
Yeah.
If I could just kill two more rabbits on horseback.
Good luck finding a rabbit.
Rabbits in this game are just everywhere.
But never when you want them to be around.
What is that down there?
What is that?
There's something up here.
Oh, it's a skunk.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Can you just spray my skunk?
This is a, it's poor.
All right, let's track the skunk.
Can I get sprayed?
I kind of want to just get sprayed.
Come here.
Come here, spray me.
Why are you so, you're so slow.
Come here.
I don't know.
I'm not going to kick a skunk.
They're so cute.
I'm not, no.
It's not going to spray me.
It doesn't spray me.
I can't do that to a skunk.
Go live a very healthy life.
For at least the next like 11 months.
Because that's how long you live.
And that's just sad.
All right, come back here.
Corner it.
I don't think I can.
It's open field.
I can't, what is it going to do?
Throw a punch at it.
Well, what if I just go like this?
Spray me.
Spray me in the face.
Do it.
I don't think it's going to happen.
I need to get a skunk fact?
Oh well.
I tried.
All right, back to camp.
Run a little over the car.
Turkeys.
Did he just die?
Where is he?
Is he hiding in the bush?
All right, so let's see if the turkey will spray me in the face.
He just face planted.
No, I don't, I don't want to hole in that one.
Let's go.
Can you lasso a turkey?
That's not going to work, right?
Where the hell did he go?
He's just in circles.
Where did he go?
Where the fuck is he?
I don't see a turkey.
Whatever.
I'm going to go.
That was full-on.
It's like mouth into tree.
This got outspotted by a turkey.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Speaking of animals.
We got hay.
Pet the horse.
Okay, civilization.
Hey, partner.
Head still rolling from the road.
Oh, wait, wait.
He doesn't have any weapons.
I'm just kidding.
It was a joke.
Here, take your horse back.
Stop.
Take the horse back.
I was kidding.
Hey, come here.
Come here.
It was, I was making a joke.
Whoa.
Where's his hat?
No, no, no, no, no.
Give me that back.
Psycho laugh.
Good joke.
I wasn't, I wasn't really trying to make a joke in his
jump to his horse.
And then he got mad.
Bro, why, why would he?
Hey, nice hat.
Where'd you get it?
I found it.
Who got Bill?
I'm coming with you, man.
Let's take care of this.
Let me maintain this gun, though.
How is it?
You coming?
No, I don't need to do that.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Let's go.
All right.
Lead the way.
Is it going to be a devil cross?
It better not be.
So how'd you find him?
He said he was going hunting.
Never returned.
Was able to track him pretty easily.
Only a matter of time before they decide to pick up camp.
Ahead for town.
That's really cool.
The mission can come to you.
That's pretty interesting.
Fair point.
Is this random?
It might, it might be.
I thought he was just going to run to the tree.
He's a problem.
We all know it.
I need some cores here.
Hold on.
I need health and deadeye.
If I have anything, they can do that for me.
I think it is.
That's okay.
That's good enough.
I really probably should just refill the deadeye, but whatever.
Okay.
Okay, we're getting close.
A rescue Bill.
There they are.
On foot from here.
Any more arrows?
Um, sawed off shotgun.
Double barreled pump action.
I think I'm going to use the repeater here.
Let's take out your position.
How does this thing look?
We could use a cleaning.
All right, we're good.
It's in pretty decent condition.
So we're going to stake this out.
So Bill is over here capturing.
Anyone you are, Arthur?
I don't know where he is.
Actually, I might be able to get him.
All with one deadeye here.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Is that Dutch?
None of you guys are the guy I'm supposed to be expecting.
Look at that horse.
Look at that fucking horse.
Come here, you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come here.
Look at you.
You're huge.
No, get out of the way.
The horse.
Hey, I need to...
Whose horse?
Oh, it's Bill's horse.
I was going to say, damn, man.
Can I have that?
Take Bill's shit.
Arthur, when are they going to learn?
I can't make him have an accident.
All right.
Well, I should be getting on.
All right, Morgan.
That's it.
That horse is crazy.
Well, whatever.
That was cool.
A little random encounter.
I think I've looted everybody except for these guys over here.
Don't leave just yet.
What about crates and shit?
Boxes hanging up here?
I don't think so.
I don't see anything.
There's a hat.
Ah, ah, ah.
There it is.
Right here.
What?
There is a lot of stuff.
No, I can't take any more brandy or biscuits.
What am I going to do?
Get out of here.
I'm finally blocked in.
Money?
There is money in here.
That's a dollar.
One dollar in your chest of stuff.
Might as well use it to cook.
So big game.
Playing big game.
That's really good.
Cook one, eat it, and then store three of them.
We're full on all the cores.
Make another one.
Cook the baked beans?
Can you do that?
I'm getting hungry.
I'm getting really hungry.
Something more important, though.
The internet's been fine, right?
This is pretty promising stuff.
6,000 up the whole time.
I have 23 drop frames in four hours and 30 minutes before that.
How long is the first stream before I accidentally was an idiot?
An hour and 10 minutes or something?
When will I do 1080p streams?
Now that is going to take probably a little bit longer
because I'm going to need a full streaming PC to do that.
1080p 60 FPS is, I guess, obviously the grand of all potential streams.
The only thing with that, though, is did they ever fix the whole thing with...
I remember hearing about how, oh, yeah, if you have like an 8,000 up 1080p stream,
a shitload of people can't even watch it because it'll buffer out the whole time.
Does that still happen?
Is that a problem that's been fixed?
That was a problem before.
Even putting the stream on low, it brings it down to a point where you still can't even see it.
1080p 30?
Yeah, you can do that.
I can do that, too.
I just don't...
I'm not sure because I have...
I'd have to do a little bit of research on 1080p,
mainly because it's a...
This computer is...
I got a six-core processor.
Here we go.
Let's go right here.
I have a six-core processor, so I could probably handle it,
but I don't know if I could do it on every game.
Great.
Another psycho.
You care about this girl?
Stand up for yourself.
She'll come around.
Yeah, I've been waiting.
Trust me, kid.
There ain't so many good men out there.
Make yourself one of the good ones.
Thanks, mister.
I hope you're right.
I got points.
You have a great day.
I hope you're doing all right.
Bullet to his head.
Wait, don't move.
Can he hit me in the head with a rock?
Are you scared of what?
I was going to hunt those.
He's still talking.
He still has a bullet on the radar.
Waste away like some fallen leaf.
I kind of want to listen to this guy's whole dialogue.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Come on.
Can't move around here all day.
Where does he go?
He looks so odd.
I was trying to talk to him.
Just Superman punch him?
I can't.
Guys, we're evil.
We're only evil when it's a random act of evil.
You know, if somebody stops in the road
and they're like, who the fuck are you?
And I'm like, who the fuck are you?
You're not.
I'm not just going to murder this guy.
Wait, I can't.
I have to like...
Okay.
See you.
There we go.
I can't be in cinematic cam, dude.
Like, say hello to the guy.
Not much.
Let me be.
This guy's not happy with me right now.
I got to stay back.
I got to keep a distance where I'm not following him.
Tay, it's right here.
This is the distance that I'm legally allowed to be behind him.
Before he gets upset about it.
Restraining order?
No, no.
I'm just saying like in the video game world.
Rabbits!
Who's just screaming?
Did you hear that?
He just fucking screamed.
Is this guy going to walk all the way back to my camp?
Just go?
I know.
I need to know where this guy's going.
Here are your choices.
Okay.
Follow this guy and see where he goes.
Or shotgun to his head.
That's like...
Those are the two options.
See?
Follow.
I don't have an off switch.
I don't have an in-between.
It's one or one hundred.
What if he leads me to something?
But not zero.
No, never zero.
Why would you ever give zero percent?
That's a good thing.
Who is this?
Horsebag Sonic.
Right, that's what your name is.
Partner?
Hello?
Might as well be friendly, I say.
I've been following him for so long.
All the best.
This is a nice walk, though.
Nice and misty up here.
Look at this.
This is great.
I mean, technically I am going in the right direction, so...
It's getting kind of bad out right now.
This is not getting good.
This is...
The weather's getting a little treacherous.
Hey.
Hey, mister.
Walking home in the rain.
Yep.
I feel like we're playing an old Recess game.
It's like Red Light Green Light.
This feels illegal.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No.
No, okay.
What?
Oh no, another random person!
No!
No, no, no!
Don't do this to me now!
Please!
No!
If you could help me with these shackles,
I just might have a chance.
Oh!
Okay, quickly, quickly, quickly.
How did you end up like this?
Quickly, quickly.
Just shoot the damn chains already.
Come on!
All right.
Oh.
Oh, yes.
He's running!
Yes.
Perfect.
He's still talking.
Don't let him get away.
Robbery tip?
Horse?
What is that?
Is that the same guy?
I don't even think that's the same guy.
I think this is a different person.
I'm gonna run out of juice here.
Where do you go?
Where, where, where, where, where?
What is this?
What happened?
Somebody find him.
Somebody point him out.
Point him out!
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Give me the fucking horse.
Get on the horse.
Where the fuck were you?
Where the fuck were you, buddy?
Took you long enough.
Where is he?
Found him.
No.
That's not him.
God damn it.
Oh well.
Congrats on a waste of time.
I know.
Honest to God.
Who are you?
Hey.
Hey, Wallace.
This here's the kind soul I was telling you about.
The one that got the venom out of your leg.
Oh, it's the, it's the venom guy.
I know I can never repay you, but you head over to gunsmith
and pick out your choice of item on my tab.
Thanks.
Yeah, it seemed like the least I could do
with him being sent straight from the almighty to save my life.
Yeah, the almighty.
Always a doubter you are.
I'm a man of this world.
You guys told me to shoot him in the head.
Anyway.
Free item.
Anything?
I could take any gun for free.
What can I do for you?
Fitter outside told me I could grab something on his tab.
One with the bite in his leg.
Oh, he's good for it.
But all he's good for between the two of us.
Well, take a look around.
Find something you like.
Now put it on his tab.
What?
Any gun in the whole game?
In the whole catalog?
Hold on a second here.
Rifles.
72 bucks.
145 bucks.
180 bucks.
120 bucks.
These are locked though, unfortunately.
85, 95, 148.
One free gun.
Oh, dude.
I got a pistol cartridge.
It was $1.50.
Now it's zero.
All right.
I gotta calm down here.
Just give me the most expensive gun in the whole catalog that I can buy.
Do I get to save this or do I have to do it right now?
This pump action, I already own it.
I already own this one.
I can't even buy these because they're locked.
Well, this Springfield rifle is 120 bucks.
I don't have this.
Varmint rifle 72.
I need one of these to get clean kills on it and some animals.
Master Mauser pistol 250.
210.
150 bucks for the Volcanic pistol.
Schofield 84.
Volcanic.
Why is Volcanic so much more expensive?
I think I'm going for Volcanic.
Yeah.
The most explosive pistol ever.
Schofield?
Volcanic.
Shit.
Springfield.
Not Volcanic.
I mean, it's either Schofield.
Or the Springfield rifle.
120 versus 84.
I'm probably going to get it.
I need a good rifle.
Modern Firefire, these Firefields.
Is it single shot or what?
Yeah, the rifle that I have is kind of junk.
Yeah, I'm going to get it.
Single shot.
Okay, that's fine.
You can't aim.
I'll learn.
You get Volcanic for free anyways.
Well, this one's 120 bucks.
The other one's 80.
But more bang for buck.
I'm getting it.
Fine choice.
I'll let them know.
And then we're going to deck it out.
Components.
Hey, the thing was for free.
Might as well deck it out.
Rifling.
Customize groove to improve stability.
More range on it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Iron sights.
Improved sights.
This shit's $5.
I got it for free.
You can put a scope on it.
Medium scope.
Well, that kind of defeats the iron sights then, doesn't it?
Let's put a fucking scope on it.
Screw it, man.
Let's do it.
Straight grain.
Wide grain.
Basic grain.
I like the straight grain.
And let's get a wrap here.
I do not know.
It helps from wear and tear.
I got a trophy.
Okay.
All right.
Styles.
Metals.
This is the barrel.
Gold?
Blue?
Frame.
To the whole thing.
Oh, that looks nice.
I kind of like the muted gold here.
I don't...
Yeah.
We're going with...
We're going with brass.
What's about the hammer here?
Brass.
The sight can be...
It's just a brass.
Okay.
At what point am I just making like a fucking tuba?
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I'm turning this into a French horn.
If I blow in the end of this, it's going to make fucking musical sounds.
All right.
We're going to go just straight up steel here.
Ooh, baby.
Full engraving.
Can't really even see that.
That's 28 bucks.
Engrave the barrel?
No.
Engrave the frame, though.
Trap door.
You can't even see this shit.
Carvings.
Grip.
Oh, man.
This thing is going to be nice.
I like the eagle.
Hmm.
Now, the question is which eagle?
Are we talking just straight up like back of the coin eagle?
Are we talking mid-flight eagle?
I think I like the commemorative gold coin eagle that's on the infomercial.
Ah, it's ruined.
It's being covered up by the thing to protect it.
Leather.
I like that.
I like the chocolate.
Chocolate looks pretty good.
Olive, maybe?
Tobacco.
Let's get a good varnish on it.
Oh, this is the piece that sells it.
You know what I'm saying?
That looks kind of good.
Dark walnut.
There it is.
That's the fucking desk I have right now.
Dark walnut.
Can I see a better image of this?
Yeah, I have to do it.
This is my desk.
Did that just say desk?
Oh, desk walnut.
Dark walnut.
Look at that.
Look at that desk that shoots bullets.
Ammunition.
What kind of ammunition?
Rifle.
Express 30.
Regular express or high velocity.
This one's more damage.
This one's more range.
Range or damage?
The never-ending conundrum.
There's already a lot of damage range.
I guess I can get them both, huh?
Well, that was a lot of money.
Three.
How much did I just spend?
What?
I'm a moron?
Why?
I just bought high velocity.
That's $12.
That's nothing.
That's fine.
So I can switch between ammos, right?
I can just get them both.
I'm going to use the shitty ammo to learn.
I have every fucking ammo now.
Take off the scope.
Why would I do that?
Why would I get rid of my tuba horn gun desk?
Are you serious?
No.
This thing's ready to go.
Let's take a look.
Let's check it out.
Look at that.
Oh, man.
Does that look good?
So what is it?
Let's go to the...
I can't even open it.
Nice free gun.
Yeah, don't you just stand there until they get you.
The gun is free and then you spend $400 on components.
This gun is just a mobile game.
How's it treating you?
All right.
I need to get to like a little range here to aim it.
Go show the guy.
That's not a bad idea.
Where is he?
Is he still here?
There he is.
Hey, man.
What do you think?
I'll let the clerk know.
Thanks again.
Sure.
This is the best stranger in the game.
Can I sit next to him?
Yeah.
You think you can fuck with the desk trombone?
Thanks a lot, dude.
I want to test it out, but I can't open...
I can't take the gun out right now.
I have to go somewhere safe.
Snipe him from a distance.
Thanks for the new gun.
Let me try it out.
No.
I can't.
That's too awful.
Where is it?
Where's the gun store from here?
I'm aiming.
It's right.
I got to go around.
Let me line him up.
God damn it.
He's right there.
Okay.
Let me get this straight.
I'm going to go up here.
He's the best...
I just want to see if I can do it.
I just want to see how long the scope is.
How do I change the bullet?
High velocity.
Okay.
Here we go.
How do I go into scope mode?
There we go.
That's not very far.
I can't.
I can't do it, guys.
I can't do it.
That's not nice.
You gave me a free gun.
What?
Do you think I'm going to shoot him?
I can't do this.
What if he gives me another free gun in like an hour?
And there's no saving.
I can't just save it.
Look, this guy didn't give me a gun.
We can test it on him.
I missed him.
Just imagine that guy.
Okay.
The guy that gave me the gun, right?
I go out and I'm like,
Hey, what do you think?
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
Put it on my tab.
Like four minutes later.
It's just quiet.
All of a sudden.
Oh, a long scope shot dings off the back of somebody's carriage.
You're standing right there.
No crime committed.
I'm fine.
Oh, that's so fucking stupid.
Nobody's looking for me.
Oh, sorry, man.
I shot.
I shot a gun into a guy's fucking carriage.
You see me just like,
Oh, shit.
I got to get out of here.
Run off in the distance.
I fucking missed.
All right.
Let's go to church.
The same guy.
You turn around.
He looks to his right.
He sees a guy going to church now.
Oh, man.
God, somebody needs help.
Hold on.
Who?
Who needs help?
I don't.
Who?
Who needs help?
I don't see anybody.
Okay.
Um, I don't see anybody.
So let's go to church.
Whoa.
Okay.
Where is this guy?
Oh, it's you.
Okay.
Yeah, whatever.
That's fine.
Just going to pretend to be a guy's friend.
Honor money.
Last friend died.
It weren't my fault.
They said it was,
but they was wrong.
It's fun being with you, Mister.
Can I hold you a second, Mister?
Can I?
Yeah, sure.
How goes things with you?
Okay, just...
I'm so dirty.
That felt...
It's nice to be held sometimes.
Honor money.
Oh, we used to hold each other in the war.
You got sad eyes, Mister.
You look like a ghoul.
Like you've seen.
Sad things.
Remember with kindness.
This guy's going to come back at some point.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, excuse me.
Where's my gun?
Give me my gun back.
I spent so much time getting it.
Give me the gun.
Give me my gun, please.
I spent so much time getting that gun.
Give me my gun back.
Give me my gun.
Where's my gun?
Wait, what?
What?
No, what?
It's all the same.
Oh, oh boy.
Get me out of here.
Don't even want me.
This is in pain.
I thought everyone told me he robbed me.
I thought he robbed me.
I didn't have the gun on me.
I thought I had the gun on me.
I thought he stole my rifle.
I thought he stole it.
Easy, girl.
Easy.
Okay, I got it.
I got it.
I gotta get out of here, dude.
I have to leave now.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm gonna die.
I can't.
Get up.
Ow.
Oh my god.
Oh, my stomach.
No, get me out of here.
Please get me out of here.
This game is fucking so much fun.
Nice sniper role.
Reload.
I'll be so far behind.
Open this.
I just like, come on.
Give me some slack here.
Give me at least a little bit of slack here.
That was like a random, oh, hey, give me a hug.
And then like, I'm missing my expensive rifle.
I had to put two and two together.
I didn't want to lose it.
That was expensive.
And then I looked over at chat and everyone's just like,
dude, no, he took it.
He fucking stole it, man.
That NPC steals it.
I'm just like, god.
Oh, god.
I was like, god.
And you guys were like, whoa.
And I was like, god.
Nice explanation.
I punched him in the head with the gun and I shot him in the head.
That was not supposed to happen.
It wasn't supposed to be like that.
So I got one arm.
All right.
I don't want to work my horse here.
Slow down.
Let's eat.
Reload this.
I can't.
I got to sleep in this bed.
I made the bed.
I got to sleep in it.
You can't shoot a rifle.
And look, this thing's like dirty.
I'm going to be so compulsive with this.
Is it clean?
I got to clean it.
Why is it damaged?
OK.
Reload it.
How do you reload?
It's circle is reload.
Ha!
Get me out of here.
This town hates me.
What?
Did I just go back in the same town I just left?
Get me out of this.
It's a never ending nightmare.
Please no.
Who said that?
They're probably talking about me.
I haven't even had an opportunity to cool off from that.
OK.
So the rifle, it's circle to reload.
Isn't it?
Well, you're holding setting story load game.
No, I can't.
That's no Ikea.
I got to sleep in this bed.
There are no rewinds in the Wild West, guys.
This guy only holds one bullet.
It doesn't have a hundred.
I bet that snakebite guy is feeling very good about himself.
Now he gave that to you.
I don't want to watch this stream anymore.
No, you sleep in bed.
OK.
What's happening here?
The farmer?
Where am I?
Mr. Thomas Downs?
No, it's the guy who owes money.
Oh, no, no.
We ain't a charity, Mr. Downs.
Why is he standing still?
Really?
Threaten me, would you?
Please.
I have a family, sir.
I don't care about your family.
Why did have to come to this, huh?
Tell me, sir.
I didn't want this either.
Just tell me.
Tell me.
I don't want to hurt you, man.
I've done too much damage.
If you're running out on debt.
I don't want to hurt anybody anymore.
I'm not running anywhere.
I'm doing my best for you.
Or a slippery little bastard.
But I got you now.
Please.
Oh, fuck.
Be reasonable.
Okay, he's mine.
You borrowed money from my business partner,
Herr Strauss.
You owe him.
You took the money.
He wants it back what's not to understand.
Where's our money?
I don't have it.
Sell your place.
We already owe more than it's worth.
Then sell your wife or your family or something.
We ain't your idea of charity.
Is that clear?
Thomas.
What are you looking at?
I said what you looking at, woman?
My husband isn't well.
If we could just have more.
Like I said, we ain't nobody's idea of charity.
Get us the money.
Yeah, I didn't get it.
What if we're the bad guys?
I don't know.
I think he may have stolen your rifle.
Yeah, he's sick.
He like spit in my mouth.
I'm going to get the flu.
I'm going to get the death flu.
Back to camp.
So what's next?
Now they're running out of money here.
I'm going to donate this to the copper today.
I stole my gun.
Ah, how did you get on?
Not so good.
He's almost dead.
And they seem more or less destitute.
You were a fool for lending them the money.
Then people who aren't desperate
don't seem so interested in my propositions.
Of course.
Mission complete.
Bronze.
Arthur attempts to reclaim the debt from Thomas Downs
but finds him to be destitute.
Complete within two minutes.
Oh, that's because I wouldn't beat him up.
That's why I got bronze.
All right, let's go to the medic wagon here.
What we got?
Health cure.
I can't take any more.
How do I bathe at the camp, can I?
Oh, wait, actually, I have meat, don't I?
Oh, I bought that thing to do upgrades here.
Kit satchel.
Okay, I need...
Increase the carrying capacity
for all types of kit equipment
that will be used regularly.
This one is increase the carrying capacity
for all types of valuables
that can be sold for cash.
Perfect beaver, perfect beaver, perfect rabbit.
Something like this anywhere else.
I'll keep my eye out for some good food.
I'm gonna donate these, though.
I could really use some good meat for this stew.
Go to opossum, donate for funds,
donate for any provisions.
Oh, this shitty raccoon pal is good.
Sure, might as well make some money off it.
Get rid of the opossum.
Okay, let's go eat the stew
because it's available.
I'm trying to get over it.
I can't.
I'm trying, guys.
Let's eat.
Now slurp it up.
I want this right now.
What's with the same joke 100 times?
Which one?
Me?
Did I say something?
Oh, you're talking about chat.
Oh, okay.
Increase total supplies including tonics
to refill all stats as well as higher quality liquors.
Total provisions adds fresh fruit and basic canned goods.
Yeah, let's get this.
Quality and quantity of food available
in the pantry has increased.
That's good.
It's not a joke.
It's cold hard reality.
Whatever.
Real variety.
How much money do we have?
Proof of repeater ammo and arrows.
Actually, I like using the arrows.
48 bucks.
Yeah, let's do it.
Quality and quantity of ammunition available
at office 10 does increase.
You can pay to resupply munitions when stocks are low.
And then we're pretty much out of money.
I mean, we're broke, but I'm not broke.
So don't worry.
I'll take care of this.
Let's give some items here.
Eight bucks.
Put this one in there.
Gold pocket watch.
A couple of red wedding rings.
What's that face in chat?
We'll give like two of these.
That's enough.
How much money do they have?
$18.
That's fine.
That's enough.
Let's go to the ammo cart.
I need arrows.
Let's take these cartridges.
Arrows and everything.
All right.
I need, I didn't say arrows.
I need a bunch of these actually
because I used them all.
All right, we good.
Let's go to sleep.
And what time?
We've got five hours here.
Six and a half hours of streaming.
I'm good.
I think I'm going to get another water though.
So give me a second.
Let me go sleep.
Then I'm going to go BRB.
Grab another water and we'll keep going.
Sleep to morning.
Uh, I don't know how much I think is,
I need to be able to eat.
I haven't really eaten.
I had a smoothie this morning and that's it.
So eventually here, fairly soon,
I'm probably going to have to call it night.
It's including me.
I had a smoothie.
It was a pineapple, strawberry, and peach smoothie.
And it was good.
All right.
I'll probably give myself another 45 minutes
before it's time to end.
So with that, give me two seconds.
I'll see you guys in like a minute or two.
All right.
Yeah.
Probably because I got to take out Otto
and get some food and everything.
So we will do, let's do like another mission.
And then after that, close it up.
Somebody said, tired boy.
Yeah, I mean that, that, that my whole body,
it was taken out of me.
That last encounter just killed me.
Oh, okay.
So let's take a look.
This is morning now.
Let's see.
There are rabbits here though.
Let me try to get this challenge thing first
before we do anything.
Vroom, Vroom.
Vegas, baby.
All right.
I was supposed to just grab one of these.
Wait a minute.
At least let me see what it is.
Brown Jack.
Brown Broan.
Speednik said this thing's,
this thing's not even like good.
It's just big.
Hey, I'm trying to just let me pet you.
I feel like that Taima is a little bit better.
My horse is so much better.
I'm not that much better than Arthur's horses.
Okay, girl.
All right.
Now let's go.
I'm going to put my bow and arrow.
I'm going to get out of town first.
Okay.
Bow.
I need to be able to, I need to craft better arrows.
All right.
I need to, on horseback, I got to kill two rabbits.
The rabbits are over this way.
What was that blip?
Oh shit.
It's a snake.
Study, study, study, study it.
Southern Copperhead Snake.
Where is it?
I don't know where it is.
There it is.
What?
Did the snake just die of old age?
How did it, wouldn't it die?
It hit his head on a rock.
Okay.
He just smashed his head into a fucking rock.
All right.
Well, look at the quality.
Look at the quality of the meat.
It's so, it's perfect.
It's perfect.
I'm going to bring it back to town.
No.
What do I do with this?
It's perfect.
Look at the three stars.
What do I do with this?
It's, it's, skin it?
Is it, will it be perfect skin?
Or should I just keep the whole thing?
Sell the butcher, cargo it, release it back into the wild.
Just hold it like this for the rest of the game.
It'll be a perfect skin.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm going to skin it.
Oh man.
Nice.
I can make perfect.
Okay.
I'm so glad he just smashed his head into a rock.
I didn't have to shoot it and ruin it.
Let's put it on the back.
Do I put it in a?
This thing's going to get all fucked up if I do,
if I drive stupid though, right?
Okay.
This is going to be rough.
I need to get rid of this somehow.
Should I go back to the camp?
Where's like a butcher?
Not my butcher.
A butcher that I can actually sell to.
Put it in the stew pot.
No, no.
I, let's go up here.
I'm going to go up.
But do that.
We're going to go up here.
I'm going to do this merry linden quest
and then I'm going to come back and get a rabbit.
All right.
Let's go.
I want to sell it at the butcher.
If it's perfect, then I kind of would want to get some money from it.
It's right on the road.
What the fuck are you doing, man?
What the fuck are you?
Oh, there's people.
Lots of them.
Everyone disliked that.
Maybe I get some money.
Oh, they're all Driscolls.
I mean, is there a point in this?
Where I get to get rid of all the Odoyles?
Can I throw them all off a cliff?
Edison?
Okay.
Not bad.
The Driscolls rule.
Seriously.
That's what I feel like they're doing.
I don't think I've had the same hat on
for more than five minutes.
They shot my snake?
I better not have.
No, it's still there.
It's fine.
It's still fine.
Holy shit.
Speaking of guns, what is that?
This is a Warren-Kattelman revolver.
No.
That thing sucks.
Oh, does it bounce?
So it was Driscolls,
and then it was bounties.
When are they going to realize
that they're not going to take me down?
They may as well just make me the president.
You know?
At what point is it just like,
fine, you can be emperor.
All right.
You're unstoppable.
You now, like that's what...
Sorry, I just ran into Tony Hawk
and show you how cool I was.
Pay off your bounties.
I'll do that here.
Do I have enough money to do that?
I didn't realize the United States was a monarchy.
No, but see, you make me the emperor
and then 10 of the most loyal,
most dedicated generals
then work to have me removed.
And then, you know,
while I'm sitting there eating grapes
and sleeping on like salted beef,
you just like throw a fucking dart in my face.
And that's it.
I'll get fat.
I'll get overconfident.
If you think your little spell away...
Look at that.
I'm not selling that though.
Perfect carcass.
What are you talking about?
Just read between the lines.
1.6, 1.7.
I can't do anything else with this.
So just take it.
I'm going to keep this though.
Does this spoil at all?
Or is it always going to be perfect?
Yeah, I'm not going to sell this to this guy.
No, I can use it anytime it says using crafting.
I'm not going to sell it.
Really have anything else for you.
What the hell?
Sell to the trapper?
Not this guy?
No, that's the skin though.
The carcass skin to use for anything.
Let's go to this one.
Actually, you know what?
I'm going to store this guy.
Actually, hold on a minute.
Let me like at least clean this.
I'm going to go bring Whisper up.
You are dirty.
Should I be holding this or tapping it?
Don't pay your bounty whatever you do.
Okay, nice and clean.
Let's get you in storage and bring out Whisper.
Good looking horse there.
If you want me to keep that overnight,
there's room in the stable.
Okay, here's Whisper.
Saddle up.
So here's Whisper.
I think I hate how I'm saying horse care package.
Wish more folks took care of their horses like you.
All right, that's good.
You have to stable your horses.
You can't just overuse them.
They'll get tired and fucked up.
I just want him to knock the board out of his hands.
I'm not trying to be dick.
Just trying to get the board knocked out of his hands.
Change the braided tail.
No, that's how I know it's my horse.
Your edgy horse.
Okay, let's go talk to Mary.
Hello.
We loved once in true.
Now, this is the love interest.
Oh shit, I forgot to take a bath.
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to disturb you, ma'am.
Is Mrs. Linton in?
I'll go see.
Mrs. Linton, a caller for you.
The braided hair won't get tangled, I know.
I know.
Hello, Arthur.
Oh, you look like shit.
Mary.
I know, I know.
I heard you and your friends was around.
I...
Okay.
Where's, um...
Where's what's his name?
Died.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
Happened a while ago.
Pneumonia.
Bad business.
Sure.
So, uh, you've been...
You've been made a widow and come here looking for me?
Is that it?
No, ain't like that, Arthur.
Okay.
Listen, Arthur, I...
I'm...
My family.
I need your help.
You mean the family that always looked down on me?
You want me to help them?
It's my little brother, Jamie.
I always liked Jamie.
At least compared to the rest of them.
He's broken daddy's heart.
Daddy has a heart?
Don't make me beg you, Arthur.
My money, my life, me.
I wasn't good enough.
I'm sorry.
This looks like it's deliberate.
We need your help real bad.
Little Jamie's joined the Chilonians.
That strange religious order.
I've rolled around in mud before I walked to the door.
That's like how fresh that is.
They'll kill him.
You're the only person he'd listen to.
So, I'm too rough to marry into your family.
But it's okay to ask me to help in saving your family.
I'm sorry.
I understand if you don't want to help me, but...
But I think of you often.
No time will go now.
I'm begging you, Arthur.
I say let Jamie live Jamie's life
and not the nightmare that his daddy dreamed up for him.
Jamie's so innocent, Arthur.
Please, Arthur.
Will you help me?
I think I got to help her, right?
I don't know.
I got to...
Oh, it's don't help her.
It's the first coming up here.
Please, Arthur.
Oh, shit.
Time's running out.
I'm helping.
Where is he?
Somewhere out near Carmody Dell, I think.
The rancher there said he'd seen him around the Cumberland forest.
I mean, good boy points, guys.
Don't you understand?
Arthur, if you find him, bring him to me at the station.
I'll see what I can do.
I can't just do everything bad.
I need to...
I've done so many bad things.
You already owe me.
Good boy points.
Come on.
Look, don't you understand?
For every time that we run over a fucking town of people in our car,
for every time I shoot my tuba desk at somebody, like on the street,
we have to balance it out.
I have to do a good deed every once in a while.
And this is far away, Mary.
Okay, Thanos.
You can't just do all bad things.
Good idea.
No.
He's got to be occasionally good so he doesn't stand for anything.
Rated tails messing with your head.
Why?
He was thinking about blasting the lady on the porch.
I could see it.
And I didn't do it.
That's not part of my bad guy allowance.
Okay.
I tried.
I tried to kill her.
Okay.
God damn it.
I was in the middle of something.
Awful evil?
I don't know if that's the kind of character I'm playing.
That horse did right by me.
Better than my husband, truth be told.
That fool always complaining.
But does he do something about it?
Whatever.
It don't matter.
Barely lifts his hand to wave the flies away.
Actually, I am kind of playing like evil.
Marriage for me has been nothing but trouble.
He did a lot of dangerous shit.
But Biscuit?
He was a fine animal.
Jumping over stuff.
Flying over cars.
Flying over, you know, jumping over ranches.
And stuff like that.
No one had one of them mountain boys pull a gun on me once.
Koda and it stopped by a nice warm patch.
What the fuck is that rabbit?
I mean, if you want to be like lawful evil, evil enable.
I wake up and find some nasty piece of work
pointing a rusty shotgun straight at me.
Well, he gets wheezing on and I must have made some sort of noise.
Because, well, you quit it already.
Think you might have got 20.
What is wrong with you?
Oh, yeah.
Jump over three obstacles in 15 seconds.
I tell the husband, what does he do?
What does the time start?
You've never gone over there.
Over the tree.
Thanks.
Over the rock.
You aiming and knocked me off.
One.
Emerald ranches the other way.
Anyways.
Right.
For the time being.
Again.
Jump over three obstacles in 15 seconds.
That's not part of the balance.
How do you jump over the three objects in 15 seconds?
I have to go to like a stable for that.
Jesus Christ.
Just jump over a fence three times.
I panicked.
I saw the fucking text on the screen.
I thought it was like a GT.
Remember in Grand Theft Auto when they would do the random like,
hey, by the way, pass four people in 10 seconds.
And you're like, oh shit, oh nice.
That happens all the time in GTA 5.
Especially, well, GTA Online, right?
Yeah, I'm sorry here.
GTA, yeah, GTA Online.
I bet I'm going to meet all the people I've helped in the afterlife.
Well, the shell of safety.
What am I supposed to do?
Shell of safety.
Can I speak to the boy?
Arthur?
Hello, son.
Your sister is very worried.
The boy has chosen a path, sir.
Cultist shield.
Okay, let's see.
Guy on the left.
Guy in the back is the most intimidating back left.
His sister just wants to speak with him.
Arthur, I've chosen a path.
Yeah, that's the big, the big group.
The boy has chosen a path.
He's chosen safety.
What path have you chosen, sir?
Oh, browns.
No, about this nonsense.
Let me speak to the boy.
Are you always this negative and antagonistic, sir?
I'm sorry.
Don't you, ma'am.
Forgive me, please.
I am a fool for my god and a happy one, sir.
Bless you.
Use God.
No.
What do I dream about?
Who are my heroes?
Uh, Spider-Man.
Fools.
You're a fool for everyone's god.
You're a maniac.
Now let me talk to the god damn boy.
Move out of my way.
Fool?
What does throttle mean?
God damn lunatic.
Kill him.
That's enough, Arthur.
Kid, come on.
Did I kill him?
This is crap.
You're better than this.
Better than what?
Better than one in paradise?
Better than thinking these fools know a damn thing about paradise.
Now he's done.
Now let me take you home.
You're a sad man, Arthur.
You're a real sad man.
Sure, but come home.
Not a chance.
Leave me alone, Arthur.
I didn't ask for your help.
Yah!
I'll get him.
He ain't gonna outrun Whisper.
My horse is way fucking faster than yours, ain't it?
Oh.
Hey!
Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up, get up!
You're just using it.
Tell you what you want to hear.
Why did they throw all these obstacles in my way?
Get out of the fucking way.
I wasn't gonna kill him.
I'm kidding.
Obviously have to lasso him.
Just gotta get close enough.
Sorry I didn't understand.
There's gonna be a lookout for the obstacle on the road.
Of course he gets by it.
You're just using it.
Tell you what you want to hear.
Why do your sisters worry about you?
This is none of your damn business.
Oh!
I tried to run him over.
Just get old, get on with it.
This is crazy.
I can't get it.
Come on, Yates.
Stupid, you can see this is crazy.
You're the crazy one.
Yah!
Dammit, we gotta do this the hard way.
I don't have to answer to you.
The fastest horse in the game.
The horse is gonna die.
Not a good idea, not a good idea.
Oh, what did he say?
Now you're fucked.
What are we doing?
Slowly press R2 to fill the meter.
The more full the meter the...
What?
Slowly.
Let me read this again.
Hold on, I freaked out.
What is he telling me?
Load?
Slowly press R2 to fill the meter.
The more the meter...
Okay, I need to like do that again.
I don't even know what he's trying to tell me to do.
You can't, you can't, you can't do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Jesus.
The one thing I do know.
Is he gonna give him the gun back?
I'll miss you Arthur.
I don't know if I would give that back to him.
Are you and Marys sweet on another again?
That's all a long time ago son.
Let's go.
We're on my horse, right?
Well, this wasn't how I thought today would turn out.
It's been a long time, Jamie Gillis.
You were a kid last time I saw you.
Didn't try to change something.
You know, you taught me how to ride a horse.
To uh, lonier though?
Really?
You'd fall for that?
They were very nice to me.
They're decent.
I'm sure.
Please tell me you didn't give them any money.
Desk tube is not gone.
It's right here.
Of course I did.
They rely on charitable donations.
Jesus, Jamie.
Come on.
I just wanted to believe that there might be something good
come on my way one day.
Yes, that's dead in the water.
It's the turtle.
Shut up.
Father kept telling me was you won't amount to anything.
You're not enough of a man.
I had to get away.
I couldn't take you anymore.
Forgive me, but your father's a bully and a coward.
Don't listen to him.
Hey, don't talk about him like that.
What do you want me to say, Jamie?
He's a good father.
Nice man.
He won't be happy I saw you.
Please send him my worst regards.
Jump three obstacles.
I'm not going to do that right now.
I'm not good at anything.
I'm going to get to a fence and then get it done.
Tell me something you like.
Don't think too hard.
Don't fall here.
Apples, I guess.
You like apples?
Yeah, I love apples.
Okay.
Well, I was thinking more along the lines of
Somebody's got to love apples.
You know, people that own apple farms.
You got to really love them.
All right, go work in the office.
Where do you think your apples come from?
That's respectable.
You must really like shooting and robbing people.
I only like shooting young idiots who run away from me
when I'm trying to help them.
You told me what you do.
I'm sure he did.
Are you still with Dutch and what was his name?
Hester?
Jose.
Yep, still the same sort of.
And Annabelle and Bessie?
I'm afraid they're dead.
Shit.
Doesn't count.
Maybe Mary did make the right choice.
No doubt.
It is anything like the nonsense you read in the newspapers.
So, are you two getting back together?
I told you no.
Just ask me for a favor.
I had from valentine's words in less than five minutes.
Pneumonia.
You told me.
So the door is open, so to speak.
Okay, well, I got a really fast horse.
Might be able to do that.
Different people now.
She's not.
And you seem just the same.
Well, maybe that right there's the problem.
She was always too good for me.
Let's just get you back to your sister.
She's waiting at the station for us.
Meet Mary at the station.
She must be waiting inside.
Hello.
Mary, I brought your son.
What are you going, the long way?
About seeing her, aren't you?
He's going the long way here.
You're right.
Why is he limping around?
I seem to recall hearing mention of that myself.
Okay, come on.
All right, here's your rotten kid.
Because he shot his hand.
I didn't just shoot his hand.
I didn't even touch his hand.
It hit the gun.
Jamie, Jamie.
All right.
Finally, mother and son reunited.
Please.
You've father's been very sad.
Father wouldn't know sadness if it died in his bed.
He's not happy.
But I'll come home for you.
My boy, my sweet boy.
Come on.
Oh, Arthur.
Thank you.
It's good to see you, Mary.
And you, Arthur.
And you.
Have a good one.
No, don't skip.
Oh, you don't have to say anything.
I'm going to long scope you from like a half mile away when you get on the train.
Don't worry about it.
I feel like the luckiest man alive and I feel like a fool.
That woman confuses me and plays me for a fiddle like no one else alive.
I trust I will not make a god-awful fool of myself once more.
But somehow I imagine I shall.
Somehow.
There we go.
Bronze.
There.
Okay.
So ladies and gentlemen, I need to go take out Otto.
I got to get some food.
We've got we've been going for seven plus hours here.
I think it's a good stopping point.
Internet has held up very well.
What's your problem?
So I I'm probably just going to go tomorrow.
You know what I'm saying?
Try to keep this going because we've got.
Yeah, it was before I turned the stream up before I made Starplane Leap League.
But yeah, this looks pretty promising so far.
It's been very solid tonight.
I think it's only dropped 100 frames over six, seven hours.
That's pretty great, actually.
Show Otto.
I mean, hold on.
He's downstairs.
He's like asleep downstairs.
I really don't know.
I'm going to let him just hang out down there.
I don't want to like wake him up, bring him up here, and then bring him all the way.
No, I'll show him tomorrow with this.
If we still have a solid internet connection here, then tomorrow I'm just going to stream.
I'm going to get up, eat some food, grab coffee, and I'm just going to get going.
We'll just start.
Hopefully it's our problems are in the past.
Same lame excuse in Boston.
What?
Like I want to let my dog sleep.
I don't want to like drag him up here and like put him in front of a camera.
What?
He's just like sleeping.
He's being like a good boy.
Excuses.
All right, let me, I'm going to switch off here.
If you're taking off, take care.
Hopefully we see you tomorrow.
I'm going to try to stream again.
And with that, let's run the, let's run.
The bits here.
Let's see.
We've got to turn this off.
Hey, look at that.
There's an outro, right?
That's an intro.
That's the wrong thing.
That's an outro.
And turn that off.
Okay.
So thanks everybody.
See you soon.
And let's get to these bits.
But first I need to text Kim.
She is asking me a question.
Okay.
Answered question.
So let's go back down to a long time ago here.
We've got this is seven hours ago.
DivUSP.
Thanks for three bucks.
Whoa.
Excuse you.
What the hell was that?
Oh, okay, that's fine.
DivUSP.
Thank you so much for the three dollars here.
No message.
Fire of unknown origin.
Thank you for the one dollar.
Jerma sucks.
Jext Jerma.
I don't, why, I did all right.
I did okay.
Tumsup.
Thank you Tumsup for the one dollar.
34 year old Kelly eats nothing but cheesy potatoes.
Morning, noon, and night.
That show is wild.
I can't believe it's real.
Sometimes I feel like they've given them like not like fake real food or something.
Like some people eat glass on that fucking show.
Like there's no way.
There's a guy that just eats glass.
What?
That has to be like sugar.
It's a joke, right?
No way.
Freaky Eaters.
It's on TLC.
A lady eats rocks in my strange addiction.
Lady eats rocks.
You watch her like bite into them and eat them.
It's, I don't know.
How is that even possible?
Don't you die if you eat a rock?
It's wild.
It's worth a watch though for sure.
Thank you Shin Pete for the one dollar.
Finally get to catch a Jerma stream.
Feels good man.
Hey, thank you.
Welcome.
Glad you're here.
Thank you Garfy of the Monday Killer for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma, in celebration of the hundredth Garf Buck.
Is it okay if Garf sings you a victory song?
Yeah, that's fine.
He lives in my scarf.
The twinkle in my barf.
He gives me what a perfect Garf.
At any point in time or history, Odie's done.
John is done.
Garf's the cat.
He's so cool.
He's so nice.
Everything about him is great.
Who's that flying in the sky?
It's GoFont.
It's GoFont motorcycle in the sky.
There he goes gorfing around in front of your face.
Home on a journey to outer space.
Oh, I get it.
Thank you Garfy for the Monday dollar.
Is it Monday?
No, not yet.
It'll be Monday in like,
well actually it's probably Monday for a lot of people here.
We're on Pacific time.
Thank you Garfield.
Thank you also to Hydra.
Thank you Hydra725 for the one dollar.
Lego Island for Evo Comedy Hour.
Thanks dude.
Tuskor13, thanks for the one dollar.
Honestly, I missed you two being friends.
These streams always make me forget my troubles.
Lots of love to you both.
That was a great time.
That was a lot of fun.
There's a couple other games that him and I both would like to play.
Just need to figure out how to do them.
Should be fun.
Pacific time is three hours behind.
Well, yeah, that's what I mean.
8, 9, 10, 11.
It's 1130 Eastern.
So in 30 minutes it'll be Monday.
Not over here though.
But thanks a lot Tusk.
Tar Alacrin, thanks for the two dollars here.
Dermot, you can drop the act.
No one believes you actually moved to Vegas.
It's pretty obvious you just moved your setup to a different room.
Closer to the Wi-Fi router.
Man, wouldn't that be weird?
Thank you.
Thank you Optimus for the one dollar.
Optimus 27,000.
This stream really makes you feel like it's 2014.
The days of Jerma versus Star.
Bets, pirate spies, and demonic chefs.
Good to be back.
We never left.
Never left, man.
We're here.
I didn't go anywhere.
He didn't go anywhere.
It's all good.
Thank you 4th consecutive lion for the five dollars.
Damn, this stream reminded me of the good old days.
Hope you stream with Stirr more often.
I'm sure we will.
There's no reason not to.
Just need to find the right game, the right time, the right moment.
Organically, like I told you before.
There's no rhyme or reason to when I play with somebody else.
It just kind of happens.
But thanks for the five dollars, man.
Appreciate it.
Hexbred.
Thanks for the three dollars.
It just says neat.
Hey, thanks.
Thank you Hexbred for your three bucks.
And you're neat.
Moseloss.
Thank you Moseloss for the one dollar.
Great stream, Jeremy.
Always fun watching you and Star play Lethal League.
Now go watch the Patriots beat Aaron Rodgers.
I think I may have missed that game.
Yeah, that was more than three hours ago.
Did they win?
I don't know.
I don't really follow football.
I follow baseball sometimes.
Spoiler.
Oh yeah, I don't want to give spoilers.
Thanks a lot, man.
Thank you Felix.
Felis for the five dollars.
Sorry that five cents is all I can give you.
But I need to eat dinner tonight, Jerma.
Jerma Hart, buddy.
This is not five cents.
This is five dollars.
I don't know.
You may have messed up the denomination there.
Sorry about that.
But thank you for the five bucks, man.
Appreciate it.
Zalinky.
Thank you, Zalinky, for the one dollar.
No message.
Thank you, though.
Angry Ork.
Thanks for four bucks.
No message.
Thank you so much.
Rip that guy's dinner.
A Blue Comet.
Thanks for the ten dollars here, Blue Comet.
Ten bucks from Blue Comet.
Chat stole your gun.
You know, I like those moments where you like you.
I just know I'll never live it down ever again.
And it's live.
I can't like go back and fix that.
You know what I mean?
If this was YouTube, I'd be like,
oh, shit, that was really fucking bad.
That was really fucked up and stupid.
Oh, I was going to go delete it.
Nope.
Well, that's going to take me like a month
to live that one down.
But thank you, Blue Comet, for the ten bucks.
Appreciate it.
Little Money Larry gave fifteen dollars here.
Thank you so much for fifteen bucks, man.
You look like shit.
Perfect timing.
I snotted.
That was great.
And then they say blood for blood.
God.
What?
But thank you, though.
A month.
Keep dreaming.
It's going to take five years.
God.
He just wanted a hug.
I know.
But like the way that he reached around
and then like it wasn't on my back anymore.
And who knows?
There's all kinds of weird characters
and weird fucked up scenarios.
It could have happened.
Chat is still on Coffee Cheetos Chicken.
What are you on about?
Oh, that's right.
Okay, so that one, if Coffee Cheetos Chicken,
like finally like like at the end of its life,
two years from now is done,
then this one's going to be ten years.
I just said it.
Now it just resets the time.
So like I just gave it another five years.
Every time it's mentioned, the clock resets.
And then at the end here, thank you Snatchy for the one dollar.
I bet she's going to meet all the other people
you've helped in the afterlife.
Mentioned that before.
That's a funny, that was a funny comment.
And in the very end, thank you E Cookie for the one dollar.
Can you watch and react to your 500 subscriber special?
No, I've done, I've done it like three times.
I can't.
You want it?
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to give any ideas.
I'm going to close my mouth on that one.
You want it?
You wanted me to watch?
You want me to watch that?
Hmm.
I wonder how that would be possible.
Oh, I'm not, I don't know.
Guys, the old shitty annotations about
me correcting the amount of pounds it is.
These are 35 pound dumbbells.
It's 30 actually.
I'm sorry, I lied.
Those annotations are still there.
But that's it for the bits.
Thank you everybody for your monetary contributions.
Thanks to the bits, everybody.
You guys all rock.
And let's go ahead and throw the credits up on the screen.
I got a feeling it's going to be a lot.
It's going to probably be going real fast.
But thank you regardless to everybody that subscribes to the channel.
You guys are all amazing.
And here it comes.
Thank you for supporting the stream.
All you guys.
I just, I locked up when I looked at it.
Fucking god damn it, man.
It's been a long time.
Thank you.
I just was staring at the webcam.
That's why I don't do webcam.
If the webcam was on, thank you everybody.
I went like this.
No, I'm not going to turn it on yet.
I want to see everybody.
You guys are all amazing.
Hello tall streamer.
Thanks, man.
Why is my music not on?
What the fuck?
So what was the green screen update?
I missed it.
After we, I will reiterate it one more time.
But don't want to give the subs some time to go by here.
All of you.
When I came back actually streaming three days or so, it was later like 300 or 400 subs.
Were a lot of you guys just like saving it to when I actually came back?
At what point were you like, okay, I'm going to wait until he comes back.
He ain't, he ain't back.
What the fuck is he doing?
People remember like October, like all of October.
I barely stream just because of all this, you know, moving and everything.
And I, people still paid for that whole month of subscriptions.
Tons of you guys.
So then I didn't really do very much.
So thank you for your patience.
Thanks for continuing to support the stream, even when the stream and even turned on.
So that means a lot, but it seems like we are back in the saddle.
Judging by all the testing that we did yesterday and then today,
let's hope that it's a done deal.
I can't afford it every month.
You don't have to be subbed, man.
Make sure you take care of yourself first.
Make sure that anything that you give to me is something that you can afford.
Something that it's, you are completely comfortable doing.
Oh shit, it auto subbed.
Can I get a free fund?
That was a lot of people.
Thank you so much.
I'm a poor university student.
I can't afford something, which is why I look forward to survey bits to show my support.
That's perfectly fine, man.
Thank you for even doing that.
There's no obligation for you to continuously give me money.
I appreciate anything that you would even say.
So thank you.
Triple Jupiter.
Holy shit.
That likes it, man.
You got it.
What's all this facing here though?
Is that an emote problem?
Oh no, is it dash?
Okay.
Only a few days until Hitman 2.
Well, I'd better.
Oh, so many things to do.
There's so much to do.
This is what happens when you don't stream for a month.
So many fucking things come out.
So many things that I have been backlogged.
The end of the year here will be a lot of fun.
There's a lot to do.
But I am going to take off.
Right at the very end, mostly loss came in with the dollar.
Oops, this was the last dollar in my bank account.
Whoa, that's not good.
Whoa, thank you though.
Timmy Tim Tam, thanks for the one dollar.
Your special stream, return my heart.
And this is an image of me.
Oh, what?
Why is...
I was supposed to be eating the microphone.
Okay.
Why does it just link that?
I just linked that.
Why did I do that?
I...
Whatever.
Thank you E-Cookie for the one dollar at the end here.
Do 4,000 subs special.
A fourth like on Twitch?
I don't have 4,000 subs on Twitch.
If that's what you're referring to.
But thank you.
It came pretty close.
There was like a month or two ago.
Like before I moved.
Holy shit.
I think we got real close to it.
Maybe we went over for one day or something.
But and that's just fucking out of this world.
I can't even imagine that.
But how do you check my subs?
I think it has 3,900.
I did not have 3,900.
That was during the spicy move.
Hey, why are you ending the stream?
I just got here asshole.
Hey, whoa, man.
Oh my goodness.
What the hell is it?
Hey, you got like an eight hour VOD that's ready to go.
And hey, that was two full different games here.
It was me and Stirr playing Lethal League.
Which was a lot of fun.
And then some Red Dead Redemption 2.
Man, you got like eight hours here, man.
Permaband, no.
All right.
I will see you guys tomorrow.
Oh, Garfield here.
Garfield the Monday Kill.
Thanks for the one dollar Garfield.
I made a comic for you and for Holymac.
Let's see what it is.
Good morning, Holymac.
All right.
Good morning to you.
Pushito.
Who the fuck is this?
Love me, love my mask.
What is this?
I saw a guy call you bad earlier and you banned him.
Well, I mean, for those of you that are new to the channel,
the permanent ban, a life ban.
If I denominate a permanent life ban, it's 15 seconds.
That's a life sentence.
So if you're new to the channel, that's what happens.
Trevor doesn't know how to read.
Find some treasure next time.
Yeah, we'll do some side content tomorrow.
I will try to find some treasures.
We'll do some hunting.
I'll try to start at some point in the afternoon.
Again, like I've said before, the schedule is just throw it out the window for now.
Until I have the 100% all clear that the internet is 100% fixed and ready to go,
I still don't have that information.
The Cox tech guy that I've been talking to has been all over it and on top of it.
Well, there's no confirmation here yet that, oh, hey, by the way, it's actually done.
Once that's done and once that's completely, we're in the complete clear,
I'm going to have a new schedule.
So we'll figure it out.
Have a great rest of your night, guys.
Take care.
I'm going to go eat food, let my dog out and say hello to my girlfriend.
I think she's downstairs.
Take care, guys.
Have a great rest of your night.
Bye.