Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some chivalry. Medieval warfare.
Let me shoot this guy in the back. Or just miss.
Just this blind playthrough, I just did the tutorial for one second.
Oh, get it. I wonder how well I'm gonna do here. Playing as the archer.
Oh boy, a guy coming in. Oh, you wanna go? Oh, come on, come on, come on.
Block it, block it, block it. Get in my face. Oh, that hurts. Oh, that hurts big time.
Oh, so two hits, two hits. Okay, I get it.
This game is brutal. Listen to those noises.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Actually, you know what? See if I can't snipe somebody.
Oh, that was a miss. Oh, oh.
What does it look like? It makes a horrible noise.
There's a lot of dudes up there. A lot of dudes up there.
Oh, just like the huntsman in TF2. Bang!
Bang! Well, did that just hurt? I thought I just hit my teammate for a second.
Oh, that guy's throwing like javelins.
Oh, come here, you. Oh, damn it.
Oh, that guy just destroyed me.
Oh, you know, I'm gonna play. I'll do one more life as an archer. One more life as an archer.
Oh, this game is fun. Yeah, like I said, I just finished the tutorial like two seconds ago.
Coming in blind, baby.
I know, don't I have like some kind of move or something? I know I have that in this.
Okay, let's wrap around this time. I'm not gonna stay here. We're gonna go over here.
Whoa, siege weapons. I see dead bodies. This is not good.
Oh, fight going on right here. Wait, is this guy? Wait, is this guy on our team? No, he's not.
Oh, God. Oh, God. They're on the stairs.
Oh, you got him. You got him, bro. Don't worry, archer back up. Archer back up.
I don't want to hit you. Oh, I almost hit that guy in the back. Oh, God.
Get out of my face.
Let's go. Let's go. Oh, oh. Oh, fighting in the stairway is the worst.
Come on, follow me up here. Oh, God.
Every time we were swinging, we would be hitting the sides of the wall.
All right, I'm gonna go as... How do you change class?
Let's go as the knight. Warhammer? Oh, hell yeah, Warhammer.
I want the tower shield. Let's take the little broadsword. Let's do it.
I'm gonna start smashing people now. Oh, here we go, baby.
God, I'm a slug. I'm so slow. Nobody like behind me, right? Good.
All right, let's go for something like kills in a row here.
Get this guy. This guy's just slugging everybody.
Come on. Come on. Break his morale. Yeah. I'll smash you.
Oh, this is the ultimate game for like smashing.
Oh, damn it. Oh, that guy just came from behind.
That guy just crushed that guy. Oh, my God.
All right, I think we're winning.
Oh, everybody just gets stuck on the stairs.
What is happening? Oh, my God.
What? What? Oh, some son of a bitch behind me just killed me.
One of my teammates.
All right, so number one thing you gotta remember about this game is friendly fire.
You don't just like swing around in a circle when your teammates are all around.
All right, duly noted. Let's get back in here.
That guy just fell off. That guy legitimately just fell to his death.
Poor guy. All right. Form a line ranks, man.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, this guy's toast.
Oh, hey, you want me? Oh, there's a lot of people. Never mind.
Never mind. Go for the jab.
All right, coming in. Coming in hot. Coming in hot. Coming in hot.
I missed. Damn it. Oh, be careful. Don't kill each other.
Oh, yeah. This is ridiculous. This is terrifying.
I don't even want to go down here.
Did I kill him? I got him.
I'm so scared.
Give him a little jab. Yeah. Uh-oh.
Oh, come on. I want to kick somebody in the face.
This guy right here. This guy. I'm smashing this guy.
Oh, what? What? That thing's got a ton of reach.
Oh, I get hit by a bow and arrow. That hit me right in my face.
Holy crap. This is insane.
Oh, yeah. One more time is the night. I'm going to switch to something else.
I'm going to try Vanguard next. That seems like a lot of fun.
Is it like an objective we're supposed to be doing?
I feel like we're just all running in and clubbing each other.
Like, what's the objective here?
All right, one-on-one. You want to go? You want to go?
I'll kick you. Oh, no. I don't have kick.
Oh, you want to fake me out? I remember that from the training.
Overhead smash. What? I didn't block that?
Come here, you. Oh, yeah. Get it. Oh, yeah.
Anybody else? There's an archer up here. Oh, he's going to shoot me in the face.
Oh, God. This guy's broke. Whoa. Whoa.
No, don't do it. Don't hit me.
God. What? What? What? What?
I had the shield up. All right, let's go.
What do you want to do, Vanguard? Vanguard.
We're doing the spear and throwing axe and the war axe.
And when am I spawning? When am I spawning?
Did we lose? What's going on? Do we have no more, like, recruits left?
Oh, no, we do. All right. What is, like, the mission here?
I don't even know what the hell is going on.
Throwing knife. Can I just whip this?
Oh, crap. I'm sorry. I just hit that guy in the back.
I'm sorry. I'm whipping this. I'm hitting this guy right in his forehead.
You ready? Watch this. Oh, who is getting this in the face?
Yeah. Well, that didn't work.
All right. Don't worry. We got this. We got this.
Me and you, baby. I'll stab you. I'll stab you.
Oh, I'll get you. Oh, no. Oh, this guy's freaking me out.
No!
I got to get the... See, you can, like, fake people out and stuff.
I got to get the fake... I got to get the fake out down.
It's all about, like, going like this. I'm not going to hit you. I'm going to hit you.
Abandon the castle. Wow. Arrow just went by my face.
I don't want to get in the face of an arrow.
That's, like, number one thing I don't want to have happen.
All right. 1v1 me. Let's go. Let's do that again.
Wow. A lot of dudes. A lot of dudes. A lot of dudes.
Don't want to go up there. I'll wait for them to come.
Come on. Who wants to get overhead smashed?
This guy's going to jump over and just do a massive bomb swing.
I can tell you right now that's what's going to happen.
Here we are. Oh, what the hell?
What the hell just hit me?
Get him. Oh, damn.
Damn him.
There's two. There's too many. It's not fair.
Get me out of here.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, goodness. Nice.
Nice job. This game.
This game is just total chaos. I love it.
I love this game. All right.
Get him. Get him. Bomb rush him. What?
Oh, somebody hit me in the back and hit from behind.
How do you win a game?
I have no idea how to win a game.
Uh, let's see.
140 to 141.
Next objective. Defend the treachery bots, apparently.
All right.
Wow. Went behind the face. My face. My face. My face.
All right. I got to be careful here.
I keep running myself into death.
Oh, just like this. Oh, you want to guard?
Is that what you want to do? Why don't you come up these stairs?
Oh, get up the stairs.
I said that didn't kill him. That didn't kill him.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. I just got killed by my own teammates.
Dude, team killing.
This is like the most realistic team
killer game. You just go around and
crush people. What am I? Seven
and oh, goodness. Hey, I'm not doing too bad
for my first time playing. Come here.
This guy. You got to be careful.
Don't I have something else?
Yeah, I get the throwing thing. Yeah.
Got you. Got you.
Oh, got you.
Whoa. Did I? Did I? Okay, good.
I didn't kill my teammate. I thought I just killed my teammate.
Run. Run away.
I feel like a Monty Python
movie is about to play in the background here.
Wow. Swarm him. Swarm him.
Swarm him. Swarm him. They can't
kill us all. They can't kill us all.
Swarm his ass.
Oh.
I'm going to kill this guy.
I don't want to kill my
own teammate. This guy's got
to die. Nice job. Nice job.
This guy doesn't even know I'm behind him.
Man, this guy's a blocking maniac.
No, get out of the way, man.
Okay. Oh.
Oh, it was a bow and arrow. I don't even know
how you win. Oh, let me look at like
the objectives. There's so much
stuff going on. Oh, one minute,
thirty-three seconds. I see. I see. All right.
I got to get to ten kills. I got to kill ten people.
I got to make something
happen here. If you were
thinking about getting this game and you didn't know,
this game is a lot of fun.
I like love this game.
Here we go. Come on. I know you think I'm going
to fake you out, don't you?
Come on. Come on. Block it. Block it.
Yeah. What you got? What you got?
Oh, get your face smashed. Oh,
come on. You want to get faked out?
You want to get fucking stabbed?
Swear word.
Block it out.
Oh, this game makes Jerma
swear. You know it's crazy.
What is this guy doing?
Get him. Oh, kick him.
Kick him in his face. Hey,
I can swing down here. I got a narrow
weapon. I'll just jab.
That guy's dead. Good. Let's end this.
Let's end this.
Let's end this. Oh,
come on. What do you say? What do you say, man?
I'm going to fake you out? I'm going to fake you out?
Oh, god. Behind me. Get out of my
face, dude. Oh, no. 2v1.
This is not good.
This is ridiculous.
Get him.
What? What? There's no way.
There's no way. I blocked that.
I blocked that. Do we win?
I think so. Yeah. We won.
Nice. Well,
if you were thinking of getting this game, guys, this game
is hilarious and a lot of fun.
So I definitely recommend it. This is my first time
playing. I'll probably play this again.
I'll probably live stream it or something like that.
But that's going to wrap up the video, guys.
So thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all soon. And of course,
take care, everybody.