Why, hello there. How's it going? What's up? He's speaking. I, it's always a minute and 30
seconds after I turn the stream on. Have you noticed that? It is 90 seconds when I talk.
Usually, what about Golem part two? No, we're not going to play Golem today. I don't think we're
going to play Golem again. Uh, I gave it a fair score of, what did I give it? I thought it was
pretty good. I gave it like a 7.6. I thought it was fine. I like the, um, the ending cut scene
was really cool when you shoot the lightning out of your hands at Sauron. That was a good touch.
I think a 7.6 or something. I, although I don't, I'm not like a big fan of the, uh, over the
shoulder kind of 3d sonic levels type shit they were doing when you run really fast up and down
the hills and you go over the loop to loops and stuff. It was kind of weird that they put it in
the last. The last section was probably my most favorite, but also the kind of weirdest.
Um, I think it was a 7.6. Hey, what's up? All right. Today we're just going to hang out.
I like the crafting. The crafting system was good. Yeah. I'm going to stream for like only a few
hours today. I woke up with a fucking headache and it's just one of those headaches. It just
doesn't go away. So kind of annoying. When are you going to play SpongeBob Battle for Bikini Bottom?
He's lying. That was a lie. It was not. He's lying. Only a few hours. I mean, I, I typically
stream for like five to seven, but yeah, we'll just, we'll hang out for a little while.
I want to play this game called, uh, it's called Q Remastered. Seeing some people play this seems
like a good, uh, fun puzzle experience. It's a, it is a physics based puzzle game. So what you have
to do is you have, there's a ball you have to get into a hole and you have to use your imagination
to get it there. They don't give you any of the tools besides your imagination.
So I'm just going to hang out and play. Will you stream for 16 hours? That's never going to happen.
I don't, I don't think I could ever do a real 24 hour stream or more than like 15.
I don't think it's possible. My energy levels burn out completely after I want to, I mean,
maybe like six hours of being on stream. I'm kind of like, I, I, I have to leave within an hour or
two. Usually eight hours is like the end. I don't know how, I don't know what superpowers some
people have where they can just be completely normal and fine on stream for like 20 plus hours.
I just can't do it. It sucks to be old. Is that what it is you think? Am I just, am I just old?
When are you going to play tears of the kingdom? I don't know. I don't know. I have to be really
honest with you. Should I be really upfront? I don't know if I'm ever going to play tears of
the kingdom. I just don't know. Right. I don't, I can't say the answer is yes. I know everyone's
very upset now and everyone's very unhappy with me, but I just, maybe eventually there's other
things I want to do first. And in the priority list, it sounds really stupid and I, I get it,
but Gollum was higher on the priority list than tears of the kingdom. That sounds crazy.
But do you, do you understand the priorities that I have here? You know what I'm saying? Like Gollum
was higher on the priority list, not because Gollum is a better game. Where is the priority
for project Zomboid? Uh, okay. It's underneath street fighter six. It's okay. Street fighter
six is essentially, okay. I like that. I think I'm going to stream that again. Yeah. It's comedy
priorities. Exactly. Where is sorcery on the list? Where's Hilux two on the list? Where's Yakuza zero
on the list? Bucko. Ooh, that was a bucko on that one. Yeah. What's that? We can keep talking. Let's
get going. He's pandering. No, I'm pandering. Don't you think pandering would be a month of
tears of the kingdom only for you guys. And I'm going to dress his link every day. And I'm also
going to go, yeah, skip, skip. Okay. That just sounded like I didn't go all in on it. You can't
do that voice unless you go all in and I didn't fucking go all in. That was, that's, I fucking was
telling myself go all in or it's going to be embarrassing. And I didn't, you have to go all
in because then nobody can make fun of you. Cause it's like, Whoa, you went all in for that. Nice
actual effort there. Going scuts, scascute is not what he does. And it's not enough effort.
I need to do more. I try harder. But what if your voice cracks during that? Well, that's a risk you
have to take anyways. Welcome back. I'm going to play this fun game. See how it goes. But yeah,
I pandering would be if I were to be, Hey, I'm going to stream tears of the kingdom until I beat
it. And Hey guys, how about an encore? And I play the whole game again for like another month.
No, I'm not pandering. If anything, I'm probably I'm anti pandering. See who are you calling out
here? I'm not calling out anybody. I haven't seen one second of tears of the kingdom footage.
Zero. Well, that's not, that's not accurate. I've seen people, I've seen people of like
sharing like the weird stuff that they're making on Twitter. I don't, I don't want to get spoiled.
I haven't even beat breath of the wild. I haven't seen any footage of tears of the kingdom.
Okay. I've seen somebody make like a ball sack, right? Every, you've all seen it. Okay. I'm not
going to pretend I haven't seen it. What do you mean? What? Oh, working. What? You haven't seen
that? I haven't seen it. I haven't seen it. What do you mean? You guys haven't seen, you haven't
seen the ball sack from tears of the kingdom? Hold on. I mean, honey, you're a ball sack image
that I've seen. Have I seen a ball sack image on Twitter from tears of the kingdom? She said no.
Is there like a book, a ball sack? I need to look at something. Hold on a second.
I can't, I don't want, no, I'm not writing this. I'm not going to type this in. Can't you, you can
like make any object in tears of the kingdom, right? Isn't that like, Oh, look, the joke I made. Look,
I made like a bunch of crazy stuff. Kind of. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. God damn it. I'm hallucinating.
I swear to God, I didn't have a dream that, that people were making. Oh, look, I can combine any
object. And look, I made, I made a penis. Am I making that up? Did I have a dream that this
happened? Tell me the truth. I'm not making this up. Unless I had a dream that this happened.
You said ball sack. Yeah. You said, yeah, but that's why I meant the same, like kind of the
same kind of bullshit. All right. Anyways, Vinny made a flaccid penis on stream. Okay. So that,
so I know what I'm talking about. This is exactly what I was talking about. Sorry. I used,
I used the term ball sack. I used this. I said ball sack instead of, Oh, you didn't say flaccid
penis. Oh, those are not the same category. That was, I was talking about the category of,
of things that people are making. Sorry. I wasn't super specific. All right. You guys ready to
chill out on a chill stream today? You're weird, man. No, you're weird. You're the weird one. Okay.
Not super, you were super specific. You were just wrong. No, I'm just saying like, Oh,
I made a ball sack. I made a penis. I made a flaccid penis. It's there. They're in the same
category of comedic, comedic, phallic shaped object stuff that people can make in video games
with the right tools. And that can like, well, look what I did. Okay. There we go. I made my
statement. You said ball sack exclusively for so long. Yeah. But why do we have to pick out every
little, you said this and you said that and you didn't use it. You said that. Let's go.
You're digging yourself into a hole. I guys, I told you how I literally shit my pants like three
weeks ago. I did. I'm not, I'm, I'm very unbothered. All right. So how does this work? What do you mean?
Huh? Oh, they weren't here. Yeah. Let them go find it in the FOD somewhere. You know what I mean?
Okay. Draw something in the space below the cursor by moving the mouse, draw a line. We'll press.
Okay. So there we go. There it is. Draw something and have it touch the red ball.
That is not a red ball. That is a purple ball. Oh no. Hey everybody. I have the proper tools
to be able to make something really interesting here. Don't I?
I, it's eyes and here are the eyebrows. Oh shit. How do I clear this? What is it?
How do I kind of clear this? I have to change this right now. I have to change this right now
before I get in trouble. All right. Touch the left wall with the ball. Oh, oops. That. Okay.
You're a Reddit gamer. What does that even mean? Like I just, what do you mean by that?
Just like this is a game where you draw lines and push a ball to the other side of the,
what do you, why does it have to be a Reddit game? Okay. That's the left wall with your drawing.
Draw a stick and let it drop. Draw a slope and let something roll on it. The choice is yours.
Touch the left wall with your drawing. Oh, okay. Cool. New questions appeared. What is going on
here? There's a lot. Everyone. Hell. If you solve seven out of 10 questions, the next 10 questions
will appear. Oh, okay. I get it. Let's keep going. Touch the left wall with your drawing. Oh,
wait. I already did it. I got it. All right. So it's the next one here. Take the ball out.
All right. We're going to make a, how do I take the ball out? All right. We're going to go like
this and we're going to put, we're going to weigh it down, right? I mean, that was all right. I said
to do a little bit more. Get the ball out. I'm just going to fucking launch it with this like
5,000 pound brick. What's fucking happening? This is not, it's not a mobile game ad. Quiet.
It's not a mobile game ad. You're wrong. Cause you haven't heard this yet. So you're wrong.
Take the ball out. Why can I not do this? I'm going to be honest. Did you take shrooms today?
We use more, you need more velocity? Is there actual velocity? Dude, I didn't know there was
actual velocity. I thought it was like based on, all right. Well, I was doing the right thing.
Make the ball touch the left wall. All right. Let's go. Watch this shit. Ready? All right.
We wanted to push it this way. So we're going to go like this. I'm just going to build this up
until we can get it to push stacks. Can I like prop stuff up? Hold on. What if I do this? Okay.
Ready? No, go this way. How would that have possibly gone that going that way? Is this a bit?
No, it's a physics based puzzle game. Now push that. Can I add weight? Okay. I'm starting to
understand that you can actually do long pieces. I'm trying to, I'm trying to make like a hook.
Why is it so heavy? But wait on the end of it. It has to hit the left wall. Oh, that was it.
Almost. Your IQ is going down so fast. You don't even, do you have no idea how IQ even works?
You don't even know how it works. Do it at the bottom. That was like making like,
make it like a, like a crowbar, like bend it. I don't think I can do that. This is a left brain
game. That's fine. I mean, I'll, I'll, I'll figure it out. I got it. Got it. Okay. There it goes.
All right. Now what do I do? Now we crushed this. Um, this is too long. What the fuck? I want to
put, can I like push it from this way instead? Not really. Chat, you're losing it. Chat's losing
it right now. Yeah. Let me tell you something about chat. They can sit there and eat their popcorn
and scream about how I'm not doing this right. But when they get to level seven on their own time,
they're going to go, thank fucking God. Nobody's watching me do this. Wait, is he still on chat?
Is he still on six? Fucking idiot. You're a fucking stupid idiot. All right. I'm thinking
just a bunch of weight here and then connect it like this shit. Or like, can I just like go
like this and just punch it, but wait on the other end. So there is weight. All right. I'm
starting. All right. All right. I know that there's real weight. I know. All right. I didn't,
I didn't really know that. Now check this out. Will this stick to walls? Oh, all right. I have
to have, this has to touch the left wall. Is it possible that I can make noise? So I can't attach
things, right? Okay. I can catch them like that. Not really though. How do I get this to, all right.
It's got to be, catch it all like that. But then how do I, your A, let me tell you something. If
you write the same thing a thousand times, it's not going to help me. It's like you guys, you guys
are at like the zoo right now. Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid. Hey, can you hear me boy? Hey,
can you hear me behind the glass? You're stupid. I just wait to one of the, wait to one of the zoo
fucking workers comes out there and throws you out. Don't tap on the glass. I'm busy.
Okay. I need to work backwards. So if I were to go like this, I'm just,
I'm just curious what happens here. And there it is. Now I just have to very carefully try to make,
Oh, fuck you. Not you. Shit. I almost did it. Wait. Shit. Damn it.
But how do I get the ball to move? I feel like it's, I can just have a ball hit it like this,
but it bounces too fucking high. Chill stream. Relax. All right. That should be fine. That'll
do it right there. Yes. Now everybody sit down. Finally. Hey, finally. Hey, excuse me. Zoo
attendant. Yes. Hey, am I allowed to throw stuff? No, no, you've, you've never been allowed to do
that. Oh, too bad. Too bad. I could scream at him though, right? Well, technically no. Oh, okay.
Can you get a picture of me in front of, uh, giving the peace sign and like the middle finger.
Can I get a picture of that? Two years supporting this clown. Well, that's accurate. Thanks though.
You need to be studied because I didn't figure out a physics based open-ended puzzle
level in the time that you have allocated for me to do so. This guy had trouble with a physics
based puzzle. Study his brain. Okay. All right. Watch this one. What? Oh, I can't draw in the blue.
Okay. So I can, can I just go like this? Draw something and touch the red area. Can I build
just like, like a staple tower? I think that makes sense. And then just kind of from here, I guess
make like a little bridge and then study him. Study his brain. Study his brain. Oh no.
Put five balls in the plate below can be done heavily if drawn persistently at the same point.
Put five balls in the plate. Uh, how do I get them out of here? All right. Can I just drop like a
huge, like, can I just like a big like grenade? I think I can do a big grenade. Okay. That's what
I'm going for here. Yep. All right. I'm thinking big, big grenade. And then once I get them up here,
they're going to go like this. I need them to go like this. Fuck. Um, okay. How do I undo? Okay.
How do I get them to get out of here? I win. What? I don't know. You didn't say what balls need to go
in there. I win. That should work. I have balls in the plate, but how do I get them to get out of
here? I need to scoop them. Can I like drag them out? Let me scoop one. Can be done heavily
if drawn persistently at the same point. I don't even know what that's telling me to do.
You need a big scoop. Hold for more weight. Actually real. Wait, are you serious? Hold on.
Are you actually kidding? Hold the mouse down in the same spot. That doesn't work. Hold. I,
what do you think I'm doing? I'm holding it right now. You liars. Please read heavily. I don't know
what that can be done heavily if drawn persistently at the same point. What are they talking about?
Bigger ball is more weight. Yeah. I figured that out. It didn't really do anything though.
I tried this already. Wait, if I miss me filling it in like this actually doing stuff,
like spending more time like this. Well, okay. That's good to know. I thought it was just make
a ball and it would be heavier, but apparently I have to like go like this inside of it too.
It's literally not how it works. All right. That has to do it right.
Make a triangle. Make it point this way. Hey, that kind of looks like Nevada. That's where I live.
Dude, you can't fit it in there. Make it smaller. You can't. I can't make it smaller. This is as
big as I can make it. I can't fit anything down here. Do it from the ceiling. I can't put it
higher than this. Get in there. Yes. All right. I got one. No, I don't. Okay. I'm thinking have a
big flat top like this. So there's a ton of weight because I can't go higher than this
and it'll just smash right through. It'd be like a nail driving in. I mean that didn't really work,
but I might be okay. It was too close. All right. So that I need more velocity. I this is,
I can't go higher than this. Make a true wedge. I'm going back here and I'm going to make it a
big ball with a point right here. I can't make it heavier than this, but there's no way for me to
make this heavier. I just have to get lucky and get it to actually hit balls out like that.
And there it was. I apparently, apparently this was the right object. This like
fucked up piece of shit that I made. It was the right one. So I was going to remember that.
There it is. One, two, three. I can get these. God damn it. One, two, one, two, three. We're good
right here. I wish that just, it wasn't this high because you can't get any real weight or leverage
from this. Don't even say skill issue. I'll tell you about personally. One, two, three.
Fuck you. Come on. Right here. All right. I need literally one more. There it is. Get out of here.
Arrow dynamic Andy. Arrow dynamic Andy. Take the ball out. You got it. That was embarrassing. Well,
here's the thing. It wasn't embarrassing for me. So you are putting, you are putting on embarrassment
on me that I do not have. I'm fine. I feel great. I feel good. Why did I think that was going to
happen? Pull it down. Come on. Check this out. All backwards. Oh, why is it falling forwards?
All backwards. This guy does not get physics. Neither do you. Neither do you. What do you know?
You don't know. What do you know? What do you know about physics? Huh? Did you write a paper on it?
What do you know? Hey, what do you know about aerodynamics? I have an idea. All right. Wait
a minute. Hold on. Somebody just said they laughed out loud. Stop question marking me.
I didn't do anything wrong. I didn't do anything wrong. Pull it back. Pull it back. What are you
doing? That's not, that's not how you fly a plane. Are you out of your mind? What are you doing?
There it is. I got it. I actually got it. That's definitely, that's it right there.
I win. Oh, question marks, question marks. Over that. This is not a chance in hell that I didn't
just take that from mod chat. No way. Not actually physically possible that I, that I
took that directly from a mod who drew that exact thing to do. Um, make the ball touch the left
wall. You got it. I want to see, I want to be able to freak out. I want to make it so it can't go
down. You know what I'm saying? Yeah. Like this. I want to, why can I draw where I want to draw?
All right. So now it can't go this way. So it has to just go, looks in the right spot.
Like I'm playing a claw machine. There it is. You question marking. I just beat it.
I don't know. I have no idea. I almost need to see this burst. I need to, because it needs to be
heavy here to fall this way hard to launch this up. But how do I get that to actually do like,
do I have to do, I need to draw it. I wish there was a, like a paint mode. Because if I go like
this, will it like, no, I need to like a thing to just launch it up. Oh,
Oh, what do you know about that? Huh? Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't,
I don't know how this works. I don't have a physics degree. Okay. I don't,
do you understand like where leverage points are to pick up a toy on the ground?
It needs to be further out like here. What are you, I didn't want to hit space idiot.
This end on the right side, this side has to be longer than this side. How the fuck am I going
to do that? Hold on. No, I need to, it's so funny going over and looking at the chat here.
It's just people screaming their interpretation of what they think I should do. You tap them on the
glass right now. Like how am I supposed to read any of this? How did I graduate? I didn't go to
college for physics. I didn't go to school for physics. Huh? Bro, I can't believe you graduated
from your physics math college. I didn't. That's it right there. Come on, grab them. No, I'm just
too much. You got, that can't be, it's got to be like a bow in the middle right there. Bang.
Don't forget about the counterweight. I almost had it. Okay. Shh. Where am I sir? Shit. I can't
make him stand up. All right. That's going to be bigger. No, I didn't want to hold stuff a little
too long. Yeah. Oh, that's going to be way easier. Why did I not, why would I do not, this is going
to work in only like a couple of tries. Why did I overcomplicate this? This is so much easier.
Oh my God. I just heard it. Okay. I heard that from across the whole fucking, I heard that from
far away. I was really far away. There it is. Don't fall forward. Have, no. Stop this shit at once.
Ooh, wait. No, no, no. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Just stay right there. We're fine. Draw something and touch the red area. You got it. Yeah. Don't
worry. I know how to get up there. I've played Tetris before and lost every time. I have an idea.
I have an idea. Watch this. Take this out. Oh, you guys are going to fucking freak out when you see
this. That's the right idea. The ball was just too big. See you. Make the ball touch the ground.
All right. This is going to, this is going to take us a little while. I think you ever heard of a
square. I want that person permanently banned and then I want you to unban them. And I want,
I want them to give a paragraph as to why they think this should be allowed back.
Okay. All right. Let's just like fuck the whole thing up. How does this sound? Oh man. Okay. Is
this like stupid? No, almost not really. Hold on. Almost not really. Wait a second. Wait a second.
Wait a second. There it is. I just got to weigh this down. There it is. Oh, what happened? Okay.
Cool. Oh, wait a minute. Okay. We're at, where are we? Primary one. Okay. Yeah. I'm not ready
for that. Make the ball touch the weight. I already did this. Didn't I already do this one?
How's this one different? Make the ball touch the left wall. I did it already. Yes, I did. Oh,
it's just to get it out before. Oh shit. That's okay. That is different. I just, just wait
before you do your question marks. Just wait a second. I'm fucking up and oh, it's really heavy.
Come on. That's gotta be it. Yay. Oh, not yet. Wait, you're doing the same thing over and over
again. That's what I'm trying to. Yeah. Well, you have to, I'm deducing what's going on.
Turn the music off. Yeah. Let's get it. Let's get our own soundtrack in here because this is,
yeah. How about, give me an OST. Did it again. Guys, that's what you do. Hold on. I'm not quite
ready yet. Can I even save this? How about, what do you guys think? How you guys doing?
You could turn off music and then just play, we could play our own. That's a really smart way to
do this. Um, people will get mad if it's not coming through my stream. That's a very smart
thing to do though. All right. How about, um, pizza tower? Yeah. I love that so much, but
animal crossing. Yeah. Animal crossing is pretty damn good. Celeste is really good too. How about,
um, yeah, let's go with animal crossing. Which one though? Super Mario world. Oh,
that's a good one too. I'm doing that first. Super Mario world for the S N S O S T.
And let me turn this off. Uh, what is it? There we go. Uh, here it is. Is it? Yep. Yeah. That sounds
good to me. Shit. This is too big. What are you doing? Damn it. Hold on. I'll get it. You need
enough weight to pull it back and then you need the support here to really give it the leverage
that like, but then what the hell? Hold on. I think I actually just did it. No. Now what needs to
happen? Fulcrum fulcrum fulcrum. What is a fulcrum fulcrum fulcrum? That's the first time I've ever
heard that word. I don't know what that is. I'm telling you right now. I've never heard that word
said out loud point on which a lever rests or is supported and on which it pivots the pivot point.
Pivot point sounds way better than fulcrum. Fulcrum actually sounds pretty cool though.
Fulcrum is actually now I'm going to start using that because I actually kind of like that. Nice,
dude. All right. All right. So the pivot point, I need a different pivot point. Don't use words
that I don't understand. Oh my goodness. Okay. I'm almost there. I just have to fix this and it's
good. Watch this. This is stupid and it's really bad idea, but I'm going to go for it. I've ruined
it. I didn't have the fulcrum in the right spot. I still think I can do this though. Watch this.
I didn't want to click again. I got the fulcrum point in the right spot. That was much better.
So it needs to like pivot here, but how you can't change the width of your lines. That's why it's
kind of hard to do this. Push it down from the right side. That's actually not a bad idea. It's
going to just wedge it in there. Let's actually do something. Hold on. I didn't actually win.
So that music doesn't make sense. You're getting mocked by the music. Oh, wait a minute. Hold on.
Why do I think it has to be in one piece? Right? I got to put the fulcrum down here.
All right. Now what happens? Got it. Almost. Almost. Fulcrum's got to go right here. Okay.
I didn't want to do that. Now just smash the whole thing with a rock and it'll fix itself.
Pull it. Oh, shit. It's almost there. I can't. I think I got it though. If I knock this down,
uh, fulcrum is too high. We're going to do double fulcrum. I think that works.
Double fulcrum into pull, grab. I just freaked out. I almost had it though. Bro, are you, I'm tweaking?
What? Is it going to do anything? I'm just doing this to make it look like I'm, I'm doing better.
Wait, weigh him down. Fuck. Let's do it again. Shit. One or two is fine. Is that in a good spot?
It's hard to tell. No, it keeps hitting it. Stop doing the claw. Well, how do I get it to pull down?
The claw works. You just got to make sure it's small. How big should I make the fulcrum? I feel
like the fulcrum needs to be further in. I can't color the fulcrum in. And I did learn a new word
today. So I'm going to use it many more times tonight. It's not heavy enough. Make it wider.
This is the one right here. This is it. It's got to be in tighter, like here. Why can I not color
this in? Stop doing the triangles. All right. I got to pull it over this. I got it. That's the one
done pretty much. But now I can, can I, I can, I, I, can I, can I fix it? I almost need to make,
okay. Hold on. Let me draw this out. Here's the fulcrum point, which is where it's going to tip.
It's going to hit this, pull it tip. So it's going to tip. So let's weigh it down here
and let's make a line. The point of this fulcrum. See what I'm saying? So now when it pulls down,
it can't get all screwed up. So now what's going to happen is I'm going to pull it down. It's going
to go over here. Ball's going to fall out. What do I do? What do I do? Okay. I'm going for it.
Yeah. Right when we got to Bowser's castle. All right. Take the ball out. Okay. That's the
right idea. Hit it with a bowling ball. It is a little extra weight Alex in the container. Okay.
Let's go. I'm going to do a mini one. Okay. Now the idea is to hit this, hit them, hit them right
in the bottom of the chin, fly them up. He's getting in. Where'd he go? Okay. Well, I guess
he's gone. Is it too high? Is he eventually going to fall down? I don't know. That's definitely the
right idea though. It's supposed to be a little bit smaller, not as powerful. Well, it went the
wrong way. Perfect. God damn it. No, no, no. Just wait. I should have gone from up here. I got him.
I'm going to pull him in. Hook strat. I fucking ruined it. You better come back down. I'm going
to be pissed. No, wrong way. This is it. This is the one right here. Okay. I'm not going to
mess around. Not huge, but big enough to get the weight. There he goes. And thank you. Clutch at
the end there. That was clutch at the end there. I think I can take that one. That's pretty clutch.
Make the ball touch the red area. First try. First try. I just made a tank. Suma wrestler,
touch the left wall. Got it. Check this out. You might've thought that was a mistake. If I wasn't
talking, it would have been fine. I was, I was villain monologuing and lost when I had the whole
fucking thing one. All right. Make the ball touch the left wall. All right. This is going to be
interesting. Okay. Let's go with the tank strat with the long stick hanging out. And then we're
going to add to that. I'm going to put a little bit more weight down here. Boom. Now we're going
to restart. Just like scrape it with just with your weird like finger. The idea is to have the ball
right here. Be the thing that smashes into the side with my physics based technology
with patented physics based ball creation technology. Patented physics based ball
weight technology. Make the shape face right. You got it. You know exactly what I'm doing here.
I don't know anything besides rock smash something. You know it's happening. I know how to do a
see-saws. Oh, we've got a little bit of a counterweight problem. Fulcrum. We take fulcrum
in a big good spot. Bit by poisonous snake. Feel face scaling numb. Oh, good thing we have continuous.
This is the one right there. There's a little saliva in my mouth. You know, it's the real one.
Fucking thing. What are you talking about? It's stuck on the wall. There it is. Oh, how was it?
Why is the face the other way? My family is in my living room watching you play this for an hour
straight and my dad has been getting pissed at you not knowing what a fulcrum is and now he's
yelling at the screen because you're hook strats. Hold on a second, dad. First of all, I appreciate
the constructive feedback on how I'm playing this game. I appreciate the constructive feedback.
But, I don't know. I was about to just like start screaming at whoever this is.
But then, I don't know. I feel like whoever the son or daughter is in this case, I feel like they'd
be like, oh my God, I got to switch to somebody else like right now. Quick, quick, quick,
switch to somebody else. And who else is streaming right now? I don't care who it is. Okay, I'm going
to be fine. I have an idea. My idea is very simple. See, what we have to do is we make the
fulcrum point here, add the seesaw bit right here, and very easy. We get Batman to show up
and we crush him. We kill the Batman. Oh, Joker, you have no idea what you're doing.
You can't complete this puzzle game. We're going to have any characters show up on Jerma's stream.
Shut up. Dad just laughed out loud. I heard it. I could hear it through the television.
I heard dad laugh at the television after that one, and I'm not happy about it.
What was the point of drawing these? I'm just going to do the hook again. What? What am I doing?
I don't know. Stop the hook bullshit. Stop the hook bullshit. I'm doing it the other way.
I had a good idea. I need a way better fulcrum like that. Now see this. Now hear this. See this.
You seeing this? Watch this. This is going to be unbelievable. Dad, hold on to the couch
because here it comes. Hold on to something. Hey, hey, it's very funny. Hey, son or daughter,
come and give me a hug. What a great bonding experience this was between us.
Exactly what I'm looking for. That's what I'm looking for. What a bonding experience
you had over this. That's great. I'm glad. I hope the strength of your family is stronger now.
What the hell is this? What is this? Still Mario? This is not Mario anymore. Any mods in here that
can give me a hand with this? That's a good idea. I think it's a combination of hook strategy
and ball strategy. Two of my favorite things in the game. Now that's going to work. That's
a combination of hook and ball strategy. Maybe up a little higher. Make a scooper like that.
Kind of. It needs to be small. Even smaller than that? Really? This will do it. That's it
right there. Oh my god. Make the ball heavier, not bigger. I don't, I don't know what that means
because I don't, I don't get what you mean. Was that actually a thing in the game or were people
making that up? It's real. So if I just sit here and hold the button down like this, this will be
much heavier. Give it a point. That's the one right there. All right. All right. We're halfway
there. I now I'm thinking hook strategy here. I just have to push this over. Here's my idea.
I don't think it's going to work, but I could try. I'm thinking make a long road and just drop a
boulder down here, but I don't think that's going to do it. Put a hook on the hook. Why did I even
listen to that person? Why did I listen to that person? But make, hold on, make like one of these.
Will that like help kind of move it? Come on, stop. Maybe that little dip will be enough. Smash.
All right. This is not horrible, but it kind of is horrible. It's too long. It needs to be way shorter.
But this needs to be longer and this needs to be shorter. This needs to be barely right there.
Now we're going to make a first hook. Is this too big? You think this is too big?
That's my favorite item from Costco. Um, uh, I don't know. Cheese. I do like the point though.
Make this sort of like a triangle. Have a point that just smushes right onto that line. I want
this thing to flip. It's upright. All right. It's upright, but how do I get it to go all the way?
Cause I can't delete anything. It'd be a fulcrum. I need something to wedge under it as it flips.
Something over here. Maybe if I go like this, will it push this? I don't know. Oh, no.
Flip it the other way. Can I flip it? Hold on. Let me cook for a second. Watch this.
Didn't even think about that. Did we? Didn't think about this. Did we? My dad is screaming at me.
Hurry, dude. You're evolving backwards. Please. You don't have to do every level, but I'm,
I want to see, I want to try. He needs a recipe book. VOD watchers skip an hour. You know,
when I'm watching a VOD and I look over a chat and I see some, and I'm just hanging out with my,
you know, sandwich and my, you know, my large turkey sandwich, lettuce, mustard, mayo mix,
tomato, one thin sliced tomato. Just kidding. Take that off. Don't put that on any food.
Lettuce, mayo with some turkey stalling. I don't like looking over and people going,
Hey, skip for an hour. I don't, I don't tell me what to do. You just spoiled that the stream,
the streamer didn't, you know, I don't tell me what to do. You shouldn't be telling the
VOD watchers what to do. VOD watchers skip an hour. That's their decision. They just did,
but at least it was their call, not yours. Insecure Andy. I'm just fucking, I need to see how it
bounces. Okay. You need a fulcrum. Make Alex touch the right wall. You got it. Okay. When in doubt,
when in doubt, you just, just use the hook. I don't think I can do anything with the tail,
this stuff on the way. Right wall. Okay. So if I go like this, what music is playing?
A club penguin, I guess. Uh, what else? Use a hammer. Okay. That's an ax. What? No, wrong.
Really? What do you mean? Touch the ground with the red object. A little bit of a claw strategy
will work pretty good. Shit. Pull it off. Just have to touch the ground. All right. Now I need
to knock this over. Touch the ground. Touch the ground. Oh my God. Uh, yes. That's the red area
with your drawing. You can't draw in the blue area. Um, don't need a fulcrum on that one. Make
the ball touch the left wall. What do you think? Oh, let me talk about Gen loss for a little bit.
So those who didn't see, uh, generation loss, it was Rambo's show. It's a three day event. It was
really, really cool. I'll just give you a, I know that, um, there's been a lot of behind the scenes
stuff you may have seen, but, uh, I don't know how much anybody was paying attention or knows or
the second day, uh, Rambo and I came up with a lot of that stuff together. So it was really fun.
That was a long time ago too. The hook longer on the left side. Yeah. I'm thinking like this.
That's not a hook. Now it is. I was really excited because obviously Rambo had this incredible
passion project and it was kind of just like, Hey, do you want to do this? And then originally
I was potentially going to be in a mask. Uh, Rambo was like, Hey, what if we just put you in
a bunch of prosthetics? Cause that mass that I had was going to be, Oh, what are we going to, I guess
try to speed a mass. Should I have like makeup on? Should I, you know, should we make me look,
how do we do it? And it gave me this great excuse to get into all that prosthetics,
touch the left wall. And I do, I have this mold. It is a one-to-one complete replica of my face.
Like I said earlier, down to every pore. It is better than HD. Show it. I'll show it one day.
You need to smash that. You're repeating yourself. I know cause I'm thinking and I can't do,
I can't talk and think at the same time, but it was really cool to be a part of it. I remember,
so that, that Wonka kind of like candy room. I remember I was writing it down and I'm just
sitting there going, is this like, is this going to be in the show? Is this going to like make it?
And it did. I was really happy about it. I hung out with a lot of really cool people,
got to meet a lot of new people and a lot of people that I've never communicated with
like ever before. Obviously it was really cool to, to see Vinny. That's the first time me and Vinny
have seen each other since like PAX 2015 or something. So that was really, really awesome.
I'm not doing this right. This is making me irrationally angry. Well, at, at least you're
aware of that. You know what I mean? Like this is making me irrationally angry. It's actually
really important for you to kind of decipher that this is a rational anger. It's a rational what
you're saying, right? You've been being mindful of that. That's really, really important. Time
that person up for an hour. Shit. Can I have some help? Can anybody help me? I know what I have to
do, but I can't visualize it. Yeah. Walking around those sets. That was absolutely the biggest
project I've ever been a part of, ever been on. There were so many individual sets. Now, you know,
honestly hats off to Rambo for having the, you know, having the ability to want to put on something
like that and to be able to be that passionate about something. I'd love to see that stuff
because that's, it's not easy. It really isn't. So honestly hats off to Rambo and everybody else,
obviously that was working on the project too. It was really, really, it was, it was exciting.
It was fun. I got to go in prosthetics and be a fucking weirdo for like six hours. And I think,
I think he wants to do more. I think there's, I think that's, I don't know, he seemed pretty
excited to like kind of keep doing more stuff. It's like, hell yeah. That's, I love it. What
about your ass breaking the door? Yeah. I mean, I, my ass didn't break the door. I broke the door
with my body and then I kind of, at the very end, my ass was sort of the jokey part that I could say
broke it. I didn't actually break the door with my ass. It, it was perceived that way because I
mean, obviously that's what exactly what it looked like. And then I'm seeing a lot of copium and
CAPAs. I, all right, I stopped making a long hook over and over again and do it right. Were you
actually stuck? Kind of, I kind of, because those doors were made, were not, they were not operational.
It was like, there were people that were opening and closing those two doors. Like they were
opening them and closing them. And I kind of just pushed it, going through it too fast.
This, yeah, they were like Star Trek doors. The reveal of the two foot long revolver.
At least we're making music. I'm sorry about this. Draw the weight on the left side. All right,
I can pay attention again. How do I get the ball over there? Terma straight up murders someone. Yeah.
I remember when we were talking about that scene, I was like, okay, so I'm, I, I, I'm gonna shoot her.
Whoever it is. Because the way that that was going to work out was it was always going to have to be
somebody, right? There were only two or three people that could have been in there. So it was
like, okay, who could it even be? Who is the, who are the possible candidates that could be in this
room? Because obviously that was the chat interaction and stuff too. So as we're going through, it's
like, okay, so it could be you. It could be you. It could be, all right. So now how, so I have to
shoot someone. How do I move this? This is a mobile ad. I know it's a mobile ad. I'm skipping this one.
Also, if you wanted something interesting, let me talk about this because this is, and let me turn
this music down because this is weird. So during the first three rooms, so the, the surgery room,
the carousel room and the electric zap key room, I didn't have any direction in my ear.
So if you're wondering why I didn't pick the right person on the carousel is because I had,
I did not know who it was because we didn't, I didn't have it in my ear because I had,
it was a technical problem. So for the first three rooms, I was just like, oh, oh, fuck. I need to,
I need to pay close attention to everything going on because I have no direction in my ear.
So it was, there was an internal moment as we were starting that third kind of carousel scene
where I was just going, all right, man, this is a good luck because I don't know what's really
going on. I kind of just went in there and it was like, all right, I'm just going to have fun.
And that's exactly what it was. It was such a fun time to just put on that, those prosthetics.
I loved that. I loved every second of doing that. I think I even said to Rambo, I was like, oh man,
imagine, imagine we had like three more rooms to do. I feel like we were just, you know,
we were just getting right into it. Yeah, there's a point where Slimesicle, because I think Slimesicle
had direction in his ear. And there's a point where he's just like, hey, uh, don't, I mean,
if I was somebody picking, I think I would probably, you know, I may have, you know, maybe pick,
uh, pick her. And I was like, oh, what do you, yeah, that's really you. Is that what you,
is that what you think? Okay. All right. You. Oh yeah. I, Slimesicle saved my ass so bad.
I had absolutely no idea who, who got the audience poll. So I'm just sitting there going,
oh, okay. If you go back and watch it, I just, I just start stalling. I start stalling for time
because I just start doing duck, duck, goose. That is, that is the moment in the show when
you can know somebody got picked and I have no fucking idea who it is. I have not a single
solitary clue. So duck, uh, duck, I don't fucking know how I'm going to get through this one.
I don't know. I guess I was going to be like a weirdo with this prosthetics on and let me
walk around in a circle. Okay. I got this one. I know how to do it. We can put these back.
And that was, uh, uh, Valkyrae and Psychuno were the rats. They were a lot of fun to work with.
Valkyrae was super into that. It was awesome. Yeah. Super, super nice. They were really,
really cool. Just kind of hanging out and talking about random stuff. All right. How
do the, how are the rats going to act? Let's see. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
That's it right there. Now, come on, come on, come on, come on. This is a hook scenario, right?
What are your children's names? Yeah. Just, just walking up to Austin, just like, you know,
fluffing up his shirt a little, come here, you, let me, come here. What are your children's names?
It's just like, oh, fuck. Uh-oh. He is so goddamn fucking funny, by the way. I love
working with Austin. He is so fucking funny. Maybe I could just grab this one too. Let me,
let me try the grab. You know what I'm saying? The grab worked pretty well on the other one.
Why wouldn't it work well on this one? All right. We're getting somewhere. What about your runway
walk? Yeah. I've seen that pop up here and there. I love that cartoon villain shit, you know, going
into the, to the, the candy room, like that Willy Wonka inspired room being like, oh, hey,
can you hold this for a sec? Oh, the detonator and, and, you know, the, all the things that
you could get out with. I love the loony tunes bullshit. It's just, it just does it for me so
much. Is this going to do it? It needs to be really, really heavy shit with the walls flavored. I
don't, I don't think so. The goal with that room was to show people like, well, you do other shit
here. What do you, why? What? There was a bit that didn't get used that I really wanted to do,
but I guess there was just not enough time or not enough space or whatever. So here's what I
wanted to have happen. And it was, it was close to happening, but it just kind of didn't work.
When we were initially doing concept stuff, I thought it would have been funny if the,
so one of the rooms seems like a bit of room to room to room. Okay. We're in this room. Okay.
I made it out of this one. I'm on the next room. So take the party through the new room and they
open the door. Okay. What's the next one? What's the next weird saw inspired crazy puzzler weird
room. Right. And it's just a living room. It's just a regular living room with nothing weird.
And I just say, well, um, you know, I run an Airbnb out of here sometimes too. And actually
they're going to be here in about 20 minutes. So just, this is, there's nothing in here actually.
Just go to the next one and they just walk through it. And it's, it's a nice normal room,
but all that to just do one, like 15 to 22nd routine. Yeah, I get it. I think we need a folk
room or the other thing was, uh, it kind of started growing from there was what if there was just a
family in the room, like on vacation and show people like getting towels and like,
oh, we're going to the beach really soon here. Oh, we're right. We're like, as if we're getting
ready to like at the hotel, what is the cheesecake shit about? You want to know what the cheesecake
shit is about? What do you want me to tell you? Has Rambo talked about the cheesecake shit?
Has anybody talked about the cheesecake thing? Cause it was, it was literally not for anybody,
but for five people that were at dinner the night before. Okay. So they did. They have people have.
Okay. So let me, for those that have not heard the story, and I'm just going to do it really
quickly. Cause you may have heard it like three or four times already. So, and I'm not going to
play the game. So don't just relax. So at dinner, uh, there was a big dinner where there was, you
know, cast and crew. And we all kind of just went to dinner at this nice restaurant, right?
And one of the desserts was cheesecake. So one of the producers and they, we had a lot of people at
this table. So there had to have been at least, at least 15 plus people at this dinner. So at the
end, we got this big package where, okay, we have to feed all these people. We're doing a big group
thing. We got a bunch of desserts and it was probably like, Hey, I mean, it's 15, 20 people
sharing desserts. You have a bunch of different desserts. You've got like, I think we had like
eight to 10 cheesecake slices. They were just cheesecake everywhere. And one of the producers
kind of just looks over, we took a few bites. Oh, this is so good. Wow. It's so delicious.
And he kind of just looks over and he goes, wow, it's a bad day to be a cheesecake. And we were all
like, what the fuck was that? He's like, man, it's a bad day to be a cheesecake, isn't it?
And the whole kind of table is just like, it was like funny, but at the same time it was like,
all right, yeah, that's like, yeah. Cause it is kind of a bad day to be a cheesecake. Like
we're eating a fucking lot of them right now. And Nikki, who was sitting on the other side
of the table, she was laughing her ass off at this, just laughing her ass off. And we kept
saying it and kept kind of going over it. And at the table, we were kind of sitting around going,
all right, we know we're going to be on camera tomorrow. I'm going to do everything I can to
try to make as many people break on camera as possible. I'm going to say that tomorrow.
I'm going to find a way to say this. And people like, dude, please don't do that. You're going to
fuck up the whole show. You're going to ruin the whole show. Cause everyone's going to start
laughing. And it's that it's don't do that. Like should you do that? So I just like waiting for
the opportunity to be like, Oh, so you know that in joke that everybody's like, don't be careful.
Oh, I had pasta today. And that's how I told him I knew it was coming. The people knew it was
coming. The five or six, like seven people at that table knew it was coming when I started
talking about what I ate. So I'm like, Oh yeah. I felt pretty bloated after that. But for dessert.
Oh, let me just tell you it's a bad day to be a cheesecake. All right. Yeah. And that's the
fucking story. The goal was to try to make somebody just desperately fight with trying not to laugh
and fuck up that scene. It was, it was just like a good time. And you know, okay, you know,
whenever you do an event or a show or something, this is what, how I really believe and how I
really feel. No, like jokes are fucking around or anything right now. If people are having a good
time, then I feel like everything is better. The whole show from cast and crew. Everyone's like
actually having a great time. People like laughing. People are really into it. People have just,
you know, this is a fun time that we're all enjoying together. That's the most important
thing. And you look directly at Nikki as well. Yeah. I was going, I was like, okay, I, I know
you're, you're probably going to laugh. You're probably going to break. Um, I don't know. I
don't think I can do this one. What's this one? Make the robot sit on the chair. Wait, what? Can
it be my chair? How do I move this fast enough for, hold on. Should I push his legs? That's not going
to work. How do I make something happen here? I need a fulcrum. Big triangle. You mean for him
to sit on and get like launched? I'm not going to care about this right now. I'm just going to try
to figure out how to move this well. Okay. I don't have much time. I wish I could, there we go. It's
got to be much faster than that. How am I going to make that faster? Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait,
wait. This is hard. Can I just like box him in for a second? Okay. Upside down triangle behind
the chair and then push it forward. Yeah. But I'm upside down, but I feel I wanted to try it the
right way. How do you do this fast enough before he sits down? That's close. Go. It's not heavy
enough. It's not heavy enough. This is very, very hard. Wider, wider. I can't go much wider.
Otherwise it'll just hit the top and not do anything. It's close. Can I like weigh it down?
I think this is still possible from here. Block the guy's ass. I thought I tried last time,
but he's kind of just, hmm. He weighs too much. That doesn't help. You need to move the chair to
the guy. No, I don't. What are you talking about? There's nothing. I can't make anything weigh fast.
I can't, nothing can weigh enough before he's sitting down. See what I mean? Like I could make
it heavier, but you have to do it instantly. Like, can I like just box him in for now? I can't
unless it's, I didn't, what the hell did that do? I wonder if I can, no, you can't just slide back.
I don't get it. Like the sumo wrestler touched the ground? You had it? It's a pain in the ass. I
don't want to do it. I don't like being, I don't like time limits like that. Let me just do it.
I don't want a time limit. I don't want a one second time limit. I mean, I want to be able
to do it at my own pace. I don't want a one and a half second time limit. Oh, this is going to be
fucking hell. Okay. So I kind of need to just go like this, but it needs to weigh. Well, actually
this won't be that bad. Just make it really heavy. You got to touch the ground though. So that
actually might, close. Oh, nice turd. It's not heavy enough. Touch the ground. This weighs a
million pounds. You're saying make a big M or big W? What do you mean? Like how would a W work?
Weigh it down, then draw more above it. Let's go with, or are we going to go with the claw technique?
Hook technique is good. Keeps steady. This thing just needs to weigh a shitload. We're just going
to squish. Do you know what I mean? Just weigh this whole thing down. If this doesn't work, I,
I don't know what I have to do to get it to be perfect. All right, you ready? Let's let it go.
I didn't know this was part of the universe. The hand is part of the universe. Right. Make sure it
doesn't grab because it'll hook on. I like, they like this music. What is it? Is it still Club Penguin?
I like it. I should put on, I want to put on Smash Brothers music. You know, the one that goes,
it's actually getting stuck on the, this is actually the way to do it too. I just keep having to get
caught on stuff. I'm an idiot. Like an idiot. Don't go too close to the edge because it'll get stuck.
How do I, nothing is heavy enough. Nothing's heavy enough. It needs velocity. Put it up higher. I,
I can't. There's a hand in the way. I cannot do anything here. So the highest I can drop this from
is right here. Go from the ground up. How does that work? That's kind of close. Get it. I mean,
I could, I could sit here and grab this all day, but that's just not going to happen. That's what
I wanted to do in the beginning. All right. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Kind of was doing it.
Come on, do it. Is there a refund timer going? I'm way past that. All right. Let me think if I were
to, it needs to go boom, boom. So I mean, once you start drawing, it just drops. So there's,
I wish I could freeze stuff. I wish I could like hold something here, but I can't. So it has to,
when you start a drawing, you got to go from the ground up. So like, what if I do this?
Like just block it so it can only go to this area here and then just knock it somehow. And what if
I just drop a, what if I just dropped this on here? Like just go poink. Not going to help.
We can't hear the music again. Right there. I mean, I just, I just don't, I, I don't know.
There's no dodge roll in this game. I can't play it. Um, what is this? Make the balloon touch the
left wall. I think that's what they want me to do. Maybe just little bits. I hate this game and I'm
not even playing it. We're fine. Make the balls touch the red areas. These have to spin. Let's
just see what happens if I go right in the middle. Well, that's how you get it done.
Give the girl the balloon. Oh, you mean a crusher with a rock. Oops. Uh, can I,
I can't put anything in here. Oh, I can. Oh, I did it. What's going on? Pick, touch,
pick up the balloon. What's happening? What is going on? What, what the hell was that?
Why won't you stay? Stay. There we go. All right. Make the ball touch both red areas.
Ex, excuse me. Somebody said lower the game volume. Is it allowed? Make the ball touch both.
Excuse me. Looks like it's time for a fulcrum. That's right. Good call.
I'm fine. I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble. How do I get this to bounce? There it is.
Do that quick thinking right there. Make the balloons fly away. Just wait probably, right?
I imagine it's probably something like that. Yeah, there it goes. This game is addicting.
Release the balloon. Make the red ball touch the left wall. Why does it keep saying red?
Nice fulcrum, bro. I got it. Okay. Pull the bottle cap out. Easy. That's when I got this one done.
This one's in completely cashed. I didn't know the bottle was going to fall. Study this guy's brain.
Someone's trying to beat you in a race of the game. I'm not racing anybody. I'm playing
casually on my own time. This does not say, Hey, there's a, I'm, I'm racing right now. Red ball.
Okay. I got an idea with this one. Have your thirties been better than your twenties?
Um, that's a good question because I feel like in your twenties, you're kind of figuring out
who you are. And in your thirties, you kind of know who that is. I got an idea here. Hold on.
Watch this. Ready? This is going to be like a golf club. That's the right idea. Hold on.
Well, that was dumb. I think the rock has to be bigger and then this has to go all the way.
And then that's it right there. Keep pulling it. Close. Yeah. I mean, I honestly, I feel like since
I turned say like 35 or so, you kind of, I kind of just know exactly what I'm, what I want to do
and who that person is and who I am. In your twenties, you're really kind of still figuring
out like, Hey, what exactly am I doing with myself? I've said this before. It's, it's not a race. So
I know a lot of people in this channel are in their twenties. Um, it's not a race. Don't think
it is. I didn't figure out shit until I was well into my late twenties, early thirties. And still,
I'm still figuring out. I mean, look, I don't know how to do the f*****g Thagorean theorem here.
That's it right there. Oh, this needs to be so much heavier. Yeah. Maybe it's too heavy.
Maybe this needs to be heavier. Wait a minute. Hold on. Watch this. Now, theoretically,
I don't have a theory at all. S**t. S**t. It's right there. God damn it. Do it already. All right.
That pulls it. I think I got it. I think that's the one. I remember what that looks like.
Go like this up right here and then that here and then boot it. I think that's it. It wasn't,
that's too long, but all right. That's the right idea. S**t. Still too long. Have a big exam next
week. Wish me luck. I studied. Good luck. I've learned since the last time somebody said little
bro can't just say good luck to somebody. He has to go on a 15 minute rant about like pot pies and
stuff. I heard it. So I'm, I'm doing it differently now. F**k. It needs to be like a bend. I don't know
anything about this. We all do different things. Okay. If you're like, Oh, I know how to do this and
do that. That's good. I'm glad you know how to do it. I'm a tinkerer. There's a difference. You want
the thing to fall to the right, but keep building it up against the right wall. Dude. I know this
just at the zoo right now. I need to like bend it. I don't know. Move the ball first. I mean,
I guess I could move the ball first. Oh my God. No, stop. Move. Finish breath of the wild. Do you
suck at this game? You just added it three more weeks to when I'm going to play breath of the
wild. Remember that I need to remember this exact thing that I just did. I already forgot it. I
forgot it already. I wasn't even paying attention. Object permanence. I just not burning anything into
short term memory because I'm about to put a hole through my monitor. It's really hard before,
you know, before you like, you know, put your head, but the monitor, it's hard to be like,
Oh yeah. I like just like pay attention more. Why don't you ever headbutt a monitor? Oh,
I can't believe I'm up against. I'm up against. Oh, what's the character from League of Legends?
I can't even name one rise. What's his name? Oh shit. What's the, what's the, what's the
character's name? Oh yeah. It is rise. Oh fuck. I'm going against rise mid. Fuck dude. It's over.
I'm going to lose. Not from the music. All right. First of all, do this first.
I had it. Then it's like here and then like dip. And then I did this. I think that's what I did.
Did I not do it like that? That was a career ending joke. I've done like a thousand of those.
So I don't think so. I wish I could draw more than once and not have everything just start to move
when I'm done painting. I wish it was a button I could press that was like, okay, start the physics
now. I don't care. You can't have everything. Have your brother Dave do it for you. I would bet
that half of you guys wouldn't be able to do even a third of the ones that I'm doing. Is that,
do you think that's correct? I would bet that. I bet a third of the people there probably couldn't
do even half of these. What do you think? Are this a third? Do you think 30% of 20,000 people?
Probably a few thousand, right? And who cares? All right. Let's release. Let's do that. I got
an idea already. You know what's going on. He's free. Okay. Let's put on pizza. Pizza.
Pizza tower. Why not? Hook the balloon on the dot. Hmm. Well, how the heck do I do that?
This is a great soundtrack. Yeah, there it is. Turn it up. It can be kind of low.
Doesn't have to be super loud. What the hell is that? I lost everything. I lost my chat.
There we go. Does anybody know how to turn off that feature of windows, which I don't,
I don't understand why it was ever implemented. You ever have like, I've got like eight windows open
and then like I for some reason clicked and dragged and moved to a spot on one of the monitors
that just minimizes every fucking single window. What, what were they doing when they made that a
thing? Oh, Hey, I'm just like moving a wind. I'm moving one of my windows. Uh, maybe a little too
close to the stop. Just minimize every single window you were working on. Oh, this is a good
idea. No, I didn't want to let go. Whoops. I've skirted out. I want to freeze it here because
when I let go, it's just everything falls. Actually, this is probably the way to do it.
Now I have to turn it on first. Why would you get stuck here? Of all places, you were just moving
up the line. What stopped you? That, well, I thought, okay, it has to stay on there. Oh,
this is going to be fucking hard. This actually will be very difficult. Oh man. Okay. How tall is
this? I'm trying to make it so it doesn't fly away. Okay. Can I do anything now that I did this? The
hook has collision. I mean, the goal now is I'm trying to like that. Oh, do it already. It's too
low. I think it should get it right there. Latch, latch. Oh, no, it's too low. You're right. Damn it.
Okay. All right. We're good. Now I got to figure out how to just knock it this way. You fucking
idiot. You idiot. You idiot. I've uninstalled games for fewer less than this. That's why I
want to let you know. It's in the right spot. Should I just like make a, just go like this
and like drag it this way? No. Wait, it's going, it's going. Shit. It's right here. Come on. Oh my
God. Fucking asshole. Get on there. Dude, I look, there is plenty of space. This is absolute
bullshit. Why can I not draw here? It's fucking me up. Big time. I'm going to get this. It's so
close. It's right here. This hurts to watch. This hurts to play. Just in case you're wondering.
Shit. No, I want it to stay there. Actually might work out. You can solve this with one line.
You're talking about like, do this. You have to activate it and then go like this. So it floats
over and gets hooked on it. But the problem is the balloon doesn't want to move anymore.
Do a ramp with a hook. Have it go through the string. I mean like this. So we'll drag it up.
No. Stir beat every level. You're going to let him win. Stir did not beat 1200 levels.
I stir probably played this for 20 minutes and then just left and moved on. I'm going to duck.
All that matters. I don't care. Oh, that moves. Okay. Hold on. I quit. I'm taking the IQ test
instead. Use the mouse to draw shapes. Click on the, don't judge me based on what you're about to
see because it's not fair. It's actually completely, it's going to be completely unfair. Okay. Click
on the IQ icon for a comprehensive diagnosis. It is recommended that as many of the 20 tasks
be completed as possible. Okay. All right. Put your drawing into the beaker. You cannot draw
in the blue area. Okay. So we're going to make a, we're going to make like a bridge. Oh, I was
trying to, can I restart it? Cause I was trying, I was, I was, I was trying to make it. I, this is
why I want, I wish I could just fucking like, you know what I was trying to do here? That's what I
was trying to do, but like I, it fucked up. Get in there. All right. There it is. I, I, this should
have been two tries. Make the red ball touch the red area. Let me think about this for a second
before everybody screams. You got an 80. That's 80 IQ. No, no, that's, we have to wait for the
assessment. By the way, you're taking time away from my IQ test. I need to touch the red area.
Okay. Oh, I thought this thing just saying I was an idiot. All right. So let's think about it.
I'm going to have to knock this forward. It is not to go in here. It's to go here. So let's start
by going like this. It's got to be steep enough where it can make it like that. Okay. I also need
to go. I need a ramp here. So it goes, I think that should do it. Like, you know what I was going for
that is my, is my IQ bad because drawing with a mouse sucks. No, that's not intelligence. That's
drawing with a mouse sucks. You might get there. You've had practice though, two hours of practice.
You need to do 10,000 hours of something to be a fucking good at it. I'm not even close to being
there. Here we go. How was that better than the first one? Draw something and touch the red area.
Okay. So it's got a drop over here. So it's going to make a, like a little tower, right? There we go.
What's that? 130 IQ. What's yours? Make the red square touch the left wall. Come on. I didn't mean
to do that. I, how do I, that's what the fulcrum was. I would have had it this one. I'm going to
get like two IQ on this one. I didn't, why did I even make that thing? Fucking smash this thing.
Push it all the way. Come on. What did I get? That's fine. I'm not doing my IQ assessment yet.
Go already. I did this one first try before. Shit. 130. Red ball, touch the red area. Watch this.
First try. Whoa. I forgot that it doesn't stay. That's my fault for not remembering. I think I
still might be all right. Play Street Fighter. Um, no, I fucked it up. That's too big. That's
got to be it. Hey, 110 IQ. Get out of here. Draw something and touch the red area. Oh,
I see what's going on here. Uh, I don't got it. Oh, not like this. What do you think I was doing?
I made the T specifically for that. Have only one snowflake in the container. Um, we, I didn't know
that's what you, whoa. I think I just got it. Oh, come on. Get over there. Oh, 170 IQ. Lower the
coat hanger. Retry. Where are the fulcrums? I don't need them right now. I'm fine as we are.
Lower the coat hanger. All right. So I wanted, I needed to spin this way. I got an idea. Really?
The momentum is not going to work. I think I hate him. You wouldn't do this in the, you would not
do this in the amount of time I'm doing it. You wouldn't do this. You wouldn't do this in the same
amount of time. You wouldn't do it. You wouldn't be able to do it in the same amount of time.
You wouldn't do it. You wouldn't be able to do it. Get off, dude. Are you kidding me?
There are engineers and architects in chat. Unlatch it. That's technically unlatched.
There it is. There actually might be. That was 130. That one was a hard one.
The yellow ball will start moving when something touches it. Put the balls in the cup.
Salvageable. Oh my God. What the fuck? Are you trolling, dude? I don't, do you really think I
would be able to do that if I tried? If I really tried, do you think I would be able to put pixel
perfect capture that ball where it was? Stop trolling, dude. Two lines, dude. I'm begging you.
I got it right here. See, I didn't know. Okay. I didn't know they had collision. I thought that
they could go through each other. I did it. And that one was a hundred IQ. So I'll take the
complaints. Throw Alex up 10 meters. I know how to do that. I did it accidentally like five times
already. I guess that's 25 meters. I got, that's not even 20 IQ. What? How was it? That's a worse
one so far. Take the ball out. Play new music. The music's playing right now. You can definitely
hear it. I'm almost done with my IQ test. This will be it right here. 120. Almost done. Don't
let the cup touch the ground. What cup? Don't let the cup touch the ground. Oh, I have to turn this
up. Okay.
Let's go. Come on. Does that work? There it is. Make the beaker touch the red area. You know what
we're doing. You know what we're doing. You ready? Shit. Oh, he's fucking laughing. That's like,
dude, your fulcrum sucks. Hey, leave my fulcrum alone. There we go. This is it. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, come on. Really? Oh, 40, 40. This thing is heavy. This thing is heavy.
Bang. Got to place the ball on the other side of the. Okay. Check this out.
I have to like whack it over there. You're the most interesting mind in the world.
I have to whack it through here. You need a fucking fulcrum already.
Don't tell me when I do and do not need to fulcrum. Hey, this is a conversation between
A and B you're talking. Seize the next letter and fucking get out of here.
You know what I'm saying? I keep winning apparently. What do I keep winning? Okay.
I don't know what I'm doing. I don't know what I'm doing this for.
I was trying to make a ceiling to fuck. I don't know why I made this.
Ceiling for what? So it didn't launch? I don't know. To guide it.
You literally had the idea. The right idea for the wrong side.
I get a good fulcrum here. Why do you keep doing that? I don't know how you get this ball to go
in this hole. You know, it would be okay. Let it do it. Go. It's the line's too thick. I mean,
I don't know. I have to like get it to hit this way. How big does this gotta be better than that?
Catapult, catapult, catapult. Yeah, I know. So it has to be launched from this side.
But how the fuck? You can make it with one line. The line is the fulcrum.
Don't let these clowns bully you. Just do your best.
If they were still VIPs, I would VIP you for five. You know what I mean? All right.
So it needs to, the ball needs to fall here and needs to launch from this side that way.
That's gonna be such a, this is gonna be impossible. Just make a half pipe.
That didn't even want it to go that way. I don't think this is ever gonna work like this.
Maybe like support beams. I'll just make a hook at some point, right? Oh, what? That actually kind of
worked. Fall that way. The weight is on the right side. There's no weight over here. Look at how
heavy this fucking thing is. I don't know anything about leverage. Because I don't even know how to
change a tire. I have no idea how to do that. Guess what? None of you do either. None of us do.
It's a, that's a big problem, isn't it? The best part about this is if I can't do something,
just say everybody else can either. That's how I get, how I feel better. This is the kind of
shit that you go to like school for eight years to do all this. So you can fucking figure out this
puzzle correctly. It's closer. How is this not weigh so much more? Like the weight thing,
I don't understand. I made a ball and it does, it's not heavy. This ball is fucking massive.
How is this not pulling down so hard? Get in there. Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
I can bump it in there, can't I? Yes. Make the ball touch the left wall. Uh, okay. Seems kind
of easy. Thought this would be kind of a hard one. Okay. Hold on. So I have to touch this. I guess I
could just touch it with something that never hits the ground over here. So I go like this,
but it's not like this is going to be a big, right? Like who cares? Well, I had it just hook this,
have it go like this. Is it going to stand? All right. Wait a second. What are you doing?
I'm listening to pizza tower. What happens if I fill this? What will this do? I just want to see
what happens. Okay. So you're only 18 in, in three and a half hours, bro. This is like the
fourth game mode I've played. You got to go back and watch the fog. Okay. Hold on a second.
How's this for some fucking IQ? How's that for a little bit of IQ? How's that going to work?
Two more. That did not work. I forgot it falls. Um, I have to like, okay. So here's the weird part.
I have to activate it first because it won't pull it when I, uh, I have to turn it on first.
I can do that. I mean, could I effectively just put balls in here and pump it that way? Okay. So
I got an idea. We're just, we're just hooking for a second. Hold on. I said that needs to go the
other way. Okay. Got to go all the way around. Boom. Shit. Right idea, but the wrong placement.
I almost think I could make a ramp. I go, what if I go like this and then what if I go like that
then like this? Nevermind. Actually might help. Hold on a minute. Not at all. So how do I get
this to spin completely almost 180 degrees this way or this way? Well, I can't, it's not going
to be able to ever go this way. So it has to go flip to the left. It has to wait a minute. Okay.
Hold on. Okay. That's kind of cheating, but that kind of works. Oh, we're almost there. Look now.
I just have to go like that and it's gotta be like harsher. It's gotta be like a sharp point,
maybe lower. There it is. Let's knock it this way and I'm done. It'll bounce back. It'll bounce back.
Ah, all right. Now we just wait. He didn't read chat. Surely the chat, but I was just talking to
my mom. I know this is bad. This is salvageable. Okay. Now we just have to pull it back this way
and it should be good. You know what we're doing. It's definitely high enough where I can. No,
I can't. All right. Now cut the shit and just move it. Just pull it this way. Grab this and hook it
over here. Finally. Now just move that. Oh, this'll do it. All right. This is the last one. And then
we'll see what my actual IQ is. Wolfram Frank. This is it. This is going to be it right here.
Check it out. This is it. Just flip it. That's what I was trying to do.
I think it's close enough. There it is. All right. Let's go. So I'm there. I'm right there.
This is an AI learning program. Yeah. And guess what? That AI does this shit like 50 million times
before it understands it. Dude, you're poisoning the data right now. I'm fine. I just, I don't,
I don't know. Anytime, anytime the word pulley lever or hook is in the conversation,
I'm talking about Star Wars with three or four other people in the room. You know what I'm saying?
Like I very much enjoy gardening. You know what I mean? I like a garden. I can tell you about
gardening. Fertilize, how to fertilize. Well, I don't, I don't know about pulleys. I don't know
about weight distributions, forklift things. I don't know that. That's a skill. That's a skill.
That's a really, that's a skill that you have to learn. What is the perfect pH value in water
for cannabis plants? I don't grow cannabis, but I can't answer that question. Nice. Gotcha though.
All right. We're doing it my way. I really expect us to believe you just grow in sunflowers and
never delved into the devil's plant. Um, I like marijuana. I don't grow marijuana. How do I,
how do I get out of here? How do I figure this out? I can't figure out how to do all the shit to
twist and pull and grab and what about like this? This is stupid. It's like a dumb idea.
What if I just do this and then drop a ball here and just flip it? Does that work? It grips it
correctly. Theoretically should. I think radically. My hypothesis is this looks like it's going pretty
well. Okay. Deduction. Deduced. Pick it up with your hand. Let's do some sess with focrums. Um,
I did this one before. I don't, it's like grabbing it, having it be like up, left,
down, up, weight, counterweight, counterweight this way. No, I don't, I don't, I have no idea.
I just want to just tip it, but it won't do it because I'm trying to make a hook,
but eventually it's too big because I can only draw a certain size. All right. Well, hold on.
Is it now possible for me to pull this and I just whack this now? This is it. This has to be it.
Everybody say a prayer because this is it. This is question 20. Fuck you. Ha, you can't make it
small enough for it to dip. Dip the shit. I didn't, I didn't even mean to do it, but I just solved it.
I just made a makeshift fulcrum. I didn't even mean to solve it. I don't know. Okay. What about
this? Like, no, I wish I could just change how big the painter is. All right. What the fuck?
Why is your chat so toxic? Um, I don't, are you guys toxic? Yes or no. This is a yes or no question.
Are you guys toxic? Yes or no. And I want you to be honest.
Knows you saying yes. Work on that. Work on that. I ain't going to say it again. Work on that.
It kind of looks like a nose. Okay. So what a big stick in a box at the end.
That might work. Work on being even more toxic. Now you got me angry. I've been hanging out,
just chilling, playing this game. Now you've really, really pissed me off. Are you ready?
I'm going to beat this on the next try because of that. I just, I just don't get it. I know a lot of
people will probably get it. And they're like, dude, I get it. I don't get it. I would get it
if I could shrink the paint brush. I don't get it. Have you seen the new butt hole emoji? No,
I haven't. I hope it makes you happy. You do you. How do I do this? Actually, I'm like completely
stumped. I don't, I don't, I don't get how you can make a hook that can pull it down without
hitting the ground and have it go all the way over. I guess that's kind of correct. Maybe just
hold on and try that again. It's too big. Everything's too big. I can't make it smaller.
If I could make the hook part smaller, it's kind of correct. What if I, is this a stupid idea?
Kind of. Go the other way with the weight facing the other side. I don't know how far out I should
go. How far should I do it? Oh, that's kind of an idea. It's not a bad idea. I think I'll get it
doing this. Is that enough space? Oh, it's almost like it needs that gap there. It's close. It's so
close, but it's not going to do it. Can I just bump it? I'm going back to this. This is like a brace
for it and then maybe it'll just flip over. Wait, fulcrum, left side fulcrum. I need to lift the
left one. What if I do it thin? Look at how thin that is. All right. All right. You got a thin crust
or thicker crust for pizza. Get them distracted so they stop, you know, making fun of me.
Okay. And now let's really get at some momentum. Go. Oh my God. There it is. I don't want to freak
out, but I think I'm in trouble. I kind of need to hit it again. Yes. It was correct. All right.
It's time to get the results. My IQ is, you ready? What's the song I need? What's this? What's the
song? I'm going to drag this out. What's the song when Saitama is going to punch somebody
in One Punch Man and it goes,
what's it called? I'm going to do the thing where I play an epic song and reveal it. What's it called?
Saitama's theme. Is this it? I don't hear anything. I don't hear it. I don't hear anything.
That's weird. Do you think it's over or under a hundred? Oh, there we go. Now I can hear.
All right. Is it over or under a hundred? You guys ready? Here comes the epic thing.
So I took an IQ test today and it made me understand that it doesn't matter if you're good
at puzzles. It doesn't matter if you can dodge a battle X. It doesn't matter if you can fight
anybody. We're all strong inside. We all have what it takes. Whatever is underneath this,
it doesn't matter what it is. It could be 50. It could be a hundred. It could be 150,
which would make me better than all of you. Way better. But even if it does say that,
it could be 20, but it's not going to be. It's time to reveal the IQ. And again,
don't be discouraged when you see this number. Really? All right. I'll take it.
That's better than average. Nice radio station. That's my name. Well, it was under a hundred.
Oh, I did. You guys didn't. Oh, okay. Oh, shit. All right. But, uh, okay. Here we go.
I wanted this one. Is this this one? There it is. All right. So that's nine, nine, eight, five.
Cool. That was fun. So what efficiency? That's okay. Let's go over it. Comprehension.
The ability to understand where to apply force to control the position and angle of an object.
I know how to fucking punch really, really fucking hard. You understand? Insight. Wise
enough to see that it is actually simple. That's all right. That's fine. I just like choked.
Inspiration. Eye-opening thinking. That's all right. Aggressive sensations that generate
large movements with strong force. Efficiency. The shrewdness of having multiple functions in
one object. You give me a stick and that's that I use that stick to swing at people
in the caveman lands. I'm not going to make it a tool, but I'll tell you,
I can comprehend what I can comprehend a stick. It's so funny. All right. I'm right at the top
of the curve. This is normal. This is normal. Humans are here. Okay. I'm very, it's average.
I never told you I was a super intelligent person. I mean, I feel like I think it used to be over.
This is not a real IQ test. Why am I acting like it is? The number is your username. Yeah.
German985. You're one point below average. Whatever. You said it was going to be higher
than all of us. Don't be discouraged. I'm 128. No, that's good. 130 is better, but 28 is all right.
I want to see a couple other things though. That chatter is a genius. All right. What is this?
The blue ball will shrink when touched. Make it go touch the ground. That's when you have 100 IQ.
That's how you figure it out real fast. Make them fit. We need some more music. Man, I love that
Saitama song. Don't you? I don't even like, you know what I mean? Oh, you know what I mean, Vern?
Don't bat-chest me. No, actually don't bat-chest me. That song is great. That's an amazingly composed
song. The composition in that. I know composition. You just saw that I do. It's phenomenally crafted.
I know how to crap things. All right. So you got to go quick. I need a new OST. Did you put your IQ
in your username? That's cringe. German98.5. Ocarina of Time. I did say I was going to do
Animal Crossing. That's right. You guys having fun? You having fun? Hey, you having a good time?
How did that not fit? That was a bug. I like this one. Orange objects will disappear when touched.
Make the balloon touch the left wall. Come on. IQ under pressure is probably a lot different than
sitting quietly in a testing room by yourself. Yeah. Water balloon. Put every drop in the beaker.
Ah, interesting. Interesting. Interesting. Nice. Where's my water level? That's an old one. That's
a really old one. Do you know what's crazy about iPad games and mobile games now? I don't know if
they were like this before. Holy shit. If you go to the, what the app is tracking and the privacy
stuff that Apple has in the Apple store, it is unbelievable. What you need to know about me,
for me to play your match three video game. It's fucked. I remember looking at one. It was like,
oh, like, I don't want to say a wrong game, but one of them wanted, it was going to like email,
like location, precise location, purchase ID, device ID. It was literally every single possible
thing. Every single possible thing. It was just like, why do you need all this information? And
sometimes you'll go to one, it'd be on the app store and you're like, all right, what do they
want from me now? Let me guess. You want like my fucking credit card number and everything. You
want to know like who I am and everything about me. And then you scroll down. It's like this app
does not collect any information. Sometimes I just buy those. Sometimes I just buy them. I just buy
them because like, yup, you're, I get you. And you're fucking, you thank you. Billionaire,
millionaire rich. I mean, a lot of these are like $2 guys. And I play them. If I'm
on the fence for a mobile game and mobile game developers, I'm talking to you directly.
If I'm on the fence about a mobile game, if I'm looking at it like, hmm, all right, this is like,
this is like two, three bucks. Okay. Well, this is like a game. I go right down there and I go,
you taking anything? If the answer is no, I'm not on the fence anymore. I'm going to try it out.
I'm going to check it out. I'm talking to you. What about that family guy game? I don't know.
That was like, it was like eight years ago. I don't know. I have no idea. This feature
wasn't available in like iOS two or whatever it was. And, and also sometimes you go to that,
the privacy thing and it's like, oh yeah, it's collecting, you know, like device information.
Okay. Like you, you know, bugs and stuff. All right. We need to know what kind of device this
is to make sure I'm all right with that. I'm okay with device kind of information. That's fine.
That is fine. But once it's like, Hey, um, what are your emails? I don't, what are you,
what are you talking about? Oh, that was close. Oh, that's close. I like in behind the knee
and then right there. And then a little bit of fulcrum action and let's go for it. I actually
just hit my hands on my thing. Don't do it. You have a home alone IQ. What does that? I,
what does that mean? I think I know what that means. That means that like in a scenario where
I'm going to be dropping paint cans on strings to hitch people in the face. Is that what you mean?
Like that's what I can do when it comes to deducing problems. Hey, Jerma, we have this
complicated problem that we need to, uh, uh, for, you know, customer information and, uh,
can you give us a hand here? Yeah. How about you put some paint cans on some string and then when
they walk in, you let go of the paint can holding it in a pendulum fashion and it'll break their
nose and shatter their fucking face. Well, this is a, this is a marketing call in which
I was trying to figure out marketing stuff. Oh, just call me when you need me. The home alone
movies are some of my favorite movies ever as one of the specific reasons why is because it lives
in a cartoon world, but it's supposed to be like real life Chicago. If you took a paint can to the
face, you might die. It might kill you. The, the second that one of those dudes falls down the
stairs and there's like nails sticking out. They're dead. I do love, uh, the Joe Pesci psych.
Nobody does that anymore. When was the last time you heard of razza frazza?
They don't do it anymore. Oh, there's also the, yeah, this is one of my favorite parts of the
movie. Marv literally throws a brick at this kid. Like he's trying to hit this kid with a brick
and like he's trying to, it's, it's, it's unbelievably throws it as hard as he can.
The brick is going very fast. I, that's one of my favorite scenes. That was quick. They're
legitimately trying to kill him in that movie. They really are. How do, how do we do this?
You need to touch the bottom one. Well, Oh, look at that. Hey, I know what we got to do.
What are your thoughts on cheddar checks? I'm going to have to recommend you a far superior
product. The far superior product is the cheese it mix. The cheese it mix is the best one of all.
The cheese it mix is cheez-its, which are phenomenal. They're pretzels, which are phenomenal.
It's the little breads, which are phenomenal. And it's the little white puffs, which are phenomenal.
Ain't no bullshit in there that you want. There's nothing you're going to skip over there.
It's only the best part of every single mixed, uh, snack mix up thing. And it's got a lot of
little breads in there. You just know complaints when you take a handful because sometimes you
don't, the checks ones are fine, but sometimes I get to the point where there's kind of too
many checks left and I don't really want to eat checks anymore. That does not happen at all when
eating the cheese it one. So that answers your question. What the fuck? Really? What is going
on here? What is happening? Oh, I get it. I need to like swing it. How am I going to do that? I
got to yank it. Wait, what if I do this? This might be kind of weird. Leave only one. That's easy.
Make the ball touch all the red area. That ball? Shoot. I'm sorry. Yeah. Uh, I don't know. All I
know how to do is make seesaws and fulcrums and hooks that don't work. Make a hammer and have a
pivot around the center. Is it? Oh, I did it. Yes. New quest. Let me tell you something.
Quasimodo. Quasimodo. No, you should not. Don't ever feel like you can't talk to me. Quasimodo.
Keep your drawing in the red area. Three, two, three, two, one. Put all the blue balls in the
beaker. I think I can handle that. I think I can handle it. Quasimodo. We get it. You watched that
movie like a week ago. Yeah. So what? Can you please say stones the way that you do? I don't
know. How many subs came in today? The stones. What the fuck did I think that was going to do?
It kind of worked. Yay. The springs actually do that? Can I make these? Make all the yellow
balls touch the red area. Ooh. Well, uh, how do I do this? It's time for a fulcrum. It might be.
I think you're right. I don't know how to do this. Make the ball touch the ground.
Just fill it with packing peanuts. Son of a gun. I think you're onto something. Yeah.
Make the balloon touch the left wall. How is this going to get through? How the fuck is this going
to get through? I mean, can the ball even fit through there? Put all the red balls in the box.
It's an easy task. Just got to get a little bit of wedge action in here. Make the balloon touch
the left wall. Wait, I have to pop that. How am I going to pop this? Oh, I know. Displacement.
Fucking touch it already. Touch it. It was never going to work, was it? Maybe it will. Oh, wait a
minute. Okay. I can do it with displacement. What are you? What? Touch that wall. Oh, I didn't think
about what I was doing. It's all right. I'll get it with displacement. Shit. All right. Just touch
the left wall. Hurry up. Touch the wall. This shit is fucking hard. It's just like, it makes me want
to just get up and run a lap. I just want to get up and run a lap. I just need to move. You know,
do you know what I mean? You know what I'm saying? You know what I mean, Vern? I said that like
thousand times tonight. Got it. Got it. Put more than five blue balls in the beaker. Oh, displacement.
How would you ever make this work? How would I scoop? Make a spoon? That's not how a spoon goes.
I don't. I mean, how do I make it scoop? Like, how? How would I make it? All it does is fall down.
How do I? How the hell do I make a wedge? Make it pointing down. I don't. I love his brain. Just
make it straight like just like a knife just falling straight down the middle. But how am
I going to scoop them into the thing? That doesn't help me at all. More than five, by the way. I don't
think that's going to happen. Where is it? Remember how a shovel works? Yes. A shovel works by me
digging down and then lifting up. All I can do is let go of the shovel in my hands and drop it on
the ground. See what I'm saying? So here's your shovel. These are my fingers grabbing it, right?
So I'm grabbing onto the shovel here, my arms, and this is we're not going to finish that drawing.
Oh, that's one too. I think I can just do it. I'll just get it. Ready? We're just driving a nail
into this. Put one of the balls on the ground. That's fun. What was this one? No, OK, I did a
lot of these already. What about this one? Touch all the orange balls. The orange balls will explode
when touched. Why would you do it any other way? Make the red bar touch the ground. This is going
to be really hard. Oh, still possible. That right side. Get in there. It's right there.
Yeah, that's annoying. It might wedge in. This is my like, how annoying can I be in one day stream?
We're getting our limit. OK, I think I can just drop it from here. Just don't get rid of area.
Why would I get rid of everything though? Make the red ball touch the red area. This is moving.
It's not something weird. Like, hold on. I just want to see what happens. Oh, I can't even. Wait,
what? Oh, I see. OK, you have to blow into your mic for this one. It's interactive. What was that
on the DS? DS game. Um, I think I'm just going to make a big one. Does that work? Oh, keep going.
There it is. Oh, no, it's not. Oh, keep going. Keep going. It's almost there. There it is. Yes.
Oh, OK, this shouldn't be that bad. It's not that bad. And I've even made him do a front flip.
Uh, what? Come on, do it. That should be good. Uh, no, just a little too much. I think I got to
queue another one up. Yep. Just like that. Got to do one and then drop this one from a little bit
higher. Uh, I can't draw in this circle. So for when yelling at me. I just had it too. One chat
never got in my head. I just beat it. Why did I let it go? Really stopped it perfectly in his foot.
All right, don't move. Very nice. Very nice. Make the red areas touch each other. My goodness. This
kind of hurts my head. Make all the red squares fly out of the screen. Drop some big balls on it.
I think that's probably correct. What else we got? Did this one? Did that one? Make the rabbit touch
the flag. It's slippery. That'll be enough. Is it too much? Just a little. How gentle do I have to
be? OK, it'll get there. Let's give it a second. Move the red thing into the screen. Move the
red thing into the screen. Wait, I got an idea. Well, that was bad, but whatever. It was bad. OK,
I'll get it right. All right. Inched out a little. Come on. Yep. Oh, I blocked it. Pull it? Like,
I don't know. What am I supposed to pinch it out? Does that help? Way too far. You know what I'm
doing. Let's fucking go. Oh, almost worked. Almost worked. You know what I'm doing. Going for it again.
Would you guys allow me one more Quasimodo? Can I do one more? Can we do a poll, please? Can I say
Quasimodo as that character one more time? Let's do a poll. It's going to work. It's your stream,
man. Quasimodo. I don't know. I can't grip it, though. That's not a bad idea. Wait a minute.
We'll use displacement. Yes, 83% said I could do it again. Yeah, I'm not very good at this.
It's OK, though. I'm just having fun. You mean like this part here? That's actually, if that's
what you mean, then that's definitely a great idea. Can I weigh in the end down? Can I weigh it down?
I think it's too heavy. Grab top and slide to lock it in. I don't know. I don't know how you
do a pulling action. I don't know. Someone's smart to figure it out. Pour it out. Oh, I did it.
I did it. I did it. I kind of did it. I did it. Did I do it? Did I do it? Didn't do it. I had a
lot of momentum on it. Just rip it down. No. All right, now get out of the way. That was perfect.
Oh, more. That has to be it. I don't think so. It went back in. Yeah, I wish we'd just stop moving.
It's hard to actually hook onto it. All right, now it's coming out, but now it's going back.
No, there it is. God damn it. Does this have to be longer maybe? I don't know how much longer
I'd want to make it till I pull it there, like pull it back. Oh, yes. All right, now keep going,
please. Come on, do it. No, it got to the end and screwed up. Oh, don't do this to me right now,
please. Oh, my God. What is even happening right now? Wouldn't it have to go out this way?
You have to get it to go on its own. I think that will weigh it down enough and then fall off and
then fall off and then fall off. All right, it fell off. Fall off. All right, now do it naturally.
There it is. Get it out. Should be perfect now. It's look at it. And then look, it bugged out again.
No, I think it's good. Good. Almost. No shit. What the hell's going on here?
Fuck. It's too wide. I don't want to make it this wide. Can I pull it down? Spin it. A physics
puzzle where the physics fall out of the hole. All right, so the thing's going and then it just
like detaches. Like, why does it pull out and start going in a random direction? What just happened?
Like, I'm not even allowed to do what I just did and I just did it. All right, start. All right,
it's going to have momentum. Right, go. All right, now can I stop it? It's still kind of going.
See, it's all fucked up again. What's happening here? What is going on? Shouldn't it be going like
this still? Like, how would it be stuck here? Like, falling out of the back? Why does it
keep doing that? So what's the play here? I don't get it. Hook it again. I'm blocking it now. It
doesn't weigh enough to keep going. Can I just try to, I don't know, just pull it off. Push it
out with balls. I don't want to get any stuck in here. I feel like it's so close. I just want to
drag it off. I guess I could go like this. Can I like just pull it down from here? There it is.
And that should be, ah, all right. We're getting there. We're getting somewhere. We're getting
somewhere. I'm afraid to hook it, but I'm gonna. All right, we're, oh, is it in the perfect spot
to just fucking ruin everything? Come on, dude. Really? No, it's not. You hooked it too deep.
I think I can still do it though. Hold on. I think I can do it if I go like this and just have it
drag it a little. I'm going to grab the whole thing and like spin it. Do it. No, it's happening.
Pull it down. Pull it down. You can do it. I, it's not over. It's not over yet. This just needs to
a little bit more weight has to be up here. I'm going to wait till it gets to here and then let
it go. I'm going the other way. Okay. All right. There's a little bit of progress. At least I moved
it. Drag it down with my last try and I'm done. Okay. That was a good pull. Very good. That was
a great start. Okay. And now what do I do? Good start. Phenomenal start. I'm just going to pull
it down like this. I'm not putting anything in there yet. I'm so afraid to hook this wrong.
Do an L. You mean, okay. So you mean like this, like that, like that hook with L do a seven hook
hook an L and L will fall. Yeah. No, no, no. Go all the way, please. Okay. It's almost there.
I'm so scared to fuck this up. Oh, it's so close. That's it right there. I went. Yep. There it is.
Thank God. Roll the thing out to the left side. Roll the thing out to the left side. I don't get
it. I'm so glad that that went completely off screen. I don't even know what it was. I got it.
Okay. So I just got to pull it now. How can I pull it from here? I have an idea. See if it works.
You got to pull it off screen. Come on. Crunch it. Oh, yanked. Uh oh. What was wrong with that?
How did I not yank it? Let's pull it all the way to the left. All right. This is the last one.
And I'm going to call it for tonight. This game is fun though. If you're, if you have a brain
and it works and you have it, I would say at least like, you know, like a seventh grade education,
you'd probably have a good time playing it. I wonder should it be bigger here in the middle?
Oh, I'll do. I'll try the hell levels. That's a good idea. It didn't even grip. I wish there
was a fill tool. I would use it right now. Oh, I got it. I got it. Um, pull it down. How far?
Wow. How big is this thing? I yanked it. It's a, it's a, I won. Keep going. We'll get it already.
I wonder if it's stuck more at the top. I just dragged it more ramp. I don't think I can get it.
Inch it in the middle. I don't think I can. All right. I'm done. Wait, look at how many levels
there are. This is ridiculous. Let the red ball touch the ground. Okay. I can't make anything up
there. Can't make anything down here. I have an idea. I'm curious. It's too bouncy. Jeremy,
you're crazy, dude. Uh, I'm all right. Okay. All right. So I effectively made a exit to have a new
idea. Okay. It doesn't weigh enough. I apologize. I looked up the IQ 130 speed run record and it's
all hooks with balls attached to them. I should have not slandered you. Thank you. I really
appreciate it. Okay. This one's crazy. Keep 10 or more drawing objects on the screen. Uh, what?
10 or more objects? I guess like the only way to do this is to click a million times. All right.
God. You have to move the, I can't do it in the same spot. It's, it's too hard because you have
to move the mouse too. That's fucking impossible. Hold on. Let me get in the right mindset here.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna take the music out. I'm just gonna go. I'm in like a shitty position
here. I need to like be, I need to get leverage on them on the ground. I almost had it. It's just,
it's the, it's having to drag the mouse too. It's like fucking impossible. Hold on. Oh,
let's go. I get it. How many is that? This is actually really fucking hard. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight. Okay. This is good. This is a good way to do it. This is,
how many is that? One, two, three, four, five, six. No, hold on. I gotta get like five or six
out. Shit. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Hey, fucking hand hurts.
Why did I do it the other way? My whole body hurts now. Okay. That's one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine. Aye. Game is like crashing. Look at us. Something's wrong. Hold on.
Oh shit. I can't. It hurts. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10. Aye. Go left and right instead of, that's a good idea. Nine every time. Fuck you. Damn it.
I can't. It's so hard. It just like hurts to do. Where's the actual game area? Okay. Like look at
this. Not even the right area. I can't click up here. Stupid. Two, three, four, five, six. That's
10 objects on the screen. Where's the, what are you talking about? One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine. This is 10, right? No, it's not. You gotta be fucking kidding me. No,
the lag just ruined everything. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. You gotta be
fucking kidding me, dude. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. I got five here.
Six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Holy shit. This is a good one. Look at this idea. Watch this idea.
Watch this shit. Ready? This is the one right here. Guaranteed. It's coming. You know it is.
That's it right here. What? It's a finicky fucking game. Okay. It's finicky. I'm gonna fucking eat
my hand in a second. Oh my God. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. I'm going to
bite my fingernails. I did it. All right. I'll see you guys later. That was fun. That was crazy.
All right, guys. See you soon. I will see you guys in a couple days. Friday. We'll do Friday.
Maybe Friday, Saturday. Friday, Saturday. Friday, Sunday. Thanks for hanging out. The game, by the
way, is called Cue Remastered, if you're wondering. Play this again sometime. I think I've gotten out
of all the beginner and intermediate levels to a point where you actually have to really, really
be very intricate. You can't just draw hooks and seesaws anymore, but it's fun. It's a cool game.
I like it a lot. It's a good idea. I had fun with it. Multiplayer would be cool with this. It would be.
Yeah. I'll see you guys Friday at four o'clock. Pacific. That's the next time I plan on streaming.
Keep an eye on the sus. Thanks for watching. Anything else I wanted to talk about today?
I don't think so. Are you going to show the video that you're working on when it's done?
Yeah. I'm working on a video. You'll see it. It's not a big deal. It really isn't. It's just a
stupid... This video is probably going to be like seven minutes long. It's like a six to eight minute
video, but I need to make sure I'm in the right mindset because it's going to be... It's one of
my favorite videos. Is it going to go on the main channel, German985? It'd be kind of funny if this
was the video that I uploaded and you'll see why when you see it. Because if you don't know that
I moved over to Twitch pretty much permanently, if you don't know that and you just thought I
disappeared, you're going to think I sold the channel because this video would just... I mean,
it's going to be me in it. I'm going to be talking, but you're going to think that I sold the channel.
Like, there's going to be no way. It's going to be so jarring for so many people. I can't... Actually,
maybe I will just do it. It'll be funny. Yeah. Yeah. You'll see it. You'll see it. It's coming
out in about two weeks. Maybe earlier. It depends if I really just want to go for it.
All right. Good night. Goodbye. See you soon. Thanks for watching. Thanks for hanging out,
obviously. Have a great night. Call your mother. See you soon. See you Friday. Four o'clock Pacific.
Have a great night, everybody. See you soon. Okay. Hold on. Somebody said,
can you please confirm that it's not another Spider-Man update video? No, it is not. This is a
video. This is a real video. It's not a Spider-Man update video. Good guess, though, because that
would have been a really good guess. All right. See you later. Somebody said,
Jeremy, I know you're still here reading chat. Yeah. Yeah, I am. Usually do until the video turns
off. I see the shit, you guys, right? I'm watching. All right. Goodbye. Hey, it's me again. I'm really
trying to get this to end at five, five, five, five, five. Five hours, 55 minutes, 55 seconds.
See if I can get it. You guys remember that? I would... All right. I have 10 seconds to say this.
Do you guys remember, like, seven years ago, I used to end a bunch of my streams with me
just screaming and then hitting end stream? That was like a joke for a while. All right.