So why can't I say names?
I thought there were like 50 characters in this game.
I don't know, I thought so too.
But apparently there's only four.
Oh, well.
Alright.
There's 20 characters in the game.
Just go to random locations. Doesn't really fucking matter.
Like, let's just play the game.
Alright, let's go.
Oh, look out, it's a spooky statue.
Okay, so Jerma is the red vest.
I hear static.
Yeah, there's a tape.
Oh, get that tape.
Alright, we got it.
Is that something back there?
Can you guys see that? No, that's just like a tree.
So the closer you get
to the cassette tapes, they start buzzing
and making noise and stuff so you can find them.
I feel like Stealth, is this you? This looks like you.
That's not me.
That looks like Bizarro
MLC Stealth.
Turn around, turn around, run, run, run.
He's right behind us. He's literally right behind us.
There's this giant monster running.
Jesus Christ.
What if he's gone?
What happens if you look at him?
Is he gone?
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
Why are we all acting so nonchalant about this, by the way?
This is not running.
You'll never catch me.
That's not running. Are you guys all running?
Everybody sprint right now.
I want to watch people sprint.
Let me sprint away, except it's just walking.
He's right next to us.
What?
He really is.
He's right there.
This guy's a fucking chump.
Where is he?
Where's the attack button?
I'm telling you right now.
I'm going to punch this guy right in his face.
He's not here anymore.
Oh no, I lost everybody.
You guys are right next to me.
That guy's a wuss.
Are you serious?
It was scary for two seconds.
He just stands there and stares at you.
He just goes like this.
Am I staring at him?
Why is my guy freaking out?
I think if you sprint too much, you get scared easier.
What's the problem?
I don't know.
He's behind us.
He's behind us too.
I don't know where to go. I'm going this way.
Let's go to the green thing.
The green thing is making us all screwed up.
I'm not walking to the green thing.
It's like a big ball of radiation or something.
Why is this thing emitting radiation?
What happens if I touch it?
Is anybody close to me right now?
He's screaming.
We lost him.
I'm dead.
I went to the radiation thing
and he popped up in my fucking face.
Where am I? I'm a ghost.
Can you guys see me?
I swear to God, I'm a ghost.
Is there somebody inside of this thing?
I see you.
I'm going to come attack you guys.
I think I have to come kill you guys now.
I'm a ghost.
That looks really creepy.
I can't hurt you guys?
You look scary.
What do I do? Just stick around with you guys?
Isn't this a Bill Cosby movie?
Why is my flashlight so dark?
The guy is very tired.
And his flashlight is flickering.
His flashlight is flickering.
This rock formation looks like a genus.
It looks like a middle finger.
Do not go to the green radiation rock.
I thought it was a super magic power
like I was going to get flight or something if I touched it.
You're right, I did.
I did get super magic powers.
You're forever trapped on this earth as a ghost.
Is this another person?
Guys, come over here.
Where's over here?
What is this thing?
What is this?
This is going to kill us.
Stealth died.
I don't see. What are you talking about?
That's where the person died.
What just happened?
Piece of crap.
We just got you killed?
How did you both die instantly?
Look at this blood on the walls.
This blood on the walls.
This blood going up the stairs.
I hear some white noise.
I hear some noise too.
That's green radiation.
Somebody touch it again.
That's like in the middle room.
Stop looking at it.
Somebody just poured it into the wall.
Who just went in the wall?
Who are we missing right now?
Boo.
I think Boo did.
Boo just teleported into the wall and he's gone.
What?
Don't look at it.
Don't look at the roof.
Stealth, why are you walking underneath it?
Why are you walking underneath it?
That's like a tear drop of radiation and hatred.
What are you doing?
Oh my god.
This is where we lose.
He's literally right next to me.
There's a tape.
Yeah.
Got it.
Six out of eight baby.
Where's the monster now?
Where's that pile of crap monster?
It's getting to a point really right now
where I can't even see on the screen.
Alright we have to turn around.
We have to go back in tear drop radiation.
No we don't.
He's going to be right here.
He's behind us now so we have to go in tear drop radiation.
Are you serious?
We have to go back in tear drop radiation.