Hey, what's happening? We are all set up. Sometimes Terraria just takes a while to get it right,
but we're good. Welcome everybody. Currently in the game, but not... Let's see if we can see if
he's ready. Is he ready? Nobody heard you do that. Quick, do that funny thing you just did again,
because nobody heard you do it. Um, has anyone ever heard me do this before? Ever? Hello? Hello?
What did you call me? I was kind of glad that I didn't, I didn't have it muted, you know what
I mean? I had you muted, so I was kind of happy about that. Honestly, um, I think what you should
do is like just mute me now. Mute you now, okay? You're muted? What? I don't understand, what's this
joke? It's like... I thought he was gonna do... I thought he was gonna do... I thought you're gonna
do like a funny thing when I muted you. I thought you were gonna like somehow... I thought you were
gonna come through the game audio. The joke is that you'll finally get a week off where you don't
have to talk to me. I thought the joke was Terraria has in-game VoIP, and I'm gonna talk to you in
there now. That would be pretty funny, but it doesn't. All right, so if you didn't... if you
weren't here last time we played this, you probably noticed... Or the time before that.
Or the time before that. Or any of those times. Um, everybody in here is dead. He did this thing,
he did this fucked up thing at the end of the stream where he accidentally summoned like a clam
I mean it was a hilarious final episode to last week's season. So if I'm you, I watch that and I
catch you up. We're on episode 74 right now, I think? Mm-hmm. Of the Terraria let's play.
The thing is people start appearing like this guy appeared on the roof. Sometimes they might appear
in the lava and just die again though. Oh really? That's a possibility. Yeah, that happens. Do we
should we fill that space or something? No, see, because all the bunny rabbits are walking into it.
So they really are. It's a bunny rabbit death machine and that's important to have. But there's
nothing we can do about this. No. We can't just put a platform here and they won't walk into it?
Don't don't do it. Because when it's night time and there's enemies out here and they're walking
the lava you're gonna be happy then. No, don't do it squirrel. Cute squirrels. Don't do it. Don't.
Don't do it, please. He's gonna do it. I'm trying to scare him away. See? He's like,
I'm smart. I'm a squirrel. You saved a life. Okay, so what was the last thing we did?
The last? We've killed one mechanical boss which are the first bosses after normal mode.
Okay, yeah I remember the mechanical skeleton guy. We have to get some of the new ore that's in the
world. There's a lot of things to do. Okay. You can gather ore if you want. Like what do you
want to do? What's your fantasy right now? I like to fight the bosses. That's the most fun.
Okay. I have to look up how we craft the new mechanical boss. Light of the ebon hammer.
Is this bad? It looks pretty bad. There was a copper axe that I finally I just saw in the
storage. There's a lot of dumpsters laying around. Is there anybody we can even sell to?
The girl on the right. Why are they, how come they're not in their houses? Because when they
appear they show up. They like walk here. You know it's all cinematic, but because our houses
are prisons they can't walk into their room. So if we, actually I don't know how multiplayer
does it, but usually if you like leave the area and come back later they'll just be in their house.
Huh, okay. All right, well you want to go collect some ore? Collect some ore? Yeah. Sure,
because we absolutely need a Mithrai Anvil. Or a Mithrai Anvil? Mithril. Okay, let's go down our
tube. Down the tube. I need to get you a pickaxe that works. I still have that shitty one from
earlier. Yeah, you can't mine these ores. So, should I even come down with you? Yeah,
it'll be, you know. If I can't mine anything I might as well just tell like a funny story
to my chat. Oh yeah, tell a funny story to your chat while I play Terraria for you.
All right, wait, wait, wait. Party up. Red team. Red team. Red team, party up.
Oh, what's this thing? How do you do that? You right click on it. Oh, cool. How do I get out?
Is it R? E? R, okay. You're dying. Be careful of dying. I'll be all right. Things hurt. I like
don't remember what my items do or like I don't have much of memory. Well, it has, it is a weak
angel statue. I'm gonna get that. I want the rope just in case I need that. So, what is the
ore that we want? What is it called? Well, actually we need to go deeper. Holy shit.
It stops right here. You didn't build the rest of the roller coaster. I didn't build this.
They just here underground. Oh, that's cool. We need Mithril. You ever heard of Mithril before?
I'd say it's Mithril. M-I-T-H-R-I. What does it look like? What color is it?
It's much lower than this. Come back to the the helivator. Oh, okay. That was part of the wall.
He lied about the story. No, I said if I don't play, then I'll tell the funny story.
Oh, look, let me just tell you something.
This is one of the things we need. Is that Mithril? Oh, shit. I can't even get it. He hates that,
by the way. He fucking despises that. The I'm shaking the ice in my coffee around the circle
thing is like I may as well be like grabbing his ears and screaming at him. It's awful. It's so
loud. Are you saying like, oh, ha ha, he hates it. Everyone hates it. You guys hate that?
Anybody in here hate that? Do it again for a test. Anyone who wasn't paying attention.
Who hates that? Nobody. No, no, not really. Not really. I like that sound. I like it. No,
no, I'm not seeing any yes. I'm sorry. I think you're just being outvoted here.
Outvoted? I thought you said we had to go down further. Not like where? I was wrong. We need
to get palladium first. Palladium. Yeah, I'm just I'm right here. You see this orange looking shit.
That orange stuff. That stuff is palladium palladium palladium. Yeah, make a joke quick.
I thought you were quicker than this. Make a joke. I don't even make a joke right now.
What is this? This is this is this is the terrible terraria tatterdates. Okay. Why are they terrible?
Oh, shit. I did just say terrible. Didn't I? You did. Is it because it's with me?
No, I like terraria. Is it fun? We're just gonna beat the game. What are you doing?
You keep changing your mind. You keep changing your mind on where you want to go.
No, because you're like, oh, we're gonna go deeper. No, we're gonna go here. No,
we need this. We need that one. Actually, we need palladium. No, we need we need mithril.
Go back down. Go back up. I just want to I'm just you know, hey guys, so I was I was at the
Dunkin' Donuts drive-through today. And oh my goodness, could I not believe what I saw.
I pull up. I've got a $1 bill in my hand to pay for my small coffee. And what happened? Is that
what you want? Is that what you want me to do? Yeah, please finish the story now. Why can't I
jump off? All right, here we go. I did it. Oh, fuck. That's a big wheeze. So guys, I'm at Dunkin'
Donuts. And I'm at the drive-through. You really want to like set up squad streams, huh? My chat
always tells me to do it. And it's I give them what they want. All right. Squad streams. Okay.
Stuart wants to squad with you. Except I have accepted. Are you gonna be in a mood the whole
time today? This is not my fault. All right. How hard can you wheeze without like getting hurt?
I don't know. Like, for instance, like, say something that's like a funny joke.
Um, pee pee poo poo. I just hurt my stomach. Yeah, that's gonna hurt me. I don't want to.
God damn it. I'm actually I hurt myself. I really just did. I like hurt myself. God damn it. I
didn't even tweet this stream up. Oh, no. You've been really messed up. Is that the title of your
stream too? Terrible Carrara? No, it's called chunky soup stream. What is it? What does that mean?
That's it. It's gonna be a long one. It's gonna be a chunky one. Okay, let me tweet this. I'll get
back to you in like 10 minutes. I still don't have a magic mirror. I'm leaning back right now to
stretch out like my stomach muscles that I just like ripped in half. Okay. All right. So just keep
playing. Just make sure just get that that the P or whatever it was. Okay, I'll do everything.
But I don't have a thing. I don't have the returno cone. The mirror? Did I get didn't I
give that to you last week? I gave it back to you. So do I have it? Let me see. Well, I'm like away
from the I'm away from my keyboard right now. Oh, all right. All right. Do I have it? I do. You want
it? Uh, should I give it to you? Is this a sign that you're giving up? No, but I mean, you said
you here take it. No, no, I'm gonna I'm gonna throw it into this abyss right now. You better
catch it. Don't. Will it break if it hits the ground? It'll explode. No, worldwide. Here. How
do I throw this to? I don't know. I've never played this game before. Is it not right? Oh,
no, no, no, no, no. Okay, I got it. I got it. So I'm gonna keep looking for that or the harm.
I'm looking for the orange or or the other one, right? I'll see what I can only the orange right
now. Okay. Only the orange. Only the orange or what's that? Chad, you gotta help me out here to
get the ice hearts. People are saying get the ice hearts. Rune stones. We need those.
Uh, no, we don't. We don't. Oh, right. Didn't you tell me don't ever listen to anybody in chat
for this game? I mean, you can yell at me for that. It's just that there's a decent probability
they'll be wrong or they're really gonna ruin your single player learning experience by spoiling you.
You know, I'm looking for this. Oh, shit. I'm popping a spelunker so we can find this.
Is it in a certain? Is this the biome that it spawns in? It's just everywhere underground.
Assuming you've been down here. Usually not. Oh, not a not that deep. Don't go down to hell,
you know? No, I'm not in hell right now. No, I'm not right. I am. What the fuck is going on?
You stop doing that. I'm trying to. Uh, I don't think it's sitting down here. So this is to get
a better pickaxes, right? What you were saying? Uh, yeah. Well, no, it's to get a better pickaxe
to get me me thrill to get a me thrill. Yeah. Anvil, which you need to craft like basically
everything. Thanks for thanks for not streaming on my birthday yesterday. I appreciate it.
Happy birthday. You can't say happy birthday birthday was yesterday. He missed it. Well,
you don't know that I could be like in Australia. I could be like a full day ahead of you in time
zone. So you missed it by two days. I was going to just do a huge wheeze again, but I really hurt
myself last time. So I'm not doing that again. It's the stuff I probably have close to enough
already. How much do we need? Not much. Just need enough to make a pickaxe so that we can get the
better words. They say go to hell. What would you do? I didn't do anything. Oh, you dynamite.
I'm so glad this is not like Minecraft where you just drop everything. If everything you die with
it just stays on the ground. There is a mode for that. Is there like to play that? Um, I don't
think I'd like to play that. I would be very bad at that. And then there's hardcore mode.
There's a hardcore terrarium mode. Yeah, that's probably insane. I don't see any over here.
I'm just gonna go up. What is all that shit on the mini map? The top, right? All the gold stuff.
Is that just sand? Yeah. So it's not up here. It's not up here. I'm gonna go see how much I've got.
We cannot get that. Okay. Well, did you check up this way? I'm gonna go see how much I've got.
This is lead. Lead's good. You're doing good. I'm proud of you. After doing that wheeze,
this is gonna sound kind of weird and gross, but I I'm gonna have diarrhea in like seven hours.
What? Yeah, like it means doing that wheeze, like just turned all the food in my stomach into
diarrhea and it'll be then like another eight to 12 hours. It'll be diarrhea.
I liquefied all the fucking stool in my stomach by wheezing. Okay. Germa, I've got the pickaxe.
Oh, so that's what chunky means. Oh, oh, oh, whoops. Nevermind. Forget it. Cut me off right now.
Say anything. Do anything. Cut me off right now. What about Hillary's emails?
No, worse possible other scenario. Anything else? What is this stuff? Enchanted shard?
Uh, that's irrelevant. What? It's irrelevant. It took, uh, yeah, sorry, man. You're wasting your
time. I thought I found something cool. I'm sorry. You said this stuff is easy to find. I don't see
this shit anywhere. Where are you? It's hitting me. Oh, like the things that we said. Hey, take
this pickaxe. Hey, Germa. I know. I know. Give it to me. I'll take it. Okay. Now, you know, like
the pink stuff over here that you see? Yeah. Large palladium pickaxe. Now we can mine the pink stuff.
Really? Oh, we really need it. Which is going to be lower. Is that like a like,
is it like a pogchamp moment? Do I have, is diamonds cool? No, no, no, it's not. Okay.
So now we can get this stuff and that will, I have so much trash. Let me get rid of this, um,
serpentine, ruby. I feel like all this stuff is good though. Flaming arrow,
Jester's arrows, granite block. No, that stuff's trash, right? Granite block is trash. Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, is it? Huh? Huh? Huh? What, what, what, what, what, what?
What? It's gone. Are you, are you lying to me? I think this is a joke. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right.
So we need to, now we can just find the pine, uh, find the pineapples. Yeah. I can't get over
the fucking thing that just happened. Okay. So what, the thing at the Dunkin' Donuts? No,
let me tell you, I'll tell you. Never before have I seen something so funny. Wait, isn't that what
you always tell for a shitty story? You were in line at Dunkin' Donuts. I've heard this before.
Yeah. Cause I, you've never finished it. Cause I spend like two thirds of every day at the
Dunkin' Donuts drive thru. What's wrong with you? I'm a regular, you know. Do they know your drink?
What's your drink? Lodge. That's just a lodge. That's it. Just send me the cup out the window.
I just want to pretend to drink it. I'm supposed to, my doctor told me to cut back on caffeine.
So I still order the coffee, but I just have you give me the empty plastic cup.
That sounds awesome. Give me the regular. Who the fuck are you?
That's funny. Angry trifold map? What is that? I have to go back to town and I'm throwing something
away. Silver ore. Um, all right. I gotta, I gotta disappear for a sec. No, I gave you the, I gave
you the mirror. He did. I'm just gonna have to follow you down until you decide. No, I'm going
back up. Just go back to the elevator. Yeah. Screw that. What, what is this? Oh, that's like
titanium or whatever it is in this world. It just never ends in Terraria. You know,
you're always just doing something. What have you done so far? I'll take the lodge.
All right. I'm going to go back to the elevator. Diaper check. What would that even entail? Hey,
oh, hey, dude. Just catching the stream. Diaper check. Is that implying that I turn the webcam
on and prove that I have a diaper on? Yeah. Why would you want to know that? Well, no,
not that you have a diaper on that it's still clean. Oh my God. Like, we know you have one.
Like, we know you have one. Let's check. All right. Can we have, can we like,
all right. Welcome to the stream guys. We just started. No more like, like shit diapers and
like poo poo jokes. PP poo poo? I know you're going to do that like three or four more times,
but I want to make sure that I put, for the record, I'm not doing them anymore. Okay. Okay.
I miss the old German and PP poo poo jokes. So I have, right. I'm going to take some wormhole
potions. How many should I take? Three or two? Two. I miss young German. You can't be young
forever guys. Don't you understand? I can't wait until you're like 80 years old and you're
streaming and you're just, I'm not going to do that. You know, that's why it'll be fun to watch.
I just said that and now everyone's going to freak out. What? No, I knew it. All right. So
I'm coming back down to you. I'm not going to take a wormhole. Why would I? You're just like
straight down. Why is there a dino? This is mine? Dying Mountain Dew? What? No, there's like a,
I have like a dinosaur friend following me. Will he, is he going to die if he hits the ground?
Hold on. Nope. He didn't die. No, that's bullshit. What? There's a giant clam somewhere again.
If you fight it. I don't think I want to do that. It seems to cause a lot of problems.
All right. So where the heck did you go? You went like down. I went left. You know,
I'm just getting an ore. You know, I'm, I'm contributing. Yeah. German. Yeah. I'm teleporting
to you. Three, two, one. Just start digging holes. You know, here, you know what? I'm going to give
you some dynamite. Yeah. Give me some of the bombs, man. Here's a hundred, a hundred dynamite.
I just threw it right there. Cool. Just start throwing them around. Yeah. Just go wild. All
right. Have fun. That's what I'm talking about. Where are they? Right here. All right. All right.
Let's go. How to occupy an idiot. Couldn't be in a mood today. I'm in a mood every day.
Glad I don't think that's true. You haven't even complained about it being dark ones yet.
No, you've changed. All right. I'm going to start firing them down here. Oh, what's this?
Enchanted shard. No, it's the same thing I got last time instead. It wasn't worth it.
Yeah. Oh, shit. That's lava. Oh, oh, watch out. What are you doing? What are you doing?
Oh, what's over here? I think I found something. Good. I did. Do you see these little
purple pinwheels in the air? Uh-huh. Pick those up. Corrupt mimic. Ow. Is that it? They're going to
die. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Don't die, dude. Stop. Leave me alone. You can't even see that thing on the
screen. He's just dumb. How could you even see that? I zoomed my eyes onto it. You see these
purple pinwheels? The purple pinwheels. The spinning, glowing purple. Up there. Yes. The
soul of light. The soul of night. I got you. So find those. Any reason why they would drop?
Oh, killing enemies in this biome drops. You got it. Every enemy around here that's dying
that you're killing off the screen. I see a farming the stone. They're all dropping. You got it.
And they're used in like most recipes. Careful. Careful. This is bomb. You ride this fucking dark
down here. Dude, seriously? Who made the earth this way? Oh, shit. Did that actually get me?
I'm actually so glad that you're playing as the AFK guy. How did you occupy an idiot?
Just any time that you have anything to say like that, just say that.
No, like these things that travel through walls and kill things are the like
this stage of the game. There's nothing better than another one of those things. These mimics.
You're an idiot. That's what you want. That's how you want people to treat you. Huh? No,
no. The joke is that like that says that's like, that's so overdone. That's like leaving the
fucking steak on the grill for three days and you forgot it was on a joke. It's not a joke.
That was not the joke. And I think you need a little bit more self-respect. I think I killed
the mimic. No, there's another one. Oh my fucking God. I'm just like going you deal with that thing.
I killed the last one. Can we not break this stuff? What's this? He's a better axe.
I think that's I forget what it's called on this world titanium. Grab that. Grab that stuff in the
lava. That's down there because there's a lot of random shit in there.
And then the stuff again down there. Tell me what to do again and see what happens. Go get
the items in the lava. Now. What happened? What happened? Oh, worm hook.
I have the kind of stupid gel. I don't know. What is it called? It's the one that it's like the
right. I can't tell you. I think this one's a little better. I can give it to you if you'd
like it. Maybe. I mean, I'm just I'm doing what you told me to do. I have a lot of these things.
He's in one of those moods today. What's that supposed to mean?
No, actually what you're supposed to say is damn Joe. No, no, no. It's how do I occupy an idiot?
Dumb. What would my mother think about when you guys say that? I mean, imagine like being my
mother who watches every one of these streams. Does she? German idiot. German so stupid. He's
pretending he's so is he pretending to be this dumb who raised him? I've seen that one a lot.
Who raised him? I found some more that stuff. There's a lot of those down there. Am I gonna
get hurt by this? Holy shit. That's a lot of stuff. Wow. Wow. Too many too many things. All
right. You have me on this kick of pick up all the purple things and I've got a lot of them.
Okay, I'm doing so good. Wait, I'm good for what was that on the stuff over here?
Oops. I need to get this shit over here. What's that? Granite energy storm.
Oh, to me to me. Wait, maybe not. Can I handle this? Yeah, I can. I can handle this.
No, I'm good. What do you drop? Oh shit. Energy manipulator. All right. Hold on.
I'll update it. Oh, Earth Elemental is not what you're killing an Earth Elemental.
Where the fuck am I killing this thing? I just I don't even know what
happened. Did I do it? Got him. All right. I need light. This is the or or or
Mickey or or orient in the blind. Believe in yourself. What is this stuff? Or
or a clicky claim or or it or a shell or a ship or a shell ship. Hey, orange. You're glad it
didn't say banana. That's that's good. I think if you come back, we're ready to fight some bosses.
Hold on. I'm drowning. He's in one of those boots today. I'm coming back. No, I'm not coming back
yet. There's too many treasures. That thing depth meter. Blink root gel. Get rid of this.
Okay, I got it. Whatever it is. All right, I'm coming. I'm I dude, I'm like obsessed right now
about these purple things and I have this so many of them. Tell me something. Tell me to do
something else because like I've got like I probably have 200 days. I have probably 215 of these
come back. Okay, I'm coming back. And I told you that a while ago. Did you listen?
No, I don't think you did. It's too dark. Okay, I gotta figure out how to make these blocks.
All right, I'm coming back with like a ton of stuff. We need souls of light. Fuck souls of
light. Souls of light. Anybody else see what's going on? I don't. I'm not drowning. I'm fine.
Drowning pleb. Hey, nice room you got there. Whatever. Drowning pleb. Drowning pleb. Drowning
pleb. Hey, relax. And you come back, we're gonna fight a boss. I'm just gonna use my wormhole to
you. I don't care how expensive this is. They're not that expensive.
Okay, I have like 150 of these things. I have 35 of them. Put them in storage.
German was slain by a giant clam. I need to look at some of the stuff though because holy shit.
Oh my god. What? It's not that big of a deal. Are you fine?
It sounds like you're putting me inside of a washer. I'm summoning this fucking boss. Don't.
I seriously have a full inventory. There's a limited night time. I don't want to miss it.
Okay, fine. Do it. I deposited everything. Where are we fighting at? There's a guy outside.
What in the name of god is going on with this guy? Dude, this.
There's people that are doing this. I'm trying to stay alive. Ow. I'm dead. Could you not be dead?
I have really bad weapons. Let me just do something here called I'm gonna spawn the boss
when you're not ready and I don't even know what this is. It's a worm. How many times have you
fought worms before? It shoots fucking portal to turrets everywhere. Is it gonna come in here?
It's dead. Did it die like in the wall? No, it died up here. I'm supposed to let you pick
things up and look at them and go ooh. Well, I was about to do that and then you said
he's in a mood. They really only drop materials to make things.
I picked up a bunch of shit down there and like oh I really want you to look at it.
Hey, I'm spawning the boss now. What? Go. I don't even know what I said. I wanted you to look at
it. When did I say I wanted you to look at it? You just said that I want you to be able to pick
things up and look at it. That's what you just said. You said right now. I didn't say look at them.
You said to go ooh ah look at that. What did he all right am I insane or did he not just say I
want Jermba to pick up the items to look at them and go ooh ah am I insane? No, I was talking
about the boss and then you were talking about what happened in the freaking hole. I'm talking
about both. All right, so that was fun. We have a lot of money. All right, we need souls of light.
I picked up a bunch of shit though. I'm not even kidding. You know, you know, look at it at your
own souls of you said you said souls of light right light okay souls of flight light souls of
flight or souls of flight light okay so not souls of flight souls of flight are also important
though okay do you have those there are seven in the inventory yeah in the chop thing yeah I
thought maybe you had found some but there's no way I actually found a beam sword and everyone
I saw like at least 25 pogchamps when I picked it up okay is that good I didn't get a chance to
look at it I mean that's what the fuck is that are you kidding me oh you got to be kidding me
am I right uh I mean I think I'm not a big fan of the proc rate on this
it only procs like once every second I'll load the key quick diaper check one of these days
you guys are gonna keep me like banned that'll be a that's a good twitch staff is gonna be like
hold on wait wait wait wait we gotta check this guy's bod he's like he's put he's like showing
a diaper like inside of a diaper on stream that he's wearing we gotta check this bod this whole
thing in and out I think best case scenario you get banned because you only get banned for like a
week and then you come back and everyone's like what because everyone everyone talks about you
for a week you know drama got banned for like showing his diaper on stream
you come back and have like a hundred thousand people viewing it's great
dude I heard about this guy yeah he's like he like wears a diaper on stream like what the
fuck yeah he's not right all right so this I mean I have some cool stuff I
can you check can you check the deposit area because I seriously just you you freaked me
out I had a full meter and I threw everything in there wow what's new yeah but I didn't have
even 10 I teleported to you and didn't even have 10 seconds you didn't even give me 10 seconds
now you know what I'm gonna go do my own adventure go who needs you I was gonna mute you and just do
play terraria in your server okay I'll mute you and we can talk to each other next week like I
said the beginning where are you what are you actually doing though I'm looking for souls of
light souls of light and they're down in that area you got it they should be there should be
enemies that spawn them here you know no no I'm gonna take a look at the inventory I'm gonna look
at the materials and I want to see what you can turn the beam sword into yeah do that because my
viewers are fucking smart and they want to see combinations and they want to see the intelligence
part of the game not just like I throw shoot stuff down in dungeons what's going on steampunker has
awoken and there's like a there's a they're having a party there's a halloween organ being played
here's what you do plug in the soul of night into the the guy and uh let's see what you can make
well where is what can this turn into solstice claymore my god changes projectile color based
on the time of the year inflicts day broken during the day and night wither during the night
wait is it a blood moon I just told you that it was a bunch of shit going on
pirate guy that flips oh this is the okay this is a good event we gotta kill these things kill
these things yeah we're looking for broken hero swords and stuff well I just got something pretty
cool broken hero swords um what is that I can talk to something up here it's like an angel
menacing moonstone so what eclipse is different than a blood moon oh yeah in there I don't think
I ever had a randomly spawned one what's that tesla defibrillator there are too many items in
the game I don't know what to do it's too many and you know it's because we're going too fast
you know if you're playing with yourself take your time you get to enjoy the experience
but I've ruined it that tends to happen whenever you play a game with start you just
do the go to 100 immediately but it's also kind of a good thing is if I played this on my own
stream on my own just hey I'm gonna open up terraria and wait that's what we're going to do
today there was not only two bosses there would not be any mods I'd probably be at 800 by 600
resolution and um I I would dig out but still be in my first spelunking mission going down
I would have picked up like 10 and thought it was cool
oh wow there's 10 wow what do I do with 10 okay now we're getting going
how long does this last next week all night yeah I've never seen those vampire essence before
what's that nothing why is this lady outside vampire essence yeah I've got it too any bosses
um there's one mini boss I think episode 54 and 55 of the tin arc yeah and I would have okay I'm
gonna be careful in the title of this I just got fucking air shot by that guy I'm gonna die out
here you don't even need to be out there just stand by the door indoors and watch them all
going for a lot of while your stuff kills them also take the warm up um anyways I was gonna say
what was I gonna say oh yeah the episodes would be titled um something funny and pop culture
referencing like uh terraria episode 55 the adventures of tin tin with me getting 10 for
like four episodes oh I see what we're going with this and you don't stop getting 10 till
you have like 999 okay I understand the minus twos but mine but I didn't that I'm saying that
that would be a terrible thing to do I love how you guys you all right you guys like give me like
minus twos and plus twos the stuff that I didn't even do if I think about a bad joke it's minus
two I can't even it's like I can think about a potential bad piece of humor if I opened up right
now a recipe book no if I opened up a recipe book and read like how how to make like a like
how to make the best corn on the cob just the recipe itself would be it would get like a minus
two wouldn't be me no German listen those are bots on twitch that just show up and spam minus two
altogether they're all owned by one person and it's an extreme or self-conscious
your joke was actually really funny
yeah okay I remember you know like the minus two thing right I was playing Sam and Max a
couple weeks ago and jokes that Sam was making in the game they were minus twoing me
that's how far we've gone oh yeah that's what I mean it's like it's not even about you it's just
it's not even about me anymore I think they thought you made Sam and Max
it's you didn't make this this is cool see now now I see plus twos but I made that joke I'm not
getting the plus two they're putting in your channel I know there's a whole lot of you know
there needs to be like a regulatory board that oversees the like the plus two and minus two
market because it's highly manipulated okay so what do you want to do you didn't get me like
broken hero sword I do I'm making archelous do it I don't you know don't you need the thing that I
threw it uh broken sword right I think I deposited one or two of them somebody said broken hero
so it drops from moth rom it's the mechanical bosses that drop the broken swords no star is
seriously not and he's really stupid star is fucking dumb stars an idiot I have 500 hours in
terraria star just is being like annoying that's weird weird yeah it's just kind of weird dude just
imagine did I get anything like that was worth using I feel like I'm okay you've got me in this
uh in this position where somebody who's in the house uh vampires teleporting which is weird
because normally you have to invite vampires and that is true yeah I don't think this game's
accurate I feel like everything I pick up is not as good as I have these aliens that go through
walls and kill everything well you're a summoner and that's that's your whole point I know if you
want to be a magician you have been doing it wrong I know I'm just I'm just saying stir is smart and
handsome and funny yeah whatever oh yeah I have this thing too forgot about this thing this is
this is a very long eclipse moon well I mean it's all night and nicer they're pretty long
so we just just stay here until they're all until this is over so I'm getting Nancy I mean you can
go do whatever you want I'm crafting the god sword and I'm changing my whole terraria build
if you can even imagine what's going on in my head right now
oh
these things are really good too and this is not even a summon this is a sentry
I'm star boy now oh you actually made it yeah that thing looks pretty insane
it's melee damage go get him very colorful yeah just brighten everything up
for her just in case anyone wanted to be able to see what was happening on the screen
who's the next boss um we have to summon we need the souls of light to get the last mechanical
boss okay so after this moon is over we're going to go get the mechanical um dust whatever the
hell the thing is uh light dust I want to make you a hallowed uh staff hallowed staff
I really want to replace the sans head I forgot how to make it yeah I'm getting I'm just gonna
store the sans head I don't like it I'd rather just do this this thing is cool too
yeah I like this thing better oh you got a tentacle oh yes oh yeah
it really not that great though is the eldritch tomb a summoner weapon
um no I don't think so I think it's just I mean technically it's a summoner weapon but
it's a material though what can I do with this what can I do with it this is the auger the
elements very fast average knockback burst of elements the tentacles to spear your enemies
yeah it's just like a better version of it what does it take tomb of fates and what can I do with
that how do I get a tomb of fates shadow form hex doll galactica singularity humanite bar all right
can you please what can I do with that is there a mod list yeah uh if you do exclamation point
mod but maybe not anymore it was there before hey wait a second what can I do with that
you leave me alone I'm just playing terraria look at this thing cosmic immaterializer
eventually maybe I'll make this one day 5 000 summoner damage yeah that's insane
this is a very long night no it's not it's an average length night didn't you know that this
um you know we also need to do what's that we need to go up into the upper layer in the sky
that we haven't done that until wyverns so we can get souls of flight you know when it's daytime
you're on wyvern duty or even right now I think they spawn anyway yeah they're really big long
snake dragons and they drop souls of flight so just go up a high high high for this guy
yeah high high high okay and I'm gonna try and find the underground hollowed biome
50 bucks hold on is it gonna be the same joke I don't know but I hold on I just I'm
I'm looking off the screen I think I just killed what did I just kill was it a wyvern
what's going on essence of sunlight ball of flight hold on let me I'm gonna die in here
I'm moving in here I'm getting with okay wait wait wait is that lava I don't think so we're
talking lava all right what they say was killer crockemeier thank you for the 50 bucks they say
uh remember when this was a salmon max stream tomato sad well thank you for the that's a lot
of money but um I've played all I've played almost the whole thing I've played through the first two
full seasons of that game we're gonna play season three don't worry we are how much higher do I have
to go star but seriously that's a lot of fucking money thank you like in space like I'm floating
right now is that high enough yeah I don't know ropes I don't have any rope I gotta come back and
get some and I am looking for bowls of flight they're looking for the long dragons yeah I
already killed one long yeah okay and then they drop souls of flight and then you come to me
and you tell me I have them and then I say good job how many do you want um uh I need you to come
to me the twins are fighting me I need help this is the last mechanical boss we need um
I'm on my way randomly spawned on me I'm going to base what they're gonna follow me here
I wasn't ready for this I think they might have left they left I thought it was about to be daytime
no what the fuck is that thing called I think you despawned them they really leave
ah dude I'm gonna go back there be ready to wormhole to me if I start crying like a little baby
yeah I'm flat crying I was probably gonna die to him and you tell me I'm gonna I'm gonna make
my way up to the uh the wyverns wait no not this thing's cool but not good enough for me
what all that is when will you learn you must learn learn what everything you must learn the
way of the dance that's what that's what you have to dance get it I'm so happy everyone's so mad at
that I do that so often it's like it was never funny but I just I like to say it are you fighting
them no I think I'm all of mimic I got all my gear is for throwing damage still
but sword is not doing very good uh that looks like streaming don't you just like streaming
no my own prison Jesus
vibrant what is that I like this song from the sky because this song sounds like a noise I would
make with my mouth of that well that's why I like this song the best
hello oh damn what's this stuff oh essence of sunlight do we need any of these uh yeah
they're important got it oh wyvern take it fast no oh fuck don't don't panic I panicked
it's all right is there anything I can die is there anything to do with the system never mind
whatever what all right cool never mind I was just I was just testing to see if you would like react
fast if I was in trouble I gotta build a platform up here give some wood is it wood in the storage
probably uh Ashley says germa doesn't know the souls float huh what do you mean doesn't know
doesn't know pepe he doesn't know pepe he doesn't know he doesn't know that guy pepe
wait what do you mean the souls float I'm confused what do you mean you know what let
germa experience terraria at his own pace you know what I'm saying it's too late for that
come on this is episode one you know that it's too late for that episode one germa starts fresh
episode one you won't believe what happens and everyone in chat needs to be on their
best behavior because his mom is watching terraria episode one you won't believe what happens to me
and I just I cut down like 10 trees what if someone did make that youtube video oh
terraria episode one you won't believe what happens to me and actually like 20 minutes in
like something cra- like something flies through his window and there's like bees everywhere in his
room yeah someone throws a hornet nest in there you would have no idea what happens and it's
just like oh it's just typical like like a clickbait video yeah I don't know like like a giant ant
like fights him in his room he starts a fire like his house burns down it's just it's it's
insane you need to see it must click I'm not clicking that must click terraria episode two
making my first house click this something crazy happens it's like okay must watch must watch
top videos of 2019 yeah I get like a giant alien ant comes in breaks through his fucking wall and
they have a fist fight and he like knocks this fucking thing out it's like an unbelievable thing
yeah earth's first contact with intelligent life from another planet and no one knows because it
was posted on youtube yeah as like a terraria video title so if no one ever saw it I'm just
waiting for these things to spawn hold s to dance are you dancing right now no must watch
and then episode three it just goes back to normal like he's he just makes like a house
in terraria in the next episode here we go would you watch the rest of that guy's videos
absolutely would you skip to the end or are you watching I mean if if this motherfucker knocks
out an alien on camera like I'm gonna have I'm gonna subscribe to the guy he may have saved us
all but he's more interested in building his house or he's doomed us all yeah I mean the aliens were
gonna send back up but they saw the video the main like commander of the alien forces gets
addicted to his like fucking terraria let's play I really want to see what he does next
it says I must watch no no he's doing it wrong episode 12 says you won't believe what happens
I wonder if he killed another one of our alien commanders you're doing it wrong
you're doing it wrong I mean he's the alien he would know oh god am I dead tranquility element
come on spawn spawn I don't understand we we were on our way to conquer earth but for some reason
I got really obsessed with this 10-hour ayaya video we can't invade anymore this is quality
yeah we were gonna kill them all and use their brains for fuel but not when they come up with
stuff like this oh no they do this what have you done I'm having a great time right now
I'm just defending earth from the aliens I uh I don't know how to find what I'm looking for
I do have like fucking 22 of these things earth elemental is that you or me that's me there's so
many emotes for that is there uh look I'm gonna be honest with you guys I just don't get it I don't
get it who's your favorite anime character um Edward Elric why is that funny because I don't
like care it's the only one he's seen I feel like you should care that's because he it's because
he's short I'm gonna go up higher no I'm gonna go this way I'm gonna go that way I'm gonna probably
have like 30 to 50 of these things so hopefully I'm supposed to actually collect these and this
isn't some big like debate uh I mean you have enough I have enough yeah okay I think you might
need to help me do something I fell off the platform what do you need uh I'm trying to find
a specific underground biome I gotta say I'm having some trouble uh locating it okay what
do you want me to do about this uh help me locate it no wait hold on oh no I wanted to catch it
no why fuck I'm busy I love ducks that just made me so sad okay um I'm coming to you
no you know the point the point is to not come to me because we're both exploring the same spot
no I was just doing I was grinding um for those um flight emblems whatever the hell
it the bowls of the flight emblems the flight um gift of flight now that's a youtube video
that I don't need it um okay soul of flight oh you've been getting souls how many do you have
a 40 oh we only need it like 20 well we got plenty they're in the deposit box hey go to the
craftman crash show him the soul of flight you got it and check out find a wing that you think you
can create I think we have dragon scales we have we have some other feathers dragon blast but yeah
we're gonna we're gonna make wings dude angel wings demon wings fairy wings harpy wings
butterfly wings bone wing flame wing frozen wings I feel like I've had buffalo wild wings right now
you are this is a this is a list of like how hot they are and have like the different seasonings
that are on them yeah okay bee wings I've got this hitter and read them all well no just find
one that you can make based like okay feather soul flight 20 soul of light we have 25 soul light
no soul of light is what I'm looking for right now demon wings I think are probably the easiest
demon wings also they need soul of night yeah we have a lot of those so what's the difference
are they all the same exact thing except all right what about um the ones that we can make
are basically all the same we have pixie dust because fairy wings are also available uh there's
like four or five harpy wings I guess the it's just speed flight time yeah demon wings are the
ones we can make because we need soul of night we need one more soul of flight because uh this
39 they take 40 what they take it's 20 soul of flight to make one demon wing so you're gonna
need one too right oh there's a frozen feather in the storage is that what do we need a frozen
feather can make uh better wings oh shit really better demon wings oh ice okay oh shit yeah so we
have an ice feather so who wants the frozen wings which which ones which ones do you want
I was thinking look I'll get like a couple and you get a couple and we'll split them
rock paper scissors shoot I was gonna get two bone wings uh two frozen wings and then
if you get the you get the flame wings and the butterfly wings we can you can have some mine
okay but which one do you actually want whichever one's faster that's the frozen one so I'm just
gonna make it and give two okay um we don't we don't actually have a frozen feather do we
what's going on here we have some ice feather um we actually both can have ice wings because
we have two okay yeah I remembered finding a bunch okay cool so um which which one of
these special tables do I need to make there we go frozen wings got it I need to find let me get
one more um the essence of flight essence of kiss no because then you can have it too
okay I mean whatever you say what are these what is equipped to is this like an accessory um yeah
it's like a regular accessory slot should I put these on rather than put on the boots or should
I keep the boots on experiment terma figure out for yourself let's see you know what do you want
someone can do this first and you can just glide so you'll never die from fall damage ever again
oh you can't take fall damage while you wear wings wow okay that's cool uh I'll take off the
bracelet okay yeah that's good yeah I want that mana though that mana all right I'm going to get
one more of those uh things do you have enough mana I cheated in the game how do we somebody
will get this I'm gonna say it once oh my mom's watching so now you can't say sucks anymore
huh even though my mom just said mobile sucks but you can't say it because then she'll think
that I'm hanging out with druggies again all right you want the ice ones too yeah okay got
one for me it got one for you yeah I used to be up daddy I love how you're like completely okay
saying that with your mother watching what's wrong with you but you're not comfortable around
your mom you like hide who you are around her he's already he's gone my kid is not negative
deposit my gold do I have too much gold oh my god thank you for the reminder all right I got you
wings hopefully you like them you are 4600 feet away that's far yeah I'm trying to find this goddamn
underground underground hollow biome what does this person do shot blood moon medallion oh you
can make it a blood moon for two gold summons uh this guy that's cool so you can just whenever
you want have one of those invasions happen yeah huh that's cool but you had to have had at once
generally I see cool all right do I need to do anything else yeah you need to find this
underground hollowed biome underground hollowed biome oh and you're just wasting time fighting
toxic sludges you killed a hundred of them and you could have been helping me real cute
um I can't tell if you were sneezing or somebody came in the room and put their
leg hands around your neck I was sneezing sneezing you're all right feeling better now
oh shit the alien quick help her to find the inner edge of the non-natural evil biome and
reflect on the map to easily find the hollow you know right there I don't right here people that
are watching uh star shed in my do I got it right there the edge of the of the non yep I got it
people saying I got it what come to me where are you at the edge of where the evil biome begins
yeah right here this is where it begins yeah and I've been underground here right at the edge
right here yeah press m I'm on the other end we'll see how this goes well no I mean like
press m and look below you I've been down there what's this stuff his map doesn't show
your map oh so you've already been down here well yeah straight below you I've I've been down there
okay who's hitting me the background shows it yeah nice I see where he's already done it he said
just do it anyways yeah I mean he may have missed it
summoner weapon proficiency leveled up go diagonally down diagonally down
oh my god dude the left I'm going go left and down okay now break the stuff what is this stuff
go left and down I guess no left and down go left and down I mean I'm as left and down
as you could be angry ice skates ice torch cool are you mad bro
there's a big potion down there you know I'm just digging a hole you know so refresh my memory on
what you want again so I can make sure I'm not doing exactly what you want exactly to a tee
I want to find the underground hollowed biome left left that we can acquire souls of light
it's right there it's here did I found it keep going you find pink ice then you pretty much
found it I mean I did find the pink ice but it was like it was it was barely on my screen
it was very small area I think is that you and me that's probably me hey it's me I've got this
pink stuff over here did I get it I think I got it yeah over here is the pink and I just was like
this is this is there's like nothing here I guess I shouldn't have been such a ninny
pink water pink blocks come to where I am I mean I'm I am where you are I'm just below you
yeah but I want you to give me the wings you ninny stop no I'm gonna keep bullying you
until I get those wings you ninny I think we found it yeah this is it I was just a dummy and
went in a different way this is it I made it remember it was me that decided to go this way
and chat was right what are you doing how did I not take why am I not getting killed by that
you just dropped oh it's because we're on the same team all right here are you wings
um I don't drown so just like give me food somewhere else you just drop them here yeah
but I don't think such a baby we were just standing in base high water
yeah here take them did I get those interview uh you might have if I'm picking up slush blocks
here thank you uh yep uh you're welcome what's that cool thing over there it's the legend of
Zelda thing what's it called cliff airy I love the fairy pearl stone hey mom mom what's your
favorite pokemon the mother taste test there are wrong answers oh I know what it is actually I
already know this it's fucking norlax yeah that's a good choice ten okay so we found the biome
now we need the pink glowy pinwheels I think this is a good place to stop
so thanks joining guys we'll see you uh next time also you see these crystal shards on the walls
yeah like glowy crystals you need those the ones like a bit of brick okay yeah yeah you have to
like go up to them they create light strange why are you just like a you just like a dinner napkin
because I have rogue items on that make me invisible ish so it's just my wings showing for
some reason oh what about these ones these things are cool these uh soul of light oh we need these
don't we yeah good space uh the ebb and stone blocks are worthless right can I confirm that
with you yeah and what rotten chunks worthless we have like 90 okay what about uh worm tooth
worthless all right what about pink ice block worthless purple ice block worthless
ice block you don't want it I thought I thought there's a cowboy hat a cute heist home ice home
ice flush block pearl stone block I want to pay someone to cut together stir saying
we need those and jump the turtles we do need those banjo kazooie enemy that was just like
that was great yes cool oh you got me crystal shard crystal shard I'll take that
we probably have enough for this thing intact geode also might be useful I don't know if we're
past it yet actually do we still need a pletium um it doesn't hurt but not really well it's here
it's unlikely bullies just in case I'm gonna get it uh what about is it more up there
ice what's this stuff yeah I'm super out of room I feel like half of this stuff is just worthless
heck is that no I'm not doing a diaper check stop
can you please though I'm just getting all this
ore and I just feel like I'm gonna get it I'm sure if we're here we're probably never coming
back here ever again ideally everyone's asking for you to make a jojo records I have not seen
jojo so it's hard for me to do you think we have enough crystals I have like seven or eight yeah
I did beat the fighting gold beat saber level though so did you do all of germacraft the whole
thing no I mean I did I did the rat we are the rat song and I did the it's your birthday today
which are both on beat saber yeah you didn't do germacraft episode one it's like 16 minutes long
I didn't do it I wouldn't be able to beat it I'd stop a minute in I'm just so obsessed with picking
up all this stuff I'm gonna get these wings are so good good thing I did all that grinding
yeah dude you're fucking I'm going back to town I'm gonna open up this chest
and I'll join you magic mirror oh oh found another magic mirror is that an enemy stand
gold do that flame an arrow they uh suspicious looking eye I don't know what that does um what's
a suspicious looking eye summons the eye of Cthulhu doing a fucking boss in the game what is this
help hello I wouldn't okay I'm coming to help no no I just didn't know what it was I was freaking
out because I'm not fine I want to make sure you don't die because they drop good things help
that was such a polite help I could have been like
but instead I was like help help me help
help me don't die here anything good uh there's a magic magic mirror here do you have any room
what the hell was that neat what was that germa 985 thing you just shot up
it's the crystal vial shard I don't have any room yeah uh listen listen get the magic mirror in
there uh I have one you get that magic mirror I don't have any room I'm out of space I need to
go press the deposit button I know I know I have so much crap I know okay I'm putting the mirror
inside the box I am back okay good okay I'm throwing this on the ground for you it's like a
it's it's a thing ooh
summons a massive crystal spike is it what can I turn into hell burst cast a beam of flame
oh my god our thing's full oh he's gonna get so mad have you been dumping shit in here
there's what oh my god I am mad at you I don't know oh nine cobwebs do you understand
like this this fucking thousands of items in this game and I've never played it before
you brought me to a big dinner you brought me to a huge dinner that has no you brought me to a
buffet I'm at a buffet right now the biggest buffet in the world and you are you happy by the hand
dragging me around you gotta try that you should try that too oh no no no I'm telling
the peach cobbler is so good wait need to come over here though and watch out for the boss watch
up with the monster like like firing yeah there's just aliens and monsters everywhere too but oh
come on no try that have you ever had uh the pizza here I don't I don't know what the pizza is not
try it though it's good I don't know what pizza is you know I'm sorry for you dude he doesn't
even know what pizza is you keep you keep like giving me more stuff to try and there is one
singular throwable spiky ball in here I don't want to go to a buffet I'm scared of the boss
the boss this is like a monster he's got like a chef's hat on I think I'll try I'm gonna try
to make that thing there are 38 musket balls in here what's like what's wrong with you it just
this is one of those games where you just auto pick up stuff and I look I told you if I played
this game by myself the first like three times would be like this is what 10 does I now know
what 10 is I know but I'm saying these things so like because me saying them out loud hopefully
understand why this is stupid in the future there isn't like a copper axe in here we have
five bands of regeneration yeah but I don't know it's it's like I I don't look I don't want to
throw something away and it'd be because this is somebody odd unique items this is what I'm
talking about no you can't make an argument for literally putting two silt blocks in here
there's no defense oh and you're collecting furry tails
I don't have any defense for that but it's because I'm depositing because look go back
I want you to go back to this whole entire like YouTube 75 episode let's play this
every time we come I'm making a point I'm making a point that sucks and there's two of them in here
no but every time we come back to town I have a full inventory and then all of a sudden it's just
like here comes a boss get get out here this is a fucking worm and I'm just like oh shit
that was one time no it's happened like 10 times actually no there were three enchanted
armor and spell books in here there was a two stack and a separate one damn it one I'm trying
to put one in two slots okay I want to make that uh let me see if I can make that what the
hell is it called again I don't know man you got you just like got under my skin there for a second
oh you've been under mine you've been under mine buddy like don't you know I know that when you
like we made this the world of warcraft reference before but if you're like a level 80 in wow
and you convince someone to play world of warcraft and you've done every dungeon before
that person's not gonna know what to do with linen cloth and didn't you can't bring me to
play world of warcraft then you hated every second of it came out and you you literally made fun of
it to a point EPS you and I fucking crushed you no you you you complained for four hours and then
like everybody left the call that's exactly what happened that was the first time that I actually
the first time I was a huge complainer there was like six people in this like team speak call
and over four hours you just see like boom has left the channel this is so fucking dumb this game
sucks like why doesn't everybody play this game and they'll see stealth has left the channel oh
this is so boring this game is so bad two and a half hours later didn't blue has left the channel
it's just me and you in there after like four hours that's not how it happened it is exact
exactly how that actually is not how it happened yes it is no do I get to tell my story or am I
guilty it's just guilty okay do we have a flame lash no where do we get flame lash I want to make
this I don't know what that is google it flame lash terraria flame lash can be made by using the
hell bars do we have any hell bar hell bar you mean hell stone is it like the magma bar
should I make this thing I'm just gonna make it fuck it why not what's it called these recipes
are so obnoxious not magma okay actually I might be wrong I'm sorry please don't make me the one
oh it's all right it's all right how do I make that yeah all right I'm sorry but like oh Jerma
he's like how do you not know all this when there are enough bars in this game so far that equal
an ice cream store worth of fucking flavors I'm sorry this is just the bars
give me a break you can't make the flame lash off it just got real quiet that was weird what's
going on are you here what yeah what this is weird and what you guys hear this it's like too
silent this is always the rain right okay that's freaking me out all right so do we have enough to
do the thing you wanted to the boss thing flame lash is found in shadow chests in the underworld
okay cool put this back I'm gonna just try this though because 26 magic damage that sucks
this is 24 you done crying the sans eye is still the best thing I am not gonna do that
where'd it go oh let me see this I mean it's kind of cool it's kind of like the vile thorn but
it's just a straight line out like that people say we should find a shadow key
do you agree with them all right yeah uh sorry I was looking at crafting recipes okay um
um are you okay with that like are you upset check your check diaper just shake around check
diaper guys there's nothing in my diaper okay I'm gonna shake around there's nothing in here
god okay did you put those souls of light in here yeah there's like nine of them okay we're
fighting a boss tonight drama are you ready yeah I'm not ready I'm not ready
did you not hear that you must not have heard that you would have been no
test I had my volume down for a little bit and also anything that was recent I did not
where's the potion guy oh there he is I have a shadow key no I'm good
clipping do you I kind of want to hear that on my own time though like not on stream
because it was disgusting did he just blow a fart no are you is it you gonna summon the thing over
yeah like give me one second well then fine I'll be like thank you for the 50 dollars to
chunky baloney this is my kind of chunky stream well you are you are chunky baloney nice with 50
bucks 5 000 bits it's a lot of fucking money man can you stop swearing my mother watch that's up
there's a lot of freaking money man okay jerma I'm gonna ask you kindly like one time well
would you kind of yeah help me fight this boss the twins have awoken
are we focusing on one eye right eye or left eye I I don't know we are equally doing damage to
different eyes this is not efficient dude I don't know oh he's got a gun out I don't know got a
cannon dude now that's on top here dodging right there oh I had it I'm gonna get hit at all I mean
these wings I think are like way faster than we're supposed to have at this point in the game
so you should be dodging pretty good
hallowed bar the twins I'm invisible the biomechanical watchers oh no biomechanical
the biomechanical watchers of the night originally afraid as security using the
souls extracted from human eyes these creatures did not belong in this world it's best to be
rid of them place in your inventory to gain invisibility at night I don't like this because
I can't see who I am he said he is on drugs hey all right can you can you do me a favor though
can you confirm with everybody watching right now that this if the if the cameras weren't rolling
I'd be doing the same shit no he puts on a knack no I know you're bullshitting he's a lot more
violent off-screen and verbally stop what were they not supposed to know you want me to lie
you're a liability what are the boss I want we need more hallowed bars how many I think I
I think I picked up some yeah I know but I want more you want more between us we're probably
going to use a lot oh it's this fucking thing again I hate this thing
that thing sucks why would you say that because it's just annoying it just covers the whole
screen and releases like 30 little ads that shoot lasers in every direction yeah so what
you're like sad that you can't avoid all those lasers he's still using sans laser in hard mode
what a casual is that a casual thing to do I want to get you the hallowed scepter thingy but I don't
I don't know how to oh there it is I have um I have 25 I threw it to you I threw it to you
it's you have whether you take these then because I don't like take them did you get them okay I
took them yeah okay 55 magic damage slow speed very weak knockback summons a barrage of enchanted
swords at the mouse cursor's location 56 versus 55 uh the really good thing about that is you can
cast it through walls in the ground which also shows you if you want to find uh nice sources
but also that multi hits like crazy like if we fight that here you know what we're gonna do it
we're gonna fight that boss again just so you can see how much damage you freaking do
okay wow because it hits every single segment with all those that is pretty insane
I just burned all my mana though I hate this thing those hearts everywhere above here I'm
picking them up I'm just starting attacking you I do look very dangerous this thing is
oh did you see the deepest meter at the end there is there a meter you're so far behind me
there's actually an item you can put in your inventory to see your dps but I don't have it
bad because trash because terrible because awful bad trash terrible bad bad game bad player trash
um what can I this I really really like this to a point where I want to see what this can be
turned into I think I think I think we have to kill another is the person is the crafting guy
dead where's uh Jeffrey I think he's actually dead we need to kill another another I don't
have enough hollow bars oh no I do I knew it like they had to be so I threw you like 25 yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah stop yelling what buy the blue juice from the purple wizard guy makes it
so you don't run out of mana yeah I actually had potions before we just kind of have a bunch in
the inventory I'll pick out are we fighting that thing again uh no no okay but is Jeffrey dead is
the crafting guy dead I think so no that's too bad make a mana flower it automatically uses
mana potions went out of mana you know what that is too bad
this guy
dimples a random look at these npcs
like look at this spend medals oh it's just like a board you can just like cosmetic stuff
when am I gonna play dos uh when we're done with terraria oh he's going for a long one tonight
you guys don't worry you're gonna be in a tree right oh pog pog on one pog
enable pog I already have all five of my slots taken up
buy the better man uh who has the mana potions the good ones
not the shitty ones because this is a lesser mana potions does he have any better ones he
only has these ones um I can give you mana potions get rid of the dancing jello guy
78 greater mana potion I don't even know where you got these I don't even understand how you
got these I've been getting them all in the game all right so disable disable like the jello dancing
guy that no one uses that's the first time I think I've seen that since I enabled it so
uh what's going in its place what the fuck what no how about should I enable I think I'm gonna
enable uh maca s is that enabled by default uh no no it's there oh actually yeah there are global
ones wow you're a streamer you don't know you didn't know that either I have a wide assortment
of very good better twitch tv emotes some of them handmade so you better back off
stop acting like you know me all right sure give us pepe face yeah I'll give you guys pepe face
all right holy shit uh I need to go farm in the hollow to make more arrows all right so what
should I do uh think about what you want to craft look if there's any accessories you can upgrade
yep and then what you need to do that okay let's see what we got here we got
the wings but the guy's dead boss we can fight but the guy's dead to like check the crafting
stuff I'd have to like open a web browser in another window oh yeah ooh a tough call there
maybe uh whatever I'll just I'll just go with you uh can you go to talk to popo the potion seller
mr potion the wizard yeah yeah no popo popo it should be his name the guy who sells potions
fizz ban there's nobody in here named bernard bernard the potion seller bernard well how would
you say I'm walking around in circles okay what do you want before he died his name was popo
what do you want I want a battle potion battery potion rates um hold on let me cycle through this
dictionary worth of potions to find it battle potion no I need money first uh there's money in
the storage there should be did you did you make golden platforms from gold maybe why did you do
that the pirates probably dropped them okay you want battle potion shine battles summoning
get some leaves magic power yep uh invisibility inferno hunter heart heart reach battle potions
uh it's alphabetical order I'm an idiot enemy spawn rate all right I gotta hold on here
all right I got it battle potion coming to you coming to you for a smoke break are you just
walking I mean I'm going to very fast I'm true we're fast people now all right all right now
my squash use that pixie dust and unicorn horns okay use I'm using a battle potion now
yeah we just gotta stay around here and kill for like just a second so I can get a bajillion
super arrows and then we can you know it'll be like the old time like the old times uh this
battle potion is intense yeah oh it's unicorn you chainsaw it's a drill I've never made one
before and I never will again this noise is annoying I feel like it's slower that's not
going that fast I think it just seems that way because I'm not swinging it oh rapido
um battle question not doing shit this is kind of terrible increase enemy split you should you
should you take one too I'll go buy one I have I have like six of them oh throw me one
zerg potion can we even get those right now drills are slower and you can't see where you're mining
so they were they just 100% useless why won't germa rechat I just I just did
I just did I just did I'll be right back I'm just gonna kill things and pick them up
this is pretty intense spawn rate okay yeah this this is it this is it this is the shit
are you ready I guess what I'm up with ready for what
what we have to do this for 10 minutes we don't have to do it for 10 minutes
but uh that's how long it lasts oh god does this mean I don't know what are we what are we
there's so many okay I'm just I don't know I'm just picking up stuff
okay yeah this uh I've never done this before this is so good for farming
wow they just like hit a wall cheating watch out behind behind behind behind behind
just so don't despawn just picking up as much as I can what's this I can't believe it actually
spawns this ready how much is this potion there's like 10 gold I think 15 maybe
oh god oh shit and then we can we're getting banners like crazy but I can't put them anywhere
that would help a lot just uh how much money we picking up so too much I just want to stop
and place these banners star has killed his 900 pixie what the seems a little broken
okay okay we can go back now after you kill 900 pixies I think you're done
oh we'll have plenty of pixie dust I'm safe I just stand in the box and hold my clicker here
my clicker oh well you got your 1000 pixie yeah my 1000 pixie
that is like picking up all the stuff I have 10 pixie
okay
we I feel like at least just pick up some of this stuff over here
oops wait 300 blue slime hey I'm feeling like I'm playing Diablo 3 again
ah oh that's not even a joke I really that's just this is what that game turned into
just do nephilim rips and just hold the right mouse button down while numbers explode on your
screen somebody got in I think I'm growing it I want unicorn banners do you have any
I I mean hold on let me get into the safe place it's still five more minutes
hold on unicorn pick up everything and go back I don't even know what they look like
unicorn banner I have two yeah place them on the the ceiling here what is this doing
increases your damage against unicorn that's so dumb this is dumb
what are those is that for pixie's damage oh oh oh oh oh oh it's a blood moon oh it's shit
no oh no no yeah I'm dying too I gotta get out I gotta get out
I can't get out I'm stuck I'm dead there's gnomes
are we safe yeah as long as the doors are shut all right we got a lot of stuff what the hell is
that what on earth star cloak what is going on over here please stop I've had enough of this
getting in
I want to go back to the normal thing we were arguing about
that's the clown uh it's over I mean it's still a blood moon but it's over I don't even have
enough room what is that deadly blood feast or staff I'd need that um uh I don't know what I
I'm sorry I'm gonna have to do this I don't care if you get mad at me what you're dumping all of
your shit you just did a dump you took a dump yeah I mean I'm gonna go back and look at it all
okay the crafter guy is here now too so you can talk to him all you want
there's like all kinds of items heavy blood drinker okay I'm submitting a boss what
okay
tell me say in your best boston accent heavy blood drinker I I don't have a bar I can't even pretend
the game is lagging because I'm trying so hard I'm gonna die all right what on earth
can I even do now yeah in comparison that battle potion wasn't doing so good
okay wow 50 summon damage summons a flesh-eating zombie it's they're not gonna like seek targets
like these things do though no these don't get replaced for a while uh banners banners banners
just a yellow coat that's not you uh you threw all your unicorn horns and stuff in here right
I dumped literally everything in everything in there you can equip the apple you get a mount
where does it go wait where did that just go um that's gonna replace your frog transformation
that's all right is it is it though heavy drinker
I should be yeah do you need the blood drinkers for anything I don't think so can I have two rain
coats on do you want these uh eviscerating claws no I'm not doing throwing anymore we need the
pharaoh's breath for anything no no don't need the carnivore tails don't I'm just I don't care
I'm selling it at this point like what am I gonna do you know what uh here take my drill
for your big axe uh phylactery lich gave 50 dollars and they say Jeremy tell star
thanks for making you play terraria because it convinced me to download it and it's a blast I
just beat calamitas that's that's a big boy he's really been at it oh hey thanks star
thank you uh star for getting me into terraria and thank you phylactery lich for the 50 dollars
thank you star now but that's a huge amount of money thanks a lot that's fucking a lot
5,000 bits every eighth magic cast cost no mana that's I'm I'm getting rid of that you're not
gonna touch this ever again when star finishes it yeah but I'm gonna we're gonna beat the game
I'm going to what what hey guys I'm gonna beat terraria on stream I can't believe you're not
gonna go back to this after you beat it what beating terraria I don't like the way that looks
I want to commemorate the time we killed 1060s in one minute you just gave like an upper a full
upper row of teeth to our building yeah we have to put now make another mouth down here you're
gonna put a bottom row of teeth down there nope we only have a top jaw all right there's a boss
we can fight in the underworld right now well should we I want to put this away and then
this thing you said that the zombies uh suck right yeah
just because they walk around and don't fly true hollowed staff I need a broken hero staff
or twins ire I wonder which one is better the true hollowed staff it looks pretty good true I
haven't used it but the hollowed staff is really good so how hard is it to get a good how hard is
it to get a broken hero step not very we just need to summon the eclipse again I got my mouth
cool all right so you wanted to do the next enemy right yeah I'm not even gonna pick that
shit up on the ground would you go to the left uh we have to go down bagpipe the hell
I just picked up a bagpipe there's been a few of them
no come to hell hey hey jerva
remember that's cool uh I would never use this weapon though giant clam again it's probably
gonna it's gonna do like the mario ground pound down through this whole thing isn't it
what the giant clam no you have to attack it before it'll follow you but won't this my guys just
attack randomly no they don't target it no okay so who's this guy we're fighting in here uh I
don't remember he's a guy I think I've only ever fought him when I was way over way past his power
level I don't know what he actually does we're dropped okay well we got a nice open area here
uh you ready is there anything I need to know about this guy I don't know anything you don't
know anything about this guy oh we're going okay so I'm gonna take my potions let's go
I didn't fuck I didn't get any potions okay uh where's my item I just took them all I got
like two minutes I know whoa he broke the ground there
down in there I don't know what he dropped let's see is this an item or his nasty thermogenic
impaler melee damage uh he this it looks kind of cool you're not laughing you're not laughing
you're not laughing all right get over here I don't look at this this is like what he dropped
he hasn't dropped uh this trailer though that drill I gave to you oh did you yeah you just
didn't want to do my boy I'm like yeah uh yeah he didn't really drop anything I can summon them
again I mean their drop chances are uh I need health don't summon them yet I just stand still
to regenerate I have potions didn't I have them did I just positive things I think I did
do you see this yeah what is that it shows where yeah that's where my cursor is
so you're like don't lose it but you have to waste an equipment slot on I kind of wish I had that
to be honest because sometimes you can lose your cursor very easily yeah but I don't want to use
an accessory slot for like nothing uh I get I'm ready when you are yeah you actually might be at
the point where you need new armor but I don't know if any of the current armors give as many
summons as that one does uh so I don't know which armor would be good for you uh I'm summoning boss
okay lead your targets lead your targets lead your targets that looks elaborate in there
and on it it hurts okay hellstone brick what do you give uh I just got another
impaler demonic bone ash is that worth anything no uh oh well too bad uh stay here stay here
I will aye aye uh try to get flame lash while I'm down here yeah did you say it was in like a
chest or something I want to fight the uh wall of flesh again it drops a couple things we could use
sure the bone ash is an ingredient in the zerg potion okay uh we can just buy zerg potions
so it doesn't matter uh oh it's on the other side that was very very very easy
yeah that's how much stronger we've got corruption key what's that a legendary
poon hammer cursed by a powerful jungle creature this is 0.1 drop hey hey hey hey I got this the
corruption key people are freaking out I have the hollowed key I don't really know where I think you
if I'm correct you have to kill plant terra before you can use any of those
and then they're in the dungeon but not always I actually don't know they're saying go to the
corrupted chest on the dungeon yeah but I think we have to kill plantera first
what was the name of the key corruption corruption key my chat's saying correct well we can start
um preparing to kill plantera we haven't really been to the jungle at all that's the next thing
we really need to do use the key to open the corruption chest in the dungeon after killing
plantera yeah I have two hollowed keys as well
what is this this thing's kicking the shit out of me what the fuck is this thing
what is this thing I'm seriously this guy's kicking my ass um chat rooms what is the best
armor we can get for you right now god damn it oh there was a mimic apparently
petal armor he currently he has the dungeon armor from before hard mode
we're looking for summoner armor sir just ignored you I went back home
you were saying what is this thing which is what you say every 10 minutes so like it wasn't a big
deal I don't know man there was no boss meter the mimic usually it says doesn't a mimic usually have
a boss um health bar yes it didn't have a health bar it had it's just a standard enemy health bar
I'm gonna sell this shit whatever all right the corruption key is in the
stash uh our inventory is full yeah I know you I know you're gonna go in there and you're gonna
you're gonna be very mean to me and I know you are well see it's because you're the one that
fills it and then I have to clean it obsidian rose equipable darth plagas copy pasta was too long
I don't know if that means I need more hollowed bars again potions magic power summoning pot
obsidian pot I mean where's the mana pot life regen max health magic power obsidian skin
regenerate there is magic pot I think we're we actually need more houses because we haven't had
a traveling merchant in a long time I really want this upgrade here for the true hollowed staff
broken hero staff well uh we can do the eclipse right now will I get a broken hollowed staff from
that um yeah really a broken hero staff yeah are you lying to me I'm not no that's what you're
uh the guys aren't selling the thing to summon the eclipse but I know where to get it
I think it might be confusing things are you anyway at night time I need to fight the uh
mechanical bosses again so I can upgrade our storage so it's not always full um who do I
have to give the glacial crystal to I think that guy died like 12 hours ago in game time
oh like this guy earnest right here okay well how do I do it do I have to have it in my inventory
probably oh there he goes hey thank you I think I can give you another quest if you need it
come back later you're welcome what was the point of that adventurers loot box
loot box some good shit in here 20 hollowed bars and it was okay there was a box inside
of the box wait wait you just got hollowed bars from it oh I can't I can't put this
anywhere our house is not big enough we made you made the ceilings as tall as we are I can't put
my because if it's one higher then you have to grapple to the ceiling to talk to people
I got 20 hollowed bars from that box here take them thank you how much can I sell the painting
for nothing okay now our storage goes up to 520 so you can just keep dumping all your useless
shit really thanks all right where we going well now I have all these mechanical boss summons
you do well why don't we get on it it's not nighttime yet very clearly looks like it's
nighttime by the way I don't even have 400 health you don't know um what are you at 360
oh well um then go find a fire heart loser you look like a new all right all right I'm
getting antsy get nancy what are we doing skeleton prime this thing again what why did you
dude I'm gonna die you're looking like a noob right now I'm dead I just took all my potions too
just silently spawned two bosses am I all the way over here why did I spawn over here oh you
accidentally unset your bed probably just worm holding me I'm already pretty much there
oh my god where is he
can you kill him already did you pick up the stuff the other drop boss drop yes
okay dump in storage strange plating huh cool 45 hollowed bars I'm just gonna put I'm just
actually I actually am just gonna dump it in the storage so you can like we have space now until
until we don't um okay
so did you get the thing that you wanted to get from that are you satisfied I'm satisfied what
were we gonna go do after there was a thing after that we're gonna go kill the planet
planetarium or something with corruption key we're gonna go kill planet tiger am do you have I
swear we had this the honey heart honey heart I think I was yes we do not that hold on I swear
we had a sweetheart necklace sweetheart necklace I probably have to make that with the honey heart
well the honey heart's in there I do I need a pass at this necklace I don't know what the
hell to hold on let me see what some of this can I upgrade any more of this stuff
all right what can I do with this 12 increase damage or max minions by three holy shit
how do I make this damn thing I need a papyrus scarab pygmy necklace summoner emblem bottled
water corpse sunlight holy water I think I actually have all this stuff to do this
12% more to do the 12% more damage one the avengers emblem yeah yeah you should
that also upgrades into other things all right soul of might so smite sight fright I don't want
that many I uh sight and fright there's too many things I ever feel like there's just too many
things yeah I'm just gonna have to do this at a different table
there's a secret table I have to do this on there avenger emblem bingo so that's just
plus 12 more damage what's my favorite kk slider song the one where he goes
okay probably that one are you enjoying that huh you enjoy enjoying quacking
there's a you put a fucking grave in here it just keeps getting worse
I remember putting it in too I specifically remember putting it into that buck melee knockback
pickup range 15 magic damage that's pretty good
prime necklace do we have a pygmy necklace I don't know I don't think we do we do not
well for now that's fine all right we got that one now what about this one angry fear monger
wait you're angry at me what did I do there's an uh turn undead I don't want that
I didn't do anything I need to replace that this I gotta I need a better accessory something else
this thing's like why do I have this on do we have any accessories in here that I haven't been
using where do I make chains I think I'd rather have the mana regen what's this
fire damage on attack hmm that sounds interesting let me look at it cross barriers sandstone boots
light underwater I can put this on can I decrease this non-minion damage by 10 percent
do I really care that much I guess I could have more of these out I don't know it's just five
percent damage reduction is really good too I thought that was magic for a second other wait
a minute no I'll just keep on the five percent damage reduction for now yeah okay all right
uh I'm ready to do whatever you want to do next that's trash I don't know hold on I'm
getting on the bottom of this what's wrong oh I do need a honeycomb how do I how do I go down that
route well we don't have a honeycomb they don't have another panic necklace my life is ruined
germa I thought I was gonna be happy you know what's wrong okay let's spawn all my friends
and then from here let's do a dive where's my drill I got rid of it he said it was too bad
we're going to the jungle either way which is far left okay far left do we need the corruption
key because I it's not I don't have it no okay if I pass you I get a thousand dollars host advantage
oh we're here you did not pass me no so I don't do not get a thousand dollars
okay so we need to go down into the jungle oh there's our I'm so fucking mad about that I'm
not paying attention say it again I mean I need you to pay attention right now yeah well I'm
explaining to you yes yes yes I'm ready okay so there's a thing called Plantera's bulb it's like
a little flower that spawns your minions won't auto attack it but when it gets destroyed Plantera
gets summoned okay don't destroy it when we find it we need to make some room don't destroy
the shell also keep green dragon scales and any uh turtle shells you find queen bee
okay certainly have this is just fire right now what do you got anything worth picking up we got
bee wax stinger drop any honeycomb no I'm looking for honeycomb honey just pink gel
a piece of shit I never liked her anyway okay so let's keep going down to find the
Plantera yeah don't real fast I'm looking get that oh yeah we need to get you new armor
we're saying 10 spider nest and then you kill black recluses until you get enough spider fangs
oh life fruit what's life fruit do oh that's really good that increases your max health over
400 it's like the next step really yeah what's that blue for over here is that anything let's see
demonite now what's that this is a palladium
so how obvious is this thing is a huge earth um remember the cysts that we destroyed for the
other boss yeah it's like that okay and also actually even see it on your map really it's a
uh it'll show up as a plank a pink four by four square pink four by four square there's a chest
right there oh I can already mine glorified I didn't realize that also actually you stay here
I'm
a lonker potion show it and all that and they also show life
guys can't get over the diaper candy what the fuck is hitting me what is hitting me thorns
um shotgun I just picked up a shotgun yeah shoot someone you won't you're a little baby
that was kind of crazy
there any reason to use the pick over the drill uh the drill is just annoying
oh we can't even use life fruit yet I think we have to use like going down
too far or this is like new b biome what's that no just it's like a little guy crap
oh we're gonna queen bee so need my honeycomb I see honeycomb I see it unless that was something
else I think I'm out of no room you didn't get any drops from it I think I'm out of space
I got everything but I did not get honeycomb uh tin ore get out of here
I have seeds I need that right should I eat the heart now but should I wait
oh you can't eat it yet wait you need to get 400 health and then there's some other step
that I'm not I think I know what it is let's throw the bomb it would be really easy to get 400 health
by the way if you want to go do that while I'm looking for the bulb um where's the best place
to get that the fire stuff uh so you go down to hell then go left okay you know how there's
like a ceiling to hell yes they kind of there's five flame hearts that just kind of line the
ceiling uh I had been left and right and gotten a lot of them so a lot of them are gone but it's
just above hell very slightly okay so just get down to hell yeah go left though I I got more
from on the right than I did on the left what's that there's no hearts in here I put the um I put
that life the the life root it's in the storage is that one oh I found a bulb find blazing hearts
all right I'll go do that I'm going to hell I wait what you did I just assumed I was at full health
apparently not I want like some red glows on you know how like you get shot very much appreciate
that so you're saying get down to hell and then go left and just look for them the ceiling above
hell so like if you're on the platform you're not going to be able to see it you kind of have
to check the ceiling they're like very they're like right there let me see what you mean by that
let's see if I can figure it out because this is hell right I think I'm in there I think I'm
at hell now right is that not quite the place with all the lava yes at the bottom
yeah I know but but like is hell very large yeah people say no go further down oh yeah yeah all
the way at the bottom okay all right so then you say go left um why can't I jump okay I'm good all
right looking for blazing hearts I'm on it dude I love Edward Elric I just found the philosopher's
stone did you very cool man that's very cool I just love Eddie I wish that he would come to me
and show me what it means to be a boy you just like said words you won't even think you just
said words out loud you didn't it doesn't matter what they were exactly call that word soup oh my
god Edward L for looking for it what happened you couldn't put the fire out fire oh I can't
stand on those right all right okay never mind yeah forgot about that yeah maybe next time put
the fire out all right let's do it again die again this weapon is not fun underground
don't I can't stand for some reason I just thought they were the same material here
almost got me again with that little trap door all right do not stand on these it doesn't work
that way I kind of need to go over here though what is it can I even do anything over here
I'm gonna go up where's my rope oh yeah oh I should hydrate it by now I haven't drank water
all day have you really not what's wrong with you yeah I mean I had a little nothing anything
up in here nothing up in here um it's possible that I got them all I think if we also have
all stone you can you can craft them I mean there's probably some somewhere but like if you went to a
different world and it got down to hell really quickly you'd find them immediately is all I'm
saying a lot of cool things in here yeah we just like went to our own separate servers and like
didn't play together well there's definitely nothing else here heart statue does that do
anything some just do things but no just ignore them now anybody see anything I don't see anything
all right all right nothing but there are some magma blocks up here that I'm gonna get
like I was just saying if you're desperate just mine health stone like if you really can't find
anything I'm sure I gotta go further over this way I'm gonna accidentally summon plantara isn't
that on you not on me yeah what what yeah I can't summon plantara down here I said I I swear I'm
going to accidentally summon planter and then you were like already got defensive
don't make me laugh not when there's all lava underneath me it wasn't a joke it was like
the court recording of what happened this uh magma turtle worth anything
to a zoo I have no idea what do they look like you'll you'll know when you see it
it really is like a heart with a I know I know I know right I I'm just being an idiot
okay what do they look like you got me can't mine this I don't even know why I'm mining
chlorophyte because I don't think any of us are gonna use it these are really helpful though
just like peruse an area let's go up I'm thinking up yeah so one heart is 20 health right yeah
if you found any I just need one more okay I'm at planter's bulb one more we'll do it
dude diapers lol I'm not saying it
ow found it got one okay teleport to me now I gotta get it first blazing heart
teleport to you I need to go back to the base first that's important
I also found this weird like ribbon candy storium
all right let's go back where's this diaper thing
it's a good joke all right so permanently increases life by 10 I thought you said it
gave me 20 oh I just assumed well I need two more apparently well we can do that after
I can do that later and again you can craft it with hellstone and we should have the stuff
to do that I would look into that before you go on another goose chase hellstone brick or hellstone
like no no not brick right hellstone bars lava bat banner no I thought that was bacon do you
need uh hermes boots or anything I just put them in the storage no link root seeds trash trash
what about the mario hat auto trash and actually is a mario hat 20 restoration posters that's not
bad all right I am ready to come back to you to do the thing that you want to do here oh and boy oh
boy do I want to do this thing with you okay so I'm going to teleport to you once I get a wormhole
potion wormhole potion and I am coming ready hi hi fly up here
I'm gonna finish this and we could probably just start it I think are strong enough
to not have to worry so this thing is scary uh a little bit this is our up and down safety net so
kite it up and down rather than across the plank and I need some open space there for my bow to
even work look diaper check ban the word diaper I end this nightmare ban the word diaper add diaper
to like the not show up in the chat let's just do it you better be ready I'm ready weird that they
always go for you
but I got to the om part that was really not that hard yeah no it's falling oh mo
oh that was it's oh no with an m apparently a temple key what's that uh temples the next
thing we have to do that's actually we should do while we're here if your inventory isn't
uh I just got rid of everything okay well then we need to find the entrance to the temple which
is that like the bottom right of the jungle usually okay uh do you get anything else
let's see uh energy core honey block bloom weave bud bomb plantera uh boost item grab range
rocket living shard temple key quick grenade launcher this thing is insane
I think it uses a grenade ammo other than that not really I don't think
oh yeah now illuminate so we're just gonna kind of dig down to stay within this area
yeah it's like the dungeon but the bricks are like orange that's it right here oh all right
but we can't dig through it so we have to find the actual front door
I'm assuming the front door is uh down oh no it's at the top top oh just keep going to the right
I'm mining this stuff I'll be with you oh this is it right here the door is in lava
uh there can we do anything about that uh you can take a little bit of damage
or if you have a lava immunity charm on you I don't how do we open the door you're gonna
have to dig through the obsidian walk to the lava easy easy oh wait wait wait wait wait wait let's
do this I threw a grenade down be careful okay grenades don't hurt people don't go down there
that's like a really bad construction yard
hey watch out don't go over there yeah we're also gonna have lunch underneath it
okay you just need to man up and go open the door
ah okay okay wait wait wait wait wait what what what's going on what do you mean wait
everywhere there's like the walls are shooting at you right now okay just chill just chill
okay the enemies down here kind of hurt there's a whole bunch of them there's spikes along the walls
full inventory ammo what are you lizard door I don't want a lizard door I'm so mad that I have
this I'm just getting rid of all this shit fuck this stuff what oh what's going on here
okay the one thing you really need to watch out for down here is there's spikes that shoot
there's dart traps but also there's these like spike things that drop from the ceiling
and they bounce up and down and they do a lot more damage than it looks like they do
got it and then there's a boss one at the bottom how do we how do the traps activate though
that's the big question for me floor pressure tracks that are very hard to see
if you like you see those faces on the left wall on the right wall
these two little blocks these are trapped by the way dude I just I just walked over here in my
inventory got full again like you know this is insane this is too what do we do with this stuff
I got 50 100 rockets if you're being used I don't know what I don't know what to do
you understand go back to the base go back to the base recall put your stuff in the storage then
wormhole back to me and then we can stop arguing it's insane it's it's too many things to have to
keep track of um some of the one of these things is really really good though it was a lot of
damage what was it I was in my inventory magic dagger insanely fast attack speed
I'm coming what oh god what did I do I press b wins goss after this is it safe to go in here
what is safe to go in here yeah just be very careful I'm just not touching the ground
oh see those are the spikes healing things I'm just standing up here
could you describe what was going on right now to somebody that didn't that doesn't know what's
going on um we're inside the lizard temple that has been closed for centuries
and we're we're here to you know stop the prophecy
mm-hmm as best we can what is this duck quacking song those are the lizards oops
we're also they drop a very specific item oh no there's chests down here that we need they
usually have the thing in it I can't open this because I'm already in it yeah I don't have any
space open that chest and top left there's a power fragment which is what we need to fight the boss
okay uh power fragment this is lizard power cell yeah I'm gonna make a
horrified arrows I think we have a lot of that stuff now he doesn't look at chat anymore
all right I'm gonna be real the last probably 25 times I looked at chat there was probably
eight messages saying like look at something there was like a diaper comment what what can
you say your chat loves diapers so that's you should do like a sponsored deal with like a
diaper company so what are we doing with that altar over there we are clearing the room of
traps first so just activate all the traps no you have to like actually pickaxe and destroy them off
the wall oh don't worry you just wait I'm doing it I'll do it I can do it oh look out a spider
okay so uh this one thing is up here you want the explanation or you want to be surprised um
go ahead and uh just what should I be aware of uh it's a big rock man big rock this it jumps up
into the air and tries to land on you the first phase is fairly self-explanatory don't get jumped
on and then the golem's head pops off and flies around and shoots at you okay I'm ready okay you
need to go use the solar fragment on that altar for the power cell oh Jesus well he was just gonna
land here this is this uh the mario 64 guy okay and once we destroy this his head pops off in
that weapon is pretty terrible for this so what you would be targeting here like what
should be fucking oh there's a body oh I'm in pain too
oh fuck I touched a trap oh I think both died in the same place I'm I'm all my fucking things
are hitting the ceiling I'm doing half the time nothing like if I dodge then I can't hit him
oh well oh well we tried oh well we tried uh this thing looks kind of ridiculous demonic
spearman 89 melee damage attacks apply a stacking poison you should take a look at this yeah it's
really good but nobody's a melee boy did you say you wanted this this glorified stuff bullet
glorified bullet glorified uh glorified arrows fake coin solar pebble um I think it makes decent
stuff I forget you'd have to look it either makes decent stuff or it makes nothing what about a dual
hook uh garbage here take this new pickaxe new pickaxe pickaxe axe kind of redundant so is this
a pickaxe we never made you that armor either did we it's both oh okay so I can just get rid of
this other one uh no I still have the same armor that I had from a while ago it's pretty good um
we can go kill spiders I want to go grab my gold I dropped like 50 gold we need that power self
right so I should take keep it yeah it's easy to get a few more there they all drop it how
we doing on potions let me see what else do I want summoning potion mana regen potion regen
potion yeah give me more of these why you fuck off summon your dudes they're not here yeah you
done
get this math five of these
those iron skin get those already have here regen rage potion yeah just get it just be a psycho
look at these wrath potion yeah I'm just gonna I'm gonna just load the fuck up
freeze damage by 10% just get like five of them titan thorns
all right I believe I am ready to do this again are you ready to do this again you can start
going there and I'll be able to teleport on you I have a few things to do okay so we need to go
down we gotta go left so I'm just gonna start flying oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait what is it did you get living shards in front her uh I think they're in the yeah they're
in the um it should be in the box all right let's a little bit further so down down down down down
okay let's go no go oh what is this bloody I'll take it holy shit this mine's fast
yeah oh my goodness is this like the end of the this is late game uh there's still some more
pickaxes how is that even possible it gets wild there's like rideable drills that you can just
destroy in a while what the fuck is going on in this chat room
what are you guys what there's like people like panicking in here
why can't you guys just relax oh shit queen bee queen bee queen bee we'll need honeycomb go get it
never honeycomb uh terraria yeah we're just kind of hanging out playing terraria um kind of getting
like a little bored though in chat oh I know I'll just start spamming diaper fuck owo
that sounds like a plan the way to go man shout out to all the diaper fuck
what you guys even fucking relax is it over here it is how many people in your chat do you think
actually wear diapers or like people that wear diapers and got offended by this joke and like
zero this no zero absolute 100 zero oh okay well now that you're a denier the guy definitely got
zero dude nobody is here what's so funny about you ever wearing a diaper when I wear one every day
I'm trying to like get away from this I'm trying to get us away from it my chat is in emote only
mode because they've lost their minds dude how do you all right are we talking politics in the
chat too how do we go from like diaper talk to let's talk about like the current state of like
the republican party did diapers affect the economy the uh everything really the environment
biodegradable diapers affected all it gets serious all right um I'm kind of there
we don't need just to be clear we don't need those like light crystals right
life crystals I don't just the regular the default ones I don't think so
all right I've made it you're there I'm here yes
you're not in the boss room keep going well I didn't say I was in the boss room I said I was
like here I'm trying to go like too fast I'm getting hurt but in self only mode
so yeah that's not gonna help oh my god it's your fault I don't get what the big deal is
you know okay I gotta sit here for a second you die you can get one more heart crystal
uh I think I need to be blazing hearts though don't they they do fucking inventory's full
well I have another life root just wait did you die no every banner I'm throwing in the trash
I never want to pick a banner up ever again that's kind of a green dragon skill yeah keep those
inept blood feaster I don't want this like annoying blood drinker I don't want a superior
blood feast that looks pretty good but it's not good enough I'm leaving a trap for you
because you're going to run down here and like touch it all
okay here's my item trap that you're gonna like get full because it's here
uh well I'm just gonna teleport to you and skip the trap
that's true okay uh I am like I'm like pretty much there I'm like there are you there are you
pretty much there I mean I'm I'm literally standing right outside at the front door out here
all right don't let's not I don't want to summon this yet because I want to make sure I take my
potions and I have full health okay that okay hold on let's get that full HP okay okay you
created us this is because I didn't create you guys okay Star what do you do when your chat gets
bored and they start well my chat my chat is always bored that's the trick oh god all right
not won't be long now okay I will be ready do you have the material or do you want me to use it
uh I don't have one you have one I do I'm just waiting I'm ready okay I'm going to take my
potion yep summon my other guy here we go okay and three two one here we go
um
he's dead Pixar pickaxe and Pixar too oh this is better uh you have one of these
uh yeah I got a pixel oh yeah okay I just made the core fight pickaxe I didn't I forgot that this
one was they instantly give it to you for free and it's better okay come here take this life
fruit you're a life fruit what's uh next up we keep going down uh no I'm grabbing the altar
we want ads we guys don't you understand every time I've tried to run this is my channel is
broken every time I run an ad on my channel the dashboard tells me failed ad it doesn't work
I can't run an ad I think that's advertisers don't want to be involved with you is that what
that is yeah that means you've like severed every tie I can play an ad if you really want to watch
if you play an ad does it say ad failed please try again later I've never done that I'm gonna
do one right now I'm gonna do it right now ad break run a ad ad it's playing oh fuck it is
playing that's the first time it's ever done that I swear to god no no I don't want to eat
fucking ad you got Geico oh nice I got a pizza rolls commercial oh Geico's better
their commercial's so good hey welcome back everybody
do another one I can't physically can't do that
did you do 30 seconds yes I did you should have given them one hour of ads do a three
minute ad break and have my view count drop by like 1500 people you'd be surprised how many
people aren't even at their computers right now in your viewer count who's this little guy
jack skellington rescuing green counterweight what yo yo yo yo yo glove you can use two yo-yos
at the same time 50 gold for this shit it's really good if you use yo-yos I guess does he
just go back on his own yeah this guy's cool I think I need to make houses so what's the I'm
like what's the goal here what do you mean what kind of a current mission are we on
that's gonna that's lava and it's gonna I'm I'm mining stuff because I have a full
the current goal is to get you the better summoner armor which you have to go kill those spiders for
okay I'll be back and I totally found oh we also we can go open the uh corruption chest
because we killed flying terror we need the key right yeah I do have I have the corruption key
is the one we need is that correct yeah also grab the hollow key there are two hollow keys
I'm gonna bring them both you haven't looked at the game in an hour what oh you missed something
huge man I wish I could tell you it was great this alien landed the spaceship behind us
and that actually I like knocked out the alien missed the ad yeah there was an ad
there was like a samsung galaxy ad all right I'm pretty much ready to do whatever I've got my
friends are you though yeah I've got both keys I'm ready to open some boxes on camera uh start
walking back to the temple place where we just were no to the right to the dungeon to the duel
with a dungeon I know what that is I've been there a few times yes okay I've made it to the
chest piece dungeon is over here this is kind of epic thanks man my game is lagging I hear the
noise and then it does it lag lag is funny what is whoa what's going on in here the dungeon has
like new people here oh yeah because it's hard mode oh there's a big globe there's like a big
coin ah there's like I there's a lunatic you fucking activated the lunatic cult I don't know
what that means what does that mean I don't know what you're talking about do you understand
I forgot that you wouldn't know and you would go there and you would just kill them because
you think it's Diablo 3 well I'm still alive good luck I'm busy what happens if I do spawn
him I don't know actually also I don't even think we want to kill him because when you kill him
the pillars spawn and it turns your game into a fucking nightmare is he still on me
he's not is he no okay zero um we're gonna have to find another way to get into the dungeon
because he's gonna be standing there you just walk by him you just walk by him if you don't
kill them all you just walk by him um but my I have guides that just attack I can't stop them
you can summon them I guess you're right I guess you're right yeah I think so that was snail
oh no it's not earth elemental okay that was me there's nothing here anymore all right I'm
in the dungeon okay I'll be there in one second I'm making myself armor armor how far down just
all the go all the way down uh you're just looking for that specific chest that hopefully
doesn't crash in multiplayer oh it's that chest it's like the blue one no it's not that blue one
there's a lot of different types of chests down there is it will I know it when I see it is it
big what is it I I don't know what it looks like oh okay don't touch the blue ones people are
freaking out don't touch do not touch the blue ones yeah we we did that already here we already
did that accident one it's all right it looks like a key so it looks it's kind of like a claw
a monster hand or something like purple and yellow um what the fuck was that and why did it
all right looking around trying to find it you'll know it when you see it all right
there's a spawn of also um there's also like uh snake ladies snake they won't attack you if you
don't fight them and they're a little bit stronger than everybody else um you have to
remember I have these guys should I just show I don't want to on some of them though they're
doing a great job doing killing stuff um I think they won't attack them oh oh shit I can make this
right wait I thought I had a panic necklace and I don't I can almost make this is that it
that's it no what's that icon that's a weird icon here should I not touch this one
wrong one that's a different key oh okay so well the key will pop up like that uh I think I found
the snake lady so don't attack snake lady you said uh you don't have to I mean you can but
she's a bit stronger okay I'm gonna take that as a do not it's gonna be hard because there's
all these idiots in this room all right don't attack oh fuck dude how do you hey chat how do
you create a crimson biome in this world so I like you don't have to leave that's how you
get panic heart oh I'm just getting juggled right here oh fuck I'm gonna die I'm dead I'm gonna die
I'm dead I'm dead are you no um I will be in a second give me like one second I'm making
like a super necklace I have no my healing potions are on cooldown no I I literally just clicked on
you to teleport to you as you died literally a fucking like I had like zero health and I
went down I was trying to use that thing as light and I aggroed one of the fucking snake ladies
with like five hearts I told you not to aggro the snake ladies I couldn't help it I was trying to
see where I was going god damn it quite clear about yeah and she was off screen and I was
going like this to see where I was going so I could get quick what the hell what the hecky
I almost had it too I was moving around pretty good too until she threw frozen orb at me
and it filled the whole hallway I was in and it did like six hearts hey you by chance didn't see um
you know on your way over there wait why are you why are you going that way I'm just looking for
one place real fast uh where there is like crystals in the background and aliens
crystals and aliens I have no idea what you mean why can I not use this it's near the dungeon I
guess who the fuck is plague ringer oh it's nothing I got him I don't know what any of
this stuff is really useful stardust I feel like that's gonna be useful at some point
what about this ectoplasm ectoblood or anything I'm just gonna say sure
a tally counter who cares I'm so disappointed right now I really was like doing just fine
I still I have greater I need like greater healing potions where do you get those uh you
don't start getting them till after oh okay so I'm not supposed to have them no the ones that heal
200 the max I think we have right now is 150 unless there's crafting that can be done or
potion seller sells them I don't think he does I remember that all right I don't want to use the
unicorn because I can't just fly and go like this welcome hello somebody said I should buy the tiki
armor is that worth it uh I don't know what it does for what it is there's a lot of items
you need to get a freaking it's worth it for you to get the uh spider armor just do a zerg
potion in the oh this is it this is the thing you walked through it you didn't even say anything
I said you didn't hear me just say I walked over it apparently I would I said I was I walked over
I didn't I was talking to my chat I need I need 25 stardust not all these enemies drop
time for a zerg potion are you really gonna do that yeah I've had this stardust in the box
I picked up a bunch of it yeah
there's 10 how much do you need every time I've gotten more than 10 or 20 you're like well you
got way too many how many do you need I need a thousand have fun farming I don't need very many
I need 25 whatever you're holding right now is probably enough uh it is two I put like 10 in
the box and I just said I got 10 from the box why are you laughing oh yes you did I you I said
two and you went you did a laugh stifle well because you'd been here the whole time I thought
you had more and two just like I just got here I flew back over here remember I died I go to
the dungeon go die in the dungeon again oh one of these guys cultists no don't kill them though
for real like don't actually do that all right this time I'm gonna be ready this time it's gonna
be a different story yeah I'm ready I'm gonna go down and I'm gonna find it I'm gonna make sure
I'm smart about it do not I'm not gonna use that thing for light because of the the the potential
for disaster with the I was gonna say molasses lady but it's uh it's medusa lady making my way
over here not a big deal everything's fine we're gonna head this way gonna check it out
over there ain't nothing in there not a big deal not a big deal yeah I can't see
them hello that sound my bow is weird my ox um get out of my way
oh so it looks like what does it look like I'm pretty sure we'll know it if we see it
apparently um you can hover over and determine what goes into that thing right so we don't want
to go that way well that's where I died over there yeah I died over there these necromancers
too are awful they really bother me am I like to have a slow debuff or something why would you
ever have that in a video game like I why I have a slow debuff in any video game I don't know
I'm sorry that it makes you angry okay oh my god well this place sucks oh yeah actually also
these ectoplasms and stuff I have been picking her up yeah they do things as well as the night
alloys from paladins you guys hurt you not so much I need a second so like is there a faster
way to regen if it is use my potions um a regen potion bacon kind of stuff a lot of hearts in
there yeah remember we can we can just go through their walls now and uh in this place
also you're you're you seriously are getting hurt as badly as you're getting hurt because you have
really old arms you really need to really yeah well I'm just gonna buy the tiki armor everyone's
saying tiki tiki tiki I'm like all right don't open that one not that one it's not this one oh
it's not no careful I'm not a joke anymore this is hard have you found any uh gold keys uh I have
hollowed key corruption key and okay oh I should pop a a uh a certain potion down here right I
don't think you should do that but and I just want you there is a gold chest over there
another one of these wait what is that hollowed key is it a hollowed chest got it come to me
I'm killing an idol on hold on is this it that's it oh what the fuck is even hitting us
there's a dark trap on the big booty there's a rainbow gun and a bone welder
oh good I've never opened one of these
I want like a man to reach it and shit I got a million oh what have you done
what have you done what did you just ran in here I just flew she's flying up here get out of here
lady I'm so glad I took those potions let me see the items ah hold on get wait a second
what you and I both have like one health can I see what you picked up
I don't know I'm scared you're on fire you're gonna die I'm not on fire
how am I on fire what I think you're poisoned actually oh it was poisoned well here's a rainbow
gun and a bone welder used for special crafting oh bone welder's dumb it's dumb yeah oh this thing
just stays in place that's pretty good how many can be out at once one or more than one I don't
know I can only make one can I do it twice well yeah that's still really good to just shoot once
I'll take it if you don't want to use it it's all just fire at once and go back to what I was doing
it is magic damage technically all right what can you turn it into hold on I want to see what
crafted into cosmic rainbow barrage of rainbows you need meld bar core of calamity and five bars
of life that's you can do that after um like right before the final boss cool that's got the
achievement um I guess you can just fire that once and whatever yeah you can you take it you can use
the hell else is here you sounded disgusted when you said that blue brick do I do something
wrong all right the ecto blood and the ectoplasm I've been picking it up and putting it in here
you said we needed it right uh yeah uh because that makes specter bars dark matter
wait wait chat chat does specter bars make a summoning armor for germa how do I do that
makes magic oh he's right there he's going he's going for it he's doing it faster than you guys
are sorry oh this is important all right whatever you can hold on to it dark steel core
I feel like this stuff might be good for somebody someone somewhere you said bone welder sucks uh
we already have one we already have no we don't it's just you can make like doors out of bones
that's all it is and actually yeah we do have one right here I'm pretty sure is that it
jerma get figure out this tiki armor or go get the fucking spider's shit okay tiki armor who
sells it who sells the tiki armor tiki guy I know where a spider area is we can just go do it
no I don't know I want the tiki on them okay they're in it's the witch doctor in the jungle
you have to build a house in the jungle to get him no we have the witch doctor where he's
underneath us he's in the reject housing
where is that right here yeah okay I think I found it
uh imbuing station mantis cane he only sells this shit if he's living in the jungle
how do we move this guy in the jungle you have to build a house in the jungle and then there's a
button that can tell you who to tell someone to live there okay so I just gotta make a square in
the jungle with a door and then say I want this guy over here yeah let me let me figure out the
recipe for the um instant house um why do I not have this scary mask increases your minion size
by 150 percent and 10 more minion damage I don't know get it why didn't you have it
it's 90 gold all right I'm telling you I'm gonna get this why didn't you have it
dad didn't even know it existed that's not an excuse I think it is actually okay where's that
gold there we go I'll take a hundred of it no more than that I'll take a hundred it's fine you only
need the pigby staff in your inventory they had people saying don't listen to chat they're wrong
do we have a pigby staff I've never seen one I mean if I found one I would have destroyed it
one percent fucking melee speed really I have to go reroll this bewitching table we already have
one of these right uh we can fight plantera again to get it I can get the portable oh shit this isn't
what I thought it was summons plantera so what we want you want to fight plantera again I mean we
can do that yeah should I just go find a bulb though it's right here this is 20 gold portable
oh okay do you want to fight plantera I mean if if all I need is this if if if plantera drops
the pigby staff that's all I need to go like and buy it whatever he has uh hold on I don't they
would I don't think this is this is not a jubade I don't think they would do this to me right now
oh where's the guy that rerolls yeah yeah you need the pigby staff that's so much money to
reroll this it costs one platinum and 50 gold to buy the armor set is this no so is this this
this actually I know how sometimes it's like it's an accessory but it's a mask it's it's just and
it's an it's actually an accessory so I'm gonna have to remove the uh the fear monger all right
10 million damage minion size let's see how big they are now oh my god this is gonna be obnoxious
you're not gonna want to know you're not gonna want to need to you're gonna have hate standing
near me okay yeah so 25 chance to drop from plantera look at how big these are that's it
there's a there's a summon later that you can get after um after the cultists and you do some other
stuff that every time you summon it adds to the length of a dragon right so it's just one big
long dragon depending on how many summons you have it would look pretty funny that big what did I just
do what'd you just do I don't know I deleted a hunt I deleted 100 fucking coins somehow
that's pretty good how's that possible what just happened
you do it again you show me how you do it well I do I think I just oh I made a platinum coin
oh yeah no platinum is 100 gold oh okay they just like kind of scared the shit out of me all right
I'm gonna buy the other thing don't throw
okay wish we fight this then can I have some of it anywhere I just try and do it here you I think
we have to be in that jungle to fight plantera yeah so I also bring more than one that doesn't
say that it just says port of bulb doesn't say anything about needing to be anywhere yeah but
I'm pretty sure you do like I mean are you just gonna trust me or are you just gonna keep like
why don't we just fight it up here okay summon it here jerma is that oh don't do that everyone's
losing no jerma do it summon it like click it and see how it works um no no no I've been told
what's gonna happen so it enrages outside the jungle okay that's good to know thanks guys
appreciate that I don't want this fucking thing all right so how much money do I have I don't have
any money that's good touch the summon table and make sure I get everybody out and let's go to the
jungle which is over here I'm on my way we are your bad conscience so is this technically the
jungle like in here this is the jungle right like right here no no not where I'm standing currently
they like over here no no it's actually the third time you've asked that while standing in that spot
so so I was just trying to be clear who's this it's just some guy just some there's some guy
come and fight me it looks like what the beat what'd he drop nothing actually nothing
oh he drops plague canisters and I think they're for crafting nothing
all right so you want to just fight where we fought when jera last time yeah
let me fight down here yeah I don't know these idiots is over here now
oh
plague canister here's a here's an actual plan terrible so we can do this fight yeah so
stop here this is the third one I'm gonna fucking die down here aren't I
you can't die to plague bringer you died a plague bringer it's over I'm gonna I'm dead I'm gonna die
plague bringer because I got hit by poison or some shit I don't even know what it was
I'm dead I died didn't even die to plague bringer I died to the melter
no I died I died to the to the to the overwatch ultimate that's on the screen constantly the whole
game when you complain about overwatch and you don't even play it complaining about overwatch
transcends that was free that was for your chat I'm dead yeah you're dead too yep I died from
full health I touched a pressure plate there was an explosive I didn't see it I'm dead
trapper bulb by plantera at spawn well that would be the end of this portion of the stream
I need mud you got mad I dropped 40 gold there so you got really mad at me for putting mud in the
inventory box yeah look at this there's mud in here I need mud don't you wish I was still doing
you know how easy it is to get mud you tell me you know what you think you're so tough
summon plantera in the house and then leave the game
and then I'm banned from the server forever that would be such a stupid move no I'm not
going to do that why is that just that seems to be like the majority general consensus in
this chat right now is to do that no really no you know what you must do I'm going back down
here let me guess we have to fight three more of those like undead bees why you have to be mad
because I am it's only game I am in that spot where we were
okay if you want to come to me I will be ready to do whatever you get against
building a quick house building a quick house there's an NPC I know we need and that is
definitely not here I'm missing a fucking chair I can activate activate plantera right now we're
no balls no I want to I want to get this item I don't want to just cause the game to be a hard
game I wanted to get the staff so I can get the tiki armor so then we can go beat oh here's a
bulb there's a bulb I have one in my inventory already but let's do this one can you handle
doing this without a rope setup I don't know is this gonna be right here I guess I just go
for it I guess let's go that was a no probably not I'm ready where do you really need to get
oh are you okay I'm remembering that this actually so you can get here
fucking stuck in the goddamn wall oh this is bad please go down please go down please go down
please go down good luck just kill it I killed him staff nope nothing I got a vuvuzela
yeah all right well let me just get my shit together I wish I had the bagpipe
uh I can summon plantera again
heal up yeah I just have to just sit here
the band
I have apples that's it
oh my god I thought it was a plantera I hate this guy I really do he's not even that hard
he's just annoying did he die yeah he's dead I need to regen I even have the regen potion
equipped right now I'm eating it all right so I don't even I don't even understand
it's actually we need to go kill the uh I'm still getting for you I'm taking like times
three damage right now and I have to take you are who's fault is that I just want to fucking
regen this thing sucks make a campfire do you have any wood can you make like a campfire
he's listening to me oh sorry I'm muted I put a workbench here I was trying to do it and I don't
think I have the things to do it I forget what you actually need uh a campfire yeah I only have you
would all right I think you're not letting me use that I'm ready I'm gonna summon ready
now is it to use the item that's it just consume it yeah yeah oh yeah get that thing out here
where's it oh it's over there all right give me the staff staff uh I don't think so
man uh nimble seedler damn it what's the drop rate on the stuff 25 you only brought one
I mean it was 20 gold you want to spend like 100 gold on
bulbs fairly expensive wouldn't there was one on we went by one here yeah we went by one up here
didn't we look further up this way I remember there being one like up in the beginning I see
it on the map I love jupiters me too that's why I have it as an emote there's only one jupiter how
could you love jupiter you're ready not yet let me get up there well once I summon I'm going back
down um all right go ahead and go okay down the front oh it's above us staff staff oh yay
you got one take me staff all right I don't think it actually needs to be in the jungle so
teleport back and go talk to witch doctor just to double check if it does I'll build a house here
oh that's 67 summon damage summons a pygmy to fight for you is that good I thought I just
really I could reforge it right yeah let me just go talk to them let me bring some money too
uh anybody knew how you like if there's a reliable way to find your mushroom biome
okay tiki mask tiki shirt tiki pants axe number of minions
minion damage and oh okay this is much better five seven and six six seventeen and twelve
I mean this is just so much better and what's the set bonus on this this is expensive
save the painter he's fine okay so I'm gonna buy it all tiki mask tiki shirt and I have to come back
with more money for the tiki everyone that lives up here is dead the painter survived
huh oh yeah remember when everyone up here died and they're saying to save the painter
he's safe down there he's doing just fine those are all the npcs we want to be the safest
well it's actually good that this guy's alive still and by the way I don't think there's enough
money I need 10 more gold I have a potion oh I have I have gold wait I can turn can you
can you turn the platinum oh okay save the painter save the painter he's gonna be fine
tiki paint all right anything else that I could get from this guy no probably not all right I'm
gonna go back up and look at all this shit so uh I'm gonna let's go in here tiki pants cool
tiki mask shirt increases your max number of minions increase your max number of minions
max number of minions minion damage 30 percent how many how many can I have now
let's see what it looks like uh I uh I gotta look I don't uh yeah I'm ready I um I think I need
normal wood you want to say I'm gonna cut trees down all right now let me see that stuff
this is 58 65 if I've re-rolled this I can get rid of that junk but I might I'm gonna re-roll
the damage aren't I plus 20 you re-roll everything re-roll everything how much better are the other
pygmies I've never used it
I mean one two three four five six seven eight nine ten I can have ten of these
one two three four five six seven eight nine ten this this is cool
let's go you I wanted to use them look at that we have to I've been doing the ice claspers for so
long let me just play with my like lemmings for a while play with your Pikmin yeah I'm gonna play
with all my Pikmin yeah I'm absolutely gonna use this we're ready and now that I did that
I'm still gonna use this this thing is just even though it's only 26 damage I feel like it's still
the best thing I've picked up I want to we have not made we have not come across a broken staff
right the hero broken hero stuff I need one of those broken hero staff where do you get that
I'm gonna get like lost in all these people so I need like a way to make it so I can differentiate
myself okay I'm the one with the raincoat on I'll get I will actually get stuck so
show a solar eclipse can we activate a solar eclipse star sorry I'm muted uh I think the
tablets that we found in the lizard area allow you to combine together to create an eclipse so
look for the tablets inside the tablet storage solar tablet fragment that would be yeah I think
you need four and then you can summon one eclipse it has to be daytime really uh it is and then I
conserve potion and then we'll get it for sure okay so I can yeah it's it's eight of these fragments
to make a solar tablet to summon an eclipse so just make a couple of them yeah well we're
really gonna need one okay but they're not used for anything else as far as I remember
well I'll just make one I'm not even using these grenades what is this shoddy heavenly tail
just pick this up randomly outside built a house in her house
I love these guys painter can't even leave now I'm loving it yes I'm not yeah I don't care if the
other ones are better these ones are more fun all right this looks good should I reroll this
I'm gonna reroll this one percent melee speed is absolute dog shit and we have money I have enough
money to do it once one percent melee speed like come on that's terrible here we go one two three
well um better than I guess better than it was before okay I got the tablet what do I
my potions let me see these things like suck I'm getting rid of these
let's sell a wormhole I need to buy a new potion what do we have potions in here we got a ton of
things in here greater healing potions take them ancient ice chunk I'm gonna store this for now
stars who needs them all right summoning potion that's what I want take them all
night owls shine splinter here we go mana regen generation potion swiftness potion
oh oops it's okay I think I just threw that in the trash oops no it's going in there okay
so now I need the other potions that he sells good to know which ones
this one looks pretty good life force I need more money give me that platinum coin
did you take the platinum coin out no what happened to it I didn't I didn't do anything
here it is magic damage wait regeneration right I already have seven of these where was the heart
one more max hp life worth there it is I gotta get five of each at least all right
dos but I'm gonna I told you this is a chunky this is a chunky soup stream I'm not done
you guys have to stay up for another 30 hours after terraria I'm gonna go take like a bathroom
break come back and we're gonna play dos this is not gonna be like a five hour stream today I told
you guys yesterday or the day before this is gonna be like a at least like a seven to nine
eight hour plus stream oh we need expert mode for that what's this what's this new thing over here
where's this car that's where the cobweb is I get it now okay I was like what the fuck I have like
280 cobweb yeah it goes to your ammo but I'm sure you already know that kind of at this point
but I guess I'll keep the rope uh all right uh what's next um we never found the dungeon chest
before that's right we did one thing didn't lie about dos no we're still gonna do it I already
got it ready I was prepared I have at least a couple of games on dos ready after this
just I'm gonna go to the bathroom get some water after this and we'll go all right soldiers what
do you say nightbot died oh oh well so was are you are you have any stingers are you like baking
a cake or you have any stingers yes I have put them in the the box okay we're gonna fight this
boss fight this boss the plague bringer goliath okay I think we can just summon it here I'm also
just realizing these guys are 150 larger so they're just like huge um I can't summon them
it might have to be daytime or something daytime or something whatever that means oh we have to go
to the jungle I love going to the jungle we always seem to have to do that huh do they fly with me
ha ha ha they like they find little broomsticks they just annihilated that thing whatever it was
I don't even know what it is oh shit we're doing this come back to me come back to me
the martians are invading this gives you some crazy fucking op items but uh spaceships are
really tricky we're not strong enough for this not okay well why do we do it then because
when we kill the spaceships the reason why you're digging so far down here I'm stronger than we are
right now what's the point of this bunker uh because spaceships shoot down laser beams like
independence day and they can't go this is a just in case or okay zerg potion
you're thinking about it that's the thing I am you're thinking about it work you just got your
armor right yes oh he's gonna do it he's gonna do it he's gonna zerg potion with the aliens
and we're gonna die in 15 seconds you only have to spawn apparently the zerg potion is too much
I would do like battle but zerg was just there is a block of enemies it really is pickling
um they're coming it takes time invasion doesn't end until you kill them all
oh I see you oh yeah I do see you over there I mean they're flying around all over
the place how come where why are they not over here all the invasions like warn you before they
show up you need to go to spawn they attack the houses no I'd be at spawn they everyone's
saying we have to be at spawn okay I've seen them not at home here they are oh also you can get the
OP UFO mount that just lets you fly forever
so we could be outside of them you find them um okay I'm building another bunker
oh I just got juggled so bad I have the perfect weapon for this actually
get off there guys watch out don't get killed um I used it why did you do that they're gonna get in
they're gonna get in don't let them
they're in they're in they've breached
stuff's gonna start to de-spawn isn't it I one of us has to go up there
one of us has to go up there dude and like get something what are you talking about
isn't she gonna de-spawn there's gonna be 10 000 things yes there is everyone's saying yes there is
oh well yeah go get it what my inventory's full I got something thank you can we do it
oh we are the valiant infantry I love how you very reluctantly joined in
well the what the correct way to do that would be for you to start and then me to start very
loudly after you and then somebody else to do it too yeah and then like six more show up
oh we are the oh oh we are the valiant in inventory tree we're the one
that's always how it works so what the hell did we just get for doing that
that's I got the bard triangle shield generator lane electro rebounder martian uniform torso
no I like the rank code green slime shield drone beacon I gotta start yeah you got everything
I have to start from the top man this is like too much me to even look at
healing someone's a shield drone rapidly laser drill I got the same thing is the shield drone
beacon any good someone's a shield drone to rapidly shield allies shields ally life equal
to your bones healing up to 25 only one shoulder guardian maybe someone at once wingman fires a
concentrated laser beam oh man yeah holy shit this thing's awesome yeah aliens get a lot of
really cool items these are a lot of mana but the thing is great is that the one where you charge
up it's like it just shoots a beam no it just shoots a rapid just straight line oh there's
one that charges and then shoots a straight line super beam that's really cool it's kind of like
the sans eye thing the skeleton thing but it happens immediately and can happen way more often
it does more damage yeah you can upgrade wingman like 60 times really I have the illuminati weapon
you know triangles are actually a source of power it's in the shape it's like that's why they use
the pyramid you need two wing men this thing shoots three of the same time yeah all right
what about some of this other stuff let me see the shield should i just maybe just use this
does it count as something and i only have let me see um banners
i'm gonna get me in trouble if i put this in there there's still a pit
what are you looking for uh what
deflect enemy projectiles everything i don't understand
shield drone i already have one of these but whatever uh cactus leaf desert feather talon
i don't really know what this is for i don't even want to open the presents i don't care
all right let's go check out let's see what this shield thing does i don't think it's going to do
anything unless you actually have bonus healing like you have stat points or items going towards
that i guess but i don't think it's it's not technically a summon but is it no it's not a
century either i could i could just have it does it matter do i have zero i can just kind of have
it here i guess it doesn't matter i guess not it's cute i guess it is just kind of cute what's
what's the harm uh where it come here let me see oh you're all the way out there i was gonna say
i forgot why i came this way i had a very good reason i need to start to look i know that for
you we need to kill the um so that's the cryogen and calamity mod gives you a really crazy century
uh ability it gives you a whole bunch of really good stuff but mostly that
all right we should be able to do it though so you want to do that or how do you what's what's
your uh what's your what's your plan here are you you said that you didn't want to go that long
i changed my mind it's toraria man once you're in it you're in it because it's been you know it's
been five hours right now yeah i'm i'm i'm good to go all right well then let me just go pee
let me come back okay it's been five hours and i haven't gone i'll be right back go pee
hey hello i'm back did you miss me uh hello i actually you know what i really did
well that's good let's test it on the pig
this thing is absolutely destructive what is the alien laser beam oh yeah oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah all right so i have the solo tablet was it what was i don't even remember
what this but we were doing this for what did i need i needed something for what i don't know
we needed to do the eclipse for something we for a broken broken broken staff broken hero staff
that's during the daytime we were going to go to the jungle to fight like bring her goliath
and then i saw the martian thing on the way broken hero staff right okay so let's go back
to the jungle uh you head there and i'll teleport to you okay touch the table bring out one of my
guys and away we go i love all these friends they just surf on their spirits great and then
sometimes they all just collectively look down and go kill it they all just do a dive down and
kill the things there okay uh jungle i have acquired the jungle it's dark down here
okay i'm gonna get over here oh hey here's a plague bringer hey why did we did we walk over here
if five seconds ago i might as well just spawn one i didn't buy any potions this guy might be
a little tricky platforms or anything uh i do not i do not we should be fine nice water
fall thanks whoa what did you summon this yeah okay it's a lot stronger than i thought it would be
this is like end game level shit at least in terms of damage it deals if it hits you
he's really fast poison too
too
38% though that's not terrible yeah i mean pretty good it's just oh shit he didn't go away
he's still there let's go ah damn it unfortunate any good food in here what would it be under
we're like the burgers somebody has like a burger right the cook is to the right i want just like
the meatiest food yeah i think we would beat it if we actually potioned i mean i i like panic
potions but it wasn't very good um cook i don't see a cook he's outside of our base in a random
house why is he down here i don't know some people just end up out there all right let's see
steamed carrots full for 45 seconds increase knockback increase magic damage movement speed
life regen here we go apple pie so when i want um juice head off dude you want to try that again
yeah i need to make another something this time i think i'm gonna go with the other um
summon for this i forgot how i made it that's the problem is that they're on the ground
and a lot of the best like hardest bosses are flying around yeah the ice claspers definitely
better for this i have to de-summon you guys okay i have my ice claspers they should be much better
uh am i blind i should have it what is this altar that's over here i'm gonna use this as well
it feels like it's better than aiming with this because it flies around so fast
are we just going back to where we were yeah i'm trying to figure out oh i need lead bars that's
kind of random oh no i have them i run to a tree stop what would i give terraria out of 10 obsidian
um i don't know a four i'm getting generous all right that went too far i have no obsidian
no and we have none um i don't like it eight and a half seven eight point four eight point eight
eight point four maybe eight point four i'm sticking with that one right now eight point
four omega lull what that's pretty that's good all right what would you give it you are like
mr terraria what would you give terraria um 10 that's a lie no it's not you're not going to give
this game 10 i know that's perfect why wouldn't i give this game a 10 because i i know that you're
just being like facetious i'm not
what is a better craft them up game that terraria doesn't deserve the 10 because it's the best one
yeah but you take you to 10 for a certain category or i'm talking like overall like how you feel
about the game not just just because this is a better crafting game than day z doesn't mean
that it's in every single other one i think that's enough to be like you know what something has to
define what a 10 is and i think terraria sets the bar in my opinion for the type of game that i like
what's a game that's six out of ten days gone i'm sorry i'm sorry you're disappointed that i like
things i really let you down days gone might be like a five eight what's a better craft them up
uh
are you over there i'm just trying to think something star forge no
you're fucking kidding me well i mean i didn't go that i didn't like it just go that far but
i tore this is i played star forge for like an hour um i don't know i guess there's not i guess
there isn't like a better crafting adventure fighter kind of i mean minecraft do you see what
this is doing yes what it's doing it's going to do that all the time and it's not giving me any
shield it's just going to annoy you it's like putting zeros over my head i thought those are
bubbles okay so uh don't use that thing oh wait i needed obsidian that's why i was down there dude
i got so distracted by that toria question and i found the mushroom biome i mean i do it yeah
okay overall i think it's like somewhere in the eights but i guess it is like probably like the
best or one of the better crafting fighting so here's the question because you're doing right
now what you're doing is the game of the year is an eight out of ten rather than being a ten what
what would have to happen for the best game of its genre to become a ten well that's a it's
a very personal question because like what i think is a ten overall you might not think is a ten
overall well yeah i'm asking you what you think the game is missing uh i don't think it's missing
anything i think it needs to have things taken away like what i think it's a little too chaotic
well also remember this is with mods so if you did want what's chaotic oh right well i can't give
you a real opinion then my opinion is is completely invalid because i i'm playing not i'm not playing
the real true version of the game you see guys you could learn a lot from germa this is how you
successfully with an audience manage to not have an opinion about something and upset nobody it's
very a delicate walk you have to do but he's very talented at it it's hard to say i'm very
talented what how is that a delicate what i said the game is like an 8.4 that's a very good score
that what i think the game is over a seven which is like wow a seven is still a fun game
game i would play a seven i've played plenty of sevens before so have you yeah i'm not
disagreeing that that an 8.4 is just wondering what the points were being taken off for
realistically it is probably just how chaotic it can get but then you came in with that little
rebuttal saying you're playing on mods sir that's why so it's like okay well it's maybe
it would i guess it would be higher i don't know okay what's a six out of ten for you what is a
six a ten a six yeah like days gone is was like a of the highest five maybe six maybe that's like
a six out of ten game well let me let me look at like installed or games yeah that's hard to
remember like all the remade list of sixes uh sakiro get mad um why do you think i'm gonna
get mad someone in your chat and someone in my i mean i didn't like sakiro as much as i liked
bloodborne i thought sakiro was a way way way worse game than bloodborne
i don't know if i would give sakiro a six get mad i'm not i'm mad i'm not mad at all i'm
teleporting to you i'm not i'm very calm about this whole conversation okay i am potioning up
yes so am i i am putting things down i'm ready ready as we can be i guess
okay i got baited by my own guys they went and attacked something over there
try to not stand near each other if we're getting hit with the same charges
oh did he really just wait to do it over there oh my god he's just hit me every time
he's obnoxious teleport to town if you need to to heal the nurse and teleport on me with
the i'm
i'm just gonna live so you can come back i have to put that on a hot key
his hitbox is so big okay i'm coming are you good yeah come quick
fucker he already got me
okay i'm gonna die soon or what
he's dead oh what did he drop good me i didn't get any oh it's all here
oh yeah yeah yeah maybe if you weren't so zoomed in you could see the boss better
the hive 106 range damage launches a variety of rockets that explode into beads
the worst life regen getting rid of that out of here i think that's all i got
the hive is a legendary weapon i don't know what ammo it takes probably we can do the eclipse now
i guess rocket did i go too far blood bloodborne is like a nine nine nine eight nine no
it's a 9.85 yeah i think so what why can't it be a 10 why is everyone so stingy with the 10s
because it's 30 fps and they didn't decide for any reason to like upgrade or deported or
you know put it anywhere else that's a good point it's an attractive well thought out point
it's really the only thing i'm a very smart guy even on the ps4 pro the summoning alter
what's a 10 out of 10 game ocarina of time super mario 3d world i mean brothers i mean
super mario 3 i mean two super mario 3d we don't even save that no no it's new super mario brothers
we don't say that again oh my god i'm so sorry that actually we're doing the eclipse that work
you need to like get on this okay uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah just do it activate it
where's my way i have the tablet i just dumped it in no i didn't it's right there i saved it
i want my uh one of the pigmes for this it's more fun that way i'll tell you when i'm ready
all right you ready here we go consuming super mario galaxy so nothing wrong super mario galaxy
super mario galaxy is very very good super mario sunshine see i'm gonna have to have an
unpopular opinion here i think super mario sunshine is not a good game i'm sorry do you
have any gold um some um it's in the box in there oh there was one gold in the box i think
we're i think we're poor we are unless there's a plant in there oh there is a plant i don't know
if it's unpopular or popular i just didn't like it i tried it a few times back when it first came
out and then years later i just i just wasn't doing it what's going on here what the hell is
happening you know what's happening what did you spawn a boss no i did deserve oh shit of course
you did i'm going out there what about luigi's mansion there's a mini boss i canceled the potion
what the fuck everybody oh no not again not again with this shit it just how could you still
fly over here he's dead let me in the door got it it did like a little laser through here i hope
i don't need any of those people save on painter we could use the painter right now
wow are you a video game i'm doing the banjo kazooie thing that they all do
oh see now there's like no enemies in the dumb well you didn't i killed it you didn't have to
turn it off oh the potion guy is dead oh because i was about to die i was scared i'm sorry i mean i
could buy another somebody wrote play something better is i have two broken swords i can make a
double i got to wait that's not what i need i need the staff oh where is he over here broken
hero bow ah two swords and a hilt no staff huh that sucks you know what sucks is that the potion
guy is dead and it's all your fault my fault what my fault somebody said elder scrolls has better
crafting okay he's entitled to that opinion can i give you another unpopular opinion what is this
like unpopular video game opinions i i think elder scrolls games are not good is that like bad
um i mean you're wrong and i might i don't know i just i they feel like i don't know
oblivion was all right i liked oblivion for a little while but like i feel like skyrim just
didn't just didn't do anything for me at all it's because you're a mod list fuck no no you're not a
modless fuck modless you deny it no no i um i did a bunch of mods okay were they nude mods
this is a safe space no they were not nudity mods okay
he hesitated no listen fallout also is not very good i think bethesda did bethesda seriously just
like somehow hypnotize everybody to think that they make a good games they make this is this is
unpopular opinion night it is i'm sorry they make a specific type of game that no one else makes
fallout new vegas was good it was fun it was interesting it was really entertaining
right but like fallout 4 i thought was not very good at all fallout 3 was kind of a buggy broken
mess and all the games were like that too like fallout new vegas was good i really liked fallout
new vegas oblivion was fun you're asking you say unpopular video game opinions and then you say new
is the best fallout i'm gonna hit you with fallout 4 was better no no it was not it was not absolutely
not yeah it was fallout 4 was not better than fallout new vegas no way fallout new vegas was
a cheap reskin of fallout 4 that used things modders had already made for fallout 4 to make
new vegas like survival mode that was introduced in vegas was just a mod for fallout 4 i don't
believe this at all how do you not believe it that those are facts fallout 4 was a action game
they had a protagonist that just talked and there was no such thing as interesting stuff
there's no factions no wait wait it was an action game there was a protagonist who talked
yeah that was that was the worst part about it it wasn't me anymore it was the guy that sounds
like chris pratt was that it was chris pratt that was the actor that did it apparently
no there was no like no no no like fun things to crazy things interesting things to do in fallout
4 is an action game chris pratt is the main character
fallout 4 is an action that's i i don't i don't consider fallout 4 to be like a
true full rpg like fallout new vegas what it's a fun yeah it's a fun action game but it's not
i it's not what i wanted from like my fallout game and it was based in the city of boston
and we're talking about that's like my favorite place so that gets like two full letter grades
from me but then i moved to vegas therefore those two letter grades then transition over to vegas
i was mixing out i was i meant fallout 3 fallout 3 is better than new vegas and new vegas did we
really just have a full fucking argument and you were in the wrong game yeah i was saying fall they
made fallout 3 fallout 3 is a better game than new vegas new vegas just introduced all the new
mechanics in new vegas were just mods like ripped from fallout 4 and from fallout 3 you are arguing
for the wrong game but i will still say fallout 4 is better than both of them
what that makes it what do you wait wait wait what hold on a fallout 3 is better than new vegas
and fallout 4 is the best all right you better be careful someone right now is making like an
incantation like spell you're gonna get cursed we did fallout 4 streams and people liked them
and i said you know i'm gonna do new vegas next and i installed new vegas i installed mods and
i opened it and i was testing it to make sure it worked and that game is fucking garby wait which
one new vegas you don't like new vegas at all like at all no no really i think the story is better
but barely and who cares
uh i i thought new vegas was like very fun and charming he's doing this on purpose
i'm not that's the thing though unpopular opinion i actually have these opinions that are so wrong
and there's nothing you can do about it oh my god well i mean i do think that i don't really
let's put it this way i would not put any of the last 10 to 15 year bethesda games
in like a top 10 list of best games i've ever played i just don't think i would
i did enjoy them some of them but i i thought some of them were also pretty not good either
well i wouldn't put fallout new vegas in like my top five best games top 10 best games i enjoyed
a couple of their bethesda games and that's all right that's completely fine name the top 10
super mario rpg diablo 2 the neverhood no sorry let me get that right bloodborne mario rpg
card crawl um oh my god i'm just kidding oh no i was saying i was saying oh my god
because the bow i've been using is awful like the modifier on it is awful i didn't quite catch that
sorcery yeah there you go so what are we are we good to try something else now or what are you
doing you never got the thing you needed so we're gonna need to do another fuck that's right during
dating do you have it you you've been team fortress yep chrono trigger oh wait what's the current
question i was reading what's like your top 10 like favorite games it's the best top 10
right yeah bloodborne's on there for me yes right see it is a very good game
so what was okay what was your big problem with hero um it was just it was way too like over the
top like heart every change that they made to the dark souls formula to make it new was bad
it was just flat out bad oh um i thought you're gonna say it was a rhythm game no
because it was is that your thing no i i'm one of those weirdos that equally hated and equally
loved sakira at the same time it's so polarizing in my brain remembering how much i loved certain
areas and how much i hated certain other things i wouldn't put secure at a six though that's just
like whoa that's a little too far so how many attempts did you do with the last boss before
you said i don't want to do this ever again i'm curious i gave up before then so for them
yeah at the boss before the last boss i i think i i did everything up until the final boss and
had already seen the final boss on like speedrun streams and didn't have the desire to do it
okay i did play it for a while on one stream but that that one that doesn't count is sakira
is sakira worse than dark souls 3 uh no dark souls 3 is second place after bloodborne if
you're counting bloodborne as a souls born game okay so you think so you got you do bloodborne
dark souls 3 is like your top two and then dark souls 2 dark souls 2 is you think dark souls 2
is better than dark souls 1 yeah did you play demon souls no it is your problem you have to
play demon souls bloodborne is number one demon souls number two dark souls one is number three
three dark souls uh then probably dark souls three sakira dark souls two for me
sakira way bottom throw it in the trash a bargain bin
all right come on we the reason why we're sitting around is because we have to wait
till the next morning yeah we can't do eclipse until morning and i'm just like going through
recipes and stuff uh there are items that let you skip the morning and stuff like that
but i don't it's almost i don't or i'm having a nice time talking to my boy
you would really like demon souls if you liked bloodborne it follows a lot of the same weird
principles that bloodborne did especially like the hub world stuff i've seen quite a bit of it
i'm absolutely shocked that they have not done even a like a remake just not even a remake just
a remaster just ported to oh yeah yeah ps4 with a higher resolution and up to frame rate i don't
why would they not do that i don't i don't think i'll play it unless they do and even then i've
seen enough of it and i'm kind of burnt on like too many souls games as is yeah oh dude what about
elden rain i'll play it look from software has that formula where they do something so interesting
that they're all worth playing because it's something you know that formula you know it's
going to at least somewhat follow that really interesting unique formula so it don't matter
they're all going to be worth trying or at least worth playing ah shit i do need truffle
i think welcome to the podcast this is called the unpopular opinion podcast
that is what my you know my friend comes on and uh makes everyone angry for 30 minutes he just says
everything that you could possibly want i'm sorry i want to agree with while hitting his mic you
can't stop them you got a tablet i used mine already i don't have them all right well it's
morning so i'm gonna have to make one what's it called slab day day slab but what's it called
daystone what's the what's the material i know but like take a look at the screen right now
and i want you to see something this is very important for you to see this because you need
to understand something how many ice cream flavors are in this box imagine needing to
pick one of these flavors um what's it called solar there i'm gonna go to the right you have
to use the right utensils for this well it was in daylight what is this thing called the slab
i'll be back no no no i'm going to do it you can do it without me i'm just going to grab mud
outside on the left did did you have oh wait wait wait wait wait this dumb thing out here
you know now that we've summoned it one time one of the people should be able to
even if you don't have it okay guys i'll be back i need i'm on an important mission
help me out here what the fuck is happening further left what i'm so glad didn't have a
battery in my inventory because that would just summon the boss yeah is am i i thought i just
tried to do this all right let's go no you guys can get out there it kind of does the first part
of the bowser laugh from mario 64 that like you want to talk about an unpopular opinion there's
one if you would take that and slow that down and pitch it down it would be the exact noise that
the actor made you know why because i'm the actor that did it someone had to say it they say what
did it shut up shut up shut up like shut up any more uh any more unpopular opinions
no shut up idiot shut up i dropped one platinum whoops i thought i had a lot of help i'm just
trying to build the fucking mud biome where's look at these the ice thing what's it called
clasper what's it called the claspy suppo oh right here
all right let me ask you this unpopular opinion stream what is what do you feel about uh peanut
butter fluff like fluff do you like it eat what is what is that you never had fluff before
unpopular so we already got another one i don't know i i want educate educate it's like a
marshmallow fluff cream that you can put on whatever you want it usually goes with
peanut butter very well a flood it's called a fluff another sandwich i don't believe you
you don't believe me can we not kill this guy so i apparently dropped 400 blocks of mud and it's
just gone look out for monthron oh too many hits did monthron die in here lady i need help
well she has a name i don't i don't know what anybody's name in here is if you said i will
give you a thousand dollars to name the guy right here on the left i would not be able to do it
i i have no idea i couldn't even guess i'll guess um if i
finro i don't know erin i thought it was an f
nailed it do you have any mud in your inventory jerma who cares if i have mud or not you know i
care i don't know i you made fun of me to a point where i stopped picking up this stupid shit
and come back to bite me it has you should have just let me kept being a moron and putting
dirt in the inventory well you know what you did and i needed it all and i used it all and
down and now jerma has it confirmed no i don't i don't have any mud hey unpopular opinion yeah
mud sucks i know right it's
monthron oh it's just melting i just melting oh this thing is ridiculous broken hero shit
or is it i don't know i don't know how good that is but it looks good you're not melee guy right
uh no i'm bow guy yeah are you sure you don't want to be melee guy if there was a thing that
was like 150 space yeah yeah i'm sure my last playthrough i was melee guy i don't want to do
it again okay yeah you don't want me to get my main in here do you i guess not uh when is uh when
do we get another uh attack from monthron i don't know i think we have to kill a certain amount of
guys incoming mom's run how did i even get in here that's isn't even that's impossible for me
to get in there i didn't that's not even possible to get in there it is it is uh did not drop
i really hope we get one more monthron if we get one more monthron it might work
we should because we did it early the warp staff outdated i think it kind of is but it's
just free to use it's not like it's taking up any extra space or anything
like it's half two centuries so um you gotta be kidding me there's 27 gold in the ground right at
the left door what the fuck man what is even in here it's chasing me are you serious dude
i had no it's what is in there there's this 27 gold right next to you drop down drop down right
now you can get it no i can't it's too far why wouldn't you attack it because i didn't have any
mana
still no broken stuff right sword nail gun oh man this is fucking insane
313 damage wait what is it what the fuck i've never seen number that high
okay honestly like this is should i just look at all this stuff
i feel like it's just convert to a uh melee guy this is like so much more damage
how much damage are your ice claspers they're uh 57 58 and how many do you have like seven
them i don't even know what's in the house it's in the house it's whatever it was it was in the
house i'm of the i'm of the unpopular opinion that maybe we should not build our house with
like a fucking bread cut through the middle of it so they can get in we have just an open this
whole side here this is teleport to me teleport to me what the fuck what do you mean teleport to me
you're right never mind don't you know what i don't fucking need you
i said i didn't need you and i meant it did you get a staff i didn't get anything from him
so i might have missed it mothra on in here you motherfucker die
dude you need to be able to kill a mini boss it's too much going on did you kill it
i i never saw it i don't have any bullets and i think the guy who sells wooden arrows is dead
they just stopped getting in the house shut the doors they can't get in if you shut the
door oh yeah oh the fucking ring lady just got in oh okay the doors are both closed
let's test that theory well i mean the uh the sexual like ghost guys can get in yeah that's
what i'm saying just complaining and normal people that were these guys the like the ring
braids i'm talking about not like regular zombies your things i have all of them and they know they
run around in circles six times you just did a movie mobster laugh i don't even know what that
means okay any broken steps tesla defibrillator this thing okay look at this this thing is 313
melee damage hey but i'm saying you have 50 damage times seven five ten ten twenty twenty
and all the damage bonuses from your equipment five percent five ten times that is it's like 555
damage okay can you stop whining now yeah right quick to convert i'm gonna sell the um the
shotgun and stuff what do we the hand cannon like are you gonna none of us gonna use any of
this shit right what you cut out no one's gonna use any of this shit right we're not gonna use
like the cannon though dart rifles all this stuff uh likely no dart rifle is material and it's a
range weapon i'm doing range so like maybe i just tell anything that's just keep it everything
so yeah why not is it full again no i'm just saying like there's a bunch of just random junk
in here of stuff that we're not going to use i like this a lot i wish i could i need a sentry
is there a better sentry thing that i can find yes we need to kill um cryo whatever his name
boss cryo boss i could tell you the materials we need you can start collecting them okay and
then we can kill that boss and you'll get a really good sentry cool why are they firing at this
person thanks to the 50 bucks lefranda 5 000 bits star what do you think somebody that give
would give 50 fucking dollars what do you think their uh their comment would be
like no five thousand bits no comment just guess that's what i'm guessing is that there was
nothing no peepee poo poo oh nice yeah my man well thank you for the fucking huge amount of money
star gets fucking five percent of every uh dollar on this stream so yeah um you need 50 ice blocks
and then we have everything else the way you responded to that was
all right ice blocks i think i have just i think i have those in here already
no i think i have this snow in here all right ice blocks you got it and what else
uh souls of night souls of light how many of those each three each souls of night
okay souls of light okay just need ice blocks how many ice blocks do i need 50
and you also need essence of a loom five which we should have in there essence of the loom i got
it all i got it all and who makes this uh the ua make it at the anvil a cryo key and you need
light and light in the night right yep let's see what happens here at the anvil
so key and we have to use it in the snow biome cryo key summons cryogen how many of these do you
want if we can make two i can make potential i can make three make two because we might die
the first time okay let's be prepared oceans etc all right i'll do my best is this guy this guy
fly around or is he on the ground uh he flies around and shoots ice projectiles
everywhere okay so i should not use the picklies all right anything else that you need i need
wooden arrows i have i have 500 of those anything else um i need to crack them into holy arrows
try use the sycon knife allows you to go into step all right this thing is it's funny and
it's cool but i i move one mile per hour okay i need me arrows because the other the guy's dead
here come here take all right i am touching the table i'm getting out all my friends
oh my god this thing is full we have five swamp rots in here i think we're good from the swamp
rot let's do it i'm gonna run into those yeah uh help me sell duplicate garbage
okay i'm sorry i got potions i'm ready to go i've got all my friends
touch it again just fun all right you ready can you help me sell i did like a lot more a lot more
of stuff that is there is so much outdated nonsense all right i don't okay so we're looking for
duplicates duplicates first like it's really hard for me dude because i downloaded like three or
four of those like phone virus emoji uh apps and there i now have like 500 fucking emojis
it's hard for me to even know which one of these i don't know what to click on i don't know which
one is it okay then what were we doing just like go go do whatever you want to go do
it i should i sell this i i found one just go do whatever you want jerma you're gonna do it
anyway just go do whatever you want just trying to find a duplicate your mom lets you get away
with everything all right everybody let's go old armor and old weapons all right i'm getting rid
of this old armor there's six empty buckets in here i don't know if that was me i feel like that
was you uh what six empty buckets oh that's me keep those empty buckets don't you fuck with them
uh how much do they cost because i okay they cost like nothing but they're annoying to me
see if it were me i would think that that was a useless item that is like a jerma put this in
here because he's stupid apparently not how many top hats how many vanity items how many raincoats
are in here you're wearing or i'm it's you don't want like just we that we could be fun friends
together we could wear you wear ankle no all right i'm on my way all right after this we
have you want to call it here after this no i don't is that a problem i mean i was supposed
to play dos and you told me you wanted to only play for like three hours yeah but before i told
you that didn't you expect that i would want to play longer i mean we usually click about four or
five hours we're going on six here no we're not yeah yeah we are no i can't open this door
uh counter argument no i don't know i can't how do i can you open this door why can i not open the
door because your toes are blocking it oh this is chunky stream yeah oh yeah it is okay so what are
we doing you wanted to go for like 10 hours today so yes i want to go fight the cryogenic guy
you need to go to the frost biome which is over there yes i see and fly play whatever you want
yeah i know i don't know i'm just chilling he's trying to yell at me all right frost biome
incoming nine hours of terraria one hour of dos two hours of bits
no it won't be that long there's a blizzard going on over here i wonder if that's if i should stay
here should i stay in the blizzard yeah just you know just you don't worry about things so much
so i got the i had beef of backpack like an idiot and took all my potions
okay uh i don't have any potions lost this little scary should we do something right here
we fight him here and i never made arrows i threw you like a hunt 500 well i mean they're wood
arrows i never upgraded them so should you want me to summon them here yeah all right here we go
you ready let's go consumable summons cryogen how do i consume it the same way you consume every
item in this whole game where do they go did you okay just get this is not the ice area okay keep
going to the right it's counting this is corruption did i did you i threw them to you do you have them
yeah okay okay ice golem has arrived stir has defeated the 50th sloth demon i ain't doing
no the ice bomb is dead okay cool three sec okay doing it okay cryogen okay he's being a chump
great i expected more dead there's a martian thing over here martian thing i'm i'm getting
martians who's this guy uh he sells some really good shit he's a new mp3 oh damn okay he'll appear
over there right oh you guys spawn like immediately um there's a thing here
it hurts i'm teleporting back yeah i'm going back to the bunker because it also has alien banners in
it ice golem i kind of want to see what i have but i can't really take a second here yeah just
teleporting me now are you in the bunker i'm in the bunker how's the rainbow just going into the
bunker that's a great spot for it yeah there he is stupid aliens don't know what ground is because
space travel is for it
35 oh what do i have that's letting me dash oh cryogen let you dash that was annoying
i don't i wish my cursor was dead yeah i think there's another one right here
so
i got bored i got bored i gotta go back in i'm dead i got bored
oh i forgot about this part that hurts so bad oh my god what have i done god what have i done
you bastard just couldn't see i just i could i'm just watching the finale of a firework show
and there's only so much of that you can take come on dude i just wanted to respawn
look what happens when you leave the bunker it's freaking out
out no i don't want to fight i don't want to be overstimulated i need to we need to like
um i'm going back to the bunker yeah we have to exploit the human's weakness the boredom for
killing us the only way this keeps sending thousands of people their wrists will start
and that's when we strike with the real weapon
icebreaker
i like body itches am i like allergic to this welcome to the meat grinder i i hate the dashes
in this game there's two senses of there needs to be a dash button too much noise these sounds
this is actually kind of is fucking with me i'm not gonna lie this is fucking with my head
i'm doing a few hard blinks you know that's when it gets to the point where you hold on a minute
we got to slow down i'm going in all right uh where's this last uh it's done there's a meter
at the bottom right deflects enemy projectiles snowstorm staff fire the snowflake that follows
the mouse cursor 63 to 60 let's check that out glacial crusher icebreaker laser drill
oh that's the thing you've been using
so this does not use mana i can just keep doing no yeah it it uses the thing that appears above
your head which is bard inspiration no i'm talking about this snowflake i guess it just
breaks when it hits something oh is that a melee weapon no magic all right star think all right
think i'm gonna try i think it's time to transition to the other stuff that i was gonna do
okay i've been sick almost six and a half hours okay i forgive you how close are we to
uh i'll be very very clear and completely and totally open about this
that last encounter um just like i need a break
yeah i understand you've said that a couple times i'm understanding what you're where you're coming
from i feel like i just got off uh a ride at the carnival you know the ones that like turn you
upside down i've never been upside down before so now i don't i don't there was this riot called um
this is right called the zipper you ever ride that the zip now it's this weird it's this
like 12 of these enclosed uh canisters and they they go on a belt up around in a circle and they
are independently can move completely in a circle as well so what happens is you it's a room for
two people in there this thing is on its own independent axis and it's going upside down
yes we could do this together so that ride sucks so much and has always caused a problem for people
because at least three or four times a night they have to spray down three or four of those
cans because somebody puked in it so yeah i feel like i just got off the zipper i really do would
you like to get back on the zipper we can do it again next week next week you're gonna do the
zipper uh yeah that's what you you you want to play this sooner than that uh no no no that
sounds good can you stop shutting this door it's i don't want to why i don't know close doors
i hate this door i hate this door but yeah um uh this is fun how far are we to getting close to
the end of the game okay so what happens is you know those things you shouldn't have killed the
cultist you kill the cultist guy it summons four pillars around the map which are kind of like
you kill waves of enemies then you can destroy the pillar you have to destroy all four and then
after you destroy all four the moon lord appears and he's the final boss cool plus all of the other
bosses that are modded but that's the core game okay so we think we'll be able to get to the end
of the base game in like the next couple streams maybe two three streams uh the next stream will
definitely be moon lord i would expect unless we just kind of delay it oh well then we could just
i don't know i i'm still having fun time yeah like the the stuff immediately after moon lord
is a lot of fun because that's when you your items start to get ridiculous like moon lord
even gives you a portal gun which is fun to goof around with so now i realize what you meant really
wild when you were saying that so now i know what you meant by you kind of have to just pick
something you want oh melee summoning magic ranged rifles yeah there's so many fucking things in
this game that you just have you do have to just pick something well by this point you've
you've also specialized every accessory and equipment choice to be like oh i'm the summon
guy and if you're like oh i want to switch to melee every accessory has to come off and you need
to like combine into a million yeah all right well that was fun yeah enjoy the rest of your night
everybody over in star's side and if everybody people are leaving because they wanted to see
terraria then we'll see you later moving on to dos for a few hours well we'll see i'm just gonna
play for like 10 15 minutes like finish this stupid mushroom buy room and stuff okay well
everyone say bye to star say bye star bye go away
i can't do it i can't i can't bring myself to do it i can't bring myself to do it because he's like
not even over here right now and if the whole house was gone when he came back and he wouldn't
even know and it would be fucking terrible plus when i would have to like beat the game no i'm
not gonna do that i can't do that like i still have to live here over the next couple of weeks
i know no that's too far from me i'm not doing it all right let's switch to dos let me go i'm
gonna go grab the water i'll be right back i'm still here i'm just over there can i like scare
them no i'm gonna get lost trying to do that i'm just leaving i said i was moving on to dos so
that's what we're gonna do but that was fun i'll be right back i'm gonna grab a drink just some
water and i'll come back and we'll do some dos i already have a few queued up that i think might
be interesting i'm gonna leave the squad stream by the way because why would i still be doing a
squad stream change the title to games and demos he's bragging about how he could beat you in pvp
yeah i feel like the terraria pvp is the same thing as diablo 2 pvp where you'd have a sorceress
with thunderstorm and decked out with like plus 40 skills and when you walked out of the rogue
encampment you instantly died from the lightning bolt so that's fine it's probably not as it's
probably pretty imbalanced i'll be right back see you in like two minutes