Let's open up... I'm gonna change my tweet as well, because it is not correct. Let's get rid of that.
Let's put a new one up that just says, uh, Pic... Picross. Picross. All right. No. Picross. Picross.
I don't know what's right. How about just Picross now? That's fine. I'm okay with that. Hey, look
at that. All right, so those of you that are gonna stick around, we're just gonna play Picross.
We're gonna do Picross. Hey, Picross, ask me anything. How does that sound? Uh, ask me anything
Picross stream. Well, ask me almost anything. Oh god, that was a... kind of just opened that one up.
PictoPix. There it is. My favorite little thing to play. Let's get it on screen. Have you ever
played 3D Picross? I have. Ever gonna play Bayonetta 2? Uh, probably not. Are you gonna...
Am I gonna do Scrabble? I'm probably not gonna play Scrabble. What are all of your political
opinions? All right. Uh, hold on. Do I still have the Twitch integration? I think so. I think
it worked. Another 50 dollars from NotEKinz. I said it wrong. Thank you for the 50 bucks
correcting my mispronunciation. My goodness. This is like 400 dollars. I made like
four or five hundred fucking dollars by having a bootleg Dreamcast broken disc
and a top-down hard game that I gave up after like 45 minutes. Thank you guys. That's
fucking insane. Uh, I think the Twitch integration still works. Let's find out if it does.
PictoPix. There it is. So where did we leave off last time? So we made the mushroom, the boots,
and he's... I'm bragging. No, no. I'm fucking surprised is what I'm saying.
All right. Is Twitch integration working? It is. All right. So there is Twitch integration in
this game. No, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want you to play. I don't want you to play. I need
to relax. Wait, why is it? All right. So, okay. Let's fucking reboot the stream and play this
chill puzzle game. Everybody, here's how you play. So as you can see, 10 by 10. It's a
baby mode 10. We're just doing this to get everybody prepared. But no, let me be fair here,
though. There are probably a lot of people that are here that were not here last time
a week ago. So I... How do you... This is how you play. I'm going to do it. Time me.
I'll put a 30 second timer on screen. No, 10 second timer on screen. Ready? 10. So every
one of these numbers is a corresponding square. So for three, for instance, there's three squares
in a row down this column here, right? So I don't know where it is. I have to use deduction.
See? Nine. That means there are nine here. Every time there's a space, there has to be
at least one cube in between this number. Got it. Time's up. That's how you play.
So we got... That's it right there. Actually, no, that can't be certain. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight. Yeah, that can't be certain. You weren't listening? Just enjoy
the pictures and enjoy the hangout session. See? I know this is two here. Where's my X?
There it is. So remember, I know for a fact there's no way because this one has to be a
space. We're just going to relax. Are you going to shit talk Joel again? No, this is
my relax session. I'm not shit talking anybody right now. So for instance, we've got three,
six, seven, eight, nine. Not enough. And you can... I'm not using it right now, but there is
Twitch integration. So you're probably going, well, how did you... Because this is nine out
of 10. These have to be filled in for this to make any sense. Same thing with seven,
right? Seven, as you see, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven has to be there. Which, hey, look at that. We now know that the three is
either here or here. Right? You understand? And this guy... Oh, right. The spam. I probably
should just turn it off. Should I just turn off the integration until I let you guys play around?
I don't mean to spam. It's not me spamming. All right. So we've got one, two, three, four,
five. One, two, three, four, five. Can't do that. Let's see. Five, two. This is one.
There's a one here. Eight. So I told you like I told you before. I know that it has to be
there. Okay. And we got two. There's only one more here. Am I going to play stunt man? Yeah,
I will. You can complete it. Yeah. You guys, every like two or three, I usually let chat do one.
So interestingly enough, see how we have this block here. This has to be seven in a row.
Therefore, see one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. These have to be filled in. One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven. Paying attention. I'm happy that you are. Take a
look what happened here. This is five. So one, two, three, four, five. Already done.
This is also already done. So we can feel the whole rolling. This is also not done completely.
See how there's nothing else here. It's grayed out, which leaves. Hey, look at that. Two.
And what happened here? Three, space, two. It's that simple. Whenever we do it together,
we just try to screw you. We're space Michael. Wait, there actually is music.
It was turned off because it just, it's the same song. It's the same like jazz piano.
Boring. Whatever. All right. So let's see. What do we get to work with here?
This is done completely. There's still a couple here. Seven, five. So one, two, three, four,
five. One, two, three, four, five. I think we can do more than a few of these.
Two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. Yep. All right. So three, three.
Mark them. So there's a one here somewhere. This song makes me want to shit. No,
we're not doing the brown nose joke again. Where's the one here though?
Play Chowder Man instead. No Chowder Man. It probably is just one, two, three, four, five.
No, it's definitely not here because if this is the, if this is the two,
right, then there's nothing there. So you have to assume one, two, three, four, five.
And there's three, which leaves that. That's done. Put on Chowder Man.
You guys really want me to put on Chowder Man. Do you really want that?
I have a, why is there a command that says I have a YouTube channel where I upload my
videos in 4k? That's a lie. That's not real. All right. I'll play Chowder Man for like 30 seconds.
Okay. So take a look here. Three, one, two, there's a block. One. No, it has to be
somewhere in here. Therefore one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three. That has to
be it. This row is done. This row is done. This song is killing me. Make it louder.
You don't actually want this to be louder. Hey, look, it has to be there. It has to be here.
And then you got two. Let's see. We cleared out this, this.
All right. You want to stop talking? Fine. It's probably here. It's just Dig Dug. No,
it's not Dig Dug. This is probably just right here. So, oh, you can, by the way,
hashtag guess. You can guess what it is. I wonder if it's down here. It might be like
here. What the hell am I doing? Chowder Man, sir. I don't know what the fuck I just did
that for. I just fucked the whole thing up. I just tried to complete it by guessing. I don't
remember which way it was. This is not really there. There's definitely some type of C
person. Fixed A7. No, that's not right though. All right. This is literally causing
my brain to cease functioning. It's actually making my brain cease to function playing that
song. Is it Garfield? It's not Garfield. Then that is here. It's probably here.
Let me just fill that in. Uh-huh. Yep. The question is, yeah. It really, it just beef
brain me. What is it? Is it Sonic? Sonic the Diver? All right. What's next? This is
called Hot Dad? Oh, that's the artist. Oh, okay. We'll just keep it on. All right. Here
we go. So you're just doing how it works. Good. Let's see. That one's going to be
one, one, one, down, five, one, two, three, four, five. Bingo. These I can't tell. That's all the
ones there. Hey, look at that. You got to be here. You got to be here. You got to be here.
No, you don't. That's not even true. Why am I even pretending that that's the real answer?
It could be either side. One, one, one, one, somewhere in here. That works. And then
let's see. This is four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four.
Yep. Here's your two. It was there actually. It's definitely here too. It kind of has to be.
But I don't know that yet. Yes, I do. They get to four. So we got one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. Look at that. Three, one, two. Here's the one here. So that's
four down. This is done. So that's here. Okay. Here's your four. Tools. Looks like a question
mark so far. Seven. I have to have my tools. One, it has to be here. There's two, two. There
it is. What is it? Hey, it's a paint roller. Who got it? Nice work guys. You want to play
Splatoon music? Oh no. Splatoon as in that's what that looks like. Yeah, I got you. But
let me play. I'll only do one more and you guys can do it. Pizza song.
This guy, C-Man doesn't have an OST. I don't think so. Play the theme from Margo's Wet
Nurse. Wait, isn't that the song that goes like, yeah, this song's fucked up.
All right. I'll do one more and you guys can do one. Three, four, five, six, seven,
eight. No. Wait, hold on. Three. Actually, hold on here. That's three. These ones has to be here.
Yeah. What a creepy fucking stream this is. Hey guys, I'm just playing Picross and listening
to weird like fucking lullaby music. Are you guys enjoying the stream? Yeah, this went off
the rails, huh? Let's see. Two. It could be, no, it has to be here. One, two, three.
No. How many teeth do I have? Let's see. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen. I have fourteen teeth.
That's pretty good. What the hell is this? It's a cartoon. What kind of fucked up cartoon is
this? One, two, one. What is this? Cartoon? Speech bubble. How would you get that?
Anybody get that? All right. Well, I'm gonna do one more and you guys do one. My last one. He's
addicted. It is very addicting that this game is so addicting. I would put it in my top,
probably my top 250. Seven to eight out of ten games I think I've played over my life
that I sometimes like to play sometimes. Wait, that's not true. This might be part of the,
no, it has to be. One more. It's just like crazy taxi. You get to,
we get to guess the picture together. See, this is probably a field goal. Let's see. One,
one. That's two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. So here we go. This one's for
free. I love getting them for free. How long is this song? Might as well play the winter
lantern singing. Oh, I remember how terrifying that was. The one that goes.
Is that what's coming up? Now this is a real good one. This is the, this is Garman.
All right. Spoiler alert. If you haven't played Bloodborne, it's one of the best
games ever made. Go play it and then come back and watch the stream. Try to beat it
in like less than two or three hours. So that's one, one. It's probably four. Yeah,
this is a drink. It's Glitch, the twitchy mode. Deal. It is the three. Unbelievable.
Okay. Look, can I just say if Sekiro is even 10% of how fun and amazing I think
Bloodborne was, it's going to be game of the century for me. So it has to be here.
I can see it coming together.
Possibly one. That's gotta be there. We've got one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Here it comes. Yeah. The best part. The best part of the whole song.
At the end of the games that I'm excited for. I mean, Sekiro is just, is number one.
I've been waiting for, I've been waiting for a From Software game that's not Dark Souls
since Bloodborne released. And that's not to say anything that's anything wrong with Dark Souls.
I just like when they do something a little different. All right. What is it? We've got it.
It's like a beer. Beer glass. Oh, some of you guys got fucking destroyed. One, two, three, four,
five, six. So only seven or eight of you got it right. All right. I'm gonna do one more.
You guys can take it. Last one. It's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
It's our turn. I'll give you one more. You guys can get a go. Two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight. Not quite. One, three, one, one, five. I mean, it kind of has to be here.
That doesn't help me very much though. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Also
part of a four and one. He's never gonna let us have our turn. Four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine. No, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. That has to be the three. And look at that.
When you really solve it, it itches a part of your brain. So this is one, two, three, four,
one, two. It can't be any of these. Let's go ahead and do this. It could be two and then
six. I'm not sure. This is the most intense PictoCross stream with this music. Yeah.
I like it. It's think music. Two, three, four, five, six. Yeah, that two and the six
is three, right? Look at the one, three, one. One, two, three. This has to be part of the three,
right? Because if it was one, two, three. No, this is the three here. Got the ones.
This is also a one. There's your two. I think the same thing's gonna happen here. It is
three. Get that space down. And then there's your two. There's your six. Now let's see.
This is three. This is part of the four. It has to be. There's your two. There's your one.
What is this an image of? How do you go from that to Gwyn? Come on, Gwyn. Watch it. Watch it.
One, two, three. One, two, three, four. Come on, Gwyn. Come on. Got it. Okay. I'm gonna laugh
if this is like gingerbread house. We got it. A lot of you got it this time. All right.
All right. All right. All right. It's time for you guys to play. This is fruits. I'll make it. I'll
give it to you right here. Have fun. Get it done. Every five, every like eight seconds,
it fills up whatever the most typed into chat. Write for it again. Did I get teleported
like a week and a half ago? Did I think I went through a wormhole and I'm in the sea? Yeah,
doing the same thing. All right. I'm telling you right now, if you guys fill this cube,
you did it. You accomplished it. Congratulations. But I'm taking control back for the rest of the
stream. You beat the game at that point. You get the game over. You see the end credits. That's it.
All of a sudden, everyone's like, no, no, shit. Remove that. Remove, remove it.
He might be serious. Don't fuck with him today. He got it. He played a bootleg
Dreamcast game. He's already on edge. I'm gonna get like chat on screen. How do I do this?
Can I pin this? How do I pin the chat window on top of this game?
Yeah, I can do that, right? Pin. Pin this window. Customize. How do I pin this? How do I use pin a
Firefox tab? Are you guys doing it? You know, you're clearing everything. Good. I actually
don't know how fucking I can do this. The large vocal in wrong stream chat. I'm not judging
anybody. What are you talking about? Right click the top of the window. All right. While
you guys fill in the same thing over and over again. It's I think an add on. Oh, that is a good
one. Daughter of the Cosmos. That is that's probably one of the better songs in the whole
soundtrack. All right. I'm about to I'm about to grab the wheel. You guys are falling asleep
here. Like, come on. What is this? Take control back, please. I'm drawing every toss.
Stop. What do you mean stop? You guys you guys just keep going like this.
You just did it for me. You just did it while I was showing you. All right. Okay. Why would
you clear this? We almost had it. Clean slate. Look, I'll leave what you guys did. There you
go. Oh, good. End the stream. No thoughts on the Halo Master Chief collection coming to
steam. That's actually kind of cool because I never really played them. When is that
expected to be there? This year there's no date. Oh, that's cool though. Yeah, back when
Halo was a big deal. I mean, it's not like it's not anymore, but when it was a really
big deal. I didn't have a regular Xbox. I didn't have I had like a 64 PlayStation 2.
What is in the Master Chief collection? You guys are going into the second phase.
Yeah. All right. It's every single one but up to five. Wow. I thought it was just the
first three. That's kind of cool. Are you guys, are you doing it? Am I about to assume control?
That's it. This is going to be it. You win. Congratulations. You filled the cube.
Look it. You did it. You see the credits. Here they are. This song.
All right. All right. I'm going to fix this. This is a fruit. All right. The question is
how much is left in the song? No, I can't beat this in 10 seconds. Never mind. What's
next coming up there? What's the next Bloodborne song? No, this is Nicolás.
No, this one's too scary. I don't want this one. Cos. Or some say Cosum.
Gas coin's a good song. All right. Let me fix this. Boom, boom, boom. We've got five. One,
two, three, four, five. This is going to be part of the four. You got one, two, three, four.
Can't be here. That's really the only thing I can do. I want you in my room. Why? What are
you talking about? Oh, that's the boom, boom, boom, boom. I want you in my room. That song.
One space. One, two, three. Play that. I'll play that after this. We're going full on
copyright stream. I mean, the title of this is now Throwing the Towel, right?
Is that part of the one of the seven? I don't know. Destroy the Vod. No, I don't want to
destroy it. Two, two, maybe four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. Not quite. Hi, Vod. Can you
hear me? That was one, two, three, four ones. It can't be any of these. Give us back
control. No. Hmm. I wonder which one this is. This is probably part of the four. Well,
this is, I'm going to, yeah, this is four if it's free. This is probably the seven. Yes,
it is. Right until he gives it back. I don't think you're going to get it. Sorry. You beat
the game. You did what you were trying to do. Four. What does that do? Five, one, two, three,
four, five. Let them play. They did and they won. They did a great job. I was very proud.
I was so happy. It was wondrous what they've done. What was it going to put on? Does anybody
know what the name of that song is? Is it just called Boom Boom Boom? Or is it called I Want
You In My Room? There it is. This is the one that goes. We like to party. We like
to party. Boom, boom, boom, boom. Right? No, it's different. Look, I already threw in the towel.
I don't even have to explain myself louder. I'm not going to pretend. I know that part.
Here it comes. And then here's the Minecraft part. Yep. What is it?
So, um, last night when I was going to bed. Oh, I forgot to tell you about my dream. Oh
my God. Is that this dream is fucking worth sticking around for. I hope you stayed here
from the beginning of the stream. If you left and you were like, oh fuck, this is
kind of all fucked up. We'll try again tomorrow. No, you've stuck around for this long. You're
going to get one of the most ridiculous dreams I've ever had. So listen to this.
I'm in my bedroom and there's a knock at my door. I go to look through the people
and there's a bunch of company. Oh, fuck. Oh, there's people coming over. Oh,
my house is not ready. Oh, just a minute. Right. Hold on a second. And I'm like picking
up underwear on the floor and grabbing shit and throwing stuff in the laundry. What's over here?
Sweep, sweep. Right. There is dog shit all over the floor and all outside. Right. So I'm
picking up shit with my bare hands. Just picking up like pile of like auto shit,
pile of auto shit, pile of auto shit. And I go to answer the door
and I'm cupping like five or six shits in my hand. Like to try to magician hide them,
like as if they're not there. It stinks wicked fucking bad. It's unbearable.
And I'm holding them like down below behind me. And I open the door and everyone kind of
starts to come in like, oh, hey, how are you? Oh, good to see you again. Yeah. Well,
you put that you put your jacket over there. And I have like a lot of shit in my hand
and nobody really knows yet. I spend the next what seemed to be 20 to 30 straight minutes.
I couldn't get out. I couldn't like sneak out to the bathroom. I couldn't go upstairs.
I couldn't. No, no, no, no. I'm greeting people coming in and like hiding this fucking
baseball of shit. And everybody I'm doing so good. I'm getting the hang of this.
No one is stopping to like look at my hand. This is brain power. We already heard this.
So finally, I get an opportunity to like, yeah, oh, hey, hi, Mary. How are you? I have to hug
this lady. Like, oh, she comes in for a hug. I got to what I what am I gonna do?
I've got two hands here. One of them is has a wad of dog shit. So I put my hand around and
do like the hover hand on one side and like pat with the right hand. Now, somebody else looks
over here and sees what's happening. What's in my hand. And I have this little like,
yeah, but they didn't. I don't know. I don't think they really grasped what it was. They just,
I kind of had like eye beams going towards my left hand. It was holding like a martini glass.
Like, what the fuck is she doing? And I'm like, I'll be right back. And I run into the
bathroom. Then I finally get in there. And I think I'm like safe. And I just like this.
I go like this, right? I go like into the toilet. I don't know why I could have just
placed it but I like I like yo yo it down like into the fucking toilet. And my hand is just
it's just caked with shit. And that's when I woke up. Glad he stuck around for that one.
It was the most panic induced and I thought it was real, right? You everybody you always
think a dream is real while it's happening. But somewhere in that halfway to end of that
dream, I like I could feel that people knew what was going on. And that's the panic there.
I forgot it was a dream. I was there for that. No, it was fucking ridiculous. And first of all,
the number one thing you have to remember. Why is there a party going on at my house? Why
are there like a dozen fucking people coming in one after the other shaking hands? And why
is this shit all over my whole house? Like dog poo everywhere? What kind of fucked up slob
am I? And then I thought about it. And after I'm streaming tomorrow, but after tomorrow,
I'm going to be taking like probably three or four days off because I have like friends
coming up. Maybe that's why I had that dream. That's probably why. Anyways, back to the
back to the game. So I'm going to Yeah, it's a prophecy. Just make sure there's no
fucking dog shit all over the place. Take auto out. I have such weird dreams. My dreams
always just don't make any sense. I told you guys about the Gordon Ramsay one where
I didn't know if we were going to split the bill or not, right? That happened like last week,
two weeks ago. What the fuck am I? What's wrong with my brain? This one kind of got me here.
Six, one, two, three, four, five, six. Get that on this one. This one's five. So one,
two, this can be blocked. Is this the legendary PictoPix streamer? Yeah. I wouldn't say
legendary. What am I doing? You're legendary to me. Thank you. Thanks. No, seriously. Thank you.
So tomorrow on tomorrow's stream, we're probably going to have a little bit better luck.
I have a couple of plans for tomorrow. We'll see if they happen or not. I'm not done
streaming tonight. Don't worry. It's still going. Is that going to? No, is that impossible
for me to do that? One, two, three. No, I can't figure that out from here. One, two,
three, four, five. No. All right. I got one, two, three. One, two, three. Let's just mark X's.
It's not really going to help that much, but it's okay. Two, one, four, five, six. One, two,
three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. Same deal on this one. Now the
question is, is this one, two, three, four, five? No, this is part of the five.
There's two, four, five. Close it. Wow. You've walked the span. Thanks. Idiot.
Huh? Oh, there's this people are spamming the song. I get it. I get it. I forgot there was
music playing. This is wrong. One, two, three, four, five, six. What happened here? This is
wrong. How did I do this? Oh, fuck. This is completely wrong. Shit. What was the last
thing I did? Uh-oh. Oh, no. What did I do wrong here? That's two, right? Two. Let me
just do, I think I can fix it a little bit later. Let me just see what happens here.
One of these rows is wrong, but it's okay. Two, two, uh-oh. No, this is the row that's
wrong. That's why. Okay. Because this has to be two down like that. All right. I got it.
I think I fixed it. Two, two, one. This is so wrong. How did I fuck this up this badly?
This is so, look at how incorrect this is. One, two, three, four, five. What?
Something went so horribly wrong. Oh, I gotta restart it. Sometimes you just have to detonate
it and come and do it again. What's next? I don't know what this is. I'm so unreasonably
sad about Space Channel. Me too. It's okay, though. Can't happen every time. Even if
you plan something, it doesn't matter. It's okay. There's always next time. You know,
there's always another day. Don't worry. Everything's fine. I'm good. I feel great.
I feel great right now. I really do. What's another good, what's another little soundtrack?
Put on the Six Flags song? We like to party, right? Put on the Venga bus. You know,
people ask career advice sometimes. And what, what I should do, what, if you had advice,
Jerma, what would it be? Honest to fucking God, write a song that is catchy as fuck
and collect royalties for the next 2000 years. Your entire family will be,
just make a song like this. Just make one song that everybody that plays on Six Flags
commercials only need, you need one. You don't need an album full of great music. Just make
one good song and then Seinfeld it until you die. Just spend every waking moment of your life
trying to come up with one catchy song. That's pretty bad advice. Don't take that advice.
Collected fucking royalties forever, forever. We get a check for like a hundred thousand
dollars every year for this one fucking song. All right. I gotta pay attention. That's wrong.
And paid now happiness is just around the corner. Three thousand people are doing it right.
What? Let me, I got, I, I'm, this song is getting me. It's just catchy.
All right. So we've got five, two, I screwed it up here last time.
That's how I fucked it up before. Now I understand. Because I did five, five,
one instead of five, one down. That's where it all went so wrong. There we go. Fixed.
What does that say when you guys went to Six Flags? Now do it at time at 50% speed. Is it
still fun? It sounds like a different song. Don't you just want to fucking make this go
faster? In my brain, it's trying to be as fast as it should be and it's not letting it.
I hate this. This has to be here. One, two, three, because there's no way,
even if it's five or even the way this might be five here, then I'm,
no, okay. Even if this is the end, two has to be here. Four, four, three, five. All right.
I got it now. I'm going to look, people are going to leave. I've gained viewers since the
song has been on. Huh. See if that cult strip will go in point five, boys and girls.
All right. That hurt. That's giving me like anxiety. I need to stop doing that.
Oh, God damn it. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. It's not what I wanted today.
This is not what I wanted. Did anybody get it right? Okay. I'm stopping this.
No, some of you guys got it right. I want to do, let's do like a 15 by 15. Let's,
let's get a, let's do like a 20 by 20. Let's get a real one.
Why is this so slow? Oh, right. Cause it's still, what's going on? Dude, times two speed.
No, I want people to keep their brain cells, pump it up. No, I don't want to be that loud.
I'm going to wake up my neighbors. I want you in my room. Wait, boom, boom, boom, boom.
I want you in my room. We'll spend the night together to get there in my room.
Boom. What? This is the same song. That's where I, that's, I'm going to call it there
right there. What else? What's this one? The coconut song. What does it say? 69 million
views. What is this? The coconut song. 70 million views. I don't see the appeal.
All right. What's this one? It just says coconut, coconut, coconut, coconut.
What the fuck is this stream? This is called throwing in the towel.
Let's all right. Fine. I'll give them another chance.
All right. This is actually, I like it.
Big, big nut, but this delicious nut is not a nut. This is probably one. Yeah, this is one.
No, I don't know. It might not be.
I don't have a lot of info to go on on this one.
I don't have any info. I got, I have info for this one, two, three, one, two, three.
I just don't know. This is 70 million views.
I need more info.
Where's my nut button? That's a good question.
I'm stuck here on this one.
Because pretty much anywhere I go would be technically incorrect without just guessing.
Let's just assume that this is one. Does that help us at all?
It kind of does. Assuming that this is one and not one, two.
That's a great song, but I can't, I need to think. What else we got here?
It was just getting good. No crazy frog. I did Beat Saber crazy frog. I'm not going
back to that hill. No, not the duck song. I always never liked that song.
You can always put the left cross regardless of one and two. Yeah, that's true.
I got one for you. I'm going to play this.
Everybody here right now, maybe you have some questions on whether or not.
I don't know if I like this guy. I've been here for a little while.
Maybe I've been around for a long time, but I'm having doubts that maybe this guy
knows how to run a stream or not. What a fucking idiot.
I'm about to change everyone's opinion because you're going to hear me play this
song and you're going to go, I automatically enjoy everything he's ever said or ever will do
or ever will say. Okay. Just making sure you guys are aware of that right now.
So that goes to see it for now. All right. We're good. Oops. Oops. Oops.
All right. It's 60%. That's fine. That's fine. I got a better idea. How about now?
How about now? What is it? How many people said, 27% said highly negative.
I mean, you did that for the joke. I appreciate it nonetheless.
Another remix of this song. Play the right version. What do you mean the right version?
All versions are good. Every version of this song is fantastic. This is incorrect.
What song is it? This is the moon theme from DuckTales Remastered.
Who knows what's coming up next? All right. Did I blow this? I may have.
Has to be here. I may have blown this. I'm not going to say I didn't.
I blew it. Maybe not. I blew it. What have I done?
Two busy pincers in the mood. Restarted. All right. I fucked it up. That's good.
It's okay. It's okay. Where was the first one? What have I done? I don't remember.
One. One, two, three, four. Block it. One, two, three, four. Block this.
This is just JoJo's Bizarre Adventure. No, no, no. I was about to mute it.
But she better be Smash Brothers DLC. Seriously. I don't want another Fire Emblem character.
The song is very bad. I didn't say it. You didn't.
All right. I got to pay attention to my fucking newspaper game from the 80s.
Distraction. Distracting. Distracting. Distracting.
What did I do the last time? I did... It was five. I don't remember.
This is assuming this is one, right?
Because then... No. No. This is not right. It's not correct.
You have all the info to solve Row B. I know, but I keep hearing jump into the air.
And my fucking split personality brain is dancing right now. There's a part of my brain
that is doing like the swing. Like, oh, hey, spin around. Grab that person by the arm.
Go around. Like the tap dancing and shit. And then there's another part that's sitting
here trying to do math. There's two people sitting here right now.
One of them is having a great time dancing at some fucking wedding.
And the other one's playing a game on stream. I'm just ripped in half.
All right. So that means... So we got one, two, three, four. I had it last time.
B7... It can't be there. I mean, it could because that's one and then space two.
Stop. I have to stop. I have to get out. I have to leave the wedding.
All right. Come back to me. Come on. Like, back in.
Sit in here. I need both of you here. Not just one.
Together. I'm like Majin Boo. Just all of you get back in here
for like a couple minutes and then I promise you can just go back to what you were doing.
Okay. So this is one, two, three. One, two, three. Let's get rid of...
No, I don't know. Okay. This? No. We're here.
One, two, three, four. I just don't know which side this is on. It can't be this.
Okay. All right. Okay. All right. All right. Everything's fine.
See? He sat back down. So then that's three, one.
Now the question is, where's this other three? So this is the one.
Yeah. This could... Okay. There's your four, right? One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. Hold on. One, two, three, four.
I don't know that info. Pull that back for a second.
Two, three, four. One, two, three, four. I don't know that info.
Okay. That leaves us with one. I have it now.
Okay. All right. Go ahead. Go. You can go. You can go. You can go.
You can go. Are you sure? Yeah, you're fine.
Just if I need you again, I'll call you back. Really?
Yeah. Go on. Thanks, man.
Right. All right. Come here. You're not breaking it.
Thanks a lot, man. Go have fun.
Two, three. No, I fucked it up again.
I need you. Stop. Get back here. No. Get back in. Get back in.
Stop, stop, stop. Back, back, back, back. Get back in here.
This is going to be three. This is wrong.
This has to be three. This is incorrect.
You see what I'm talking about? What did I do again that was wrong?
Because see, this is what it was. This is impossible.
That's not possible, but that can't be right.
So this is just wrong. And the question is, where did it go wrong?
Where did it go so this is wrong? Let me just pull this back.
God damn it. Am I pretending?
No. I'm just tired.
It went wrong with D7, did it? I got fucking restarted again.
Every time I see it because blah.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
We have this because of this information.
That's all I have right now. That's what it was before.
So now this is where it goes off the rails for me every time.
And I don't know why. Sometimes, okay, I blow through
some of these and then some of them, I just get stuck.
So there's no, four has to be here.
It has to be one, two, three, four.
This is what it has to be.
This is as far as I got before it was just...
Now this is also, this is a one.
That's the middle one. There's one down here.
And then three is up here somewhere.
All right. Now three...
Wait, are you shitting me?
I think I just got it right there.
I think I just got it wrong.
Is it wrong? Why am I crossing out D5?
Because look, see?
It's three, because I think this is the one, right?
Otherwise, this can't be the three.
This can't be the last one.
This is the middle one.
D5 is getting crossed out because it's the one.
It could be the three.
But if no, if it's a three, one, two, three, one, one.
No, it can't be the three.
Three is above here.
One, two, three, because then there's a space, ones.
But I mean, I guess it could.
Yes, it could. It could.
Because then this would be this.
No, but that doesn't work either, see?
Because now it has to be here.
Which would then be one, which is impossible.
See what I'm saying?
Because if it's three, then one, then one.
So if it was like that,
then that would mean it would have to be either here or here.
And if it's here, no.
If it's here, you only got one, one.
You can't do two here.
It's probably this.
That's realistically, because then let's take a look.
That covers that.
Here's this row.
Let me just see what that looks like now.
Okay, that looks right.
Yeah, that's right.
Okay, we're good.
Fucking puzzle, man.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
All right, now the question is,
is this where that way?
I don't know yet.
But this is five.
So one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five, I believe is correct.
Which would be one, and then three, right?
Okay, and that ends this, and that ends that.
What's coming up next?
A cowboy bebop, apparently.
All right, now we can do this.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Here's the four has to be right here.
It's a two.
All right, that's done.
This is done.
And here's the two.
And then here's the two.
Beautiful is the one.
All right, what the hell?
What animal is this?
That took a long time.
Oh, is it a rooster?
That was not a chicken.
It could have been.
All right, what we got?
Seven, eight, nine.
We can go, let's see, one.
So just by deducing it with our logical brains.
Let's just say one is here.
That's space one.
So let's mark this just for a second.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four.
Got big bits coming.
I missed it.
Oh, Jesus, Freudian weapon.
Freudian weapon has just earned the 50,000 bits badge.
50,000.
Thank you for the 50 bucks.
5,000 bits, Freudian.
Really appreciate it.
And thank you for the 50 fucking thousand.
This song is terrible.
Skip it.
All right, one guy and you get to be the one guy sometimes.
What is it?
The whiplash soundtrack?
What is this?
I don't know.
This is more whiplash.
I'm thinking whatever.
This is just jazz.
But thank you, Freudian, for your massive contributions to the stream.
That's a shitload of money.
I can never expect somebody to fucking pay me that much money.
Thank you.
Is this their influence?
So we get two somewhere in here.
Two, one, one, one, three, three.
So we got this blocked off.
This helps us a little.
One, two, three.
And then down here.
All right.
That's all I have for now.
Two, two, two, one.
What else do I got here?
This is probably the one.
It is.
All right.
Well, there's the next way, that two.
Which then brings us to three.
And then two.
There it is.
So we got three and three again.
One, two, three.
Space.
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Space.
This is an animal again.
We got two.
Two fucked it up again.
He fucked it up again.
Fucked it up again.
What did I do?
It's right here somewhere.
Let me think.
I went too fast.
So this is one, three, two.
So hold on a minute here.
This can't...
No, this is fucked up.
No.
What am I missing?
I've got to go backwards again.
Let me see.
Bye.
Okay.
Hold on.
What happened there?
One.
Right, this is wrong.
Is this...
This is still...
I don't think this is...
This is not right.
This is wrong here.
No.
It's all fucked up.
I did something fucking stupid somewhere.
I have to do it again.
I have to go...
I got to reset it.
I just fucking peed my pants.
Let me start again.
All right.
I can't handle this.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One space.
One.
There it is.
All right.
Where did I go again?
Boomer needs a diaper.
I probably will after this.
Just hand it over to the 70-year-old lady
who comes into my olive garden at 11 a.m. every single day.
She solves these like they're nothing.
Well, I'm going to make that joke funnier
because that's probably...
She probably does it for seven hours a day every single day.
She's probably done every single Picross puzzle that has ever...
She's probably done 50,000 of them.
She's been doing that since she was like 52.
She's got two decades of fucking experience.
She may as well get signed to a fucking esports team.
Anyways, where were we?
One.
There it is.
Big brained grandma.
Okay.
This is done.
I went off the rails here somewhere.
Let's find out how.
This is probably not...
This might be the one or that might be part of the three.
No, it's not.
Got to fill it all in.
Okay.
One.
This has to be the one because this is one.
It has to be that.
So now...
Do I miss Boston?
Sometimes, yeah, depending.
How is C7 filled in?
Because, well, this is what I did.
So if it's seven space one,
then you have to assume that there's a one and there's a space.
So let's just say it's here.
There has to be a space here.
Therefore, the seven has to be somewhere in here.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
So that's why this is filled right now.
Good, Jeremy.
Very good.
Yes, I used my brain.
So now...
All right, let me focus for a second.
Two, one.
And that looks pretty perfect, but...
Because I had the...
Last time it was two, I had the two filled in here.
And it's probably here.
What a smart lad.
Okay, I'm on the right track here.
So that's...
There's the two, yep.
So this is where I went wrong before.
Can't be here.
So this has to be over here.
So then this two is down here somewhere.
There it is.
And there's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I finally got my brain around this one.
Don't know any of these yet.
So one, hold on, one.
One, two, three.
So one, two, three.
The two is done.
There goes this route.
All right, let's get it.
Let's speed it up.
You guys have had lots of time to guess this one.
Two, there's the three.
But you haven't had any idea what the hell it is.
Two, two.
Two, one.
Three, three.
Two is there somewhere.
One, two.
All right.
Two, two.
One, two, two.
One, two, one, two.
One, two.
Two, two.
Two, one, two, one.
One, two.
Two, two, one.
It's going to be surprised Pikachu.
One, two, three, four.
That does that.
See you later.
Okay, see you later.
And see you later.
Finally.
This dope did it.
Here, play, keep talking and nobody explodes.
I actually own it for VR.
I'm going to wait till nobody wants to play.
Anybody get it?
There's a wolf.
I don't think anybody got it.
Yeah, but I do own it for VR.
You'll see it at some point.
Got some free filled in ones.
That's good.
Which leads us, that's two.
Okay.
That's five, one, five, two.
Two, one, one, two.
All right, what can we work with now?
Well, it has to be here.
And then that has to be there.
Good to know.
That's also part of a one.
This is three.
That's a one, four, one.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Not quite.
Two, two, one.
I don't know.
I don't know any of these yet.
That one's empty.
Five, this is part of five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay.
Three, that's part of the four.
That's part of the two.
That's part of the three, I'm going to assume.
No, no, music.
Right, right, right.
Sorry, sorry.
My bad.
I apologize already.
Right, Megan?
Yeah!
You say that just once you'd like your hamburger hot
and your lettuce and tomato cool and crisp
all at the same time.
Yeah!
Well, I say you got it.
I'm talking McDonald's and lettuce and tomato hamburger.
The McDLT.
I'm talking quarter pound of beef on the hot, hot side.
Stays hot.
The new McDLT.
Hot, hot.
Less lettuce and tomato on the cool, cool side.
Stays cool.
The new McDLT.
The cool stays hot.
The cool stays crisp.
Put it together.
You can't resist.
The hottest taste.
The coolest crunch.
Hot, hot.
Keep it cool, cool.
McDLT.
Hot beefy McD.
Cool, crisp, L-T.
McD.
L-T.
It's a good time.
Hot beefy McD.
With a great taste.
Cool, crisp, L-T.
At McDonald's!
Okay.
So I gotta mark the ones.
Which there are a couple that I didn't do, right?
This is the three.
Because it's not one, two, three.
So it's probably one, two, three, or one, two, three.
Can we go back to McDonald's?
No.
Three is?
Hope you have a nice relaxing Friday afternoon.
What's today's date?
Friday night.
I'm your master of ceremonies.
German on eight, five.
Dylan Jacobs.
Grew up in the southernmost port of Mississippi.
Learned to play the guitar when he was eight years old.
Gonna have a selection for you here.
Her it is.
Mom makes a really mean apple pie.
Be in the studio shortly.
With us tonight.
But first I gotta get done with this P-Cross level.
All right, where am I going?
Here, here, here.
P-Cross?
It is P-Cross.
It's P-Cross.
Two, two, four, one, four.
One, one, two, one, two, three, two, one.
What the hell is this?
Floral?
All right, I gotta slow down because I'm feeling I'm in
at a kind of insane pace.
I need to...
And then what an insane pace he's going at.
Slowly hover his head over and press that one.
I'm going at an insane pace.
What did you say before?
Like Arby's grandma?
No.
I solved all the ten...
Is that eggs?
How did you get daisies?
Five, six of you got daisies right.
All right.
15 by 15.
These are gonna take a while.
13, 14, 15, therefore two.
No, I don't know that yet.
One, let's just cover these up.
That felt pretty good.
This is empty now.
What song am I playing?
This is background chill-out music.
Music for relaxed study, work, relaxing jazz music.
There's a coffee cup on the counter.
Resident sleeper.
Well, just relax.
What have you got going on today?
If you have something to do, somewhere to go,
or maybe if you got nowhere to be at all.
But if you are going out, skip it.
Stay here.
Watch your 33-year-old moron
try to complete 80-year-old Arby's grandmother's puzzles.
Olive Garden, not Arby's.
Why do I keep saying Arby's?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Reminds me of a story.
I'm not going to tell a story.
No, don't.
Who cares?
There's lots of ones here.
There's your three.
There's your second three.
And there's, is that, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Start-up top.
Six.
These are all six.
All of them.
Nice.
All right, what about the bottom here?
We've got five, one.
This one.
That row's done, okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
It's full.
That's full.
Full.
Three ones.
That's a seven.
Three and then the one.
This is all full already.
Seven.
This is a computer.
Some form of computer, guys.
There's seven in here.
That looks pretty done to me.
And it does.
Oh, it's a floppy!
Floppy!
Nice.
This one's already done for me.
I didn't even vote a baby level.
15 by 15.
You sure it's not like eight by six?
Well, I even have this as a 15 by 15 level.
All right, so we have six here.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I mean, it can just be this whole fucking thing.
Any more sixes?
There are.
Or high numbers?
What about one, two, three, four?
Damn it.
This stream is boring.
Well, I'm sorry that you think that.
But it is.
This is not what I wanted to do tonight.
I kind of got fucking screwed.
My Dreamcast overheated and exploded.
And I wasn't able to play the Dreamcast thing that I wanted to do.
We're just relaxing.
I'll probably call it here in like an hour.
What am I doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow, I think I'm healthy enough to do VR again.
I'm pretty sure I'm good to go.
The last couple of days, I really wanted to just not do it.
I have like another four or five VR experiences I want to do.
So expect Minecraft VR.
Yes, it's going to happen.
Minecraft VR is going to be tomorrow.
And probably a handful of other things.
And I can't fucking believe.
Here's the worst part about that.
That stream will probably have the highest view count of any stream I've done in the last year.
Last time I played Minecraft for like an hour,
my view count went up by like a thousand to two thousand people.
I don't know why, but it's okay.
It's all good.
Over ten thousand?
No, I don't think so.
I would be surprised if that stream had that many.
No way.
But that's what we're going to do tomorrow.
I'm definitely healthy enough again to do it.
But for now, we're just chilling out.
Just playing this little pick-ross game.
We're dialing it back a little.
And we'll get back to it tomorrow.
If you got somewhere to be, if you got somewhere to go,
or if you think it's boring, then we'll see tomorrow.
You know, it's okay.
Not every stream has to be fucking crazy.
You know, sometimes you just paint a picture
and do it very slowly because you're bad.
But with that being said, let's go.
Let's just keep playing.
Whatever the music.
He's picking out all the one negative comments.
Yeah, but I want to be, let's be real about it.
I'm playing pick-ross.
When I told everybody like,
Space Channel 5 tonight, guys.
Space Channel 5.
You already, oh yeah.
Choo, choo.
Can't wait.
That makes sense.
So this is one, one, yeah.
This is the two.
Also one, also one.
But yeah, VR will be tomorrow.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
It's not enough.
Is there a derma discord?
There is.
It's open to the public.
There are a couple of sub-only.
Well, there's only one sub-only room, actually.
I can't make it tomorrow.
Will you cancel it?
No.
It's not going to be a long stream.
All my VR streams are less than four or five hours.
So it's okay.
You go, you can, you catch it.
It's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Now we got some info.
Mike, no.
Okay, this is part of the three then.
Three.
Which way?
Well, it's definitely not here.
Two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
No.
To the stream again tomorrow, another day.
Just put aside five hours.
Yeah, and I can't, I can't expect everybody to make every stream.
What kind of psycho would I have to be to assume that everybody is going to be at the stream
for five, four, five, six, seven plus hours?
You know, people have shit to do.
Got, you know, some people got places to be, things to do.
That's a lot.
Like, there's a commitment to sit here for, you know, eight hours.
Some of you, like a lot of you guys stick around for a long time.
So this is the one then.
However long you stay, that's, I'm fucking happy you came.
Okay, two, there's three.
All right, getting somewhere.
Three, cover that.
So let's see what happens here.
One, two.
No, I just, I don't know that info yet.
Where bots were not actually here.
Oh yeah, I see 2,800 unique IPs.
That's not true.
I don't have that information.
One, two, three.
One, two, three, sit one, two.
All right, let's go right there.
Doesn't really help that much.
No, not really.
We're special bots, so we get our own IPs.
Are you pulling, are you pulling my leg here?
I think you might be.
God, some of you guys just tell tall tales.
One, two, there's four.
So one, two, three, four.
No, this might be that one.
We're either here or we're here.
No way to tell.
Shit, a lot of ones.
Modest Narcissist, 10 community subs.
Thanks a lot.
10 more community subs on top of all the other ones.
And all the fucking money.
Thank you.
I'm kind of stuck here.
One of these I know can be filled in.
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three.
It's probably there, but it could be here too.
Okay, I just got it.
I got it.
All right, I just had to look at it first.
Okay, good, good, good.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Block that out and go.
Good, get rid of this.
There's the two, there's the six.
One, two.
Oh, it's just wonderful.
That one's done.
Two, three.
All you need, it's cascades once you get one.
Once you fill in, you see it, your mind locks in.
And then bingo, the whole thing gets filled in.
That's two leaves us one.
One more.
It's probably up here.
There's one, two, three, four, five.
There's another one.
All ones across the board.
Now let's see here.
This is a three.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He blew it.
You had it and you blew it.
Because look now, this is only, I blew it.
Look, this is not part of the three.
It's one, one, three, two.
Shit.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
No, this is the one that was given.
So this, this has to be here.
Let me just keep troubleshooting this.
Because that's done.
This is done.
Let me see here.
Guess snail.
It's, yeah, it's definitely a snail.
Let me see if I can just draw the picture now.
It's here.
Okay.
One, two.
I'll get it.
No, no.
What happened here?
Where's the one here?
Here?
It's done.
It's so close.
Which is incorrect.
Here?
Fuck.
One, two, one.
No, this is not right.
Oh, one, one, I'm not seeing one thing.
I screwed it up.
I can't.
You do it.
You guys do it.
I'm too fucked up right now.
You do it.
I just do it.
Just do it.
Somebody do it.
I'm going to close all these out.
You're not going to fill A.
No, no.
Somebody do it.
Somebody get it.
I'll, somebody do it.
Clear G5.
You got it.
I'm just done.
My brain is fucking scrambled toast.
And fill in G4.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I'm not picking that one.
G5, L4.
Okay.
Looking good so far.
You guys are fucking bailing me out here.
Thank you.
Remove L4.
It's gone.
It's working.
And fill in L6.
Oh, thank goodness, you guys.
Thank you.
Well, congratulations, whoever guessed snail.
I'm telling you, it's music.
You guys wonder, why does he not have a playlist on?
I can't, I can't focus on anything going on.
Why does he not listen to music?
I can't.
Unless I'm like locked in a room.
This is one, two, three.
Any zeros?
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
No, it's not quite correct.
All right, this is music.
Okay, so one, two, three.
One, two, three.
The rest of this is garbage.
Get rid of it.
Can you put on my mixtape?
Maybe.
Depends on what it is.
This is one, one, two.
Let's see.
So we got two, one, one, one.
Two, one, one, one.
One, two.
Put on the rat's mixtape.
Well, there's five.
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, one.
Okay, so divide all this.
What the hell else do we have here?
Three.
Got to be here.
There's your seven.
Lightning on the gentleman.
Lots of ones.
There's the three.
Fill this rest of it in.
This is gone now, too.
So is this, and so is this.
And just that one up.
Cover that here.
What happened to Jerma's audio software stream?
Yeah, I know.
Too many ideas.
They're all gonna happen.
Did you see the Jerma is a liar video?
I did.
Play it again.
One.
This is two, one.
Filled in.
What is this music?
Is this a boomerang?
One, two, three, four, five.
Two.
Cool.
That's the rest of the eleven.
One, one, one, three.
That is a three here, too.
One, two, three, one, two, three.
We got four.
And then a one.
We got one, three.
Where's that four at?
Right there.
And then right here.
What is it?
Comb?
Oh, music, right.
It's a pan flute.
Hey, nice job, guys.
Hey, Jerma, thanks for these streams.
I can get through horror games more easily.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Don't get too scared.
Remember, it's not real.
Okay.
Got seven.
This is four.
Seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Can't do anything else.
This is gonna be hard.
I really appreciate these quiet streams
since I can be the one guy more often.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow is very, very...
It's rared up to be really loud and tense.
There'll be a loud one tomorrow.
You'll see.
So one.
Let's go with one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
So now we can figure this out, right?
Because it can't be up there.
So it's gonna be one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, space, two.
And got it.
No, I don't.
I don't know.
That's wrong.
What can I do with this?
Seven, two.
Well, there's a four here somewhere,
but I don't know where because I don't have any more blocks.
None of these can be figured out.
It's too little of them.
Dermabate.
I'm making you mental by not using the middle mouse button.
Yeah, I know.
It's just different play styles, you know?
Three, four, one, two.
So that has to be there.
There's the five.
Five can only be down, yeah?
Yep.
Now that hell unlocks this,
which in turn lets us determine that you got one, two, three, four.
Yes, I can do one, two, three, four.
Therefore, what about this one?
Three.
You can do one, two, three.
One, two, three, there.
Four.
Closing in on this one.
Let's see.
Still trying to...
This is four, two.
Just which way does this...
Because if this is here, right?
Say that's one, two, three, four.
Then it has to be either here.
No.
But if it's here, then it has to be here.
So I don't have enough info.
Dermabate wants to play RuneScape?
I mean, I've never played it.
I can do something with this knowing that the six is down here though.
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
So knowing that...
All right.
What does that lead us?
So that gives a few...
Bingo.
And all you got to do is unlock one.
The whole thing starts to complete itself.
Now this can go down.
All right.
Let's go one, two, three, four.
Or one, two, three, four.
So not enough info.
Yes, there is.
Because of that new line I just made.
Oh, that's some good cider, yeah?
I wish I had a cider right now.
I'd just be hanging out, sipping it.
So let's see.
That's done.
There's no way to know that.
Well, there's no way it's there.
So one, two, three, one, two, three.
Not enough info.
I mean, it really wants to be right here, doesn't it?
Five, two, and this is one.
One, two, three, cross that.
Okay.
Too much info on the screen for me.
Even though it's more desirable, I know.
Was this an accessory?
What kind of accessory is this?
So it's not here.
It's none of these.
It's not this one either.
Good to know.
It's Shito.
It is Shito.
I wonder if it's going to be yellow.
Shito.
No, it is a pipe.
Did we already do this one?
I feel like we did that one already last time.
Maybe not.
Hold on.
Let me take a look.
Yeah, we did do that one last time.
I was wondering.
See, look, we did it.
Remember mustache, watermelon.
This is where we left off.
This is tools.
Also 15 by 15.
This one looks interesting.
13, 14, 5, 8, 15.
So we can do this row.
So it's a tool.
And there are no zeros this time.
No.
No help this time.
13, did that.
All right.
Any more that I guarantee?
Let's see.
That's 3, 6, 12, 13, 14.
No.
7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Not quite.
I need to get something else here.
Some more data.
But let's cancel this stuff out over here.
So all these down here.
Okay.
Again, same thing with this one.
Any more?
That's a 1.
That's a 7.
That's a...
I can do this one now, can't I?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
5, 1, 2, 3, 4.
Nah, I can't.
Guys, get some pretty good guesses so far.
Who knows?
All right.
7, 1, 1.
Well, it has to be this way.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
There it is.
Maybe give us some more info.
There's 2.
Cross this whole thing out.
Is that 4?
3.
It's got to be here, right?
Yeah, because 1, 2, 3, and then 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Yeah, that's it.
Is that done?
Well, row gone.
13.
Close it.
14.
Nice.
There's the 5.
This is a really weird looking tool.
It's got an umbrella.
This actually could be an umbrella, maybe.
A fairly busted umbrella.
Let's not do that yet.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
There we go.
4 somewhere.
1, 2, 3, 4.
1.
Yep.
All right.
What are that?
Any more info?
What the hell is this tool?
Looks like a wine opener.
1, 4, right?
I mean, it has to be.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Don't know.
Could be anything.
5, 4, 1, 1.
There's your 1.
3, 1.
That's done.
Do I have this incorrect?
This looks completely wrong.
Doesn't this look completely incorrect?
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
2, 1 is the 2.
All right.
Almost done.
4 somewhere in here.
3.
No, the 1 is there.
This is the 2.
This is the end of that.
8.
Done.
3.
So now I have to consider where the 6 is.
Because that's 3.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Space.
1, 2, 3.
No, not quite.
That's done.
That makes things a little easier.
Because then, yeah.
Cool.
Is this a hammer?
That's clearly a hammer.
It's somebody holding a hammer.
Well, nice job.
Got another easy one here.
What time is it?
It's been about 5 hours.
I'll keep going.
I'm good to go.
Probably like a little while.
I think this is done already.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
I live it is.
Play some music?
I got one right now.
I like this is very, very...
It sits in the background.
It's not causing any problems.
My two halves can sit together.
I like this for now.
Yeah, it's pretty good coffee shop music.
This is really good weather channel music.
You know, while you sit there and watch
to see if your school got canceled.
Where are we?
1, 5, 6, 7, no.
But I can do this.
Because, I mean, if it's here,
let's just do that.
Because then it has to be space.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Okay.
Dude, school got canceled?
Are you serious?
I used to love that.
It was the best thing ever.
Nothing could compare to when you got up
on a snow-filled day.
Looked out the window.
Saw that there was a shitload of snow outside
and you're like, there's no way I'm going to school.
Somebody tells you, no school.
And you go, I cannot wait.
That's perfect.
Go outside for like 40 minutes.
Come back in and play Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles,
Turtles in Time all day.
What a day.
That's zero, zero.
This is also part of seven.
Well, wait a minute, hold on.
Can I just do this now?
No, not yet.
This might be the three.
This is the end of the four.
So let's just say 1, 2, 3, 4.
Right?
1, 2, 3, 4.
Those days were awesome,
but I'll never forget that day we were
the only school in the valley that didn't have
their school closed for weather.
Yeah, that sucked.
When you were certain that school was going to get canceled
and then no, it did not.
You had to go to school.
Or like a two hour delay, a one hour delay.
That was worse than just going to school
because then that sinking feeling in your gut.
Oh, there's a foot of snow on the ground.
One hour delay.
I would rather than add an hour to the top of school
than let me come in an hour late on a school day,
on a snow day.
That sucks.
All right, let's focus here.
So this is the two.
I don't know if this is the one or the three.
This is part of the seven.
So let's see.
I closed that down a little.
This could be the one.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Not much more info I can go on there though.
This is the one.
And let's let's see how one.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
No.
I don't know what to tell.
Not yet.
2, 7, 2, 1.
Let's see.
1, 7, and 1 could be down here.
Which means 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Awesome.
Does that do anything for me?
I don't think it does.
Unless this is a one.
No, it is.
So this is going to help here.
Whenever we had a delay,
my mom just called in to say it was too icy where we lived.
Fucking that's a 300 IQ mom play right there.
All right.
So let's just say that this is the four here.
So let's say that this is the one.
1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4.
All right, nice.
It's clearly the four.
For a 75 IQ kid?
How do you know that?
You don't have that information.
What do you mean?
Was that you?
Wait, who did you write?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did I just read maybe their best friends?
No, no.
How would you know that if it wasn't?
Did somebody somebody find that?
I they're friends.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
That could be possible.
How did you not figure that out?
I don't know because who knows?
This is the three here.
I figured that out.
So I was three.
All right.
This is an animal.
We're all friends.
We all have the same IQ.
I'm going to assume it's these two are both filled in.
In that case, then it would be aye, aye, aye.
Hold on.
This is five.
So one, two, three, five.
So that goes up this shit.
So then same thing with this.
Get rid of this nonsense, which in turn move those out of the way now.
Fuck.
There's another one over here.
Let's just say it's right there.
Combine our IQs together.
Me dumber since I start watching.
You're probably smarter.
You just feel dumber.
I think that helps here.
Yes, progress has been made.
I did it.
I clicked one.
Actually might be a rat.
So then the three is over here somewhere.
Wait, that's down there.
Yeah, that's the only place that can be.
I mean, it could be here, but then that would be one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
No, I don't know.
I can't tell if that's down there or not.
Fuck.
Well, this is obviously a two has to be back here.
So it's not this.
Oh, okay.
I just helped myself there.
That helps.
How much does that give me?
Enough.
Oh, perfect.
Okay, cool.
So this is seven now.
Fill that in.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One is somewhere over there.
Ten is filled in.
There you go.
Five could be anywhere right now.
Seven, start on two, three.
Well, I just threw that one completely under the bus for everybody that thought this was a rat.
It is absolutely not a rat.
It's very, it's a rat with a tall head.
Looks incorrect.
No, I can stay.
So, hey, look, perfect opportunity for a one.
What the hell is this?
Is this a bird?
I have no idea.
Well, let's just say, what the hell is that?
Four is somewhere here.
I need to figure this out.
Could be here though.
It could.
What?
Why is this down here?
It shouldn't have a detached leg.
Is this poo?
It's not poo.
Four, three.
This can be filled in.
No, it can't.
I think it has to, this one of these has to be here.
Because if, let's just say it's, if you got one, two, three, four, get a space,
which leads to one, two, three, or one, two, three.
It has to be there, I think.
I'm not certain though.
I'm going to keep that there.
That's not right.
What animal is this?
Yeah, I had it right.
I am stumped.
I don't know what, what this could remotely could be.
Is this the head over here?
Or is this the head here?
Or is the head down here?
Is it like curled up?
No, it is the two.
Okay, I still haven't figured that part out though.
It's done.
All right.
Is it a, it's probably a rooster probably.
Kangaroo?
Maybe.
This one's tricky though, because I can't, I just kind of need to, what is it?
It's a seagull!
Wow, four people got that.
Nice job.
Stream has been saved.
12, 13, 14, 15, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Let's see, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12.
Okay, same thing here.
11, 11, 12, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Nobody saw that.
Zero IQ.
That's 11.
So this is 12 down.
That's eight, nine, 10, 11.
He's got a fucking beef brain.
Well, that's the one.
Sure.
Let's continue down.
Six, three, seven.
Any more that I can do?
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11.
It's not 12.
So close.
This is a toy.
Three, go like this.
Let's see how much we can get here.
And it's one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, five.
Okay, anything else?
That's the one.
No, no more info there.
Six, we can do some of this.
Three, again, we can go like this.
Two is even better.
Seven, three, four, five, six, seven.
Okay, let's get to work.
Back to be two, one.
Rufor is wrong.
What do you mean?
Oh, I thought for some reason I thought it was the only the...
Yeah, I'm stupid.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's true, that's true, that's true.
Because look, there has to be a two in here.
Yeah, no, that's correct.
I had it right.
Just not this one.
The eight and the two.
What do you mean?
Other Xs.
This is row four.
This is the one here.
I mean, I guess technically you're right.
This could be the three, right?
Technically that you could be right.
No, I'll leave it.
All right, let's get started.
No two there.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Three, six, three, one, two, three, four, five, six.
Four is to work with.
There's the two.
There's a two in here somewhere.
There's the 11.
Two and then two.
I'll take a look at that.
Found them.
Found that two.
And then seven, nice.
Which then leads us to two.
Cover, cover, cover, cover.
Now this is great because look at this.
Say goodbye to everything up here.
Everything up here.
Not quite up here.
It's just row.
This game does not.
I don't think this game has an OST.
I'm pretty sure it doesn't.
It just has one song that plays some way over and over again.
All right, so this is definitely one, two, one, two, three, four, five, six.
This is part of the three.
Five, one, one, two.
No, I can do this now.
Five, two, two, three, six, nice.
Three, four, gone.
This could go either way for a little while.
There's two.
So then one, two, three.
Got to be right in the middle there.
And it has to be right there.
Thank you.
Eight, you got to connect these.
Fill in the three.
Where does that lead?
That's two, one, two, three, one, two, three.
I wish I had this one earlier.
Six, one, one, two, three, four, five, six.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That leads to one, two, three, four, five.
This is a toy.
I know what this is.
All right, this should be fairly self-explanatory now.
And then the four, and then the eight.
Rubber Duckie.
Congratulations to those of you that guessed it correct.
One, two, three, four, five.
A lot of you guys said boat.
Yeah, it looked a lot like a boat when we first started it.
Bath Duck.
Nobody says bath duck.
Bath Duck sounds like a Russian translation.
It's bath duck.
Let's see.
So this is 15 by 15, but it's actually not.
That's 14 across not quite what we're looking for.
I'll find a good one here.
I can still do it though.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
So let's just assume that this is in the middle.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I can do these.
And then over here, one, two, three, four, five, six.
So that's one, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I can get that done at least.
Is that far enough?
It is.
There's our six.
This is a food.
Food.
Knowing that, that's all I know at the moment.
Except this could be the...
This might be the two or the four.
Could it be the four?
One, two, three, four.
Space.
Not the four.
This has to be the four.
Which leads...
That's seven, five, two, two.
Let's see.
Two.
Well, let's do this.
Let's narrow it down because I can do some of this.
Wish I had something over here.
Seven, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
I can at least get it kind of narrowed.
This is the janitor game from yesterday.
I know this is a little more involved than the janitor game.
I will say.
Shit.
I got this one, yeah.
Yeah, no five.
This is five, four.
So five, it has to be here.
So do I have enough?
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four.
Nope.
That's enough info to get the middle, though.
Because again, let's assume that it looks like this.
And just go like that.
And then go like this, right?
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three.
I mean, I'm just going to assume this.
Now this is interesting because this makes this the one.
Same thing over here, right?
No.
This makes this the three.
If that's the case, that would make this the six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Yeah, I would make this the six.
Whoops, and this is a two.
Let's see.
Three, four, five.
This is an outside source from music.
It's not from the game itself.
Why is everybody doing the oh my god face?
I'm seeing a lot of oh my oh no face.
Why, what's happening?
What's wrong?
Whoa, that like blinked.
This has to be five in a row.
Narrowing this down.
Can I even get one here?
Nice, okay.
At least I can get that.
So these are all two, two, two.
Again, we got, it could be here, here, here, here.
That means that this is empty, right?
It has to be, at least.
And then this is two, four, two, one, two, three, four.
Still possible.
Can we leave the border's bookstore, dad?
No, I can do this shit for free.
I just have to pretend I'm reading books and pretend I'm browsing.
Two, three, four, five, three, four, five.
Ooh, I think we got it.
That's how you narrow it down.
Yes, okay.
So then now we got two.
Still got nothing over here.
Let me just get this out of the way because this is two now.
So it has to be here, here.
That one is not correct there.
One, two, one.
Again, that can be closed.
There's your two right there.
But is it?
I know that's correct.
But is this also a two here?
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
All right, slow it down here.
And that's one, two, fuck.
One, two, three, four, fuck.
No, what did I do wrong here?
What did I assume there?
Because that's one, two, three.
This was, this was here the whole time.
This is new here.
The one and three.
But that, uh, where did this go wrong?
I don't want to reset this.
I feel like just one block is wrong.
Three, two, move this.
Hold on.
One, one.
No, this, this is, this is the wrong, this row is wrong.
Something's fucked up here.
Because two and then five, how did this come up?
This is the correct part.
Yeah, this is fucked up.
Damn it, I'm gonna have to restart it.
Oh, it's the worst part when you play Picross.
You jumble up one thing and then you can't,
your brain has already done it.
So you try to go back and you're like, fuck.
What did I do wrong?
Three, two, two, four.
No, but that's not right.
Why, what's so wrong here?
You know what I mean?
Like this is so wrong.
Something fucked up in here.
Either this is wrong or this is wrong.
E and F seven.
E seven, F seven.
Something like right here is just bogus.
Just if I could just work around it.
Yeah, that's true.
I could just work around it.
So now one, two, three, four, five.
This is the only possibility is this.
It can't be anything else.
Then if that's the case, let me remove this.
So there's two here.
There's two again.
Two, there's the two.
Cover that.
There's your three.
There's your two.
There's your four.
I think I fixed it.
Yeah, I think I got it.
Yep, and there's five.
Perfect.
Okay, thank God.
There it is.
Okay, nice.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, it's wrong again.
What happened here?
Because two and then four.
All right.
Is everything else intact still?
I think so.
Everything's intact.
Guess resident sleeper.
That's not what it is.
I'm going to try again.
Well, that takes care of that.
All right, saved.
One, two, three, four, seven.
I've got a lot to erase here.
All right, it's two again.
I think it's resident sleeper.
Close.
Close, very close.
So this is a food.
What type of food is this?
Uh-oh, and then, and then.
Oh, it's so close.
It's right here.
Got it.
What is it?
Cookie?
It looks like a croissant.
Look at that croissant.
A lot of you did, actually.
Nice work.
Meme food.
I love croissants.
The problem with croissants is
I never order them because
it doesn't matter how you try to eat a croissant.
You get sawdust all over you
like you're in shop class.
Bite into a croissant
and there's just shavings of wood everywhere.
Don't eat that shit in your car.
Like you made a birdhouse
in like the, in your passenger side.
10, 11, 12.
All right, it's 15.
This is construction.
Speaking of construction.
And don't eat in your car.
Pay attention to the damn road.
All right, so we got 11, 12, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
So 11, 12, 13, 14, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Okay.
What about over here?
10.
Take a look at this.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Cool.
Sick.
Nice.
Yeah.
This is definitely not a three.
God, I love Picross.
I have an unhealthy obsession with these games for some reason.
Me too.
I come back to it.
They have a couple of great ones for iPad.
I just open my mouth and lie in bed on iPad
and play these maybe like once or twice a week.
Picross, yeah.
I say Picross because it's like saying Reese's.
Reese's Pieces.
I don't say Reese's Pieces.
We've had a conversation about this, I know.
But it's nice to come back and see
how we're doing in that conversation.
So now what?
Well, that's not a three.
Neither is that.
Narrow down our 11 here.
Doesn't help very much.
It's Reese's.
There's no wrong way to eat a Reese's.
And there's no wrong way to say Reese's either.
All right.
Let's put this to bed once and for all.
Everyone's saying I'm wrong.
You're wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
Let's see.
I'm curious.
I just want to get a poll and chat's opinion on the whole thing.
Every stream is the same argument over pronunciation.
Yeah.
Some people have accents.
Some people say things differently.
Come on.
That's one.
So two, space, one.
So it could be there and then here we go.
So here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Thank you.
Another one.
I don't, I hate when there's too many ones.
Well, so 30% of you guys from the sampling here say it that way as a Reese's.
The bookstore is closing.
No, I'm like, I'm not leaving.
I'm not leaving the bookstore.
What else can I do here?
There's shit posting.
So, well, it's definitely not down here because this is the three.
One, two, three.
So look at that.
We got our nine and our two.
Is it the whole thing?
Oh, I'm stupid.
Just fucking Reese posting.
Reese's PCs.
It's how I've been saying it since I was a kid.
I can't change it now.
I have to, no, Reese's PCs.
Then you were wrong as a kid.
That's fine.
I'd like how it sounds better.
Fair enough.
There's a one in here somewhere.
Might be here.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Something's wrong here.
What's wrong here?
This is not, this is all right.
This is fine, right?
Oh, this is okay.
The future is now, old man.
What do you mean?
I don't know what that means.
I mean the future is now.
Is that too many tens?
Your time is up.
My time is now.
I got plenty of time.
What do we got?
Well, one's one.
One, three, one.
This is some kind of construction.
Was it building material?
Wood?
I would say wood.
This could be one, one, three.
I don't want to blow it.
This on the other hand is one.
This is three here.
How does that change this?
All right.
Where's this last three right here?
No, don't guess.
Three, one, three.
Sure don't miss any place I can fill in.
Right there.
And this three is the right there.
All right.
What is it?
Stairs?
Oh, damn.
Okay.
I think that makes sense.
A lot of twos.
Two, four, six, eight, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen.
Damn it.
Not enough twos.
I can start off down here though.
That's good.
This whole bottom area is just three.
Cool.
It helps a lot.
And there's our three right here.
Perfect.
There's another two.
Another two.
That's a one.
Yes.
Shit, a lot of twos.
Keep that in mind while we're progressing.
Two, three.
Here.
More twos.
Two, two, two, two, two, two, two.
It's probably mirrored, right?
I would assume.
Is it mirrored?
No, it's not.
It's my turn.
No, it's my turn.
Three.
There's another one.
All right.
So weirdly enough, this is not mirrored.
Why?
Two, two, one, one, two.
Two, one, one, one, two.
I'd like a turn, please.
No.
So this is from fantasy.
Whatever that means.
Concerned that this is wrong already.
But I don't think it is.
There's too many spaces here.
What about here?
This is another one.
Another one.
And another one.
Okay.
Is he enough?
Same thing over here?
That's all I can go off of at the moment.
No, this like fucks with my head.
All right.
Slow down.
It's one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
So none of these in the middle are going to be filled in.
Any others like that?
Yeah.
Three.
One, two, so one, two, three.
All right.
Any more like that?
Maybe.
What is telling you to fill in what squares?
We're like really relaxed.
We're just chill now.
I can explain it.
Because there are actually people that are asking questions.
You know, people are asking questions.
So let's start with this.
The cubes that you're filling in correspond to the numbers.
So for instance, three.
That means that there has to be three squares filled in in a row for this number here.
This way, right?
Because on this row.
Now, the one here means that after you, the three,
there has to be at least one space before that one comes into play.
So again, let's just say for the sake of just doing it,
it was three, space, one, space, right?
Because there's a space before this one.
One, space, two, right?
That would be, this is not correct.
But that space can be one or it can be eight.
Doesn't matter.
And you're supposed to logically deduce,
I just fucked up this whole line.
What was it?
No, okay, I'm fine.
That is only one.
Yeah.
So if it's 15 by 15, you start,
for instance, see how I started down here.
Filled in all 15, all 15 again.
And that completed these rows.
Now what happens is then take a look up here, right?
Because this is the top of the grid.
This is the bottom of the grid.
So you work from the bottom up here.
So see how that's two.
Both are filled in here.
That's done.
So then you put a marker here
because you know that there has to be at least one space.
See how down here, once I filled in this row again,
there's three, one, two, three has to get filled in.
Marker has to go here.
It's very interesting, very relaxing.
And it makes a picture.
That's the best part.
Okay, but how do you play it?
You know how to play.
I don't get it.
I'll make it really easy after this level.
For the handful of people.
Yeah, I mean, there's 2,500 people here.
And maybe 2,400 of you get it.
But what about the new people that came in
that just want to, you know, are curious?
We're just hanging out.
It's not like, it's not a big deal.
Not a big deal at all.
It's fine.
All right, so let's get back to it.
Three, I sense sarcasm.
No, that's an old reference.
This could be the one, because then that's two.
But I did give myself this, which is good.
So this could be one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
So, okay.
No, that's not, I don't have that info.
Because that would mean it could be here, but it's not.
So I got another two, right?
Because it's two, two, two.
Same thing on this one, right?
No, that's two, one.
So that's three, one.
That's a one, which makes this the three.
Perfect, done.
No info required.
Somebody just guess ham.
Why would this be ham?
Two, one.
Two, wait, wait, wait.
That's one.
Wait a minute, two, one, one.
This could be two.
What about this one?
Two, two, two.
Need more info down here.
Yes, space invader.
Now that's a pretty good one.
That's actually a really good guess.
It very well could be.
Let's fill this shit in, because this has to be here or here.
And one, two, three.
This is all no.
And this is filled in.
Two, two, two, two.
This is done.
Okay, nice.
Is it?
I'm confused.
I'm going to lead us up here.
Is this four, one?
One, two, four, two.
Four, one, two.
Four, one.
Could be up there.
Four, one, one.
But that could be one, one.
So let's leave that here for a second.
See what we did up here.
This is one, this is three.
There's the two, nice.
Still not sure about down here.
Two, one, three.
So could this be two, one, one, three?
No, this is it.
So this could be anywhere here.
All right, got that though.
Three, two, one.
All right, this is interesting.
It's either here or here.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I can't denominate this.
Hold on, let me see here.
All right, now I got this now.
So that's two, one.
One, two, right?
Because then now is that.
This would be three.
Don't want to get sloppy.
I'm missing a lot over here.
Let's see, two, one, one, one, two.
That's four, close it up.
That's three, close it.
This is done now.
All right, I'm almost done.
What even?
Maybe this actually might be a space invader.
I have nothing in this row.
How?
One, two, three, two, two.
No, for some reason I thought it was going to count higher than that.
Two, and there's the one.
Yes.
So, well, didn't fill that one in.
All right.
Where are you?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Over here, I'm over here.
Well, it could be here.
Two, two, three.
Well, the one is obviously right there.
In there somewhere, that's done.
There's three.
All right, closing in.
Six, one, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Seal it.
Two, two, what is it?
Spider?
Space invader?
It's a cave, a dungeon.
Nobody got it.
I don't know how you would have.
This is a very long music track.
It's, we've been listening to this for an hour and 44 minutes.
That's kind of surprising.
All right, electronic.
What time is it?
How are we doing?
Six hours.
I'm, I'm still all right.
I'm still just hanging out.
We're not done.
I'm going to go for like another little while.
Put on the Tetris OST.
But we're so relaxed.
All right, this is Tetris 99, full official soundtrack.
Regular Tet, like you mean like the
You can fill this whole thing in.
I need more ones.
I need more.
It's filling the zeros first.
What the hell am I doing?
Anymore.
Well, I found the first one.
And then it could be one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Nice.
Fill that out.
How are we now?
One still.
By this point, you should have had consumed at least 24 ounces of water.
Uh, I'm probably pretty close.
I've had a glass of water here the whole time.
Well, this is, this is the six.
Therefore, this is the six.
Then this has to be one, one.
It's info I don't have, but I can do at least those two.
What's the song called?
This is called Tetris 99 Main Theme.
You can download it off of the internet somewhere and enjoy it with your friends.
You can throw a party if you wanted to and put it on a six and a half hour repeat.
You could, I'm not saying you should, but I'm just saying it's possible.
Torrenting Tetris music.
No, that's not what I mean.
This has to be the six, right?
Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
One of these is the two.
This one's probably the two.
If not, then it's down here.
Well, here's the eight.
How much did I fill in?
I forget.
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
I'm just gonna go like this.
That's more info than I had before.
I'm okay.
Is it all filled in?
Get a one and then a two up here somewhere.
This is something electronic.
Six.
So many ones.
Three, one, three.
More ones.
All right, what is this two?
You want the pirate marching band?
Why?
Do you really want me to put on the pirate marching band right now?
I...
Okay, hold on a minute.
This video has almost a million views.
There's a 737, 34,000 view video
and then a 173,000 re-upload for 10 hours.
This video has almost...
This video has been seen a million times.
Really?
I didn't even know that.
Holy shit.
Here it comes.
I little did I know that this year...
This many years later.
This stupid thing that I did.
Played at half speed.
Also not even true.
This is how I found out about you.
I imagine that conversation.
Hey, here's this guy that I have watched.
Check him out.
Two.
Don't you wish this was broadcasted nationally 4 AM
at everyone's alarm clocks?
I'm not entirely certain that I would like to do that
because that would probably get really bad.
Something just auto-played.
This is YMCA, but it's got a twist.
How long is this?
There are so many rat remixes.
I've heard a bunch of them.
All right, where am I going here?
Probably down here.
I can't focus on anything else.
Two, three, I have six.
One, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Ah, three, one, one.
I'm getting speech jammed.
It's still going.
I can't do it with this music playing.
Why did that take this long to play these songs?
I don't know.
It just kind of never came up.
I need more info.
A poor craftsman blames his tools.
Or, okay, if you were making a birdhouse
and I came in and started going,
Retch, retch, we had a retch.
In your ear, you'd probably be like,
what are you doing?
No, no, no.
What's the next one?
This is the mixtape.
I think this is just the original one.
I can't.
Yeah, I know that that's on osu!
Where am I?
I'm like going forward, forward, forward.
I skipped the best part?
What do you mean the best part?
What happened to my smooth jazz?
I was working on my brain function.
How long does it take you to make those lyrics?
Uh, six or seven minutes, probably.
Maybe ten minutes.
There's a new one that I have.
And it was supposed to be for the third one.
I might as well just do it.
I might as well just tell you what it was.
Yeah, well, this is a secret chillout stream.
Would you like to load the lyrics for the third rat song?
Because I can't imagine a time
where I'm going to be able to work on it for real.
And if you hear it, it's fine.
So it was a little play on words.
it's the same sentence, but three times means different things.
Are you ready?
So it starts off like a like a rap beat almost.
And it goes.
where they at where they at there you go that actually was the whole song it is
that's how it is gonna be like bunches fucking trumpets sounds gonna make a
real one that's fine yeah it was where the rats where the rats just where the
rats where they at where they at yeah where the rats like this you know now
you already you know yeah like where the rats then where are the rats where
they at they've got to come out of the sewers and shit while it was
playing they're all gonna get more crowded more people more rats singing at
the same time that's where to go that that that's the song that is the song
let's go make it let's make it right now yeah fuck it I'll bear it back
hold on I'm still going I remember I said seven to eight minutes it was
probably a lie probably took like 30 probably like an hour let me get let
me make sure this is going here I wasn't just gonna pull a song from
royalty-free I was gonna have it made so there's no song to go along
with it I can zoom in here I'm gonna do take figure oh yeah here
comes a take a live take I'll do I'm gonna do one part of it it's easier to
do in two breaths and that's a little bit of them this has a little cleaner
you want to make that I'll just make the fucking thing right now hold on
it's gonna be louder though it's kind of soft and I'll just do like a
little I'll do like a little beatbox behind it
where the rats where the rats just where the rats need to be a little
higher than that not that much rat lore incoming I
wouldn't say rat lore let's see how does this sound
no a little off here I moved it too much I need to really unfortunately have
to crank my microphone for this I really don't think I can actually do it
on stream it's a way off key as well way off key it's got to change I was
here that's not bad let me turn this up
I am here six years later he did it on stream in 20 minutes perfect okay
how about the next part next part is to be a little bit more a little bit more
synced up here audacity why do you suck what's going on here why can I not
move this oh that's why something is wrong here what's going on
audacity what are you doing wait yeah audacity what are you doing to me
why can I not drag this what the hell the fuck is going on here yeah
for some reason I cannot move the track anymore it's like broken you know
audacity really is terrible for recording tracks but I kind of just
threw this open so I don't understand why I can't do this I've done this
probably I've done this probably a thousand times and I cannot select this
and move it and now magically I didn't even magic I can do it now
somebody has magic fucking potions see how this sounds
not bad not bad maybe needs a little bit more on the end here and then I'm
gonna copy it once and I'll give you a real take how's this we're gonna retch
whether yet whether yet yet we're gonna retch good we're gonna retch we're
gonna retch just we're gonna retch pull that forward a little just a hair
we're gonna retch we're gonna retch just we're gonna retch we're gonna get
all right here comes a new take
yeah it's problem with audacity is when you record it puts everything else off
sync for some reason you can't have to go back in this is just for fun I'm
I'm not really trying to get it perfect or anything, I just want to get you an idea.
Need two headphones in for this.
I don't like that one.
I like the end of that though.
No.
Do it again.
No, do it again.
It's going to be like, way to yet, way to yet.
Way to retch, way to retch, just way to retch.
Fucking audacity.
Way to yet, way to yet, way to yet, way to retch.
No, why?
Way to retch, way to retch, just way to retch.
Okay, let's change that a little bit.
This is how you do it, man.
This is what I used to do.
I used to sit here and fucking do this all day.
Way to retch, way to retch, just way to retch.
That's not so fucking wrong.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah.
Way to retch, way to retch, just way to retch.
No, that's too low.
Way to retch, way to...
Way to retch, way to retch, just way to retch.
That's the tone I'm looking for.
I think we can get this copied a couple times.
Yeah, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
This one's a little too low.
I'm going to give another take here.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
Yeah, way to retch.
No, that would be like...
Way to retch, way to retch.
Uh-uh.
Way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
No, that's wrong.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
Way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
Yeah, yeah, way to retch.
Uh-uh.
Just way to retch.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
No, I can't.
Move this to creative.
I'd have to show it.
Way to retch, way to retch.
No.
Yes, way to retch.
When it comes up like that.
I'm naked right now in front of you guys.
You understand that, right?
You're seeing me completely undressed in front of you.
Way to retch, way to retch.
Yes, way to retch.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
He's fucking naked.
Now let me just get the next part, because this is fine.
Way to retch, way to yet, way to retch.
This part needs to be moved, but...
Yeah, way to retch.
Okay.
Then it's...
Way to retch, way to retch.
Yes, way to retch.
Way to yet, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
Uh-uh.
Way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
Way to retch.
Uh-uh.
Way to yet, way to yet, yeah, way to retch.
Way to retch, way to retch.
Yes, way to retch.
Way to yet, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
The VRB screen is still on.
You clown.
Yeah, way to retch.
Way to retch.
Way to retch, way to retch.
Yes, way to retch.
Way to retch, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
I like that end here.
Okay.
I should be able to see it now.
At least I think you can.
Can you see it?
No.
I have to move this.
Hey, look at that!
Okay, so as you see here...
Way to retch, way to retch.
Yes, way to retch.
Way to yet, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
I like the end here.
I don't like the beginning.
Way to retch, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
I like that part.
Let me see.
Way to retch, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
Way to retch, way to yet, way to yet, way to yet.
I like that part.
That's almost unhuman how much that is the same.
That's way too close.
Let's go to...
Change the pitch a little bit.
It sounded a little creepy.
Let's drop it a lot and see what happens.
way to get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
way to get
I gotta get a really really mean one too
way to get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to get
every other way to heck should be lower
way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to
get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way
to get way to get way to get way to
get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to
get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to
get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get way to
get way to get way to get way to get
way to get way to get way to get
wait a rat
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I don't know
hold on
once was a man named gold rodrits
he had fame
power
and wealth
beyond your wildest dreams
before they hung him from the gallows
these were the final words he said
my fortune is yours for the ta-
come true
since pirates
have been a grand lot
searching for one piece
the treasure that would make their dreams come true
yeah
now you're just dreaming
don't give it up
blue face
no
give it up
dream it
don't give it up
don't give it
no
that's not even
come on
if that went to court
I wouldn't fucking lose
okay
I would win that case
here's how the story goes
we find out
by the treasure in the grand lot
there's no doubt
the pirate whose eye
is on it
he'll sing
I'll be king of the pirates
I'm good at everything
all right
and I
I ain't losing cell phone
woman up
dreaming
don't give it up
blue face
dream it
So long, don't give it up now, baby.
Don't give it up, don't give it up, don't give it up.
Throw it out.
Throw that out of court.
Doesn't belong here.
GoldenEye faculty music?
What the fuck are you talking about?
This way to rat, this way to rat, this way to rat,
this way to rat, this way to rat.
That's perfect to go by.
How would you even fucking think about that?
I have no idea.
All right, let's go back to the puzzle.
Let's finish what we were doing here.
And then I'm probably gonna call it.
And we'll do VR tomorrow.
Back into the headset.
I feel pretty good.
I'll be good to go.
Holy shit, this was a puzzle stream.
Yeah, it was.
Gonna finish, this is electronics.
Well, it's on the plate for VR.
I'm gonna do Minecraft VR just to get it out of the way.
And then after that, or maybe before that,
depending on how hard it is to set that up.
I do have at least three or four more VR games to play.
And then, so we had a stream yesterday,
stream today, stream tomorrow.
And then after tomorrow,
you're not gonna see me for a few days.
Taking a few days off in a row.
I've got some company that's coming up.
So I wanna spend some time with them.
So after tomorrow,
you will not see me until three days later.
Just wanna make sure you tell you no.
All right, finish this puzzle.
And then I'm gonna call it for the night.
I gotta clean this shit up, yeah, I know.
Fucking PictoPix again.
No, look, all right, I'm just gonna call it now.
I'm just gonna call it now.
That's the end of the stream.
Thanks for coming.
You know what, you guys do it.
You guys finish it up.
All right, let me finish this.
Self-conscious streamer, it can't get over it.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
All right, six has to go up this way.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Let's just say it's probably up here.
Has to be at least one of those.
There's three.
Am I gonna play Devil May Cry for Sekiro?
I'm gonna play Sekiro day one.
So the day that Sekiro launches, I will be streaming it.
I'm going to enjoy that game.
I'm gonna play very, very patiently.
I'm gonna just love the fuck out of it.
So when is the gamer duel with Joel?
That's a good question.
Joel and I just recently became Discord friends.
So probably not,
probably that's probably not gonna happen
until after I get back from seeing friends.
We'll see.
Anywho, how are we doing here?
One, two, three, one, two, three.
Don't have enough info for this,
but we do have enough info to go here.
Cause that's that.
After all this time, you know?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
I just don't know which way.
One, one, one.
Is Discord friends marriage?
I don't think so.
I would say no.
What about down here?
I don't have enough info to fill that in.
It's three and three,
but it's don't have enough info.
I need more up here,
but how the fuck am I gonna get that?
I need to cancel some shit out up here.
I could do this,
which then lets me do that.
All right, keep going.
So it's pretty much mirrored until down here.
Six, um, damn, one, one.
I would say right here,
but it could be here too.
No, no, it couldn't.
No, it couldn't.
No, it could not.
Let's go with, this is done now.
All right, that's enough info.
Let's go.
That's three.
Perfect.
Three again.
All right.
Getting there.
Another three.
This is the six.
Perfect.
Five is gonna be right in the middle here.
Ooh, feels good.
Two, one, one, one, one.
There's eight.
Almost done.
Cool.
Two.
Yes.
Gotta be here.
Close it.
There are four.
Hmm.
Has to be right here.
This is kind of freaking me out though.
So it's gonna be back this way.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Maybe not.
Okay, so two, two.
Nice.
Almost done.
This is all filled in except the top rows here.
Hmm.
Interesting.
What is it?
CPU?
Chip?
Microchip.
Good work everybody.
And that's it.
I'm gonna call it here.
Thanks for watching this absolute mess
of a fucking live stream.
This is the third game.
Had some technical issues with the first one.
Second one was all right.
It was good.
I have nothing really bad to say about the second one
except for the fact that I'd rather just chill
and play Picross.
Tomorrow, VR.
We'll do a good four or five hours in VR tomorrow.
And then I'm gonna take the next few days off.
See you real soon.
Let's get to the bits and the subs.
Thank you guys for sticking around.
And again, sorry for a stream
that was all over the place.
Hope you still had fun.
Let's move on to the end.
Let's go.
What do you say?
All right.
See you tomorrow if you're taking off.
If you're not taking off,
we have a little bit of this to get through.
A whole lot, not a million.
Get some shit open.
Came to the last hour, but I had fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
Good.
What?
I think I'm about to close my Twitch window
when I had Audacity open somehow.
Let's open it back up, please.
Okay.
Cool, cool, cool.
So let's go back.
Earlier, about seven-ish hours ago,
we had a 250 from Lazy Luke.
No, this is yesterday.
Sorry.
I'm stupid.
Here we go.
Sad Vega, thanks for the three bucks.
Appreciate it.
Space Jenify part one, baby.
Woo, what a blast.
I'm making cheesy goji to Crunch Tacos homemade
and boy, they're good.
Also, did you up the cost of three to be read out loud
and we still doing the ones?
Very curious to know.
250.
I'm sorry that you were so excited for Space Jenify.
I was too.
Maybe I was doing something wrong.
I don't think I was though.
Something was going, something was wacky.
250 is the minimum for me to read.
And again, I wanna make sure I reiterate this too.
Just because you give 250 doesn't mean I'm going to read.
Obviously something that I still have to be
comfortable reading.
Maybe it's something that I don't really wanna address
or talk about, I may not address it.
And a lot of times, sometimes people even put
in their messages to not say these things.
So fair enough, fair enough, right.
But it's 250.
But again, it is also at my discretion.
He didn't answer if he ate ass.
I already did, I did.
But anyways, sad Vega.
Glad you're feeling better.
Also, whatever happened to Dr. A, Dr. Agon's,
Dragon's Dogma.
I was gonna try and play alongside you.
So you could have some pawns not named Poopypants
or awful things.
Hope we get back to that sometime soon.
Isn't the creator interested in making a new one?
I should have just played that today.
Well, I mean, P-Cross is just on the mind.
I probably should have just opened that today.
That would have been like a perfect opportunity.
Oops, oh well.
It's coming out on Switch, that's amazing.
But after Devil May Cry 5,
you're gonna make another one, right?
But thank you, sad Vega.
Thank you, Pro Star for the five bucks
with the John Halo Master Chief Collection coming to PC.
Do you think you'll play those games on Steam?
I'm gonna say no.
I don't think so.
Unless like people really wanna see that,
would you guys really wanna see me play Halo 1
on stream?
The story mode?
Is that something that people would wanna watch?
I feel like the Halo games are,
you know, just kind of shooters with the story.
I don't know if it's something I'd wanna stream.
They're great games, but just kind of a story shooter.
The multiplayer, are they turning on the multiplayer?
Like will Halo 2 be online on Steam?
Well, that's a big deal.
Okay, that's a big, I didn't know that they,
I thought maybe they were just gonna turn
the servers off or something.
I just, it's just the, oh, okay, that's it.
I might even just play the multiplayer for fun.
Community maps too, holy shit, that's amazing.
That's a lot of money.
Dye335 just gave $200, two, holy shit.
He just gave 20,000 bits.
He just dropped a gigantic bit bomb.
200 bucks.
Thank you, first of all, Dye.
Been watching your videos since before.
Twitch back in 2011, honest to God,
best streamer I've ever watched, that's, thank you.
Anytime anybody says something like that,
I always wanna try to do better.
That means an absolute fuck ton.
Thank you so much for the $200, Dye.
So much more money as well tonight.
There was so much money from other people.
50, 50, 50, 20, 20, 20, 30, 15, 15, 30, 30.
Thank you guys all so much, for real.
That's a shit load of money.
I am spoiled rotten.
I'm glad you think this stream is worth paying for.
I'm gonna keep trying to do better.
Very important point.
Can always strive to do better,
to try more, to do more things.
So I appreciate it.
Jess, you got it, thanks for the 250.
I think this was summarized history,
but it sounds like slam poetry.
What is it?
Something that I said?
War bad.
Spice trading.
Trade sugar, tobacco trading.
Economies, collapses.
Entrepreneurship, industry, steam.
Am I playing the $100,000 pyramid?
Natural gas.
What are we, what's going on?
England?
England.
America.
Slam poetry.
Oh, that's the C-Man.
The C-Man stream, right.
Okay, I remember.
That sounds like something my English teacher would do.
You sure we're not the same person?
Thank you, Jess, you got it for the 250, and the clip.
Hey, Kristen, thanks for the five bucks.
Left, right, choo-choo, hey, hey, hey.
Left, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing.
That's a pretty good summary of Space General 5 part one.
Thank you.
I'm sad that I couldn't really get that to go.
It was kind of futile.
I didn't want to give that game a bad name
because I love that series.
I just love that game.
It probably is the fact that I just didn't have a CRT.
On the bright side, the VR game you think
is a remake of part one.
Well, that actually, the cards all fall
in a perfect spot, if that's true.
So that's, we'll just play that.
Where are we?
I got lost here, there we are.
Hey, grapplemace, thanks for the 250.
Any chance of another stream like Picross?
I honestly loved it.
PS, where are the Pikachu socks?
We bought you for Christmas, BibleThump.
What a, grapplemace, that was six hours ago.
Any chance of another Picross stream?
Well, if you are still here, there you go.
If you're not here anymore and you might catch the Vod,
you're gonna be happy about that.
Thank you, though.
Thank you, Freudian Weapon.
I am here, thank you for Picross.
Thank you, grapplemace, for sticking around for that long.
Hope you liked the Picross.
And then Freudian Weapon of 250 from Freudian.
This game makes me want to dance.
I think the aliens are taking over my brain.
Nose wipe, yes.
They tend to do that.
We had, I'm getting, they moved.
We had a bunch of community subs tonight.
I think I missed some of them, too.
Let me see.
The Lake Drinker had five community subs.
Epic gave five community subs.
Kazzy, five community subs.
Thank you, guys.
Also Castillion, or Castalion, gave 10 bucks.
Hey, Gerber, sending my love from New Zealand.
It's been rough here, given what's happened.
But I just want to tell everyone
that they're good people and a great community.
Regards, a Kiwi fan.
That's absolutely fucking terrible what happened.
Actually, last night I was just kind of reading up on it.
And it's just fucking terrible.
Yeah, this shit is absolutely heartbreaking.
It's one of those scenarios where you just wish
that shit wasn't real.
Just sitting there in bed last night,
just going over, reading on my iPad,
different things, and just seeing what happened.
Because last night it was, somebody mentioned it.
I didn't even know what happened.
And then just, you're lying down,
you're just sitting there staring at the ceiling,
just going like, why the fuck is this shit real?
Absolutely fucking horrible tragedy.
But thank you so much, Castillion.
Thank you for 10 dollars.
And stay safe.
And you read more about it today.
That's why it's just, it's so,
it's just such an awful fucking feeling.
I just wish people were fucking better to each other.
Really.
It's awful, awful shit.
But regardless, we're gonna move on from that.
Thank you again, Castillion, and again.
Stay safe, all of you.
That goes for everybody.
And right after that, there was,
there was 150 dollars thrown in here
from something or other, Juno, SEPTO,
something or other, they gave 100 bucks.
Just dropping, just huge stacks of money on this stream.
It's, thank you, guys.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
from the bottom of my fucking heart.
That's a lot of money.
And La Cranda, 100 bucks.
I just forgot how much money was back here.
La Cranda, 100 bucks.
Smashly, 50 bucks.
Jesus.
You guys are, you guys are too much.
Really.
Hydrate.
I'm good, I got one here.
When the stream's over, I'll go get something to drink.
To drink.
100's not 100 bucks, but any amount of money
that somebody gives the stream is appreciated.
I wanna make that really clear.
I know that some people say, no, 250.
Oh, that's, he's increasing the bids.
What if he does it again?
If you give a cent, it's wildly appreciated.
I don't want it to be one of those goal posts
that I keep moving like, yeah, come on out here.
You wanna say something, that'll be fucking 10 bucks.
That's not the intention.
That's not why I'm doing it.
That's not why I did it.
You can't give a cent.
Right, oh yeah, that is because if one cent,
yeah, all right, hold on.
If you have one cent on bids,
somebody can put a quarter down
and just spam the chat with one cent donations.
So that's why it's 25 cent minimum.
If like 50 people bought a dollar
and then all of them just spammed one cent cheers,
it would just be like, it would just be a mess.
But he appreciates every one of those 25 cents.
That's right, if you give one cent,
doesn't even know his own rules, but thank you.
I've seen it happen, it's not pretty.
Yes, that's true.
We got Alf the librarian, thanks with 250.
So I couldn't find a book
because one of the richest men in the world
already bought 50 copies.
But do you want a history of the Dreamcast book?
I already got one right here.
It's the manual, it's everything I need to know.
If you give him one cent, he tells you to fuck off.
Oh, I don't.
Hey, thank you, Bebraham.
You gave 10 community subs earlier.
Thank you.
Another $50, I forgot how much fucking, oh my Jesus.
Natikins gave 50, a hundred, right?
How many, a hundred bucks, how many?
My God, a hundred bucks.
Jesus.
Thank you Tiss Chaboy for the 10 bucks.
Jerma, you're my favorite streamer.
I've never left a streamer video without laughing.
My ass off.
Been watching for years.
I'm sorry this isn't much,
but it's the amount I can afford.
Love you, Jerma Jerma Hart.
I've said it before, just you being here is enough.
Now this, I don't have this without you watching.
So you guys are way more important.
Money is not as important as you hanging out
and having a good time and enjoying this shit.
Thank you.
Somebody said about the socks.
Yeah, they got lost in the mill.
I can't even, I can't say that anymore.
I'll tell you the truth.
Jerma the liar, somebody stole them, bought them.
They got sent to the door and somebody spiked them.
Yeah, it's fucked up.
I don't know, somebody stole them from me.
Oh, that's fucked up.
You want me to make another video?
I just like, every time I go to like buy them,
something comes up, like I hear like a fire alarm
goes off, right?
When I get, I'm hovering over purchase
and it's just, I gotta get out of here.
The fire alarm's going off.
It happens every time.
You want me to buy you a new pair?
No, this way.
I got a plan for that by the way.
That says I'm doing a bit voice.
That's the problem when you broadcast yourself
and record yourself hundreds of trillions of times.
That I can't sneak anything.
Oh, I wonder if what he's saying is true.
You've heard every cadence.
You've heard every one of my mannerisms.
I can't pretend, I can't lie to anybody here.
Even if I wanted to, it'd be impossible.
Sue, what the hell, what are you linking here?
What is this?
Jerma985 revelation.
Oh no, this, oh yeah, we watched that.
You go to get expanded, but it's all good.
I got a plan for those socks and the whale.
But thank you, Tissueboy.
Thank you, Dorkcube for the 250.
Thank you.
You say, I can't give you 50 dollars like these other guys.
I should feel bad about that, right?
That I can't give you more money.
Yet you're, I know you're baiting me here.
I'm not gonna take the bait,
but I'm gonna tell you thanks for the 250
and you don't have to give 50 dollars.
Speaking of 50 dollars, thank you,
Communist Taco for the 50 dollars.
Maybe I will try the PlayStation 2 version
or I'll just wait for the VR.
The VR one's coming out soon, right?
I feel like the VR one will just be better anyways.
Something or other thanks to the 250, you like pickles.
Yeah, I do.
I like pickles, they taste good.
I don't like sweet pickles, I like dill pickles.
And they gotta be crunchy.
None of these slippery bin inside
of an old lady's mouth for 30 seconds
smeared out of their mouth and put into your sandwich.
No, I want like the crunch, the snap pickles.
The ones that have like,
not the ones that have water all over them.
Sweet pickles I don't like at all.
Was that a meme with Drake?
Sweet pickles like, no, no, no, no.
Dill pickles, that's the one, pointin', right?
That'll get like a thousand upvotes on Reddit somewhere.
It doesn't matter if it's like a bad reference.
That's a terrible shit, like dog shit post meme,
but it probably will get clicks.
Pickles need to be soaked to become pickles.
Yeah, but then you take them out of the jar
and you wrap them in paper towels
and you squeeze, squish, crush, squish, crush,
unwrap, and they're dry.
Sure they might have a couple of hairs on them,
but you know you eat three inches of ass
every year anyways from meals.
Thank you, rise, fall of Ziggy Stardust for the 10 bucks.
Here's 10 great British pence.
In return I ask, do you eat ass?
Oh, pretty good timing on me reading this,
but thank you for the 10 bucks.
I've answered it already.
Thank you, Tishyboy for the $5.
Can you check the subs you missed?
Those people deserve acknowledgement for their bravery.
Yeah, well, if you're new,
I run a sub credits at the end of the stream.
Shows everybody's name on stream, on screen,
that sub during the stream.
I've found it's a very, it's a good system it seems,
but thank you for the $5, Tishyboy, appreciate it.
Pigeon, thanks for the 250.
I'm happy to report that my profile
on this community has received an A.
You got a 94% on that paper.
The professor marked me off for no quotes from you.
Dad, I told you I had to use a quote.
What did I say?
Eat vegetables and shit?
You could have just put it in there.
You could have just put it at the very end.
By the way, and like leave like a hyperlink to a clip
of me saying, eat your vegetables,
like good luck on your paper.
And he would have been like, what the fuck?
Well, congrats on the paper.
94%, you should be proud of that.
That's a very good job.
Appreciate the 250.
And then we had the Cremator, thanks for three bucks.
You asked about games to play.
What about Grand Theft Auto 2?
It's free on Steam.
GTA 2 is free on Steam?
Is that true?
Am I getting baited or is that actually real?
Free?
I don't know.
It was free for some time now, really.
You can't buy it.
No, I don't know.
I'm really drunk.
Well, drink some water.
But thank you for the three bucks.
Appreciate it.
Rise and fall of Stardust.
Thanks for the $5.
I don't know what this is.
This looks like Morse code.
I don't know what this is,
but thank you for the $5
and thanks for the Morse code.
It's not Morse code though.
It's something else.
This actually might be the top portion of an ASCII art
that they maybe tried to put the whole thing in
and it just auto-deleted everything
because there's only a certain amount of characters
you can put through to Streamlabs.
Maybe.
I don't know.
It's hard to tell.
But thank you for the $5.
Thank you to three bucks Cremator again.
I don't know if I don't wanna take,
I'm not gonna click on that link.
I don't wanna see what happened to your hand.
Hopefully you're okay.
Hopefully you're all right.
Whatever happened to you.
Hey, thank you DeusMorte for the 250.
If you like Picross,
there's a cool one on the DS called Picross 3D
where you start with a cube and uncover an object
within using the Picross number system
you might be interested.
I think I owned that.
I owned two Picross games for 3D.
Yes.
One of them was normal.
The other one was a 3D one if I remember.
That's cool though.
Maybe I'll check that out.
That'd be cool to have for a stream.
Hey, thank you DorkCube for the 250.
Oh my God.
I have a story to one up the Oreos in mom's bed.
I don't even care that it was a dream.
Yeah, but that's not,
it wasn't a real story.
It was me telling you a dream I had.
That didn't happen.
I actually threw up in my mother's bed.
That is a real story, not a dream.
Thank you Alpha Librarian for the 250.
Turns out you need to sign
an ultimate gaming question sheet for the book.
You can get the book for 20% off.
No, that's all good.
I don't need any books.
I got plenty of them.
I read a lot.
12 books a month at the end of the year.
Ferodian Weapon again, $50.
A lot of fucking money.
A lot.
DorkCube, thanks for the 250.
This may be an odd question,
but I just listened to a podcast earlier
that reminded me of the topic.
Did you listen to Ska when you were younger?
Ska, does the Mighty Mighty Bossstones count?
That's close, kind of, but not really, right?
Yes, I loved the Mighty Mighty Bossstones.
The Mighty Mighty Bossstones were my favorite band
when I was 14, 15.
Maybe even a little younger, like 13.
You look like a Ska listener.
What does that mean?
I remember being on the bus to a field trip
and listening to the whole CD twice
because it was a long drive.
I had a Walkman with one of those discs,
disc players, it was great.
And back then, the biggest technology was making sure
that if you grabbed or moved the Walkman,
that it didn't...
That was a huge technology.
Non-skippable discs would mean you could pick it up,
you could put it in your pocket.
If you went on a bump in the car, it didn't skip,
it buffered.
First, by the way, first ever form of buffering
was CDs having the no skip feature.
It would almost download and prepare,
buffer, you could even say, two or three seconds ahead.
Somebody made a million dollars with that
because then that turned into buffering.
Fucking Bob buffer, nice job.
But yeah, Mighty Mighty Bossstones.
Hey, C4G, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Germany, do you have any VR games
you'd most recommend from the ones you've played?
Absolutely.
I have Beat Saber and Superhot and they slap.
Also, please say something really funny here
so people clip it so I can find this easily
when I wake up tomorrow, thank you.
Do you want to do the horn?
Somebody will clip that, it's gonna be like horn
and then you'll be, there it is.
But Superhot VR is probably,
I would say in the top five for sure.
Blade and Sorcery was really, really great.
Pavlov is probably the best game
that you can play for multiplayer, I think,
at least what I've played so far.
If you haven't played Blade and Sorcery, it's fantastic.
Pavlov, again.
Even like Climie, Climie was really fun too.
Very simple, but there's workshop support.
But we'll see, maybe my opinion changes tomorrow
because there's another three or four games in VR
I'm gonna play tomorrow.
We should have a great time, looking forward to it.
Oh, Dread Halls, that's right.
If you like horror games,
Dread Halls is probably the best one for VR.
Does not, do you think there would be a shitload of them?
Dread Halls, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely.
The bar fight game was funny,
but it's really only like 30 to 40 minutes.
You don't get like an entire experience.
It's like a 25 minute experience
to punch people in the face
and throw chairs at people.
Hot Dogs, Hot Dogs, Horseshoes, and Hand Grenades
is another good one.
If you like simulated weaponry and a million different axes
and there's like a sniper rifles
and like the range,
there's all kinds of stuff in that game.
Did I see the tweet by Twitch about Dread Halls?
I did, yeah, it's funny.
It's funny, they like, they bleeped out the swears
and they like cut me out.
They like, yeah, get this,
I don't, we don't want his like big,
ugly, gross body in here.
We just want like the, with the joke.
Yeah, the official Twitch Twitter
did a little, nice little shout out on their Twitter.
It was really cool, pretty cool.
But let's keep going, almost done.
We got just a little bit to go through.
It's time for slime, thanks to the three bucks.
Hello, Jerma, please activate that cool gamer loot
in stream legends.
You got it.
What level is the guild?
Are we, have we taken over anything yet?
All right, you ready?
I don't know if you have to have it open or not.
Level 38.
All right, if you want it, get it open.
I'm not sure if you,
maybe you have to have it open or not.
Three, two, one, here you go.
Remind me to do that again tomorrow.
Because if people are having fun with that
and it's just something interesting little idle thing
that they do for fun,
then yeah, just always remind me to do that.
But thank you, it's time for slime.
Hope you enjoy your free stuff.
Hey, C4G, thanks for the $5 here.
Also, Minecraft VR is honestly pretty good
as long as you liked Minecraft to begin with.
The cows are too big, so they're kind of scary
and you get nauseous like really easy.
So you know what I changed my mind, it sucks.
Also, Hatsune Miku VR sucks,
which is the same because I love Miku,
but it's not worth $25.
Okay, I'm out of bits, bye.
What is Hatsune Miku VR?
Isn't, wait, isn't Hatsune Miku the pop star,
the animated pop star thing?
Oh, okay.
Well, I'm sorry that you didn't think it was worth it.
He doesn't know.
I mean, I do, I just told you what it was.
I just said what it is.
Miku and Jerma collab when?
I don't know.
I don't do collabs.
Or organically we'll hang out with somebody
and maybe we'll do something together.
He doesn't know.
Get the Miku game.
I don't think so.
Thank you, Genny, Benny for the three bucks.
Jerma, you're telling me your Sega is dead.
He overheated.
It's dead.
No, it's fine.
That's the first Dreamcast game
that I had a problem with.
So I don't know.
It was weird that the background wasn't there.
Scenes were disappearing.
The game, remember the game just locked up?
That was really weird.
They were just standing there and she was blinking.
That was odd,
but maybe it was a problem with the Dreamcast.
I don't think so.
Fucking bootleg.
I can't believe it if that's true.
I made such a big deal about opening that wrapper and shit.
People are probably talking so much shit
and laughing their ass off
at the fact that I'm like,
oh, look in the wrapper, cool.
It's like a bootleg fucking disc.
What?
80 year old.
We all get scammed once in a while.
Thank you, Pika Banana for the $10.31.
That wasn't a boring stream.
We're here for you, not the games.
All the crazy games you play
wouldn't be as fun to watch without you, Jerma Hart.
I really appreciate that.
I do.
But still, I want each stream to be fun.
I want people to not go,
oh, here we go again.
Or, well, this sucked.
Oh yeah, that was bad.
Even if that's the case,
I know I never want that to happen.
I want each broadcast to be as good as the last one,
as good as the one that was a week ago,
as good as the one that was a month ago.
And it's not, I'm not really,
I'm fine.
Like I had a blast.
Things were fun.
I wasn't upset or anything.
It's not like I'm mad.
It's just, you know what I want?
I want it to go the way that I want it.
And when it doesn't,
it can be like, like shit.
Was the whole stream picked across?
No.
We only went to picked across.
That's not even a pick cross
because of the technical problems I had with the Dreamcast.
Kind of threw everything out of whack.
But it's all right.
We move on, we play, we do it again tomorrow.
I still had a lot of fun on this stream.
I had fun on pretty much every stream.
I had a lot of fun on the last stream
from yesterday, you know?
It's, I don't, I'm not like giving points
and taking points away per stream.
Like, oh, that one was an eight.
That one was an eight.
That was a seven.
That was a two.
I just want them to go well.
Right?
Modest Narcissists,
thanks for the $10.
No, 10 community subs, not $10.
What am I talking about?
Thank you.
For all the community subs.
Thank you, GeniBeni for the five,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10, $11 here.
Hey, don't you think chat's annoying?
Like that pianist.
You're right.
Let's get some rock music in here.
How could you say something like that?
Jerma, it's illegal to download music
and movies off the internet.
I'm gonna go to internet jail.
It's not illegal to listen to music
on official Vivo YouTube account.
You wouldn't download a car.
Thank you, Siroc for the 250.
When you die, science will preserve your brain
and will harvest all your unused video
and stream ideas.
Also, Joel streamed 3D Movie Maker five days ago
and he got Sans to be in it.
It's a wonderful program.
I hope he had a lot of fun.
That program can be hell
to get to run stably at like 800 by 600.
Hopefully he got it to work pretty well.
But it's a blast if you can get it to work.
Sans confirmed for wrap movie three.
Something about the thanks in three bucks.
Hey Jerms, grandma found out I had her credit card.
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta go.
Don't use, don't do that.
I know you're fucking around.
But don't, don't, fuck, what are you thinking?
Are you fucking, are you serious?
Don't do that shit.
Sorry.
Say sorry.
Freudian weapon thanks for the five dollars, Freudian.
Random thought, but your old 500 subscriber video
really helps me power through my workouts.
It's the same kind of energy I try to have at the gym.
Yep, I used to love working out.
I miss those days sometimes,
but I'm kind of a mess if I'm honest.
I get like sore really easily now.
It just sucks, but it's all right.
Same energy.
I forget that it was almost eight years ago.
No, that was eight years ago.
I made my first YouTube videos just like fucking stacked.
Almost 10 years has gone by.
It's a long time.
Then I'm just happy to still be here.
I'm happy that eight years later there is,
I still, you know,
people still think this is interesting.
I still think this is interesting.
Holy shit, it took me forever to focus on anything.
Eight years?
I could barely keep my shoes tied for eight years.
Thank you.
I do miss those old workouts though.
They were a lot of fun.
Tingy thanks for the 250.
Hey Jermbo, I don't know if you're away,
but Twitch allows custom cheer modes.
I think we can see some custom cheer modes
related to the channel.
Maybe animated Jermachomp or OG Jerm doing the same.
Hope you consider this.
I'd love to see it.
I'm sure chat would too.
Yeah, actually, I gotta get in touch with Lordell
because there are a bunch of random things
that I'm gonna add to the channel.
We talked about it a little bit last week.
There will be animated cheer boats.
There will be new screens.
There will be some new music.
There will be some new animations.
It's been long enough.
I think it's time to do some more.
Maybe some more emotes too to fill up some slots.
I'll be getting in contact with him very soon.
There's another Vroom.
Another Vroom.
There they go.
Vroom emote, that's not a bad idea.
I feel, I don't know though.
I feel like, do you think that would get tiring
after a while?
It might.
It might be a next situation where it just cars.
I don't know.
That's a tough one.
Thank you Paul in shirt for the $5.
Jerm, I made a gamer test for you.
Do it on stream.
This is a random link here.
This is something that I wanna make sure everyone's aware.
I don't click random links in bit donations.
If it's an mgirl link, if it's a YouTube link,
that's fine, but I don't just click random links
unless they're, you gotta be careful.
And Jerma lied about Minecraft VR is,
you're gonna have to change that username tomorrow.
But thank you for the five community subs.
Discord image links too.
Yeah, those are fine.
But if you have a link that's not one of those places,
you've got, we probably,
here's what's probably gonna have to happen.
I'm probably gonna have to get them screened
by a mod or something to make sure that it's,
you know, whatever it is
and then they can tell me about it later.
Well, as I'm in the end here,
because I really just can't click on random stuff.
Somebody, a person, no.
A person to taste the food before the king eats it.
But really though, oh, he dropped dead.
I'm not eating that meat pie.
What if a mod betrays you?
Long story short, if it's not Imgur YouTube Discord,
or like something that is,
I know exactly what it is from the link,
hyperlink itself, I'm not gonna click it.
I don't make that,
I'm probably gonna put that in the rules too.
I gotta be careful.
I gotta take care of myself, right?
But thank you for the $5.
And while some links might not look malicious,
I'm not saying this one is.
You never know, you just gotta be careful.
Notavirus.gov.
I do appreciate anything that anybody makes,
but we're probably gonna have to do a system
where links get sort of pre-screened.
Because I feel like I have missed things
people have sent me because I didn't wanna click it,
because I was like, I don't know what this is.
I'm gonna get a system in place.
But thank you for the $5, thank you.
Don't click, it's a gnome.
But that was right, Dai gave 200 bucks right there too,
like 40 minutes ago.
Pasta's almost ready.
That's from Kim.
Oh shit, boys and girls, pasta.
All right, I gotta get out of here, I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here, I gotta get out.
It has been like eight hours, huh?
I haven't eaten, shit.
All right, well, thank you to Dai for the 200 bucks.
I'll be spending that on pasta, guaranteed.
Feroidian weapon, thanks for the 250.
Wow, it's not often I can stick around for live bits.
I usually just listen to the VOD with my morning coffee.
Have a good night, I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, thanks for hanging out.
That's interesting that you watch the VODs
with coffee in the morning, that's cool.
It's an interesting way to do it.
Hey, Jewish bro, thanks for three bucks.
I ordered a dork cube and all I got
was a bunch of rusty razor blades and a lit cigarette
and is streaming your only job or does Kim work too?
Also, Ratmovie3 or Riot, Kim also works.
Kim has a job, tomorrow is my birthday?
No, your tomorrow is my today.
I don't know why I thought that you said that.
But on top of streaming, I also do construction.
So a lot of the bridges and buildings
and department buildings and stuff, I design them.
I design them and then I build them by myself
in less than two weeks.
Yo, this guy's a professional liar.
I should play a fucking game
where I just don't say anything true the whole stream
and then people have to figure out
what is a lie and what's not.
Let's do that, that sounds like fun.
Have a way to chat to get involved
and I'll just say a bunch of dog shit all stream.
It's just a reverse lie detector.
That's every stream.
All Mew, thanks for the 10 bucks, all Mew.
Oh God, oh God, Jerma, I'm sorry,
but I can't pay the protection this month.
Oh shit, please.
This is all I have, I can't afford to lose.
You almost got me to say that.
Thanks for the 10 bucks though, all Mew.
Thank you.
Hey, Bobo, Bobo Bobo, thank you Bobo Bobo for the 10 bucks.
No message, 10 dollars from Bobo Bobo.
Thank you, Wreckersd, Wreckersd for the 10 bucks.
Jerma, I tried to send this three times,
but it was very silly.
Chat helped me make sure I got it sent this right
this time, so shout out to the wonderful boys here.
Love you and enjoy the holidays, Dad.
Thank you so much for the 10 bucks, Wreckers.
Incredibly generous amount of money to give me.
Thank you, glad you figured it out.
Thank you.
And thank you, the Cremator for the eight bucks.
Jerma, it's from a flame thrower
with the spray and lighter.
Oh, well don't fucking do that.
You gotta be fucking careful, don't do that shit.
Don't play with that kind of stuff.
Go open up Gary's mod.
What are you thinking?
Be careful.
That's very, very much something you should not be doing.
But thank you for the eight bucks.
Take care of yourself, be fucking careful.
Hey, Bobo Bobo, thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey Jerma, I've been a fan of your content
since the grandpa face reveal.
That's a long time ago.
Can't tell you how many times you've made my day
by watching one of your videos.
You've helped me through so much over the years.
I want to give you a personal thank you
for all that you've done.
Well, Bobo Bob, I actually think it might be Bobo Bob 99.
That's $20 here from me.
That's more than I could ever, ever expect somebody
to pay me for any reason.
And that grandpa face reveal,
I do remember making that.
That was a fun one to make.
Thank you so much for sticking around
for like fucking seven years.
That's a long ass time, thank you.
Grandpa is dead.
No, grandpa is in hell.
So, you know, whatever.
Okay, so what does that mean exactly?
Right, you know the lore.
I don't need to explain it.
Jess, you got it.
Thanks for the 250.
Making a full song on stream would be really cool.
You could use your beatboxing ability.
Joel did one before with beef songs called Pigeon Techno.
I still wanna do, I still wanna do that Fruity Loops stream.
I wanna get people to actually play instruments though.
It's too many.
I gotta focus on one of these ideas.
I had just too many of them.
There is something in particular that is gonna,
it's summertime, it has to be nice around.
The one of the main things that I've been wanting
to do for a long time cannot be done
until it is a higher temperature.
It's getting there real soon.
You're just gonna see it one day.
I'm not gonna talk about it.
It's just gonna happen.
Garfield of Monday killer, thank you for the 250.
Jerma, it's Garf.
I just got out of Captain Marvel.
What a movie that was.
It had a funny orange cat in it.
Fun fact, Goose the Cat was played
by four different cats.
Two of which are named after muppets,
Gonzo and Rizzo.
Ain't that sweet.
Like to see some cat representation in mainstream media
other than Secret Life of Pets and yours truly.
Okay, thank Captain Marvel, more like Cat Tan Marvel.
Thank you, thank you, Chad is just loving that one.
Chat, more like Cat Zing.
That's thanks, I will be here all week.
Is Shazam any good?
Is that out yet?
That's the other Captain Marvel.
I'm gonna go see Captain Marvel.
I'm gonna go see the other Captain Marvel Shazam.
I'm gonna see them both and we'll see what is out.
No, it's not, you just did the smiley face
like the I'm lying face.
Early April, it looks pretty good.
Yeah, it looks wholesome, let's put it that way.
Thank you, Garfield.
Thank you to Matt's friend for $30.
Hey, Jerma, it's my birthday this Sunday.
Can you sing me happy birthday?
How about I just say happy birthday?
March 17th, have a good birthday.
Have a fantastic birthday bash.
Thank you for the 30 bucks, it's a lot of money.
Heel's birthday, man.
Cake and ice cream isn't on its way.
Thank you, Alf the librarian for $3,
but Jerma, my books are 20% off.
You could have a friend 90% off.
Buy one of my fantastic books.
My library has retro and new books,
even fan-made books, rat's books.
Where do you live that you have all these books?
Do you live in a, oh, your name's the librarian, right?
I get it.
It's another character.
Why do we have like five different
role-playing characters here?
Now I'm starting to get it.
Every stream there's like a new character.
It's part of the universe, oh God.
But thank you.
Thank you to Hike Zero for the 250.
Here is my rat movie three song.
I can't wait to watch the full length feature film.
Jump and chomp.
Did you, wait, did you already put this together?
Did somebody already do this?
You already did this.
Let me get it in here.
Why can I, I can't get this to play.
What the hell?
Uh, hold on.
It worked for me, hold on, let me see if I can.
Oh, no, that's why.
Okay, I got it.
All right, here we go, let's hear it.
We're the rats, we're the yet, we're the yet, we're the yet.
We're the rats, we're the rats, yes, we're the rats.
We're the yet, we're the yet, we're the rat.
We're the yet, we're the yet, we're the yet, we're the yet.
Ha ha, what?
We're the rats, we're the rats, yes, we're the rats.
We're the rats, we're the yet, we're the rat.
We're the rats, yes, we're the rats, we're the yet,
we're the yet, we're the yet, we're the rat.
Yes, we're the rats, we're the yet, we're the rat.
We're the rats, we're the yet, we're the yet, we're the yet.
Something like that, something like that.
Thank you for that, that was fucking awesome.
That was what was in mind.
They may have been some lyrics in the middle
to add some flavor.
But thank you, Hike Zero, that was fucking,
that was great, thank you so much.
Thank you, Nickname Jack for the three bucks.
Decide to join a random TF2 game
while you're talking to virtual fish.
Someone recognizes my name as a reference
and just asks, did you see the fish
called Jerma a virgin?
And you know what I did, absolute gold.
Link, link, link, link, link.
Here is the link to the rat song
that was carefully crafted.
That's fucking hilarious.
Thank you, Nickname Jack.
And then finally, let's run the credits
while we do, is it one or two more here?
Credits, there they are.
Here come all the subs, all the resubs,
all the new subs.
You guys continue to keep the wheels spinning
on this stream and then some.
Thank you, everybody.
Oh yeah, the librarian came back in for five dollars.
We can give you your books, our books for free.
I don't need free, I don't need a free book.
I wanna come in there and I wanna rent it
like a blockbuster.
I wanna go in there and I wanna bring that book
back in three days or I have to forget about it.
And then my parents get a bill in the mail
for $268 four and a half months later.
That's what I want.
Thank you, Cremator for the five dollars.
Video game flamethrower isn't as fun,
but it's safe and it's not gonna hurt you.
Then wait for the library to go out of business
and never pay the fee.
I don't remember, did you, did,
they used to probably go to collections, right?
If you, did they do that back then?
I don't remember.
If you didn't pay for months and months
and months or a year,
did Blockbuster ever send your bill to collections?
I don't know.
If you don't turn up for a year, they would erase it.
Wow, that's kind of ridiculous.
I mean, I guess how would they be able to keep track of that?
They would have to be sending
so many people to collections.
That's why they went out of business.
Oh, hey, Geni, Benny, thanks for the five bucks.
Stream is over, that sucks.
Am I gonna read the TF2 comics?
I read them all when they originally came out.
This hasn't been a new TF2 comic
in like a couple of years, right?
At least a year.
Will you be covering Pokemon Spear and Bow
when it comes out?
Probably not.
I don't really play Pokemon.
Finally, Cremator, last bits.
I'll take your word for it.
You should try it and feel your eyes melt.
It's, no, no, I'm not gonna do that.
I'm not gonna do that.
They say, but don't worry, my hand's been through worse.
Take care of yourself.
It's not worth it.
Well, you won't be covering them
because they're not real.
Oh, it's not real.
I can't stop hearing the new rat song.
All right, guys, I'm beat.
I will see you tomorrow for VR.
Get some sleep.
Thanks for sticking around, everybody.
I'm gonna go eat some pasta.
Photos, thanks for 250.
Ah, messing this up.
Sorry, have a good night.
Looks like you got it.
Thank you so much, Photos.
Photo S, Photas for the 250.
I will see you tomorrow for Minecraft VR
and some other stuff.
Have a great night, guys.