I feel like our team is going to lose, so I'm just going to spend all my time coming after you.
That's okay.
Oh, I can see you. I just saw you.
I don't see you.
Hey, what is going on, everybody?
Jerma here with a Tribes Ascent gameplay commentary, and this is going to be a live commentary.
This was taken from Ster's livestream last night.
We did this at like, God, maybe 3 or 4 in the morning is when this all actually ended.
So it went pretty late. It was very fun.
And I wanted to cut up the last maybe 15, 20 minutes of the stream, and that is what you're watching right now.
And again, playing with Ster.
His link will be in the description as well as MLC Stealth, but you guys already know Stealth, so I don't have to do an introduction for Stealth.
You probably know who Ster is too. What am I talking about?
But yeah, they will be in the description. Go check them out. They are really cool dudes.
But this video, this is a not so much a gameplay video as it is a me running from my life video,
because Ster is really good at this game and I'm not so good.
So it's me pretty much just running away from Ster and him trying to melee me to death.
So it's pretty entertaining.
But I'll let the live commentary kick in, guys, now.
So I will see you all next time.
Take care, everybody.
I'll do the double team.
I'll just smash you in the face.
Where are you?
I gotta shoot you. You have a YouTube channel.
Oh, I keep missing this guy.
Now he's dead.
Where are you at, Shazbot?
Shazbot?
Shazbot, Shazbot, Shazbot.
No, I just heard noise. It was this guy.
It was this slippery snake.
Oh.
I missed so much with this gun tonight. Oh my god.
I keep getting scared that you are right here somewhere.
For one of these times, I will be.
Help that this guy is teleporting.
Mike, go over there. I dare you. You're gonna get hit by that grenade.
Go over there.
Like where I just threw a grenade.
There's a lot of over-there's. I don't know where you guys are going.
I'm very, very, very confused.
Undo it.
Unconfuse yourself.
Whoa, whoa, what was that?
Die!
Were you just having a sniper rifle at me?
Oh, get blue plate mailed. Whatever it's called.
Oh, a knife.
Is this like medieval times?
Plate mail.
Blue plate special mail.
It's very special. My blacksmith made it this morning.
Oh, come on.
Oh yeah, eat grenade.
Maybe if I'm like really unpredictable.
I can't like be predicted.
Oh, is that the definition of that?
I'm over here.
If I'm like really unpredictable, I can't be predicted.
Come on. Come here.
No, god damn it.
Oh.
Humiliation.
Oh, you are so lucky that
things didn't go my way.
This guy.
You're gonna walk right into that man and it's gonna be your...
your demise.
How did that hit me? I don't understand.
So is there an item in this game that when you hit somebody
it plays like music?
What?
Seriously, I just got hit by a grenade and it was like
I swear.
I promise.
No, I refuse.
No. No, this cannot happen again.
Not a second time.
Grenade.
Fine. Fine. You die a normal death.
Oh god.
I got an assist.
I got destroyed.
I got the assist. What do you know?
There is a blacksmith. See, there's the anvil right there.
See it?
What's this like a rhino? Oh, it's a tank.
I thought that was an animal.
What is this guy doing?
I want to ride the rhino.
It'll be fun.
I want a vehicle.
Then I'll be the coolest guy in school.
There's like circles on the ground.
And on the thing on the circle.
Hey, vehicle.
Alright, I'm going to go look for it right now.
Hope you weren't lying to me.
I have to kill that guy.
Oh no.
It's MLC.
How do you pronounce that?
MLC. What are you talking about?
They're just letters.
No, it's actually milk.
Germa, why do you have so many people like AFK back here?
Because this team is fun.
So, where's that Germa guy?
I see him. He's way on the other side of the map though.
He is going to get punched.
Wall hacks.
Let's see where I am.
Moto crossing for extra points.
Is that true? Alright.
That's not a thing, is it?
We're going to catch you.
Oh, I got you.
I got you.
Your teammate just walked by and was like
He wanted nothing to do with that.
Yeah, why? That was weird.
Like, oh, you two can have your fun. Bye.
Yeah, you're just punching each other.
They really need a weapon in this game.
That's like the sandwich for Heavy.
Where you can just walk around and everyone will understand you're stupid.
Wait, what?
He just walked...
Oh no, there he is again.
I'm shooting behind me.
I can't believe I missed.
Some brute killed me.
Some brutish guy killed me.
Oh, hi.
Okay, so where's your Germa?
Here's some more like
noise grenades.
I just ranked up.
You're doing good, right?
Seriously, listen.
I'm like, listen, you guys can't even hear it.
I threw two grenades at you, Germa.
See, I'm going to make a video
of this and I'm going to turn that up
so everyone can hear it.
I want people to know that that's music plays.
It's like elevator music.
When you do what?
But by that noise grenade.
Impact Nitron?
It's like an ear ringing noise.
Every time I...
Or maybe you're talking about fractals because that's
totally a disco party.
Fractals.
So this one doesn't go to 300.
It depends on the amount of points there actually are.
Sorry.
How many times am I going to have to hit you?
What is no joy?
When you killed someone who was on a streak.
Oh, cool.
I don't know.
Wait, where'd you just go?
No, I'm not falling for this one.
Who are you talking to?
You're a freaking infiltrator.
Where's your health?
How'd you get the health back?
I don't know.
I'm running. I'm getting out of here.
The slide.
You're joking. You can't run.
Over here.
Get away from me.
Grenades.
I'm coming in from the top.
Oh my god.
It said I suicided.
Hold on.
Did I throw the grenade at you and then walk over
on my own grenade? I think that's really what happened.
What a smart person I am.
Hey.
We did it.
Hey, good game. Shazbot, everyone.
No, I was 12 and 14.
My goodness.
I'm 18 and 11.
Unlock's available.
What am I unlocking?
Should I unlock
the doombringer or the
infiltrator?
You should get a weapon for a class you already have.
Oh, but it's so...
Don't get doombringer. Don't do it.
Oh, okay. Fine.
Unless you like standing around doing
nothing.
Well, I am pretty much a slug in this game.
You should probably go doombringer then.
You get like a minigun.