Hello everybody. I'm going to introduce myself right here. My name is Jerma. I'm going to start doing gameplay commentaries.
Some people might already know me from playing in servers, but some of you probably don't, and this is my introduction to you guys.
I'm not just going to do Team Fortress commentaries, I'm going to do other stuff too.
But most notably I'll do Team Fortress stuff, because I love the game. It's my absolute favorite game in the world right now.
It has been for a while. I've been playing Team Fortress since Beta, and before that I played Team Fortress Classic for three or four years also.
So I'm a huge fan of the series, and when Team Fortress 3 crumbs out, I'll be getting that too.
So, I'm playing right now. I jumped in a little late here. This is Gold Rush. I'm playing Dead Ringer Spy with Kunai and the Latorenga.
Whatever, however you pronounce it. I believe it's Letronger. I think that's how you actually say it.
But you know what? I don't give a shit about name pronunciations. Who cares? This is a gameplay commentary. You guys want to see me kill shit.
So, as I said I'm the Dead Ringer. This is Gold Rush. They're pushing the last point. I'm on defense.
And this scout stood still for too long, so that means he's dead.
A pyro lights me on fire, and I want you guys to pay attention to something. This is really, really weird.
So I'm on fire right now, okay. So I better look for some health or get healed by a medic or something.
You'd expect me to do that, right? So I don't, and my life doesn't really go anywhere.
But I'm still on fire. And for the remainder of this video, I'm going to be on fire.
See, I just picked up health kit right there, but it doesn't matter. I'm still on fire.
I don't understand why that happened, that there was something going on in the video editing process.
Kill that Heavy. I think that medic was about to charge an Uber or something, but he jumps to his death.
And I don't know why I did that, to tell you the truth. He could have just ran backwards.
So I'm still on fire. Let me pick this health kit up again. Still on fire.
I'm not sure if it's bugged, like I said. I love Dead Ringer. I love the spy. It's my most played class.
Next to that, I think it's Engineer. Yeah, it is. I think 100 hours or something.
But Dead Ringer, people will complain and say, well, Dead Ringer is for retarded people that are stupid.
And this spy, by the way, notices that I heard the noise, but he doesn't try and come after me.
Usually you turn around and want to go after somebody when you hear the loud Dead Ringer noise, but he doesn't seem to care.
So up here, I get this Heavy. Missed with a stab, but I get him anyways.
This sniper, I get him as well with the revolver, which this revolver is hard to kill people with because you have to shoot them.
I think it's at least three or four times if you have 125 health or 150 health, like some of the classes do.
But this scout, I think he's a spy. He thinks I'm a spy. We both go, haha.
Now watch this part right here. I don't understand this part and you'll get a laugh out of this.
This is a spy and we both know it, but he just keeps on walking.
Apparently he didn't care that I bumped into him or that I was a spy. I don't even know.
I thought he was a bot at first and then I found out that he wasn't.
So if that was you, shame on you and maybe you'll get better by practicing.
So right now I'm just kind of trying to lure somebody out here. The soldier, I get him.
And that's what it's all about with the spy, just trying to mess with people's heads.
And as you notice, I walk sideways and I walk backwards a lot because if you walk right at people, as a lot of you know, you're a definite guaranteed spy.
See, I'm trying to pretend like this scout is my enemy and I fool this spy, but it doesn't matter because I miss anyways.
And nothing happens from it though. He didn't really come after me.
I think that's the same spy who killed this engineer. I believe that's the same spy that when he heard me uncloak, he didn't really come after me.
He just kind of shot in random directions and that was it.
So I get this medic and I get the soldier. I have ruined their days.
And this is, like I said, the last part of Gold Rush. I started a little late.
But it's okay because this is a pretty good run and I'm still on fire.
Nice little jumping, little side stab on that medic.
And yeah, I had to bring up the dead ringer because there's no way I would have survived that at all.
Which is the best part about the dead ringer because if you had a regular invisibility watch,
half of these situations you'd be dead. I'd say probably more than half.
So I try to tele-frag this engineer and it doesn't really go so well because he's obviously not in the way.
He actually hits me with his wrench and it doesn't kill me.
I think I was over here. I think he crited me actually to tell you the truth.
See right now I'm in no man's land because this is so many people around and this heavy knows it so I go down.
And everyone doesn't really hear it but I just kind of freak out.
There's too many people for me to even really do anything significant.
But hey, I tried and that's when I died.
So look, I'm still on fire. I'm still on fire. I've yet to be put out.
And it wasn't like this when I was playing, by the way.
Only when I saved the video.
So I guess this is some kind of bug with demo files where it does this.
And it really is kind of annoying and hopefully it doesn't do this more often.
If you guys do commentaries, if you guys can give me some tips on what exactly could be going on here, I have no idea.
But I'm not going to let it ruin my day.
It actually subsides right here.
I had to cut to I think something crashed.
But yeah, it's gone now.
And this is still the same life from what it was before when I walked out.
I just had to cut it.
So I take the hit from the heavy, bring out the dead ringer, go back to the little spot here.
This is a great place to go.
If you don't go here, you should go here every time.
Kill that soldier, but that other soldier is not going to have any of that.
If you're using the dead ringer, that's a really good place to go.
Because I believe when you're behind a wall, the sound of the decloak of the dead ringer is very silent.
So where are the last ten seconds here?
And we are winning this.
And obviously I come out here to demoralize the other team.
And it was a pretty good run.
And hopefully you guys liked it.
And if you did, let me know.
Leave me a comment.
Let me know if you want to see something else or if you guys want to see more.
I plan on doing at least a little bit to try and, you know, try and get into it.
But thanks for watching.
And hopefully you guys enjoy it.
I'll see you later.