Oh
This quickly this quickly someone's like unloading already dying. Well, I need a gun
German there are guns up here. There's a desert eagle at least. Oh, well, hey somebody fuck come with me cuz I don't want to die
I can come in German. Come right here. Oh
Someone wants a gun sounds a lot like a test. Yeah, but it's awesome. It wants to protect himself
I'm a detective
Sad fan. What do you get away from me? That man got called out before I believe that he's a
Batman is confirmed dead right now. I was
Okay, okay, okay, okay
There's so much craziness going on right here
Let me in that room don't let me out here with to let me in that room
Oh, I didn't even see
What's this chicken? Yeah, I saw that earlier saw that earlier
Nobody shoot it cuz that's gonna like cause a lot of problems
Kill it kill the chicken
Let's go explore cuz there's to confirm dead we gotta go find one of the confirmed dead. Let's go find the dead bodies
And it should be
Shibby to do shit. Why do you have a gun? I literally have a pistol and the shitty ones
I can't do I think oh, well, we got people down there traps and cliche
Whoa, we're shooting
You know, oh wait, wait, wait, wait before we get don't jump to conclusions. Don't jump to conclusions. Wait, wait
He he was trying to hit me with the crowbar. No, don't jump to conclusions
I'm gonna drop the gun. I'm gonna drop the gun right now. No, what what don't listen to him?
He was he was trying to hit me with the crowbar
Don't shoot me. He was dude. If anybody don't
Upstairs upstairs check the body stealth stealth. Get back in check the body
I don't jump to pay do he I think should he was the terrorist he was
Check this check the body before you do anything crazy
Run stealth is stealth of the traitor stress stealth in the German stuff in German. I got one
Oh my god
What happened I'm not gonna say anything
Oh, I just burned to death German did you throw that grenade? I did not throw a grenade
All right, so can we like calm down here and like let the detectives like try to work this out
All right, so can we like calm down here and like let the detectives like try to work this up
Let's let the detectives work this out. They're like robbing the bank
Seriously, what's with the explosions?
Dude I had to like reload the damn gun