Holy shit, he's early. Yeah, very early. There's a reason for that though.
There's always a reason for it, and these are the reasons why.
It is 12 p.m. Pacific. I'm awake. I'm kind of back on an incredibly early sleep schedule and
I went to the doctor yesterday. I didn't mean to be on this schedule, but I went to the
doctor yesterday and had some blood work done, and they took like seven vials of blood,
and I was like, well, I'm getting a little fucking lightheaded. I came home and I just fell asleep.
I like went right to bed, and I woke up with like 4 30 in the morning. So I mean,
come on, we're here, right? Blood talk? I mean, it was in the vial, so you didn't
have to touch the blood. You just have to know it was there. So I'm going to go over a few things
that are very important, and they include all of you. Well, maybe not all of you,
but a large portion of you. So give me a minute. I will be right back and we can get
started. Okay, see you in a second. What the fuck are you guys saying? This guy's too early.
Yeah, I mean, don't expect streams like this to happen all the time, but I was blood
tired last night. I'm not going to be blood tired every day. They took too much of my blood,
and then they made me really tired. That sounds really fucked up. But tonight,
or today, or today, it's not even tonight. Maybe it's tonight for some of you guys.
We're gonna play Hotline Miami 2. I'm going to try to finish it. I have a fresh take on it.
It kicked the shit out of me a couple days ago. But I said I was going to persevere,
and I was going to try my hardest to beat it. And even if we don't, let's just say I get to
a portion of the game where I can't do it, and I'm going to freak out. It's all right,
because there's also I got a bunch of community workshop levels as well. I got a little
sampling of workshop levels to check out. So if it does get to a point where it's just
not completable for me, we'll be good. So let's talk about... No, not yet. Not yet.
I'm gonna wait for most people to be here, because it's about Christmas. It's about the
Christmas Eve stream that is happening, and it's going to involve you guys. Do it now.
All right. You know, fine. Fuck it. We'll do it now. How about we wait? Now do it now.
So let's start by saying that there's going to be a live stream on Christmas Eve. That's
December 24th. The stream is going to be at some point in the afternoon Pacific,
probably like early evening. I'd say around maybe probably like three to four p.m. Pacific
time is when it'll probably start. And it's going to be a Christmas slash Halloween
extravaganza, because I missed a Halloween stream. I typically like to do Halloween
themed streams. So we're going to do both. And at the apex kind of the climax of the night
is going to involve you guys doing some stuff. And what does that mean? Well, there's going
to be a secret Santa chat gives me presents portion of the stream. Remember how a week or
so ago we talked about, man, wouldn't it be funny if chat, I just let them kind of decide what
to buy on Amazon? Well, what a perfect time to do that. So there is a channel. There's a channel
in the Discord called Secret Santa suggestions. What you're going to do in that channel is
you're going to give suggestions of what you would like to give me for Christmas.
And from those suggestions, they will be selections. The moderators are going to be
selecting. So there's no voting. There's no nominations or anything like that.
It's just suggestions the mods are going to be taking from that channel are then I'm going to
buy them. But I'm not going to know, because I'm going to have Kim is going to buy them for
me. And then she's going to wrap them. And I am going to have no fucking idea what they are.
And I'm going to open them on stream. So there are some criteria involved in this,
you could probably imagine. No, let's go over them right now. You want me to talk about it. So
let's talk about it. They will absolutely, absolutely no living creatures. So oh, that's
right. Let's let let's put on the list of 50,000 ants. Oh, no, no, no. Your suggestion has
to be under no more than $50. So we're talking zero to $50 is what your suggestion
can be. It has to be an Amazon link and it has to be prime ready. So has to be an Amazon link,
has to be prime ready, has to be under $50. But the channel, what happened to the channel?
Is it not there? The channel is gone. No, it's here. The channel is gone. No, it's here.
It should be okay now. So by the way, in that channel, please do not, that's not a chat
channel, by the way, not a chat channel, not a chat channel. Wait, no, don't do that. Oh,
wait, wait, should I? Wait, okay, but I'm gonna I'm gonna disable those permissions for a second.
Let me explain this. Listen. Okay. So everybody just jumped in there and fucking started
spamming. Let me explain the rules before you do anything crazy. So in remember, that is not
a chat channel. That is a suggestion channel. And you are only allowed three suggestions per
person and the bonds are going to be very strict on this. Okay, it's a chat channel. We get it.
You know, that channel is a chat channel. Read the spam that got in. Okay. No, no, no, no, no,
no, I'm not. I'm not. Because I don't I don't want to give any opinions. I don't want to
know what you guys are going to have me buy. And that's that's the thing. I'm going to be
opening presents that I'm purchasing, sending to myself, wrapped up from you guys. Because
think about that. And people say, well, he's buying his own Christmas presents. What an ego
maniac. Am I though? You know, you guys subscribe to this channel, you guys give money to this
channel. Be sure that it's not you guys with your suggestion. He's a fucking psycho.
What like an ego maniac. That's right. I want to open a present. These are presents to me.
But I did mention that I want to do it. And the maximum money is going to be 500 bucks.
So there's not going to be a shitload of if you so by the way, knowing that,
and the mods are going to have full discretion here. Oh, I have an idea for a present. How
about like a $499 vibe? Don't do that. It has to be under 50 bucks. The lower I mean,
you could make it a good suggestion if it's higher in price, because that gives you more
of a, you know, reason why it would be picked. That'll be a fun idea. And that's just
one portion of the stream on Christmas Eve. A $50 fake vibe. Metal Socks just gave 50 bucks
right now. Thank you so much, Metal Socks. They say, Hey, Jeremy, I haven't been able to
haven't been catching up the streams. Works pushing me hard, but watching the
VODs and the second channel stuff really made this whole year for me. I hope you know that
I hope you and all have a happy December wean and a happy new yard. Well, thank you,
Metal Socks. That's big money. Thank you. Can we donate bits towards a bigger Christmas budget?
No, no, no. $500 is it. That's it. No, no bigger Christmas budget. By the way,
because of the short notice here, that channel suggestions are only going to be able to be put
in that channel until tomorrow, tomorrow evening. You know, essentially like a little
bit more than 24 hours from now because I have to get them here. So if you have a suggestion
and you got a good one, make sure you get it in there. Make sure it's an Amazon prime
link, a link to an Amazon product that is prime shippable. Otherwise I'm not going
to be able to get it here in time. Don't tell me, don't give me any ideas. I don't
want to see any of these. If you got a good, if you got a good one, get it in there.
Why not a bigger budget than $500? Because I don't know, I didn't want to be sitting there
opening like 60 Christmas presents. You know how fucked up that would be?
Hey, well, Merry Christmas to me. Here's like 75 Christmas presents. That's just like,
that's like next level. Can it be eBay? It cannot. It has to be on Amazon. No animals,
no live creatures, no parrot. Listen, no perishable food items. If your item is perishable,
do not link it in that. It's not going to get used. No sexual shit. I don't even have to say
the D word. You know what I'm saying? Like no, none of that. That's not going to get taken.
Boring. No, it's called, I don't want to get in fucking trouble. I'm going to be in the
studio guys. You want to send me like 20,000 ants and have me open it and be like, oh,
and have the ants go all over the fucking studio. I'm going to be fucked. Yes. Oh yeah.
That would be real fun. If you have fun with it, don't send me any fucked up shit. What do
you mean don't send me? I'm buying these things through the Kim, the proxy, and then she's going
to wrap them and I'm not allowed to see them. Do you not trust us mods? No, of course I do.
All right. With that being said, let's move on. Hopefully you got enough information there.
I don't trust the mods. Thank you KXE for the 30 bucks. Oh shit. EU German stream.
Excellent way to celebrate turning 30. Hope you have a Merry Christmas friend. Hashtag charity.
Happy 30. That's a big number. That's a big milestone to get over. Thank you for the 30
dollars. Now I've been stalling enough because this game beat the absolute shit out of me.
I think I've felt, I think I felt worse. Yeah, I'm not sure. I may have like felt worse
after being mad at Hotline Miami 2 than I was after seven vials of blood being removed from
my body yesterday. I don't know which made me feel more uncomfortable. I don't know. That's a
tough one. What song is this? Oh, I'm actually not sure. Buy more blood. Bloodborne gamer? No,
not blood. I had, I had a lot of blood work done yesterday. All right, so we're gonna go
123456789. Where were we? We were at number 20. Release. I wish I could drink Jerma's blood.
I wish you wouldn't. I wish that you wouldn't do that. Why did I read that? All right,
I gotta be like calm and collected. I gotta be ready and I'm gonna complete this. I was very,
very upset. This music is very loud. I'm gonna, okay, hold on. This is distracting me already.
No, that's all right. Okay, here we go. I think I remember, yeah, I remember this part. This guy
chases you around. I have, why did I have to start at the very beginning here? All my muscle
memory is gone too. This is gonna be a disaster. This is gonna be a fucking disaster.
I already know. All right, I got it. We're good. What happened to the, what's with the
audio? What the heck happened to the audio? All right, now I remember this part. You walk
through here and I'm gonna die right now because I don't remember. No, I do. Oh, that guy has a
gun. All right. Oh boy. That's one, two, three, four. Windows everywhere. Does that guy have a
gun? That guy's got a gun. Two guys with guns. Anybody, who else? That guy, that guy, that guy.
All right, I gotta watch out. Old god. Why is he not coming after me? Why is that guy not
coming after me? He just shot me and didn't care. Somebody please come after me. I don't want to go
in those rooms. It's just death. What the fuck? Why won't he come out here? He did come out here.
Okay, he came out that time. Is he not, okay, what about this guy in there? I wonder if I
can hit this door and throw it at this guy. That's what I'm gonna try to do. Okay, I'm
gonna knock that guy out of the door, throw a crowbar at this guy's face, break that guy's
neck, shoot him in the face, and then throw the, I don't even know. I don't know what I'm
gonna do. Perfect. Okay, I did it, but what did I do? Is there anybody else? I think I got that
guy in there already. Okay. Damn it! I wasn't trying, I was trying to hit that guy. Fuck!
I was trying to hit the guy with, the guy with the fucking gun. Not this dumb ass. Good,
come out here. All right, that's the only guy with the gun. These guys have to
worry about those two. Can I pull them? Whoa. Oh god. That was so many of them. I gotta
throw this thing down. You know another thing I don't like about this place?
It's like the lighting. The fact that it gets like that dark and then the red.
Get over here. Dear lord. Okay, pull this guy out here and go up. Come on, why are you
not chasing after me? Shouldn't he be running out here? Oh god. Okay, just gonna deal with
this guy and then I get a gun and we can do it again. All right, here we go. Don't fuck
it up. Come on Jeremy, don't fuck this up. Wait, somebody has a gun. Somebody has a gun.
Give me that gun. What? He doesn't hear that? There's a guy with a pistol. There he is.
Okay, here we go. He can shoot me through the walls but so can I. Bingo. Give me the new
gun. Nobody else, right? I'm so paranoid. You know, it would be nice. Why did that take so
long? Okay, no gun. Gun, gun, gun. One guy left. That's it. Please, please have this be the last
guy on this floor. I can't see all the way up there though. I think it is. I'm going for it.
Holy shit, I just got so scared. I thought there was a guy right there but it was a
fucking plant. Okay, here we go. Got it. He's back baby. Give me the gun. Give me the gun.
This is so sloppy. I got to get this fucking gun out of here, man. Oh yeah, yeah.
Fuck. No, well, I wanted to shoot you. I'm so confused here. Am I like picking up the gun
without right clicking? Hold on a second. I'm really confused. I'm running over this gun
and it's picking up. Like, I'm not hitting right click. Am I out of my mind? Oh boy,
all right. What do we got? Fuck. Okay, I think I was going to... Got it. Okay,
now wait for this one guy. Give me this gun, please. That one, I think. Who's left? All
right, we got a ton of people down there. Gun. Got it. Anybody else? Gun. Got it. Oh my
god, there's a people in there. Fuck, I forgot about the people in that room. God damn
it. Oh my god, there's some people in there. What the hell was that? And I told myself today,
listen guys, I said I was going to be fucking calm. I wasn't going to freak out. I was going
to be very, very careful. I'm okay. I got this. Everything's fine. I said I was going to be
cautious. I was not going to freak out. I was going to be very, very collected today.
I think so far I've been okay. You know what I'm saying? What do you guys think? I've
been pretty calm and collected. Tons of... Oh, I didn't want to shoot. I just accidentally
shot that guy. All right, give me another gun. I don't have... There's no other guns here.
Sir, could you... There's another gun. All right. Right, what's happening? What's that?
What? I don't understand why I don't... Jeremy, don't do it. But I don't understand
why. I don't understand. I don't understand why it was locked on and I couldn't get the
lock on to come back. I don't... I don't understand. I'm infuriated right now. Stop it.
It's all right. Everything's going to be fine. Just pick up the gun on the ground.
Don't worry about it. Just think about it. It's like Christmas time. You know what
I mean? Like, isn't that nice? Christmas is fucking nice. The holidays are here.
You know? I didn't get more than one... He's dead? All right. There's people down
there and that door is open. So I got to get in here. I got to shoot one guy.
That guy got a gun? I just fucking panicked. What the hell are you doing, Jeremy? What have
I done? It's ruined. No, it's not. I got a gun right here. Fucking door. All right.
It's just this guy with this pistol. I'm going to go down here. I'm safe.
That's it. Okay. Just wait for... That guy's dead in that room. Okay. One bullet. No,
it's too risky. Uh, give me something else. It's too risky. Told you it was risky.
See? Nobody else is alive. Come on. I was told this is like the hardest level in the
game. That's what my horoscope said this morning. That's it. Oh, I almost died. Okay.
Get changed. This level is where I quit for six months. Six months. That's a long time.
Who the hell is this guy? Is this guy Duck? What? I... I don't understand this guy. He
Ducked. Does he... What? What am I supposed to do about this guy? I guess just avoid him?
Okay. What do I do about the Duck guy? There's a bunch of Duck guys.
Melee? Huh. Well, there's a melee here. Let's see if this theory works.
Ooh. All right. So they... I can't shoot these guys. Oh my god, he's running so fast.
Oh, I didn't know they... Holy fuck. I like how... I need to like crack my fingers for a
second. They like hurt my chest. I could... Come on. Get over here. He doesn't see me?
This guy's gonna see me. Give me a gun. What the fuck? What just happened?
I went through every single window. It didn't hit anybody. Okay. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh
my god. What do I do? I need a melee weapon. I need a melee weapon. I need a melee weapon.
Knife. Knife. Punch. What happened? Okay. We're fine. No more guns? I think this guy
just has a... My guy just has a bayonet. See through, but it's okay. Just pull this guy out.
That guy can see through here. Oh! Okay, we're fine. There's another guy there.
How do I get rid of this guy? Oh, like this. Got it. God. What? I was... What am I even
saying? I'm trying... It's not over. There's more to do. Oh. Cafeteria or something? No
guns. Why use the shotgun when I can just go like this? I didn't get the combo. That's
all right. Whatever. Pull this guy. All right. There's another big guy. Get the gun.
Okay. Big guy. I mean like, whoa, you got big guy. All right. We got a psycho though. I got
a... All right. This is the plan. Shoot. Grab melee. Hit guy. Or shoot, throw, punch. Right?
What do I do? Did he come? Is he over here? He has a gun? I thought that... No. I thought
that was one of those... Oh, what? I thought that was one of those crazy guys that...
Fucking hell. Oh, that made... Like why... Why are you doing that when you have a gun?
Is there a reason for that? That made me extremely upset. I'm upset right now.
You're just going to sit there and pound on his face and you just have a shotgun in your
pocket. No, I didn't have any bullets. Taking the gun with me. That guy's got a gun. Just pull
him if I can. Actually, shoot him. All right. Let's try this again. I need that one shot here
for him. All right. This guy has a gun. Oh, fuck. What am I going to do about that? Okay.
Well, I have to kill this guy. Fuck. Okay. I gotta run in there. No, I don't. Huh. Okay.
All right. I have to throw a knife at somebody's head. All right. Here we go. Knife this guy
right in the face. No, knife this guy right in the face. Wait, there's a pistol? Pistol?
Does it have bullets? Did I... Oh, there it is. You know, what would I do without you guys?
What would I do without you guys? What the hell would I even do without you?
What? I'm pan... What happened? What? That's not a door. What? Why did this not open? What?
What? What? Why did the door not... I walked right into it. I don't understand. What the
fuck did I just do? No, no, no, no, no. What? What the fuck did I just do? Did I just go back?
I just press... No fucking way. You gotta be kidding me. Really? That that just actually
happened? When you're in the middle of a level, you just... It's that easy to go all
the way to the beginning? No way. You gotta be fucking kidding me. What? No, no. Not even
like a confirmation, right? What? It's just like, now you're at the beginning again.
What? I'm so fucking mad right now. I can't believe it. That was like on floor three or four.
If I was on the first floor, I would understand, but why? There's no way to
undo that. And why did the music get so quiet? Yeah, I guess I just accidentally
restarted the entire thing. Now I gotta do this all over again. What the fuck?
Okay. Well, I think I'm so upset by that that I like, I don't even know what to do.
I'm going to do it again, but I'm, I'm so like annoyed by what just happened that I can't even
give you a reaction and I'm just going to play. Let's go. Base cam. All right. Fine.
End of the stream voice. Somebody wrote, I would quit for six months over that.
No, I, but I'm, I'm all right though. I've, I figured these levels out before
as a list. Go ahead and just don't get so upset that you can't just have no emotion right now.
This guy with gun, what else is over here? Give me another weapon. I gotta be ready for
this. I'm going to pull people into the bathroom. I didn't even know there was a way
to go in there. Oh, come on. I didn't even know there was a way to go down there.
Why did it rewind? No, it's coming out. Why did it rewind all the way without a confirmation?
What's what's what's with the cotton? No, no confirmation.
I can't believe it. I can't fucking believe it. Oh, no, I can't just relax.
I didn't even know they could go through there. Get in here. You
did this. Stop it. Just do it. Just I can't fucking, why would that even be an option?
I'm so fucking mad. I need to relax, man. I seriously need to relax. I'm gonna like
eat my microphone. But I'm, I might not sound that upset, but deep down and inside of like
my fucking veins, this is like when the evil villain is so dangerous and so terrifying and
somebody makes fun of him or slights him and he doesn't look upset. He's very collected and
he's just sitting there like, Oh, yes. Isn't that an interesting thing you said? And he's
so collected about it. But deep down, you know, you know that what he's he's planning.
He's planning to eat his microphone when he goes home. That guy doesn't have a gun.
I don't want him to see me. All right. Let's I gotta run up on this guy and get him.
Run up on him and get him. I can write. I know I can give me that gun. All right.
It's time to guns. No, I'm not going to do this yet. Yes, I am. I already did it.
Got it. Okay. I got it with one shot. Thank you. It's that easy. We're fine. Oh,
fuck. That's still going. Right. I'm, I still have to do this whole thing again, too.
I think that like when I, when I know that I, I'm just like fucking angry
and it's making me play at a level that I've never even seen before. Okay.
So we're good. Two guys up there with a gun. Anybody down there? I don't think there is.
Nope. Gun, gun. Let's go ahead and pull.
Of course that guy's still alive. Give me a break. That guy hit himself in the
fucking head with the door. I don't, I don't like the shotgun.
I seriously don't like the shotgun at all. It just causes fucking problems.
All right. Give me. Got them both. Yes. That guy can probably see me. Does that have,
that guy have line of sight on me? All right. Only guy with the gun right here.
Oh boy. Right. Give me this one. Very close to being exactly where we were and
deleted a bunch of fucking time for no reason. Wiser rewind. Give me that.
All right. These guys both have, that guy has a gun. That guy up there has a gun. Did I get
the guy over here? It was two, right? This guy in the bathroom. All right. I'm going to say
I'm going bathroom. Oh my fucking God. What have I done? I saw the guy behind me.
Oh my fucking God. I can't, I don't, I did it already. Oh, that's it up there. Okay. Give me
the pistol. No, fuck the pistol. Explain it. I want a full written report of what happened
there. All right. Now we got these two. Didn't hear that. I guess. Fine. You fucking can't be
serious. Oh my fucking God. I can't fucking believe it. Just give me a weapon. Any of
them that had bullets. Is he dead? Did the door hit him or is he dead? I don't know.
I think he's dead. The guy with the gun right here. I'm trying to fucking shoot the guy behind
him. What the, why? He knocked him down and he, I still shot him with the shotgun
and he absorbed every single fucking pellet. Just never forget, never forget that I did,
I pressed enter on this and almost did it again. Press R to reload. Can I pick, please? Anything,
please? Can you just go back to pick a chapter? No, it starts at the very beginning.
Damn it. These guys, that guy has a gun. What the fuck was that? All right. I need
something here. All right. This time I can't let that happen again. I got to get back to
where I just was. I don't think these, any of these have, no, no bullets at all.
I'm in trouble. I guess I could throw, nobody has a gun over here. Yeah,
they do. Shit. I have to pull this guy in here. Give me your gun. Okay. Can we please try this
again? Without like a total disaster. All right. How did I even get shot by that guy?
This guy was, what the heck happened? All right. This crunch time here. Get it done.
For the love of God. That, kill that guy last. Because there's two, there's a pistol
on the ground there. He's done, nobody has line of sight. All right. Here we go.
I got to make this happen. What the fuck is you doing over here? What are you doing over here?
What do you think you're doing over here? What are you doing over here?
All right. Finally. Don't press escape ever again. My heart is racing right now. No,
I already did this too, didn't I? Did I already, where's my fucking character? What the
fuck? What? All right. But by the way, when I press R, why doesn't R go now? Who's left? Oh boy. Oh
boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. When there's somebody up here, I got like collapsed on by somebody before
this guy. I need a melee. That's it, right? Somebody else ran after me before. I remember
distinctly. Fuck. Somebody came after me with, I need to get a melee. Give me a reliable
melee. I don't even know who's down there. Nobody has a gun. That guy. I knew I saw,
I knew he was coming. This guy has a gun. Nobody in this room. Just this guy here. Come on.
You can see me. Get over here. How do you not see me? Jesus, man. Don't go in there.
Don't go in there. Just wait. Fuck. Come on. I don't, I don't want to go in there yet.
Oh, he almost did it. He almost did it to me. Last guy. Now we're back. Kill them. I know.
I'm trying. It's just very nerve wracking. This is where I was before it. No. Actually,
I kind of like that strategy. That you stupid door. It has to be the same color as everything
else. I liked that strategy before it was a fucking terrible strategy. Fucking guy.
I thought it was a fat guy. Fucking God again. Where's the fucking sprint guy?
I right clicked three times to try to pick that up and it didn't pick it up until like
the fourth one. Why? I seriously, he just fucking like instant teleported around the corner.
I need that gun. The fuck. All right. Can you not like fucking hit box me from five feet away?
Same thing up here. Where's the guy? He's right up here somewhere, right?
Jesus game. Come on. All right. We got one, two, a guy with a gun. I'm going to melee over
here. Is this a toothbrush? Bring this gun a little closer because I know for a fact I'm
going to fuck it up and need it. What the hell? What the hell? Where's the gun? Oh, what happened
to the gun? I threw it up here. I'm going to shoot this guy from over here. There's a guy.
Is that guy alive to the right? I think he is. Is he? He's not moving. Is this guy alive
right here? He is. It's one of these idiots. Okay, gun. Fucking bird noise. All right. I
got to be very careful here. This too, this too much can go wrong. Don't do it yet.
Okay. Got it. Last guy. This guy has a gun. Yet. Escape. No, it's not over.
Don't have a guy. I don't have a guy come over to me. It killed me.
Oh, okay. We've got this. We're evacuating. Go get yourself out of here.
I'm just kidding. I'm not going to press fucking reset. Oh boy. Hey, I still got it.
I might have failed that level though. It depends. Not even a confirmation.
What do you think? D? That's all right. C-. I got a better score because I rewound.
After that, well, there's not a whole lot more to tell. If I may ask, where did you go after
you escaped? I guess I might as well tell you. I went to Hawaii. You see, that's why I need
you to get me a plane ticket. By the way, those of you guys that are watching,
this is like 80% of the way through the game. This is not like Hotline Miami 2 part 1.
We played this a couple of days ago. I'm just finishing it up. I'm going to play it until it's
done. And there you go. Spoiler if you've never seen the game. This is not level 1. You see,
that's why I need you to get me a plane ticket. It's not for me. It's for my mother. I'm
really worried about her. She can't take care of herself. I was hoping you could get her
to come here. I understand I'm going to have to check my bank account. I'll get the money
for it one way or another, okay? Wouldn't be right otherwise. I don't think you understand
how much of a help you've been. By the way, those of you that are just joining us now,
I want to make sure I make this very clear. We talked about it. Let's talk about it for like
a couple minutes right now. Christmas Eve is going to be a stream. And you, yes,
you are going to be involved if you want. There's a channel on the Discord right now
that is designed for you to give suggestions of what you'd like to buy me for Christmas.
And it's going to be secret. I'm not going to know what they are. It's going to be
secretly purchased. You don't have to buy anything. Yeah, I'm going to buy it
through a proxy. So I will not know what it is. And they're going to be wrapped and I'm
going to open them on stream on Christmas Eve. That is what's happening. Your suggestions have
to be an Amazon link and they have to be prime shippable. Otherwise I will not be able
to get them in time. Has to be Amazon. Has to be prime shippable. Shippable. Shippable.
There's too many P's in that word. And your suggestions have to be between zero and fifty
dollars. No more than that. Maximum budget that's allowed is fifty bucks. And the mods are going
to take this from the suggestions and I come up with a Christmas list and that's one of
the things we're going to be doing on Christmas Eve. Zero dollars. Dear Evan, I haven't heard
from you in a while. I miss you. The kids miss you too. I think we can still make this work
but I can't live with a man who puts his job before his family. I still love you. You know
I do. I hope you love me too. Please call me when you read this. Sharon. 49.99 or
fifty dollars. Like fifty. Five zero dot space zero zero zero. Why are there multiple
things to look at here? Hold on. Wait what? Act six catastrophe. Did I just go am I
writing a story right now? You wanted to see me boss. Yeah we've got things to do tonight.
Like what? You know the strip club on 77th? It's opening up tomorrow. So? The Colombians
they own the place. They're having an opening party tonight. VIPs only. Let you find out.
How do you think they invited me? Bring your guns. We're going to make sure they have a
fun party. You want to start a war with the Colombians. Is that really a good idea?
Got a lot more people than we do. After my father died they went in and stole our territory. Our
business. You think I'm just gonna let that slide. This is really a good time for it.
This is not going to be a better time while we wait. They keep expanding. Now who's the
boss here? You or me? You got any more objections? You're the boss. They'll do
whatever you tell me. Alright then let's go. So now I play as this guy. You guys know that
machine that you punch and it tells you like how many pounds per square inch your punches are?
I can get that thing over like seven or eight hundred. I can almost get that thing.
I can almost max that thing out at nine nine nine nine nine. Stop changing characters. I have no
control over it. Yeah okay sure. I'll prove it. Next time I'm available and I'm in front of one
of those things I'm going to I'm going to hit that thing over a hundred pounds per square
inch. I impress people all the time. They go holy shit man. Well you go like it's my turn.
They're like like 620 and I'm like oh wow that was pretty good. You know another guy
goes up like oh wow the 540. That's a lot dude. That's a fucking shit load. Good for you.
Somebody else comes up and like spins around runs across the room sprinting and then they punch as
hard as they can. Like seven seven hundred and then the whole place fucking screams and I just
like crack my neck a little bit. I'm like um let me try. I'll try. It sounds like fun.
I get up there and I fucking destroy this thing and the thing goes like
and then people just their jaws drop because I do about 800 fucking per pound per square
inch punch. I know I can do it and I'm just letting them all have like their moment
with their like 600 pounds per square inch punches and I let them have it and I'm like yeah yeah and
then I get up there and I'm telling you this is real. I'll do it. You want to see like how
ferocious of a person I am. The next time one of those is around I'm going to have somebody
videotape me doing it. 21st scene. This is called the screw. What was it called? I didn't
I saw it for one second. Roll dodge. That's all I have. Oh seizure. Okay I can't pick
anything else. I don't want to dodge roll. All right let's go. I didn't why did I not hit that
guy for? Oh okay all right all right all right. Pretty good line of sight on me right here. Come
on. Windows. I didn't know those are windows. I didn't see them. So we got to pull this guy
through here. God it's so dark. Come on. Where are you? We go. Here comes two other guys. All
right. Pistol right there. This is a problem. Let's see if I can pull them. All right.
All right. That guy's just dancing over there. I need to light up again so I can see. Turn it
up. All right. All right. You get you get one piece of pez. Let's go with this. I can't tell
it was anybody else. There's a guy right here. Well where'd he go? Where did that guy go?
God damn it. All right. Well I'm just gonna go in here and shoot these guys I guess. All
right. I don't know. I can't. That guy's a window. That's it up here. I'm just gonna
keep going. What the fuck? That patrol took so long for him to get down here.
Where the hell was that guy? All right. Again we've got these two guys. Got a knife. Pull
them over here. Why are you like this? What? Am I missing something here? Am I
missing something here? Is he like up? Who the hell is this guy? Why can I not? Okay.
That was weird. That patrol didn't get him. Shit. Last guy. There he is. What? What? Where?
What? What killed me? There's a guy in a bush. Why am I fucking not surprised? All right. I
gotta shoot this guy. I just took the guy's head off. All right. Again I can't see anything
on the ground. I guess there's a gun here. All right. Watch out for guy in the bush.
That's great. I love everything about that. Fucking asshole. All right. Let's go. I have
a choice apparently. I can't go that way. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. He came out this time. Well. Well.
Okay. I'm gonna miss somebody and I'm not gonna even see them. I guarantee that. Someone's
gonna be like hiding in a sofa and they're gonna shoot me. The dog. Don't let me forget
about the dog. I will forget about that fucking dog. Is he still alive? What? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Why am I? Stop doing that. Huh? Why am I making that fucking noise? Relax. Dog. Dog.
Who's left? I don't know. Maybe the one with 20. All right. We got guy with a shotgun. I'm
gonna keep this guy locked on because I know I'm gonna fuck this up. Told you. I just
didn't even look. I hope I got somebody. What is the fucking door in the way?
Who is left? I'm so paranoid. Right here. Last guy? Yep. Okay. I guess I'm gonna go over here.
Well. That was it. Apparently. Go to the car. But what about over here? I want to go up
that way. Is it the same? No. It's the same thing. No. Just different entrance. Okay. Well.
That wasn't hard enough for you. No. That was okay. That was fine. That was like a nice level.
It was challenging. Dark. Nice. Always a C. All right. Somebody tell me. I'm unlocking
items that I'm... I thought that was a fucking like... I thought that was a monster and those
were eyes for a second. I was like who's in like a different costume? I thought it was like
a weird like bear costume. Whatever. Let's just not pay attention to it.
Ugh. We sure did a number on those bastards, huh? Call us for a celebration, don't you think?
I don't know, boss. That's what that is. It's not... there's no nudity here.
That's those people in costumes. Those are just like eyes and that's like a head and they have
like hats on. You know how I make like 40% of every rumble character in the new 2k games?
That's... that's what it is. I don't know, boss. You don't know what the hell is that
supposed to mean. I think I'm gonna head back home. I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
And why is that? You've got all you need right here, don't you? I gotta get home to my girlfriend.
Been a long day, you know? You guys see that fucking shark? Yeah, it's a pretty big shark.
Boy, that girl sure did a number on you, huh? You know, a real man doesn't need to rely
on women to live his life. The minute you get attached to anyone, you know you're fucked.
Besides, that girl of yours is way too good for you. One day she will come to her senses,
you know. Well, that's none of my business. Go on home if that's what you want.
All right, see you soon. Oh, before you go, I left a little something for you on the desk outside.
Buy your girl something nice. I can't, like, smash this? What is it? Oh, nice. Money! Thanks
for the money. Oh, I can't go in the cool car? I let the door open? It's all right. All right,
boys, this is it. Tonight we'll be rich. We can do anything we want. The Colombians will
have nothing left. They'll learn to fear us. Toast to our new lives as kings of the street.
This kind of sounds like a cool Bowser theme song from Mario and Luigi RPG games. Don't die
on the third floor. All right, I'll try not to. Am I supposed to be getting attacked here?
If only we could hear it. You can hear it. Uh, guys? Oh, what an end. What an end to the
arc. Oh, there's guys right there. Let's see if we can spring something together here.
Turn the mouse sensitivity down. It's fucking me up. Need a new weapon.
Ooh, boy. Come on up. Pistol, please. All right, this somebody, this people down here.
I'm gonna get lit up by this guy. No, okay. They don't have line of sight here?
No, just I'm checking to make sure they don't have, you know, pull them. What's the point
of that? How do they miss? Just this guy. What about down here? Nobody. Okay, got ya.
Pistol. I would like that. Fuck. I don't know. Knew it. Okay, we're good. Straight up.
Okay, we've got, ooh, I didn't mean to do that. Well, okay. I feel like I have to stand here.
Sensitivity, please. All right, let me think about this. So, this guy's gonna get up.
And then, nobody. There's a, watch out for the walls. I got a guy here.
Why ya, why we? Oh, okay. Whatever. Who has sight on me? Somebody all the way up there?
Okay, I get it. Okay, get you. Get you. Watch everybody come around the corner.
That leaves you. You. And somebody else, I guess. You two. I need to make sure that none of you
people up here are going to kill me like you. One, two, three. That it? Nope. Couple of guys
left. Although, I want this gun. It's more reliable for me. What do we got? See if I
can get them both. Nope. I should still be able to get you though. Oh, no, I didn't. I got
him. I got him. Is it safe? That's the question. I don't think, I think it's just this guy.
Nobody else in this room. No hidden people. No bush. Almost guy in a bush. He was, he was
turning into a bush guy. I got him before he transformed. Do it before he gets up!
All right, we're good. Is that it? Oh, no. There. That should disable all the security
doors. I heard about this guy, the Joker. Yeah, he's crazy. You hear how weird he is?
Yes, I have heard about how weird he is. Whoops. I can't. What the fuck? The Joker
misses at the beginning of the movie. Don't worry. You've never seen, I've never seen
Star Wars before. This, yo, it's fine. You'll be fine. How are you still living? How are
you still among the living? You got shot. Oi! I don't know. I have a gun in my hand.
Oh, you put the gun down when you do that. All right, let's see who's up here.
You. Dead. Dead. Dead. Anybody else? Ah, place to hide. Good vantage point. Guy with the gun.
We got fat guy. I need another gun. I need that. Give it to me.
Ah, you. Be right back. Oh shit. Okay, I'm fine. Why was I even locked on? Made no sense.
Ha, now I'm not locked on and it was a problem.
All right, that's it. Just the two guys in there. Shouldn't be too much of a problem.
It will be though. Of course it will be. And hey ho ho. Got it. Okay. All right,
just slurp it up. Did you say I'm high as fuck? Father, what are you doing here?
I'm not here. You know that. Yes, I know. Then why are you here? I don't know. I want
to make you proud. Such things don't matter. I can see you haven't changed. You're just like
me. You won't get in it until it's already too late. You know, it's me the chicken. Your
father is right. You don't get it, do you? Not that it matters anymore. It's all the same in
the end. And there's nothing wrong. There's nothing you can do about that, is there?
Goddamn. But father. We already told you, Dutch. He's not here anymore. In fact, neither are you.
That was a B for effort. A C- for effort. My face came on. Let me turn it off. Thanks
for reminding me. Uh, you are style unlocked. Blood? What was it? What? Why is it already
laughing? It's already laughing at me. Blood tired. I am still a little blood tired. I don't
know about you guys, but when I get blood taken, it takes me like three or four days
to completely recover from it. I just feel my life force draining and it just, it throws me off
for almost a week. It took six, seven vials. What do we have here? And I had to breathe into
a bag. They were testing to see if I have, um, Healabacta pylori, which is like a bad
stomach and intestinal bacteria. That's a whole ordeal, but everything's fine. Don't worry.
Uh, what do we have here, Johnson? That's not real. They were just fucking with you. What?
H. pylori is like a bacteria. I looked it up. What do we have here? Looks like your
perp's been at it again. This one got quite the treatment. How much for a vial of my blood?
You're not getting any of my blood. This is one got quite the treatment. He left another
message. You have to stop them. I don't want to take any more innocent lives. Whoever did
this must be completely out of their mind. He's a whack job, all right? This city seems
to be full of them. Did he leave any clues behind? The chief's going to be on my ass
with all the press with this will get a shell casing and a couple of prints.
No, you know, you know why I would never give somebody my blood because that's everything.
Like you're talking about everything. Oh, you're concerned that your passwords are in
there. Your DNA is in there. Your entire genetic makeup is in that vial. Everything
about you that ever will be and ever was. I don't want you guys to know what my fucking
body passwords are. Are you serious? A shell casing and a couple of prints is going to be
hard to see if they match the victim given the state he's in. Might find more when we do
a more thorough inspection of the place. Well, I hope you do find something. Not to put any
pressure on you guys, but my job's on the line on this one. We'll do our best. All right,
don't think I'll be much use here. I'm pretty beat. I'm heading home to catch some sleep.
Let me know what you find tomorrow. We'll do sir. I don't know. I don't know what my blood
type is. I have no idea. Four? I don't know. I don't know. Brute force his blood. No,
sooner or later. I don't want anyone to have that because sooner or later in 500 years,
you'll be able to like read people's thoughts with their DNA and shit. You'll be able to like
recreate somebody's brain and look up like, like in their brain catalog, everything they've
ever done or said or anything they ever spoke of. You're going to be able to pour my blood
into like a machine and go through my back catalog and find out last time I shit my
pants. I don't want you to be able to do that ever in a thousand years. Time for bed. Why would
you care if it's a thousand years? Because I can't, I don't know. I don't want, I can't find it.
Thunder and lightning. I can't find it. What am I looking for? You'll be able to take that
blood DNA brain thing and you'll be able to just go watch a video recording of me,
like a POV of me eating a booger when I was 11. That's scary. No, we got a huge amount
of community subs here. Furt, thank you Furt. Fernandez for the 10 community subs.
Thank you so much for 10 community subs coming in right now. Am I missing something here?
Looking for this. For Smash. You know, Convert. You know, Convert for Smash.
What are you doing here? This is a crime scene. Well, you know what they say.
Twitterers always return to the scene of the crime. I guess there must be some truth to that,
huh? Right, who are you? You don't recognize me? We're related by blood, aren't we?
Think of me as your son. You created me after all. Give me back my gun, creep. You want it,
huh? How about a hug instead? What? Did I drop a TV on his head? There you are, hop on in.
Your next scene is up. So step on it. Is there a reason why we took the dog van from Dumb and
Dumber? Okay, um, your next scene is up. What just happened? What did I just do? What?
So this hotline Miami is just a movie? Is that what this is?
Oh, I need that gun. Speaking of guns. I got stuck. I got stuck. I got stuck. Speaking of
guns. Give me that one. Holy fuck. Got the gun over here. Anybody else in this room? Oh yeah,
there is. What is this guy? What is that guy? I don't know yet. He left it. I'll deal with
him in a minute. I don't know. I had the glass. He was, ah, I had that so clean too.
That really was clean. Glass windows. Every fucking, every fucking level has to have a
glass window. Everywhere. No, always a mistake. Never hit space on anybody for any reason.
What's the reason for it? It just takes extra time. You just get extra points.
I'm just a C minus fucking streamer. Why do I care about like the extra 200 points?
2000 points. Rewind. What are you talking about? Why would I rewind? Why would I do that?
No, I'm not going to rewind. I missed a cut scene. If I rewind, where is it going to
put me? I broke the game. Why did I break the game? What? I better not regret this.
I went all the way. How did I get it to work? I have no idea. What was I? Was I delirious?
What were we talking about? DNA? Detective Pardo, you're a disgrace. I've never heard
of anything like this before. Normally, I never offer any kindness to a person such
as yourself, but since you are a police officer, I will now give you a choice.
Turn yourself in and confess to your crimes. Maybe they'll go easy on you.
If you don't, I have several officers waiting outside to arrest you.
Sir, I'm not sure what you're talking about here. What is it you think I've done?
Think I have a pile of evidence here against you. Ballistics report, fingerprints,
witness statements. To think a police officer would be the Miami mutilator. You make me sick.
Now hand me your badge. I'll have one of our officers take your confession.
Sir, there must have been some mistake. Someone must have set me up.
I'll prove it to you if you just let me go, okay? You're going nowhere, Pardo.
Don't make this any harder than it already is. Sorry, sir. You'll have to take me by force.
Well, I did really miss a lot, didn't I? I just walked on the movie set and then started
punching people. That doesn't work on dogs. All right, all right. That's it. Keep it going.
Pistol. Oh, oh, oh, why? I'm actually upset by that. I'm actually pissed off. What am I doing?
I want this gun. That one. That one. I want this one. Okay, so we've got
gun. No gun. Gun, gun, gun. Watch out for that gun. I didn't even get the guy. Oh,
fucking that's called panicking. All right. Hydrate. I'm very hydrated. Yeah, I've got a
water here. I'm good. What about the guy in here? No, that guy would have just killed me
if he had a gun. I was prepared for it. You know, I was very prepared. Oh,
grab the shotgun. Oh, yeah. Here it comes. This is where I get. I had it and it was so
clean and I did it. I did that. I had that. So I got all nice shot, shot, shot, shot.
We call this bullshit. This is called bullshit. By the way, nobody in the world,
nobody on earth. Let's go over like offices. Okay. This makes sense. Nobody has a window
to another like coworkers office like this. This window doesn't do anything. Nobody has
a window like this. This is called whining. Nobody has a window here. And who built these?
The window should be here to the outside. I've seen something like that before, actually.
Wait, I won. I won. I'm not whining. Am I? Is this whining? This guy with the taser.
I'm about to start fucking whining. Okay. Got him. Die. I had it. What am I doing?
Just shoot him. I mean, why do I have to be paranoid of 15 people with guns? Fine,
I'll do the strategy and it would have worked. Just shoot him. What the fuck was that? Dude.
You know, I wanted to pick up the same weapon twice. That'd be wonderful.
Got it. Okay. Geez. Any more windows? Gun. What the fuck? Whoa.
Oh, fucking office windows. Why do they have? God damn it. What the fuck?
What the hell? It's so unnecessary. He's terrible at 80% of every game he plays.
Give me a break. Please. What? This shit is fucking hard as shit.
People have quit this game. Like not played for six months. You saw the chat room. People
went away from this game for six months. I'm still here. One guy said that. Yeah,
and that's fine because the game is fucking hard. I read a post on Twitter where a guy said he
couldn't even beat the first room. All right. Come on. I got a C on these levels. Did I
get that guy too? That worked. That worked. Now, I went to Twitter. There was a guy that
was like, hey, I can't beat the first room. Can somebody help? What do you think the
responses were? Idiot. Fucking this stupid door. Hey, you want to know what all the responses were?
Idiot. And then he finally beat the second floor. And he went out back on Twitter and he said,
hey guys, I beat the second floor. I'm really trying. It's a tough game.
Idiot. And this is how you make me making this story up. So? You don't think this
happened at one point? Somebody said this. Give me one pellet on this guy. Come on. Nobody
else is up here, right? Get good. Most people get good. Oh, I've got some news for you. I've got
news for you. Go open up the achievements of this game on Steam. How many people have gotten past
the first level? It's not even going to be fucking 30%. I can't answer that. How many
people beat the cleric beast? It's like 40. You're one of 40 people that did that. You
should be proud of yourself. Put your hands behind your head. Get down on the ground.
29% of people have the beat the game achievement. So, yeah. What the heck? That's less than a third
of all people that have played this game on Steam. Stop flaming me. Stop flaming me.
Two out of thirds of bad? No, it's not. Come on. You can't look at it like that.
If 70% of everybody doesn't beat the game, does that mean that 70% of people aren't good
gamers? I mean, probably. You're probably right. Don't shoot. I'm a detective. Here's my badge.
I said get down on the ground. This is your last warning. Let me through. I'm a police.
I don't get losing for that, right? You'd be surprised if you go look at achievements
and trophies. This is Pardo speaking. Cough. They're casuals. Are they though? What if they
just aren't good at it? It's okay. That's okay if you're not good at it.
We need you down at the station. I don't feel too good. I'm gonna have to take the day off.
This isn't really the time. You're not a pro gamer. T? C-? I've never failed a level.
Hey, you there. I'm here to see your boss. Bring him out for me, will you? You don't have
an appointment, do you? Besides, the boss isn't in. Oh, yeah? Well, his car is right
outside. Boss has many cars. Was there anything else? Playing that game, huh? My back suit
won't be telling that, okay? Time, guys. After today, we'll be in the big league again.
Just remember the plan and don't be late. If you are, we're toast. All right, I'm going
in. Wish me luck. What? I don't get it. Takeover is the last 24th scene. Killing
punches, no weapons, bloodline, firepower. What is firepower? I guess we'll find out.
Uh, okay. Oh, this must be T-pose, I remember. Oh, that didn't work. Maybe it will.
Fuck, come on. Oh, who's left? Watch it. But where are you gonna come from? Over here,
I see you. Almost out of bullets. I gotta get this last guy right here through the glass.
Okay, who's left? That's a big gun right here, isn't it? No, it's not. Those are the
guns I just had. I was just wearing those. All right, that's fine. Let's go. This is all
cleared down here. Window, though. Watch out for the window. Watch out for the window.
I panicked, but it's okay. I need that gun. Uh, this guy right here, I should get side on
him right there. Nope. I'll try it again. I got it. Okay. What about you right here?
Got it. What? What's going on? Uh, is there a reason for that? One guy over there with
a gun. Everybody else has melee. I don't think, unless I miss somebody over here.
Yep, I did. What do I have to do with you? What do I do with you? What the fuck? No. What? I
tried to punch him. He has so much reach. Holy shit. I mean, I knew it was the duck guy,
but he has like some insane reach. You can't punch him. Okay. So I need a melee weapon?
Because I could punch the other. I could punch the other guy that was running. That was melee
only. Apparently not this dude. How's that guy doing? Oh fuck! I ran out of bullets right at
the end. 64 bullets remaining in that. I say that like that's not very much. Same deal. All
right, where's the melee weapon? Right here, down around you. Let's wait. All right, then you
and you. Little dog. Yep. Give me a melee weapon. No, I could probably get you too.
No, I can't. Whatever. I think I need a gun. I believe I, yeah, I need to kill these dudes
here. One more guy up there, I think. Maybe not. Can I pull him out? Can I like throw
a knife over there? Over that? Or let hit it? I'm not sure. Once I shoot this guy,
though, he's gonna run out. Is he out? No, he's not out. Okay, now melee weapon. Let's go.
Pull him out. Let's go. Got it. Okay. Over there. I didn't check over this way though. I
got everybody over here, didn't I? That's where I started, isn't it? Okay, let's wrap around
here again. No other dogs. No random stray people. Okay, I just want to check. I think
there might be another guy over here. I didn't mean to click my fucking thumb.
Ah, holy shit. Okay. So we got one guy left, I think, right here. That's it.
Nobody's standing. Nobody in a bush, right? I'm not gonna get pushed. He's above me. Wow.
What? Oh, he came from the top. Oops. I knew he was coming. Shit. He's coming. Oh, he's
coming. He's coming. He's coming to get me. He's coming to get me. The guy with the melee
is on his way. Oh, fuck. Okay, relax. What else is there? I need a gun. That'll do it.
Windows. Anybody above? I think this room is safe. Yeah, this room is safe except
the windows. Wait, what? Did I knock it through? I just used them on 10. I knew
somebody else was gonna come over there. I knew it. And I fucking freaked out.
Good. All right. Now. Oh, what? There's a window there. They can shoot through here.
Ay, yi, yi. You go through one, two, three, four rooms with this window. There's no other way
you can get over there. Any windows up top? There are windows right there. All right. I gotta
go up. Hold on. All right. Fuck. What? This like across the map. You can't see anybody.
Fucking hell. I'm just gonna sit here. Out of bullets. Somebody's coming. Which way are
they coming though? Are they coming this way? Who else? Anybody else down the whole hallway?
I gotta go this way anyways, bud. Yeah, he saw me. He's coming. That's the guy with the
fucking this thing. Shotgun. I'm gonna get collapsed on. I know it. I'm so paranoid.
Someone's gonna fucking come all the way down here. All right. Safe. What's this? I can't
pick it up. Dog. I have to snipe them over here. I gotta try because this is gonna be
something else here. I gotta pick off at least a couple of people. Dog. There's gonna be a
dog coming. Just wait. You sure? He's coming though. Where's he going? I don't know where
he's going but I'm gonna wait. Excuse me? Did I fall off the map? Did I walk backwards too far?
Is that what happened? Fuck it. No, you can't do it like that unless you memorize the entire
level. You have to, I have to memorize the whole level to play it like that.
All right. Here's the dog. Wait till he goes across the entire map. The whole thing.
I can't believe it. There's probably another dog coming. All right. I got a bunch. Who the fuck
are you? What are you doing on the stairs? Why are you in the very beginning on the stairs
out of my line of sight holding shift the whole way up? What the fuck?
All right. Here he comes. Got it. I gotta piss so bad. No other dogs. Dog. Somebody.
Is somebody here? Somebody's here. Okay. I gotta sit here for a second because I just
may have alerted like at least two. Oh my lord. Okay. Did I get him? Nope. Just wait.
We'll make it over here eventually. He'll find it. Thanks for the new gun. Now it's
a question of shooting through here. Where the fuck? Holy shit. There's an entrance there.
Move out of the way. All right. Anybody. Somebody. I gotta hide it over here.
Just hide here. No. Where? I got a safe room. This one's safe. Right? No, it's not. Yes,
it is. There's only two other people in that other room. I think I'm good. I'm gonna go
down. If I see a dog, I swear to you. I'm so ready for a dog. Where is the dog?
Look at how far away you are. I'm so fucking paranoid right now. Any other guns up here?
This one. Did I get him? I'm gonna go for it. Whatever. Guy on the stairs. Right? Nope.
Is it? Okay. Wait, wait, wait. I need to. Okay. There's a machete right here.
Give me the machete. Oh, you idiot. You fucking idiot. Is it safe to get that?
One guy right here. Holy fuck. He almost just got me. Last guy. Right? Nope. That guy
would have killed me. Alright. So looks like I gotta go down. Last dude right here. No windows
for him to shoot me. Nobody else. Just him. I know I freaked out right there, but you gotta
do what you gotta do. Alright. Another one. This way. Fuck. Damn it. Alright. Wrap around.
Let's do it again here. Give me the shotgun. So I gotta take this guy out
cleanly. He's all the way at the end and then shotgun blast once. I, whatever. Three shots.
Who's up there? Okay. It's safe. No, it's not. I can't go over there. Dog. Dog. Big guy.
This room is safe. I need a better gun than this. Windows. No, I gotta be. Dog. Nope.
Can go. Just gonna make sure no one's right. Okay. There's another dog. Watch it. Watch it.
That's not gonna make anybody sprint over here. We sure about that? Give me the other gun. These
dogs are freaking out. Are they trying to come get me? I think they trying to get me,
but I don't know. I gotta go. I gotta take those. Okay. There's a melee only guy right here.
I gotta get this guy now. Okay. So give me a melee weapon. I'm gonna go pull that guy out.
Come on. Come on down here. Alright. I think that's it for that. I need a gun back.
They're coming for me. Are they? I have to kill them right now. I gotta go
up down here and I gotta shoot. Alright. That's my plan. Watch out for that guy.
Those dogs are coming after me. I don't know. I hate not being able to see over there.
Dogs are coming over here now. No, they're not. It's not safe standing there.
One dude and then it's safe and I can collect guns. That guy. Is that a melee only guy?
No, just a just a guy. I'm just like losing it. I'm freaking out right now because I'm
terrified of something behind me. Okay, done. New gun. I can go down.
There's only one two remaining. I have to go from this room. No windows.
I just have to shoot. There's a door. Don't fuck it up. I fucked it up. I
fucked it up bad. I fucked it up real bad. Okay. Wait, that's not it?
Where? Okay, that is it. Is it? I see the arrow. Okay, it is. This game is gonna give me diarrhea.
It really is. Fuck, there's even more. No, is this it? Alright, this is the end. I'm just
gonna get rid of everybody in this room. Is there any special gun I can pick up in here?
I don't think there's anything else. I'm dropping the gun on the ground.
You got some balls coming in here alone, but this is as far as you go. That's how you greet your
guests, is it? You can drop the AK now. Face it, you're already dead. And why are you still
talking to me? Got him. I'll give you 10 seconds to surrender. Maybe I'll let you live.
You're out of your mind. Uh oh. One, two, three, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Hey, how does it feel? How do you like it? I've been playing like that the whole game.
Do you have a problem with that one? I give you... Alright, fine. That's okay.
Sick. Why don't you swing on by and check it out? Anyone there? Click. Wait, those jelly beans?
Come on, those are drugs. Okay, hey boss, take it easy on those pills. You shouldn't
take too many of them. Can I stand up? What the fuck is this? Oh no. You're really gonna
throw Yoshi's Island fucking mushroom level at me right now? This is gonna make me sick.
Oh no. I hate this. Who the fuck are you? Why can I not hit this guy?
Dog has like two heads. Please tell me I can like first try this. This is actually
gonna give me a problem. Alright, come on, let's go. Congratulations, you beat the level.
Uh...
Is that a bear? There's an actual bear in here. What the fuck? What? Okay, I get...
No, I get it. I get it. Well, actually, I don't get it. I'll get it if something else happens.
Alright, wait. So this is... Alright, this is... I get it. I get it. I understand it.
What? Gotta get a grip. Gar. Uh-oh, windows. Of course. Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
Yeah, alright. He's on a... This is... This happened in like the third level, didn't it?
I get it. No, I get it. That was like the zebra. What is that? Uh, I guess I'm gonna...
Does that explosion hurt me? I apologize to those of you that are, you know,
photo-sensitive to this kind of shit. I don't even know if I'm shooting this. Was that a tiger?
Did I win? I did. That's it. Keep going. I got an axe. Um, I don't remember bats.
Oh no, it's the two ducks. Okay, it's the... It's my favorite character! Ooh.
That's my favorite character. Or two characters. Uh, alright. Oh, ffff...
Alright, it's just doing a gigantic fire-breathing dragon. Oh my goodness. Um,
I killed one of them before. Dodge it? Easier said than done. Are they immune to damage?
Oh, okay. I see. Holy fuck. Alright, so I can only hurt them at a specific time. Oh man.
When can I hit you? Do it! Sorry, swans. Whoops. Do I need that? I hope not. Is this the end
of the game? That's it? Okay, that's the end of the game. No, the last game had a post-credits
chapter, right? That's probably what's gonna happen. Well, yeah, the ending was not actually
the ending. Out of chronological order. Uh, so I... I have no idea what the fuck that game was.
I have no idea what happened. I have a general understanding of kind of what happened,
but I don't think I do. There's a video on YouTube that greatly explains it all.
Because that was- that was the son of the first game boss. And they were all part- they were
all in a military troop together, right? First game is Jacket, and no, the- the- the son- that
son wasn't like part of the group. But I'm talking about the whole thing. There was so
many characters- one guy was a serial killer? Alright, so Evan, what's your opinion? Do you
think there's any truth to his claims of a conspiracy? I couldn't find any substantial
proof of a conspiracy, but my research strongly indicates that there might have been one.
Hopefully my book will get people to start asking questions. Perhaps a more thorough
investigation can be conducted in the future. You're implying that the official investigation
wasn't thorough? From the police reports I've seen, the investigation was a complete mess.
A lot of stones were left unturned, so many questions left unanswered.
I really hope we'll get to the bottom of the whole incident one day.
And when can we expect to read this book of?
We are interrupting the program for an emergency broadcast, the president of the
united states has been assassinated. A press conference in washington was uninterrupted by
a league of armed men during what appears to be a coup d'etat. The president was shot and
killed, the russian president was also shot dead in the chaos that ensued- what?
The ringleader of the uprising appears to be a u.s army general- in this time no official
statements have been made experts believe this will be seen as an act of
war against Russia the fear of repercussions may be severe stay tuned
as we will be purporting live from looks like you've gotten yourself quite
comfortable over here you know what they say about good times don't you
yeah good times never last that's right soon this will all be over I had a
feeling things would catch up with me are they on to me oh no this this
is much worse how long do I have you you don't have much time no one
does there's nothing I can do about it right no by now there's nothing anyone
can do about it okay no need to fight it then I'm glad you understand leaving
this world is not as scary as it sounds was on drugs so that was on
drugs nuke didn't that happen in the first one too didn't that happen in
the first game huh okay no didn't you like walk out of the door in the
first game at the store and it did this so this is a nuke was drunk no
that was in this game okay so it's the war between USA and Russia this is
the prequel we're getting pulp fiction this is the opening to smash
ultimate I'm not really I mean so many computer entertainment they had really I
thought it was just I'll go insane if I play hard mode no I can't do a hard
mode some of you guys are superhuman I'm not I'm just a mere I'm just a
mere mortal I can't do hard mode try one level on hard there's a new
opening to hard mode well we'll take a look at it and then I do have the
sampling of some community workshop stuff cuz that's pretty interesting and
I'd like to check it out well I did it I beat hotline Miami to remember when I
started and a bunch of people in chat said he's not gonna finish this game
there's no way never he's never gonna finish this game I remember that
two days later done I said that and I stand by it hi he's how do you
stand by that if I have you just watched the credits roll you're not
gonna beat it I stand by that statement all right so new game hard is it is it
gonna continue or does it matter if I do I still have to press continue we're
gonna just do hard mode I just want to see the cutscene I like this song
the song is really good the whole soundtrack is great but I like the
title card you all came back huh why you all know how this ends don't you
what the hell are you blabbing about who are you people why am I here
you're not really here are you hmm is this another dream it's all a dream isn't
it enjoy it while you can soon you will all have to wake up I think I've heard
enough hey guys let's get out of here there's only one way out of this
unfortunately why have you taken us here everybody's dying to tell you
what's up that is all pointless you're all heading the wrong way at
best you'll end up in the cemetery so what I'm not scared of dying you
don't care what happens to your friends either do you I feel like my acting
level here is like it's like tick-tock level like can you imagine like the
split screen here you don't care what happens to your friends either do you
keep on following in your father's footsteps I've told you where they
lead look I'm sorry for I appreciate it but I'm not really who you think
I am remorse is not going to get you anywhere I'm afraid you think you
everything huh you I didn't I don't get why is it you do the things you do you
just gonna sit there and judge us are you is that what you think you don't
know who I am do you fine have it your way just who are you that I'm
the opposite of why you are writing your book I'm something you will never
understand looks like it's just you and me left now we met before haven't
we yes yes we have I'm glad you remember I know you didn't ask for any
of this I wish we could have met again under different circumstances this is
the guy from the the guy that the warden you know
okay this guy what's his name what's his fucking name Andy no and not not
Andy Griffith though the guy that was in Andy Griffith that was like the
bumbling warden don knots there it is okay I wish we could have met again
under different circumstances me too galaxy film presents in association
with Don knots that was an actual boomer joke yeah whatever some of you
guys are old enough to know what that is a lot of you are midnight animal
press space to execute a knocked out enemy that didn't do the tutorial hard
tutorial look at this beating it she's upstairs go get her finish the
game on hard stop what stop stop no stop what what stop oh okay come on here
comes the Garfield Garfield what oh that was fun don't have that on some
people were warning me about that before press space for hard mode here
we go okay there okay so we're gonna do let's go here skip the intro chat
just saved you all right here we go I'll get it I gotta beat one level on
hard and I'm allowed to do anything else come on first I can do like the second
level on hard fuck fuck this is hard this is harder than it was before I
think there's more enemies nice okay that was much harder than the other one
I felt like there was like an extra five to ten enemies yeah yeah yeah so
what do I get on hard you can't do it all right you can't do it oh gosh
you can't do it on hard he's not gonna be able to do it on hard not
even hard god god of it what do you mean what oh it's bit press space for hard
mode press okay there we go all right let's go with Tony watch this oh oh
it's not bad no I got stuck on the I had it too that's too bad keep getting
stuck on this really yeah the no gun thing really is kind of giving me a
huge hard time right now I'll try it really it didn't I feel like with
a gun I would probably have done this already oh come on get over here get
over here you're clearly looking at me what the fuck oh my lord really is just
play peekaboo with this guy I don't know what the hell I was thinking I
don't have to prove anything my that's the one that's the one to try
to do it it's I'm having fun rewind and pick a different class it's too
many people far away with guns huh I don't understand how sometimes you
just don't see me and other times you just pinpoint accuracy kill me
instantly so we got one two three so you can pull this guy again I'm gonna go
up top and punch that guy in the face I think I think I'm gonna do that
mmm don't get cocky just get it normally all right got it look at me
right what's that mean that's an a-plus I'll take it a-plus look at
how much better look at much better proved going back to these other levels
all right now let's do hard mode oh I can't not s-plus do it again without
cheating oh didn't you guys see what Sakurai said you can play Smash
Brothers any way you want there's no correct way to play all right I'm
gonna go I'm just gonna take a break grab another water and I'll come back
I'm gonna play some of the community workshop levels I have a bunch of
them already downloaded we'll give him a try be right back I 760 at 50k
6-core processor Nvidia GTX 1080 1080 32 gigs RAM somebody asked him my specs
work stop flexing no I'm somebody just asked and I figured I would come back
and say it all right so let's do the community workshop stuff this looks
pretty interesting off let's go to the editor the 1080 for Christmas um no
all right so here we go got here's what we got there's already already one here
that I that I see as you can you know that's here this is just a small
sampling there was a lot of community levels figured out just get some of
these there is a secret level too well we'll try it who could that be
on and compact I think it's one of the characters in the game so we're
gonna go we'll just start here this is called auto angel high score best time
unknown there we go so 30th then 18 my name is Sarah and I'm an Android from
the year 20 55 in the year 20 2019 in eco-terrorism clan called MEC caused
virus apocalypse leading to the death of 70% of humanity and here I am in
2018 it's time to prevent me see from destroying the world here we go
those outdoor okay already dead I'm already dead got it do I get his gun oh
I own it's alright it's milk it's a military mission I guess I'm gonna
conserve my ammo that's good got the gun in the right room
top here whoo I didn't see him in there did not see all right so somebody said
he didn't get the Garfield one no I didn't pick the Garfield one I did not
choose the Garfield God am I doing Garfield I'm not doing Garfield I had
to skip the Garfield one I got the Ninja Turtles one instead Garfield we
want Garfield well you can't always get what you want for Christmas okay
shit
fuck I was trying to change I'm just not being patient with this one ruining
Christmas how far up is that guy there's a guy with a shotgun over here which I've
gone left I was a bad guy the guy's a gun like is my game crashing no
okay safe safe safe just gotta the guy's a gun over there the door opens the door
opens the door opens whoa this guy's gonna shoot me come on get over here
oh fine the gun and then I take care of that guy over there that's it
right yeah what what the fuck no oh my god no where the hell did he come
from he was all the way down there one fucking guy just sprinting come on get
that guy have the gun right here one two three I know watch out for the guy
that sprints over here sure I can see him I'm seeing that he's gonna get in
there and stab okay didn't see that guy that's that would have been
horrible all right keep going dog dog whoo anybody down no no I could go
down
what does it say yummy wow it's close safe safe safe no dog guy with two
guns apparently I had to okay I have one bullet left and this guy with a gun
I'm going to just go like this save that bullet for okay three people here
is there ammo on this level is that ammo technically good let me just wrap
around here I don't like it's nice
okay check in make sure those there big guy come out don't know I forgot he
wasn't dead oh fucking got him with the door shit shit shit shit shit shit
shit damn it just a little tiny little miniscule itty-bitty mistakes that's
so small you can't see him you need a microscope to see him all right
takes care of that let's go up that's stuck in a door I gotta be careful only
I get three bullets here nobody is there somebody in this room no I just
these two don't fuck it up got it okay that's it no one guy left watch out
for the windows you can see through windows I need ammo this is gonna be
bad I need to go get ammo is that an ammo box I don't know we're about to
find out it is Wow Wow Wow okay Wow Wow staircase again I feel like I
should get ammo okay uh right here what what the hell the
fucking computer
we get guy right here needs to be stabbed and get shot across the way from
you not gonna happen sorry oh I just watched myself die there's
nothing I can do there my god there's the door block melee weapons to my is
that seriously happen what name of God is that jump for that
why no windows there okay one bolt left I think this is another big guy
where is he
maybe not yeah he's right there all right I need to kill this dude right
now then I guess I can hide in here is a weird spot to be now I gotta get
this guy too shit come on look at me I got the Russia Russia get these two and
then call it a day knock out the guy with a gun all right I got two I have
one bullet it has to be on that guy we're going through here actually I
don't know up here this is probably safer I think I can pick this guy off
first there we go that's it no it's not it who's left one guy somewhere
just sit around
oh it's this dude in here the guy that's been crouching all right don't
fuck it up you got to hit the computer first we may have reached the the top
no this I was here before it was
elevator I'm gonna get ammo did I miss something here then I was just up
here well okay they have a window there nobody else let's see if I can
just get through this quick one two no wait for this guy to come around
that should be everybody right boss battle that's far enough asshole well
look who's this you must be that degenerate who's been killing us that's
right and I've come for you really think you know all of this is gonna
play out pretty much go ahead kill me but us NBC will not be divided just
because of my death brothers and sisters will hunt you down and then
the earth will be saved from ungrateful assholes like you nothing
you're wrong the one who's getting hunt down will be you emcee bastard oh yeah
I'm so scared we will see about that got it where's Garfield though we're
good I'm not doing Garfield for slick that's pretty cool that's fun I was
auto angel we'll do that one later s4 should do Garfield this one's called
guest I think you actually play as an alien in this one I ever find her yeah
see I'm an alien oh I'm dead movies over all right we got windows
oh all right okay all right easy now come down here visit head office watch
out for the guy with the glass all right I'm gonna say I'm gonna know
right here nope right here come on come on keep going I can't get you
to do that what's left nobody else one more guy through here through here
wait till he comes up this is cool it's cool being a little alien lobster
thing I got it put your eggs in them right click on them what is right
clicking do this one's tough so I'm gonna go down here and then watch out
watch it watch it they got a shot on me from a lot of angles the guy
with the pistols gotta go to up top one down below that guy's a gun
right click hold on I let me get to the beginning of the next area because I'm
almost done and this is kind of tricky see me through the window and come
after me all right anybody else over here and nobody in this window can't
tell oh it's just this guy that's it for that line of sight this guy wait
hold on easy somebody might have been line of sight this shouldn't be too
bad debate him out last guy come on over here I guess I could wrap around
the other side good night that's what I actually yeah floor cleared all right
now I'm gonna right click I'll right click on the next person I didn't do
it right click my scorpion no I'm an alien a lot of guys with guns up
there so bait him down here like this what how did you not how are you
not seeing me get a better look that was gun hey look at me hey look
at me more okay I gotta get that guy in the front first you just wait that's
not right click that space okay looks like melee melee melee I have the gun
in here easy now okay watch out whoa this glass this glass okay stupid
idiot I just took what cartoon character that is turned into it's a
stupid idiot I didn't see I didn't think it shoot over the computers I
oh I go down here that happens I gotta clear these guys out first I thought I
had it that first time too stupid no I got to greedy stop getting greedy and
just do it just do it oh my lord I can't I got I'm trying to do it too
fast so got a gun coming over right now another group and then I should be
able to go get the guy over there should is the real question okay
that's it guy in the middle right here hello almost died that was real close
okay no more here comes I'm okay seeing when they see me through there now I
gotta wrap around one guy in there these guys to see I gotta use this
cover how much can they see really really you don't see me you sure see
me look over here oh fuck in Russian I guess it's that's it it's just him made
him out come on maybe not I'm kind of afraid to go over here though okay
nevermind right click on a corpse Oh right click doesn't do anything right
click does not do anything I can assure you events now that's funny
whoa I was in the van I really was in the vent okay hello I'd like to
right click on the down fat guy the next time somebody says the word right
click I'm gonna lose it whoa okay that was weird weird door that door really
threw me off I really I like this level though this level is actually
really really fun the other one was good too I like being the alien I got
a bait weird door oh fuck I thought I checked down there I did it was
this honey down there but I didn't see where was that guy this thing is it this
person here windows guy with a gun down there okay I got another opening here I
gotta pull you that leaves one two they can I that's gonna be fine let's
go in there and click click click click all right let's go actually can
pull them in through here that works took a shot this guy is gonna see
me and try to shoot me and then he's gonna freak out run after me
we go one two three go no okay anybody else that's it just this last guy
another floor going good fat guy fat guy a guy with a gun another guy with a
gun pistol knife I'm gonna flow right now you I'm in a flow right now
whatever that was and I started talking and it fucking ruined everything
fuck did you come from what just don't make any sense
oh they're all it's a giant patrol really so I'm going to get the fuck
control what any more patrols is that's it okay now I should be able to get
this clean or so I thought all right guy with a pistol come on over fuck
with my float holy fuck there's a patrol oh god oh god he gets you
through the wall oh boy okay it's freaking me out
wait wait I didn't think he had a gun I think it's just a patrol and that's
it now there's one guy up there there's a window in here so I'm gonna hide
over there try to get the gun fun it's true it's too risky too risky I
told you it's too fucking risky stupid I thought I was trying to do
oh stupid why I was trying to come on oh I'm so angry right now what the
hell fucking door that the door fucking ruins everything every time every time
delete all doors from the game I want to put a mask on this removes doors space
please what in the name of God you come here they come all right I can't
I'm not gonna fucking ruin this again just let them go around I'm gonna
get up there doesn't have to get a much better position I want to get
together you know I'm saying I'll get him there let me get the rest of
these guys over here only one dude here
they have a gun they're making their they making the run around here all
right one guy up and then I got to get down here and kill the first guy make
it so I'll meet you down there is the ambush what is he I'm supposed to
be an alien it will be alien I got to kill a guy with the gun first and
then I'm just gonna run here we go no more talking just action another
floor it was long all right event right click on a down fat guy that was fun
that was very fun let's go guest this next one is called
moonlight s for Garfield maybe I'll get Garfield at the very end these are fun
that I want a whole alien video game moonlight okay well okay the guys get a
gun oh okay die please whoo look at that turn around I still left I just
gave him a gun what just happened why did they get more bullets I think I
got everybody listen that guy begun yep he did who dog that guy begun to
okay this is gonna turn me let's go up here
I'm gonna go left yeah
okay right yeah okay
hey Peter I'm gonna need you to come in on Sunday I fucking ruined everything I
don't know what to do I don't know what to do who I'm just running away
I heard it I'm so fucking mad right now it's
unbelievable to me all angry I am gone please I thought I was dead you were
so wrong that guy is gonna cause problems for me holy fuck okay get him
now oh shit all right anybody any of the dogs just the two guys here watch
up the glass a lot of glass over there and he can shoot through it that's not
glass right no all right just this one guy another guy over here more people
in here what serious am I missing something here guys who am I missing
that guy right there the cigarette guy who's left what
I just blinked I hard blinked like six times okay right there that was pretty
challenging those one oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy lots of windows I
think I have to go down Wow Lee Wow Lee Wow Lee Wowie shit come on I'm
saying Wow Lee by the way Wow Lee this is gonna be tricky this one's gonna be
tricky I didn't yeah can't fucking believe it come on really take care of
that guy right now
like a one bullet kind of bush guys are gone it's gonna attract people
though you gotta be careful I'm it there might be a dog in this level
okay got the big guy okay one guy up there I think it's safe to stand here
it is oh shit oh I gotta be quick about this one oh watch it watch it
yep asshole don't think so
it's just the left side it's left everything else cleared out there are
a lot of people here just blind firing thank God that guy would have
just fucking destroyed me I need another gun whoops now I definitely need
another gun
better than that
I'll get his gun better okay I can snipe that guy from here as long as I
know where the hell he is I know I can shit what the fuck oh come on the
perfect fucking angle what was that angle my god you gotta be kidding me
that sucks I was being so careful too and just he went through fucking
windows
back my machine gun I want a machine gun I think I threw too far I hit this guy
from here oh I of course I can't do that but they can the enemies have a
beeline straight sniper rifle through every window but mine's I can't shoot
inaccurate I did inaccurate oh god you gotta be kidding me it's just so huge
and there's so many windows it's sloppy now
that would I just kill what the fuck is happening well where those bullets
nowhere I had a didn't it said I hit somebody didn't go over there fucking
stupid door all right you saw you just watched that happen twice that last
one why did not hit it's gonna hit the door all entryways and all doors and
windows just get rid of him he's coming where he's not gonna come this
way all right well I kind of need a gun you're kind of right here
at least now I can shoot this guy you're up there well watch out for this
guy okay place all right I'm in a decent position just don't blow it not being
able to see oh my god I can't talk I don't know who you are
I'm missing oh in there
put random okay that the guy with the chainsaw that's it right yeah I
need it man after this I gotta see why this person calling me I'm gonna have
to take a second after this level here one guy with the chainsaw and then
that's it this guy the cigarette don't get
fucking baited here let's go throw this at him here we go all right I
didn't blow it all right hold on give me one second let me just make
sure there's nothing important that I have to take a look at here give me
one second all right we're good as I do have the studio so I just want to make
sure it wasn't somebody from the studio trying to contact me about
something so we're good it was Hollywood mr. Hollywood that's for
the Christmas Eve stream I'm gonna be in a big space because I need to
have the space because wouldn't you like to know have to shoot in the guy
like three or four times they should just die there are a couple other
things that I'm doing on that stream that really really stupid requires the
space dog all right this is not a huge place is that guy a melee guy I
can't tell I don't know is he might as well just pick up a melee and I'm
so paranoid about the one fucking guy down here being melee is he just
go look I'm just gonna look it's like what the hell no he just not he's got
like red eyes or something what the hell was that for
speaking of the witch
where the hell he blocked every shot he blocked every shot well nice job
I'm gonna have to take the shotgun what do we got hmm dog pistol right here
though let's get rid of the dog dogs are hard to deal with then here it's a
silencer what the fuck happened how did he shoot that wrong I don't know I
don't have any okay what I don't get it oh he's through there of all the
fucking places just this guy there's no windows there right there's nobody
else in the room no just you okay I got stuck didn't they just do this
holy shit okay well fuck have a melee weapon on any more of those guys
yep one is one of those guys in the bottom right and a fat guy so I'm
gonna go let's go to the top right we'll wrap around at the bottom nobody's
gonna walk up there a cigarette guys don't for that wait till he does it
again got it gun on the table we're gonna go
kick shoot you are here oh no no no no no no no no no no no that's not a
like fucking come on no what oh my god give me a break and the guys duck into
oh lord what happened there pain in the ass time and go out there
all right where is he I need a melee weapon just take one with me
first really locked on and everything but remember he can shoot me in any
angle no matter what the angle is it doesn't matter they will always hit you
they don't have like a spread it's just dead
is that a melee guy like I don't think so all right still going
this super shotgun
elevator
silence I mean I had to be silent there there's no way I'm gonna well that's
not gonna work wasn't mainly weapon okay right here the knife that leaves
with me that money up there and that's it I think I see a window and then your
friend over here got it that was tricky that was very fun though very tricky
but very fun dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot that's not the car that's
not my car you sure this is not my car what it's where you came in I have
I mean you think I remember that I can't write it is this level is like 25
minutes I don't remember what happened it's not it right this is the
hardest part of the game is like just trying to find the car there's like
six levels here why I guess I'm gonna go up the stairs should I be
going down the stairs we're going the elevator and then down the stairs
why does it keep wanting me to do that and this is down it's hard to
even tell which one is up and down I'm all the way up now this could
be either one this could be up or down I love tongue twisters north side of the
bottom floor is this does the elevator take me to the bottom floor
because this is the top floor now I have absolutely no idea where I am all
right found it I accidentally just found it that was fun so that takes
us to this is patrol pain train and then teenage let's do teenage
mutant ninja turtles okay roll dodge killing punch chainsaw and guns
for two machine guns roll I don't want to do the roll dodge uh how about two
machine guns two machine guns what it's actually a ninja turtle this is
awesome you have to make sprites for this this is cool
whoo that one felt good that felt good okay the pizza box is it oh
this isn't so or this is cool I only have 36 shots left ooh got me
okay there I wasted so many bullets on that so that this editor seems pretty
elaborate oh I don't think I can I need a gun all right well now I know he's
there oh I was just fun to do you know I don't care if I lost that's fun
to do I gotta forget this is the nunchuck how many people up here one
two I'll get you to come down yep you as well thank you this guy's a
gun he didn't see me really holy fuck what was that oh god damn it was one
of the okay it was one of the melee guys the dog killing me I gotta shoot
that bad guy missed missed missed I got it I don't care there's like fun
dude you know I don't even care up here how do I do this with you I
need to go the other way that guy's a shotgun you don't want to go over
there but I'll go now one two three oh really oh fuck me oh fuck me fuck me
fuck me fuck me fuck didn't hit anybody nobody got hit by that nobody
did no one oh and I'm dead this one's giving me so much trouble let's go
around this way dumb dog do you see that like World of Warcraft NPC ship
you just like change direction six times in not even a second yeah the
shotgun I'm gonna pull everybody right no I give it for the last guy the last
guy's the one that's a problem I need a melee weapon I think the shotgun I
don't ever seen one of those enemies before oh no thank God is it a melee
is it melee do I have to melee this guy yes I do I do that's it all
right keep going the hell is this bull shit he dodged did you see that dodge did you see
that inhuman dodge that wasn't even human and I know it was a dog but
still oh my lord watch out for the dogs what did you hear where'd he go
where's the dog fuck it that was tough now okay I gotta go I'm going the
other way I think yeah I'm gonna wrap around this way I'm gonna get
myself destroyed dog that's number one reason why what's he got back here
oops I knocked over your octopus I'm sorry what this I'll take the
shotgun that sounds good nobody up and nobody down one here that was almost
really bad it's not an octopus well it looked like one we should Michael
Angela's fucking dead who are you wait are you holy shit I didn't know you
actually exist why are you acting weird look you don't need to hurt me or
anything just go please leave me alone secret that was shredder that was cool
I like I like the TMNT gimmick it was good good job that was Socrates yeah
he sucks anyway don't worry whatever I don't know okay I'm just so I'm not
focused on the direction I'm going I'm focused on the enemies and it's a lot of
mental work why can't it just be an arrow pointing where you need to go it's
all just gray arrows I don't remember where the fuck I came in I have
absolutely no idea I don't remember any of this get me out of here there's
the exit oh my fucking god it was this that was the car that was good
all right we'll do we'll do compact here it comes
Cherub a 985 that's just me wow that's actually really really cool I I'm dead
you should that's a lot of people who are I gotta shoot him that takes so
long to do that all right what we got I can't tell what's down there but
there's a lot of there's only one guy with a gun no these is a safe
just bait him out what's in there okay empty empty empty another big guy so
I gotta be aware of that I gotta kill this dude first and then take care of
the big guy is that a beer that's awesome
whoa okay floor clear that's great what's up here a couple of movies did
you make this in two days I'm not sure if they're watching or not but
that's that's pretty awesome I gotta stay behind here all right
that's clear oh don't get caught shit I'm so paranoid about that guy whoo close
all right is they can shoot through that hold on nobody there one guy
right there he's got a melee weapon you got to be kidding me that's so
awesome I can't fucking believe glue man is in there that's so that's
ridiculous that's amazing well done am I gonna go kill glue man what about
through here is guy with a gun oh boy I gotta pull you you gotta get over here
all right floor cleared I can't kill holy shit no no that's it all this is
alternate universe this is not real there's more here okay what's up here
oh my god this is too much is that auto no I'm not gonna say that any
windows only a few that what who's that I can't tell from here who is that that's
Santa Wow that's so cool all right I'm going in here I'm gonna look at other
stuff I wanted to look at this level whoa because Santa had a chainsaw in the
rumble attention to detail is wonderful comes another group oops ooh did I get
him no I get him no I think that's good there's one more dog just gonna see me
if I walk over here I'll be ready for the dog dog incoming dog gone oh wow no
way thought I got that way before he did okay I'm going too fast all right
he's taking care of one more patrol coming down he's getting impatient I
know that should be enough of that I can actually walk over here now I'm
not sure I want to they're gonna come oh fuck there's another dog oh fuck all
right where you go it's the disco diaper lying down still there and I
get Santa from here oh shit what is Santa Santa has chainsaw right all
right come on Santa let's go you and me no you Santa's gone couple of
beers yes up here is this one dude and then the two beers and that should
bring me to I gotta get it easy hits here got it who oh this one person
remains wait glass no but you're trying to fool me with the glass got
it that was compact that was the was great I know how to get out of this
hardest part of the level that was fantastic thank you for that B plus that
was a lot of work that went in a lot of work went into all these excellent job
so that leaves us with patrol and pain train as we do patrol oh don't worry
I'll get Garfield we'll do Garfield before I turn the stream off Garfield
will be the last one that I attempt so let's do patrol by plank all
right so that's me sniper rifle I can't shoot I can't just rewind I can't rewind
no rewinds are allowed actually actual game mechanic all right let's try a
different approach here give me an open door really whoa what who saw me what
the hell was that this guy shot me through there I have no idea who's
shooting me who's shooting me what is he standing up is it it's a turret bush
it's not this guy is it is it this guy I don't know maybe we'll find him
later I like the sniping aspect of it oh I got that thought that was a wall
so I can snipe you from here okay it leaves who that guy right there what
the hell is oh can I even kill these guys I think these guys and I think these
guys are turrets I think that's that that's actually by design I think I'm
pretty sure maybe I can melee the turrets because if I go like this oh
boy he's just not turning well wouldn't I be able to shoot him then
like he's no that those guys are definitely supposed to stay alive so I
can't go this way I gotta go the other way once I take out the this
big dude once the big dude is dead what about it this way I guess I can wrap
around you know I can't I'm supposed to get in there this guy shoots through
here I gotta get a good spot to shoot this guy hmm I'm the let's see all
right now I wonder if I can just walk up here and then down huh whoa
melee melee melee melee well I have to get close enough before I can do
that gonna take these guys out again let's try it again okay I'm gonna try
doing that again I have to shoot this dude now get in here but um I can't
stand here you can shoot through the door I feel like you shot through the
door last time no it was somebody else oh fuck man I think I can so who
is who is this which I don't know guys shooting me because this guy
dies where's the other big guy he's right there so I'm gonna I'm gonna have
to snipe through this hole I feel like I kind of have to how do I line that
up is he gonna shoot me if I go like that through there maybe but I think
that's gonna be hard to get over there I think I can do it from like
a better angle I don't think so I'm gonna have to run in and shoot
through here right like this what the fuck who the hell are why are you
standing whoa what that just scraped my brain what the hell I actually all
right so fuck just come out here so I can figure this out again what in the
name of God all right so they have to melee that guy and they they're not
just turrets they're not turrets so I I didn't even shoot that guy all
right here we go again so now maybe I should just shoot the wall and bait
this guy okay that changes things I just just shoot him just shoot the fucking
guy well the reason I thought it was a
turret is because they were shooting backwards and they weren't doing any
animations so I mean what am I supposed to think all right let's take
a look I don't there's any way I can get shot in here it's gonna pick
this guy off fucking dumb door really you give me a break so then fuck it just
do this why would I ever even do this just attack them they're not like
turrets to just go like this and then maybe I can go in that room now
someone snuck up on me there all right then you're here I think
somebody's coming out here I can't get off that okay so now I'm safe to go
up here and into this room because this guy's not here anymore so let me
see what's available up here hmm I guess I could just pull them but this
takes a while to switch back I gotta be careful okay anybody have line of sight
no but this guy is he stand I don't is that guy standing no not anymore okay
much left one guy no more than one guy I'll wait for you and leaves just
to you sorry well okay let's try this way whoa all right I think I have to pull
you first the right idea really you saw me through here there's one more
guy over there but see if I can kill this dude right now hmm nowhere I'm
gonna go this way really it sucks there a guy with melee that was down
there no god what the fuck I'm trying to right-click okay gotta get the fat
guy here just bait these guys I can kill them what killed me what did I
shot this guy down here don't fuck yourself guy oh my god I thought I hit
a knife really what is what are you talking about what the fuck come on oh
boy let's kill me I have to wait till he stands but I can't see when he
stands I can't move give me a break happens every fucking time let's try
this again so one of these guys has a gun I got a slow down I don't have
any ammo oh no that's not good is there ammo down here somewhere is
everybody left down there am I gonna shot oh god please tell me no it was
coming up here good thing I have ammo right next to me that makes this a lot
easier so where's the last guy in there pig or something oh holy shit that
good thing I didn't move oh my god that's so lucky that I didn't move I
need to get to a good spot because this guy what the hell you gotta be
tethered right like that threw me off so bad why did he tether at the door he
like ran right to the edge of the door and then just instant turned around
went back well now I have to go back down here wasn't there somebody else
over this guy right here I'm gonna kill this guy first because oh fuck not
this time just go step in the fucking head it's not it who's left
what's happening oh this one guy right here give me ammo oh dear oh dear I go
this way I can't go that way hmm you're gonna have line of sight on me
here isn't it it's so that's so weird to do trying to like keep it on him
across so far fuck is he no he's never gone good okay let's see that
guy all the way at the end there that would that would have killed me I need
ammo shit shit can he shoot over here this is tense all right one melee guy
down there I have to shoot this guy I have to stick my head over this way
and see if I can bait him to stand up which I did and I didn't shoot him
though come on am I not waiting long enough apparently not all right that
guy take care of this guy right now but anybody have line of sight they
don't so let's see if I can't kill this guy oh my god what was I doing oh
fucking tried to oh my god I fucking didn't run at him I was too busy
thinking of them whatever oh now I'm just rushing god damn it for some
reason I don't know why my brain right there I just like that guy was
a melee cuz like I said oh melee that's a melee guy kill this guy
right now and also after you shoot it takes a full almost two seconds before I
can switch back to the knife so and I'm not compensating for that all right
where the hell am I gonna shoot here I gotta shoot him what the fuck why did
he not chase after me why is it always the guy like down here this guy
doesn't want to chase me what the guy up top does what the heck are you
talking about in trouble here I need to get that off I'm gonna worry about this
guy and I may have just screwed myself quickly turns around and then I'm just
gonna run over and get it and then run away let's take care of him all
right back away where before two guys up there the melee guy down here I
gotta get rid of you so let's do that now let's try to make this
happen did I already get no make sure I get this dude all right come on now
I mean I guess I could rush but I'm actually gonna how many bullets do I
have one bullet not good let me try to shoot am I gonna hit anything with
this okay I'm gonna go for it I'm gonna try to take I wonder if it's gonna
run anything I'm so fucking dumb all right that's it what that's an
interesting spawn can't go over there I have to run I have to run it and
stab this guy get oh boy this is gonna be tricky okay huh oh I thought it was
this guy thought it was a cube I mean save this bullet pig guy okay he's
done there is one more guy with a gun that's in a current patrol all right
what do you got let's see it don't have anybody else here oh shit okay am
I safe right here they can't shoot through these I don't think leads me
to here when I shoot this this guy's gonna come running fuck I have to hit
this that's a weird angle though I'm gonna wait till they turn around okay
I got it nobody else down there there's a pig down there can I shoot
through that we're about to find out yep oh fuck oh I didn't think you'd
run through it oh come on I didn't think you could like run through that
for some reason I thought it was a wall oh whatever I'm so long so much
patience I had it too that sucks where's this other guy same deal I'm
gonna go the other the same way get them both no all right same deal I'm
gonna need ammo I think this ammo right there are you there's the ammo
box up here all right come on who else all right there's one sniper guy
there and there's one melee guy here I need to I need to do you see what just
happened there holy shit I just switched too fast one last guy I don't want him
to shoot me though he's gonna get line of sight on him and he's gonna
kill me there's a wall I have to shoot him from here this is a wall
there's another area holy fuck go why did I want to go here oh boy no
what I think I did it oh that one was fucking hard the difficulty wasn't in oh
how many enemies there were it's just placement needing to stand in the
right places I'll take a C- on that one all right this is the last one
this one's called pain train and then we're gonna play Garfield I'm gonna
play like just the first like we'll see how far I get in Garfield it's
called pain train now what do I get I guess we just go punch well see how I
tried to avoid those cuz I thought they were walls fun fact why did this guy
not shoot take his gun to everybody hide in the trash who did I hit that I
just shot the pizza ooh well that wasn't good okay we're good more boy
okay we're just we're just going through who's that's it just gonna smash
him in the head nothing over here good thing I that was in the right time
because I would not have done that what's left a couple of guns is for
cleared fast moving fast let's go oh boy shit I gotta hit that guy forget
about that no fuck ah I got caught up I stand there
melee this is a silence gun whoa fuck whoa no I can't punch him oh shit okay
damn it I screwed that up I just how did I miss every shot I have to hit
that guy with a melee weapon so let's go ahead and bring a melee weapon
down here what do you say is that the only guy that has that problem there
dog sorry that dog like just blew up my blood pressure this is a weird room
oh somebody's still alive didn't say floor cleared he doesn't usually say
that area clear okay leave area up I did all right I did but does this
count the door was the last enemy I had to kill the door I think that's
it I have to go back through the train what can I do another boy waste me what
wait what are you talking about where am I supposed to go the bus stop so
anything I need to go here all right it's the sofa bus stop a see I got a
hundred and four thousand hundred ninety two thousand I went over the
max score how is that all like an a all right it's time to show what's
time to do Garfield and then I'm gonna I gotta take a break from this
game in fact that's pretty much the end right all right I beat it so let me go
get the Garfield shouldn't take me more than a minute or two here okay
workshop so if you're us what we're doing tomorrow we're gonna do a giant
everybody join atlas if you have it video game night that's the pirate game
the pirate game is there a reason why I can't search the workshop right
browse search the workshop atlas was delayed until Friday really huh
can I search the workshop what happened okay this is it yeah Garfield campaign
all right I've installed it just need to restart the game I can't believe I'm
gonna play the Garfield fucking campaign I think I have to maybe I can
restart let's see I gotta restart the game December 21st I haven't I gotta go
back to the doctor on December 21st mmm I was planning on doing that
tomorrow and then taking Friday off to go to the doctor again and then well
that kind of changes things open this yeah and they pardon me if I sound a
little tired today I was up at about four o'clock in the morning because
every time that I have blood taken from my body I just every time I have like
blood work done especially when it's like six or seven full vials I just
pass out I get so tired so if I sound a little tired I apologize but it's
time for Garfield is Garfield not here Garfield there it is okay Garfield
what the fuck I don't which one do I want lasagna lasagna or lasagna is
lasagna or it and lasagna fuck I don't know which one of these to do I don't
know why I'm doing this in the first place what is the is this gonna okay
what is lasagna skip the intro is it intro what is the intro no I guess
stuffing your face as usual you gotta have a gonna have a good meal
Garfield you fat cat you're so big and fat why are you so fat I eat John
it's my most relatable character trait you're eating us out of house and home
Garfield look at all these grocery bills I don't have money for this I'm
in the mood for some lasagna I'm taking your car John I hate this all
right I love this at the same time though I hate oh boy they got guns
they got guns the Garfield these are guns I'm not sure Garfield can use a
gun nothing about this is nothing feels right about this I need mailing no John
okay got a gun two guys one at the door level clear go to car at least I
got an s-rank all right let's go hey John I got me some lasagna put it in
the oven will you I'm gonna take a nap John do you hear me can you
understand what I'm saying it's over Garfield it's all over I've got no
money left on my account were officially broke Garfield you finally
did it you fat cat you ate us into poverty oh boy John look like the time
has come for you to get a job don't you dare put this on me you greedy
lazy piece of cat shit your insatiable appetite caused this you fat cat sure
blame the cat on your financial distress now put my fucking lasagna in
the oven John no Garfield it's over never again will you have control over
my life you despicable trash you're out of here you're out goodbye Garfield I'm
throwing you out what what just happened what what what the fuck this is what
this went in a completely different direction dear Garfield if you're
reading this it means I'm my mostly what oh way to rub you might be
utterly worthless but there's still not your survival now lives in the
hands of your most failure your firstborn son what the fuck is happening
my son I have a son yes you're a father Garfield 25 years I've kept his
existence I'm still getting over what just happened it's fucking with me it
is time for you to sort that mess out all by yourself his name is Tony
he lives at the 61st Street ten minutes or at least he did the last
time I heard of him I loved you Garfield what happened to us okay this is I don't
like this perhaps we will see again just Jesus is Lord Almighty I actually have
an illegitimate son oh fuck I need to sit down I fucking hate Monday this
is supposed to be Garfield thank God I don't have a job that'd make it
even worse well dude Tony you're laying on my piss rag oh shit no this
is so sorry I didn't realize it's okay I can just pee my pants you got mail
yeah nice is that play Garfield it'll be fun no it's a letter okay from who I
wonder I must get to the bottom of this all right oh my god oh that's
great spit it out who is Kaiser Jose all right can I just play the game
play Garfield play the Garfield one can you tell me what it says I can't read
sure things citizen let's see hello Tony my name is Garfield we need to
meet I recently found out something about you and me and I don't know
what I should I say let's just meet up okay well what does it say some
guy named Garfield is requesting a meetup last house on the left bring
lasagna lasagna why that's my favorite food how odd should I go
detective yes okay Tony if you're going out bring me more lipstick okay
okay I'm kind of lost right now I like the song this is a lot of fat
guys sit a guy with a gun how am I gonna get rid of this guy to pull
them out okay what is that what is going on right now well that guy's a
gun nothing just says Florida Oh guns whoa whoa Wow Odie really careful
because that guy will I got a gun no knife okay hello Tony I'm Garfield I'm
your father dad you're a fucking house cat well I've got to admit I'm at a
loss of words pops sorry for using the phrase fucking house cat earlier it
made me sound like I'm disappointed or something but it's just it's okay
Tony I understand I too was pretty shocked at first when I learned I had a
son I have no memory of your mother don't recall ever having sex with a
human must be due to that stroke I had yeah I never met her I was raised
by stray cats and and now those I'm not going to read this I think it's
and how about the stray cats they taught me how to fight and hunt we
got along quite well and how I see they were my channel to my feline roots my
father is a cat it all makes sense I'm glad you feel that way what do you do
for a living nothing I mostly spend my day sleeping and sometimes I punch
them dudes with my friends you truly are your father's son proud of that
well no one's ever been proud of me before you really mean that since a
soul mate in you Tony can I be your dad you've always been my dad
Garfield neat happy days are ahead for both of us we're gonna do much better
than me and John who's John oh my owner you had an owner
duh how do you think a house cat is supposed to maintain itself John's old
news now oh god you mean ah it's fine he was an ass oh what made him
ah oh god I can't let's go have some father son time teach me how to
ride a bike no I'm a goddamn cat you got a car what do you need a bike for well
well I guess it's just I think it'd be a useful skill riding a bike yeah okay
we'll do something else okay something more fun let's go what did you just
walk into I haven't I'm not sure yet I haven't figured it out you haven't
moved an inch while I was gone and seeing this crap entertainment for cats
I wouldn't do that for a million lasagnas you know we could do
something together for a change like what it's raining it's been raining for
three days it's a perfect weather to sit indoors relax and just watch dumb
VHS tapes don't think of something come on pops I want to get to know you
better there ain't much to know I eat and sleep and screw around that's
about it no one is that one-dimensional come on let's go and
just drive around talk shit is that the stolen fire that's not good here
meow would you just say to me punk hey nice you can talk maybe imagine it's
kind of hard to tell are you hi good for you now excuse me I've got to go
out in the rain with my son ha son of Garfield boy that Jim Davis never
runs out of ideas they're talking about you on the streets what are they
saying you are a fat cat and wonder why you are so fat apparently they're
quoting some video or something I don't know don't care how's Orson I have no
idea what you're talking about hey we were supposed to go get going if I can
make a recommendation you should check out that new perfume shop oh the
orders they sell okay sounds like a plan the quicker we go the quicker we
can get back thanks mister godspeed fat cat they seen okay like go after
the bad guys Garfield got me there's three more levels after this one there's
an entire fucked up Garfield campaign now I need a gun here I gotta go right
left shit is this fan made yes so hotline Miami to introduced a level
editor which allows anybody to make a full campaign oh I need a melee oh
dear oh I didn't think I got him I'm gonna switch it oh man I'm like my
gamer fatigue is exponentially growing and now give me the gun whoa I need some
gamer juice I'll be okay hello are you gonna hello what the hell really
fine I'll just throw a knife at your head all right that is melee that
guy's got a gun that's not melee so let's pull you itchy nose I gotta shoot
in here oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck empty empty okay really this is stuck in the
door all right this guy's not melee some
that guy down there is though so I need that's it it is one last guy
where's the last guy there's a Shrek campaign there's a lot I think there's a
lot of content here there's a lot of community made stuff what was I coming
back here for actually tag him out tag team whoo that's also a gun back to
the car okay no I'm not gonna do this Shrek campaign I don't know if I'll
barely make it through this one you done with that sig are you smoking just
about we're going back home it was great to finally meet my father after
living without him for 25 years I had two big expectations about how life
would turn out to be after that yeah well I admit I'm still kind of
amused about this whole father thing but I'm trying my best
okay hit what was your presence would help me shape up but instead we
continue to sit on our asses and do nothing but isn't that what
everybody wishes they could do have no responsibilities do what they wish and
be their own pastor not me I hate Mondays me too because I'm jealous of
people who get to go to work just another day it's okay that's what
parents are for you want to take a sniff of this perfume I got what it's
a real killer I haven't smelled anything like this before what this is
oh it's drugs I said no okay take it easy it's just a perfume I'm getting
soaked read it all I'm so overstimulated already what the fuck is going on who
the fuck was that what's going on it was a suit what he was one of them it
was a suit spying on me looking from the shadows how the fuck did he get
here oh I'm gonna get him dad calm down maybe you're just seeing things I'm
not there was a suit in our house quickly after before he gets away I see
you there through the window I'm gonna teach not to mess with the
motherfucking Garfield dad Garfield wait ah shit god damn it not like
oh my goodness oops I get stuck two there I can go three come on out
oh I almost had a gun so it's gonna be tough I'm gonna throw something at you
I can't really really really we want lasagna well you're getting it right
now aren't you isn't this what you wanted didn't see you come on oh what
the hell I just got baited so hard trying to go too fast I can't go out
there and kill him you gotta come here damn it man I can't walk out there if
I walk out there I'm dead I'm gonna go that way and really I'm just trying to
rush too fast I had it really well the first time too this sucks really
come on why don't you know should be the first time all right get down
here then he did come down what feel like I can pull more than just
yeah I'm gonna go down that one guy with the gun is such a pain in the ass
I think I do have to go that way though oh boy oh fucking come on what
where do you come from did you walk all the way over here that was such
bullshit what oh no no oh I thought that's I'm gonna
have to take a break I'm starting to feel the like gamer throw up there's
only so many hours you can play one of these like fast-paced super twitch
spin around and hit everybody don't make any mistakes games where you
actually diarrhea your pants okay whoo I'm so drunk I'm drunk so it's
worse I can't imagine playing this game drunk all right I don't think I
would get out of the first two room look clear looks like we're going over
this way eat that you piece of poop it's time to calm down I can't believe
this shit how'd this happen I mean how long have these suits been I guess
I have no idea but you should try to relax here smell my perfume it'll
soothe your nerves dammit look around you something sinister is going
on I want to get to the bottom of this why do you keep offering me that
bloody perfume all the time just this once please that I promise it'll help
you concentrate it what is going on why does he want to do this so bad
fine hand it over oh it stings Jesus oh I'm sorry dad oh fuck I can't see
god damn it I told my nose I wouldn't take this shit ah I see the
rings of Saturn what is happening to Garfield what the fuck is happening I'm
so I don't have more to say about this this wasn't five and a half hours into
this game I'm puking what the fuck's going on shouldn't you ask what is
going on what he he he John our buckle I just did how are you alive or did
I Garfield I beg to differ in fact I'm feeling better than ever seeing
you in that cage this was all just theater it wasn't it you didn't you
didn't Tony isn't my son oh he is your son all right and without him I wouldn't
be sitting here getting my revenge I'm sorry dad he made me do it I had no
choice you could have said no fuck I guess I could have and you John what
could you possibly seek revenge for for years of torment god damn it I
was your owner Garfield but you always treated me like shit you're the most
ego egotistic self-centered asshole I faked by death and set you to fire your
long-lost son Tony so you could see what it feels like to take care of a
worthless cat like you huh so you thought instead we end up bonding quite
well yeah kind of also I'm a grown-ass man I don't need my daddy
looking after me then I decided I should just get rid of you tell me
Garfield who was Tony's mother hell if I know well I do it was Liz you mean that
vet you were always hitting on you know that damn well we've been on her
clinic a million times and every time you struck out imagine the anger that
boiled inside me two weeks ago when I found out you had been sleeping
together Liz tried to hide your son from me by letting the marry up with
the exposition what's your endgame John me and my catnip society will turn you
into lasagna and serve to the poor how delightfully ironic is that bastard so
you are gonna kill me huh just like Odie already had to be put down
because you kept kicking him off the table don't try to put that on me
Garfield nobody likes you dad my revenge will be complete thank you for
all the years not put him to sleep no what the oh fuck they throw me into an
incinerator like in the Bond film help somebody you are not Garfield just
leave the incinerator the hatch is open oh all right I'm trusting you
rubber chicken person don't let me down the stones of happenings tell your
future and what do they say an old friend I swear to God if Heathcliff is
in this fucking game dr. Liz will see you now all we have tapes of
magazines put it in this tube what wait hold on you got something in your
eye hey don't worry about it it's a giant maze no way that that's not
happening on this stream I'll tell you right now absolutely not
hi Odie woof woof thanks you too hey Horton how are you doing I've seen
better days yeah ditto as much as you'd love to lay down on your ass and
just forget but there's still something that needs to be done I know
get going then go over there turn left where you see dark light on the
right oh oh the door is open oh oh this is lasagna las on fuck
who's left down I mean melee pull him that's it for clear go go go go fuck
we may lay but I need to get rid of weapons up here well for that one
outside that was brilliant
keep going Garfield kill the cat fuck I need a gun yet okay I gotta get in that
bathroom
shit is it bullets one bullet wait I gotta get rid of this guy
there's that bad guy there he is he's a melee weapon this guy has a gun though
and a knife right here let's see if I can I pick it up can I pick the knife up
no don't even try it just get a minute anybody has a melee weapon down
here oh wow I missed this is a mod yeah this is the Garfield the Garfield
campaign on the steam workshop
the red arrow is for here wasn't crazy there's an elevator where's the
elevator I mean clearly the red arrow was telling me to go that way but saw
an elevator oh okay I'm just following the red arrows just following the red
arrows I was following the red arrows come on that's not my fault come on
melee come here come here come here there is I need a hard John Garfield
Garfield think about what you're doing remember all the good times we
like like the time I drank ha ha ha all the wacky times remember those yeah I do
so thanks for all the years that's it hey Garfield oh hi Tony they're showing
the fly on TV why am I still have my eyes bucket out of my head
oh that's a good movie grab a cold one son you know they shot an alternate
ending for this oh yeah yeah Veronica has a dream of her baby with
butterfly wings oh that's beautiful especially after all the gruesome things
yeah it's kind of burp well there we go I love the Garfield created by Jim
Davis you notice the continuity error in this campaign by the way 21st as
he's thankful of being unemployed but later he says he's jealous of people
who have jobs that kind of shit happens when you work without notepad
and don't write down your story apparently or is it a continuity or
maybe Tony was just trying to impress his whole friends sadly we
might never know the true background of this mystery nevertheless I hope you
enjoyed and check out my other campaigns a brave man is a man who
dares to look the devil in the face James Garfield
well that was outrageous it was absolutely outrageous I think that's a
great one to go out on well Garfield actually said that all those it's a
actually surprising to see just how high quality and worthy of being in the game
type of content that people are making and I don't think I even scratched the
surface there's a lot to bet you were too cowardly to read half the story
I'm not going to play the Shrek one maybe one day you'll just know I'm
not gonna not playing Shrek you can call me a coward all you want I'm
gonna play the Shrek campaign coward coward coward coward coward I can't
believe John drank dog no I'm not saying it my god no all right no
that's not a coward because I don't want to say I guess if I say that then
I get to be edited in a hundred thousand different ways I don't what a
load of bullshit well time all right that hey good night everybody that's
where we're gonna end thanks for coming out to the stream that's where
we're gonna end see you next time it's just an expression what's saying
I'm going to go jack it I'm concerned for the future of content and when I
press them when I click the button I gotta take a break I do I can't play
this game for more than like six hours it's a great game maybe maybe you'll
see Shrek start the next stream so I don't know what the hell I'm gonna do
tomorrow I have to come up with something because my plan was I was
gonna play Atlas tomorrow but that has been delayed so we'll figure
I have a couple of potential ideas play Shrek all right I will play I will play
this Shrek campaign tomorrow okay but we're not but doing something else
after that somebody just in all capitals called me a liar well then
you're gonna have to tune in tomorrow we got him no you don't I get but I
didn't say how long I was gonna play it for why you make this this
campaign probably took like 30 hours of work to make you know it's not
fucking I'm making my own campaign I'm gonna make my own hotline Miami to
campaign and we're gonna play it it's gonna be terrible but good night
everybody I'll see you tomorrow final thoughts on hotline Miami as a series
there's a great series the first one I enjoyed a little more than the second
ones campaign but the second had way more content and much more to do it
was way harder both very very good games I would highly recommend them
wrong overlay oops well that was embarrassing two has the better music I
mean they're both great I would probably say if the first one's not as
difficult as the second one second one's a lot larger there's a lot more
enemies people are off-screen there's a lot more windows and more doors I like
this new end stream that's right it's just pulling from Shrek and there's
a the two is worth purchasing for all the community content for sure there's
so much you know Shrek and Garfield themed campaigns but with that we are
going to wrap it up we're gonna do the bits and let's actually put on the real
goodbye music what do you say because this is this is a little too upbeat I
think there we go but I'll see you guys tomorrow if you're taking off
we'll figure something out hey German German 258 thanks for the one
dollar help I just escaped from German's basement I'm one of his
many clones he had me make outdated fortnight references for him and it was
horrible thank you uh outdated how could you how could you make an
outdated fortnight reference right now it's like the biggest thing in the
world fortnight is the biggest thing on earth thank you the yellowest for
the free box hotline Miami one half a half worth the buy one and two
worth the buy yes and yeah you say any one and two worth the buy this game
doesn't this game go on sale all the time too doesn't typically get
picked up in some of those sales yeah I absolutely if you're up for a
challenge there's plenty to challenge you in both of these games and they're
just fun anyways so I would say yes thank you the yellowest for the three
dollars Garfield a Monday killer thanks for the one dollar just hopping in to
give a little bit of that Garf love whoo-wah check me out German I'm doing
the Garfield dance of good fortune just for you I'm just word vomiting
right now but then again would a Garfograph be a Garfograph without it
there's anyone to the power you have with a Garfograph Garfographs have
the power to make Jerma say anything Garf wants well as long as there's
nothing legally binding or morally Garf'd up somehow Jerma would you
consider me a mortal cat chaotic neutral I would yes I would consider I
would consider you to be chaotic evil I'm just kidding neutral chaotic
you Garfield doesn't get to be an RPG character okay they never did an
episode or a panel strip where he was playing Dungeons and Dragons pacing of
that read yeah I know what was Garfield's first bit message that's a
great question thank you ginzebo for the four dollars
jolt jolt home men 10 is fat Jill Tom is fat easy you spelling a word
backwards or upside down or something what are you doing thanks for the
four dollars thank you ill himself with the two bucks game is too hard
for streamer that's not true I beat it I beat it with all at least C minuses
that's not too shit metal socks gave the 50 bucks earlier thank you for 50
dollars it's a lot of money and by the way before if anyone caught the
stream a little later make sure that you go to the discord and you check
out the secret Santa suggestions you got to get a suggestion in there over
the next like 16 to 20 ish hours because I really have to get those
packages ordered for Christmas Eve so let's go over it one more time just
like a TL D TL DL too long didn't listen Christmas Eve I'm doing a
stream where I'm giving chat a $500 allowance to buy pretty much or give
suggestions for whatever they want me to buy I'm gonna have somebody else buy
it and wrap it for me so I don't see it and I'm gonna open chat Christmas
presents on Christmas Eve the very very short version of the long story
there so it has to be an Amazon link that channel is not to you know
chat in or anything it needs to be an Amazon link and it has to be prime
a bull that has to be prime shipping otherwise it just will not get here
the mods are gonna pick out they're gonna be funneling them through they're
gonna be seeing them they're gonna be taking ones that they think are
interesting or fun or funny there's no voting isn't it's not like a contest
it's just and obviously if a bunch of people say the same thing it's it's
that's gonna have weight to it right there are there are channel pins
please go to secret Santa suggestions if you're interested and read the
pinned message because it's a little bit to look at it's got to be up to
$50 no more than $50 suggestion you can only suggest three things per
person and there's no guarantee that the thing that you suggest is gonna be
picked but we're gonna have a bunch of random shit to open I remember we
talked about this a few weeks ago oh wouldn't that be funny if chat and the
mods kind of just bought a bunch of stuff on Amazon and I opened it this
is kind of part of that so should be a lot of fun I have no idea what
they're gonna be I'm gonna make sure I don't see it Kim's gonna wrap
them and Kim's going to buy them so we're going to work I'm going to buy
them on my Amazon but Kim's going to do it so I'm not gonna know what they are
this is a really bad idea it could be if there wasn't rules no live animals no
bugs no perishable food no shit no bad stuff they're rules you got to read
them oh what do you mean oh come on oh come on what about a $50 Amazon gift
card no no it's got to be an actual some kind of item so we'll see how how you
guys come up with some stuff should be funny wait what you mean I can't have
you buy piss can you even buy pee on Amazon the number one reason why there
are these rules in place is number one because they have to I have to
get to be shipped here in less than four days and number two I'm gonna be
doing it in the studio so the mods already joked about this before oh
10,000 ladybugs it's like if I open that in this studio oh boy am I gonna be a
lot of fucking trouble like oh yeah sorry uh in the studio that I was
renting out oh I put 10,000 bugs in your studio oh no no no nope no this
is like I'm not it's the same place that I did the green screen scream so
I'm going there again it's gonna be a whole lower deal stop calling it a
studio you mean the the TV and film studio that I'm doing this in we're
talking about yeah it's a studio it's where I filmed the green screen
screen like how you call your room in office all right whatever yeah whatever
what do you want for Christmas well let me tell you I would like if you
guys could possibly and I mean this for real I actually mean this for
real it's not a joke I'm not kidding around I want I want some saltwater
taffy I'm serious that's the number one thing that I want for Christmas so
you know I'll give you a little hint there and I really would like some
saltwater test some good saltwater taffy you said no food taffy is not
perishable no I'm talking about like sending me sandwiches or making me buy
like fucking deli meat or something no the candy is not perishable can't do it
no food no it's candy is not food no food it's your rules but that's what I
want for Christmas so bad get it yourself anyways it should be a lot of
fun I'm looking forward to the things you guys come up with and me
opening them without knowing what they are and it sure there'll be some
interesting things do I like licorice I do not like licorice I do not like it
no sir I don't like it anyways let's move on here let's go to the spas
thanks for the $1 gamer time it was it was a pretty good gamer time
tonight I think extra cheesy thanks to the $1 $500 worth of garden gnomes
incoming no and another thing the mods obviously are not gonna pick out
a bunch of repeats so if you guys want to if you guys want to try to suggest oh
no no everybody just suggest I'm not gonna even say anything but like 60 of
the same item to make it like $150 it's not gonna happen we got to have
some variety you know I mean only I just want candy let's get a Smash
Brothers ultimate so you can play it on stream I already own Smash Brothers
ultimate do not do that I swear to God if Smash Brothers ultimate is
there I'm going I am going to I'm going to immediately donate it so somebody
else can enjoy Smash Brothers you don't like Smash Brothers no no I have I
already own it but anywho thank you to KXZ we got you already but thank you
for the $30 we did do an EU friendly stream today I was up very very early
and I knew I wasn't gonna be awake I'm gonna be probably falling asleep
here in the next three or four hours just because I was up so early around
like four o'clock in the morning so I got up early and I'm gonna be passing
out here soon but thank you so much for the 30 bucks oh it's just joke
glad that um some of the EU crowd can get a reasonable time today hey the
spaz thanks for the four dollars have you ever been to the EU no I would
love to but it's just not something that I've had the time or the
really the resources to do because that's a big commitment it is it's a
long way away you got us you can't just go to Europe for like two days oh yeah
we spent a weekend in London no that's not gonna happen you're gonna
be in there for at least a week or two but it is a large amount of
travel large commitment London in Europe well you know what I mean
though come to the EU I know but like you know what I'm talking about
but happy 30th birthday to you cake see as well you're still here hey the long
egg thanks for the one dollar why do you get your blood removed often are
you okay I have been struggling with an annoying thing for about six months I
don't know what it is and I'm not going just like oh hey this is what
this is the problem I don't know all I know is like I've told you guys
over the last three or four streams I've been trying to eat a different diet
I've been trying to stay away from gluten to see if that helps but I've
been having some weird stomach and back and chest pain for about six
months and that's why I've kind of been at the doctor a lot to try to
figure out what the fuck is going on with my body and why it's doing
this and there's been stay healthy no I'm fine don't worry about me but if
you're wondering why I'll go to the doctor well I can't stream tomorrow I
gotta I gotta go to the doctor I need to eat Flintstones but it's
potentially something as simple as too much bad bacteria and that would be
really really great if it was because that's very easy to fix but
if that's some really just strange medical happenings that really has
nothing to do with my intestines quick send him taffy see I would feel
so much better if I had some taffy no all jokes aside I'll figure it out
don't worry about me I'm fine but I am there I did I have been at the doctor
a few times don't worry about me I'm gonna be just fucking fine eat fish
and garlic and have spinach and vegetables make sure you eat them hey
cloud thanks for the $1 thanks for streaming thanks for watching really
thank you the faux Jacko thanks for the $1 hashtag charity thank you for that
the slimy squash thanks for $5 slimy squash hey Jeremy I've been watching
your video since the beginning and you've always had the ability to help
with my depression and make me feel better without fail I'm at the lowest
point in my life so far and I want to hear what advice you might have
love you and I'm glad I've never you've never stopped making me laugh
it's the same advice that I I say kind of often right that's sometimes you
might feel pretty fucking low right now right but you got to take each day
at a time is slow it doesn't happen overnight it takes a while but as long
as every day or every you know once a week once every few days you're
really trying to either better yourself or try to figure out why it's
not easy and I always feel I always feel for people that you know say this
kind of shit because you know I've been there you guys have heard the stories
before I've felt like fucking shit before you know ten years ago or so
you just got to try you know you're so sweet chairman no I mean I but I
want also to you know have people realize that there isn't just a simple
hope this is how you fix it that's it it's all fucked up that's how you fix
it because everybody's so different you everybody has such different wildly
different personalities viewpoints beliefs things that they like this
they don't like that it's it's hard somebody a problems right different
problems there's a lot of different points you can come from so it's
very very difficult because there's so many ways takes time to get over it
it does but I really do wish you the best hopefully you get it all
figured out much love to you somebody said therapy therapy
helps yeah if it's something you think would help you could get out there
start talking to somebody because you never really want to have it just kind
of sit there and just wallow inside over and over and over again it's
it's not healthy you know it really is better to at least have somebody
that either knows or is a professional and I'm not a professional at all that's
another thing I guess we need to address is I can only tell you the
things that have helped me or the things that I think are a good idea
but at the end of the day I'm not really equipped for it but I really do
wish you the best hopefully you figure it out soon takes time I am a
professional streamer oh well I'm not a professional therapist or a
psychiatrist so there is that not a professional gamer I've never went if I
went where in my resume has said or financial advisor I know I said that
too I'm not a professional gamer I'm not a
professional financial advisor I'm not a professional when am I a
professional at skiing you guys don't even know okay well oh let's off that
one I won the silver medal in the 2000 in the 2000 in the 1999 in the 2004
Olympic Games silver medal and I mean lids off that now I can't well oh no
no what the fuck I can't believe it not gold okay nobody you know you
don't want to get on the Wheaties box that's like the Madden curse you
want the silver medal shines more 2004 was summer yeah I mean in your part of
the continent your part of the world when you guys I'm sorry I don't maybe if
you don't know this when it's summer on one part of the world it's winter on
the other we live in different hemispheres so 2004 it was summer but
it was winter on the other side of the planet and I did my competition on
location because they wanted to make sure that they had they want to make
sure they got that competition in the Olympics the winter when did what do
you mean Olympics I was talking about the like the junior high school kids
like junior varsity league when did I say Olympics what the hell are you
talking about we were on a very difficult bunny hill I felt like
probably four or five times and it wasn't fair because it was really
really really huge huge dude that was in my class and he just went
straight and put all his weight down and it wasn't fair Alzheimer's settling in
what a graph is making up crazy stories again but thank you the whole keg for
the ten dollars and twenty cents congrats on clearing it twice term I
here's your Christmas present hashtag charity thank you the whole keg I did
that completed it hey peaceful Haley thanks for the one dollar hi Jeremy
merry early Christmas hope you have a good Christmas and open up some
goodies I really appreciate you and I know it's stupid but I want to be
like you you're sort of my idol anyways whatever see you next stream well you
want to be like me I want you to be you I want you to be like you you know
but I am you everybody's got something trust me everybody's got something you
are just a vessel no that's not not herpes oh my god thank you
Haley but always remember if I'm your idol I mean I'm I can't even imagine
somebody saying that it's thank you that's I don't I don't know why I mean
I guess that thanks being somebody's idol you know I mean don't be so hard
on yourself no that I mean look when somebody says something like that it's
you know it makes you think it makes you think that you know I want to if
I have that much of an impact on somebody then I want to make sure that
it's like good didn't it you know makes them feel good makes them feel happy
and I don't ever want to have like a negative impact on somebody's life it's
just I don't want to do that really makes you think but I am honored and
absolutely floored that somebody sees me as their idol thank you we had a
bunch of community subs we'll just go over first Fernandez thank you for
community subs Lorag Lorag gave ten community subs I missed it somehow I
think I was just entrenched in the video game thank you Lorag two large 20
community subs coming in from both of them sir rock thank you sir rock for
the two dollars and fifty cents yeah 1502 here every month I collect soda
cans and beer bottles and collect any spare change I can find so I can get
so I can go eat at the buffet at the Golden Corral when I went
yesterday with some other beers I got a pile of fried chicken but when I went
to go for the smiley face fries I couldn't find any voice voice that way
they have smiley face fries at Golden Corral how does that work I love those
fries so this is a part two from Sir Rock here so I asked one of the
waitresses we had smiley face fries well she said they stopped serving
him and we have to eat thrice the daily calories required for a normal
beer me and the other beers left and started throwing trash at the front door
until they threatened to call the police on us we got we got out of there
right out right very quickly that's part two thank you for the five
dollars sir rock smelly boy thanks for the one dollar you're gonna play
smash hashtag charity I feel like I've completely missed the smash train
there and I'm not very good I got I got really knocked down a few pegs
I was like I'm very ready for online and I went to online and just got
destroyed it was embarrassing so I don't think it would be really good
stream it would just be losing online is getting fixed any of that online
was having a lot of problems before so that's why I kind of stayed away
from it Mario tennis all over again no I don't get angry at smash I
don't get angry at smash because smash is people are really really good
at that game and in Mario tennis you just play as fucking Rosalina and Luma
and you get the super spin and it's like where does that what it even is
that I just got angry okay well I'm gonna slow down I'm feeling alright
thank you brand the man for the one dollar thanks for keeping me
entertained while I study for my Japanese final also I'm looking
forward to the Christmas slash Halloween stream hope everything goes
well hashtag charity it should be a really just interesting time it'll be
fun it's going to be fun just to open these presents alone and regardless of
how long it takes me to build the motorized train set and yes that is a
spoiler that takes to make but anyways thank you me too thank you Meezu for
the one dollar actual god gamer streams hotline Miami 2 for 3,000
people hashtag charity I'm just glad you liked it glad you thought it
was fun great job of keeping his secret that's it come on you don't think I've
got more secrets you think that's it that's gonna happen on the 24th I'm
gonna build a train set and then open up gifts from chat come on you don't
think I got you don't think I got like a fucking magic thing up my
sleeve that is what it is yes part of me just wants it to be that now
oh god a hundred dollars just came in right now a hundred dollars one
actually 101 cent so over a hundred dollars spoil the entire Christmas
event or pre-recorded it's not gonna be pre-recorded the moon calf 100 big
money bits and they say Jeremiah been watching since the early TF2 days and
I always appreciate just how much time and effort creativity you put
into the ever-increasing insane projects thanks for the years of
quality madness a 2019 bring even more hashtag charity thank you for putting the
charity there cuz that's it's a lot of money look how long it took you to
make a birdhouse I'll be fine but thanks for being here for so long I
really appreciate it and I'd I hope you stick around we'll see if you
still feel the same way in 2019 I hope you do thank you so much for
your extremely large contribution thank you so much again the moon calf which
brings us back down to a little bit earlier sticks renegade thanks for the
one dollar germs the type of guy who says yes to eating ass Divas thanks
for the three dollars Divas hashtag charity thank you another three
dollars here from a honey chain hashtag charity thank you both of you
peaceful Haley thanks again for a dollar since I started the dab fund
that long time ago I'm now starting the whip and the whip end not none a
fund this is a good cause what is that nae nae I'm such a boomer what I
don't know what that is I don't know what that is I don't like scour the
internet for all the references I'm way too young to be a boomer I know
and that's why I don't get it I was born in 1991 so how could I be a boomer
that's a song that has a 1.5 billion views I mean if you have a YouTube
channel that gets to a point where you have more views than people on
earth I don't even that's that's and that's like God status if you have
like 10 billion views on your YouTube channel did that get more people
have more people have seen you there's only like 20 people on earth 1.5
billion people on earth so I'm saying that there are channels that have like
what seven eight nine ten billion views why would I read that what did I do my
point is if you've been viewed more times than there are humans on earth
if you have a YouTube channel that has that many views you're that's
that's really popular you guys are confusing me now you they are I'm
from the alternate earth what's it like what's it like man what's it like over
there do they have how do they have crunchies that they have crunchy food
they crunchies we got crunchies all right but thank you thank you
peaceful Haley thank you drum aged door thank you drum aged or for the five
dollars good job completing hatline Miami to another you have the taste
of the great indie game I wholly recommend playing Lisa the painful RPG
is one of the best games I've played I've got a lot of recommendation
recommendations play Lisa is that a stream game is that a game like this
that a stream game or should I play that game off stream is that a stream
game yes yes absolutely yes yes yes yes yes okay well I look into that and I
know I said that in a weird condescending way but I will I'll
probably go by it every game is a stream game thank you for five dollars
though I really appreciate it thank you Heathcliff the Friday thriller the one
dollar ring ring hello this is Heathcliff hotline number one kitty cat
man in the Miami area call 1-900-WOWEE if under a what ask your parents before
you call cats we have we don't have as many cartoon dogs as we do a
cartoon cat I won't be satisfied until half of you in this chat are some
type of cartoon animal there actually is a lot is there a lot thank you Heathcliff
thank you thank you to pug ninja for the one dollar you never fail to make
me laugh keep doing you hashtag charity thank you glad you enjoy hanging out
here actually and thanks for the one dollar dude you have to wear a
Hollywood quality bald cap on stream at some point next year I told you I
was are I was gonna do that on the painting stream where me and
italics were painting underneath that bandana was gonna be just a bald just
shiny bald ass head but I didn't I could I it didn't I didn't have it I
don't know maybe I'll do that one day thank you the long egg for the one
dollar have you downloaded the lethal league mod someone made of you I
think it was shown during the green screen movie night I actually want to
play I want to I want to like play that on stream haven't had like a
place to put it though maybe after the holidays I'll try to get
because I know that people are making games maybe I like showcase them and in
the next week or two because I know there's at least three or four of their
people have but thank you thank you man boy for the one dollar please stop
swearing my 13 children watch this channel hashtag charity I can't I'm
sorry just every time you feel yawning I told you fucking they took
too much blood so are you gonna let me ask you guys guys be like this
because I'm like this when I go to the doctor and I get my blood taken and you
sit there I've by the way I've never seen ever I've never seen a needle go
into my arm I've never looked at it I don't know what it looks like I have
no idea what the mechanism is I just know that it hurts for a second and
that's it and I don't look it changes oh yep I don't ever want to
know so what I do is I did this little technique that right when the needles
about to go in for either a shot or for blood work I will take my index finger
and I'll put it on my let's say I'm getting blood drawn from my left arm
I'll put my index finger down on my right knee and I just got just give a
little bit of a little scratch little little scratch scratch on my
right knee not hard or anything because it tricks your brain once it
goes you know okay they say here comes the pinch I just start
scratching and then you it your brain doesn't know where to feel a sensation
so you're kind of like messes with your brain anyways after the first because I
had to get like seven vials taken out of me and that I saw that and I
was like oh okay well I'll be alright after one vial you kind of just sit
in there and you say okay everything's fine they got that's the one vial I
usually only have like one or two vials take after the third vial I
could really start to feel like they were draining my life force vial number
four and five I could just you know when you're getting blood taken and you
just talk to like the nurse or the nurse practitioner and you hate every
second of it so uh how you know you just move here yeah yeah I just moved
here great place oh cool so what are you into I died I like
hamburgers please let me alone leave me the fuck alone you just
don't want to talk you just I hate that because I always feel like I have to
put on like a show because I'm like panicking internally and I'm trying as
hard as I can to focus on trying not to panic internally and now I have to
tell you what my favorite food is and at like vial number six and seven I
don't like I don't care about needles they don't scare me I'm not
scared of having my blood taken or having a shot or anything but you
kind of psych yourself up after you've been sitting there for about
five minutes and I've never given blood before I they take like at least
I think two or three times what I had taken out of me yesterday and at at
that seventh file I remember like the world was kind of starting to close in
and it wasn't because I was scared of the needle it was because I think
they were just taking I think they were just taking all my blood you
know I'm sitting there like they're taking too much I think here we go
I'm starting to feel it I'm going out no no everything's fine everything's fine
hey so where did you move here yeah I was here from Massachusetts hey you you
good man yeah yes I yes do you need do you need like a water or something
yeah how about you go sit down over there just come with me you okay to
walk yeah no I'm not absolutely not you sure yeah man I'm cool and you
using every ounce of your fucking energy and body to walk like a human
to where you have to go sit down because you think you're gonna be the
world's closing in you're like an alien in human skin pretending to walk stop
saying yeah when you mean no I don't know why I do that I feel like a lot
of other people do that too you said this exact sentence during your demon
soul stream that it's relevant just eat him yeah and that's another thing
you have to you're supposed to eat oh have you eaten today and then I
think about it and yeah but what does that mean does that mean oh I like
ate a piece of a carrot no no that's come on man no you have to eat like a
full meal all the material so if you eat it all today this is a literal
question yes I had a crunched a carrot once I had Captain Crunch in my
underwear why are you like this I don't know yes I ate ass today and
doctor's face so yeah you're about to have your blood work done have you had
anything to eat today yeah I ate ass today I feel like I feel like the
doctor would laugh if I was a doctor I would be like holy shit this guy's
fucking crazy and I would laugh high five but long story short that was the
first time in I don't and maybe ever that I've ever had that much
taken from a doctor and one and one girl what a great story tell it again on
your demon soul stream thank you smelly boy for the one dollar streams with a
beater in a row hashtag charity was there one did the did the beater streak
keep going not counting now I don't I don't think there was not that I can
recall snort streak kept going too I don't know we were counting a snort
streak when did you guys start doing that it is during moonlight I I don't
remember I'm gonna say I didn't but that's just me thank you smelly boy
for the one dollar thank you Freudian weapon for the two bucks happy
Wednesday glad you you got the studio space hashtag charity me too the
studio that I've been working with they're very very awesome very very
nice people they think that the ideas and the stuff that I want to do is
really really fun and interesting so it's good this is still playing why is
this music still playing this games on the games don't even open where's it
coming from okay hotline Miami 2 is just stuck open in the background
even with the program closed weird all right and this is apparently this is
apparently when I said
everything I don't know what to do I don't know what to do I'm just
running away oh holy shit and I said hey Peter I said hey Peter I was doing
office space that was not the correct Peter yeah yeah yeah yeah that doesn't
count because it was after the stream what is the correct one we're
talking about Joe Swanson from Family Guy Peter meter reader let me tell you
something Peter Peter that's not guy from office base or Willem Dafoe saying
Peter don't tell Harry Peter Peter see different Peter Peter Peter Peter
Peter it's different see it's different oh I give me one second Peter sorry I
just talked to somebody real quick yeah it's different it's not the same
thing so didn't come but thank you uh cologne Colonel zero thanks for the
eleven dollars Jeremy you're the best thanks for making me laugh all the time
German heart charity hashtag charity awesome thank you so much Colonel zero
zero for the eleven dollars thank you Jamie for the one dollar hashtag
charity thank you thank you oh you blokes for the one dollar thank you
for the one dollar hey German first time donator here loved your old YouTube
videos with star or stir would you say TF2 is dead now hashtag charity no I
don't think so it's really hard for that game to be dead it's not that's
a free FPS that's on Steam that everybody knows is a really good game
so it's that game can really never go away forever I mean is it
probably is it a little the other numbers probably less than what they were
five years ago I would probably but it doesn't cost anything and it's one of
the best FPS it's one of the best games I think I've ever played so a
game like that does it's like it doesn't go away it's just constant
influx of new players that have never played it before and it's like holy
shit imagine going back and removing from your brain ever knowing what team
fortress 2 was you would open that up and it's just Wow look at all this
stuff to do there's a lot of things to do but no it's a great game it'd
probably be around for a long time thank you have gone for the one
dollar hey German just want to say that your streams and the second
germ of its have helped me stay mentally strong in law school the
green screen stream caused the stress of impeding finals to melt away
under unending laughter looking forward to the Christmas Eve stream it
was the green screen stuff was absolutely fucking phenomenal I was so happy with
how that turned out I'm happy that you can hang out here and keep yourself
you know grounded and find some relaxation thank you for being here
and hopefully we see you again real soon and good-looking law school that's
a lot of work good luck you'll get it though you know you will hey
Captain Morgan thanks for the one dollar when are we getting German
Pluto we need the compact planet hashtag charity you already have German
Pluto I mean when are we getting German Pluto it's right there
Captain Morgan again for one dollar oh I forgot about the compact planet
thank you no creativity for the one dollar you do good work German keep it
up hashtag charity thank you not much I can say besides I'm fucking happy
that you think it is good in a world where there are so many people to
watch I'm humbled and sometimes surprised that a lot of you guys choose
to watch me so why would I take that for granted right I want to try is
fucking my damnedest to keep going so mostly lost thanks for the one dollar
I to say die of diabetes when I'm about to pass away hashtag charity
talking about John Arbuckle in the Garfield mod mostly lost thanks to the
one dollar for your information this is the video they kept referencing in the
Garfield level they kept referencing a video
oh I thought I haven't feel Garfield you fat cat you are so big a cat why are you so fat
hi John it's what I do it's time to get Odie off the table don't do it
Garfield that's our pet dog Odie you're going into orbit you stupid
what I can't handle that here's the video what's with the boy the boys cuts
it's cutting itself off over and over again
where are the three cheese song I ate this fool where are the taco shells I
ate this fool where did all the hamburger help her go such a bad kitty
that's the I've had it with you that does it I've done that's the last
drop are the left stuffed in your face as usual weird video that was
right but now it makes sense thank you mostly lost thank you goof goofy new for
the dollar 85 hashtag charity no message just adding charity there thank
you smelly boy thanks for the one dollar during the Garfield mod you kept
skipping words at first I thought it was because they were swears but it
became clear that you were skipping them because they were too big
hashtag charity that's not what happened I was just tired I'm just
tired and I was just skipping over dialogue you have to like bump my arm
a little while I'm lying down because I have the book in my hands and all of
my children are around me and it's like I'm reading reading reading
reading reading eyes closed little nudge and then that's when the Prince
decided that the castle was a little too high for him to go so the Prince
decided nudge and the Prince decided as it happened when I was a kid when my
mother we used to read stories she would fall asleep in the middle of
reading them and we wanted to hear the rest of the story so me my brother
would just give her a little like just a just move enough a little bit
so she felt the movement and then she would just start reading again from
where she left off it was very very funny thank you smelly boy thank you
cloudy for the two dollars hey Jerma just want to say thanks for the streams
also thank you for playing Garfield I love that fat orange cat most people do
not me though I do but no I do thank you Kyralo for the one dollar one day
they wake up and the smell of pancakes cooking the first mole sticks
his head out of the hole and says I smell pancakes the second mole sticks
his head out of the hole and says I smell syrup the the last mole tries
to stick his head out of the hole but I get stuck behind the other two
so he said all I smell is molasses what joke book did you get that out of that
is a joke book that's it that's a dirty joke book paragraph that your
local novelty gift shop you know the one with the guy that has like it's a
weird caricature of a guy's face and his ass is towards the camera on the
front cover of the book and just like a huge fart cloud is coming out
of his ass and he's like guys is he holding his fucking nose and he's
like looking staring like oh and it's the dirty jokes that's where that came
from that I'm not that's not me making like a making up something that's real
and that's a real product that somebody sells or at least they used to thank
you Brandon for the one dollar you should play Lisa on stream it's an
amazing game think you'll like it that's a perfect Christmas present
don't tell me anything I don't want to know what it is I got you
nothing that's okay you're here you're here your presence is enough dragon
breath thanks for the one dollar hey German there's a good chill stream game
you should try called this or a cleanup detail you use a mop and bucket
to clean up a horrific workplace yeah me and a tallex actually played it a
long time ago was there a video of this or clean up detail I swear to
God I have this vivid memory of a viscera cleanup detail video I don't
know I know that I recorded it or was recorded playing it I know me in a top
maybe italics has a video of it where we played together there's a Christmas
level as well hashtag charity could make a good stream they probably added a
lot of content so it might be worth another look here we go here's here's
a video all right can you explain I have no idea what's going on so can
you please explain it because I have absolutely no idea what's happening
here all right we are space janitors yeah random generic first-person shooter
like corridor level yeah this is I remember this funny moments funny
gamer moments that's all the German voice that's old German microphone my
voice hasn't changed young German I'll thank you graveyard ghoul for the
one dollar you mentioned a long time ago about doing a smash stream I
think you said you wanted to do world of light but I'm guessing now
you've beaten it so if you have does that mean we could have mods versus
German tournament if you were here earlier when I talked about smash I I'm
painfully bad at it I get so just slam dunked on every single game that
it's probably not something I'm going to stream I went through world of
light I went through about 60% of it so I still have about 30 or 40% of
the map still to do that's what makes a good stream yeah but I mean it is it
funny for the first like hour and then it's just like okay this dude just
can't win any games enemy going like fuck fuck well that was today was
today a good stream was that was that a good stream today because that's
exactly what I'm describing especially the Garth mission be fun to
watch maybe I will do it they would have to be probably after Christmas though
because I've got too much going on but thank you graveyard cool hopefully that
answers your question German 502 thanks for the one dollar hey German it's me
your favorite clone 258 when missing recently have you seen him I'm getting
worried last I heard he was screaming something about fortnight anyhow I
have continued our cover-up on the incident that happened last year you
know the one involving the jolly red guy people are catching on anyhow I should
continue my work I'm almost done editing your first fortnight compilation
on the main channel cheers hashtag charity yo wins the fortnight stream
fortnight fortnight fortnight fortnight fortnight fortnight fortnight
fortnight do you guys understand what I'm saying thank you clueless sniper
for the one dollar no message thank you actually two dollars from clueless
sniper whoops they forgot to add hashtag charity well thank you ha ha say
it again I already made my peace you already heard what I have to say about
it hey thank you dork for the ten dollars first time donation been
watching you since like 2012 I'm about to be deployed like the other
people always say you brought me joy when I felt like the world was
metaphorically empty you do you and I can't wait to see what you do when I
come back good luck best of luck to you of
curiosity are you US military overseas military I know this was about 40
minutes ago or so if you're still here but regardless take care of
yourself good luck and thank you so much for not only your service but for
being around for that long much love to you take care we await your return
US Army because sometimes when somebody with people say that they're oh I'm
going into training or I'm gonna be deployed or I'm always curious as to
if it's US military or if it's a different like overseas military I'm
usually very curious but thank you again for ten dollars as well cheese nuggets
thanks for the one dollar thank you for words of support and care towards
people down to the luck that clamor to your stuff to cheer them up from time
to time you're definitely one of the sweetest most genuine streamers I'm
afraid of 2019 due to feeling like I lost everything in the last month but
thought knowing things that work out in the end etc and your genuine words
of empathy towards messages like this is a great small comfort thanks Jeremy
we wish the best we wish the best to and they say gay pride
pac-man world 2 on steam when that's a great question where is pac-man world
2 now why is it not been re-released and remastered but no I mean I'll be
real honest with you oh it's thank you for your words and support and
care to us people down their luck and clamoring I'm I'm I'm a person too you
know what I mean like I know what that's like you know you are nice try
alien so when I see people having a rough fucking time it you know it's
it empathy is I don't know nobody ever wants to watch somebody not have
a good time be feel bad about themselves or their life you know I
genuinely it makes me feel fucking bad so because I take a look at you know the
things that have happened in my life and where I've gone and where I want to
go and where I've been and it's um we all we're all doing this together
we're all doing it in the same time you know and I would feel terrible if
I just kind of wrote this type of stuff off is like yeah whatever oh
you're having like trouble and stuff of dad whatever no way you know what I
mean of course I fucking care about it cuz it's something that I'm I'm happy
that people can come here and enjoy themselves some people I know do like
watching me suffer it's so it's a comfort when you care that just
shouldn't be how it is that just shouldn't be the way it is and I don't
think it is I think it's just like a people thing I mean I I always feel
terrible when somebody just doesn't feel like good enough doesn't feel
fucking smart enough doesn't feel good enough doesn't feel liked or don't
worry about what other people think that's tough though you know because
it's I say the same thing like oh just let things be yeah we know if
somebody wants to be like a dick about something or if somebody wants to be
like genuinely like and we're not talking about like banter right we're
talking about like genuinely feeling bad and being treated poorly nobody wants to
feel like that well I do think about it a lot because I've got into this
position here where you know there are a lot of people that watch this stream
and this channel has grown a lot and I do see from time to time people
struggle and people not having a good time I'm just glad you can have a
good time here I don't want a broken record myself but I do think
about that so thanks for being here it's the same motorcycle every time but
like this sound somebody just keeps just driving down the road it's the
same same person on the motorcycle every time is it at the same times too
I'm scared of motorcycles did I ever tell you guys that motorcycles to me
are just a bicycle that goes really fast and I'm really sloppy on a
bicycle I think motorcycles are really cool I think they're really really
awesome I love driving around in motorcycles in a video games I know
that's not real but I think they're really really fucking cool but they've
scared the shit out of me hey cloudy thanks for the two dollars I don't
want to brag German but I'm also very talented athlete I came in third
place in the 2010 fifth grade water balloon toss so I'm kind of a big
deal hashtag charity no that is that's a pretty big fucking deal you
know how hard it is to hold those things and when they throw them really
high and you have to grow go all the way down to the ground and support it
all the way down and it doesn't break it takes talent another $50 came in
from Duke like I said do work last time and I added an R for some
reason 50 bucks I say screw it you deserve it read my other donation if
you see it that's that's $50 from me thank you good luck take care of
yourself the Duke not dork I know I'm just like I'm just stupid and added an
R as much as I skip words sometimes I add them too I don't know why but
sincerely sincerely much love to you hope we see you soon you're here
cheers to that as I say sometimes as we say right we say that does
German think that birds are real why would I not think birds are real 80
yeah it's ADHD it is he's tired and he got his blood stolen give him a break I
know almost done with the bits here thank you bet three for the five dollars
I would give my blood to you if you needed a blood transfusion Jerma thank
well thank you for that you're with laughing my ass out of everything's
birds are real have you ever seen a baby pigeon no because pigeons are
robots I can agree with you there that is a government program that is
a government run program where they are trying they're testing out robotics
what's my blood type I don't know I actually really don't know what it is
and I always tell myself the next time I get blood next time I get blood
taken next time I get blood taken I'm gonna ask I always forget and then
Duke again with ten more dollars fun fact is no German is actually
spider-man maybe a few years ago when I was a little more physically fit
could I've passed as spider-man I could be like the spider-man with like the
hanging gut I got one of those and I never thought that was gonna happen
it's it's getting older guys listen to me I looked in the mirror six or
seven years ago and was just like flexing and standing to the side and
puffing out my fucking quads and just there's no way that that person's
gonna have like a fucking bloated stomach it's never gonna happen I was
convinced I don't know how it happens it just does I look in the mirror now I
still look all right I still look pretty good but where did this like
weird fucking fat guy like baby fat stomach come from it's been drinking
Dunkin Donuts coffee every day but I never put sugar in my coffee I
didn't have sugar in my coffee there was no calories in my coffee there's
probably like 30 calories in my coffee every morning it happened when you
build the birdhouse he became a real dad I'm fucking old man I'm getting old
33 34 35 is gonna creep up so quickly and that's gonna I don't I
didn't think I was ever gonna be that old when you're 20 when you're like
23 24 25 you never look at the future and go oh man yeah 33 no no you're
like I'm cool like I'm hot 25 I could do this I don't have a fucking attack on
Titan's stomach and then boom hits you but thank you again Duke for your huge
amount of money here thank you Novi thanks for the one dollar I can't
wait for the beater compilation hashtag charity I haven't said it
enough time so there'd be a complex that compilation would be like five
seconds bro I'm 19 and I'm gonna be 20
next year what the fuck you have no idea what's the what's the Palpatine
quote we started both get being really old and like you need to be what is it
you have no idea what you're talking about it's something like that 19 19
man if I was 19 I would be sprinting I'd be jumping just because
because I could I would like lying my back and spin I can't lie on my back and
spin anymore I used to do that it was so much fun you can be bionically remade
in ten years don't worry now be fun I thank you Saran wraps for the one
dollar started watching you less than two weeks ago and I already adore your
streams first of all welcome there are a lot of new people over the last
few months so we all welcome you thanks for even checking out the
stream in the first place you do so much for your viewers skits etc that
other streamers would never even consider even as a new fan of your
streams are always a gift hope you 2019 is fantastic
hashtag charity thank you saran wraps hope you stick around because there's
way more to see in 2019 double D thanks for the one dollar sorry for
torturing you with those fortnight references there's some music to make
up for it hashtag charity is this is this my favorite song from hotline
Miami to I thought it was gonna be for that music I did yeah Duke again Duke
gave another $11 here bring you up to $81 thank you so much Duke tell you
the truth you are spider-man don't fool us any longer all right I'll rip off
the rubber mask and there's Peter Parker under there there's all that's
Peter Parker but thank you Duke and you also say active duty US Army get best
though man and like I said keep doing you good luck on your deployment Duke
we'll be here when you get back and that is going to conclude our bit
reading portion of the stream which takes us to the subscriber credits
subscribers subscribers here they come tons and tons of resubs and new subs
every stream read credits all right fine
now what you used to he's doing it so fast read faster okay hold on I was
seeing how embarrassing that was with the mic off and it was very
embarrassing and I'm glad I didn't do that joke dropped joke dropped joke
dropped hey thank you scribble for the one dollar haha there's more bits to
read hashtag charity using beatbox and fine thank you scribble for the one
dollar more beatboxes all right same time tomorrow or normal time I don't
know because of me going to bed and getting up such strange times I'm
probably gonna I really don't know because there's a chance that I go eat
food and then go food blood pass out it's possible I'm thinking such a big
deal out of this I had my blood taken yesterday it's like oh you see the
thing is I had my blood taken yesterday so I'm gonna go to bed like
I'm blowing that out of proportion so much I'm over exaggerating that so
much more beatbox okay but I think probably around the normal time
because there's a chance that I'll stay up but there's an equal chance
that I fall asleep in like an hour or two so I really don't know forgive me
I'm sorry I've kind of screwed up my sleep schedule here yesterday but there
will be a stream tomorrow at some point will I will figure out when
definitely definitely after like noon and absolutely before like five or
four Pacific time so between like 12 and 4 p.m. Pacific is when the
stream is going to start a beatbox again okay and that is the end of
subs thank you all so much please install BT TV I don't think I will I
want to be able to stay in an interview you know in like a couple of
years so German 985 what it's like some advice you can give to the you
know you're the number one streamer on earth what's some advice you can
give to some fellow streamers don't ever install BT TV I never did I
can't use computers I just use blackboards please hire me I don't
even I hate blackboards they make my ears hurt anytime I'm in a room with a
blackboard I want to leave the room because I just imagine the sounds
coming out of the blackboard the sound makes me ill you can't see the D
emote it's all right I got my own emotes see that one is this right
here's the dance you go the dance one was sour please right I have one
of those see I look I'm just I'm dancing over there sour please it's not
animated yeah but just imagine it is I thought that was a nose wipe yeah but
it's you people use it in different contexts where's Wowie emote really
showing my under pressure vocabulary skills on these hotline Miami 2
streams Wowie whoa wow whoa but anyways guys I'll see you tomorrow not
exactly sure what we're gonna be doing but I'm sure we'll come up with some
see you soon take care have a great rest of your night
ta-ta for now and bro luck just gave a dollar I missed the stream here's a
dollar to show you my apology don't you don't have to be sorry can't
make every single stream it's it's it's not right see you tomorrow