Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Doing a lot of Team Fortress 2 the last couple of days, and that's because Man vs. Machine is just a ton of fun,
and especially this Man Up mode. And the only way you can get into a Man Up mode server is if you buy one of these Tour of Duty tickets.
They are 99 cents each, and these tickets allow you to not only play in the Man Up mode servers,
but after you complete one of these six missions, there's only six right now, you are going to consume that ticket,
and it's going to give you a random item. Now, you are definitely going to be playing for these items.
It is very, very difficult. As you'll see in this video, this is one of the most intense things ever,
that I've ever done in Team Fortress, or gaming in general. You're going to see some really intense moments here,
stuff that comes down to the absolute wire, and I believe Shibby has this on his channel as well if you want to see his perspective.
Just wanted to give this video a brief introduction. Playing on the map Decoy, this is wave 8 only,
and I hope you guys enjoy the chaos that is about to ensue. So thank you guys so much for watching,
we really do appreciate it, and enjoy the live commentary. Take care, everybody.
Go back and spend it.
Yeah.
Back, and crit boosts.
I haven't even got to shoot anybody yet with my sentry.
Oh, I got destroyed projectile. I can just keep shooting rockets. Nice.
Alright.
Oh shit.
How was that mover again? Demo.
Do you want it now?
No, don't use it. Hold on to it.
I need ammo.
That money.
Do it now.
That paper.
Pick up the ammo crate when you can.
Oh, these guys are all going to die when they step on that.
So that's not taking all the ammo from the dispensers?
Yeah, I'm shooting your rockets.
Very good, very good.
I haven't even got to kill anybody with the sentry yet.
Might as well.
Oh, that was dumb.
Here comes another super soldier.
That was dumb.
He's got all crits. Watch out.
Money steps on that.
Watch these rockets. I got it, I got it.
I need...
Here comes the con and the heavy.
Heavy with the medics.
You got crits?
Heavy with medics.
Oh boy.
Here he comes, here he comes.
Oh, I died, I died. Shit.
What is he doing up here?
Is there a path change?
I don't know, but we got to get rid of this tank.
Tank always goes left. You're good about that.
Oh man, there's bad news.
They're all over here. They're going up that right...
They're going to try and go up there with you.
I'm going to try and take the medics.
Oh, damn.
Medics are gone, medics are gone.
This heavy should go down.
He's dead.
Nice one.
Two snipers.
We got to get rid of this thing.
Oh, coming up again.
I am officially out of ammo.
Oh come on, step on that.
They're just walking over it.
This heavy's coming up onto it.
German, get rid of detonator on them.
Yep.
I'm waiting, I'm waiting for him.
I'm going to need help with this tank, guys.
Yeah, I'm here.
We got this heavy over here.
I don't think we're going to get it.
I'm coming back, I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
Tank, tank, tank.
Oh no.
It's alright, we're here.
We're here, we're here.
Kill it.
Oh no, it might be too late.
Nope.
We got a big dude here.
Yes.
Alright.
Do you got...
No.
That was nuts.
I almost got crits.
This is the first...
Hey, this is the first...
No, not yet.
This is the first we've ever been.
Alright, do it now, do it now, do it now.
Go.
They popped uber.
Oh, come on.
Please tell me they're going to all have no open with this.
Come on.
Damn it.
No.
Fucking sniper.
Fuck.
It's alright, it's alright.
Get the medic, get the medic.
There we go.
Got him.
Get this, get him.
Get him.
No.
It's alright, it's alright.
This is the furthest we've ever been.
Just relax, relax a little bit, relax.
We only have like a little bit left.
There's a sniper around.
Heads up.
Be aware.
Watch out for this guy.
Got to kill his medics.
Oh, he's over here on the left.
On the right.
He's ubering.
Fuck.
It's alright, it's alright.
Knock the medic away, knock the medic away.
He's got to go down in a second.
He comes up here.
Yes.
Oh.
God.
I got to go.
I'm going to go buy crits.
Another one.
He's got medics though.
Alright, do not crits me.
Do not crits me.
Crits somebody else.
Oh, I've been knocked away.
Shit.
We did it.
We just did it.
Oh, we did it.
Yes.
It only took us like three fucking hours.
Oh, anybody get anything good?
No.
Oh, that was one of the most intense things I've ever done in gaming.