I'm so glad that I got killed by a default demoman.
All right, say default demoman as fast as you possibly can.
Default demoman.
No, it has to be like, it has to be like default demoman. Let's be perfect.
Default demoman. Default demoman. Default demoman.
This almost sounds like I'm gonna have to put effort into it.
Default demoman. Default demoman.
Default demoman. I'm gonna do this.
That's wrong with me. No, get away from me, baby.
Oh, are you gonna...
Oh, sentry? You want to get sentry'd?
Son of a bitch!
Oh my god, rampage.
This is another sentry gun.
God, there's so many sentry guns. This game sucks.
Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here, Covenant Piss right now.
Covenant P, Covenant Poo.
We're going to be doing a live commentary right here.
Playing on the map CP, Gravel Pit.
Got Mrs. Buttsack gonna be healing me for this round.
Gonna be live shellcasting, like I said.
And here we go. We got the first point here.
We got a sniper coming out of the corner.
We got a B. Now the A is being captured.
Now B is being captured.
I got the quick fix Uber right here.
Trying to get this Pyro off the point.
I get him. I'm getting this shot in the back.
I've got another demoman coming from the side.
It's unfortunate that he was not able to get through here.
There's a sentry gun here.
Two sentry guns in a really stupid dumb place, but it's okay.
Let's keep going here. I want it.
I took this part of the live shellcast out
because I didn't make it very much.
So it just...
Boss that medic right there, but it's okay.
We got a teleporter over here.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got the teleporter down.
We got the engineer down as well.
Jerma seems to know what he's doing here.
Oh, now he's at spawn.
What the fuck is he doing at spawn?
Ladies and gentlemen, he's doing some really crazy stuff right here.
You kept that going for a really long time.
Where the fuck did he come from?
I'm just like whipping this guy.
You want to get whipped?
Oh my God.
How many people can I whip?
Let's find out.
Let's find out how many people I can actually kill with the whip.
Here comes a scout.
Here we go.
Oh no, here comes Pyro.
No medic.
Damn it.
Here we go, ladies and gentlemen.
Coming down the corridor.
He sees a sniper.
Huntsman sniper, by the way, which is helps out.
He hits the bait.
It's a crit.
A crit rocket.
Guy hanging on the side of the wall there.
We've got some really important things going on.
There is a soldier up top here.
Jerma gets a culture.
One shot with the direct hit does not get the kill.
Default the moon.
Trying to do a shoutcast and it gets ruined.
And did you see that air shot?
Ladies and gentlemen, we'll just get that right.
Get into this here.
Another devil man around a quick fix.
Uber, is he going to get the devil knight right there?
Gets one shot, two shots.
Here he comes around the corner.
Gets the shotgun.
One, two, and a three.
Third time's a charm.
Pyro going after the medic.
He gets a one shot, two shot, three shot.
Does not get the kill.
Gets the bet.
He's got to get that whip attack.
Yes.
That is so...
You know what?
Let's just stop right here.
Can I just say this?
If you can do that, you are talented.
You just really are.
Because I don't know how people continue to...
You know, Heavy, just fucking die.
Oh my God, I'm terrible.
Oh boy.
You know, I'm fine.
Oh my good...
Ow, my butthole!
What?
Is there something wrong with this engineer?
Like, what is going on?
Why?
What are you doing?
We have a point to cap, you know.
We have to go over there and get this point.
No, I...
Sir?
Sir, excuse me.
Sir, you have to go that way and cap the point.
I'm done with you.
Let's see how...
You see?
You see what happens?
You see what happens when you don't do that?
You want to step inside for the next Game of Thrones.
It's gonna be so much fun on the next Game of Thrones.
You have this song style that you always, always go back to.
And if you were like, actually, like an artist, like a musician...
Yeah?
You would be the worst.
Why do you say that?
I'm gonna go to the next Game of Thrones.
That's like the...
You're always so excited about like nothing.
That's a theme.
That's like the general theme song music.
Have you ever heard like a theme song from anywhere in the 80s or 90s?
Holy shit, did you see this pyro?
Every theme song in the 80s and 90s had a motto.
The Otto?
Like, for instance, like, we were moving on up to the east side.
Like, that was the song's motto.
And it said it like three or four times in the exact same tone.
Right?
Yeah.
Here's another one.
Oh yeah, child's in charge.
Like, the child's in charge.
Come on.
You know what I'm talking about.
I do know what you're talking about.
So that's why when you say...
When I'm like, you better step inside for the next Game of Thrones.
Like, the next Game of Thrones is the motto of the theme song.
The Otto?
No.
The motto.
No!
There's a pyro just standing there, like, hitting this engineer at spawn with...
What the fuck is...
Hold on.
What the...
What was that?
Why did the whole earth just rotate like 100 miles per hour?
Is that like a bug?
What the hell just happened?
Where the shadows like move across the ground?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's actually a pretty common bug.
I've never seen that before.
That was ridiculous.
It looked like somebody was like speed hacking above me.
All right.
Let's see how long it takes me to get headshot here.
Okay, that didn't take long at all.