All right, I'm back. Well, not quite. I'm gonna get a drink. I gotta make sure I got my tweet ready.
I've never done this before. Gotta make sure I do it right. I gotta make sure my tweet's ready. Did he shit himself? All right.
Okay, fuck. Wait, I haven't started the sponsor stream yet. I haven't started the sponsor stream, but it hasn't started yet.
We're still on IRL. Don't, um, all right, enough. All right, enough. I have not started yet. So
relax, quiet. Give me one, give me one more second. Hold on. All right, I'm almost ready. I'm almost ready.
I just have to change the, um, I just gotta change my game and the title.
He's acting like he's going to prom. This is, I've never done this before. This is a big deal.
This is a big deal. Let me refill my drink and I'm ready to go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. All right, one more sec. He's going to prom.
I don't, I don't know why that was there. I don't know why that was there. Yeah, no, just take that out of here.
I don't know why. There's a pair, there was a pair of underwear just on my desk. What the fuck? Why?
I don't know why it was there. Okay. I want to give one sec. All right. I think I'm ready. Hold on.
I gotta make sure my tweet's ready. Gotta make sure my title's ready. I'm, I'm honestly, I'm actually
happy to play this. I'm excited to play this. I played the demo of this game and I was like, that was actually fun.
I like to play more of that. So here we are. What happened? I just got back. We, uh, moved on to a sponsor segment.
First time ever. I am pogging right now in real life and you'll see real quickly. Double checking the tweet.
I think that's fine. I think that it works. Okay. Okay. I'm not doing a YouTuber voice. Uh, no, I'm not doing that.
All right. I'm ready. Tweet is going out. There it is. That's a legit, that's a legit sponsored tweet here. First ever.
I've never done that before. I don't have Twitter. Dude, get out, you gotta, what? Yeah, we got a hashtag ad.
Are you nervous? No, no, I'm not at all. It's team 17. Yep. He's corporate Andy. That's, hey, that's me.
All right, you guys ready? I'm at this, I'm actually very excited. This game is gonna be good.
I played the demo. Please help with this. Can you see? This is a man size sponsor.
You should be able to see it now. Hey, you can see me at least. All right.
You ready? No, I'm not supposed to disappear. All right. So, well, what is this game? What is this?
Well, hold on a second. Let me tell you. This game is a game where you, uh, it's an action adventure game.
It seems pretty interesting. It's a game where you craft potions. The game where you, it's an action adventure
experience and it looks really fun. I did my research.
I played the demo. Might be too loud. It runs in 1,440 p.
Soundtrack is good. Don't swear. Stop swearing. Damn. All right, new game. Let's go. Uh,
I'm gonna play this person. Epic music. Oh, I gotta get, I gotta get the face cam off. At the crossroads of existence
there is a serpent that bites her own tail.
Stop swearing. You're making me look bad. And on, and on and on she gnaws without ending or beginning, only harmony.
And yet there are those who would be, who would sicken her and force her jaw open.
I'm waiting for the pogs because this is, I'm telling you, you're gonna like this.
Cycle broken, balance undone.
Until all that is left is the poison of the serpent rogue.
Yeah, you make potions. Actually, my cam might be in a good, I gotta move the cam.
You make potions and you go out and fight stuff.
Any NPC I believe can be killed, which is kind of scary.
I have played it a little bit to decide if I was like, yeah, that sounds like something I could do.
Let's go. We're going to two headphones and it's fucking scary. I hope you're ready.
Now you got a health bar up there. You got a stamina bar up there.
Solomon, the first steps are always the hardest.
Don't worry. You'll soon grow accustomed to your body.
You've quite a task ahead. It won't be easy, but I'll make sure to teach you all the right lessons.
For instance,
that'll be your transport out of this in-between. We'll meet again warden in a more stable place.
It's pretty. Lights off. Lights off. You got it.
You got it. Lights going off. Let me fix the cam.
Oh, that's better. All right, let's go. And by the way,
I'd run if I were you. The corruption is coming.
Actually, probably should run. Running takes stamina. Can you hear it? All right. Sounds good to me.
Is this Elden Ring? No, this is okay. Hold on. Can you die in the tutorial?
Go, go, go, go. All right. I'm good. No, this is not it. This is
there's no like dodge roll. I don't think I'm pogging so hard already.
You should. You actually should be.
I believe this is on everything by the way.
This is not just on steam. It's on. I think it's on everything. It's on like switch.
Wherever you want to get it. It's such a long journey. There it is. Source of corruption.
It's blight spreads like wildfire. Given time, it'll consume everything. This cannot stand. There is much to be done.
New quest. The corrupted land. Investigate locations.
Okay, I was trying to fuck around and just walk off the edge, but I just found a secret.
Okay.
Sure.
What the hell is in here?
All right, we got apples, raw meat, tea leaves.
Ingredients can be used to craft powerful potions with unique effects. From raising the hollow
to transforming yourself into another species.
But before you can use such ingredients, first you need to study their structure in a research laboratory. Got it. Anything else in here?
You can pick up stuff, right?
There's aloe. Check your inventory. Press Y.
Everything has weight too.
Yeah, you have to like, okay, you have to research shit
before you can make potions.
There is fighting and yeah, it is like dangerous. You can die and there's consequences for dying.
What is this? Discover.
Poor creature. The corruption truly spares no one. Corrupted dog.
Go through the fog. Fog dork. This is pretty, this is not, why would this be pre-recorded? What are you talking about?
When did we get to get to the swearing segment?
All right, so this is like the town. All right, so here's the brewing table.
Care to brew that special potion before you can use an ingredient? You must research it in the research laboratory first.
You should research it. Jim, is this a scary game?
No, I don't think so. I collect knowledge about brewing and experiment with bases of ingredients to discover the true power of alchemy.
Be aware that crafting potions without knowing the recipe can result in the ingredients being wasted. Don't fuck around here.
I don't know anything about these, so it would probably be stupid if I did it.
All right, you you got to research it before you can use it. I'm, I can swear that's fine, right? Can I?
Should I not be?
Okay, so research. You have to research ingredients before you can use them.
Repeat after me, please. You got to study a few samples first. You can track the progress in your journal. Very cool.
All right, so I need, I got tea leaves.
I need, okay, I need more.
All right, so that is vitality.
There's like little hidden chests and shit around the world. It's pretty cool.
This looks like a warden's chest special container built specifically for your kind.
Warden chests are connected in such a way that items stored in one location can be taken from another. Like a, like a diablo 2 chest, right?
Anybody can use it?
I'm not swearing.
All right, there's already stuff in here.
Healing potion.
Yeah, take it.
Damage, I think you can use potions on anybody, I think. Maybe I shouldn't take all this.
That was a portable lab recipe.
Chicken form?
Transforms the user into another creature with all their strengths and weaknesses.
Yeah, whatever, I'll take it.
Let's take a few of these too. All right.
Oh, yeah, you can cook. I forgot you can cook.
Yeah, you can use a cooking plate such as this to enhance the properties of your dishes.
Each cooking attempt requires one piece of log, which would be converted into charcoal.
Jesse.
Be aware that cooking without knowing the right recipe can result in ingredients being wasted.
So if you don't know anything, then there's no point. So I'm gonna hold, do I know any recipes?
That worked.
I have a choice steak.
All right. Well, I don't want to fuck around.
Do I know how to make any potions? Vitality and unexplored. Wait.
Do I have to research that?
Okay, I have to research that 20 times. Charcoal.
Okay. Yeah, there's a punch.
Two damage, that's not a dummy. Okay, cool.
There's a punch. This game is very pretty. It is very pretty.
It actually looks very nice. All right, here we go.
And the wardens meet.
Away from the darkness but under his shadow.
The wardens are sworn to serve the cycle and protect balance.
And yet, this is a dangerous place even for our kind.
Anyways, why don't you try and explore this area for materials and equipment?
It's worth training your offensive skills with the dummy as well.
This is no peaceful realm, not anymore.
Stop reading my messages.
Yeah, I mean, it gives you a little bit of like what to do.
But you kind of just do whatever you want, I guess.
This seems pretty open. Wait, what is this?
Chop. I can't chop that. What about this?
This is like a big map.
So I eventually have to go here. We'll get it.
Plague doctor? Yeah, there's a plague doctor.
The kiosk lost souls are drawn to it like moths to a flame.
So much left undone, it's hard coming to terms with it.
They don't know what to do so they leave requests.
You wouldn't understand wanting is unique to those who lived.
That's why we can help and that's why we can earn rewards.
Their dear gold, their precious hope.
How much is the game?
Well, it's available right now and it is currently.
It is available on Steam right now.
I think it has a 10% off sale at the moment.
Let's take a look.
The game is currently $17.99. It's part of a bundle too.
$17 bucks? $17.99? Not 19, no. $17.99.
Let's go. That's less than a Hulk Hogan grill.
That's way less than a Hulk Hogan grill.
All right, so what is this?
This order is stained with blood so I must be in dire need of a healing potion.
So I need healing potion.
Don't have those on my chest? Oh, shit.
Okay. I didn't even make that though.
Five gold. That easy.
That's easy. Simple.
Now what? Corruption is a way of changing things.
Often for worse, but sometimes for the better.
All right. I need to collect fucking berries and stuff.
Come on. I got berries, berries, berries, berries.
Anything else on here? Was that a pumpkin?
Just take everything. Fascinating little box, isn't it?
They used to not only research new ingredients,
but also to create powerful potions on the go.
This one's mine, but you can take it.
No worries, warden. I'll make another one for myself later on.
Fresh berries. Give it a try to use it to research a new few ingredients.
Okay. So you can, if you're out and about,
you don't have to come all the way back here.
Research, pick up, or craft. All right. Research.
I got three berries, so now I know what this does.
This is add. Add. Should I pick it up?
What about this other stuff here? Tea leaves?
Yeah. This game's all about, you got to make potions.
They're like the most important thing in the entire game.
I think if you die, you need to go get your stuff too.
The game does not, it's not like, oh, I died. I'm fine.
No, you got to go pick up all your shit or you're in trouble.
All right. What do tea leaves do? Do I research it?
Yeah. All your stuff. This seems pretty well-made so far.
Yeah. I told you guys. I was very clear.
Yeah, this is a sponsored stream, but this game looks really fun.
I was interested from the get-go.
This hats. How do I get new hats?
Ooh. Remove corruption from 12 creatures.
Catch 25 fish in water banks. This fishing.
Buy five items from the merchant.
Discover 15 creatures in the journal. That's cool.
I only have the regular hat. All right. So let's go.
Let's go. Should I cook some food? I already have food, right?
Anything else I didn't see? What was this?
Can I do this? I think I, okay. Well, that didn't work.
Use left bumper to block and it's right trigger to attack.
And then right bumper is sort of an ingredients list. Cool.
This is the, all right. Why is inventory?
Oh, I can put, all right, hold on. Equip.
Ah, all right. Okay. Right bumper.
All right. So if I drink a damage potion, what happens?
It fucking hurts. You can, okay. I can throw it though.
What are we doing this? Is it in five damage?
Well, drink this. Did I just waste a bunch of ingredients?
Okay. All right. What about the fish over here?
You need to finish the rest of the stream in the Elmo voice.
No, dude. Are you serious? No.
Ooh, fish. I need a fishing rod.
All right. I got materials. I need a shovel to dig.
What's this? What's this?
You know, were it up to me, you would never have come to this place to face something so dangerous.
To face something so dangerous, but allow me to offer some guidance.
If nothing else, you'll need to cross the wasteland at some point.
There's an ancient tree with roots that spread far and wide
and that tree, it burns with a ruinous flame.
The corruption, of course, and it won't let you through, not without a fight anyway.
Good luck. Hope we'll meet again before the end.
The dev said do Elmo. Is that a lie? Are you making that up?
To fast travel to another location, select the menu.
All right. So now what? That was just like a little tutorial design.
All right. So I'm just going. I'm just going somewhere.
Stranger. The well is whispering. Can you hear it?
It does. It does. The bustling murmurs of creation rising fiercely into this realm.
Don't believe me? He pressed your ears.
Sorry. Throw a coin, make a wish, and you'll have a glistening remedy against corruption.
Drop coins. Its words warm you from within.
Hey, I don't want to. How much money do I have?
I have eight dollars. Why would I do this? I have eight bucks. What a waste.
I don't want to do that. What's going on over here?
This is the pantry, a great place to store food.
We managed to find human followers. They can feed themselves here.
Feed followers? Should I cook an apple?
Hey, bro, a roasted apple. Calm down.
What about apple? What about an apple braised turkey leg?
No. Actually, should I just bake these?
Oh, I don't need wood. OK. I got a baked apple now.
Who's this? There was someone waiting for me far and away on the other side of the other side.
But now the farewell pier is hidden, covered by the looming vines, the killer plants,
the breaker vines. They endure safely from the no more fire for a much needed cleansing.
Those tall plants, looming vines, he called them.
Perhaps there is some information to be gained about it nearby.
Well, that was a bomb. OK. Sorry about that.
OK, so how do I get through this? OK. Well, don't touch it.
This is really cute. It is. Yeah, this is really cool.
I need to be like picking stuff up. This game is all about preparation
because everything is dangerous, I think, out there.
So I don't just want to walk out like a dickhead and not have any tools.
So let me figure that out first. How do I make a shovel?
Wait, didn't I get a... I did. Portable lab recipe.
Oh, all right. I can make that now. What about over here?
Cheese, crusty bread, sunny side up egg. Ooh. Do I sleep?
I'm going to sleep. Sleep. Oh, I'm holding the button down.
What is this food meter going down for? Oh, shit. OK.
Eat an apple. Oh, yep, yep. You have to eat for the stamina bar, right?
OK, cool, cool, cool, cool. Oh, yeah. More crates.
What's going on over there? I have so much food.
You hear threatening growling and barking nearby.
Those hounds seem to have gone feral and they're fighting each other.
What? Discover. Those hounds were actually fighting over scraps,
but this one looks too weak to defend itself. Maybe if it was fed.
If you want to tame a creature, first, you need to research what they eat
so you can feed them and earn their trust.
All research results will be displayed in your journal.
The more creatures of the same species you find, the more information about them you'll learn.
All right. Wild dog. To learn more about a creature, select the menu
and then choose the journal. The journal. Oh, dog.
Favorite food. Raw meat, choice steak, or baked meat pie.
I have steak. I just made it. Where is it?
All right. Choice steak. How do I use it?
The pound is much better now and seems to have taken a liking to you.
Perhaps if you fed other animals, they might have a similar reaction.
Really? Okay. Should I keep feeding them?
What's up here? Wasteland.
Just like the old warden said, which means that must be the corrupted tree.
Hope my Friday's going well. Hope your Friday's going well, too.
He's starving. I'll feed him. I'm going to take care of him.
What's going on? There must be some way to heal that maelstrom and clear the passage.
I have to heal it? All right.
Reach the corrupted tree. Did I prepare? Do I have any food?
All right. I have aloe. I have crusty.
All right. I need to equip the crusty bread. Can I use this as a weapon?
Okay. I can use the bread as a weapon. This is some stale ass bread.
Will it actually work? What's this? Oh, turnips.
A mandragore. What the fuck?
What's going on? Hey, how do I pick this up?
Oh, I got it. A mandragore obtained.
The chest up here. Ow.
Do I have to get hurt by this? All right. I think I have to take the damage.
Was it worth it? I need a pick lock for this.
What's wrong with me? What's wrong with me?
All right. Another mandragore. Okay.
Oh, I need wood. I can chop the trees down. I need an axe.
What's wrong with me? I'm going to die. What's going on?
Oh, I'm taking tick damage. I can't die in the first...
I'm dead. Okay.
We just had to see what happened when you died. We had to see what happened.
After perishing, you'll be returned to a safe location like the house.
Your belongings, however, will not.
Your items will remain in the same spot where you fell, just waiting for you to pick them up.
If you fall again, they'll be gone forever.
Okay. Well, I had a lot of stuff, I think. I got to go get it right now.
Where's my stamina bar? Shit.
Okay. I have no... I don't have a stamina bar.
All right. Where's my stuff? Okay. Over here.
Okay. I got to go. Where was it? What's this 20% thing at the top?
I was over here. I cleared that.
I went over this way. There it is. Okay.
Bag. Take it all. Oh, thank God.
What is that? What is that? A corrupted chicken?
What am I supposed to do? What is following me?
Portable lab has been stolen. What?
Get out of here. Leave me alone. I don't have a stamina bar.
What the fuck? He stole my lab.
Okay. A wild rat. Oh, I'm learning about them.
Can I... Like, what do I do about this?
All right. I need to eat something. Just eat all this cheese.
Only two? All right. Somebody set up egg.
What is this thing counting? What's the 33%? 33%.
What's that mean? Ooh. Oh, I got a torch.
Oh, hell yeah. It's a weapon. On attack, remove three target vitalities.
This is a weapon. All right. Finally.
Can I light it? I need to get the lab back.
How do I get the lab back? He doesn't have anything on his inventory.
Horus undiscovered. Who's Horus?
Should I discover Horus? Why am I fighting this thing?
This shit has durability. Ow, you piece of shit.
All right. Did you have anything?
I'm fucking dead. No shit. Don't die from thorns again, please.
There's a chest in here. Did I get the lab back?
What is this? Open.
This chest is sealed with a strange lock and there's an inscription beside it.
My prize is under protection three, which only the one that glows shall see.
This is a, I can light this. Can I?
Does this work? Oh, all right. Cool.
How long does it last? I don't want to die.
Moonstone and three textiles. I got to research this.
It looks like it comes back. I need my research lab.
Did they actually get rid of it? Yeah, it stole it.
I can't. That piece of shit actually stole it.
The rat went south with the lab. I don't want to miss anything.
So it does seem pretty open. I was curious at like how open
this stuff was actually going to be.
There it is. He stole something else.
Get over here. It's this thing. All right.
I got my shit back. I got my shit back.
Give me this lab textiles. Discover wild rat and oh, my crusty bread.
Where's my weapon? I think it's 60% whatever that is.
Oh, you can heal by sitting down. That's actually really helpful.
All right. Let me, let me open up the lab.
Let's get that lab open portable lab.
Okay. So I need to research charcoal.
I need 19 more. Four more feathers and I know what it is.
Three more mandragores. I have enough tea leaves.
What is it? Remove.
So when you go to the crafting table, you do like add something vitality
or like remove something vital, right? I think that's how it works.
Do I have any more? Yeah, like add vitality.
Would that do anything? Sloppy potion.
No. All right. That didn't work.
Because you have this four slots. Remove vitality.
You can probably make like hurt potions, right? All right. That's cool.
I'll pick it up. Should I burn these?
Is my torch dead? Shit, it is.
Okay. I don't have a torch.
I'm back to using like the chicken leg as a weapon.
What's my favorite part of the game so far?
I don't know. I think I needed some more time in it.
I don't have a pick lock, but all right.
It seems like you kind of just walk around and collect stuff
and then make new stuff and then keep going and then get further
into the game and then make new stuff and then collect more things.
It seems cool. All right.
I have plenty of... All right. What's going on here?
Is this a wild dog? Oh, all right.
I know more. You have a moonstone?
Well, this is what you have on you. Moonstone. Ingredient. Shining.
A special keystone. Bound to the edge.
Should I try to give this dog a snack? Oh, shit.
What about... No, no, no. Don't go. Don't go.
They like meat, right? Come here. Feed.
What's wrong? You don't want that. You don't? Dog.
Favorite food. Raw meat. Not raw meat.
Doesn't like raw meat. I thought I said raw meat.
Maybe this one doesn't... Maybe this one wants cooked meat.
Needs a steak. What about... Do you like bread?
No. I don't want to kill it. I need to cook that steak.
He's full. All right. I'm going to... I'm just going to eat this.
That's cool. Anything in here? I need a axe.
Wait, I think that means... That thing's freaking me out.
Ninety one percent. Ninety two percent.
Sealed message. What happens at a hundred percent?
Wait, material. Fuck.
Oh, world tomb and inspect in there. Oh, a worm. Another worm.
Okay. All right. Worms. I needed those to fish.
This is at 96. What's going on? What happens in the hundred percent?
What's going on? Ninety nine percent.
A corruption storm is wiping out the area.
We'll give... Run! Get out of here! Wait, what?
What happened? Travel, travel, travel. Fast travel, right?
I can't fast travel during a storm. How do I get out of here?
How do I get out of here? Where's the exit?
Shit. Is that there forever?
What the hell is that? Does it say what it does?
Does it give you like a time limit to make it so it's a little more stressful?
What the... This is a chicken corpse? What are you looking at?
Clement. Clement has an axe.
Wait, is there a... Who is this person?
Clement and this bird are friends. I want that axe.
Is there like a... Can I steal?
There's got to be like a steal, right? What are you doing?
Can I steal it? Don't steal.
I definitely can steal. All right. Well, fine.
Are they friends or something? Why are they here?
All right. I need to... I need an axe.
I need a weapon. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, okay. Enhance the axe.
Oh, all right. I can enhance the axe or I can forge.
All right. Here we go.
Make or enhance basic instruments with crafting materials.
Each crafting attempt requires charcoal or a spectral fuel.
You might need... You need to know the recipe.
All right. Well, I can't... Let me... Hold on. What's this?
Eight charcoal. Holy shit.
There was something like a chop down over here, right? Like right here.
There was a couple of things I could chop down, right?
I have no stamina. Logs and cut this.
I need glass. Okay. Shit.
I love how good he is at acting like he doesn't know what he's doing.
I don't. I don't know what I'm doing.
I played like 15 minutes of the demo.
I walked around this town and was like, yeah, I think this is going to be fun.
Yeah, I didn't play the demo for four hours.
I played the demo for like five to 10 minutes.
I didn't play the demo for like four hours.
Oh, what's the axe do?
I'm not sure. I don't know. What's the axe do?
Somebody... I'm fine. I'm doing fine.
Okay. There was something else I needed to cut.
I remember seeing it. I think it was the trees, right?
Do you keep your money? You do.
All right. Now that I actually have a weapon,
I'm going to go back out and I'm going to be fine.
What's the game? The game is called The Serpent Rogue.
It's available for PlayStation 5, Xbox, X, Switch, Steam.
It's pretty much on everything. Are we friends?
Not yet. He's hungry.
I got to get my food and come back.
Now it's on. It's on everything.
All right. Well, this is where I did.
Okay. 32. I get it.
So I'm at 32%.
I got to get out of here before that gets all the way up.
I get it. That's an interesting mechanic.
So you have a finite amount of time.
I need to eat something right now.
Baked apple and cheese, bread, eggs.
I need to cook this shit.
I shouldn't just be eating it raw.
Okay. There's a lot of logs.
Okay. I don't want to break the axe.
Does it really matter?
All right. Wait, what's this up here?
I have to clear this.
A corrupted beast.
Fight it or cure it. The only way is through.
Cure it with a sunny side up egg.
Do you think? All right.
I don't think I want to fight this thing.
Should I discover it?
Can I discover it?
Discover it.
Oh, fuck. Okay. Do not.
Oh, chicken. No.
I probably shouldn't have done that either.
All right. Get out of here.
So many horrors.
I can heal them.
What's this?
Diagro. Get away from me.
Oh, my God.
There's gold over there.
There's gold right here.
How do I get this gold?
Oh, my fucking God.
There's golden eggs here.
Get away from me.
Use. I just used aloe on that dog.
Such a heavy burden.
You're carrying too much weight,
resulting in slow movement and inability to fast travel.
All right. I got to go get all that stuff.
Okay. I got to go grab some potions.
Fuck.
When back to our world, are you strange?
Usually takes you a bit longer to return.
Of course, I know about you.
I'm the Undertaker.
I tend to the lost and the fallen.
Well, except you.
You're more of a fond and a risen.
Never seen nothing like it.
But I know metal, like they say,
let bygones be bygones.
So bye and gone now.
You don't want no ghouls.
The Undertaker can perform different actions
to help you with felled creatures.
Clear location.
Clear any location of hollow creatures.
The Undertaker will need only a shovel for this service.
Or resurrect.
Bring back recently fallen allies
in exchange for some gold coins.
Interesting.
You clear bodies?
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Okay. I need to go get my stuff and come back here
because I...
Whoa. Where am I?
Oh, I'm over here.
World tomb.
What does this get me?
Use information about this realm.
I got Undertaker lore.
Oh, it's like little lore books.
I get it.
All right. Let me pick up some shit over here.
Deal with the Val Raven.
All right. I can stop dying over and over again.
I love the music.
The music is really good.
What about your house?
Cool.
Something's inside.
How can I open this?
What's that?
I need a lockpick.
I don't have any food.
Yeah. I got to get some new recipes or something.
I got to stop dying out in that world.
How do I get that?
Oh, I have an idea.
Will this work?
Can I like throw it into the chandelier?
I don't think so.
How do I knock that down?
Look, it's at least he's getting sponsored by a game
that actually looks pretty fun.
So that is some bullshit.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. This is I'm saying this is pretty fun.
I did my research.
I'll go back to him.
This is, yeah, this is sponsored.
Okay. I was overburdened, which is interesting.
Um, looks good.
It does look, yeah.
The game looks good.
What can I make?
I just got to, I got to go get my shit.
All right. Go, go, go, go, go.
Go get your stuff.
I need raw, I mean, I need meat for the dog
because the dog needs like to eat one more.
Are you okay?
The dog's really hungry.
All right. Dog is very hungry.
What's this? Eggs?
Ooh, egg, shell.
What's in here?
This looks like an animal feeder
could come in handy when nourishing tamed creatures.
If you can get some in here.
Ah, is this game open world?
I, yeah, this feels pretty open world to me.
Open world, crafting, dangerous, risky.
You can lose all your stuff.
It checks a lot.
It's 87% right now.
I got to get my stuff and get out of here.
Where is it?
Yeah, I got to bring this stuff back and research it.
Where's my stuff?
Shit, I don't know.
It's up here somewhere, right?
He's lying down right next to it.
Come on.
All right.
I have no stamina, but I can get it.
Wait, I'm going to be overburdened.
These are supposed to be damaged potions.
I'm going to be overburdened.
All right.
Just how do I drop stuff?
How do I drop?
I'm dead.
No, no, no, no, no.
Just drop everything.
Oh my God.
I'm dead again.
This stuff is dead.
This stuff is gone.
This stuff is actually gone.
I couldn't run.
I was overburdened.
Fuck.
All right.
It's surrounded by animals.
I can't.
Okay.
What do I do about this?
I think I just have to lose that.
Will the undertaker help?
Okay.
He's camping my gear.
That guy's camping my gear and it's not fair.
He followed me around.
He camping me.
He's camping me.
Okay.
Should I wait?
Maybe I'll go to sleep.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can do this.
Corruption Storm was wiping out this air.
Wait.
This one that I'm in right now?
What?
Okay.
Looming vines.
I'll read that later.
Wait.
Would this actually come over here?
I got so screwed.
I died.
Oh, okay.
It's gone.
Okay.
The plan is there.
I'm going to go pick up my stuff.
No.
I have a better idea.
I'm going to...
Is there a sneak?
That guy's lying down next to my backpack.
Any more food?
He's lying.
Look at him.
He's lying down next to my backpack.
I can't...
If I pick that up...
I was going to pick up the randoms.
I got to run.
Here we go.
Ready?
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'll drop it off.
Just get him away from it.
Okay.
Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
All right.
Now I'm going to go turn this in.
Okay.
We're good.
No, I don't want to take all.
If I take all, I'm going to be over encumbered
and I'm going to be walking like two miles per hour
and he's going to kill me.
When a creature becomes restless,
their base stats change and they gain strength
but also lose stamina.
Make sure to keep an eye on your followers
when they are in this state
as they turn to ashes when felled.
What?
What's wrong with me?
What happened to me?
What happened?
Why am I a skeleton?
I turned into a skeleton.
Okay.
Let me go back here and deposit this.
I turned into a skeleton.
All right.
Let me put this stuff away
and then I'm going to dump this
and go get more of it.
Zura, do I have a container here?
You turn into a skeleton when you die?
I've died a couple of times.
Maybe I'm dying too much.
What have I said down?
The restless never tire.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Now, let me drop this up.
I can't.
I don't have any stamina anymore.
Is there no more requests?
Okay.
Drop this to the house.
Very cool.
All right.
Research.
There we go.
Charcoal, sulfur, shells.
Do I not?
I don't have a potion yet that I've learned.
Not yet.
All right.
Let's dump some of this stuff here.
Okay.
What?
How do I use this?
All right.
Switch it.
I want to put away like all these berries.
I'm 25 out of 40.
I'll keep the logs away.
They're heavy.
Scrap.
Portable app I'll keep.
I don't know if these damage potions really do anything.
All right.
Now I'm more confident.
I'll go in there and get it.
Okay.
I should have enough room now.
So the food doesn't do anything either.
But the portable app.
I should be able to carry everything now.
Your guy ain't ripped.
He'll die in two.
Yeah.
I should be able to go pick up the rest of this.
And then I need to pick up more stuff to examine.
Right?
I didn't pick up my weapon, did I?
No, but I'm going to carry these.
Okay.
Scary guys over there.
So these are they're just animals but they're like corrupted.
Please don't kill me.
You can heal them.
I need to learn how to make like a healing potion.
Where's my stuff?
Don't kill me.
Goodbye.
There's a chest right here.
All right.
Don't take too much shit.
Don't take too much stuff.
I got to get out of here.
All right.
Get me out.
Fast travel.
Oh crap.
All right.
I'm good.
Now I actually can research.
I'm getting out of here.
How do I heal this skeleton problem?
How do I get rid of the skeleton?
I'm looking at my skeleton.
All right.
I can research more.
How do I get that?
Oh wait.
Really?
I can't just like shake it loose.
Crawl.
Looks like a rat hole.
I need to cure myself.
I got to figure out.
I got to find a cure.
All right.
Shell.
I need one more shell to learn what it does.
All right.
How am I doing on stuff?
I got a lot of eggs.
Portable lab.
That's really heavy.
I should get rid of it.
I didn't want to drink that potion
and I'm going to fucking die if I do that again accidentally.
See.
Wait.
What's this?
Oh yeah.
I picked that up.
What is it?
Sealed message.
Can I open it?
Oh shit.
Hey this glass.
I got glass.
Cooking recipe.
Check this out.
Did you see the banana bros?
I have glass, right?
What's in there?
Coin.
Cooking recipe.
What was that?
Aging.
Cooking recipe.
Rustic apple tart.
Beef and eggs.
What else?
A maturing effect that increases the user's age.
So somebody can drink this?
So I can...
What if I drink this?
I'm a skeleton already.
Did I get a new...
No.
I got to pick up more stuff.
Okay.
Deposit everything.
Should I just go die somewhere?
How do I heal?
Okay.
I'm going to put most of this stuff away.
It's a lab away too.
I don't need it.
Textiles.
Torch.
Yeah.
Let's go with the fresh tart there.
Maybe I should keep a few of these.
Can I eat this?
I'll keep the torch.
Oh.
I'm going to go get fish.
That sounds like a good idea.
Do you have a code so we can let the devs know
that we learned about the game from you?
No.
I just get it.
I don't have like a code or anything.
Okay.
Catch fish.
Did it work?
Why are they skeletons?
Fish bone?
No.
I want fish.
Not fish.
Why are we all dead?
How many can I catch?
Should I go to a different water?
These fish bones are ancient
but they could work as ingredients
for advanced potions.
It's important to be careful not all things
that hide beneath the surface of treasure.
Kind of ominous.
Ooh.
Raw fishes.
No.
Yeah.
There's no code.
All right.
Research.
Okay.
I need four more fish bones
and I'll have...
All right.
I'm actually kind of into this.
Four more.
I think I have enough.
One.
Two.
The channel description is an affiliate link.
Yeah.
That link should work.
I have a panel where if you click the panel
it'll take you to the store page
and on the tweet too.
All right.
That should be good.
Yeah.
It's for pretty much all the major consoles.
Steam.
$17.99.
I don't know.
I think it's $17.99 on Steam.
I don't know if it's the same.
Wait a minute.
Ten.
Wait.
Everybody hold on.
I think I just figured it out.
Yeah.
I absolutely did.
Here we go.
I got it.
Check this out.
Add.
Ten.
Vitality.
Right?
Make a shitload of them.
Okay.
Now.
What's wrong with me?
All right.
Drink that.
Drink.
Ugh.
Why am I still old?
He's making potions in the bathroom.
I'm not leaving the house.
Oh, it's in the wasteland.
Okay.
I can't sleep.
Sorry.
Wipe my lip again.
Making potions in the toilet.
I should cook some.
All right.
Let me cook.
How many eggs can I?
Can I just cooked egg?
Oh, all right.
Let's do.
Oh, wait.
I need to do this.
Beef and eggs.
Oh, okay.
So this is one egg and one raw meat.
Get a beef and eggs and I'll make a shitload of sunny side up eggs.
Okay.
So I got beef and eggs.
Go kick the vines.
Yeah.
I need to, I need to not wait.
I think I have some knowledge on it, right?
What does this do?
Oh, I think I'm very overburdened.
Can I hold the axe as a chicken?
All right.
I need to get back.
I need to get back in the house because I need to deposit some stuff.
Is there, I'm overburdened with the chicken.
So you can turn into different animals.
Can I fly?
Oh, okay.
I get it.
All right.
Now we're going back out there and I'm going to go collect some more stuff.
Okay.
I can't do any of that.
Anything that is not.
Okay.
I have, charcoal has been researched.
What does charcoal do for me now?
I think I just know about it.
Deposit some stuff.
All right.
Put this away.
Keep like five ass sunny side up eggs.
I can probably cook the raw fish.
Get rid of the logs.
Beef and eggs keep it.
Scrap, get rid of it.
The potions, get rid of it.
All right.
I'm at 25 out of 40, which, oh, use that.
I learned about moonstone.
And I have a torch.
All right.
I'm ready to go back out there.
I'm ready to check it out.
What are your thoughts on the game so far?
I think, I actually think it's really interesting.
I'm really, it's actually fun.
Okay.
When I like die over and over again in a game.
And I, I don't know, there's like animals and stuff.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Can I do anything with you?
The wild dog is really hungry, but I don't know.
I, I cooked all the food.
Let me go get some meat.
This time I'm not running straight.
I'm running to the right.
It's pretty, it's really relaxing.
I'm very interested in kind of how elaborate it actually is.
Cause there's like followers, there's pets.
You can, what's this?
Chances coin can be found here.
Tomato, egg, apple can be found here.
This is random.
So wait, there's a chance that that will be there now.
I still will deal with this shit up here.
All right.
We got some wild dogs.
Four out of 15.
One of the 15 wild.
Are they different?
Investigate the corrupted tree.
Can I, is that thing there?
I think the thing's gone.
Investigate it.
How do I investigate it?
I can, I can, hold on.
I have a question.
This is a healing potion.
Can I like throw it at this and will it heal this?
Right?
Will this do anything?
I don't think so.
All right.
I gotta be careful that corruption thing's coming.
Like I'm so, I gotta get some more materials.
Go look in the hole.
Put vessel?
Corruption is specifically, especially powerful, but there's a spot here between the tree roots.
Something could be placed to heal it from the inside.
I need to put a vessel there.
Okay.
Interesting.
I'm going over here for a minute.
There was a chest right here that I get it.
What's this stuff?
Fuck you.
That just scared the shit out of me now I'm poisoned.
Hold on.
There's nothing even in there.
13 ticks of poison.
How much is it doing?
One.
What else was there?
Something else over here, wasn't there?
What was that?
Swamplich.
What do you like?
Do you like stuff?
Can I have this as a pet?
That's kind of cool.
For now, I want more materials.
I feel like it's about, that guy has a shovel and I'm going to kill him for it.
That guy has a shovel and I need it and I'm going to take it from him.
Do not kill me.
If this guy kills me with a shovel, I'm going to be pissed.
Stop.
Wait, mine's been broke?
I'm good.
Shovel, egg, and an axe recipe.
Oh, there we go.
That's what I want.
Okay.
I know I can make an axe.
I have the shovel, the stuff that I can dig up.
Cool.
I got a minute.
I don't have any worms.
Oh, hello.
Okay.
I learned more about you.
Very cool.
I did more damage with my hands.
That's kind of funny.
All right.
I'm going to go back and make an axe.
No, I need aging.
Oh, I need to make an axe and I have to come and kill this thing.
That's the play.
The play is to make an axe, make some potions, and then come kill this thing.
You need to cure it.
Don't kill it.
I need, I don't have enough materials to do that.
Wait, pick these up.
I could have just walked over there.
Are you serious?
I walked up the other side.
So if I make a bunch of healing potions, I can cure that instead of kill it.
All right.
I need to get materials.
It's aloe and then some fish bones.
All right.
More rats, wild rat.
You can learn about them and then eventually you can tame them, I think.
Sword can be found here on random chance.
I would love a sword.
All right.
I'm not messing around here.
What the fuck is that thing?
What is that thing?
Is that thing, is that thing hostile?
A fawn.
Let's get a bunch of chicken friends on learn about them.
Chicken.
I'm not fucking with that.
All right.
I got to leave.
Bring sanctum to the cursed tree.
All right.
I got to get out of here.
Oh, another message.
These have recipes in them.
All right.
Get me out of here.
Sit back.
All right.
Cool.
I think I made some progress.
I think that means I'm wet.
They're all going to die of corruption.
I think they leave.
I need one more mandragora and I know what it does.
I need fish bones.
I got all kinds of bullshit in my inventory.
All right.
What about making the axe?
I think I have a lot of materials.
Did you get chin surgery?
All right.
What do you think?
Do you think it looks good?
Oh, I need to learn it.
Axe recipe.
Do I have any more recipes to dip?
What's that?
Stag recipe?
It's a stag.
I know how to make a stag.
What's a stag?
Wood, wood, wood.
What is a stag?
I have that, don't I?
Why is it not my inventory?
I thought I had some scrap metal.
Did I not?
I'm sorry.
I know I'm supposed to be feeding you.
All right.
Well, I can't do that anyways.
Can't sleep.
So I did it.
Was it in the box?
I think it was in here.
You're in the food tab at the research table.
You can change tabs research more.
Really?
Well, I've had a bunch of wood.
I just didn't take it.
I like watching the funny man.
Thank you.
I think it's just whatever you have available.
But there should be stuff in here.
Yeah, here we go.
Just take it.
So now I should be able to do a bunch more.
Yeah.
What about cooking?
Make a fish?
Seared fish?
I'm going to hold on to the eggs
because I don't want to use all these.
So let's go back.
Okay, I have...
Right, the digging spaces.
Right.
Okay.
There was one back here.
Where the...
You should dance for us.
No.
Shut up.
I'm not going to fucking dance.
No.
No weird shit.
This is sponsor segment.
Ooh.
What's that?
I don't have an axe.
There was stuff to dig over here.
Wasn't there?
I swear to God.
Yeah, there was.
Ooh, tea.
I don't feel cold, so I don't eat clothes.
Who the fuck are you?
Ooh.
Create chicken?
A broom recipe.
I can make a broom?
Okay.
Summon a helpful creature that will come to the user's aid.
Do I drink this?
Whoa.
Bold Lush.
Inventory.
Inspect.
Wait.
Go to camp.
Play.
We can play?
I've got a bad old chicken, I think.
I do have a bad old chicken.
Okay, hold on.
And the chicken can hold 10 pounds worth of stuff.
All right.
All right, cool.
What's your deal?
Anastasia.
What are you looking at?
I just, I think I'm going to beat this person up.
I think I'm going to kill this person and take their stuff.
You want an age potion?
Let's just do.
There's also this, which I don't know what to do with this.
All right, what if I throw the age potion at this?
Will it age to death?
That's a decent thought.
Let's play.
All right, let's deposit and then go back out with the shovel.
And I'm going to make an axe.
And I don't know how to be normal again.
I have three healing potions.
Let's deposit this.
No, actually, I need that.
All right, deposit a few eggs.
Deposit the raw fish.
Get rid of the, get rid of the portable lab.
It's just too heavy.
I have the shovel.
I don't need the tea leaves, that many at least.
All right.
Okay, good.
Let's go.
Let's see if I can make a, you know what I'm saying?
Let's make this work.
I'll put the damage potions over here.
Oh, it heals the chicken too.
That's cool.
Can I make a, is the chicken going to disappear?
Oh, I don't think there's a timer.
Doesn't look like it is this timer.
Okay, axe.
Can I not make an axe?
I don't have any wood.
How do I not have any wood?
Are you kidding me?
Didn't I have a shitload of wood?
What happened to it all?
Where's all my wood?
I put it away?
Did I?
I thought I just took it out.
I didn't take it.
So I should be able to make an axe.
Who are these weirdos?
No, see, where is it?
I had like 10 wood.
What happened to it?
I dropped all the rest.
Oh shit.
Well, I have a battle chicken.
I'll be fine.
Hello, Milton.
Oh, you have so much stuff.
I can't just like break this over your head.
I got a battle chicken.
I'll be fine.
Jibber, why are you being so regular?
I have the shovel.
I should be okay.
This is technically a weapon.
So let's go.
I need wood and I need more materials
and I need meat too.
Okay, let's go.
All right, follow me.
Try, just try to kill this thing with a shovel.
That's going to take me a while to heal this thing to death.
Now, there's a lot of chickens here.
All right, discover the chicken.
Interesting.
Oh, I need the mandrake worth.
Watch out.
Get him, get him, get him, get him.
Get him, chicken.
Should I?
All right, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
Don't get killed.
Don't get killed, don't get killed.
I'm going to break this shovel.
I need it.
Oh no, the chicken's dead.
How am I supposed to stop that from happening?
Inspect?
Oh no.
I need the meat.
I need the meat for the dog.
The dog is starving right now.
Shit.
Okay, all right, all right.
I need to hold digging.
The dog eats meat.
I need to feed the dog.
Still can't open that.
All right, 69%.
And there's rats.
These are corrupted rats.
Wait, did it work?
What the?
It doesn't work.
I didn't heal him.
Don't touch me.
Come here.
Get over here.
Healing is not curing?
Where did that thing go?
Come here.
All right, I don't want to die.
All right, we got lots of meat.
I got bones.
This is perfect.
We'll be able to heal the dog.
I killed the chicken.
Well, I didn't mean to kill the chicken.
The chicken died because it was being attacked.
Okay, I think I have enough meat to have the dog be my friend.
Get out of here.
Leave me alone.
You know what?
Okay, discovered that.
Okay, let's go back and feed the dog.
You watch me on a hacked smart fridge.
That's kind of weird.
Your fists are doing more damage than the shovel.
So how do I make a cure?
All right, here we go.
Mandragora.
Completely.
All right, this is change.
Charcoal is...
All right, a mandragora is change?
Something change into something else?
Interesting.
Change.
All right, I need to put in some stuff.
Maybe heal, change?
That's possible.
Let me look at the journal for a second.
Quest.
All right, research shell.
Open the moonstone chest.
Bring sanctum to the curse tree.
Feed the well a hundred times.
Clear the passage.
No requests.
All right, hold on.
Right, here we go.
Charcoal is age.
Fish bones are the thing you need.
It's like a quantity.
Shells, I think, are also that too.
All right, I need fish bones and shells.
That should work.
German, get weird.
Act weird.
I don't need to act weird right now.
Why I gotta act weird?
I don't need to act weird.
You're acting weird.
You're being weird.
All right, I should be able to make some more healing.
I should be able to make some more healing potions.
Is that weird for you?
Do you get botox?
No, I don't.
I don't get botox.
Why do people think I get botox?
Why is it a thing I'm seeing recently?
Ah, dude, so you get like botox.
What?
See?
You're making me lose materials right now.
All right, I'm done.
Look.
See those wrinkles?
Too close.
Way too close.
Okay, here we go.
Vitality, add.
What about remove 10 vitality, right?
Add 10 vitality.
What about remove 10 vitality?
That's like a damage potion?
Remove 10 change.
Okay, all right.
So I need more aloe.
Get berries too.
Okay, that satisfied us for the next 30 minutes.
Good.
I'll go ahead and smash her in the head.
Who is this person?
Bridget?
Whoa, you have a snake.
So what are you doing here?
Do you want to share this?
You have two pieces of hair and a shovel.
What about your little snake friend?
Snake.
Oh, I can feed the snake.
The creature already has a master.
Yeah, I can't throw this at this lady, right?
No, I'm going to be a menace.
I don't want to do that right now.
I would be a menace.
I need to get wood and charcoal.
I need to cure or kill that creature.
All right, cook.
I need to make a regular steak to feed the dog.
And then maybe the dog can come with me.
The dog can probably come with me.
A hunger obtained.
A coin obtained.
Wait, what?
Makes the target hungrier.
What's the application for that?
I know you want to eat.
I know.
I got you.
Don't worry.
I have some raw meat.
I need to cook it.
Is there a fire right here?
Oh, shit.
How can people have highlighted purple chats?
Well, that's because they are using channel points.
A revitalizing potion to reduce.
Does that work?
Would this technically turn me away from a skeleton?
Okay, that's not working.
All right, I just want to make a couple of choices.
I'll make three choice steaks.
I don't have any wood.
God damn it.
I need I need wood.
Oh, this guy has his hair.
I need wood.
Where do I get wood?
All right, stop.
I need better planning.
This is to go to the cemetery.
I need where did I get the wood last time?
Just breaking boxes.
All right, I'm going to teleport over there again.
I still have the shovel.
I have a torch too.
Wait, will this work?
Hold on.
Let me try something.
Will this stop this?
Oh, it does.
All right, all right, all right.
I got something.
Set on fire.
Oh, yeah.
I thought I could use a regular torch.
So where does this go?
Pack.
Fish bones.
Chicken form.
I can go to the pier.
Why is this different?
Music change.
Pick lock recipe.
Get away from me.
Get away.
Leave me alone.
Don't take anything.
Get out of here.
Oh, I can open the chest now.
That chest that needs a lockpick.
I can open it.
Coins.
We're purple pals.
All right, I don't want to get killed.
The worms.
Okay.
Ooh, what's over there?
I think I have to rebuild the bridge probably.
Looks like the Wild West.
Press this phone.
I don't want to kill this, but is it hostile?
It's not.
I do want the fish bones, but I don't want to kill it.
Where's my shovel?
We got what was that?
Restlessness?
Transforms the target into a restless version of himself.
Can I turn this into a chicken with this?
Is that how that works?
Like, if I threw that at the big scary guy,
would it turn into a chicken?
I'm going to try it.
Oh, shit.
Who's this?
I need wood.
So bad.
Put this away.
I'm going to put a lot of these potions away
because I really don't know what to do with them.
Put the heavy stuff away.
Oh, pick lock.
Yep.
I'll keep the damage.
I'll keep the spores.
Is there a bench?
You got a bench in here?
It's been a long time since I last seen one of your kind here at me docks.
I'd be the harbormaster,
welcomer of lost souls,
receiver of others' gold,
and ye came seeking respite from the Vanlands, eh?
What says he, warden?
Can you bargain for a few companion souls?
The pier is a grim place where you can find souls bound to a nameless ship.
The only way to set them free is to bargain with the harbormaster using gold coins.
They will become followers.
So no ship, no business.
Come back later.
Is it one dollar right here?
How much money do I have?
I have 81 bucks.
Oh, it's counting it.
I get it.
When that fills up, it'll be here.
Okay.
Well, I know how to do a lockpick now.
Hi, Andrew.
You have a little chicken.
That's such a funny companion.
Your two companions are like a baby chicken.
I want that.
He takes one glance over and sees that we're still doing the same shit.
Oh, yeah.
I take a quick look over and I see the redeeming winks.
That hasn't been a thing in like three years.
Okay, so that opens the pier.
I need...
Where do I get wood?
Reliably.
Okay.
I need wood.
Otherwise, I can't feed the dog.
I have no weapons.
I'm fucked.
I have this.
This is it.
That's all I have.
In barrels, maybe?
Where was I getting wood before?
These mushrooms?
Ooh, cut mushroom.
Oh, fuck.
94%.
Get out.
I got more...
Get me out.
We got a double wink?
Oh, there's a new one.
Damage potions, rejuvenation potions, and aging potions.
I think I have a couple of these, don't I?
Okay.
I already have these in my inventory.
Where's my money?
Oh, it just goes right in your inventory.
Okay.
Oh, you ordered that.
R1, R1, R1, R1.
This thing is still here.
Can I pick this up?
Oh, your lockpick recipe.
Thank you.
More research.
Okay.
I need logs, bones, spores, sulfur.
I can make some more potions.
Vitality.
I need aloe.
I don't need more worms, do I?
No.
I need aloe.
Do remove plus restless.
Ah, will that actually work?
Remove...
I don't have...
Wait, will that actually work?
Do you hide money in your walls?
No.
Remove...
What was restless?
Charcoal?
I don't have any charcoal.
I need to...
I need to cut a tree down, but I need...
I don't have an axe.
I can make these.
Add...
Yeah.
Give me some healing potions.
All right.
That's literally 10 healing potions.
I'm unstoppable.
Okay.
Restlessness.
Change restlessness.
I need to remove restlessness.
Don't...
No.
Stop drinking it.
Don't do that again.
All right.
I'm good.
I need...
Portable lab is just wasting much.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right.
I'm going up there.
I don't care if I get killed.
I have some decent money too.
What can I do with it?
Is this like Terraria?
Maybe a little.
I can make a room.
I just need...
I'm just going on a wood collection.
I don't care if I have to punch a tree.
I don't care.
I'm going to go punch a tree
until I get enough berries.
My character sucks.
I did it.
I did it to myself.
All right.
You're hungry, but you eat raw meat, right?
Want some more?
Right, dear.
Ooh.
Okay.
This thing's actually pretty powerful.
I don't want this to die.
Let's play.
I really don't want this thing to die,
but I need its help.
So we're going to go.
I need wood.
Fucking...
No.
All right.
Wood.
I need this fucking tree to go down.
All right.
Can I blow it up or something?
Shells, right?
Okay.
Be careful.
Don't get killed, dear.
I need wood.
It's going to die.
It's not going to die.
I can teleport.
Just don't aggro the huge thing.
I need logs so bad.
All right.
Wait here.
Don't go anywhere.
Am I opening this?
Did it open?
Okay.
I guess that's a lot.
I got a sword recipe now.
Okay.
Now we just need logs.
Now come with me.
Follow me.
Help me find logs.
All right.
I'm just killing that thing, by the way.
I'm making a sword.
I'm going to kill it.
A ship with fresh shells.
Okay.
Watch out.
Don't let it blow up on you.
We got to kill this thing.
All right.
Good work.
Dog's actually really good.
Very powerful.
Highly recommend.
52%.
All right.
I need logs.
Got to get it.
Okay.
Where do I find logs without an axe?
Don't just kill random...
All right.
No, no, no.
We're getting close.
Wait.
No, no.
Don't eat these.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You don't...
That's not...
Don't do that.
They're so cute.
All right.
You have moonstone and a wild chicken.
I got a moonstone.
Okay.
Percy?
Is that bad?
Oops.
Oh, I got a ghoul.
Wait, what's that?
Should I not have done that?
Oops.
Well, they were like corrupted.
They were like a corrupted skeleton person.
I had to fucking kill them.
Okay.
How are you doing on health?
Are you okay?
You're good, right?
All right.
Seriously, I need logs.
How was I getting them before?
I don't remember.
Save that guy.
He's already dead.
All right.
There's a torch.
This is that multiplayer?
I don't think so.
Where can I get some logs to make some stuff?
I think I just sapped this whole place of logs.
Okay.
I don't want to fuck with this thing.
What's fighting?
Look, they're in here.
I just can't get them.
No, don't heal them, you idiot.
What are you doing?
Put that away.
The dog.
No.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Take this.
We're good.
That was actually scary.
Okay.
What's wrong with them?
Is he okay?
Don't get involved.
Just clean up.
Okay.
I've discovered the little chicks.
Pick up the logs that you dropped.
Where did I drop them?
There's so much bullshit over here.
Up there, right?
By the sulfur.
You could have accepted Assassin's Creed DLC sponsorship.
Why would I do that?
Stop healing them, you dummy.
But instead you took a cool indie sponsor.
Yeah.
This game is fun.
I actually think the game is pretty good.
It's definitely worth playing.
All right.
Give me all this.
Did I already go through 10 potions?
How did I do that?
Oh, wait.
I can...
Can I do this?
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Hold on.
If I give you a bunch of stuff, you can take it back to town.
Is it as it works?
Take like all this shit.
Take like ghoul skin.
Take the hair.
Take all this.
Boon Stone.
Pump.
Yeah.
Just take a bunch of stuff back to town.
Actually, we got to both go like right now.
We're good.
Okay.
Thank you.
Appreciate the help.
I'll take everything.
What's going on?
Why am I glowing?
All right.
We got out in time.
Okay.
Ghoul skin, hair.
I need 15 hairs.
Shell.
Okay.
Shell is five.
It's five instead of 10.
Cool.
So add five vitality is a potion.
It's a regular healing potion.
All right.
The person who said he's acting like he does when he plays multiplayer games is right.
You want to do a TikTok dance?
Will that make you happy?
You want to go do a TikTok dance?
You want to go put like something like you want to put something in my eyes?
Should I do a TikTok dance?
Will that make you happy?
There you go.
Slow that down.
Slow that down to like 0.2.
All right.
How are you doing on food?
Are you hungry?
I think you're hungry.
Yeah.
We do eat anything besides just raw meat because that's kind of hard to get.
Let's see.
What else do you like?
Baked meat pie.
But I only have one baked meat pie.
All right.
You can have it.
Oh, you don't like it.
Someone slow it down.
Well, just give me the clip.
I'll slow it down for you.
Please do the router turn off joke right now.
Let me sit.
Let's watch it right now.
Will that make you happy?
You want to go put like something like you want to put something in my eyes?
Let's take a look.
Let's see if it looks any good.
Slow it down.
Do a TikTok dance.
Will that make you happy?
You want to go for a TikTok dance?
You want to go put like something like you want to put something in my
Okay, let's see.
I did it fast so it could be slowed down and enjoyed.
But that was just a sped up one.
This is what it actually is.
And that made me to be a little slower.
That's fucking terrifying.
That's fucking scary.
That's really scary.
What about faster?
Why do I have such dead eyes?
Look at how dead my eyes are.
That's fucking weird.
I look, my eyes look dead.
Right?
I was like, this is weird.
Psycho eyes.
Okay.
How do I make the sword?
Sword is going to change the whole game here.
I need it.
What do I?
I need a research table.
Let's go.
Okay.
I need to remove.
I need to remove change, right?
Remove change.
Can I actually do that?
Fuck you.
What?
Remove restless.
Agro the fawn near a tree.
It'll knock one over.
Really?
Good to know.
How am I doing on a weight?
Okay.
I'm fine.
Hey, hi.
Why is everybody dead?
Like, why is everybody dead?
I'm dead too.
We're all dead.
Okay.
A sword is three scrap and one wood.
And I really desperately need it.
I need scrap and I need wood.
Bad.
Like, very badly.
And I don't want to put the dog in danger.
So I'm going to tell the dog to go home.
You just go.
Just like, go wander around and go have fun.
I'll come back and see you in a minute.
Be careful though.
Don't get in any trouble.
Okay.
Wood.
Was that fawn?
What's the net?
What do you have for a talking point?
Um, I don't know.
I'll take the torch.
I wish I could just break this down into wood.
Okay.
There's a bunch of bullshit up here.
I can clear it though.
All right.
Wood.
I mean, I have two moonstones, right?
Do I think I can open that chest for free?
Isn't there a chest over here?
I have another moonstone at the back of the house.
I need three.
Get some wood, please.
I'm trying.
Can I just like go buy somebody and have...
Go buy a follower and have them go chop wood for me?
Will they be able to make their own stuff?
I have 41.
I'm fine.
Maybe?
That's possible.
I'll give it a try.
Hide.
Really?
Stealth mode allows you to pickpocket.
But use this cautiously as it'll draw attention to you and blow your cover.
Oh, I'm just like in a bush.
That's kind of funny.
Wait, can I pickpocket this person?
Bailey.
How do I do it?
This person is st...
What are the...
Will they have glass?
How do I pickpocket?
Steel.
Oh, I took the glass out of your hand.
And all the pumpkins you have.
And a bunch of meat that you had.
Okay.
All right.
Try a follower?
What am I doing?
Bro, what?
What?
They're corrupted.
They're like zombies.
I have to get rid of them.
All right.
Let me try that thing with that person over at the fawn.
What happened to the big boss thing that was over here?
It's not here anymore.
I haven't seen it.
It's up in the northwest.
All right.
I want to see if I can get the...
The person said get a fawn.
If I get a fawn, then I can have them knock a tree over, right?
Claw amulet.
Cool.
Oh, what's that?
That's new.
Raw meat.
Good.
It's ore.
I'm fine.
I need that fawn.
Don't worry, guys.
He's doing the softlock route on purpose.
This is not the softlock route.
Why does this run heavenly?
All right.
Come with me and I want you to break some stuff for me.
Can I like talk to this guy?
Okay.
So you're saying walk the fawn over to a tree and he will destroy it.
I didn't get softlocked.
I'm fine.
All right.
Come down here.
Come break this.
Just so I don't get softlocked.
It's the moonstone effect.
All right.
Come on.
Move.
I have to punch him.
That chicken just ran into the pole and died.
All right.
Knock this stuff down.
Did it work?
It worked.
Holy shit.
They were right.
Oh, my God.
You actually weren't kidding.
All right.
Get this one, too.
I need like 10 at least.
Don't kill your own stuff.
Do the big AOE.
Break it.
All right.
That's like two more.
Get away from me.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
This one over here.
It's 80 percent.
I'm good.
I bet you'd get something crazy if you kill this thing.
Just come take all the trees down
so I can come here with a sword and an axe.
You still chasing me?
Killed the chicken, too.
No, that would be poisoned.
All right.
Just knock these down and I'm out of here.
I'll leave after you do this.
I promise.
I'm not going to kill the chicken for no reason.
All right.
This one, too.
Thank you.
Just kicked me in the fucking face.
Don't die to this.
Come on.
Do I have any healing potions left?
Why is he so?
Why are you so much faster now?
This guy is a thousand miles per hour now.
Just kick this, please.
All right.
Fuck off.
Goodbye.
Now I can make some stuff.
All right.
I need damage plus healing plus rejuvenation, aging, healing.
I can do that.
I can do this one.
Yep.
Okay.
Take the money.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
How much more do I need?
I got this new thing.
Thorner.
It's fun just to go pick up the stuff and then put it in here.
Okay.
I need.
So let's take this.
I will make charcoal, right?
Won't I?
I'm going to make some steak for my friend.
Yep.
Cooking gives you charcoal.
Okay.
Let me go feed my friend.
It's a calm game with an ice streamer.
Yeah, this is I can give you my thoughts.
It seems elaborate enough and it seems big enough.
I don't know how much bigger the world is, but I'm assuming there's probably more like
all the way up here.
It seems cute.
It's fun.
I think I actually think it's good.
I don't think I'm too pea brained to enjoy this either.
I think it's just enough for me to understand.
All right.
This might be stupid.
I'm going to do it.
Contain.
Oh, that's what I was supposed to do.
Oh my goodness.
It's a vessel.
I need a human follower to pick this up.
What?
How?
Okay.
All right.
Slow down.
I need to go.
Oh, shit.
All right.
That's what you have to do.
That's the money sink.
All right.
How much is it for?
That doesn't disappear, right?
Hope not.
How much does it cost?
I wonder.
I love I keep asking you guys as if you guys are going to know.
Maybe you do.
Maybe you guys have already played it.
So the boat, the boats here and I need a follower.
I need a follower to go pick that thing up.
Cooking recipe.
Guys, this is smoked fish pasty.
All right.
I'm just going to hang on here for a second.
Explore the map more.
I have to do this first part here.
I can't go up or I don't think I can go anywhere until I do that first little tutorial zone.
What's the downside to being restless?
You don't have stamina and you deal more damage.
Yeah, I actually don't know.
I think it's no stamina.
So no sprinting.
No hunger.
I'm sure I can look it up, right?
Let's see.
Human.
That's what that is, right?
Human with that immunity.
35 health, five attack.
No food and don't age.
Versus two attack, one attack.
What's the green mean?
All right, here we go.
I need a follower.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ratio plus L plus you're a skeleton.
No maidens plus no followers plus L plus ratio.
Oh my God.
Fucking pull in.
Where are you?
There we go.
All right.
Who's here?
Fish spawn.
Okay.
What else?
Well, there's a book.
Is anybody on the boat?
The boat's empty.
Are they on the side?
Wait, maybe I just talked to one.
Oh, the fog.
Make me peer so pretty.
You can hardly see the misery in them.
Oh, okay.
Oh, you guys have only eight bucks.
Oh, 12 health, 25 stamina.
You got a hair, a torch, and a pumpkin.
All right, dude.
I don't know about you.
Clement, three.
This is a kid.
This is like a fucking five-year-old.
Okay, Julie, 10.
You got metal scrap on you too.
I wish I had 84.
All right.
How many people can I hire?
Just take them all.
Okay, come with me.
All right, nobody walk off the edge, please.
Okay, I need somebody to pick up this thing over here.
You can go with a whole party?
That's actually kind of funny.
How many people can you have?
Okay, so we're going to go.
Let's make sure everyone's equipped.
Don't step on anything.
Be careful.
You should light your torch over here.
Hey, give me the thing.
I'll light it for you and hand it back to you.
How do I want to light this?
What's wrong with me?
Oh, whatever.
I don't care.
Just take it.
Okay, let's go.
Can I have them like collect berries and shit?
Do you pick berries up?
Inspect, wait, wander, play.
Wait, what?
Come with me.
I need somebody to pick this up
and I need you to put it down on the corrupted area.
Follow me.
Wait, who should pick it up?
Should I have the kid pick it up?
This chat is so fucking funny.
Yeah, they're fun.
Okay, pick it up.
Get it.
Now bring it with me.
This kid is so slow.
Who's this kid?
All right, we just need to bring this over to the thing
and put it down and I heal the tree.
Problem solved.
Don't drop that.
Keep going.
All right, put it right here.
Right here.
Drop it.
Put it down.
Okay.
No, put it down right here.
Put it down right here.
Put it down.
All right, now what?
Do I have to break it?
Oh god, what's happening?
Is it working?
I think it's working.
Is this working?
Should I break it?
Fuck.
No, get out of here.
Get out of the way.
What happened?
Why is it not?
What did it turn into?
Purifying?
It purifies to...
What the fuck?
I put it on the X.
No, I'm not soft-locked.
I'm fine.
I'm gonna be fine.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
What?
Why did I break it?
I broke it.
We're gonna get out of here.
Bring sanctum to the cursed tree.
Didn't I do that?
Okay.
Where's that fucking huge thing?
I didn't place it on the X.
I mean, I put it right on the X.
All right.
Why don't you just...
Here.
Just...
Why don't you just fucking take this?
Turn into a fucking chicken for all I care.
I need to get rid of stuff.
I can't even eat this.
All right.
I'm almost there.
We're good.
Just go home.
Go back to the camp.
We'll talk later.
No, no, no, no.
Don't fight.
Just leave.
So was that not what I was supposed to do?
I mean, it was like put the vessel on the X.
I put it on the X and I didn't do anything.
What happened?
You dropped it?
You didn't put it.
I almost did it.
Oh, well.
Can I learn anything about these?
Okay.
Here.
I'm going to give you some potions.
Makes sense.
And take some fucking eggs and stuff, too.
You can't have the stick.
That's for the dog.
I'm keeping the beef and eggs.
Okay.
So I needed a hundred more coins to get another one of those vessels.
So you're saying I needed to place it instead of put it.
Is that what you're saying?
There was a put command, but I dropped it.
I feel like I pressed it.
How much money do I have?
All right.
I just need to sell some shit.
I have enough potions to sell stuff.
Hold the button like when you gather.
I think there's some quest to turn it over here.
Okay.
I have aging.
I don't have any aging, do I?
No.
Hey, you know the things I just gave you?
Give them back.
Thank you.
Healing plus, right?
Oh, it's healing.
I have healing plus plus.
Don't I have a bunch of these?
That was a funny joke.
I mean, I thought I was.
I thought I put it down.
Okay.
I need I could equate add age.
Add age.
That's an age potion, right?
Really?
Add this.
What?
What are you talking about?
Add vitality, right?
Yeah, that's it.
Isn't that what I just did?
Wait, if I can I?
Okay, hold on.
Let me turn this on.
Okay.
How much money do I have?
23 damage plus healing plus is done.
Regular healing.
All right.
Aging and then aging plus.
I need to do add and then 10.
Okay.
I think I can do it.
Can you get a cake pop?
Okay.
Add.
I don't have the materials for it.
Did I stash them?
No, I did not.
All right.
I have 38.
But here's the thing.
I think I can use those potions on the big scary raven thing.
Purifying, right?
Will that work?
Maybe I should try to use this on some stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This might work.
Can I actually get in here?
That's a good idea.
That's right.
Oh, all right.
Nice.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Go, go, go, go, go.
What's in here?
Adderstone?
Wait, what's this little guy?
Wait, stop.
Wait, get over here.
What's wrong with this guy?
He's just going to leave.
Okay.
Well, I got an adderstone.
I wonder what that is.
What else is in here?
Sword recipe.
Run.
An ordinary house that can be used for sweeping out dust and uninvited guests.
So it's just kind of a...
What does it do?
Do you want this thing?
I think that's a smelter.
What is this thing?
All right.
I have so much.
I'm going to store the glass.
Watching Jerma play this cured my hemorrhoids.
That's good.
All right.
I got metal scrap.
Come on.
Just get up the stairs.
You know you can get there.
I'll get there.
I'll get there soon.
Don't worry.
I'm there.
That's a I shit my pants walk if I've ever seen it.
I mean, I'm just like a thing of bones.
I'm like a bag of bones.
I need to get 15 of these.
Okay.
Store some of this stuff because I don't need like all this glass.
Inventory full.
Yeah.
Put it away.
You can't take any more.
I'm trying to put it away.
How do I put it away?
Put wait.
Huh?
Can I not put the glass away?
I'm going to go make an axe.
I think I can make a sword now.
Okay.
Let me make an axe.
But my hemorrhoids are still there.
Hey, you.
Wait, you're not my friend.
Fuck off.
Okay.
I'm I still got money.
I'm going to try to cure.
I want to purify that thing.
The scary thing.
Okay.
Stag.
Axe.
Pick lock.
I want one of these.
I want an axe.
And I want a pick lock.
But I only I can't do two.
What's this?
What is a stag?
It's like you pick up hot coals with.
What is that?
Well, I need an axe.
I'm not going to make it.
Can I just make two?
Maybe I should make a stag.
I don't know what it does.
Remove three vitality.
That's it.
I don't know.
I'll make two axes though.
I feel like I need it.
How's the dog?
I have a chicken now.
Oh, wait.
This is all right.
This is Julie.
I forgot.
How do I turn Julie back?
Oh, God.
Okay, Julie.
Julie, I'm going to take your stuff.
Three metal scraps.
Oh, yeah.
Here, come here.
I need you to take some shit from me.
So you stay right there.
Take a bunch of this bullshit.
Here, take this.
Take a couple pieces of glass.
Take a hair.
Take two fucking pumpkins for all I care.
I need to go make a sword.
I got to turn.
Julie back to a human, I think.
Sword.
Do I make a sword or do I make a picklock?
What do I want?
Picklock is for the chest right outside the door.
Or do I just have a sword and kill stuff?
What do you think?
Oh, come on.
Really?
I need charcoal by cooking food first.
Okay, I think I have food to make.
I'll make it.
I don't think I need the sword.
I feel the sword is not going to help me.
It's already have an axe.
I can make cooked mushrooms.
Okay, that should be enough.
There you go.
Okay, now I can make the picklock and I'll go open that thing.
How much money do you have?
I think I'm just going to kill you and take your money.
Honestly, these guys have five, ten bucks each.
These dudes got five to ten dollars each.
I mean, I need money.
I fucked up the last thing I was trying to do.
Okay, can I make more than one?
I'll make two.
All right, let's go feed the dog and feed this guy too.
You want some food?
You want some shrooms?
Here, you want it?
No, I can't.
I can't feed anybody fried mushrooms.
All right, here we go.
Steak.
I think you're hungry.
You should just come with me too.
Should I bring the chicken?
Free?
Okay, you should be well fed.
All right, you two follow me because I need the help here.
Let's go.
Put on the axe.
Let's go try to make some more money.
Eighty nine percent already.
The lockpick thing is right there.
All right, like just hold on.
I can't sleep, so I can't pass time.
I can't.
I don't have time to get it.
Can I?
I can wait in the menu, right?
I thought I could.
Yeah, wait.
Waiting.
Okay, what time is it?
Is it good?
Oh, shit.
No, it takes like five seconds to get through.
Okay, wait.
I wonder what the timer is like.
Kill Julie.
I'm not going to kill Julie.
Why would I go kill?
I mean, Julie is...
I need to fix.
I need to fix Julie.
All right, it's currently going on.
I need to do a remove change on Julie.
Well, maybe Julie should just come with us.
Okay, if Julie comes with us, Julie's going to die.
So I'm not doing that.
All right, there's the storm.
Storm is there.
I'll try to purify the big giant raven dog thing.
See if it works.
Are you not live?
Really?
No, I'm not.
I'm not live right now.
I recorded this and then put it up.
There's a video and I streamed it.
And then I downloaded that stream.
And then that's the one that you're seeing now.
All right, let's go.
One percent.
I got plenty of time.
I want to open the chest up here.
And then I'm going to try to throw one of those
purifying pushes at the big scary thing.
Where is that chest?
It's like right here, isn't it?
Wasn't it like right here?
Where is it?
Where was that chest?
Oh, yeah, I think this is...
Guys, get it.
Kill it.
Thank you.
Why is this hurting me?
All right, I need to drink something.
Where's that lockpick thing?
Wasn't it like right here?
I need this.
Where's my friend?
What happened?
What happened to Clemens?
Where's Clemens?
Where did Clemens go?
I sent him home.
Oh, I pressed A on him.
He's not dead.
Let me see if this works.
Don't think that's...
I think that's locked.
Let me find that thing, though.
Is this a lock chest?
I have three moon stones.
Oh, fuck off with this.
What do I get rid of?
Here, come here.
You have inventory, right?
Take like everything.
Okay, there you go.
What the fuck happened?
Are we all right?
Dog, dog, dog, dog, dog, dog, dog.
Run, run, run.
Run over, get over.
Please don't die.
Don't die.
That'd be so awful if you do.
Go home, go home, go home.
Go, go home.
Leave, go home.
I don't want you...
Just don't die.
Leave.
Don't walk home.
Run home.
Don't walk home, run home.
Just run.
He's gonna get...
He's gonna step on something.
He's gonna fucking die.
Don't be quick about it.
Go home.
Is that gonna...
Is he gonna die?
I can't heal him.
Oh, he's over in comfort.
Hold on.
I'll fix it.
He can always die.
He's got three pounds.
He's gonna be okay.
I think he's gonna be fine.
I'm gonna purify that giant alien.
Let's purify this.
It doesn't work.
More than one?
It worked.
Um, what do I do?
Do I feed it?
What does it want?
What does it eat?
Would you eat worms?
What kind of food do they eat?
Favorite food?
I don't know.
Maybe it's the same thing.
I don't have anything.
Okay, here we go.
Chest.
Open.
Skeleton key.
Choose a direction in which to move your pick lock.
Be aware that choosing the wrong direction will force you to start over.
Okay.
Pick lock.
Um, up, down, no.
Okay, up, up, down, down.
Up, up, down, up.
I'll take the whole thing, please.
Cool.
Okay.
That's an interesting concept.
So wait.
So I can throw the anti-corruption thing on these guys, right?
That would, that should work.
Porter and Benson.
All right, let me try it.
Shit, it wasn't enough.
Didn't work, so you decide to kill them.
I mean, what am I, what am I supposed to do?
All right, I'm heading back.
Oh, I can't move when I'm like this.
Uh, 46.
Add one perk?
I wonder what the bottles do.
Um, all right, I'm just gonna like, get this.
Is that enough?
Okay.
No.
Let's eat something.
Okay.
Let me get rid of the tea leaves.
Oh, I don't even need.
Okay, I don't need the fucking five torches.
Okay.
Did you have anything else?
All right, let's go back.
How's the spice rack coming?
It's coming along.
All right, good.
You made it back.
You got a whole inventory full of shit, right?
31.
Hydration check.
You got it.
Is this game to the end of the stream?
The end of the stream is probably happening soon here.
How long did we stream for?
Like seven hours?
I want a skeleton frog.
How do you get this?
You have like cool pets.
That's not fair.
And then you guys will see me again on Monday.
This game looks cute.
It is cute.
It's far more efficient ways to play this game.
I am certain of it, but I'm having a good time.
Okay.
I wish I could make the potion.
It makes me a skeleton guy.
Samantha.
Samantha, you have $10 on you.
And I'm like, I just, I don't want to know how much money you have.
Oh, there you are.
Give me that.
I can make a pepper.
I like the music.
Yeah.
The music is good.
We should watch some old PSAs.
I definitely want to do some more infomercials.
I want to do some more longer infomercials.
Those are a lot of fun.
Okay.
What was I just going to do?
Who's moving?
Wait, why did you just move me here?
I didn't do that.
Why is it what I'm doing?
Is this like an event?
Am I supposed to be here?
What am I doing here?
What happened to Benson?
What?
My dog?
Oh no, I killed Benson.
All right.
Fuck Benson.
Who cares?
I was so concerned for one second.
I thought that was one of my friends.
Oops.
All right.
There's the moonstone thing, right?
This is the moonstone thing.
I'm certain of it.
Yep.
Okay.
I have three moonstones.
They're back at the house.
The corruption thing is going to happen.
I'm going to open the moonstone chest
and then I'm going to get a hundred dollars
and we're going to take
the group of fucking idiots back over here.
I have so much stuff.
I got a store.
Strup.
Strup is...
Okay.
All right.
I'm coming back here with three moonstones.
For real.
I'm opening that moonstone chest
and it's going to be a hundred bucks in it.
It's going to be amazing.
Any more of these?
I don't think I have these.
Has anybody picked these up yet?
Come on, come get them.
Maybe I should stop killing townspeople.
Maybe that would help.
Here, I saw you at Chili's yesterday.
You ordered the chicken crispers,
peeled the crispers off and the chicken
and then swallowed the chicken meat whole like a snake.
Was that you?
Was that you watching?
All right.
Let me research.
Oh, I'm going to figure it out.
What's ghoul skin?
All right.
Dump all this crap.
Bottles.
Get this out of here.
I'm going to keep the pick logs.
I don't know what this dag is really for, but...
Textiles.
Use the tomb.
Keep the worms.
Okay.
I don't need as many berries.
This axe is almost dead.
I'm just going to throw it away.
Okay.
So now the plan is
make a hot chilling...
Sizzling pepper.
Cool.
You doing an EU stream?
No, I'm...
I'm interested enough in the game to kind of keep playing it.
I just want to see...
I want to see what I can do with this.
I need to know.
How much is it?
I've got 31 coins.
Excuse me?
Just stole my shit.
No, don't fight everybody in town.
Why is the skeleton fighting this kid?
Well, he just killed that kid.
You killed a kid.
You just killed a kid.
I have to kill everybody.
Why?
What's happening?
Why did you just do that?
I'm going to die.
Where's Clemens?
What the fuck was that?
He just beat that kid to death with a shovel.
What the fuck just happened?
I'm a human again.
I'm human.
I'm actually human again.
Dude, you just hit that kid with the...
Did you hit that kid in the face with the shovel?
Did that get dead?
I'm actually a human.
Honest to God, what the fuck just happened?
A rat stole my wallet.
So I hit the rat in the head with an axe.
And now everybody's dead.
Yeah, that...
Excuse me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I forgot how good apples tasted.
I'm going to die again, aren't I?
Why are these people so fucking hostile?
All right, I need to eat food.
Ron, just run away.
Run away.
You killed...
This thing moved so fast.
I didn't...
Where's the chicken?
I need to...
Wait, go back to the camp.
The dog.
My dog.
My dog, dog, dog, dog, dog.
Help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help, help.
I gotta let the dog out.
The dog's gonna help.
Help me.
Help me, please.
Oh, why can't I open the gate?
Help.
Oh no.
Help, please.
Protect me, protect me, protect me, protect me.
Protect me.
They killed Julie too.
Bastards.
Okay, just get me out.
This motherfucker chasing me with the shovel.
I need to pick up more health potions that are on the ground.
Where's the dog?
That's so fucked up.
Stop, you fucker.
I need a weapon.
I'm gonna die again.
What happened to the dog?
All right, just go in here and close the gate.
They won't be able to get in.
Close, close, close, close.
Don't let this fucking giant snake in here.
Help.
Help me, please.
All right, I'm good.
I need...
I have an axe, right?
Julie.
No.
Did I get everything from the bag?
Oh my fucking god, I'm gonna die again.
He's running.
I'm so confused at what happened.
They're not gonna chase me over here, are they?
That was just chaos.
All right, none of you attack me, please.
There's a maniac over on the other side of town.
All right, sit down.
There's a fucking maniac over there.
Let me...
I need to eat some stuff.
This fish is raw.
Okay, let me cook this stuff.
You're supposed to talk to the owner about it,
but you just killed the rat after the rat stole?
I think the rats just steal.
I think they just do that.
Okay, getting better.
Just eat worms, whatever.
All right, what was the plan here?
Get rid of the broom.
I don't need these.
I don't need this much glass.
Store the hair.
Store the logs.
Store the mandragora.
Store the scrap.
Store the lab.
Store the hunger.
Yeah, I don't need the textiles.
Actually, I need to examine these.
Okay, add five vitality.
Okay, very nice.
Is that right speaker crow?
Every time I swear it's out of my window.
All right, let me see if I can get something done here.
Well, at least one thing you know from this game is
it's actually kind of...
You have to really think.
You can't just run around with a...
What do I do about this guy, though?
I mean, he's the kid.
I feel so bad about this.
What do I do about this?
It's this motherfucker right here.
What did you get?
All right, where's your boss?
Where's your boss?
Hi, Samantha.
Hey, Samantha, don't...
Don't pay no attention to the dead kid that's over here.
No, don't worry about that.
We're just going to be farming crops and shit together.
I forgot about Julie.
How do I get rid of them?
This is such a scary, awful, terrible reminder of the awful things happening.
I feel so bad.
At least the dog's still here.
I remember I had friends.
Hi, rogue.
Pay no attention to the dead kid, honest.
But that's in the video game.
That's in the video game.
Jerma, can you knock on the closet with the closest air vent in your room?
You are fucking weird, man.
You're fucking weird.
All right, I want...
Yeah, I can't believe I blew it.
I could have cleansed the tree by now and I fucked it all up.
I need another $70 and I need someone to carry the thing.
All right, I'm making money.
Dog, I need you to come with me.
You're pretty...
Yeah, you're good.
You got enough health.
Is that motherfucker?
What was that person's name?
I don't think it's still here.
Yeah, they've got...
There was somebody else.
I need to sell more stuff.
No, I don't.
Get out.
All right, it's been almost seven hours.
I should probably...
Call it tonight.
I need to pick that up.
All right, where's the...
Oh, the undertaker, right?
Let me do that.
This is a Q game.
Yeah, honestly, I think this is worth playing.
This might be a sponsored stream.
This is the first game sponsored stream I ever did.
I very much enjoyed myself as much as I was not very good.
Again, this is on Steam.
It's on PS5.
It's on Xbox.
It's on...
I think it's on pretty much everything.
What level of solid are your teeth?
Pretty solid.
Okay, so I need to be able to...
There are four bodies at the camp.
What, we're burying them?
I don't have four.
I don't have five shovels.
I actually have to bury them.
I need to make shovels to bury them.
I think there's definitely enough here.
I mean, I've been playing this for like almost three hours.
Oh, wait.
I can open this guy's chest.
Okay, no, I don't want to fuck this up.
Up, down, up, down.
Okay, up, down, up, up, up, up.
Butterflies.
Shovel.
Silver Cross.
Grants 5% chance to block incoming damage.
It's like a shield.
Cool.
Let's say read notes.
I feel like I haven't really scratched the surface of the game.
And I've just been kind of wandering around just doing dumb stuff.
If I had put that thing down and not placed it,
I would have been progressed much farther, I think.
But yeah, it's available.
They sponsored this part of the stream.
That's really cool.
I'm happy to do sponsorships for stuff that I think is interesting.
Going forward, I don't know.
We'll see.
I'm open to pretty much anything.
But this was the Serpent Rogue.
I would say I recommend it.
I think there's enough here to have fun.
I very much enjoyed it.
Yeah, I would probably rather do stuff like this
than do something that you've seen a thousand times, right?
For like a sponsorship.
But I mean, it depends.
What am I doing?
What's the point?
How many projects are coming up, right?
Yeah, I think hopefully I showed enough for you
to think if you want to check it out.
By all means, please do.
If not, then cool.
Huge, huge thank you to Team17 and Senji Games.
Hope I'm saying that right.
You got a cute little game here.
And I feel like I haven't really done anything.
And I've been playing for like three hours.
It seems like there's a lot to unpack.
But I'm very happy.
I think it's definitely worth playing.
And if you're coming up with a good system
when you first start, it's definitely worth.
This is a man-sized game.
Yeah, this is definitely a man-sized game.
Networking Andy?
That's no.
But yeah, I think that'll wrap it up.
Seven hours.
We should do the more infomercials.
We absolutely will.
That was so much fun.
That was an absolute blast.
Next stream is going to be Monday.
I don't really know what we're going to do yet.
The lockpicking looks sick.
I am going to imagine that eventually later on,
those are much harder.
I have, okay, the issue that I have with a game like this
is I don't want to let go of anything.
I want to keep everything.
I just want to keep every feather, every like chicken bone.
I just want to keep everything.
I just, I have to hold on to everything.
Can you take off your wig?
Nah, it's glued on.
This was neat.
Well, I hope it was at least worth and fun to watch
and worth checking out.
Well, see, I might just play this.
I don't know how much I'm going to stream it.
But I feel like it's kind of a fun game to play.
We'll see.
Oh, Stanley Parable is out, the new one.
That's right.
Maybe we'll do that on Monday.
But thank you.
This is the first ever game sponsor stream.
This is very new to me.
I would say you could probably expect stuff like this
to happen more often now.
Not all the time, but like I said to you earlier,
I've evolved.
I've been working with them now
and I've been presented a bunch of stuff.
This is the first thing that I thought was worth showcasing.
So they'll pop up from time to time.
You'll know what they are.
I'll make sure you know.
How's my sleep schedule?
It's not bad.
It's pretty good.
Variety streamer.
Yeah, we'll get a plan.
The Bugsnax DLC is out too.
Interesting.
What's the state of your port?
Do I have to save the game?
I think it just saves automatically, right?
32 people killed, one person healed.
One tamed, five deaths.
That's kind of cool.
Keeps track of that.
Let me see what else is in the menu here.
Okay, no, I think it's just single player.
Yeah, single player.
I just killed everybody I could.
But I didn't know.
I might get the game, honestly.
Yeah, you are free to.
If you don't want it or you do want it.
I mean, I'm not going to tell you what to do.
But I will tell you that I enjoyed that three hours that I just played.
That's it.
What's your favorite boss in Elden Rings?
Horror Loot.
The soundtrack is good too.
This is nice.
Maybe we'll have this play us up.
I like it.
Oh, never mind.
There we go.
How much does the game cost?
The game is right now, it is 10% off.
$17.99.
It'll probably go up to $19.20.
So on every platform, all the major ones on the new consoles.
Heavily focused on the crafting.
Which I probably could have done it a little more streamlined.
I could have been a little better about it.
But I just saw it and I was like, make potions.
This is a fun one today.
The infomercials then coming into this.
That was fun.
I had a very good time today.
Hope you all did too.
Will you play Inscription again at some point?
I don't know.
I feel like I want to play that on my own time.
I feel like my brain is too scattered to do a card game like that.
More infomercials?
We will.
It's not going to take very long.
I promise that we're not going to wait three or four weeks to do more infomercials.
We will do that within the next two or three streams.
We're just going to do that again immediately.
Don't forget to moisturize.
That's true.
You should absolutely moisturize.
Do Stanley Parable and infomercials on Monday.
That sounds like a good idea.
Very cool.
All right.
Again, thank you so much to Team17 and Cengi Games.
Thanks for watching that.
I know that sponsored content is something you're not used to on this stream
and something that is a lot different.
And I'll be really honest, I was a little concerned.
Because I just don't want, you know, obviously people to think,
like, oh, here comes the first sponsored stream.
It's over.
I'm going to get these every fucking day.
And not only that, it's going to be, oh, it's going to be egregious.
Oh, he's going to be, he's going to keep, she's going to shill so much bullshit.
I hope I can prove to you that that's not the case.
But there are plenty of companies and plenty of games and plenty of things that I would
probably do and I'd be interested in.
And this was one of them.
So sponsors are cool.
We know you're not a money grabber.
Oh, I can turn this off.
Sell out.
What is, what is going on?
Somebody said, what is, what is Joel doing?
Bill's doing something.
What's Joel doing?
Yeah, well, go to Joel.
They're doing a charity thing.
Is it still going on right now?
Yeah, let's go.
You're a businessman.
Oh, if that were the case, I would, I mean, if I was an executive,
I would have a fucking big smoothie and a huge ring.
God, that was so much fun.
I'm so glad that that was fun.
All right, let's go, Ray Joel.
Thanks again.
If you stuck around, I know we went late.
I know we started late.
I know a lot of people, they just, you know,
it's hard to stay up past like 10, 11 o'clock.
For those of you that stuck around,
I hope it didn't mess your sleep schedule up.
And thanks for watching and maybe we'll see you again.
If you got some time, maybe we'll see you Monday.
Good night.
Have a good sleep.
Call your mother.
We'll see you later.
Take care of yourselves and goodbye.