Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, Monday's edition. Hold on, somebody is trying to call me.
I want to show you something before this gets started. This is the goofiest dog ever. It's not Otto. Let's take a look.
Hello, my name is Rishi. So this is a dog that I'm dog sitting for right now. One of my sister's friends. It's her dog.
He's just sitting here, or she's just sitting here on my lap, and she's going to be there for the remainder of the video.
Don't worry, Otto is okay. He's down here. He was up there earlier, so I have plenty of time between the two dogs on the lap.
So don't worry, I have not forgotten about Otto. But anyways, just wanted to show you that I thought that was really funny.
A little Chihuahua dog. So let's get started with Facecam Fortress 2.
So let's get started here playing as the spy with the ambassador, the Spicycle, and the, not the red tape recorder, the regular Sapper on Dust Bowl.
Yeah, baby. Dust Bowl, baby. I also have the regular watch on today, and I'm going to get myself killed.
Wow, wow, wow. Me and live spy don't do very well, as you've seen in previous videos, but this heavy. Oh, give me a headshot.
That's a spy right there. Did I bump into a spy? Yeah. Yikes. Get away. No. Actually, what am I doing? I have the Spicycle.
What the hell am I doing? Popper, anybody here? Hmm. Don't look like it. Got to get the health that's here.
I got to be real sneaky about this, guys. Hey, there's this goat. How did I miss him?
All right, this is good, good, good, good, good. This is what I want. I want them all to come out so I can get behind everybody.
Probably not a good place to decloak, but I want the health. All right, let's go up here. What is going on right now?
Everyone's just, like, spawn camping. Oh, this is a good spot. Hey, everybody. I'm disguised as that guy, I think.
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy. Come on, do it again. Oh, he's fully charged. Oh, my God. That guy's probably so mad.
I just ruined that guy's Uber. I'm sorry, bro. I know how that feels. It's not a good feeling.
And we got a sniper coming in. Here we go. This is where I get found out. Nope, not quite yet.
Little dog is walking on my lap. Little dog. No, we're okay. I got to stop disguising as a scout.
Hey, little dog, what are you doing? Come here. Spy pyro down here, I see. I could smell ya from a mile away.
Come on, where is he? Oh! Thanks for the teleporter, mate. Can I headshot this guy? No, I was gonna go for it.
I was gonna go for it. What's this guy's health? Oh, that was pretty. That was a pretty little thing, if I do say so myself.
Give me this. Walking around with a bottle. Can I get another one? Wow, that's why I want to make my escape.
Make my escape. Oh, I thought I got him. I guess I was wrong. Sometimes you're wrong. Hey, what are you doing?
Come here. Hey, what's the matter with you, huh? Sit back down. You're being crazy.
I love right when I start recording. This is great. So I was playing with Boo for a little while before this.
We actually went to get food in separate places, and he was as calm, as collected as you could be.
Now he's kind of going all over the place. No! Pull it out. Oh yeah, Spycicle, baby. Spycicle gets you away from those pesky pyros.
But now all I got is this, and that guy saw right through me. You want to call somebody on the phone? Okay, ready?
He's like, what the heck? I don't know if you can see that or not. That's funny. Is that guy's name Wonder Bread? Wonder Bread.
I love Wonder Bread, especially in the toaster with cheese on it. Oh no, we're gonna get capped. Oh, and that's the end of the game.
Quick taunt. Oh well. Please don't kill me. See what happened right there, Reese? We lost. We lost the game.
I know it's very, very horrible. Very treacherous. But we get to go again, though. That's the good thing. Don't worry.
You know, you never have to worry in these situations. Look in the audience. What do you think they have to say about this?
I don't know, but I'm too tired. It's okay, little dog. I like to call them little dog. I like to call her little dog.
Here's one thing that I, actually, we'll time travel through setup time, then I'll tell you my story.
Okay, so what I was gonna say before is every single animal I've ever had has been a male. Every single one.
And I don't know if that's because I just don't, I don't know why that is. I just happen to be every animal.
Actually, one cat. One cat that we had a long time ago when I was, geez, I was probably 10 years old.
We had a cat that his name was, her name was Maggie. But other than that, it's, I've had like 10 animals.
And all of them have been male, and now we are spawn camping. I haven't, I've, just please kill me.
Now should I just, you know, that's what we're gonna do. Change the other team, quick. And stay spy.
See if, see if I can't make something happen here. Dead ringer. Oh, where you going, dog?
Dead ring? Can we dead ring out of here? Okay, we're alright. Okay. There we go. There we go.
I am not a spy. You don't know. Hey, I got the kook rail. Looking for those pesky spy bastards.
That is a medic being shot in the back. I need my knife. I'm gonna get that knife. We got up here.
Anything? Got a lot of stuff. Oh, he got the health. It's alright. Take a, that's what I wanted. That's what I wanted.
Get out of my face. Oh, this is not good. Standing right in this guy's face. Oh my god.
I thought I was gonna be able to backstab him. Oh, hey, come on, coitus, coitus. What do you got for a loadout?
The black rose. Where'd he go? He like, disappeared. So can we win this? Are we gonna come back from being, well actually, come back.
Well, I was on the other team and I, I was, actually I didn't really contribute to this at all. I was kind of just standing there talking.
And somebody is calling my phone. This dog is like, what is that? It's a phone. It's just a phone. Don't worry.
Let's get them boys. No, you were right. I was a spy. Now I'm a sniper. Oh, come on. Oh my god, this tree killed me.
Listen, I can't talk right now. Buddy, whoever you are. That wasn't even Burger Boy. Who the hell was that?
That was like a random number. Like a bunch of random digits I've never seen before. I never answer those phone calls.
Let me know in the comments section if you ever answer. Hello. If you ever answer. What are you doing? What are you doing, dog?
Oh my god, dog. You can't really. How did I kill that scout? I can't, I could not tell you. Let's go. Let's go for this tap.
It's a tap. You are being a real, I can't even like play this game. Oh my god. Alright, listen. Listen, I know you want like kisses right now, but I'm like playing a game.
Yeah. Alright, here. Mwah, there's one for you. So get, get back dog. You little freak. I gotta, I gotta get a good sap and stab.
I got dog lap issues. Thanks, dog. Oh, watch it. Watch it. Little dog. Little dog jumping. Little dog jumping up a lap.
No, he's not. Anywhere to be seen. He is not. Oh no, there he is. Oh, come on. I had it. No, dog. Come here. Come hither.
Alright, you want to get down? Get down this way. Go that way. Now he's going to, I have 10 bucks. 10 bucks as he starts crying.
He's going to be going, wee, wee, wee. Is that a heavy right there? No, it's an engineer all the way back here. Oh, I just heard him. I just heard him go.
I gotta, alright, time to, I'm going to switch off a spy after this. I'm going to go demo and I'm going to try and just take out all the stuff.
Oh man, oh man. He, the guy knows. He knows. He knows. They all know. They all know. Get him. Get him. I got him. Is there another set? Oh, there's another engineer.
Damn it. Alright, let's do this. Where you going? What is this setup? Oh, we need that engineer to build a teleporter. Oh, he's got one built.
What is going on here? Did he just, he just taunt killed somebody. Did you see that? That guy just taunt killed that pyro. Are you a spy?
No, you're not. But you, on the other hand, are going to get killed by the sentry that's in that room. Don't let him get it. Kill this guy. Shoot him. Do anything.
Man, this is bad. Wall. Come on, off the wall. Please let me in. Please let me in there. Anybody else? There's the sentry.
Alright, if I can, I gotta figure out a solution here. This has got to go like this. There's two sentries over there.
There's, we got one. Me and the, oh, what the hell, add. Both are down. Both are down. Both sentries are down. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh, only a minute and 50. What? How is this heavy Keith getting back here? He's back here like every time.
I was going to sticky jump. What? I just killed somebody. No, I didn't. It's this fake scout right here. That was ridiculous though.
And what happened? What's going on with my frame rate? My like frame, hold on. My frame rate's like exploding right now. That was crazy.
Yeah, I don't think this is happening. Very ironic. I switched teams and what's, maybe I'm just going crazy. My frame rate looks like it's dying though.
According to DX story, that's not the case. But what on earth? They have a teleporter over here. There is a teleporter right here. This has to go down right now.
This has to happen right now. Who is in this room, dude? You are going down. Oh my God. I just heard him. Where is he? Are we going to win? We're going to win the game.
How did that happen? You know, I'll tell you how that happened. That's a spy. I'll tell you how that happened.
They had a teleporter back here somewhere and they all were just coming to the front lines and nobody was back there anymore. That's ridiculous. Oh my God.
Well anyways, that's going to wrap up Face Camp Fortress 2 Mondays edition. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it guys.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care everybody. Reety!