I'm gonna shoot you. I'm gonna shoot you in the back of the head.
You talking to me? Why did you turn around and start shooting me? I was like, just kidding.
I shot one time, it was a warning shot. Yeah, but your gun was like pointed at my face.
Yeah, and warning. Alright. Alright, wait. Let's go pick up Boo. Let's go ba-
What just happened? Oh, that's how you detonate C4.
Oh my god, are you serious, dude?
I did like a cartwheel. Oh, I hit the cop car.
Hey, hey, let's do it. Get in the car. Alright.
Setting the perfect trap for these two. Oh my god, this is a two-wheel, a two-passenger seat.
This is a two-person car, are you serious? Oh, Boo, sorry.
This is what you get.
Oh, you threw that over there, okay. Oh my god.
You deserve that stealth. Yeah. Stealth? What do I know?
Following over this to this cab car, let's do this. I forget what button you press.
I don't know how to get up. Oh god, it's-
It's left shift, it's left shift, okay. What the hell just happened?
I just scraped the building.
I just did a two- Oh no, I'm falling.
Dude, I just scraped the building. That was ridiculous.
Oh my god. There's a helicopter after me, you know.
If you look very far down. Actually, no, it's that one that's like half blown if you look down there.
Hey, stop it. Alright, ready, we're gonna come over here.
We're jumping off this side and we're all gonna- it's left shift to open the parachute.
You ready, guys? Let's do it. Oh baby.
Oh yeah. We're the three parachuting friends.
Oh, you can detach it with F. Oh shit.
Dude, I'm just still floating around. You hold down S to like not die.
S? And then you- like W-A-S-D?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Um, guys, I forgot how to use my parachute.
I forgot how to use my parachute! What? How did you kill me?
I have nowhere near you.
Oh dear. Oh, you busted like a cap in me apparently.
You guys keep killing each other.
I plowed him.
Well, it worked as a new chopper. Dude, I feel like the Human Torch or something, like really like-
I really felt like the Human Torch right there.
Oh gosh. Where are you? Oh hey, look who's like following me right now, shooting like missiles at me.
Have you just been my parachuting all this time? Are you hitting the-
Are you hitting me right now? I think so. Alright, there's the land.
How did I die? I'll take your car, buddy.
It's like an M249 sword. Alright, let's do it.
I have four stars, I'm afraid. You do? Oh, you're back there. Alright, I'm coming to you.
Oh, will you get away from me? Oh my god.
What? What is going on? All the cops that were coming after you are like-
Oh my god, get me away! It's like an enemy helicopter.
Oh my god, dude. Oh my god.
What? Are you serious?
Why are there so many? Why are there so-
Why are they killing you?
Every cop in the city just came after me, like they just were all pulling up at the same time.
Why are there so many?
Why are there so-
Why are they killing you?
We're going to the other side. We're going to go this way, it's a little bit more of a longer drive.
I'm going to go off the edge!
The cops are coming, wait there.
Oh shit.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? We're trying to do
insane stunts.
So I lost the helicopter.
There's another one here, it's okay. How are you doing?
I'm so tempted to shoot this guy. No, don't do it, don't do it.
We're going to see if we get the cops on us for doing this.
He's like- Not yet, not yet, hold on.
Oh jeez.
I can't believe we don't have any stars.
He doesn't even get to testify pointing my gun at him.
It's the worst cop ever.
You are legitimately pointing your gun at his face.
Sorry officer.
I'm just going to go off the ground before I shoot.
There we go.
I know he's still alive, what a beast.
I'm like holding it upside down like this.
Your back was breaking to do it.
I'm laughing at that.
No, don't go over the edge!
When you see us getting close, do it.
Do it.
That's why we have to turn friendly fire off, so it doesn't kill us.
Oh my god.