Oh, mega early. Very early, mega early. Yeah, kinda.
You remember, hold on. What? I almost just said, never mind, I was gonna say, start.
I'm gonna say it, I'm not gonna say it, then I'm gonna say it five seconds, I'm not gonna say it, then I'm gonna say it. Anyways.
Whatever, just pretend you knew what I was gonna say. There's no music? Oh shit, hold on.
I got, don't worry, I've got you covered.
Do-Ga-Duh DidDit, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit, Do-Ga-Duh-Did-Dit, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit-Did, Do-Ga-Duh-Dit.
Here ya go. Fuck yeah.
Hello, yes hi everybody.
Today is going to be a very short stream. It will be very quick and to the point, well not even really to the point.
We've got some things to do today, a couple of very interesting things that I find incredibly interesting.
Are there a couple of websites that I came across I have to do with this community and I really really want to do them
Because one of them is very relevant to like a week ago, and the other one is just cool
So this is not the final stream. No no no now. This is the this is it. This is the last one
Hold on these like cat ears are so itchy God
I'm just getting this no fucking cat ears
You see they look at the chat the chat just went insane the chat just went boom
No, I do not have a catboy costume on right now. You say the words catboy and all of a sudden
Oh my god here come the floodgates of chat messages prove it. I'm gonna prove it. I'm gonna put the camera on
The first thing we're gonna do
So this this stream is gonna be probably like an hour maybe tops
It depends on how long it takes me to do the greatest video games of all time tier list
That could take like four hours. I don't know that's fine
But we'll see one hour Andy
No, there's no catboy today. We're just gonna hang out is everything okay? Everything is fine
Guys the streams not 45 minutes because like something is wrong
guys, I only got like 45 minutes and
Something is very wrong, and I'm please help me
Let's get a bunch of community stuff. Thank you up mega dial for the 20 community subs whoo zero. Thank you
That's a lot the first thing I want to do is very relevant to what we did it
Well, let's just go over here. You know what hey, hi. How are you so oh, he's got the cat ears
No, I got the twitch TV shirt on how you doing. How's everybody doing? What a letdown
I this this is not a cat boy stride didn't make that clear that this was a cat boy stream
I look a little stuffed in here though
Don't I don't I kind of look like I don't fit in here
I feel like I'm wearing like a sleeping bag or something like oh, I'm here for the sleepover
Just put a just put a pillow behind me, okay
Is it extra small take it off and reveal the cat where no this is not a scenario
We're like all the reason why he looks like he's got a bunch of clothes on he's gonna unzip this is gonna be a full
Catboy made outfit what are they even in is it a made outfit? Did I just say that it is a made outfit it is okay?
You wish
What anyways first of all I apologize in advance for the image that you're gonna see on the screen that you're gonna get an image
On the screen, and I'm very sorry, but it's relevant to
What we talked about last week and somebody I'm gonna give credit for credit
This is from the germa a wet ace for me. I'm not no don't say anything
German 985 it was on here on this way. This is a place. I'm not saying I don't want to say what this is
It's just a it's a place that I found it's a thing
I was about to just shout it out, and that was a fucking huge mistake potentially okay
What you're gonna see on the screen here? I'm very sorry, but it's got I'm sorry do you remember when I recorded those messages?
Your personal message free happy birthday or anniversary message from when the imposter is sus guy there
It is let's begin okay, so let's do let's do birthday alternative birthday message for oh
You can't see the drop-down menu, but I have a huge drop-down menu here. Who should we do how about how about Jeremy?
We'll do Jeremy first. Let's see can you hear it. Yo, German 95 here. Just want to say oh
Excuse me is it somebody's birthday today? Oh, of course it is happy birthday Jeremy
I'm so happy to see you on your birthday Jeremy
I was told you're a big fan, and I'm coming to you personally nobody paid me to do this except
They did if it was at least five dollars, and if I talk for more than 30 or 40 seconds
It is some of these are over $200 mine wasn't happy birthday though. Have a great one
It's a personal message from the when the imposter is sus guy all right. How about uh how about Emma?
We'll do birthday message one for Emma. Hey, I want to wish a very special happy birthday to Emma heard
You had a big day today. Happy birthday
Look at the unsureness in my face. This is I don't I look like I just don't want to be here
I look like it really does look like a lot of cameos
When you see a cameo and the person you can tell this is like the
60th the one they've done in a row watch just look at look at my face
Very special happy birthday to Emma heard you had a big day today or a big day. I don't even care
I'm not retaking it just do another hundred in a row
I shall happy birthday to Emma heard you had a big day today
Happy birthday to you hey your friends put me up to this your friends put me up to this
But happy birthday nonetheless heard your fan
It's been so great to hear from you Emma. Have a wonderful rest of your day. Why is this so much more time? Yes the streams
Wink oh my god that oh my god. Have a wonderful rest of your day. Yes the streams wink
Oh my fucking god. I hate that one all right. What about anniversary message? How about how about uh
grace and
how about grace and
Goku race and
Goku you know I
Heard it was somebody's anniversary happy anniversary you two. I heard the story
I heard how fun it was it the proposal was fantastic
I heard that was fun too happy anniversary guys. You're gonna do good things
You're gonna do good things happy anniversary a fun. It was it the proposal was fantastic
I look like why do I look like I'm in pain here also was
Fantastic I think I blinked like a hundred times
That was just like it the proposal was fantastic
I heard that was blink like 15 times guys. You're gonna do good things. You're gonna do good things happy anniversary
Oh blink twice if you're in trouble all right. How about
Jerry Jerry and Jerry and Colton Jerry and
Colton you know I heard it was somebody's anniversary. How about wait? How about Otto?
There's so many names how many names that I say how about Otto how Otto and Becca Otto and Becca
You know oh that didn't like that Otto and Becca. You know I
Think it broke
You know how about happy birthday to Otto? Yo, German 95 here. Just want to say oh
Excuse me is it somebody's birthday today? Oh, of course it is happy birthday Otto
I'm so happy to see you on your birthday Otto. I was told you're a big fan, and I'm coming to you
Oh, I love nobody paid me to do this except they did
So you just give this to give this to all your friends any on their birthdays and stuff you don't have to pay me
Anything like I'll never have a cameo. I'm honestly I want to add to this
I want to do like congratulations on the new job, and I'm gonna have like another fucking 500 names
Everything that you could get a cameo for let me just do it for free you understand
Let me just do it for free
I will sit here and record just off stream like another thousand names and like ten different recordings
And just just just use mine for free don't pay for it. I'm pretty famous come on. There's
9,500 people here. I think come on. It's free all right. How about Otto and
How about okay? How about how about happy birthday Miranda? Yo, German 95 here
Just want to say oh, I did I say excuse me is it somebody's birthday today. Oh, of course it is happy birthday Miranda
I'm so
All right one more anniversary. How about how about mark and?
mark mark and mark yeah, I think I broke the anniversary one how about Keith and
Julie Keith and Julie you know I heard it was somebody's anniversary
Happy anniversary you two I heard the story the best part about I heard the story
That they say that for every single one of them so people usually write a whole paragraph to the person doing the cameo like
oh, this is how they met and
They read that and they've probably already forgotten, so they just they just say you know I heard the story
What happened in the story what happened in the story?
Can you name one verb that was in that description or one at your one noun?
You can't probably and come on. I'm doing them for free. I heard how fun. It was okay. I love this alright
How about what I want to do one more birthday? Oh, this is a good birthday. Happy birthday Thanos
Yo, German 95 here. Just want to say oh, I did I say excuse me is it somebody's birthday today. Oh, it's course
It is happy birthday, Thanos
Thanos I was told you're a big fan
Just like somebody okay, somebody said that in the chat, and I looked over and just read it
I five here. Just want to say oh, I did I say excuse me is it somebody's birthday today. Oh, it's course
It is happy birthday Thanos. I'm so happy to see you on your birthday Thanos
Well there you go. This is you can use this eventually
I'll give you the link before you break it so there it is. I'm surprised. It was made this quickly Michael of okay
All right, all right. I'll do Michael. Why is Goku on here? Why is Goku on here?
Michael I didn't even do Michael. I didn't do Michael. I did Mike. Yo, five here
Just want to say oh, I did I say excuse me. Is it somebody's birthday today? Oh, it's course it is. Happy birthday Mike
I'm so happy to see you on your birthday Mike
I was told you're a big fan and I'm coming to you personally. Nobody paid me to do this except they did I
Can't believe I didn't do Michael. That's actually pretty bizarre close enough. Do it right now. Oh shit. All right fine, Michael
Carl Zander Alan Lucas
Scott
Ready for this one?
Whoever has this name is gonna be real fucking surprised because they're gonna go through and they're gonna do a few of them that aren't
Theirs and this one. Holy shit. You ready Rachel?
Ethan Blake Zach
Sydney Justin
Tyler Gabriel Terry
Florence what?
Melissa
Ariana Corey
Kevin I was trying to do the home alone thing when she's in the plane
Taylor all right, I've we're not doing this again, but we are gonna do something else. Wait, Chucky. You'll just crop me
You know, it's alright
Chucky is gonna be super blown out. Chucky is gonna be like
160p the next thing we're gonna do this now. This one is gonna be a ton of fun. Are you ready for this one?
This is called
Jerma's chat real or AI generated this device
This thing has been trained on
This chat it is pulled
Thousands and thousands of messages and it is for me to determine if this is something that was actually written in the chat or
the AI
Robot came up with this learning what you guys have said over the years
Let's find out so we have to see how many of these we can get in a row. Oh what?
What kind of a name is that that seems pretty AI generated, but I feel like that could be real real that's incorrect
Try again zero streak. I don't think this is how it works. That's AI. Yeah, come on
This is like that one episode of spongebob where he's trying to get the seal. That's real. What only one
All right. Well, you get it. You get outwards too bad
None of it's going to be in the actual game real you got a misspelling their robots. Don't misspell
They're fucking intelligent without to say that they're not intelligent, right?
I'm going to rent out the level-up lounge in the MGM casino to host my own convention. What the fuck is that?
German on 8 5 2009. That's AI generated. I didn't do that. This game is so fucking hard to watch. That's real
This is the last time you can play this game. I think that's probably real
What the shortness of his arm Sleever is making me uncomfortable?
Sleever
That's AI he's actually not going to say it AI what you're not a clown you're the entire
Circus imagine having a girlfriend when you have twitch chat. I feel like that's AI
We're talking about how we can seduce you. That's real
This is like yeah, you guys have gotten do you you're like fucking lewd levels have gone up like six hundred thousand percent in the last
Year, I don't think Jerma has the actual setup that sounds AI it is
Lemur's suicide tower for when they realize their enclosure sucks
Jerma the only way to win is to I thought I thought that could have been AI Jerma
The only way to win is to not play that's AI. We're four in a row here
I gotta get to at least ten in a row Jerma. I've been watching your videos for like two years
Please just stop. I think this one could be AI
But I think it's real because people like tell me to stop streaming and like stop doing YouTube and stuff
all the time
Again, let's do it again
You're gonna get addicted to the game. You're gonna get addicted to the game in like 30 minutes real
Hey, I know it's not that big of a deal, but I have to admit
I'm really bummed that you're not playing this right now. That's AI has to be that's a jumbled AI
That has to be a if it's real. I don't know what they're even talking about. Okay
Hey star, can I go to your house and talk to Lucy? This is fucking AI
What's the context behind that one? Hey star gonna go to your house and talk to Lucy. It ain't the size of the screw
It's how hard you drill that's real. I think I wrote that if you don't use the I'm the giant rat voice
You're not a hero that seemed pretty real. Are you going to do the cooking stream real? Oh my god
You know the guy from the hit movie the Phantom Pain
I feel like the ones that are very obviously AI end up being real
Wait, that's you're doing a great job. Thanks for the stream. I know I know that's AI. I know that's AI
Motherfuckers don't write that here. How many people I'm just kidding you do but how many people die when they get a jet pack?
But how many people die when they get a jet pack? I think that's real. It has the at German 985 on it
What did it say? What did it say? It's a jackpot. I said I wasn't me
I almost pressed AI because I said jet pack
Did he fight giraffe seems like I missed a section of stream and I don't know if he's optional
The thing is like people give weird random easy names to the like the Dark Souls bosses
I'm trying to think. Oh, did you get the dancer yet? But that's like short for something
It's what giraffe you get to did you get to get a banana yet? Did you get to schnaz yet?
People say that kind of shit. It's got it. Oh god at German 95. You just woke me the fuck up. That's real
Are you gonna play the DS sequel after this? I don't I don't buy this one. Am I gonna play the DS sequel?
Oh chibi-robo, that's right. We're five in a row. You're most going to be in a clown car. It's
What however, none of you actually said that what are you talking about? No one's actually wrote writ that before
I love German stream, but not the chat real it's a game about what I'm just saying like I don't believe that
I don't believe that I'm just saying that's probably real. It's a game about collecting and selling coins AI
Can you tell me what the fuck is happening real?
Whatever the joke is that the bands don't happen plumbers don't wear ties robots don't use guns. That's AI
Well, I I'm sorry AI but I have never streamed the movie Zoolander and if I was streaming Zoolander on twitch
I don't think you'd be asleep. You'd be waiting for me to get terminated to laugh us
Right omega lol when you see like that that stream has been banned somebody wrote that okay
I guess somebody wrote that I have no idea what that is, but I'm glad it's not a meme real
I don't know. You can see the pain in his face real what you guys are really fucking annoying. You're all invited
Hey, can you play cave story? Ost that gets asked all the time. You need to buy the boots to beat this real
Oh my fucking god, this is like a person and they're here right now that person here
Please talk more about sensitive topic in the chat. We love it. That this is the person's price
That's AI. You have to tell me something is wrong AI
You have to do the full three minutes slow mode real fuck. It's getting I don't know
I can't tell the difference you can buy a few of these at the market AI another person
We're being gaslighted by the height police echo the dolphin. Oh my god, Jeremy
Please real how he played the game with the discount with the like it's AI. What do you think?
I don't know you think it's is it AI real. It's real. I'm gonna say it. This game is trash
I feel like people say that every stream, but it's very specific AI. This is a good game
You just need to be really good at it. That smells very robust smells like AI to me. Yep
All right, we're at six. Are you gonna play the other games too? I mean, this is a simple question
I think I think so. Are you gonna play the other games too? They're all AI all of them are gonna be AI real
Oh, I could tell. All right. I gotta get to ten. That's what that's what made me get fired my job AI
Why are you playing this game again AI? It seems like you somehow downgraded your audio solution real
I see I get I get shit for that all the time
If I remember right Jerma actually read the message, which is why I got in trouble
I don't know what it was, but you got in fucking trouble
This is so weird Jerma is the first person who actually uses the stealth mechanics in this game
That's a fucking that's an AI. I have never ever
truly used
Stealth mechanics in a stealth video game. I get shit for it all the time. I can't do it. I'm horrible
This is this is AI. What was it from Metro 2033? How the how do you remember that?
How do you possibly remember that? This is my first Jerma stream and I'm enthralled AI whatever
He never actually moved to Vegas. It's all been soundbites real
You can use the item menu to find what you want AI. It's got the Dark Souls filter and saturation
It was so they were dry. So it was just like sunflower seeds. Yeah AI god damn it
ASMR Jerma quizzes you on an app you barely use real streamer change sus
So he won't be late real what if you did it in the wrong order AI, that's too many kids
They'll go back to their parents. Oh, I don't know real this feels a this feels very AI. God damn it
I should have went with I got hour and a half to finally get to gameplay real. Oh my god
He's still in paperclip Londo. I know it's stream. That's from it's real
You should have taken someone with better lockpicking. This could be fake old man gives himself blood pressure
Live on stream give myself blood pressure. What old man gives himself blood pressure on stream
You know what they say about a man with a big-ass dick
Not real. I don't know. What do they say guy in Jerma chat that why would you write that?
I just got here and you're still on this level. What the fuck? It's too good. Check out this clip
Problem with this generation is nobody's reading books anymore
You know saying like that's a problem people aren't reading anymore
This is AI this should be reading a book a week
It's actually it's offensive to me that people are not reading at least one to two books a week
Live watch Jerma 95 live playing clock tower 3 that's not currently happening what
Okay, um, I don't I don't know what this is AI generated clip it's not possible
No, this has to be real. How would anybody be able to know that has to be real has to be there's no way
This is not real. Absolutely impossible. The AI wouldn't do this, right?
Okay, is the guy who couldn't beat preschool games yesterday. Yes, it is. I got my first gift sub in a week
I want to see you have a stroke. No, you don't what the fuck
I forgot about the part of this game where you rode a giant fat gold, dude, like a train
Oh my god, my eye. Did you see that? My island got stuck
My
It hasn't sunk this low until now real that was even better the second time around robot
Oh my god, I'm never gonna get ten. Just get a saddle and ride the horse real. Oh my god
I thought it was in red dead. So Robie is confirmed for next Jerma rumble. I don't know. I don't know what that is
It was no best ice cream this year. I'm sad real Jerma's wearing the foam Hulk hands as he plays real
I'm not falling for this shit again. Neither am I? Hey guys, I'm back
What's up with this game AI you can use the fire staff in the house AI it all went bad because he has no friends
that's real I
TM I'm going to watch your AI. Yeah, you get a little glitched out there a little bit. Mr. Robot
I'm going to take a nap. Thanks for the stream. I'll be real. What the fuck? I swear to God
I said that all the time. I can't believe this game was made by a fucking gnome real
I think you can use the same hero to do the same thing AI
Secret bub what is secret bub Jerma? Are you sure about this? These are get really hard real
There's a secret ending if you go through the red door. Yeah, why is he doing all the DLC again real fuck?
I'm never gonna get more than 10. I'm sorry Jerma, but you can't have a bad time. That's AI real question
Is why did you play this game real people? I'm gonna go watch the VOD just in case AI
If I find a place that does that I'll be arrested for arson at real
Jerma versus internet real you should try to get the perfect ending. That's AI mystery streams means he doesn't have a plan
Absolutely real because that's very very true
I said that like a month ago
Mystery streams mean I had no idea what I was doing until about 15 minutes before the stream turns on by the way
There's a mystery stream. Maybe like maybe like once or twice a week
Come on, Jerma play some Simpsons music to charge yourself with rage real you can just do a backflip for the items
Hey, I I think I'm just gonna go it's kind of sad. I'm sorry for being late
I didn't mean to tell you that that's AI one more. Well now VR is becoming a thing. So SBA
Oh god, damn it Jerma's going to stream the new Animal Crossing fake. I want to see you get beaten up real
I do believe they've made a penis AI. You're not a real gamer. If you don't play fortnight real
I wish this game was more about zombies and less about what time it is real talking about Dead Rising
Jerma you have to be on the edge of the world AI. Jerma this fucking sucks
Please just play a game real. You can also find the GameCube version of this game
I've been trying to beat the last boss of Sekiro for the last eight hours straight with no breaks
I don't think I can do it. Why not just be in an airplane that flies fast enough to constantly stay at 3pm
For like time zones so I can stream
Okay, the context there is I was saying I might the time zones are all over the place
There's a lot of EU people here and there's like we got to find a good time for you to stream
Oh, but like you stream it like two three o'clock Pacific. That's so late. It's like well, it's time zones, man
I can't change that and then somebody wrote why don't you just get in an airplane that goes fast enough to be at 3pm
What would happen if you were in a device or like a vehicle that could constantly be at the certain point of the globe?
Where it was three o'clock?
What would happen would it be three o'clock for everybody would it be 3 p.m. Everywhere?
What if you could go fast enough every time travel you'd know it would only be 3 p.m. In the device
Oh, yeah, this is why it's bad unless you're in the same room real
So chat has he said anything about streaming today? That's AI about how crazy and we got it at that's real
I remember when Jerma was a dad AI. It's a very good game, but I don't think it's the best one AI
What the fuck is actually what the fuck I actually need Xbox live to go forward real
We already told you Super Mario Brothers 2 isn't in this that's I don't know. Oh, wait, wait, wait
Wait, were they talking about Mario maker? I don't know if that's AI
They might be talking about Mario maker 2 cuz I was like, oh, I want to make like a Mario 2 level real
Yep, I knew it stir was holding back now for his true form. Why do you have a tarantula in your house?
I don't Jerma is the most famous person on the planet
Somebody may have written this though, even though it's not true
Goddamnit
Last run and I'm done last run. This is a like a real game Jerma. I can't believe it. That's fake
You said you blasted Katamari in your car with an angry face real you can use it to get more heroes real
I don't know one more the game is making you play this game. That's fake
You can make a new house with this mod fake. I think he's gonna be like what the fuck
I'm not going to play this game anymore real. Oh my god
If you play the game, the audio is muted real
You got to get two more and name them coffee and chicken real surprised by his own tendons in his hand
Omega-lul real why do you have to look at the screen fake? Speaking of the screen?
What's with the scan lines get a snap for the vacation album real did you know that Jerma is a furry real?
All right. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. This was a lot of fun. What's with the scan lines now?
It's time to do the greatest video games of all time. I don't like these scan lines here. I got to fix this
By the way now, I'll tell you what those websites were that is the that is the that one was cameo dot Jerma dot IO
in fact
there's a lot of stuff in the Jerma dot IO by the same people in person that made the
Rubik's Cube saw game so some really actually really cool stuff. That's really funny
I saw that and I had to stream it. It just seems ridiculous. Why is Jerma background moving? It's because the side of scan lines
I got to fix this they fix it. What's with these scan lines?
Stop that what the hell does anybody else believe
That every fucking webcam that's made in the last ten years never increased in technology
They just put they they put a new name on it and just it's like oh this one is came out like a year ago
It's the exact same webcam that came out ten years ago. No technology has changed
I don't I don't think it has a webcam come out in the last like ten years that has
1080p scan lines you need a fucking floodlight to see yourself
It's not even this shitty name. It doesn't look like 1080p. It's your monitor rooms light
Yeah, but I mean that this doesn't happen all the time. I just made myself more red
Looks scary. Why is it doing this?
Real can't change the webcams FPS. Yeah
Look I'm gonna put it at 50 Hertz 60 Hertz. I'm gonna put it at
60 at 30 FPS. Oh my god, what happened? What happened?
You know, I always wondered like there's dreamers that have like full-on like DSLR is pointing down at them
I was like, why do people do that? And now I kind of understand now
Webcams are such dog shit and they're never gonna get better
We good. It's like we can only wait for so long for them to make a webcam
There's not like a piece of fucking dog shit in like 12 years. All right, here we go. We good