Hold on, we'll go, we'll go full cam for a minute. Okay. Do I, do I have Morrowind? Let's find out.
Uh, is Morrowind on steam? No, please. God, you got a big ass head. Actually,
this camera makes me look fucking huge, by the way. Look at this. I don't know what it is with
this camera, but it, I don't, I think it's fisheye or something. Cause look at how huge it makes me
look. Look at this, right? It makes me look fucking huge. Don't I look like stacked? It makes me have
like a, I have a good tiny head. That's weird, right? I don't know why, why this is doing this.
I swear I don't have, I'm not this like jacked. All right. Where, um, where's Morrowind? How do
I get it? It's the tank top? Maybe. Yeah. Do I, I don't, I don't own Morrowind. I don't think.
What's it called? Elder Scrolls? I don't own it. Am I actually, is it going to, am I going to buy
fucking Morrowind right now? It runs fine. Vanilla. Really? Okay. Well let's get rid of like the giant
arms. Okay. Uh, let's get it. Morrowind. It's on sale right now. Is this game actually going to be
fun or is this people are going to leave and hate this? It's $4 and 50 cents right now.
That's it. Holy shit. It really is 70% off. All right. Let's go for it. I'll get it. Okay. It's
coming through. Okay. Here we go. Pog. Pog. Pog. It's only one gig. This is a tiny game. Okay.
Morrowind. Can we get a, this is going to be a terrible stream game. Somebody said it's going
to be a terrible stream game. Somebody said this is going to suck. This is, this is going to suck.
This is going to suck. Well, look, this is, I guess this is what we're doing. Options. It says,
wait, it's a separate menu for the, how do I wear my options? Oh God. I think my computer's crashing.
Okay. I want, there's no HD resolutions. Full screen 1920 by 1440. I guess that's close enough.
It takes a long time to learn. Wait, I think I'm going to have to learn this shit. Hold on.
Learning is hard. I mean, I, whatever. We'll see. I'll try it. Can I even capture the game?
Let's find out. Okay. Oh, failed to create shader. Continue running executable. Yes.
Yes. Continue please. Wait, here it comes. Here it comes. It doesn't work. I think it just turned
off now. All right. It just crashed out. We got to see the opening music cut scene. I'm going to try
opening it again. Epic music. Fucking epic. The elder scrolls three. This is the elder scrolls
three. Dude, it won't, I can't open it. I can't open it. I thought you guys said this worked on
windows 10. Do I have to go get a mod? Hold on. I'm going to, I'm going to open it in a window.
Okay. Window. Okay. Let's try that. Come on. Do it. Play. Here it comes. Can you see it? Yes.
This looks awful on my screen. It's half of my monitor. It's in a cube on the left side of my
monitor. Let's go. The elder scrolls three. Morrowind. Can we get the name change of the,
you know what I'm saying? Can we get a name change please? The stream name.
Oh my God. This text is so small. Why is this so tiny? I can't even see.
This is so small. View distance. Real-time shaders. Don't do anything. Don't change anything.
Seriously. I'm back. Okay. Okay. New game. Each event is preceded by prophecy, but without the
hero, there is no event. In the waning years of the third era of Tamriel, a prisoner born on a
certain day to uncertain parents was sent under guard without explanation to Morrowind.
Whatever the rest of that says.
That's cut off. It's cut off for me too, so don't worry.
This dude fucking gave up. I didn't. This was everyone said to play this. Like
60% of you said to do this. What? What happened?
What's your name? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I need to fix this. Okay. There we go.
My name. My name is Morrowind. Last night storm could wake you. I heard them say we've reached
Morrowind. I'm sure they'll let us go. Quiet. Here comes the guard. This is where you get off.
Come with me. W and S move forward and back. A and D move side to side. You better do what they say.
Put the death counter up. How could you have died this many times in the tutorial?
You're playing music way too loud. Spacebar to open it. Whoa. This is where they want you.
Head down to the dock and I'll show you to the census office. You finally arrived,
but our records don't show from where. What? Orc, I guess. Great. I'm sure you'll fit right in.
Follow me up to the office and they'll finish your release. Oh my God. I'm huge. Hold on.
That's as low as I can make it. Yes. We've been expecting you. You'll have to be recorded before
you're officially released. There are a few ways we can do this and the choice is yours.
Answer his questions. Okay. I'll do it. Yeah. I'll get the controller off of my penis.
All right. Generate clip. You chance upon a strange animal. It's leg trapped in a hunter's
snare. Judging from the bleeding, it will not survive long. What do you do? Use herbs from your
pack to put it to sleep. Whereas save the animal. One summer afternoon, your father gives you a
choice of chores. What would you rather do? Go catch fish at the stream using a net and a line.
Work in the forge with him casting iron or gather herbs for your mother who is preparing dinner.
I would probably do this one. I don't know why it's so small. I can't say anything.
Can you talk with a louder font? I would go pick herbs from mom. Your cousin has given you a very
embarrassing nickname and even worse likes to call you it in front of your friends. You have asked
him to stop, but he finds it very amusing to watch you blush. What do you do? Feed him up and then
tell him that if he ever calls you that nickname again, you will bloody him worse than this time.
Make up an even more embarrassing nickname for him and use it constantly until he learns his lesson.
Make up a story that makes your nickname a badge of honor instead of something humiliating. That
one. That one. There is a lot of heated discussion at the local tavern over a group of people called
telepaths. They've been hired by certain city state kings. Rumor has it these telepaths read
a person's mind and tell their lord whether a follower is telling the truth or not. This is a
terrible practice. A person's thoughts are his own and no one, not even a king, has the right to make
such invasion into another human's mind. In these times of necessary evil, although you do not
necessarily like the idea, a telepath could have certain advantages during a time of war or, well,
I've got another solution here. When we know we're going up against a telepath, just think of the
worst diarrhea you've ever had in your life. Everybody at the same time. When we're charging
into fight, just think of the time you shit your pants and you sprayed diarrhea all over your
fucking underwear and stuff and they would just see it and they'd fuck them up and then you get
them. It would work. Everyone has to do it though. We all have to do it. On the death counter.
Loyal followers of the king have nothing to fear. I don't even know. I don't like that.
Pocket the extra money knowing that shopkeepers in general tend to overcharge customers anyways.
Return to the store and give the shopkeeper his hard-earned money explaining to him the mistake.
Decide for the extra money to good use and purchase items that would help your family.
I don't know. What's where? What store are we at? Where are we? You're at Walmart.
I would probably say, hey, it depends on the store. It's a mom and pop general store. All right. If
it's a mom and pop general store, I'm going to be like, look, I think there's a mistake here.
I'm not going to do that, right? I know while in a marketplace, you witness a thief cut a purse
from a noble. Even as he does so, the noble notices and calls for the city guards.
Marowark. In case to get away, the thief drops the purse near you. Surprisingly, no one seems
to notice the bag of coins at your feet. What do you do? Leave the bag there and knowing that it's
better not to get involved. Pick up the bag and signal to the guard knowing that the only honorable
thing to do is return the money to its rightful owner. Pick up the bag and pocket it knowing that
the extra windfall will help your family in times of trouble. I don't think I would get
involved in this. It's a noble. So what if I picked it up and brought it to the guards
and they go, there he is. That's the man that stole the noble's purse. I'm going to get
fucking destroyed. I don't know if I want to get involved in this. Oh, here, I found this. Yeah,
right, right? No, I'm not touching anything. Your father sends you on a task which you loathe,
cleaning the stables. On the way there, pitchfork in hand, you run into your friend from the
homestead near your own. He offers to do it for you in return for a future favor of his choosing.
Okay. What do you do? Accept the offer, reasoning that as long as the stables are cleared,
it matters not who does the cleaning. Decline the offer knowing that your father expects you to do
the work and it's better not to be in debt. Ask him to help you knowing that two people can do a
job faster than one and agree to help him with one task of his choosing in the future.
But what's the task? I think I would want to come help me do it because then whatever task...
Somebody said, what lame orc are you making? Okay, sorry, guys. There's me smash head with rock.
It's not on this list. It's only me split the difference with friend. What do you want me to
do here? No, two of us. Your mother asked you to help fix the stove. While you're working,
a very hot pipe slips its moorings and falls towards her. What do you do? Does that happen
to my mother? Position yourself between the pipe and your mother. Push your mother out of the way.
Grab the hot pipe. Hmm. I'm doing... Nope. I want option four. Excuse me. I want option four.
Put leg out, foot out and have whatever it is hit you in the top of the fucking shoe in a
matter how heavy it is, no matter what it is. It's foot out and it doesn't matter how bad it
hurts. This could be a phone. This could be a kitchen item. This could be anything. Foot out.
Catch your foot. Doesn't matter if it smashes. It doesn't matter. No, I'm not a knife. You don't?
No, no. I'm just saying like I do this with any item. I'm always the person that if they see
something about to fall, they go, oh, and they stick. I stick my right leg out to try to catch it
hacky sack style with the top of my shoe every time. But if it was an anvil,
I would still probably do it. This one. While in town, Baker gives you a sweet roll.
Delighted, you take it into an alley. Enjoy only to be intercepted by a gang of three other kids
your age. The leader demands... Wait, why are we kids? Or else he and his friends will beat you
and take it. But why are we children? Give the sweet roll without argument, knowing that later
this afternoon, you will have all your friends with you and you can come take whatever he owes
you. Act like you're going to give the sweet roll, but at the last minute, throw it in the air,
hoping that they'll pay attention to it long enough for you to get a shot in at the leader.
Drop the sweet roll and step on it, then get ready for the fight. Yeah, um, whereas lift up underarm
and wipe sweet roll all over armpit in a circular motion. They're not going to want it after that.
I'm not going to... I'm going to eat it in front of them. Where's eat it anyways?
Neither would you. I'd still eat it. It's my armpit. I'll do this one. Entering town,
you find that you are witness to a very well-dressed man running from a crowd.
He screams to you for help. The crowd behind him seems very angry. Neutral good orc. What is it all?
What orcs? What do you mean? I can't be a good orc? What are you talking about? Entering town,
you find that you are witness to a very well-dressed man running from a crowd. He
screams to you for help. The crowd behind him seems very angry. Stand aside and allow the man
and mob to pass, realizing that it is probably best not to get involved. Okay. Rush to the town's
aid immediately, despite your lack of knowledge of the circumstances. Rush to the man's aid
immediately, despite your lack of knowledge of the circumstances. Okay, here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to get... I'm going to see him running. All right, he's running. There he goes. I'm going
to run to the crowd. First person, the person that's in the front of the crowd is going to
know the most information because they want that guy the most. Not the person that's two, three,
four, five, ten rows back. That person's just there because I guess I'm here, right?
Whoever's in the front of that line running the fastest to get this motherfucker, I'm going to be
like... I'm going to match speed and I'm going to be like, what do you do? What are we doing? What
do you do? What do you do? And then see what he says. This is very contextual. If they're like,
oh man, we're just like trying to get this guy and kick his ass for fun and shoving that guy,
right? Like I'm pushing that guy as hard as I can and then I'm going to turn and it's to be like,
who? Oh no, but then they'd be after me too. Whatever. Your personality and past reflect
a rogue. Okay. Very good. The letter that proceeded, you mentioned you were born under a certain
sign. There's too many of these. Which one of these is good? Which one of these is good?
Pick steed. Okay. Interesting. That is correct. Yes, I think. You now have a stat menu. Right
clicking allows you to use your menus when you are done with them. Show your papers to the captain
when you exit to get your release fee. Read your papers by pressing space bar. Get yourself a
suitable outfit unless you don't mind being mistaken for a slave or a pauper. Okay. Select
skill to train. What? Sneak? I don't get it. Where do I go? I can't breathe this. Hold on.
Is there like a make the UI bigger? Can anybody help me? Lower the resolution. Oh my God. That's
horrible. This is so bad. Oh, I think I crashed it. Can you guys see? Is it? It's fucked up.
It's fucked up. My whole computer is locked up. Come on, dude. Really? Pick it up. Thank you. All
right. Take the death counter off. That joke was funny for five minutes. Mouse. Hello. Where's my
mouse? Okay. Let's just go. This is going to be hard to read, but whatever. You'll go no further
until you have your papers. How do I take stuff? For release by Emperor Uriel Septim, the 567th
decree to the district of Vvardenfell of the province of Morrowind. Name Morrowind. Race orc
class rogue. Signed. Okay. Cool. Take it. Oh my goodness. I can't even see my health. That's how
small my fucking health bar is with this resolution. I'm not going to even know if I take damage. Fix
the UI, dude. I don't, what do you want me to do? What happened? What are you doing? We'll let your
actions go for now, but once you release stuff like that, we'll get you arrested. I picked a
candle up on your desk. Everything is free in this room. Every single object in this room is free.
Stolen for the last time. You've made your last mistake.
What the fuck else is in here?
Can I sell this? Am I getting bad boy points?
You've made your last mistake, thief.
What else is in here? Can I take the rug? Okay. So what do I get? Where's all my stuff?
Where's all my stuff? I picked up everything. Wait, what? Did they take it? Oh, they took it all.
Stop. I'm trying to fucking get out of here. I don't even know what's in here. Oh, sick. How do
I put this on? How do I equip stuff? How do you equip stuff? Check the barrel. Get the ring inside.
Ring of healing. Okay. Take it all. You have a magic menu where you can see all your powers.
All right. Press R to ready active magic. What? How do I do this? Right click, drag it. Oh, there we
go. Okay. What does that do? Talk to the captain. Don't try persuasion on him. If you're not good
at it, he will start to dislike you. Oh, shit. Oh, that's not good. Okay. Well,
oh shit. All right. Well, I'm an orc rogue. I know. I know. I know. Orc rogue. I don't care.
Last night storm could open MW. We've reached Morrowind. I'm sure they'll let us go. Quiet
comes the gun. What did I do to the game? I can't move. I actually can't move. You better do what
they say. I don't know. This guy's on drugs, man. What are you guys? What are you guys doing down
here? You guys are snorting mushrooms down here. Can I leave? This is where you do what they come
with me. Okay, we're good. By the way, fucking shit that Dr. Manhattan did to you. I'm not a fan
either. Not a fan at the end of that movie. Hello. Hi. Good to see you. I'm here. Okay. I am
an orc and I look like this. Yes. Great. I'm sure you'll fit right in. Follow me up to the office
and they'll finish your release. Why do I hear chewy? Okay, I know what I want to be. I don't
need to take all these questions again. Don't steal anything. We've been expecting you. You'll
have to be recorded before you're officially released. There are a few ways we can do this
and the choice is yours. Okay, I would like to pick a class from the list. I was what was I?
All these are cool. I don't want to be something else. I want to be a pilgrim.
Should just be a knight be a thief. Okay. Very good. Merry Christmas. I was like, wow,
he's in Merry Christmas. And what would and it was the steed. Okay. Interesting. All right. Goodbye.
Make sure this information is correct. Looks good to me. Thank you. See you later.
Show your papers to the captain when you exit to get your release speed.
Captain, let's go. See you later. Continue through and talk to Salas Gravius.
Pretty good Star Wars. Luke Skywalker is looking at something music.
You should learn how to do combat. Pick up the dagger on the table and activate it by space bar.
Wait, that was wrong. How do I use it? Okay, press F to pull out your weapon.
Once your weapon is ready to hold and release the left mouse button to swing it the harder you
swing it. Okay. I can't how do I save the game? F5. I can't save the game right now. You get a map.
Okay, cool. Check the barrel to get the ring. Yep. Very cool. I've got my magic item. All right.
Nice. Talk to the captain. Hi. Okay, release. Nobody can read this. So whatever. Morrowind.
You're in Morrowind. I don't know why you're here. Why you were released from prison and shipped
here. But your authorization comes directly from Emperor Rul's symptom, the seventh himself,
and I don't need to know any more than that. All right. Okay. You are free, man. Before you go,
I have instructions on your duties. What are they? This package came with the news of your arrival.
You are to take it to Caius Cossades in the town of Balmora. Go to the south wall corner club
and ask for this. Yeah. Okay. We'll find them. Serve them as whatever. All right. All right.
Thanks. Report to Caius Cossades in Balmora. Balmora is north of Sidonine. The road passes
this village in this fort. So go for it. All right. I got it. You got it. Thank you for everything.
Yes. Bye. I feel like I'm fucking gerbil. How do I get out of my? How do I get out of here?
Save. I can't save the game. Press J to use your journal and review what you've been told. Okay.
I'm sure I don't know how to. Sorry, stranger. I'm training. Shut up. All right. So we got to go
north. Wait, it said check out the trade house. Save. I just did. I saved it already. Popular
scrolls. Um, what's the popular scroll? I don't care. I honestly don't care. I suppose it is my
duty to help those less fortunate than myself recover some gold. That's right. See, I had a
bad run of luck playing nine holes and lost a bit of money. Normally I'd be fine. We can usually
keep some gold in our pockets just from the money the locals pay us for protection.
But now some of them are holding out on me, especially that little
Fetcher Fargoth. He's come up light the last couple of weeks and have shaken them down.
I know he's stashing it somewhere. I'd like you to find Fargoth's hiding place.
Okay. Yeah, sure. I'm not sure where he goes, but I know he wanders around town at night.
Watch his movements. The best vantage point is on top of the lighthouse south of town. That will
give you the nice view of all of this town. Keep an eye on where he goes. Figure out where he's
hiding that gold. All right. We got a quest. I will listen outlander, but make it quick.
All right, let's go. So go to the lighthouse south of town.
All right. Is that the lighthouse? Can you swim in more wind? What the fuck is that thing?
Look at that. How do I pick it up?
Just be the dumbest shit you could ever see. Somebody in the town.
Um, how do I pick them up? Can I eat this? Can I pick it up or something? How do I pick it up?
How do I pick this up? You don't have anything.
All right. Where's the lighthouse? Bro, I can't even jump in this game.
Yep. How do I eat it? This is gross. Should I not be? That seriously is the Star Wars sound.
All right. Where's the lighthouse? Is that the lighthouse here? That's definitely it.
Press E to jump. Why would E if you jump? Okay, so I'm going to go up here at night. Wait,
can I take this stuff? Never mind. Um, you got any little secrets? Buy from merchants and traders
who like you. You get better prices. Okay. Well, of course they treat me better. I'm going to
sneeze in his face. No, I'm not. Okay. We're good. No, he's just a yard. That was weird. That was
weird. That was fucking weird. Whatever. All right. Anybody up here? I can eat this bread.
Is this illegal? This is illegal. That's illegal, but whatever. No one can see me, right? That's
illegal, but I can have it. All right. Well, can I just sleep on the ground? I should have cooked
the crab meat in here. I'm an idiot. What? What's happening? What's going on? I'm literally stuck
on this. How do I sleep on the ground? T? I don't even know what this guy looks like. Is that him?
I don't even know what this guy looks like. What's this guy look like? That's definitely him right
there. Is it a binoculars? That's definitely him right there. He doesn't have a torch anymore.
Is that where he's putting the money? That's where he's putting the money. Okay. I know where he's
putting he put the money in the ocean. Okay. All right. I'm going. Got it. Hell yeah. That's a lot
of money. I'm not going to bring it back. Heal yourself with the ring. How do I open up the,
how do I use magic? Honestly, I would probably bring it back. I just don't know where that guy
even is far. I don't even know where that guy was. So it's in the shop. Oh, okay. He's here.
Buy some stuff. All right. What do you got? Barter? Oh, dude, I have so much money now.
I'm a thief, right? So could I get like a cool dagger? Shake a fork? Oh, pants. Wait, okay.
Armor, iron greaves, iron arrow. What should I get? Why am I yawning? What the heck? I don't know why
I'm yawning. I've never yawned on stream before. It's a boring, boring game. I actually have been
having fun. Okay. Iron dagger. There we go. That's the one I'm going to take. Iron dagger. Let's go.
Where is it? Did I buy it? Um, also I'm going to get, Oh, I already had one of these. Oops.
Maybe like a short sword. What about spear? What's a tanto? No, I want to put them on.
I want to equip them. How do I? I can't fucking see anything, man. Offer? Okay. Do I have any
other clothes? I need pants. I'm going to get a sword. Sure. Iron sword. Buy it. There we go.
I need a helmet too. Do not start a new fucking game, man. I need a helmet. I don't want to talk
to you. All right. You're supposed to find the hiding place. Did you find it? You found the
hiding place? That's great. Where's the gold? You're trying to hold out on me, Orc? You found his
hiding place? That's great. Where's the gold? You're trying to hold out on me, Orc? Um, I'm going to
bribe him 100 gold. I hear you, Orc rogue. You're welcome. See? All right. What do you got? Services.
Dump? What? What? All right. I need some, I need some quests. Put me on a quest. Do you have anything
in a specific place or a quest? Oh no, I gotta go north. All right. See you guys later.
Balmora. That's right. Bring out the windows magnifying glass. All right. North. What the fuck
do these signs say? Oh, this way. I'm a caravaner. I can transmit you to this place. Nah. Yeah. It's
so dark. I can't see anything. Can I turn the gamma up? That doesn't do anything. Oh, what's this?
Yeah, I'll take it. Am I going the right way? Mushrooms. Oh, change the time. Oh shit. A rat.
Can hurt rat meat. Yep. This way. How could you do that? I don't know. I'm so blown out now.
Look at me. I'm super blown out. I'm blown out right now. That's better. What does it look? Why
does it look? This looks weird, doesn't it? I'm blown out. Why is the FPS so shitty? I don't get
it. Whatever. I tried. I asked a random dude if they liked watching you. They asked you what's
a good anime? Um, Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood. What is that? Is that friendly? Is this thing asleep?
Can I talk to it? This thing is sleeping. Can you can I ride it? That's cute. I like that thing.
Okay, I lost track of where I was going. I think it's this way. That monster is bored. No, no,
this way. Wait, something over here at adventure awaits us. What's over here? Random adventure
awaits in Morrowind. How do you quick? How do you look? What the fuck? What happened to me?
What happened? Did I walk into the fire? What? I don't understand what happened. I'm definitely
this too high for me, but whatever. I can probably get the kill. Let's go. Fuck it.
How the fuck are you supposed to do this? What class am I? I don't piano player,
whatever it is. Bored. I don't even know. What am I? I got a better idea.
You are taking up the in top. How is your body taking up the entire tunnel?
That is how how do I heal our right? I don't fucking care. Adventure awaits on the road.
This game is 80 years old today. Wait, I can use my other knife. I have another knife.
I can't use that. Oh, Balmora. Oh, a citizen. Is there anything I can do for you to help?
How are you? There's a bandit nearby. Yes, I was just walking along here, minding my own business.
Suddenly a bandit jumped at me from behind. He was a dark elf, a strong dashing dark elf.
He didn't harm me in any way, although he did take my jewels. He was quite gentle and he talked
me for a while. What? What is going on? Oh, never mind the jewels. I just want to find that bandit
again. He was charming and funny, and I simply must see him again. His name, Nellos, Nellos
Anmar, a name that will stay on my lips for eternity. Perhaps you can find him. Please,
I cannot live without knowing if you could ever love me. I have nothing to offer you in return,
but could you not help me for the sake of love? Sure. Okay, I'm sure you'll be able to find him.
He mentioned something about having to head north, so I imagine he might be found in
Peligaiad. Please, find and give him this glove for me as a token of my love. I'm certain he will
want to find me again. Okay, can I keep the jewels? All right, so Peligaiad. See you later.
What? What? Oh shit, she's a fucking wizard.
Oh, no, no, no. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What the fuck?
What the fuck? I thought I had this... I'm supposed to be a thief.
Now you have to flee. I don't have to flee, do I? What the hell is going on with this door?
What the fuck is this? Did I just let out like the demon bug? Oh my god, it's coming out of me.
What the... What is behind that door? That's way... That music is way too heroic for
what's in here. Do you understand? That was like a nice... That wasn't scary demon music.
Am I even hitting this? Dude, I'm gonna prove to everybody how cool I am. I'm gonna kill this
thing. Holy shit, I just killed... I look what I just did. So what was in here? What? It's an electric
fence? Why is there an electric fence in here? What are you talking about? That took me so long
to die too. That was an actor. What are you gonna do about it? Huh? What are you gonna do about it?
You're gonna open that door? That trap door? Come on. Why don't you open it? Open it. Open the door.
Come on. Open the door. Holy shit. You guys are fucking... You guys are fucking idiots. I can
literally just... I can just jump over this. What a shitty door. Can we talk? Open the door. Why won't
you talk? Open the door. Open it. Coward. Open the door, coward. Open the door, coward.
Oh my god. I can get over there. I don't know how to heal. I... Is it R? R doesn't do anything.
Look. Restore health. How come I can't do it? R. F. Equip the ring. It is equipped, isn't it?
Press T to heal out of combat from enemies. You got bottom right corner on the menu.
Guys, I can't see that. It's... Wait. Magic. The menu. Guys, I can't see... Okay, I have to look at
LBS because I literally can't see from here down. It's cut off on my monitor. Where is it? How do I
press it? I can't even see that either. It's cut off from here down. How do I do it though? Not that
one. I don't get it. Down the map. The other menu. Oh, this one? Oh, okay. All right. All right. I
got it. Why am I... Why am I sounding like a fucking animal? Oh my god. I'm dying. Fuck this place.
This sounds like Heroes of Might and Magic and one of like the town menus. Does this have... Wait,
I have some stuff. I get... This is 60 bucks? Put a ring? Can I put a ring on?
Um, I can't even... I can't read this. Oh, right. Let me heal.
Where's my head? What's berserk? Oh, different spell. Oh, cool. All right.
Let's go. Oh, fucking pop in. I need to... I don't have a sign. Okay. This way.
Yeah, you don't have that on you. Whatever. Itchy armpit.
Okay. This way. Oh, do you have robot legs? I don't know. No, this way. Did I make it? What's in
here? Wait. Do I have to go that way to... Oh, wait. I killed that lady. Never mind. Still... But hold
on. But what is over here? I'm curious. I want to see what's in here. What's this about? Hello? Uh,
any rumors? Okay. What do you got in here? Wooden door. Wooden door. Prison tower. Wait, can I
release prisoners? This is a really weird prison. Um, what the fuck did I come all the way up here
for? Nice view. Yeah. Can I do anything here? It's just a fort? Um, persuasion. Um, admire.
You notice... Oh, yes. Orc rogue. It's true. Okay. A weapon or something. Maybe.
What can I do here? The back of your shirt looks like a face. It does. Oh, okay. Here we go. What
do you want? Training. Are you a member? No, then my services are not for you. What do you do? I'm
a master at arms. I'm a master of all the basic hand weapon types. Willing to train with weapons
for a fee. So let me in. Frozen North sounds awful to me. Any rumors? Something. You like to dance
close to the fire, don't you? Do you got potions? I'm a trader. All right. So let's do. What do you
got? Iron club. Oh, steel throwing star. Very cool. Oh, I can sell you some stuff here. You want
this? That's worth 60 bucks. This is worth a lot of money. I mean, I'm not getting good value for
this. Did I just get bad value? No, I'm good. Okay. All right. What about... Oh, he's not cool.
Get rid of these shoes. Oh, I got but one shoulder pad. Why do you sell? You don't someone pairs?
That's weird. There we go. Okay, nice. Goodbye. Can I sleep down here? Wait, long blade block.
Medium armor. Do I have a long blade? Your webcam is fucked. Oh my god. What the hell? It really is.
I can't. I don't even know where the mouse is. I can't even turn. I can't fix it. Oh my god.
Where's my mouse? Where? This is... Yeah, this is so fucked up. Why? Wait, that made it so much worse.
This thing sucks. Whatever. Okay, so I've got to keep going. Thanks. Wait, you got weapons. Weapon.
All right. Give me something cool. Something good. Steel short sword. I have iron. Steel better than
iron. Silver short sword. Oh, fuck. Give me that. And you can take this and give me the steel short
sword. Thank you very much. Nice. Okay. Cool. Silver kills undead. Very cool. Yes. All right.
Back to what I was doing. Going the right way, right? Yes. Balmora. Ben. Ben. Are these things
alive? All right. What do you got here? Anything I can do? Change the resolution. I can't. What's up?
All right. I'm Hull. Welcome to Balmora. We're a house Halalu town and loyal to citizens of the
empire. What can I do for you? Someone in particular. None of the Halalu counselors live in
Balmora. Neleno Dorvayne at the council hall is the ranking Halalu local at the Fighters Guild.
Edis Fireeye is the steward. Atsasi Rilvayne is the Morag Tong steward. Feldrello Sadri is the
steward for the Balmora Tribunal Temple Sugar Lips. Habassi is the local Thieves Guild boss.
Who am I missing? Oh, Mages Guild. All right. Thanks for the earful. I want the Thieves Guild,
right? Who am I looking for? I'm looking for somebody in particular, right? Speak quickly.
Oh, yeah. Sadis. Whatever. Any rumors? Someone in particular. All right. I'm looking for Sadis.
Headvid. Okay. Meldor. Guard. Did I sleep in that guy's bed? Oh, all right. Wait,
nobody can see me down here, right? Oh, fuck yeah. Oh, the Affairs of Wizards. Okay, cool.
I was gonna take the bed. Shirt. Oh my god, money. Okay. I'm not gonna get in trouble, right? How
would they have known I was down here? I have a lockpick. Holy shit, you got a battle axe in here?
I'll put the lockpick away. This guy's got so much shit all over the ground. This guy has ancient
armor on the ground. Did I get it? I think I got it. This thing was an ancient relic. Holy shit,
this thing is amazing. What? Oh my god, that thing's amazing. I'm still looking for this person. Did
it say they lived here? Nope. Okay. You violated the law orc rogue since you turned yourself in
voluntarily. I'll take that into consideration. What? No, I didn't. I asked him a question.
59 gold? This thing was probably like 4,000. Hey no, I want that back. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Reload. I don't
want that. Nope. Fuck that. Nope. I refuse. You know, I got a better fucking idea. Fuck this.
watch this no more swearing but watch this dude can i hope do you think i can make it out honest
to god i think i can take everything off this shelf and just get out as fast as i can i think
i can get i think i can do it i got some of it at least did i get enough okay i got the shield and
i got the helm oh hell yeah okay perfect oh shit i shouldn't look at my hall i am running this up
fast i've run
now what is he gonna follow me for oh my god can i hide in the water he's gaining on me
wait i have an idea take him into one of those dungeons and have one of those bare things eat
him nice try is he coming this way no what you will die i was trying to steal his i was trying
to steal from where is this guy south wall all right south wall corner club bro i think i just
found it yes no where is he has no words what's this about where is this person do you know who
i'm looking for there we go okay i don't know what your business with him is but be careful
may appear to be pathetic old man but don't judge by appearances some people made that
mistake a while ago now they're not with us anymore where where is he before i steal everything off
the top row the old gray hair gobbles sugar like scuttle she ran here is surprised he still walks
but doesn't affect him that is the mark of a longtime user okay the old sugar tooth i'm not
sure where he's living now but ask bakola closest the owner he'll know all right they didn't name
you training sugar lips habasi cannot serve you if you're not a member of the thieves guild
join the thieves guild you look like you may have some skill you want to join or maybe you
want to know what we're all about yeah let me in you are now a toad in the thieves guild welcome
brother orc rogue talk to me when you want some odd jobs to do and when you think you're ready
for advancement you have a price if you have a price on your head there are those you can
talk to as well talk to pain rylic and alderaan it's tongue toad whatever all right what do you
got for a job good friend wants a diamond friend wants a diamond from habasi had okay this person
had diamonds last time they sniffed over there what northwest side of town go across the river
turn right somebody one of you screenshot this okay i gotta go to the diamond you wish to speak
or just read the journal you have a journal right but i don't press j sorry stranger my time is
short so get on with it don't press your luck where is this owner there we go all right where
is this person old chaos rents a little bed and basket just up the hill in the north edge of town
going all out the front door not the upper door to the terrace then right up the stairs then left
to the top this did you i somebody fucking write that down can i please just jump off i don't want
to walk down the stairs and fine okay so i got a couple things i go get a diamond
north side of town so let's go up here and we're looking for somebody uh somebody's store all right
where's this person located speak traveler the morag tong does not respect those who debase the
sacred art of murder he's talking to me all right northern side of town i mean that's where i am
dude i'm eating tuna straight from the can grab some mayo dude get some mayo and some bread
and relax i know you you're orc rogue the notorious outlaw let me out of here i'm not telling you
anything else go now yeah see this you see this it's made of silver no what's what was it called
oh shit my north side of town i gotta go up here wait i can just look is it is there more up here
that i'm not seeing eat that bread i don't need to you came up and fucking smelled me i
that was fucking weird i don't know man i'm sorry guys this this is what that interaction was
but walking normally i'm walking normally everyone's calling me crazy and insane
i'm i'm fucking insane right i'm the crazy one walking normally by somebody and they go
fucker you get the fuck away from me and i try to steal something and where's this place whoa
shit that person was stupid that was a player that was a player that didn't realize who i was
oh shit all right where's this house where's this house where's the house where's the house where's
the house oh they're gaining on me they're gaining on me why would i go into the guard
tower this is the guard tower and why would i go in here oh my god and then i'm gonna fucking write
in big like red ink like fuck you i was here and they're gonna know exactly who it was i can't move
i can't move i can't move i can't move dude can i eat this how do i get rid of this
how do i get rid of this i'm fucking stealing i'm stealing serving platters like what am i
gonna do with these oh why does the door open this way what are you doing i can't don't move
he doesn't see me i'm stuck in a fucking door oh my god i haven't saved it in like an hour
oh open this way what kind of a psycho has a door no you always have the door open this way every
time oh no i got i'm good okay thank god thank god i was smart enough you never catch me i will
listen outlander but make it quick now where go right for the quest
so
why can't we hurt each other oh my god fucking stop it
so put it on finish your current attack
sorry dude sorry dude i have i had mono sleeping for like honest jesus christ
how do i get i can't move this guy's been here rotting for 24 hours all right is anybody come
find him it's been two days three days i spent almost a full work week in this guy's house
what day is it okay can you imagine this person's been sleeping all right so this person's asleep in
your bed and you get in a big fight with him and he leaves and does it you like kind of i don't
know how about that guy must have been here for a while what the fuck i wonder how long he was
here for maybe like 40 minutes and there's there is a warm imprint of a person's body and it's hot
to the touch they've been there for a very very long time what is all this shit i don't want any
of this what am i just taking this guy just take out the drugs the guy had in his house just take
it all whatever how do i do it i'm just literally i'm just drinking everything that this guy has
this could be windex i don't even know what it is okay am i still over encumbered can i eat the
candle why am i sprinting what's going on okay that was scary holy shit this guy had a silver dagger
oh my god i got a whole new outfit this is perfect wow all right where's that steel dagger
yeah let's fucking go why am i holding a candle oh he's got money
just for good measure just to bm him a little bit more all right i'm ready
um wait these are expensive okay let's go
so hey hey nothing hates me man i just love sleeping can i just tell you that that's why
you even see me in a while hey you remember this thing called lucid dreaming oh shit i'll tell you
later i'll tell you later what was the quest all right i think i'm good oh my god leave me alone
dude oh fuck speak traveler ahead am i safe um somebody has a diamond where is that diamond
you gotta be kidding me man how do i swim up how do i swim up why am i not swimming up how do i
swim up how do you swim up just look up okay i think i'm good can i get out of the water
oh there we go all right so where's this house this is where's it somebody help me find this
person's house okay i have a better idea this is worse i need to go rejoin the thieves guild
what do you mean i'm already in thieves guild diamond is a northwest corner of town in the
alchemy shop all right northwest corner of town like here so i'm gonna go this way that guy's
right next to me he is guys i think i know what's wrong no it's that's not what's wrong never mind
wait this is the guy god damn it where fuck him up where but where is the guy will you get away
from me i don't want to jump in the water again but leave me alone up the stairs here
oh that one's pretty good oh my fucking god what happened i got leveled up where where is this
person the ks casada sky is in the top right part of town northeast you've reloaded to a save where
you didn't join the thieves guild okay all right i get it i get it i get it i get it i get it i get
it i get it i get it i get it where's the thieves guild right here right
i'm ready to bash your fucking brains in if you come over here
there we go all right i'd like to join the thieves guild look at i have a cool
thieves guild outfit on i'd like to join the thieves guild you may have some skill
let me in all right i'm now a toad go get a diamond where's that diamond you got it you got it
northwest side of town go across the river turn right cross the river whatever turn right or
something whatever you know any rumors all right now it's up here is that him you like to walk a
fine line don't you where is this person oh right there that's it right there northwest corner all
the way over here okay all the way in the northwest corner what the fuck is going on here get me out
of here why am i like alphabetically looking at stuff okay is this it dumber temple we're
gonna we're just gonna investigate for a minute we'll have nothing to do with a notorious outlaw
until you've cleared your name or paid your debt to society don't talk to us where's this person
you're gonna call the guards you sure about that don't be stupid what do you got in here
holy shit oh continue running executable uh yeah well i think something broke go to the jail
no i'm gonna lose all my cool i've got a cool outfit and shit all right i'm going to where i'm
supposed to go i'm going up here this is it north west part of the town diamonds in a shop in the
northwest part of town yeah but like this town is huge remove your bounty with the thieves gold
i'm not cool enough they said i'm not cool enough yet is this it oh my goodness it was such a high
price on your head everyone assumes you're a murderer i don't know the details and don't want
to know but great house falo won't be pleased we're judged by your actions and we don't need
things like you getting us a reputation as murderers so clear my name let's go clear my name
it's crazy get lost clear my name all right bye just go to jail i will eventually but i want to
find this diamond over here did i find it read the door of the place should have the name of the
person do you want something now karya of white haven okay well where is this person
read the door these guys are i have like anti magnets or something i've magnetized
they won't come near me no got it give me the diamond now i know you you're orc rogue the
notorious outlaw look i don't want any trouble but you're scaring me and i can't think straight
when i'm scared give me the diamonds i buy them off you why can i get them owner of the south
wall all right well what's what's going on give me those diamonds now i will not yield give me
the diamonds how do i do the how do i say i want the diamonds for the quest is it necessary that
you speak with me i can't go up here this guy's gonna see me 4800 gold what you've been released
after 48 days and i lost all this i'm going out like that pointless give in
i got a quick save stupid idiots i have time travel you don't i'm gonna time travel back
before you even arrested me you go up the fucking stairs you imbecile oh i could have just gone up
here all right okay in morrowind to usd what is four what is 5000 gold in morrowind to usd what
would that be we go back downstairs already you annoying little asshole there's a fresh pie on
that counter i want it can i seriously like it i gotta i have to just clear my name i have to
just get arrested i'm never gonna be able to do anything i got a better fucking idea hide the
items if what do you mean if i well this actually work i don't know what's stolen and what's not
stolen so i'm gonna throw it all no put that back on that's a pretty damn good sandwich i'm gonna
despawn them okay so what the fuck i i throw my stuff away all right they have to be in a building
oh you already aggroed this guy all right um i've had just about fucking enough i've had just about
what the fuck never mind why does he not care why does he not care give me the fucking diamond
give me the diamond now just it's in there i know it's in here somewhere just give it to me
move out of the way hold on i i'll get this in a minute hey watch out for the lady okay i'm gonna
kill her i'm just gonna kill her and leave i'm gonna kill her and leave i fucked this whole
playthrough up so bad i'm just gonna kill her and leave i'm in the thieves guild i'm a bad guy
it's on the shelf patience is limited are you dumb why would you put diamonds on a shelf that
right there you gotta be stupid guys that was really dumb okay i got a quest complete now i
gotta go talk to northeast right oh shit all right where's that okay this way i'm going back to the
guild yep make it quick outlander did i do we have any money i thought oh my god what
you are you so fast i am self this is self-defense this is self-defense this is self-defense it's
self-defense everybody all right where is it where is it down right here okay so i just
gotta go this way and then come up you're gonna have to flee into the wilderness
that's fine i just want to do my job do i don't have a bow and arrow he's a menace to society
one of the reasons why i really can't play any of the games like this elder scrolls or whatever
is because it snowballs i take a plate off of a shelf and i owe 20 gold and then i punch the
guy that tries to get the you know the warrant from me i then kill a lady in the next to the
hold on it just snowballs and now i owe 10 grand i have an uncountable amount of money that i have
to pay back so it's over just don't be a fucking loon it's like grand theft auto but in great okay
in gta if i punch a person on the street i okay oh you get oh you get you die you go you get
whatever the place you want it wasted there are game altering consequences for like punching
somebody gta style on street i know i know it's not gta but i i can't help it i'm going downstairs
any game with freedom i just kind of punch a person
watch your step you're gonna need no no more stealing let's go all right so now it's right
here no it's not where is it right there that's this building here all right quest going in
don't press your luck this better be important did it diamond i have a diamond here it is
oh we'll take everything habasi cannot pay you until habasi's friend pays habasi
but habasi has this potion to give you are you out of your fucking mind
it's a healing spell relax you never seen a healing spell before
come on man say something or move out get rid of the bounty i owe ten thousand dollars
go to the basement for a small fee i can take care of that word on the street is that you've
got about 5300 gold on your head as you're a thieves guild member i could fix it for 2678
it's smart thinking toad but you don't i don't it's still a ton what's this then it's like
somebody being like oh dude you owe 10 million dollars dude just pay me three million dollars
and it'll be fine i it's still it's over a million dollars that's gonna be impossible for me
you understand it doesn't matter what it is it's over a certain threshold sell all your armor
well can i sell my armor to this guy this guy has 150 bucks i can't get two three thousand gold
from this person what's it do i have anything that's worth anything holy shit this stuff is
worth a lot of money this is worth a thousand bucks what the fuck 300 all right i might be able
to actually do this okay can i just do this okay what is all this don't sell your armor no i'm
not gonna it suffers wounds why am i blurry that's a new camera save before any crimes
because you're just gonna be an outlaw yeah it's all right if i can help i will but don't take too
much it's all good okay so now what was the other thing i had to do find this person they're
apparently up here right go to jail you just got the armor dude just go to jail walk to the end
of the street to win the game northeast corner all right you got it god i wish there was a burp
button okay so where is this guy am i looking for i missed it i don't i don't know i don't know
what i'm looking for binaf armor go to the up the stairs wasn't that a guard house though this one
this scent is new get away from me you look like spring trap
that's so stupid the next stairs these ones no
oh there he is okay hi i've been looking for you i've been looking for you that's you i found you
i'm just an old man uh-huh uh how what am i supposed to do with you terrible place what am i
supposed to do i found him i need to kill this guy you had a package what do you mean i had a
package i had a package to give this person i dropped the book oh my god
fuck this game i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done that was fun this game is fun but
like i can't i gee the game crashed anyways the game literally shit the bed i a game crashed