Oh, no friendly fire. We always play with no friendly fire.
Um, that was a nice ghost car.
I like alt-tabbed. Let me fix my mouse.
That guy-
This guy just like pull up so I can get in his car. Thanks.
I think he just peeped you.
It's a pretty nice car. Thank you.
You didn't have to- he- what?
He's the nicest person I've ever seen in this game and you shoot him.
I only shoot- I shot- I shot him in the ass. He'll be alright.
He's dead.
Have you ever seen Forrest Gump?
Yeah, thank you for coming everybody. Shady Home is Retirement Home.
Yeah, we do a garage sale every year here.
We make sure we have two armed guards because, you know, just in case something goes wrong.
It's been such a long day at work. I just want to park my stupid forklift.
The joke is over.
Redo.
You cannot fit in here with this thing.
I'm getting in.
Oh my god, it's spazzing out.
You actually got it in the garage with a jump truck.
How are you gonna get out?
It's gonna explode.
Don't let it explode.
I can't fix it.
I don't know how you got in here. You killed M.
Oh my god, the laws of physics.
Come on, do something.
Lady, lady, that was not a good place for cover.
Crouching on the sidewalk was not a good place.
Look at this dipshit.
Oh, I'm gonna get him.
I tried, it didn't work.
All right, try to get in here again.
Where the hell did the helicopter come from?
This is not designed for this to happen.
You almost saved me because...
Okay, into the sky.
Into the sky with you.
Into the sky.
What the fuck?
This guy got you on the ear.
He got you on the balls.
This guy is taking so many bullets.
This guy is getting so ripped apart by bullets.
Now he runs, oh, because you're here.
I just want to be with Star.
Hey, Cobbs, remember how you were really mad at me?
Oh, hi, sir.
Weren't we just like shooting at you a quarter of a second ago?
This guy's kicking the shit out of me, by the way.
Can I come back you up?
You're gonna have to.
He's gonna kill me.
Me.
This guy still wants to fight you.
This guy is a maniac.
Oh, not anymore.
You gave him diarrhea.
Oh, I've got diarrhea.
Oh, give me to a bathroom.
Oh, I've given...
Jerma, look at me.
I've been given too much power.
I know how to do this.
What?
I'm dead.
I'm alive though.
It's doing that thing again.
It's doing the thing where I'm dead, but I'm not dead.
I just got up and...
I'm just getting a silly shot again.
Dude, what is...
Please, let me get...
Jerma, get up.
Help me.
Help.
I...
Move me.
Push me.
Do anything.
I'm not sure you're on the same place, like on the same screen as me.
Where are you laying?
I'm lying next to this cop car that you're rolling into.
I'm lying just on the ground right here.
I'm just getting riddled with bullets.
Yeah, I'm dead.
The same thing happened.
And I kept on getting up and getting lit up again.
Okay, that was ridiculous.