Oh, fuck, my mic's on. Hey, hey guys, how are you? How's everybody doing? You're not supposed to hear me like...
Alright, so yeah, everybody, this is- I'm just here.
So the- there's an M&M's commercial now for Halloween, and the implications in the M&M commercial
are that the M&M's are fucking dead. The yellow M&M and the red M&M are walking around a house.
It's like a scary house and the red M&M's like, hey, yellow, we almost got eaten this year.
Good thing that was a close one. And yellow is a ghost walking through walls with a big bite out of his head.
He's like, yeah, I think so too. Yeah, we really got out of that one. And this motherfucker's dead. Like they killed the yellow M&M.
He's dead. Hey, Fred.
He's dead. I'm serious. Can we watch it on stream? I don't think we can watch it on stream.
This is like a commercial that came out like today.
They're writing off the yellow M&M? No, I don't know. I'm just telling you, he's dead in the commercial.
Run ads until we see it.
Alright, we'll see it eventually. Just a couple more Samsung phone commercials. We got seven of them in a row.
Run ads until we see it. I'm telling you guys, you'll see it on TV. The yellow M&M is dead. He's dead.
He's a ghost with a big bite out of his head.
Here it is right here. Is it? He better not be bullshit. This is it? This is it. Alright, here we go. Let's watch this.
Can I do this? Is this allowed? Can I watch like an ad on TV?
Wait, it can't be. Is something wrong with this? Well, we're just gonna watch the part where it shows that he's dead.
I'm not gonna put it in the- hold on.
Here's- just wait a second. I want to show this to you. Oh, look at that. Oh, no. That's my stream key.
That's my stream key. Oh, that's my stream key. Alright, watch.
He's dead. He was- he was killed.
They killed the yellow M&M. He's fucking dead.
Anyways, we're gonna play- that was an ad. It was, but I was- I was- I was making my comments on that ad.
So I was commenting on it. Yeah, see? No, I was transforming that content.
See, what happened was the ad played and I went, see?
And I transformed it and it actually turned into mine. It was transformed.
React, Mr. Reaver.
Anyways, hi guys. Let's go back to the intro because we're not- we're not here yet.
We are, but kind of not. Here, back to the intro.
You're shilling M&M's. Guys, see, M&M's have been around for like 150 years. I don't think they need any more advertising help.
Like, I- I- I- I wouldn't- M&M's, I wouldn't be surprised if they showed up in the national anthem, okay?
It's been like 150 years. That would do- everyone knows what a fucking M&M is.
Poor Liz for corporate takeover.
Now, we're gonna play, uh, Man of Badan. It's not Man of Badan. I keep calling it Man of Badan.
It's the Dark Pictures anthology.
Little Hope. It's the second in that series that they're doing.
And we're gonna play with italics. We played this with italics last time, so might as well play them until
they're gonna do eight of these.
See you in a year when the third one comes out and then they cancel the rest of them.
I don't think they're gonna do this for like seven or eight straight years from now.
I think it's- saying eight, I think might have been a little- a little much to say.
That's almost ten years apparently, because the last one came out a year ago.
So, if they're on pace for ten years of content, maybe this is just what they're gonna do. Maybe Supermassive,
they're just like, you know what, fuck it. Let's just do this scary
movie kind of choose-your-own-adventure games, and that's just what we're gonna do for the next ten years. Maybe?
I'll give them some credit where it's due. I mean, it's kind of interesting to be able to share a story like this.
The first one was okay.
It was okay.
We had our fun with it. This is the second one. We're gonna give it a chance.
So, I don't know, we have no idea how this works. We're just gonna do new story. We'll just, uh,
Alex should be joining us in any minute here. You got scammed twice.
Um, well, no, I enjoyed the last one. I mean, it was- it was a little dopey, but it was still fun.
Turn your facecam on? You might get a facecam for some of this stream. How's that sound? Driver install waiting room.
I- I have the brand new driver from yesterday. There ain't any other drivers I can install.
This one's good?
All right, I'll take your word for it. I think we're- I think we're ready to go. Are we?
Are we good to go? I'm good to go.
Are you good to go?
Ladies and gentlemen, that's, uh-
I am ready.
That's italics. Those of you that don't know.
Oh, everybody knows.
Everybody wants to see this happen.
You think that they- these people in the stream haven't heard of me?
Excuse me?
We got an ego stroker here. Okay.
Okay, I've got a, uh,
bot trawling for anyone that who omega lols.
You're getting- you're getting hoed like crazy right now. You don't who italics.
He's been around for like- we've like known each other for like ten fucking years.
Listen, they're just revealing who is a fucking fake fan right now in your stream.
That's true.
These are people who omega lol who have only just gotten to your stream in the last
365 days.
Oh shit.
He's calling a lot of you guys out, and I have nothing I can do about it.
I mean, I could just boot him. You ready?
Let's go.
Fake fans.
You already get- he is kind of toxic though. I feel like- I've said- I've asked him like questions before and he's like,
What are you dumb? I'm like, dude, I'm not dumb. What are you toxic? And then he ghosts me for two days.
It's like fucking come on, dude.
He's right.
Oh, do you want to be Anthony or Tanya?
Whoever is left over.
Okay, so who do I want to be?
Do I want to be Anthony?
You're the like, player one right now.
Yeah, I am player one.
Anthony, Anthony, Anthony, Anthony, Anthony, Anthony.
All right, all right, all right. What is it?
Oh, because Anthony, Anthony. Okay, I guess that makes sense.
All right, you're gonna be Tanya, I guess.
Okay.
Does it say you're ready?
Hold on, you can't get ready up on a controller, you have to push the enter button.
Oh, he's on a controller?
He's not even a PC gamer?
Listen, I gotta get the last life out of this Xbox One Series X Elite Bundle version before it gets replaced in like-
Did you put subtitles on?
To play with a controller, press A.
To play with point and click controls using a mouse, press this one.
That was me.
Was I supposed to select something? Because I just left clicked and then it started loading.
Oh, you left clicked? I think you just- you selected keyboard and mouse.
Did I really?
Yep. All right, shh. Don't talk during the cutscene.
Unless there's some wicked fun to you, I have to say.
If you do, just talk over the fucking game.
Oh, shit.
Already paused.
I was turning off the volume.
I was gonna turn off the volume of the game.
All right, dude, just go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hit the- hit the button.
Ooey gooey.
I'm sorry. All right, stop.
Was it a book called The Wild Dick?
The romance section.
The Wild Dick.
This game's fucking boring.
I think I'm- I don't wanna do this anymore.
Like, oh, he drove a bus. It's just fucking fun.
I was just gonna say something I can't-
I'm not gonna say it.
I'm gonna say it because this bus is-
Oh, everyone's gonna leave if I say it.
But, like, who cares? I'm just gonna do it.
It's so loud, but I can't alt-tab without pausing the game.
Dude, this bus is-
This bus is- I can't even fucking-
You know what I was gonna say. Who cares?
What?
Oh, I was gonna say, yo, this bus is kinda sus.
I told you you were all gonna fucking leave if I did that.
Where's the subtitles?
I put them on.
Oh, I thought Little Hope was, like, the name of, like, a little kid or something.
Like, Little Hope is, like, the scary girl.
Turn on the- I will.
Oh, hey, dude, did you know that the yellow M&M's dead?
Damn. Alright.
Is he imagining this, or are the people in the bus doing this?
Are you suggesting the people on the bus are psychic?
No, I feel like the people talk on a bus.
He was supposed to drop them off.
No one was talking.
Oh, bearing updated. What does that mean?
Alright, I gotta turn subtitles on.
Listen, between scenes.
Subtitles.
Okay, did you turn on subtitles yet?
Subtitles? Minimal? What?
All.
I think all is, like,
describes sounds and, like-
Yeah, but I had them on.
I think I have mine on minimal.
Were you getting subtitles during that cutscene?
I wasn't. What the fuck is this?
I'm supposed to be going through my TV. This is bullshit.
I'm going to keep it on.
Hang on, you have a TV?
I don't have a TV because I don't wear two headphones.
I'm one headphone Andy.
Listen, I don't think there's been a co-op stream in history
that hasn't had at least five technical difficulties.
Well, this is fine.
I'll just turn it up.
Are you good?
So I turned on all,
so therefore, I should see all the subtitles.
What is happening?
I did not do anything!
You did. He's lying.
How do you get jumpscared with one headphone?
Only on the right side.
If there's a jumpscare that happens over here,
like if there's a person off-screen that's screaming over here,
if it's like,
Hey, chat, what-
Is the game playing for you?
No, it says you keep pausing the game.
I'm not.
It's just a nice screensaver
of this winter home.
There's nothing on my screen.
It says pause by etal.
I have not. I've done no such thing.
Do you have a controller? Press start.
There's no menu. If I hit escape, the mouse disappears.
Okay, what about now?
Listen, I don't like throwing out
red flags within the first ten minutes,
but I think it crashed.
It did?
Well, alright, we'll just start over and we'll skip the first cutscene.
Alright, I'm gonna return to main menu,
and then I'm gonna invite you again.
Wait, it's Alex, have you updated your graphics drivers?
In general, or like literally yesterday?
Because there was a new driver yesterday,
but I did not update that one.
You needed the Watch Dogs Legion driver.
Okay, shared story, let's go.
I'm creating your session.
Okay, I'm inviting you.
I just gave you an e-vite.
Watch Dogs is cursed.
Watch Dogs Legion waiting room.
Oh, you're gonna be waiting a real
long fucking time.
I would rather play The Surge 2
sitting on a spiked chair.
Did you say The Surge 2?
Yes, then open up Watch Dogs Legion again.
Did you get my invite?
I haven't even gotten, okay, I just got back to the main menu.
Sick.
Why are these transitional buttons so long?
Saw 2 waiting room.
Both of those games are never showing up ever again.
Dude, should I just play Surge 2
on a spiked fucking chair?
Would that be like TOS?
I don't think you would last 30 minutes.
No, but if it was like a fake spiked chair
and I'm sitting there going like, oh, oh!
No, I don't care about the spiked chair,
I'm talking about The Surge 2.
You think I could sit on a spiked chair
longer than I could play The Surge 2?
I do. In separate circumstances?
That's so funny.
Okay, we'll see.
So you're saying that I would be able to
be okay getting tortured
than play The Surge 2?
Yes.
What's your other bottom 2 game?
It's The Surge 2 and
Evil Within 2.
I hated that game.
I didn't think that was as bad as The Surge.
Yeah, Mario Tennis.
How can someone hate Mario Tennis?
I hate that game, it's fucking stupid, I hate it.
Rockstar's Table Tennis.
I didn't play it.
That's toxic?
You guys know that I don't like Mario Tennis,
that's not like a secret.
Continue the story.
Do you have a button to press?
I have already pushed it.
Okay, here we go.
I think there's just too many people playing this right now
and their servers are having problems.
Welcome to any game that's released after 2015.
Play it 3 weeks later and the game will actually work.
There's no such thing as a game launch anymore.
They just like back up a dump truck
and dump the code out in your front fucking lawn
and then
somebody shows up like 3 weeks later
and cleans up the garbage on your front lawn.
Well, this is probably good because
the first time I didn't know I was supposed to
push the controller button.
Alright, we're good, this is it, we're ready.
We're in the house now.
Stop it, James. You know I hate it when you don't take
the things I say seriously.
Come on, sweetheart, I just had a rough day today.
Can you believe they are at each other again?
I can.
You're drunk!
What a surprise!
The kids drunk?
That's not it, never is!
Drunk again, darling.
Some of us may be losing our jobs.
You've been saying that for years!
I'm more worried about Megan.
What's wrong with Megan? She looks okay to me.
Everything looks okay after 10 beers.
Reverend Carson held her back after
prayers today.
That's 4 weeks running.
Boston?
Boston.
It's a weird role for Chevy Chase to be doing.
The situation is serious, Anne!
Real serious!
Alright, here we go.
Is that one of your photos?
I don't know.
Wait, me? Like actually me?
That could be you as a kid.
It kind of looked like me when I was little.
Yeah, it's the Clark family home.
Sorry, it's the Clark family home.
Hey.
Hang on, I'm...
That was me that just did that.
Okay, I'm this kid here.
That's the bandit snatched kid.
What's his name?
He's in Meet the Millers.
Ben Shapiro?
What? What are you fucking talking about?
Hey.
Everything Megan does is an accident.
What's up?
Shapiro. Why?
It wasn't just one person that wrote that.
Like a hundred of you did.
Hey, can you come let me in? I'm locked out of the house.
Oh, this is you.
I'm going to start climbing through the window
unless that door gets fixed.
Your character looks like they're wearing a wig.
How's things?
Let me guess.
He's been pumping iron again?
They've been at each of his throats since dad got home.
That's just me from 2006
but like with blonde hair.
You're really thinking about whatever you're about to say?
Daleks.
This is a valuable, rare, and sought after collection.
My amiibos.
I'll just take these to my room.
They're Pokemon cards, mom.
Didn't you say Clefairy is worth
$355,000 now?
What's crawled up his ass?
He's being a jerk.
He's being even more annoying than usual tonight.
Real jerk.
Funko Puffs.
Hey, Dennis.
Hey. Not now, sis. I'm busy.
Is that a doll of her?
That's weird.
Hey, quit acting crazy.
Is the ghost doing it?
Oh, this is the Resident Evil 7
please, Wolf.
Why is that scary?
He walked into the room that the mom was in.
Not now, Megan.
I'd like to have a bath in peace.
Holy shit, a child
that lives here.
Holy shit.
I love the idea that they've apparently lived with her
for years, but she's just really
scary tonight.
Are you going to lock everybody in?
Maybe you should talk to mom and dad.
It's not a great idea for me to get involved.
You know what I'm like? I just upset someone.
They sounded more serious than the usual
bullshit.
I'm talking about Megan.
She's done something bad.
I can't say I'm surprised. There's definitely something off with Megan.
I don't get why everyone keeps picking on her.
Okay, Mr. Shining Knight in armor.
Where's the little princess anyway?
Megan's gone upstairs.
Maybe you can go check on her if you don't have other plans.
I'll go find her.
Ooh, this is the first
split of the evening.
Second, actually.
You had to open the door for me, remember?
Oh, that's right.
What do we have here?
Who cares?
Wouldn't that explode your house?
That scares the shit out of me when people do that.
Is that the gas line underneath to blow up the fucking house?
I can't see what you can see.
Oh, we should move then.
We're in time with the heartbeat?
I'm sneaking by dad.
Don't wake daddy.
Fuck your brothers.
It was right click, right?
It was the easiest thing ever.
It was right click.
I'm not a moron. I'm not a fish.
I'm a person. I'm a human. I'm a human man.
Check on Tanya.
Press to move to a location.
Stop moving.
The screen is just to move in that direction.
It's like, wait, it's point and click?
Oh, okay, so should we do TV?
All right, we gotta go check on Tanya.
You know what would be really funny if he's just waiting for me up there
and I just get lost in the house
and his stream is fucked
because I cannot find a way up the stairs.
I don't think he realizes that that's possible
the entire time we play this.
Ooh, examine.
Crowd of innocence.
All right, pick it up.
A must read for anyone with an interest in the Salem Witch Trials of 1692.
This takes place during the Salem Witch Trials.
150, 200 years in the future.
Pretty cool.
Wait, what's this?
The New England Witch Trials.
What does that say?
The New England Witch Trials, right.
They just say the name of the book on the spine.
What rugs is he on?
I'm not on any of these rugs.
Today's not a CBD day.
Okay, I gotta go get Tanya.
Upstairs?
Imagine walking around your house like this,
like you have no idea where the fuck you're going.
I can't wait. Oh, we're locked in.
She locked the door.
She locked it. The little kid locked it.
I'm gonna go upstairs so, like, Italics' stream isn't ruined.
He's upstairs.
I don't know what that is.
Stairs?
This is just what your dog does
when you leave for the day.
And then eventually I'm gonna walk around in a circle
three or four times. Jesus Christ!
I'm gonna walk around in a circle
three times and lie down.
Open the door? Where's Tanya though?
I'm never gonna find him.
I'm sorry, Italics, I'm coming.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hey, Italics, did I hit the enrage timer?
Oh.
Too hot.
Too hot?
I thought that was her for a second.
Burning her head in the fire.
Uh, I am, I'm putting, I'm gonna
break every bone in my body to get this open.
I'm gonna full on jump through the glass
and shatter every bone in my body and like get all cuts all over me and shit.
This is quick.
Dad!
Good thing, hey, good thing I woke him up.
Dude.
Did we have prevented this?
Everyone's just dying.
We just accidentally
killed everybody.
What?
Why is everybody trapped
in the house?
It's so loud.
Come on, Dad, you can do it.
Oh, Jesus, this is bad.
Get her out of there.
Did she do that?
Why did she do this?
Why is she, like, do you bleed
when you breathe smoke?
I think so.
It like burns you up.
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Tanya, hold on. I gotta get Megan out.
You're gonna go save Megan?
Alright, now roll your outro credits for your stream.
What?
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
Oh, that's horrible.
Holy shit. Why did...
Oh!
What happened?
What did you do?
What did you do? What happened?
Uh, are you...
Did you take control of this character?
No, I'm sorry.
I don't know what I did.
Why are they all getting, like,
mortal combated?
No, I don't think so.
What the fuck did I do then?
What are you doing? Why would you do that?
Went down with the ship.
He sprints in as the buildings
collapse.
I think that was just the intro.
Yeah, that's scripted.
That's pretty nuts.
I gotta, like, alt-tab again, but I don't want to crash the game.
Did you see, by any chance,
what happened in the house?
Uh, besides the fire
starting, no. I mean, I saw, like, the guy
crawling and getting crushed by beams.
Okay, dude.
Literally, the
little girl
burnt to death like she was on fire.
Hang on, I can hear you on this MTV music video.
They literally burnt a kid
to death.
Like she was on fire. It was fucking
insane. Uh, well,
was it as insane as my character hanging themselves
with a scarf? I mean, it was...
The whole thing was just fucked up.
Oh, we're supposed to...
We're supposed to know... Hold on, we're gonna get DMCA
for this, aren't we? Oh, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You just said the key word for today.
I hope it
was worth it.
Alright, this is real. Somebody in my
feed actually got a
YouTube claim. From this?
From Bandai Namco for, like, a
cutscene. Oh, fuck.
What do we do? Do we turn it off? Music?
What if it's just... Nah, I'm gonna leave
it on. Ah, fuck it, who cares.
It's just a game
song. I think that they custom-made
it for the game. No, no, this is like Pearl Jam,
I think. Why is it running so shitty?
And what... Why is this hallway so
long? It's Pearl Jam.
By super massive games.
Listen, I just want you to know that
when both of our channels get deleted,
it was a pleasure that
we go down with what IGN
has called a 5 out of 10
experience. Is it?
It's a 5 out of 10
game? According to IGN,
yes. IGN giving a
game a 5 out of 10 means it's a 0.
I don't think I believe that so far.
I was... Hold on. I remember this guy.
Who's in the window.
Hello. Hi.
And welcome. I don't believe
that we've met before, have we?
No, Matt. Welcome to my repository.
I
am the curator.
The guardian of all these wonderful
stories. We have met, though. Yeah, we have.
And I have a very special tale
for you to tell. We were talking before the stream
started and we were like, yeah, it definitely doesn't remember
your save.
I didn't put that in.
Salem Witch Trials in his
encyclopedia of scary stories.
Disconcerting, no?
This guy looks like Bugleberry.
Is this like a stick bug joke?
This particular
story isn't fully fleshed
out. It's only part
written and the choices you make
will complete it.
Fire? No, there was nothing
you could have done about it. What's happened has happened.
Or has it?
Anyway, look to the future,
I say. Life's
but a walking shadow, eh?
You are about to enter
a confusing
perhaps disturbing
world. I like the idea that he's actually talking to a camera crew.
How disturbing might depend on what
you choose to believe and how
confusing on the path
you choose to take.
There are an infinite number
of directions in which one could
actually there's three in this game
that actually matter.
Left option, right option,
and say nothing. Right.
What?
Wait!
We get to change the fire?
He leans down and just screams into the book.
Do you think they made this intro because
they watched our man of Medan complain
about how long it took for anyone
to die?
They're like, oh yeah? What if I kill every
character in the first intro?
What now?
They just give us new characters.
Alright, I didn't sign up for poetry class. I want to fucking see
monsters and Satan and
stabbing.
Okay, but like, you did.
That's what we just did.
Okay, gee man.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm sorry, that's just like...
It's a photo.
No, but just the way he said that, he's like,
there are photos. Like this one of my kitty.
Here we go.
Cue the rock music and the car
driving really fast and the teenagers
just not listening to any fucking rules.
Never mind, it's a funeral.
The Bible's all wet.
Who are these people?
I mean, not to be like,
didn't everybody die?
The guy with the keychain thing
is Tanya's...
Well, am I allowed to tell you anything?
I don't know, do you have info that I'm supposed to know?
I don't know what I'm supposed to say or not say.
Oh, I think it's alright.
If we're sitting in the same spot, it's fine.
The one guy is Tanya's boyfriend.
Oh, okay.
She's dead though.
When we're not standing in the same spot,
that's when we...wait.
Wait, this person's alive.
Eighteen?
Dude's like thirty-six in real life.
Wait, but he's alive.
Where is he?
Taylor, twenty-two, college student, headstrong,
sensitive.
Did I get to create a new character now?
Gone. College professor, rational,
overbearing.
Oh, you are...
It's on the bus push.
Oh, right.
I forgot about that. I thought that was so long ago
and so random that it was like, what's the point of this?
These guys are all thirty-four pretending to be like
eighteen-year-old college kids.
Alright. I'm headstrong.
Angela, eighteen.
Mature student in college.
What?
I thought they were at the fire.
No, this is the bus crash.
That was just a dream.
This is gonna be a Freddy Krueger thing.
You can die in like a dream in like a nightmare and stuff.
Who do I control?
Angela, forty-eight. Mature student.
Abrasive, understanding.
But it did tell us who we are.
So you're Taylor, I'm Daniel.
Nobody's good.
I really hope that the old lady does that.
I'm gonna do everything possible to make sure that
that old lady stays alive.
No sign of him.
Weird. He isn't up here either.
Can you get back up to us?
Looks pretty steep.
I see a trail down here I could try.
I mean, that's not that steep.
Should take you to the road.
We can regroup there.
That's a plan. See you soon.
I wanna control...no, I wanna be the old lady.
I like old ladies.
Hey, Taylor.
Help me get Andrew up on his feet, will ya?
Wait, I don't remember anything.
That amnesia.
Where are they taking these kids on this field trip?
Why are there only four people?
I didn't fail the first QTE, we're good.
Why don't we just call somebody for help?
There's food in that bus.
There's a bathroom in that bus.
What about the guy that drove the bus?
Wait, did he drive the bus?
Oh no, the bus driver.
Okay.
Oh, fuck you, John.
Hey, look.
He's a professor of fucking artificial flavorings.
It was a really easy class to take.
Don't put that much judgment on him.
What is that?
Letterbox?
Yeah, I have a letterbox.
Are we not supposed to have letterboxes?
I kinda like it.
Wait, are we together?
Oh, okay.
Mute. There's nothing here.
Alright, leave. Run, run, run, run, run, run.
He's gonna get scooped up by an eagle or something, isn't he?
I know he is.
He's going way too fast in front of us.
Why are there MOBA controls?
Hold on.
Doesn't that fucking hurt after a while, by the way?
If you click that much.
People that play League and Dota.
All day.
I love her.
I love her already.
Oh, that was easy.
That's the real college kids.
Paying attention at how leverage works.
I'm just waiting for a car just to drive.
All of them.
This is the detour road.
Nobody goes this way.
That's why we crash and we're pissed.
I'm a psycho?
I'm playing a certain character here.
We're both playing certain characters.
Uh...
That's right.
Come on.
Ah, she's kind of a bitch.
I don't like her anymore.
No, I liked her!
Oh no, she's sad.
Oh no.
No, I like her again.
What was that?
What was that for?
Is nobody going to bring that up?
Why were you just violently coughing?
Not like, are you alright?
Why is your character like, the most manipulative?
Because that's how I'm playing it.
We were all in the fire.
I mean, we were all in the fire.
This is coughing, the...
Didn't Silent Hill do this like 15 years ago?
Fuck.
Write me out of the story, please.
It's not possible. Sprint.
Why does it go, what?
I am so confused, what is happening?
Why are they doing this?
And they can't...
Oh, so it's like Pac-Man.
My question, how long did these other three people stand
waiting for them to do this three different times?
Yeah, how far is it? Is it a mile?
Two miles? Five miles?
Who, alright.
Make your prediction right now.
Who's the first to die? Who do you think?
Just out of the people we've played as, or this whole group?
Just like this group here, who's the first to go?
Guy with glasses.
I would say the same thing. Professor's dead first.
Like I said, an eagle's gonna swoop him out of the fucking sky.
True.
Throwing that one out right at the beginning.
How can we hear them twice?
Did you hear an echo too? Yeah.
They're all turning into demons.
I'm defusing the scenario.
The real nightmare is 50 miles an hour on a two-lane road.
What, we're on drugs?
They should just hold hands,
and have one person keep walking while they keep holding their hand
and see if their arm rips off.
What?
Like make a chain,
and shimmy to the left,
until the person all the way to the left disappears
or gets their arm ripped off.
Okay, god, let's take that thing instead of ripping their arm off.
Start breaking off like tree branches.
And use those as like links.
Just build a shelter and live here.
Eat the fucking rabbits.
Oh, he zoomed in on that.
We were just in a car crash.
Dude, you have a scratch on your face.
What the fuck happened?
We were just in a fucking car crash, stupid.
What are you talking about?
All right, stick close to the others.
Follow John, they're already going.
All right, go, go, go.
Okay, RB pauses for some unknown reason.
Here we go again.
Uh-oh.
Listen, I'm not the developer that made RB
on a controller pause the whole game
and then crash the game.
It's not my fault that you get soft-locked
after a single pause in the game.
Okay, there's no menu on my screen.
So is this,
I don't know.
So now you're locked out.
What about now?
There's no menu, it's just a screenshot.
All right, let's go back to the main menu.
Let's do it again. We got to continue.
We got to start right here.
I need to figure out any other buttons
that just pause the game for some reason.
So I don't push them.
Surge, tune, waiting room.
All right, that actually kicked me out
back to the main menu without having to restart the game.
Why does RB pause the game?
That's odd. This is your out.
Take it. No.
We've only just started.
We're in like chapter one
after the prologue.
I invite you. Are you good?
It's doing like a 10 second long animation
but yes.
Are they supposed to be here?
I feel like they just
got ported in here for no reason.
I don't think these models are supposed to be here.
If I had a 10, I wouldn't say that yet.
I wouldn't say that yet.
Hey look.
I think it's just telling us we have to choose
a play style.
Can we skip this?
No.
All right.
Someone else needs to do a better job.
He's been standing still
for half an hour.
The only thing they've tried so far
is walk down the road three times.
Yeah.
That's horrible.
When did we establish
the fog?
I think they just guessed.
Yeah.
We played Man of Medan.
The fog is just like a barrel
leaking somewhere.
If they do a Man of Medan
again where it's like this is a gas
in the air and it's making us just like crazy
then I'm not fine.
You know what I mean?
This is the town that produces the gas.
Spoilers for Man of Medan.
Yeah but this is Man of Medan 2.
Smog of Medan.
All right. It's Alex. Is this game
Man of Medan 2 in your brain?
This is not Little Hope. This is Man of Medan 2.
This is not the Dark Pictures anthology.
Cat. Cat. Cat.
I hope there's some Monty Python level shit
where the cat just like jumps up and bites
one of our necks.
Dude's cat.
That's the story teller.
Why are you doing this like Chad
side to sidewalk?
I'm just going man.
I didn't see it.
Who am I now?
I'm Taylor.
Are you old lady?
I wish that was me.
Why aren't we going with those guys?
Angela knows there's something between us.
Why aren't we going with them?
It's a horror game. You have to split up.
I'm talking to you right now?
This is a big deal for me anyhow.
No.
Why can you hear this?
You're like six feet away.
Did you blab to her about us?
Of course not. Didn't say a word.
You absolutely sure you didn't blab about us?
You don't believe me?
I believe she's smart enough to
I went down. I got down on
Daniel.
Daniel down arrow.
I just wanted to be sure.
I don't know what I did wrong.
You better.
I'm not sure.
I'll let Chad take it from here.
Concussion can scramble your memory.
Everyone is Ben Shapiro.
That's wicked funny.
Even me. Me too.
We standing here all night or we going inside?
All of us here are Ben.
Oh.
Ew. Stop.
You brought it up. I didn't bring it up.
I'm reacting. I'm going to react Andy to what you're doing.
This is the most business
this bar has gotten.
Yeah. This guy. I'm surprised he doesn't jump up
and start wiping the counter and being like what can I get you?
Holy shit. Five people.
Ding ding ding ding.
Hi there. How you doing?
Hey. Your bus crashed too.
But we're looking for our bus driver.
What? Have you seen him? What is?
Look at the fog outside.
It's pretty weird.
Yeah. It sure is a thick one tonight.
So thick it's stopping us from leaving.
Dick.
This is the character that knows the
mysticism behind the town.
No.
This is the character that got stuck here before you did.
Oh shit. God damn it. You're right.
How about a game?
Seriously? You want to throw darts?
Don't be like that. Ten bucks.
Says you can't hit the bullseye.
Sounds like fighting talk to me.
I'm playing darts.
Let's do it.
How do you play darts?
Go for single twenty.
What was that supposed to be?
Single twenty.
Beginner's luck. Try for double seven.
Double seven.
I don't know what that means. Right here?
At least my eyesight seems okay.
Great shooting.
Go for the bullseye with your last dart.
I just turn and I throw the dart right into his eye.
Okay.
You got the walk to back up the talk.
Stop pretending.
Stuck here with these guys?
Because of that fog?
How do you feel about all this shit?
We're in deep shit here and those guys are no help.
Don't beat around the bush.
Say what you're really thinking.
You doing okay?
Am I trying to like save us from the fog
while you're playing darts?
Probably. I'm just having a good time over here.
Wait. This is an important decision.
Just because he's our professor doesn't mean
John can act like he's in charge.
Are you talking about me in front of me?
I'm right.
You can hear this?
They need to figure out how to speak with
volume control.
Are you talking shit?
I'm going to show you how to bullseye
three in a row.
You're going to hit the fucking wall.
You're going to be that guy that's at the party
that throws two into the guy's fucking wall.
The drywall. And it's like fuck.
How much is the drywall, man? I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it, dude. Don't worry about it.
Just give it to somebody else.
I'm literally playing now.
Oh, you are playing.
I took the controller out of your hand.
I made you go look around.
Can I just stand there?
Okay.
My game just got stuck.
This place is a bust. There's nothing for us here.
For once, I agree.
The sooner we're gone from this dreadful place,
the better.
I hit a bullseye, too.
Just saying.
I hit three bullseyes in a row.
You actually don't go for the middle, though.
Yes, you do. Every time.
When you throw the second one, it splits the first one in half.
And the third one splits the second one in half.
Talk to this guy.
What?
No, he didn't.
I want to talk to this person.
We all drink too much from time to time.
Now what?
Can't a guy get some peace around here?
Is the phone working?
The phone sure seems like it's broken.
I already told you it was dead.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Nothing's okay.
I can't escape.
Escape what?
Fog?
The D-socks?
No, that's not a Red Sox hat.
That's not a Boston Red Sox hat.
Dead Sox.
Yeah, that's not a V.
I mean, I know where they're going.
I mean, it's probably trademark laws where you can't be like
the Boston Red Sox, maybe.
Deadsec.
Why is everyone just eerily sitting around?
The Zosten Zed Sox.
Alright, that's enough.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
Alright, what do I do? Who do I talk to?
Can I talk to him?
I'm just being an NPC in every video game.
I'm just waiting for someone to come over
and hit me with a fucking chair for fun.
What's this?
It's a secret. Turn it upside down.
This is riveting gameplay, Jerma.
It's a story game.
What do you want me to go drive a car and run over
a hundred people out there?
This is a story game.
Oh, I may have yoinked everybody.
I was just walking around like an NPC anyways.
Why are we assuming that that guy cannot hear that?
Yeah, and...
Don't, the Zosten Zed Sox!
Docs, I said wrong.
That's a lot of minus two's.
Fuck.
The...
It's like 11 PM.
It's closing time.
Yeah.
Cool. I am Andrew.
Let's go.
Continue toward the town.
Keep up with John and the others.
Yeah, sorry, we're controlled by players.
You just go squat over there and piss behind a bush.
That'd be funny.
Dude!
Go on, hit start.
Hang on, let me ready first.
You unready, because I still have a menu here.
Who's supposed to ready first?
You.
Like, what have we done last time?
Do you ready first last time and that's what freezes us?
I don't know.
They made too many buttons on the controller pause the game for no reason.
Listen, in my defense,
everyone knows when you're playing a new game
and you got a controller, you push every button on the controller
to see what it does.
Right?
You just do.
I do press like every button on my keyboard.
I just mash my face into it.
Thank you, we're good.
People telling you to stop using a controller.
Okay, that's chat saying that.
Do anybody even listen to what they say?
Ever?
I do.
I think I'm losing you, by the way.
Was that you?
That's because the sprint button is LB
and the pause button is RB.
You just sprinted by.
Wait, did you just sprint by?
No.
You're so far behind.
Listen, hang on, slow down, I'm behind you.
Hey, can you come over here?
Come over here.
You're not the old lady.
Oh, you are.
Will you quit screwing around?
I definitely saw someone.
I saw somebody, man.
What did you see?
Remember when those two AIs talked to each other
on Twitch that time?
This is what this is.
And Google Assistant.
Just wait like five seconds before answering.
A child.
Now you're really screwing with me.
I know what I saw.
Let's just catch up with the others, okay?
Dude, it's right there.
What the fuck is that?
That was pretty gravy looking, I'm not gonna lie.
Did you hear that?
Okay, very good.
We're freaked.
That's an elaborate, we're freaked out.
Who's doing the joke? It's like I'm rustling bushes
shining lights, not like in $5,000 of makeup.
I got an idea.
You look one way, I'll look the other way.
Then nothing can sneak up on us.
Sounds good. Alright, I'll take the right side.
Alright, we have to stay close to each other.
Hey, wait for us.
That was a nice elaborate dance.
Alright, definitely start walking the other direction
instead and just go that way.
See how far we can go.
It sounds like a Mario Kart wrong way thing
starts blinking up there.
It's probably just a deer, this is deer crossing.
We can actually go pretty far.
It's probably
gonna loop us around.
It might.
Perfect.
Oh no!
Hang on, stay close, where are you?
Stay close, where'd you go?
Oh god, I already lost you.
I stood still, you walked forward
then backward.
No, I'm coming back the other way.
It's game over.
Do not go into that real thick stuff.
Wait, could you see me the whole time?
No, I just walked by you.
Hey, don't, stay together.
Is this just like a horror version of PUBG?
Is that the veil
chasing us into the zone?
I don't think we're physically allowed to go any further.
I think that actually might be what's happening.
What is that?
Something on the ground. Alright, you wanna pick it up?
You want me to pick it up, you pick it up.
You probably haven't even looked at one piece of lore the entire game.
You're right, I haven't looked at one single item
pretty much the whole game, you're right.
I picked up a newspaper and it was upside down
and then we got pulled out of here.
A clue.
They were trying to make a campfire and then went into the woods
to get some sticks.
Alright, take the pin out and stab it right in the brain
as hard as you can.
Just immediately, oh, it's a voodoo doll.
Let's try it.
Oh, whoa.
What is your name, sir?
Andrew.
Andrew?
My real name's Andrew but my friends call me Jerma.
What's your name?
Oh, it's Mary.
What are we playing?
Oh, wait, wasn't dancing considered
witchcraft back in the fucking 1400s?
I don't. I do.
I mean, I have like three or four theories.
How can you not have seen that?
I couldn't see anything through this
impossible, impenetrable fog.
Well, go ahead. Tell them what we saw.
A little girl
appeared out of the fog and then just like
that, she was gone again.
What is going on?
Maybe the fog has got you confused.
We're all stressed out.
We all agree
that the road is an infinite loop.
Anything is possible.
Looked exactly like the girl in my dream.
Something's.
Yes, it was, right?
Maybe.
Did she stab me?
She stabbed me. She stabbed me with a knife in the arm
and a little doll arm.
Yeah, that's what happened.
Get that doll away from her and throw it in the fucking fire.
But wait until it's on a different person
than me.
Is there a doll for everybody?
I'm just going to take that doll and I'm going to
go rent out a warehouse and I'm going to get a little box
in that warehouse and I'm going to have inside
the box is going to be perfect.
75 degrees, zero humidity.
Leave it in there.
Buy the doll a mansion
in like a little RC car, like a really
cute one. Do you get all that shit in real life?
Oh wait, wait, wait, update.
Everything that one does
or doesn't do in one's life
will catch up with one
adventure. Don't you think?
Don't look at me. I
can't help you. Remember?
We sometimes congratulate
ourselves on waking from
a troubled dream.
Maybe so the moment
after death.
My travels over many years.
I've witnessed many things.
Seen and heard many beliefs.
And there's usually some
element of truth
in each of them.
He's to get rid of walls. His roommate's fucking
annoying. These unfortunate folks seem to be dealing with forces
as yet unexplained.
I mean sinister
movements in the forest. Spirits
from the past. A little girl
who may be in trouble
or maybe she simply
is trouble. See, I said
that she was malicious. That was right. Anyway, where are
we? Angela isn't getting
much tittle tattle
out of Taylor. Tittle
tattle. No kiss
and tell. What about
John, the figure of
authority perhaps? No, he's a chump.
Or perhaps he represents
something else. He's a badass darts player though from what I could
see. And then there's Andrew.
Somewhat confused I think.
A bump to the head can do
that. Andrew is, you know. Let me reassure
you. Andrew's alright.
Who's Andrew?
Bandit snatch guy.
Oh, yeah. The main guy.
Yup.
Ooh, Omega Lowell.
Okay, that's pretty good.
Somebody in chat said, this is just
an annoying DM trying to hype
up his players before they get back
in the game. That's
fucking upvote
that guy with all your points.
Super into it DM
hyping his players up.
Whoever that guy was, I want that guy
VIP'd for five minutes.
You're John now.
Yeah, we keep switching.
Wait, wait, wait.
Am I supposed to stay close to you or find help in town?
Are we splitting up or are we staying together?
I don't know. Maybe, should we tell?
Are you following me? I'm the
old lady again. Yeah, it just says
keep up with the others. I'm
the professor. Are we gonna go knock
on this random house? I'm just trying to keep everybody
in my field of view in case they disappear.
Or, you know, the game could just rip me on the other side.
I'm using my phone
as a flashlight, but I have not
attempted to call anybody in the game
yet. That shit drains your battery. There's something over
here. Why don't you pick it up?
Yeah, I'll pick it up. I
accidentally put it back down without
looking at it. I was trying to take it out
of your hand. Okay, so that's just
nothing. Why are we all over here? It's a picture
of a skull.
Ooh, a picture of a skull.
I'm getting a premonition.
I think we lost. No, they're just
standing here. It's just a very morbid
postcard.
I heard something, I heard something.
Okay, that's an alligator.
Oh, alligator POV, alligator POV.
Look. Alright, come over here. This is definitely alligator POV.
He's watching us or something.
Aww. He's standing up on
two legs. POV,
you are the alligator.
Are we all together, right? We're good?
Yeah, we're all here.
Oh, it was just an animal.
I told you it was a deer crossing.
It's just a deer.
Might get a better view from up there.
Don't go alone.
Trinkets. What's this trinket?
Ghost towns of the northeast.
I'm not reading this.
This is fucking too long. I don't care.
Is that you or your character that said who writes
this trash? I think we both just said it at the same time.
Okay,
for all future game developers, let me just
tell you, if it's longer than a paragraph,
I'm not reading it.
Go right in the middle
of both of them. Like, as
close to the middle as you can. Wait, what?
I'm just sitting here, like, mouth breathing on you guys
having a conversation.
Yeah, but like, try and position yourself
right between them. Or directly
behind me. I can't even move.
What's up?
You two okay? After what we went through
back there, we're both a considerable
distance from okay.
Sorry I lost touch with you in the fog.
It shows we need to stick close to
each other.
Let's not turn this into an argument.
Why do you sound like you're in on it?
This game is ridiculous.
It just sounds like we need
to stick close to each other.
Oh,
swamp monster.
Wait,
did we see that?
No, we're the only ones who can see
anything, apparently.
The only thing that they've seen
so far is the fire
and the little girl with the dolls.
We've seen all the monsters.
Trixie hoppetses.
Yes, yes, yes.
We want it.
Oh, precious.
This is four golems.
Yeah, you just got a double impression.
That was a two for one.
Are we going the wrong way?
Every way is the wrong way in this game.
Why are you not last hitting?
Because fuck last hitting. It's a stupid mechanic.
It turns me off of every one of those games.
Smite's the only one that didn't have it.
It's the only one that was any fun.
True. Alligator.
No, no, no, look, look, look. Do you see?
I see it, yeah. It's someone's ear.
Heroes of the Storm. Heroes of the Storm was alright.
It was too, Heroes of the Storm
was too easy for me, though.
And no, not like, oh, too easy, but like
I like having at least some
individuality in those games.
I have you to share everything in Heroes of the Storm.
I don't want to share everything. I want it from me.
I want to get like the boots of fucking justice and shit on my own.
Is this the newest Strand
type video game? Are we like delivering
a package or what? Walking?
I don't know. You're the one that played that game.
Hey, something up ahead.
Little Hope Middle School.
Uh oh. I don't like last hitting.
I don't know.
Guess we've been demoted from college, guys.
Amen to that.
He's going to go teach the middle schoolers.
Look at that.
Hey, wait.
Stop. It worked.
Did you listen? Yeah.
This is exactly what goes down in horror movies.
Self-referential.
I'll give it to you. What the hell do we do now?
It's just a little girl. What?
What the hell do we do?
She's two feet tall and has no
muscle structure. We can kill her.
What are you talking about? So bad they finally made
fear for. Uh.
Uh.
I'll deal with this. What?
Stay right here. Really?
Time to mute and I'll see you
for the next chapter.
Handle this.
Hey, remember when we took bets on who would die
first? I think you're just trying to confirm
that you were right.
I'm just stacking the deck. You're throwing for that guy.
Stacking the deck. What are you doing?
Hold up. I'll come with you.
No, don't kill her. I like her.
We're killing this guy. Listen, you've got to live with your
consequences. I'm not going to be left behind
as a secondary character back here while you go do all the heroic stuff.
No, no, great.
Hey, you two.
We just bachelorette picked
these two people to die.
This is not good.
Confront the girl. Great. Alright, you go
first. No, I go first. I want the old lady to live.
You're the one
that decided to go follow them.
I'm not going to let you pass me. This is NASCAR level
shit here. I'm just going to, you're not going to get.
Okay, I get the drift.
Nightcrawler?
What is it you want from me?
Are you? What are you doing here?
These are most troubling times.
Wait, don't go.
Stay away.
What? You're the one that
grabbed us first?
It's impossible. It's her.
A black tongue full of riddles. I will not
succumb to a witch's spell.
It's her. It's you.
Please Lord, I beg you. Rid me of these
apparitions. Oh, we're like in
each other's worlds. We're like the ghosts
in their world and they're the ghosts in our world.
Fuck.
That's what I was going to say when you said don't say your theories out loud.
Where the hell are we?
You just took credit. What have you done?
I have had my fill of you.
You just wanted to get in first.
Yeah, you didn't say that. You couldn't jump in and
said that.
Stolen.
Let's get into town. It's not so far now.
And it's our best shot at getting help.
That's a great theory.
Thanks, man.
I am very far from okay.
I'm tired and confused. I just saw my own
double in the fog.
What happened in there?
The woman came out of nowhere in the fog, dressed like an extra
from Salem. She was garbling something
in an accent I didn't recognize. And most disturbing
of all, she was the spitting
image of me.
How is that even possible? You're blowing this
out of proportion, Angela.
I am all done. Alright, I'm ready to kill that guy.
Kill this guy. Kill this guy. Can we just all agree?
Except into the center of town.
The fog decides where we can and can't go?
Fuck that.
He was in the dream and he still thinks I'm
overreacting.
Oh, no. Here comes the quintessential
decision. Okay.
Well. Don't you kids watch horror movies?
You never, ever split up.
Those movies are dumb.
Wait, didn't she just say this is the shit that happens
in horror movies? Those are dumb.
Don't believe them. I'm with John.
Um. Isn't there another person
that we're missing here? I'm not going with Taylor.
The town isn't so far.
We all go in together.
Okay, time out.
Can we all just take a breath?
Think about what our next move is?
We can check out more options if we split up.
I'll go with Taylor. It's not safe for you to be hanging
around here on your own. Oh, where's the third player?
Two teams are more likely to find a way out.
Which is what we all want, right?
Didn't we just agree not to split up?
We did.
Send them into town
to find us.
It's just like horror movies. Horror movies are dumb.
Alright, see you in an hour, it's Alex.
Do you like ghost
stories, Ms. Turner?
See you in an hour. You're in one.
And his face turns into a fucking ghost.
Alright, hey, see you in an hour
when, um, like two of your
characters are dead and all of mine are.
Hey, who are you? I don't intend on
splitting up. I think we split up. I'm, um,
I'm the, I don't want to say it, but
I'm the guy with the other
I'm the guy that like, we don't
Yeah, the guy that like, who cares, right? Like
I'm not connected with Daniel at all.
I don't know about you, but I have it at all.
I was Daniel first.
So you're doing something else.
But he has no personality as of yet.
Alright, so I'll see you in a little bit.
Alright, we're split up.
I wonder what closed the school down.
I thought it was just us two.
Even if you make it over, there's no way I'm
following. I never did like school.
Let's get out of here. Looks like there's no way
through. I might have made a bad call here.
Your guy's personality that you gave
this guy is
This is not even Daniel to me.
Don't stress it. No one made us come this way.
We'll find another way.
Okay, reassuring. Let's go.
Damn, Daniel.
Find another route out of
little hope. Stick together,
follow the little girl.
Okay, we have to follow the little girl.
I just read that in chat.
I forgot that that was even a thing.
Somebody said it and I read it.
Remember, I'm the streamer that reads
his chat out loud. It doesn't matter
what it is. Find another route.
Search for the little girl.
Don't read this.
I talked about shoving smarties
somewhere recently.
I wouldn't say that in a normal circumstance.
Alright, follow the little girl.
There she is.
You into the tube.
Concerned?
Something is real off about this whole thing.
This
This little girl is the key
to all of this. I have no clue.
Wow, you can't be doing that.
Did I reach?
I guess I'm gay.
What the hell is going on?
That didn't just happen. Quiet now.
What are you talking about? Get where
or he will find me.
Who the fuck is this?
Come on out, Mary. I know very
well you're in there. That's not
me.
What the fuck
it kind of is.
Let go.
I broke the time.
I broke time?
What?
I saw her in the forest
together with her familiars.
I am innocent. He can't see me.
I will have the truth one way or another.
You come with
me, girl. Thank you kindly.
Be silent, child.
Don't say that. That means I have to do everything you say.
Can someone tell me what just happened?
Those two kids have to be linked
somehow. No way that's a
coincidence. I don't get it.
Let's not hang around here. It's time
to go. Alright, yeah, so we're
only little girl can see us.
Only the other devil worshippers
can see us. I got that wrong probably, but whatever.
Let's go.
I'm glad you're here. Both of us are getting out of here.
I see it in the distance.
This is literally just
the crucible. Could mean someone's around.
Maybe they can help.
Let's head over. Blowing
past the lore. I'm sorry.
I don't read lore.
Okay, I got it. I wasn't looking. I got it.
No, I read lore
if it's a paragraph and put on the screen
in front of me. I don't pick up newspapers
and read it. Don't worry, italics reads
all that shit. He'll tell us.
I don't think this takes us out of this shitty town.
There's no road.
Must lead somewhere though.
I'm not so sure. There's barely even a path.
Just blowing by every item.
But I'm not though.
If it's shiny, I click it. See?
This must have been a grocery store or something.
Here. This is less than a paragraph.
Over here. Look at this.
The hope for
little hope. The carvers want to close
the factory
and sell the land of development.
That would result in the
devastation of the community.
The union has proposed an offer to save the factory
in our town. Please sign our petition to persuade
the carver. This is how I read lore anyways.
This is how I do it anyways.
Leave me alone.
How about we try the door?
Talek's already figured out how to upgrade his town hall
in the game.
Yeah, but what he doesn't know is I'm sending 200
peasants through the back door
to start attacking his town hall.
And it's a stupid shitty thing to do, but that's what
I'm doing. What am I doing?
This is the slowest selfie I've ever taken.
Oh, what? I just got 20 community subs.
Unionize your workplace thanks for the 20
subs. That's a lot of money.
Thanks? Really? 20
subs.
You don't have any food in here.
I'm surprised at what people throw away these days.
Seriously? There's no other way.
I've got no choice.
Isn't this on wheels? Why would it be this heavy?
Let me see if I can get this open.
Okay, I saw everybody say, dude, things can be
heavy. What's up with that?
Why is that that heavy? Seriously?
You're going in there? If I go in first
I don't want to be the character that dies first.
Alright, you have any better ideas?
Do you have a better suggestion? Sure.
Don't go into an old, dark, creepy ass
building after the night we've had.
Alright, I'll be right back.
And then I never show up again.
He's talking to us.
This is some Dora the Explorer shit.
And remember, chat, if you see
anything weird, make sure you point it out for me
before I get scared.
Do you see anything scary in here?
There's like a fucking ghoul behind him
with like a pitchfork.
It's right there! It's right there!
You see something? What do you see?
It's a ghoul! It's a ghoul!
And the fucking pitchfork goes through his chest.
Oh, this is great.
Go in.
Go in, dude.
Oh, here we go. Brownbeef249.
Pretty cool. Alright, so I have to let her in a different way.
What? Just happened?
I have no idea what just happened.
I like stepped on a nail.
Oh, don't worry. It's just us.
Scared me.
Why would that bring
the relationship down?
Oh, rats!
Kill her. Kill her first.
I changed my mind.
This is super creepy.
That's not her this time.
That's somebody else.
It's not going to be her.
It's going to be a scary ghoul.
Okay.
Okay. Get off me.
Get off me.
Wait, that's Angela?
Dude, this is such a mindfuck.
Leave or confront?
Um...
Talos found a secret. I gotta one up him.
Confront.
I gotta hide a secret.
Oh, shit.
What rumors? I don't know anything. What are you talking about? What's a witch?
Uh...
Okay, I saw a girl.
She was with this priest.
He's the devil.
He's got another secret.
I gotta start strangling somebody.
Finding all these secrets.
Alright, I'll kick his ass.
They didn't have guns back in the day here.
Just pick up a bottle and hit him in the head.
They did?
Yeah, but you could only shoot once in like an hour.
He'll miss. Stodge it.
And hit him in the head with a fucking wrench.
The child condemns my wife.
You will deliver yourself into the
marshal's hands for your own good.
Then I must accompany her.
She will not leave my sight.
Such action will not aid
your wife's cause.
Trust injustice.
Do not fear. I will find
a way to resolve this.
Am I still here? Oh.
How come they didn't ask me anything about like
my clothes and stuff?
Wouldn't they be freaked out by my clothes?
Where the hell have you been?
It's been weeks.
You look freaked. What's up?
You saw something else, right?
Uh, hmm.
Alright, they could, let's tell the truth.
This was different. I think they could see and hear me.
It was hard to tell exactly.
They seemed really spooked.
You see anything else?
Uh, okay.
Talk about the woman getting arrested, that's important.
Everyone needs to know that detail.
I saw this woman being taken away. Arrested.
She was being accused of witchcraft.
The spooky little girl,
she gave the name Amy to the priest.
That's what got the woman arrested.
The woman, Amy.
I guess she's in deep shit then.
Yes.
We've really screwed up here. Instead of getting out of this awful
place, we're right back in the middle of town.
Alright, catch up with the other group.
Can we just tell Italics that I killed like
eight people? Let's tell Italics
that my gameplay was fucking crazy.
Let's make him jealous
that he didn't get to play this part of the game.
Dude, I was in a fight.
There was two demons that had wings.
I was inside of this cabin that was on fire. I hit a guy in the head with a board.
I did a backflip.
The character just did a fucking backflip for no reason.
It was cool. Wait, did I?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, where is she?
That face.
Okay, we're good.
We're fine. We're fine. What are you doing?
I just realized this is literally the movie
Hocus Pocus, isn't it?
You know, I don't, is it?
No, isn't Hocus Pocus, don't they like
hypnotize the town or something?
Like the candy or something?
What the fuck? Okay.
I just scared the shit out of me. I wasn't even looking.
It was like such an overreaction too. Sorry.
I like fucking YouTuber Andy that...
This is a gas station. Should we go to the gas station?
Stop saying Andy. I can't...
You guys have burned it into my brain.
Wait, we were already here. I have to catch up with the others.
How do I catch up with the others
if I don't know where the others are?
Italics got akimbo pistols, omega low.
Oh, hey, Italics is on knife, dude.
You're still on the third pistol.
Yeah, whatever. I don't fucking care.
Alright, I'm just gonna keep walking through the mist?
Wait, what's that? A button.
Press that button. Press the button.
Press it. I can't press this button?
Why not? No, go with the...
Damn it. I think I found it.
Hey, what was that? What was that?
I just walked by me. I...
This stupid smog shit. I'm trying to go to that house.
Where's that house?
Okay, I'm gonna go to that... I think that's where he is.
I think he's in the house. It's teleporting me around.
Alright, hold on. This is...
What am I doing?
What the fuck is going on? Am I in limbo?
Oh, alright.
We walk around. There's a house though.
Do I go back in the gas station?
No, I was already... No, this is not even...
Get the fuck out of here, man. Go catch up with the others.
I gotta go in this house.
Walk the other way, dickhead.
Is that... What's going on? Am I just
in the lobby, waiting for
Italics to do a cutscene?
Wrong way. There is no wrong way.
We keep porting. Alright, I'm walking straight.
I'm gonna go in that house.
Oh, in the gas station. You went every direction
except the right one. I tried to go to the house,
but the game teleported me. Remember, it's faking
tasks. He's sus. I'm not gonna
ban that person, but just pretend I did.
Alright, here we go. There's a house over here.
Just stay on the road. Where's that house?
Right here. This is what I... Okay.
Do you understand what... Do you see what just happened?
Do you see what just happened?
I just tried to go to the house
and it turned into the general store.
There is no house. There is? What?
That's where I wanted to go!
That's where I wanted to go! I was trying
to go here until you saw that.
German, don't be so mad. My mom is watching.
She's getting scared.
Hey.
Nice jump cut.
No, but you know how we say here.
Broccoli is delicious. You should eat it every meal.
Spinach. Get good grades
in school. And go to bed
before 9pm.
That's what we do here
on German 985.
Kid friendly. Is he not entering the door?
Or what?
Really?
Come on.
We can't open it. You can't open it.
Letting you in.
I was walking around in a circle for like 15 minutes.
Let's try again.
Put everything you've got into it.
No.
Keep them out. They're gonna result
untimely to mine.
Let me in.
That's worse than doing nothing. Get out of my way.
I'll show you.
Are you guys pushing? You guys have to pull
and we have to push. We both push.
Yeah, but I wasn't doing the QTE
so I just wanted to keep you out.
Fucking hell.
Thank god she's still alive.
Thank god you did. So did I.
Daniel looks dead.
I got info. You might have info.
What's gonna happen to her next?
I like the idea. But how would we even
begin to find that out?
We've already been down those paths.
Maybe the answer lies
down the one path we haven't taken yet.
Any direction we go, the lore ghosts will find us.
What the hell?
They just reach out and grab you when it's time for the lore.
By the way, this is one of those dumb horror movies that
Honey, it's 7pm. It's time for your
lore.
Is that a
This is gonna be
one of those horror movies where everybody dies
in the last ten minutes. And the whole entire movie
is a boring shitty movie.
This game's been crashing over and over
for some people. Well thankfully
that's not happening to us besides the pause
we asked for.
No, it's not. It's been two hours. That's enough.
Dude, Watch Dogs Legion crashed
like eight times in an hour and ten minutes
yesterday.
No, no, we had a pause problem.
We didn't have a crash, we had a pause problem.
I had to restart the game.
I'm not even sure anybody can even die by this point
anyways.
I am John.
Back on the old road.
Lead your students towards the stick together.
Go to the stick together.
I guess that's what we're doing.
So we're going backwards
from that to back
across the bridge.
I had to fight like
I had to fight like three demons. It was fucking awesome.
The only cool part of the game
so far was like hitting the demon in the head
with the 2x4.
I actually found a computer and
it did the Until Dawn PC port.
So I was just kind of playing that while I was waiting for you.
The game was good.
It was not. Yeah, it was. It was alright.
It was pretty good.
Push.
Did you get any cool action sequences? I had a couple
that were pretty crazy.
I hit the demon in the head with the 2x4.
I found the phone.
One of the characters tried to fly
off the roof
and landed like right on the neck. It was fucking brutal.
Did you see anything like that?
I went bowling.
Maybe we need to check all our other options first.
Turns out John is not
only a god of darts but also just like
other kind of fringe
options. What was that little smile?
That was weird. Why do you have a Harry
Potter scar?
I could have made Angela go first.
I'll just have you know.
So if I die here,
it was for a good cause. Somebody's going to fall in.
Who is it going to be? I don't know.
Are you John? Yeah.
I'm Andrew.
Well, that means that
Karen's dead. Why would we all
go at the same time?
No, they're fading away.
My god. What do we do?
We can't stay here. The fog reminds
me of Minecraft draw distance
in 2014.
Oh look at a crow.
That be the crow? I love crows.
Honey, it's time for your war!
I thought that was the crow.
In this year of our lord
1692.
It's the same trick every time. Yeah.
No! It's the fucking
Oh! My arm! You
grabbed my wrist and pulled me into another dimension!
I may be drowned as a witch and sorceress.
Let's just pray and silence
next time.
What'd you say? What'd you say?
What'd you do? I didn't say anything. What?
What do you mean you didn't say anything? Why not?
Because I got information that you don't.
What the fuck? The devil is in the wind
seeking to help his own.
He would release her from the chains.
Isaac, let us conclude our business here
swiftly. The will of the court
must be imposed before it's too late.
The devil fortifies her.
You must bind her tightly.
They're gonna throw her into the ocean.
Isaac, fill the will of the court.
Send this witch back into the lap
of her master lest he come for us all.
Little Hope is already lost
shrouded in evil. But not as you
claim from witchcraft or outside demons
we are poisoned from within.
You will not save yourself
with riddles. There is no riddles.
The devil takes many forms.
You know that better than any.
In little Hope he has hid himself
under a shroud of innocence.
Little girl.
I could get out of that.
I could get out of that I think.
Why did she drown instantly?
Did it happen?
Where were you?
I was watching the person die.
What person die?
Her? You mean this lady?
What did you see? Tell me.
What did you see?
I'm not exactly sure.
Another vision I guess?
An illusion like before?
She was tied up in a bunch of chains they threw in the ocean.
Yeah, that's what I said.
I watched the person die.
I watched her die and you said who?
And then I was like wait, what do you mean?
You asked me who?
Yeah, and then you didn't say.
Yeah, because you were like I don't think I should tell you.
Well, because it sounded like you had seen a different cutscene
because you didn't know that someone just died.
So she was killed.
She's dead.
What does that mean for me?
Wait, that's her.
I'm accidentally gaslighting
because the last game had us confused.
Sorry, I'm accidentally gaslighting.
Okay, so
the reason I didn't say anything
is because
when I was separated from you
talking to them was bad.
Oh, okay.
Alright, I'll go first.
But it may not be, apparently.
Because she died anyway.
I gaslit myself.
Oh, whoops.
Alright, does it
count as a character death if the
character from like 300 years ago
died? It's like wouldn't they be dead anyways
because it's been 300 years. I don't think
that counts. Well, but I think they come and
claim the life of the other, of their
other half. Like right now.
That's what's going to happen.
She's going to pop out of the water.
It's you.
We're going to go.
Save her.
Hey, give me a hand here.
Hold on, hold on.
For you, John.
John?
You made the right choice.
I made the right choice.
What are you doing?
Never mind, I'll get myself
Are you serious right now? Okay.
Let me help John, I'll be right back.
Why would you do that?
Abatage!
Don't worry, I'm going to be fine.
What?
What button am I pressing? What's the wrong button?
I'm clicking, I'm clicking, I'm clicking.
Don't click.
What button am I supposed to press?
Take my hand.
I have another chance to escape.
Put your hand out and help me.
I'm just watching.
Bracive, dismissive, derisive.
Did I do that?
I may have made those things.
Oh, you did those things.
Well, you did them too.
Okay, so when it was telling me to jump
What button was I supposed to press?
I was left clicking when the timer was going down.
I had to click in the...
You have to click on the button.
So remember how you said you made the right choice
when I chose to save that character first
and then you refused to take my hand
when I came to get you?
I tried to reach for your hand, but I pressed the wrong button.
We need to get out of here right now.
I thought it was just click.
I didn't know I had to click in the circle.
I guess I screwed it up.
So it turns out if you play with a controller
it just tells you which button to press
and you just push that button.
The game is fucking broken code.
That's the worst thing I liked the most too
and I just killed them.
You just threw on purpose.
I swear to God.
I didn't even know how to click inside the circle.
That was terrible but avoidable.
You're getting backseated from this chat now.
What does this fucking guy know?
Nothing.
Literally pretending.
I'm clicking.
Fuck you, Jerma.
You gas litter.
These guys have some interesting theories.
Maybe you're choosing to believe
Daniel's theory.
My dream was lengthened after life.
Oh then began
the tempest to my soul.
I passed me thought
the melancholy flood
with that sour ferryman.
Gas lighting himself.
Which poets write of.
Unto the kingdom of perpetual night.
It's possible I suppose.
Maybe the bus driver
shed some light.
This must be very confusing
for you right now.
Doppelgangers, witches
ghosts, death
and demons.
What could possibly tie all of these
souls together?
I dare say we'll find out.
I have been granted
permission to give you a
single hint.
What?
Are you seeing this too?
Do you want a hint? Yes or no?
No, no hints.
Were we not supposed to
discuss that?
I guess we were not supposed to discuss.
I don't think it matters.
We're just smarter than the game.
We figured out VoIP.
This is the only co-op game series that you're not
allowed to talk to the person you're playing with.
You killed the best character.
You knew that was my favorite character.
If I could have saved Judy
I would have.
Sorry, I was literally pretending.
It's time for a new favorite character.
My new favorite character is
the rest of them suck. I don't like the rest of this game.
This one's deleted.
Oh great.
I love how I'm...
You had the decision last time
and I'm saying I tried to help her
but I sabotaged myself
as that character.
You made the right decision as Andrew.
Oh by the way, you weren't paying attention
but since you're Andrew now, you have a gun.
A gun?
Yeah, you got a gun. I got the gun
and they're not going to even let me use it
because you've got it.
They took that away from me.
It's mine now.
Don't worry, I just gave it to you.
What? Did you?
No.
Find a route through the graveyard.
Are you good?
I'm actually mad.
He's going to shoot himself with the gun on purpose.
No, I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to shoot myself with the gun.
Okay, if I shoot
myself with the gun, I will give a
thousand community subs.
If I actively shoot
myself with the gun,
me, and not a cutscene, not like
oh, I can't control it. Like if I
put the gun up to my head and pull the trigger and shoot myself
in the head, I'll give a thousand community subs.
Where are you? I'm reading tombstones.
I gotta make that really clear again.
If I do that in the game in a cutscene,
that's not me.
I have to right click,
hold gun to head below
shoot head, okay?
That's how this works. That's a very important
distinction. Because I swear to God,
if there's a cutscene where this character shoots himself
in the head, I'm going to be really mad
because that's not what I was saying.
Here lies the body of Abraham Alastor.
Oh.
Hey, thanks for pulling me.
Hey, the character's still alive.
She just comes up and
stands next to him and is like, hey guys.
Let's stay away from
that bridge. I want to play as
her again, even in this form. Pretty sure Daniel
and Taylor would be thinking the same thing.
Out of sight, quick!
Shoot head with gun.
My heartbeat is very irregular
right now. Oh,
it's him. Yeah, it's bike guy
again. This is the second time I've
seen him. But we always hide from him.
Why wouldn't we just flag this guy down
and say, hey, remember
us during?
No, about not missing QTEs on purpose.
Make your chat angry at you
deliberately.
Confess to a Twitch crime.
I'll go in and take a look around.
Oh, shit. It's funny that Jerma
thinks he's funny. As far as walking sticks go, I feel like
the pointed edge is probably not very effective.
VIP that guy for a minute.
I can't believe Angela's gone. I mean,
what the fuck?
It's tough for sure, but
tougher on you. You two
are pretty tight.
We split up again?
No. Oh wait, this is me and you.
I couldn't do this without you.
Don't let go.
Just do nothing and stay here.
Synchronized.
Make this moment last forever.
Hey, I found the witches.
They're this way.
Let me read that sign. What's that sign say?
Witch trial.
Witch trail.
This way. That'd be kind of weird.
This way for the witch
trial.
It's still weird because it's witch trail.
Yeah, somebody thinks they're funny.
I don't like this.
I want to go another way.
Don't think there is another way.
He can't climb and he can't read.
Quite the tourist trail.
Not a place I want to revisit.
You found a secret. Yeah, it's just a map.
The secret map.
Massacre memorial.
What the hell is that?
There's also a buffet.
Remember, you're a giggle puss today.
I am very giggly today. I'm having fun.
I get very giggly when I have fun.
This is the first time you've controlled, Taylor.
I feel like you're having the whole game.
Bridge. It's going to fall.
Hey, remember when you said alligator POV?
I did.
Is it there?
Did you get an alligator POV?
There it was.
Don't mess up
the jump QTE.
They're going to burn you
at the stake.
I have to do it?
I have a feeling we're going to get
a hundred percent worst
ending death, everyone.
It was just a debate. We're fine.
What's that?
Witchgrave?
The stone is believed.
The first person executed during the witch trials.
They got a gold medal.
That's pretty fucked up. That's not too much rating.
It's less than a paragraph.
Why was he like that?
That
little girl is evil.
That's an evil dog.
Mr. Pickles is evil.
He's going to trick us into killing the little kid.
Probably.
Or she's going to kill us accidentally.
That's Taylor, right?
No, that's Abatha.
Hey, do you have anything to say about that?
That was pretty fucked up.
Apparently not.
He fucked off like 30 minutes ago.
Where'd he go?
No working phone anywhere.
Okay, so it looks like we really are trapped here.
Still no sign of him?
Nope.
We're still looking for a working phone? That's the only thing...
We're just looking for
a way to communicate with the outside world still.
That's what I did.
Well, you were separated.
And it didn't go well.
Well, she is.
I think she wants us to go after her.
Two girls we've seen.
One is from the past.
And one is from here now.
Maybe the girl we're seeing here is
somehow a mirror image of the girl from the 17th century.
Yes.
Don't you want to wait for Daniel and Taylor?
If this takes place in 1701, isn't this the 18th century?
You're thinking there.
That's true.
That was weird.
It's because that lady died
it just jump cut to us here.
Maybe if we didn't...
That was weird. Memento.
I feel like this is an opportunity
for somebody to die.
There's something blocking the door.
Give me a hand, will you?
It's a little girl.
Heavy chair.
This place is a museum
of some kind.
It's not a museum, it's just
really old.
It's an old house.
Thank god I'm not Andrew, because if you shoot yourself in the head,
but if it was me, I would have to give a thousand community subs to my community.
Community?
Yeah, but we're both Andrew.
No, you're Andrew right now.
So if you shoot yourself in the head with the gun, I don't have to do anything.
What now?
Is it Dummies?
The book is on sale, it's only $8.
What if Italic shoots you
in the head? No.
The deal was, if I had an opportunity
to shoot myself in the head with the gun,
and I right click, aim gun at head,
shoot head with gun, then I would give a thousand community subs,
because I said there's no way I would do that.
I'm not going to make that, I'm not going to let it happen.
I already read this book.
Oh, this is the mannequin house. One of these mannequins.
You try this door? Ain't a mannequin.
I don't even know where you are.
I'm in the same room.
I'm stuck. Wait, hold on.
Are there any doors that are actually open?
Or are we just stuck in here?
It's a museum, you're always stuck in there.
You just read stuff.
Rit of forfeiture.
Yeah, yeah.
Did you push all these hanging mannequins
by chance? I did not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The board of selection on the 7th day of January
1692.
You ordered two caricatures
of the land by Western River
and they were over there dwellings upon the land
so they followed forward or whatever.
But you found a secret.
It says, Mary
confessed to
Bad stuff.
Mary confessed.
Well, what the heck?
It was her testimony
that got the other person killed.
Oh.
Did that cut off for you?
Yeah, this kid Mary had schnitzel?
The enclosed puppet or doll
is thought to have originally belonged to a child.
Come take a look at this.
I've seen this before. Where?
On the road outside that shitty little bar
we stopped at.
Angela and me saw it laying there, picked it up.
Not bad.
How many video games
is this that dude in that's Andrew?
I feel like I see his computer generated
face all the fucking time.
Maybe you just watched
every trailer for this game.
No, that's a bad idea.
You want to look at intentionally throwing.
Yeah, it kind of was.
But I've seen his face before in CG
like this.
More than once or twice.
Wait, why are we looking at the doll again?
We're gonna have another conversation about the doll.
Where's the gift shop?
It was the kid in Toy Story.
That wasn't based on anybody's real face.
Did this museum ever even open?
Be so satisfying.
The cat's gonna mean something.
The cat's gonna start talking.
Or it's gonna lead us somewhere
where the cat saves the day.
The cat is the transformation
that the guy in the
office that like
doesn't ad break to talk to us
is. He's like watching us.
Oh, right. Yeah, that makes sense. That's him.
Okay.
What did we find out? What did we do in there?
That was worth talking about.
Yeah, you're right. We're pretty overdue for a
lore hand grab. You're right.
No apps on your phone?
What kind of alien person are you?
Oh, I'm Daniel.
The professor was real keen to get into town.
Oh, yeah. Let's go through the sewer.
You don't want to climb
through the sewer grate?
There's literally a fire
on the... Look up.
Look towards the sewer, but up.
I can't. I can't look up.
What do you mean you can't look up?
Come over here.
There's a fire. You're right.
Just walk towards the light.
Well, you can't.
Video game characters can't climb
out of QTE. Okay.
Okay. Leave it at
the door here. Okay.
We don't want to get... You don't want to get me angry.
Be honest.
Anybody getting sick of
let's find a way into the house?
I feel like this happens over and over again in this game.
Dude, we gotta find a phone.
Even though we all have phones,
we gotta find a landline.
A house? Find a way in. Okay. Another place?
Let's find a way in. Now that door's locked.
Find a way around the other side. Crawl on the window.
Why can't there just be open doors?
We gotta go through the skylight.
We're probably on like two or three
different timelines. It's probably...
They're gonna do some saw ending.
They're gonna be like...
They're gonna explain the whole thing.
Another window. Oh, let's try to open it.
I never shot myself in the head with a gun.
I don't owe you anything.
We've done this like four times.
I don't want to open another fucking window
and crawl in a building. Like what the fuck?
Option one, open a door. Option two, open a window.
Option three, cross a bridge.
And option four, get grabbed for lore.
Pick one.
I choose lore hand
over anything else.
Alright, find a way to the others.
Did they just get jumpscared by the same mannequins
that we just walked past in the last
gameplay segment? Yeah, but they came into the window.
Yeah, but it was supposed to scare us.
Oh.
And enough with the movie trailer
run across the frame.
Alright.
That's true.
Nope.
Get in there and take a picture.
I'm in the medieval times.
We're on Instagram.
Okay, I'm going in for lore.
Oh, you are?
I just heard a crunch.
Okay, he's been ported.
There was a crunch and then he disappeared.
I'm going in for lore.
God damn it. We both
have a hand of cards in our hands.
I got walk around as NPC
and climb through a window. He got lore
hand. Bullshit.
He top decked that.
He's not even in there.
It's not going to open.
Oh, no. I just drew
from my deck. Can't open door
by pushing on it hard.
What's next?
What happened?
What happened in here?
You got lore snatched.
Fucking so weird. Speaking funny.
Sorry I wasn't there for you.
This woman, the one who looked like me, they just
dragged her out like some kind of
criminal. I mean, shit.
What?
Let's get out of here. I hear that.
So I saw the little kid
in like the 1700s and she started
flossing and then they said that she was demon
possessed. You know, I kind of wish
that's really what happened. I would give this game
a full letter grade if that were real.
It's not that far off from what happened.
They took the other person.
They took my double instead.
I found a knife. Maybe it was a knife
once when dinosaurs roamed
the earth. It said pathetic.
I'm not pathetic.
Here, you take it.
Why? Alright, if you stab yourself
in the head, it's 2000 something.
No, you can't say that.
You take it. I don't want it.
Just in case. You have it. I'm not taking it.
I don't have the knife.
I gave it to you first.
But I gave it back to you.
I tail tailed you, dude. You tried.
I tried. We both tried.
Watch the knife just be on the ground.
Where am I keeping the knife is what I want to know.
It's a knife. It doesn't have a sheath.
Did I just put it in my pants?
That wasn't even scary.
It's just dangerous.
I found the Bible, but there's no lore.
It just says Bible. Oh, never mind.
I found all the witchcraft.
Oh, I found caricature.
And a piece of wood.
Oh, this is the wood that I hit the demon in the head with.
The 2x4.
Amy Lambert. Amy was accused of witchcraft
by the girl Mary Milton
who claimed she saw her fly on a twig of willow
and told by the court that Amy
had been seen by witnesses many miles away.
Mary stated, I saw her lips
ever chattering. Who knew
what and recognized her
as a demon sent to me in Amy's form.
Pastor Carver admitted
this into the record as spectral
evidence. That was a paragraph. I'm fine.
Hey, can you come over here?
Sure. Do you think this is like
chiropractors in the 1700s
right here? This? No.
What my flashlight's pointing at.
That's a cheese wheel. That's like a
Marble Stiltskin wheel. Oh, yes.
Yeah.
We're going to rid your body of pain by
putting pain on top of you.
No, this is torture, right? I think
it's T-posing. Okay, so what else
do we have to do in our second playthrough
of the Museum Leopard? I heard a loud
noise, but I didn't see anything. It was this.
This thing just fell over, tried to scare me. It didn't even work.
I looked at that already. I'm stuck.
Don't look at it again. Don't look at it again. No.
Don't look at it. We didn't look in here, right?
Yeah, we checked this area. Clues.
Yeah, you read this one. What about this painting?
The doll's gone. That's what the thing
is. Oh. They took
the doll. This is
the ace attorney thing.
Look at this. The enclosed puppet
or doll is thought to have
originally belonged to a child. Yeah, the doll's gone, yeah.
In the 1600s. Creepy.
Window scare. Shit, wait,
I got it. What was the cat again? This missing doll has
got to be the one I saw with the kid.
You think? That's kind of weird.
Kind of weird? People are saying we should have burnt it. This place is full on
Nightmare Central. I don't want to
stay here any longer than I have. We had an opportunity
to burn it, remember? With you on that. The last two?
Oh, you don't know that. It said
burn it or put it back. Oh, yeah,
I didn't know that. Yeah, but I didn't want to be like
intentionally ruin the game Andy.
I'm saying Andy a lot. How many Andes are there?
I'm saying Andy a lot.
Alright, I'm not going to say Andy anymore.
You're kind of an Andy Andy. One guy
said it like a month ago.
Some people said it and then it was during
Fall Guys stream. It was the worst Fall Guys player
on Twitch, first of all.
It just stuck with me. Did you
ever even get a medal? No, not one.
No, that's not all. I did. I got one
medal because everybody disconnected and I was the last person
in the game. That's real. It still counts.
Does it count? I mean, you got
five, didn't you?
I got like three.
Oh, it's my knife.
Oh, that is the knife. You're right.
Another instrument of death
added to the group's collection.
Good work.
Let me help you out.
Give you one little
hint. He's so badly.
Okay, we don't talk about
this. We don't talk about this?
We just have to decide.
One says yes and one says
no. Did I say yes?
Well, here's a hint for people that can't
cooperate.
Cooperate!
Best line of the game so far.
I'll leave you now with some
wise words from a great
Irish playwright I once met.
I feel like the devs reaching out
to us like, please
God, just work together.
Never judge anyone shortly.
Every saint has a past
and every sinner has a
future.
Is it a lore hint?
I'm assuming he tells you a piece
of the story.
You remember how like Man of Medan,
he tried to like give us a hint that
the monsters are not what they seem.
But without just
spoiling the game, why even
have that? I don't understand.
He's just asking if you want to read his
Wikipedia article he's going to read to you?
I think because most people who play
these games, we'll call them normal
people, don't want all the characters
to die when the credits roll.
But when you do a psycho
playthrough, we are pretty ambivalent
about them.
I'm going for the
I see a shiny thing, so I'm just going to pick it up.
Yeah, this is shiny over here too.
This is
I mean, the one piece of
wood blocking the thing.
Well, I know who's next on the chopping block.
And it ain't
me. What do you mean? How do you know?
You know? Did you get a permission?
Oh, I know.
Does it involve a
gun being pointed to anyone's head?
Stand right behind me.
But like over one of my shoulders.
Oh, you bumped me. Apparently, if you
go idle for like more than 10 seconds,
it does like a zoom
in, and you get the man-of-the-dan
facial. Oh.
You have to wait. I am.
If it doesn't do it again, it's going to be
really embarrassing.
It's not doing it. Maybe it's because you were looking
at the lore. I don't know. But I got the full
Oh, there it is. No.
I want to raise his hands and go
yeeeeeeah
and fall asleep like fucking Super Mario.
Who's bumping me out of it? Did you bump me
again? I'm not even close to you. I'm on the
road.
Oh, sorry. I didn't appropriate the noise
correctly. That noise I made was Mario
climbing up a cliff.
What I meant to say was Mario was tired.
Right. I got the noises wrong.
I apologize. Okay, I'm done.
Are you here? Yeah, it's I'm a tired.
Yeah, that's my fault.
The same
road. Honestly,
there are some Call of Duty maps that are bigger
than this.
You're blowing this out. It's overexposed. I can't say
this.
It is?
I'm sorry.
It's me.
This place is as big as
fucking Nuke Town.
The fog's coming back. Foreclosure.
Bank owned. Keep up. Flashlighting
stream.
We've got a roadblock, so we've got to take the detour.
Or we can walk up to the roadblock.
Let them say, it's roadblock.
And then we can take the detour. That's what's going to happen.
Where the hell is that coming from?
Coming from the crow. It's like a Bluetooth speaker.
The significance to the crow.
Oh, that wasn't a cutscene. I was just
itching my nose.
Look at this little lake.
We can go this way.
Tire swing. I also just wish the characters
didn't walk around like they have sandbags on their shoes.
What's it doing here?
I lived in Little Hope when I was 10.
I mean,
there's a lot of wacky shit going on.
How would I not believe this?
Oh, you don't look alright.
No, it's alright. We both got
Lore snatched this time.
And it went bad.
Oh, it was just hysteria.
They're going to have a face.
I don't think we can do anything.
I didn't get a decision.
I think that she just dies.
But isn't that my character?
Yeah, but remember, Judy died.
What?
Yeah, but I got an option to like
step in or do something.
Oh.
Like say something.
Final death
of premonition.
I didn't get a promise.
By the way, it's actually
they told us to cooperate.
So I'm going to cooperate.
It's not me. It's you.
OK.
We didn't switch characters.
Actually, it's probably just both of us.
We're probably just all going to get visited.
Sure. We're all going to get a visit
from the devil.
I saw the spike from the monster
about to go into your face.
You did?
Yeah. What?
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Cat. Cat.
We got a cat over here.
Can somebody call like animal control?
Over here. Well, no, we can't.
Obviously, we can't catch it.
Feels like we're being followed.
We are being followed.
By you.
Get the fuck out of here.
That'll work.
Fuck off. Get the fuck out of here, dude.
Don't we have a knife?
Oh, my God.
Do we
What do we do? Do we?
I don't know. You tell me.
We're going to run. We're going to run.
What? You don't even tell me
I got that wrong.
Are you leaving me? No.
I'm good. I don't know why, but for a second
I thought you just had socks on.
I was like, why do you have shoes on?
Damn, dude.
All right. I'm catching up.
We're good.
We just keep seeing like the feet.
Can we see the face?
That one was quick.
This one's hard, dude. Be careful.
Oh, yeah.
It's not going to last. This road goes in a loop.
Like, where are we going to go?
Is that Taylor?
The floating pair of legs.
Taylor! Is that you back there?
Get to the church! Run!
Watch out. It's like
somebody turned on god mode, but it's backfiring.
Hey!
What are those fucking things after us?
You're going to sacrifice that guy.
Leave him! Leave him!
Get inside!
Does he not see it?
I'm going to go help him, dude.
Go get him. Go get him.
Gun! Watch out!
What?
Did you do that?
Get in here.
Did I miss?
Oh, now you come in after we shoot the gun.
I just turned the shoes off right in the fucking head.
Shit!
Come on, we need a barricade here.
No, I didn't miss. I just shot at it.
Wait, is that...
Wait, we barricaded this guy out?
We got to let this guy in. Take the barricade off.
Are we serious?
Magic feathers.
Whatever he's up to, we can't trust him.
I know you're inside.
It's a lore feather.
What in god's name is he up to?
He's going to leave that thing straight to us.
He doesn't get how much trouble we're in here.
Aaron, look me in the eye.
Don't even think about going outside.
You motherfucker, you. You take a god damn shot at me.
Oh, there's a monster.
We have to get rid of him.
We're in deep shit if that thing hears us.
What are you talking about?
That guy...
Are we in different lore or the same one?
Go. You're in real danger.
I know. From you.
You'll regret it big time if you don't leave right now.
Get out here and face me like a man, you chicken shit.
Listen, you need to go before something very bad happens.
You're threatening me? You got no balls, man.
You'll never be anything.
Why can't I just say hey?
He's trying to like...
Good job at things out there.
We're not together, right?
It's doing with us. Doesn't feel right.
Shutting that old guy out there.
It was that or risk all of us getting killed.
I made the right call.
Who said it was your call to make, dude?
This guy thinks he's making calls.
He wants to hook up with the ghost version of his dead...
Was that his sister or wife?
I don't know.
We're in the same room watching different movies on opposite TVs in the room.
It's me. I'm next.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Who knew that the ghost could be kept out just by blocking a door?
Whatever.
Meet accusations against my double.
Sounded serious.
We're in church.
Not this time. It sure looked like it was heading that way.
I'm surprised he lasted this long.
I love how the time they need to process language.
It's so funny.
I love it.
I think we have to stay here because it's a church.
Hey, grab the cross.
What if you're right? What then?
If we can stop her, it could prevent any more harm happening to our doubles.
Okay.
It happened 300 years ago.
They're dead either way.
Yeah, I guess I'm kind of confused as to what the fuck is even happening in this story.
So these are our doubles, but it's us.
Like our ancestors or just us?
I don't know.
Tripping through time.
What if those are like the actual stunt doubles?
Yeah.
For like the motion capture.
Changing the past.
Yeah. I don't know.
Hey, kid. You out here?
Are we in the bell tower?
I don't know. Are you Andrew?
Am I Andrew or are you Daniel?
I'm Daniel or Andrew.
I'm up here too.
Law grab.
Sick.
Did you get law grab too?
Yeah, I'm here too.
They had to split it up into two chapters here.
It pains me to say these words.
Just push him out the window.
Your punishment today will protect us all.
Keep our town safe.
Why haven't we tried to touch anybody yet?
We did, actually.
When I was Daniel, I grabbed somebody and they said,
I froze.
You please cannot reach him.
My fate is not a memory you should carry.
Who will be my keeper if you are gone?
You should have thought about that before you killed him.
He will be your keeper.
The decision not all are in agreement with.
Every man will face his day of judgment.
Yours is today.
No!
I almost missed that QTE.
You see, that's what I did.
It was a hair.
I didn't know there was going to be one.
CE is no longer of this earth.
He's being held by nothing?
He's being held up by nothing, but you're not here.
Oh, I get it.
It's a spirit.
That's the knife.
I didn't get a QTE.
I didn't either.
But it's like the guy died in the prologue.
It's the fire.
Wait, did you get a QTE? I don't know if I should trust you.
Did you get a QTE?
No, I swear to god I didn't get a QTE.
I am so dead laser focused on QTEs now because of the intentional throw.
You're right.
I'm laser focused on QTEs because of that.
My reputation is forever tarnished.
I have to try to build it back up.
Chad is all saying you're sus right now.
No, I didn't have a QTE.
I swear to god, go watch the VOD.
No, I'm not going to watch your VOD.
I'm playing the game. I'm here.
Don't you want to see my perspective?
There won't be any more VODs once we get timed up for that song in the prologue.
Holy shit, that was incredibly condescending and horrible.
That was terrible.
I didn't know it was going to be that 100 miles per hour.
I'm just going to go along with it.
What are my member benefits?
I'm not dead.
He is beanie.
Don't bury me.
That's quite the response.
Why did that kid Mary want us to see her brother executed?
Daniel, you're wicked high right now.
Come on.
We're missing a piece of the puzzle somehow.
Like what?
Not sure.
First time I saw Mary, I felt like I recognized her from some place.
Me too.
I know I've seen her before.
You don't know where you've seen Mary?
No, the fire.
We all were in the same house.
Maybe we don't remember that.
Maybe we don't know that.
Maybe that was like another past self or something.
Like a future self.
I don't know.
Listen, this ghost has no access to their arms and legs.
Just stay somewhere where they can't fly to you and you'll be fine.
What do we do now with that thing outside?
Quiet.
It's out there.
It's out there for now.
We all died in the fire.
We all died in the car crash.
We're making history right from 300 years ago.
I have no idea.
A church? Maybe it can't come in.
Really? It's a fucking vampire now?
I'm just saying. This is a solid building.
He's right. We're safer in here.
We're staying put.
Option one. Stay inside where the hanging monster doesn't kill you.
Or go outside where it could kill you.
Yeah, why would you leave?
What to do?
We are staying in here.
No choice.
Okay. Maybe you got a point.
Perhaps that thing will get bored and take off.
We have nowhere else to go.
What happened to the dude outside?
Where's, um...
Aren't we missing somebody?
No, not the old lady. I know she's dead.
No, it's just these four.
Besides the windows, out of all the buildings
that we have investigated today,
this is the A, largest, and B,
least full of holes building.
Yeah, it's also...
Okay, I take that back.
There's some holes.
I miss her every day.
This place keeps getting weirder.
It was a school.
Church. What's in the church?
What is Andrew looking at over here?
Go find the Bible. Go do a sermon.
Sounds like more than one.
Uh-oh, found something.
It's the guy. He got locked out.
He's trying to get in.
Somebody let him in.
It's not the guy.
It's the harpoon lady.
Why did we all run outside immediately
to stay away from the windows?
Quick, go out there and get close.
Oh, that's not good.
We're all in the mist again.
They broke a window and we all bailed.
Alright, I think this is a mute opportunity.
We are alone.
What the fuck was that?
You just have to walk forward until whatever it is
tries to kill you.
Pig? Heard pig noise.
Get ready for the QTE. You have no idea
how ready I am.
It's going to be like a hundred...
Somebody just got hit in the head by a 2x4.
Or like a wrench.
I hope Italics is okay.
I'm not... Just keep muted.
I'm just playing.
I really hope that Italics is okay.
What am I doing?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no. What do I do? Which one?
I'm going left. Fuck.
Who's wrong?
Oh, shit. What do I do?
QTE.
I got a knife.
Thank God I gave the knife back.
Did I stab myself with the knife?
Thank God I gave the fucking knife back.
No, you take the knife. No, you take the knife.
Turns out it was a fucking thousand IQ play.
I'm not John. I'm in trouble.
I'm not John.
What was that?
That was the John Travolta.
What happened? What room am I in?
Oh, yeah. Shit just went down.
Probably for both of us.
Yeah. Well, it did. But also like
the guy I was with disappeared in front of my eyes.
Like his model vanished.
It's such a good thing that I gave the knife back to you.
Otherwise, Taylor is dead if I don't do that.
Can't stop. No, wait.
He needs a break.
Forget it. Those things are coming after us.
Not you. I also saved John.
We can't hang around. Good.
You're John. I saved you.
Thanks for saving me.
Stick together and we'll be fine.
Fine like Angela, right?
That's a low blow.
What's our next move?
I'm not sure.
Dude, I was getting like almost
murdered by the monster.
Were you fighting the hanging monster?
I was. I was fighting the crawling monster.
And you popped in while
there's like a tongue wrapped around my neck
and I'm fighting for my life and I hear, are you John?
That's impressive.
I wish. No way I could get
any shut eye after what went down tonight.
Would love to though and be.
Any ideas how we're getting out of here?
Why do you always decide where we're going?
It do end up
like that, huh? It's clear now.
There's no help available. We're on our own.
Sure seems that way.
Our best shot, maybe our only shot,
is to stop that girl, Mary.
Getting to Mary, stopping her
might help, sure. Okay.
But what about the other kid?
The one that keeps running from us.
Mary and her are connected
somehow, I'm sure of it.
Maybe the other girl is trying to lead us somewhere.
Where? I don't know.
Maybe to a place we can
stop all this. We were separated at the beginning
of the game.
Mary, the girl
in the original house
was complaining about
no one likes her,
she's invisible to everyone.
She also burnt to death.
You didn't see that part. She literally was
torched on camera.
I think this is the power of friendship.
If we try to kill her, we all die.
If we owe it to the
others, be nice to her.
We all live or something.
The key to this, I'm certain of it.
He said it, not me this time.
It's not that simple.
Like you said, she's just a kid, we can't
listen to her. I get it.
We see her again. We do whatever
is necessary. There's doubles of each of us.
Our doubles.
Keep getting accused of witchcraft.
Now we're accusing this little kid of witchcraft
in our timeline. This place is safe though,
is leaving such a strong idea.
If we kill her, we do the same thing that killed
our doubles back in their time.
Would you look at that?
But who's doing this power?
How are we doing this?
I don't know who's doing the lore grab.
Who's actually doing the lore grab?
Me.
Mr. Lore Grabber, smiley face.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for the tip.
God damn it.
Yeah.
Oh, great.
Here we go.
Seriously, that was so fast.
That was insane.
How do people trip when they run?
Why do you trip and land flat on your face
like you're sliding on a slip and slide?
People don't know that humans don't do that.
Are both of your shoes tied together?
Andrew? You there?
Daniel? Who are you?
Alright, we're gonna have to mute.
I think I'm right next to you, actually.
Wait, didn't this just happen?
Oh, they're telltale-ing me.
You're getting telltale-ed?
You're saving me?
Come on, get it out.
How did I miss? I clicked in it.
You saw me click in the window.
Just let me save you,
I clicked in the window.
I didn't fail that.
How did I fail that?
You go back and you pull that shit back
and you throw it. I clicked in the circle.
Take the clip and then slow-mo it.
I clicked in that circle
in plenty of fucking time.
I did not miss.
I didn't even miss.
Give me the clip.
Show me.
Show me the clip.
Show me the clip. I want to see it.
I swear to God I did not miss that QTE.
I clicked right in the circle with like a half-done.
Don't shoot yourself in the head.
Don't shoot yourself in the head, please.
Okay, wait.
Don't shoot yourself in the head.
I thought you shot her.
The gun.
Who did you shoot?
I shot the monster.
He didn't miss. Look at that.
Didn't miss.
No one can doubt that.
But we need to keep moving
if we want to get out of this place.
John.
Another one just died. A word, please.
He literally didn't miss.
Omega Lul. I know.
I want to watch it.
Then to win a thousand battles.
Then the victory is yours.
It cannot be taken from you.
Not by angels
or by demons.
Heaven or hell.
Perhaps you've started
to realize something.
Uh, yes.
I can't pause the game.
Oh, dude, that's a pretty good hand.
20? Never hit on 20. He just busted.
I can't click that link, guys.
I can't.
May not be quite what they appear to be.
Oh, he said that in the last game.
Three executions.
Three tormented
beings and two
lost souls.
Any thoughts on what might be around the corner?
Hidden by the fog?
Ixilandi?
I don't think that you
could save them because they're being judged
for their actions in purgatory
and they were sent to hell by the demons
that crawled up them and it was them because
it was their inner demons and all that shit.
You were literally in
the circle.
Alright, can I, can we, I have to pee
too. Can I go pee?
Oh yeah, we can take a pee break. Let's take a pee break.
And I want to show this on stream. I'll be back in two minutes.
I'll be back in, uh, I need to
take five because I gotta take the dog out. Oh, okay.
Yeah. Take five.
Alright, let me see this fucking link.
Let me see. How, you show me. I want to see.
No fucking way.
Get the hell out of here. This is bullshit.
How is that, how is that not the circle?
Are you serious?
That's where I clicked. That's in the circle.
That's in the, that's the circle.
That's in the circle.
Look at that. You see where the white ends?
The white ends, it's right in that
inner lip in there.
That constitutes as a click in the circle.
It's not outside the circle. Outside the circle
would be outside that outer ring.
That is one pixel.
The life and death of Daniel.
Sharpen the fuck out of this.
Or sharpen. Excuse me.
That's inside that inner lip.
Enhance it. It's outside the
inner circle. But it's inside
the outer circle by a lot.
The tip is on the, right on the edge.
Fucking damn it.
Alright, alright. But you have to
look, I tried.
That wasn't like a, oh I fucking clicked
red, red, red.
Alright, I'm gonna go pee. God damn it.
One pixel. I'm so...
I could have saved that character.
Alright, I'll be right back.
It's inside that fucking circle.
I'm telling you.
As my first order of business,
as new king of the rats,
I will mod the first ten
people who talk, starting now.
And then ban the next ten.
Choose wisely. Hey,
Germachat, if you're so cool, how come I can't see
what you're writing right now? That's what I thought.
How come someone who can't even see
your chat can bait you into
typing in your chat? Easily manipulated.
Anyway, to my chat,
who is far more
attractive and
patient and kind and loving?
Hello, my chat.
Talking shit? What's he doing?
What'd he say? I just heard a lot of noise coming through the headphones.
What'd he say?
Was he talking shit?
What?
By the way, did you see the image?
I don't know if you saw the image that's been circulating.
About the clicking inside the...
I was in the circle.
Can you link it to me?
Yeah, here. Take a look at this.
Uh, where is it?
Someone give it to me. Yeah, it's been circulating on like
the internet and shit. Why is my chat
saying you were not in the circle? I was.
Very clearly. Take a look.
Alright, I want you to just take a look at that
and tell me that's not in the circle.
Would you constitute that as like being it being in the circle?
Or would you say that's out of the circle?
I gotta enhance. I did
that too? Hold on, one sec.
You're on like
the outline of the circle
is definitely not inside the
circle though. That still should be
a plus. Like you did
it. That should be an acceptable point.
Did you know that I haven't missed a circle yet
with my thumbsticks on a
controller? Yeah, cause you're console aiming.
I'm on the hard one. I'm on PC.
You have auto aim assist on console. I don't
have that. Hey, there's
no aim assist.
All console controller gaming
has aim assist. Of course it does. I'm doing
it like eye to eye, one to one. Like eye tracking
is hard. Anyways, hold on, give me one sec.
Somebody gave 50 bucks.
Who just gave 5,000 bits? Is this PUBG
mobile gamer really gonna lecture me on auto
aim? He doesn't know he's muted.
Who just gave 5,000
bits? I missed it. It's not showing up
anywhere. Wait, there's a straw poll about
this? What does it say?
There's a straw poll. 66
percent said I missed. 34 percent
said I didn't miss. Well,
I think those are pretty good considering.
33 percent or 30
power of many. That's a lot. Yeah, that's a lot
of suck ups.
You do realize this is Twitch chat.
If this was accurate.
Yeah, but I'm with the majority, so I
chose correctly. But if this
were truly... 66 percent have my back
and like 34 percent have yours.
So I'll take those odds. Yeah, but if
this were truly Twitch chat and I truly missed,
wouldn't it be like 5 percent?
No? Wouldn't everybody be like, oh yeah, he fucking
missed. Fuck this guy, it sucks.
That's what I think would happen. They just want to be noticed.
Alright, there was a huge donation
and I don't see it anywhere. I don't know why.
Well, they definitely want to be noticed.
Why can I not see this? I'll catch you at the end of this stream.
I don't know why I can't see it anywhere.
He didn't notice you. Was it fake money?
Alright, you ready? Ready to get
back into this? You do ready.
You do ready first, like we said before.
There we go. Perfect.
Beautiful. Alright, let's go.
Three, two, one, action.
Keep a lookout for the girl.
We have to stop her. Did you pee
on the toilet room and say you hit inside
the bowl?
Nice.
There's another path here if you wanted it.
Another path? Wait, who are you?
I'm Jon. Oh yeah, there was another path.
They may go the same way.
There's three of us here. Who are you?
Hang on, hang on. Pause the game.
What? What? I still have
your circle as like an enhanced
image. I have to
change the scene and then
yeah, okay.
Alright, let's move.
Dude, I got this iced tea from
Target. It's the greatest shit ever.
It's like iced tea concentrate.
It's like my favorite thing on Earth.
You need to dilute it.
No, I do, yeah. You do 50-50
water. It's what, the Tazo
tea? There's a passion fruit and
there's a green peach.
You do 50-50 into water. Oh,
it's unbelievable. It's the best. It's great.
Dangerous unstable structure
ahead. There's a lot of fireflies
around this mystical door.
Yeah, there is, isn't there?
Yeah, unstable structure.
What is that light?
Looks kind of beautiful, don't you think?
Don't go towards the light
here. Yeah, that's when your eyes
are glazed over and you're under a spell.
Lore grab.
Sick.
Dude, that was a lore grab out of nowhere.
Play his fucking entrance
music.
What ails you, my friend?
Goku instant
transmission.
Oh, yeah.
Why take out Merry and not like the guy
listening to her? We were just
standing over there, by the way.
I thought this was supposed to be us. Wait,
why are we just standing?
Yeah, but like why are we so weirdly
standing?
Oh yeah,
I was gonna say the same thing.
Every swear word combined.
Screaming as loud as you can.
Oh fuck, what do we do?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Little hope is no longer. That's how he's already seeing spirits strange and disturbing events have become wrong. No. I'm right a little too late you
Tell us do you find that to be a bad response one of these no?
I thought it was I would said feeling the same thing we talked about yeah
We're my friend, but it does not sit easily with me that in doing so I condemn a child
Putting it all on a kid isn't right the priest is the one driving this whole thing
Reverend Carver is a man guided by God
No one can doubt that
I'm I support you
cooperate
Second I don't know what's right or wrong anymore. Nothing here makes sense. Hi Taylor. Let's you join us
Let's just show up. I
Enter stage left. Maybe we'll see him again get him to change his mind. I made the right call
I have no doubts. Yeah, we did
You made the right call. I made the right call. We both made the right call
Really not
This girl has been grabbed around the neck by this monster three or four times
Wait, do we just not get to do anything? I think I'm just died. Oh
One pixel
Taylor where are you?
What how where are you guys always trust your ears trust your ears always not movement your eyes to see if you ears do not
You're right. I'm over here
Found you
Remember follow your nose your fruit look green apple cherry and strawberry
Dialogue choice there
I was pretty weak
Yeah, that was pretty limp I think better have been really heavy
This poor girl, I mean seriously, this is like the fourth or fifth time that she gets like smokered from leopard dead
Yeah, like fucking kiss this lady from the lobby expert mode. Okay, and it's hard to keep up
No boot from the lobby man. You keep getting grabbed by special effect is fuck out of here
I want to get to the first safe house. All right. Now. I'm John. I am Andrew
Honestly after this many times. It's probably not even scary for her anymore. Well that but that's her right?
So that's why it keeps doing it that to her
Yeah, I'm going to claim
her
Weird looking tree over here. No, I I'm gonna look at the tree. Okay, it's
It's got the stick bug symbol on it. Okay. She's not even playable anymore
Yeah, she's kind of not we have to go down or back to the road
Yeah
You coming or not? Whatever that thing was I was about to ask where Daniel was and I just remembered
Daniel is in a better place. What went on back there? No clue
Whatever we saw back there or thought we saw we're still in grave danger
You've killed everyone
To there must be something we can do Mary's in the middle of all this that I'm certain of but what if it doesn't work?
We don't know for sure that stopping Mary will help us out. It's just a theory
It may only be a theory, but right now it's all we've got come on
Let's take a look. You know if I said that I would have gotten minus two for sure all right
Well that was those were the two more
Peaceful options. Yeah, those are peaceful
Hydropraktor hey dude. Hey locked door can't wait to see the locked door and
I was just watching my character's death. You know it's really funny
You're the one that's seeing all the ways to prevent the deaths, and I'm the one that's dying
It's really not like they don't tell me what QTE. I'm gonna have to push
It's just a visual of them actually dying, but it's nice to know that they come true because then you control the character
Yeah, so it comes true. The ink is already written. It's dry. I'm not doing anything wrong. You are seeing the future can't be prevented
It's already happened harvard for mayor by the way if you're curious I get choked out really wait choked out by the monster tongue
I had a new monster. Oh
upstairs
So there is like a dramatic irony in that John was the character we predicted to die first and he may be the only
Character that survives that's true. Hey up here under the Dave state
He's back coming. You can't keep running
I'll make sure they'll find you
That guy's a menace. We're probably that's how bad a mess. We're in come on. We're like in some weird
I mean in this guy's defense
We've just been going around the old town breaking into every single building and like messing shit up
Please make sure they'll find you. I don't think he's talking about the monsters. We're probably just in some weird purgatory world
Timing how is my time to speak before the judge?
Maybe we're finally getting somewhere filled with dread my testimony will be received
The devil has blinded so many to what is real and what is not
Nothing good will come. I love this putting on the accent acting to twist the truth allow me to judge. What is true?
Abraham and joseph are allies in this deception and lest we forget you condemned joseph. He does sound like johnson
What do you now question that decision?
I've heard nothing today to sway my conviction joseph consorted with the same malicious force as his wife
That's because Sean beans accent was so good
They told all the other actors to imitate him and that's why everyone on game of thrones sounded like that
That's real Sean beans real accent
Damn imagine being that good of an actor
You tell every other fucking actor they're not good enough be more like Sean beam great fortitude to speak out against the evil here
Many would have lacked her courage
Yet her reward for exposing this brooding covered in our midst is to be besmirched. Her courage is not in question
It is her intent. We must be certain of
Her accuser is the very man entrusted to care for this innocent child
Plain to see he is not fit for such a task and I would ask the court to have Mary placed elsewhere
So Andrew double agree you are via a new ward reverend
Throw the kid under the bus. I guess
If the court agrees
First the court must hear what Abraham has to say. No decision could be made on the child until then
Abraham what am I to do?
Some would have me speak out against Mary, but could a child truly be capable of such evil
Sorry, I don't know. What do you know? Oh god. I
Feel like we're getting
trick question real
I understand your dilemma the consequences couldn't be more serious, but the girl is so young
such evil
No, the call what you have come here to say
She's my queen. Speak up boy
No out with it
Mary has spoken of evil spirits
Devilry and witchcraft. I do won't it things many cannot believe could exist here and I'm not here for history and here say
Mary is tormented don't want to hide really as I was kind of a Thanos there plagued her
stolen her innocence
Some suggest she is in league with these creatures, but no one can be certain
myself least of all
Can any of us truly know a child's mind?
You claim I lack the ability to see the truth. I thought that was you talking my beg forgiveness dogs
I swear to God. I thought that was you doing that such a thing my time is not for wasting you
I'm the one the priest have me enough for one day. I have more to say I have already given you enough time
This is you talking
Furthermore Mary is to be placed into the care of Reverend Carver's now stand down
That really did sound like you putting on like doing a voice
He just kind of turned into that that was weird. I believe we have the actor for judge very in Britain
Whatever his name was here. So what happened did the little devil child get nailed?
Okay, so now what?
I mean, this is I have to do this one. This helps us has to we now know for sure that we can alter
What happens true seriously?
We can change the friggin past
Not cool. This sucks. I
Don't know the dude yelling at us in all caps be cooperative
Cooperate has got me like, okay
Looks like a difference, but we shouldn't get ahead of ourselves
We have flip-flopping
Much it's unbelievable
Whatever's out there. It still wants Taylor. We have to go now
Okay, explore the factory bounce up. I found something. I
Remember my dad in pants like that
Emery of James Clark the guy in the town on the left. It's a weird comment
Just go kill Hitler guys. We can alter the past fuck this like dumb Salem witch trial shit. Let's go kill Hitler
Unfortunately, we would need some kind of like demon Hitler to grab our arm to take us back to that
I'm sorry. I can't explain what just happened
What a video game bug spirit just
Yanked me about 10 feet backward. I spoke demon Hitler's name and he he pushed me dude
I'll push from this end. Did you get log? It was a log grab or was it? Oh, it was like a like bug grab
Oh everything you got
Nice fall joke that on purpose
Why'd you do that just about I was looking at Lord
No, I just pressed a button. I'll look for a way out down here
Okay, we'll meet up at the back of the building
Sure, he looks really yeah, but why we have not been able to control Taylor for the last 40 minutes
There's like a crypt down here
You guys can't reach a stick down and like both work together to pick me up or something. So you're John right now, right?
I don't know so find out a second. I'm watching Andrew right now. Yeah
Maybe this is both of us. Someone's gonna get a co-op partner and someone's not
Hmm, or maybe we're just these two people. Oh
Let's see. It looks like it's changing scenes
Are you here with me as Andrew or Taylor? I just switched back to John I think okay
Well, let's go ahead and mute those mics
Thank God. I have the co-op partner because I'm the one that needs all the help
You're okay
It's a chance for you to kill two more people
Okay, how funny would it be if it's Alex?
Just randomly with the mics muted
Gets like a game over on his screen because these two are dead and he's the last one. Imagine the disappointment
Four out of four dead from me
Now he has to be responsible for somebody dying. You know what I mean?
He's gonna fuck up a cutie. I'm gonna fall down a hill
What would you do?
What was the purpose of that? Yeah, there was no point you just went down and we went I saw the little girl on a bridge
To see you same here literally it right
Hunter that dude was just looking at us. Where did you guys come from?
We just like right now. Yeah, we just walked up over you
Somebody said oh, no, it's zon. It's Hitler. That's not how this works
Somebody seen this before old car witchcraft on this car. I hope somebody law grabs me out of the trunk
Damn it. Oh
I found the little girl again. You keep a little girl
Don't shine your flashlight at her. She's waiting for her cue
Okay, okay careful. Stop. Stop. Stop. Freeze. I
Look to your left and then walk towards me slowly. No your other left. You said left you turned right
What are you talking about? Turn left and walk towards John. I did turn left turn left and walk towards John
My left the characters left. How would I know which way your cameras facing? That's what I did
You're just standing there walk towards John. Okay now without turning the camera look behind you
How do I look behind me without turning the camera? Okay, well turn the camera, but don't turn your character
No, that's what I was doing and you screamed at me. Yeah, cuz you've shown the flashlight right at it
I don't see you see the little girl. No, she's standing in the like past the picket fence. You don't see her
No, okay walk towards the fence then and let's see what happens the other okay behind you
Wait, your camera is behind you face your character the way my character's facing
But you don't talk or or somebody exposed. Okay. All right. I'm seeing
Come on. Okay. Yeah, you're looking over here. You're looking straight this way. There's no little girl, right?
Turn the camera around because if you shine the flashlight at her, she's gonna freak out. She's in the other opposite direction
She's this way, but I'm trying not to shine my flat. Oh, okay. She's all this is past that fat
Okay, I'm trying to avoid the trigger that happens when we inadvertently walk up to it
I thought you talked about like over this fence that we're standing in front of yeah
I'm just wondering how long is she gonna stand there like waiting for us to do like a spook. Let's sneak up on her
No, never mind in the fog there. You see that see that's what I cooperate
All right, so is this girl real is this girl real in real life here in our time
Is it is one in this timeline and one in like the 300 years ago time?
But like who the fuck is this? This is the current timeline one
So there's three
The lower one is the old time
No one in the whole safe while you still draw breath
You must die today
Not even your wife Amy was torture. Why do you rocks? Why doesn't everyone in town just dog pile on top of them?
It's speaking of my late wife
There is still fighting you drop the rock on his head drive the devil out for the safety of everyone here
Joseph do you renounce the devil and all his teachings?
I'm no disciple of the devil
I who
Have to stop this. Oh, what the fuck?
Just listen to me listen to me give me that's all
You give me that look
See how this poor child is tormented Joseph still clutches her with the devil's hand
more stones
The devil must be crushed from within him
Do not flinch
Wait the reverend is in on it. He's the actual which guy
Look, okay
If I had walked over there and lifted I could have lifted the rocks up they would float and it'd be like oh
And it's the Satan and she's doing that
The rocks will be floating around
And it would be even worse
I'm just trying to get the fucking doll out of her hand. It's new monster time
All right, have we considered like tying a rope around our waists so we don't get lost separated or you're you don't have a lot of time
Have we considered spelling out shit in the dirt with the rock that just says like
We're not Satan
Would you get sledgehammer
They almost got me with that one they move the circle
Why am I standing here?
That's okay, I'm handling this one
All right, I'm coming my character decided to do something
My God, I swear to God, but by this point this is pretty much
QTE's what year are we come on? This is like 2001
Don't worry fuck the QTE's I can tap faster than anybody
You just leave foot is in the air waiting to kick him in the face
We just have to load your foot
I can't get this wrong
How fast I was trying to move the mouse you have no idea
So you serious?
Please tell me you heard me
One two, three, four five with the fucking mouse
That was that was I can't fucking believe that
fucking believe it
You heard it. You all had to have heard it. I can't be held exactly what I saw
All right, listen, can we pause the game for just a second this is good don't pop
Did you go over three there
I tried so hard. All right. We're all dead. None of us is getting out of here alive. Hey, we're not dead yet
Listen something here isn't right. I had one last chance to undo
That fuck up
but they switched the QTE type on me at the last second and I I missed the last one because I had four in a row of
Move the thumb stick and hit the crosshair and then on the last one they switched it to push X
so if you try to move the thumb stick that counts as a button and
it invalidates
dude, I was like and
And what happened at the end for there man, I had to do not one not two not three but four full
Wrist across my entire mouse pad and I didn't even get halfway. You know what I did
I just moved my thumb to the left and right
controller, baby
I'm plug a controller in right now
All right, pause it pause it pause. I need a second. That was so stupid that it was
Unfucking believable. Let me just plug a goddamn controller, but here's like I don't move the mouse
You can't even do it because we it asks you if you want to use a controller or a keyboard
We'd have to like go back to menu at this point. What's the at this point? What's the point?
Shit. Yeah, it's what's the point we got like fucking maybe
Listen everybody German just didn't want to do a fuckface run after this
So he's just trying to make the first one the fuckface runs that way with that both of them at the same time. Oh
My chest is killing me that was too fucking funny it was so stupid. All right, I
Try to use a controller. What do you think Alex? You'd be you'd be the judge at this point
I mean, you know what to expect with the mouse and keyboard. Okay, that's true
I don't know if you switch to a controller. You've got it like I gotta relearn just again
That's true. By the way, somebody said it was six times. It was six full across the whole mousepad
Wait, you you missed six in a row. No, no, okay. I had I had to bring my mouse
Across the screen into the target to click and hit with the sledgehammer
But it that for some reason the mouse sensitivity was so
Obscenely slow and I have no idea why I had to do one two three four five six
Across the whole mousepad to get it halfway. I have no idea. It was fucking outrageous. Let me look hold on controls
Yeah, it's my mouse sensitivity is fucking 50. It's huge. That's just the default. Well, I don't need to change that
All right, I'm just gonna go whatever I've already know I let's go
All right me first. Oh my god, I'm like, I'm gonna have to get back after this shit
Okay, let's go. No, I didn't if I hit the DPI button, I mean this would be different. This has not changed at all
Why do I have to be three for three for killing everybody? It's not fair
How would I know that there's even anything on this wall? They don't notice me at all
They don't care. See I told you guys that was the key line. You were right beginning of the game that
Actually, that's exactly what you said. I'm gonna have to give you credit
Wait, did you hear what I just heard? Yeah, I'm currently stuck staring out of a window
But did you hear like the little girl's voice? Yes, I did. I'm I can't get out of the window
Are you are we in the same room? I'm looking at like a grandfather
With a key in it and you come like bump me can you come like grab me by the back or something?
I can't move on. It's a key in here. Take the key. Take the key. Okay, I got out. I can't take the key
No, I fucking do I need to come bump you?
You missed your cue you supposed to scare me
Me no. No, I can't even explain. It was just fucking stupid. All right, it didn't work
I'm gonna come to you because I think my game is starting to fucking
attack itself
Successful parenting. I think this is like a
Reverend reverend's cursing little girls with witchcraft through time the game based on that lore. I
Can't get over it. I it's too stupid. Hi
People are spamming right now. They say on my first playthrough
All of my characters survived even though I was I wasn't trying very hard to keep them alive. That's from IGN
Whatever wait IGN said that yeah, I can't give the game five by the way
They were probably playing with a controller probably they were I'm sure they were
games and and
Wait, where the hell? Where are we?
How many can see more that I can't touch?
Yeah, me too, but I can go upstairs and in my yoink. Let's go. Maybe yeah, maybe you'll yoink us. Yeah
You hear that? Yep. Gotta be that kid upstairs
We have to go find her. Well, this is the house that burned down
so
Why did we burn down here and then get in a car accident and then teleport back to the year like 1600 you?
She's in here eating candy
I'm chewing ice
Well, that I've just broke a tooth all my teeth in the back of gone. I think we're about to get Lord grabbed
Nice it's so
This isn't right no way I
Assure all gathered here today that our town will be free of the devil's grasp this place burns down together by God's grace
Little hope will prevail
My word on it. This court is hastily convened, but with good reason
If we are to finally rid ourselves of the evil which has infested little old then we must act today. I
Accused you Mary of witchcraft
What say you reverend?
We're gonna save her
The evidence has discovered through my investigation is beyond question who hit me in this shit drop the chandelier on right now
It's a familiar to summon and serve the devil
We have been deceived by a child by her guise of innocence
This pop it was mistakenly used to denounce Tabitha
But it has always belonged to Mary and Mary alone
She allowed her own kin to be executed as she watched in silence
Now this child this creature of Satan has the marrow to accuse me a man of God of wrongdoing
No, it's good
Neither of my options are good. This is crazy. These people have lost their freaking minds
What can I do no
If I could do something to stop this I would right now in her hour of greatest need
I don't see out of the damn pleads once more for the devil's help. Oh
Wait, I think the courts indulgence we convinced him to step in
Please guide me at this time this now. They're both gonna die. Oh shit
Carver is evil Carver's the priest right this carver the priest is Alex. I think so got him. We have to stop this
The only madness is right here in this court Carver. He's the evil one. We have been swayed by malice
The truth hidden from us, but not by Mary
Reverend Carver is the one urging us to believe in the devil silent
This is all you'll not deceive us any longer. Your true purpose is plain to see I
Will see this town purged of all evil
Better go for him. He's right. Listen to him Carver is the guilty one. What must I do to bring little home back into the line?
I
Guess burn down the whole church destroy the doll or
Yeah, you have to stop Carver. Just hit stop Carver
Don't Carver
Stop car. You have to stop Carver. It's him. Don't you get it?
He's condemning Mary to take the heat off himself
Do nothing
Where to God if he shoots himself in the head that doesn't count this outrage this is a centrist run
What I have just learned sickens me to my core. What did you just learn? Yeah, there are serious questions
Which must be asked of you?
What would he say?
Look in the first page of his bible
How can a man of god conduct himself in such a way does it just do know that those are doodles of my math homework
Fucking bullshit. You are free to leave
fool
misled by a child
Do you not see what she is?
I was just bored during the last sermon. So I do my favorite dragon ball z characters
The devil's daughter has deceived you. I feel that I used to draw a diablo two items. I see her
I see her
Satan's whore
You will pay heavily for your crimes
I was one of the first doodles in his bible. Jesus now all that little hope is mesmerized by you
if not the words
Without you I would be dead
You said how did we know that his I shall remember you all my days. We didn't know that we had no idea
That's info that past
Andrew had I guess
But why why wouldn't he immediately act on that if he knew that?
Wait, what still killed three people? They were dead fucking wait
It worked. Yeah. No, I looked in the bible, but it did old timey. Andrew didn't look in the bible
Yeah, that jerk of a priest was the real bad guy
Sure. Yeah
I mean I should feel great. Uh
But I don't I I feel nothing
Come on. Let's get out of here
How do we get out of here? Don't we just walk around the circle or is that this is the curse lifted?
Did he just storm out? I don't think he's dead yet, right the priest
Yeah, but I all right. So but the okay the house in the beginning is supposed to be
He whispered the script into his ear
Wait, and what's going on? Are you trapped in there?
um
Giving you any flashbacks?
Am I gonna catch fire in a second?
No, you you got didn't you hang?
Uh, someone's behind me
Oh here I go getting grabbed by the smoker again
Wait
You just died
Why do you just die? Because I wasn't nice enough in real in my life
I was indecisive and
Abrasive or whatever
We're being judged
But what about Andrew? I don't think I did we do anything bad as taylor?
You were taylor, right? I mean I called somebody a dick like in the beginning of the game
Yeah, but this didn't stick this exact same thing happened in the beginning of the game with the fire
Then I ran away and then I woke from a car accident. Remember?
Shouldn't have called that guy a dick
Everybody who is mean to anybody else at any point in this game gets killed by their monster double
What's the but what's the whole car accident part?
But what what's the whole burn the house down in the beginning part? Well, we uh
Every single person in the game is dead now except uh, no john no john's dead
Yeah, it comes I have to do it. I have to this infinity war spoiler
If you haven't seen infinity war then fucking just mute your everything
This is like just Thanos at the end. I thought you'd be here
Leave me alone. Will you?
That's I've lost everything you've lost everything
Are you kidding me? Who is this? Just get out of here. Go away. You should have stayed away
Big reveal. Oh
Is andrew going to jail that was uh tanya's boyfriend
Why is he so much older and why am I so young anyone those things whatever the hell they are they did it not me
Um, was there a voice line there? All I wanted to do was keep them safe. He just mouthed the words. Yeah
You okay, buddy
You seem a little confused
Don't do it
You don't need to push his head down. He doesn't even have cuffs on he can
Just get in
Wait
He just aged
He's not gonna do it all traffic through little you're the driver
You seem a little confused. Yeah, i'm fine. I just want to get these folks to where they need to be
I doubt a short delay will trouble him too much
Yeah, why wouldn't that officer be like, um, what the fuck you're talking about
Yeah, I didn't uh, I didn't see this part coming. This is supposed to be like a split personality thing
Where he just like is all the characters. Can everyone just shut up?
This isn't helping us find help. Well, but this is accurate though because everybody died
So it's he was the only one left. So this is accurate. Oh, so we like talk to him in the bar
But we were just me a bus driver. Have you seen him? That's funny. Sounds like you could use a drink
Better not thanks
I did decline the drink, but what does that have to do with it?
Weren't there specific times when we were in two different places?
So how does that make any sense? Hey, so all right explosive bullets you motherfucker. You take a goddamn shot
You're in real danger. So I just was like a delusional
I don't get it. Don't leave right now
What's with all the 1600 shit my question is why does this dude live in this abandoned town?
Yeah
In a police response times took like 48 hours. Yeah, they're coming. They're coming
They're coming. Didn't he say didn't he didn't that guy vince say that they're coming to get you they're coming
Who's coming? Why wouldn't you say like the night before but if you knew that this person had, you know problems
Why would you do that? Why wouldn't you be like hey, uh, andrew like come talk to me for a minute
They're coming to get you get a different result
I think that was the ending for you actually killed
I want to believe with demons if you don't lay them there was an ending where everyone survives and it's fine
But I don't know not a very happy ending
Or maybe it is but maybe that's just one of the is okay. What makes you happy?
It's possible. That's not what really happened and you eventually
Found him the bus driver
Maybe he can now put the past behind him. Never mind. He's telling us that was real ending
Imagine if when we got a hint in the very beginning of the game. He went it's the bus driver. It's you till we meet again
Maybe in the south pacific or the arabian desert dude. This is the next two or somewhere else
But we will meet again at least one more time at least one more time. Did you hear that?
Yeah
What did we say at the beginning of the stream?
What did we say?
Um eight of these supposed to be eight of these yeah said i'll see at least one more time
He didn't say i'll see you
Six more times
I think they've got at least guaranteed budget for one more
I'll see i'll see you again guy
In october of 2021
for man of madan
The re madanading
I'm reading man of madan3 madan is back. Is this a copyright song or is this a game?
All right, here's the thing
They have a really cool idea here like it really is like you can play a co-op
The kind of choices game with another person. It's like a horror game. That's cool
I kind of feel like they get so
Far into the weeds with how the story has to be this super twisty bullshit
Like you just make a horror make it a horror game make it like scary and just horror movie
Why does it have to have this weird going into the past and into the future and then what's a twist?
This is another twist watch out. You're not you you're this guy. You might not be me
I guess they don't want uh jackass is like us to guess the ending two and a half hours in but it's like
Doesn't really matter that much if you do as long as it's a nice story
Yeah, but that's what I mean wouldn't it be more fun if?
If the the actual story was about you get to choose kind of who lives and dies and not about like here's this convoluted
twisty story
Like that itself is fun
Like having like five to ten people that you get to decide when and maybe try to save them
Do they die? Do they not die? Is the monster there?
I I guess are we led to believe
They they explained away with the hand wave
All the other characters in our timeline, but was there any closure for like the old timeline or was that also a delusion?
Uh, i'm, sorry. There's somebody like just singing loudly over you
Yeah, it's in credits
We I we can't skip can I alt tab?
Oh
Unless it's an after credits thing. There was an after credits in man of a damn
Nobody said there is an ending where you know. Well, i'm so glad we didn't get it
There is uh, there wasn't after credits in madan I think yeah
There is an ending where you do that
Can you imagine if that's how that ended?
That would be so ridiculous. I would I would have to do it
What was with the beginning scene? It was just really unlucky house fire where everybody died
Yeah, I that's what but that's what i'm saying. Like what?
You you don't have to make this
Crazy multi-layered story horror movies are scary because there's a monster that fucking kills people and it's like a popcorn movie
i've got a skip button, but
I don't know
We don't need layers on top of layers on top of layers of storytelling like just this 10 people
They all like have their own personalities and you get to do something go on go on an adventure and be careful
Some of them might fucking die get the monster at the end
well, the problem is there's like too many characters that you kind of don't care when they die because like
Let me just throw a character out there daniel. What was his personality? I don't know. It was just
I i'm I just guy that stands around and reacts
Would you say he's a react?
something
Maybe I don't we don't say that on this channel anymore though
His personality was daniel. It wasn't just a monster. It was an allegory
Yeah, I know but
I I could do without okay. So how long is this? This is about what four and a half hours?
It was absolutely like maybe an hour and 20 minutes of just kind of exposition
Well, we could have been like running away from shit and like getting killing each other and stuff
it's kind of a damned if you do damned if you don't because uh
The less talking there is the more qte's there are
That's true
Skip germa is waiting
Oh, sorry. I thought I pressed it. I thought I had control for some reason these are
We'll start believing we are under attack by
You wouldn't believe me even if I tried hell
I don't believe it and I was there
I hope we actually get to use guns in the next one. That was fun
They say the souls of the dead were deep underground. I thought that thing was like three days ago
That's bazuzu
Isn't it?
I actually fought that thing like in vr like four days ago
house of ashes
It's actually bazuzu. Oh, there you go. Achievement unlocked fate worse than death
You played the second man of the damn game
little hope
well
There was no after credits. It was just a trailer. What are the bonus features?
Designing the demons an interview with will polter
The art book fuckface run. I mean, I feel like it's gonna take a long time to do a fuckface run of this game
Uh, I feel like it's a lot of boring bits that we can't skip
Not if we don't read any of the lore and just remember because we walked forward last time I kind of
I'll do whatever you want to just see what happens. It's up to you. We already did a fuckface run
That was yeah, but we didn't do a no talking run
Yeah
I feel like there's like probably an hour worth of doing nothing before like somebody dies
Because they really back loaded a lot of that content like in the last hour or two
Well, let's try it let's let's let's try to do nothing run and just try to kill everybody as fast as possible
The real fuckface run is a lot everyone alive run
All right. Yeah, let's just say let's just try it might as well
This is the bonus portion of the stream if you're going to leave. I mean if it's really bad
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with just like stopping after it's not like it has to be finished if uh, it doesn't work out
Uh, I give me one sec. I do want to say one quick thing to my stream
I'll give you a second to talk to your stream too alone alone
All right. So if you're taking off that was uh, man of a dan 2 dark
Anthology 2 whatever it is little hope tomorrow is halloween actually 8 9 10
It actually is halloween. I think for a lot of you guys if you're in eu
Tomorrow we're doing vr. So we're going to be playing exclusively scary vr games tomorrow for halloween
For the remainder of tonight, we're just gonna do this
We're just gonna fuck around and if this is just boring then this stream just ends
So if you take it off, we'll see you tomorrow. Maybe for vr and halloween if I don't see you tomorrow then happy halloween
And pleasure and here comes the bonus content
rate the game
I don't like it. I don't think it's like a four. Uh
It's it's definitely a at least it's at least a five it is
It's not lower than a five. It's just just not great
Let's get some input here
Hey, what would you get? Do you think that ig n gave a correct score with a five out of ten for this?
um
Or do you think this is more like a 5.8 or like a six? I i'm gonna probably say like
What was man of a dan? I think okay easier question, which is better this or man of a dan man of a dan was probably better because
It just I feel like it was more fun to play man of a dan
Yeah, I think uh moment to moment. I think man of a dan somehow made even less sense than this
But then let you like I don't I don't know you were on a boat like the the yacht then you go
Diving then you like you weren't just on fog road. Yeah, three quarters of the game. Yeah, it was like different places
It was at that weird like mansion with the big dinner
rundown house number five is
Kind of too much. Yeah
And you don't do anything during the lore grab segments except
Like occasionally talk to somebody as a spirit, which I guess didn't exist
It's 5.7 5.7. I would say I mean I would say five out of ten was pretty fair
Yeah, 5.7. I think man of a dan was probably like a six and a half
But I would say man of a dan was like a 6.8 like a seven man of a dan had more like young people dialogue
But it was um
just a little bit more
Yeah, 5.7 for
Little hope 6.2 for man of a dan final answer, but it was it's still like it's fun to play
Anyway, I guess it's like it's not a five out of ten. I regret buying it five out of ten
It's like a five out of ten if I had to be like an objective game reviewer. That's true
All right. You ready? You ready to try just to do like a don't talk run
Yeah, and just sit here and watch the movie. I guess we we can do scene selection
We can skip all the bullshit. I think you know, should we just not skip the bullshit?
Should we just do from the beginning? What do you think?
You can start start from like the house, right? Yeah
Diversion family. It's just a bus crash in the very beginning, right? Yeah, I think
This whole first three scenes here
The reunion I think is where we start from or darkest dreaming because this is this is all predetermined
All right, we're gonna skip to reunion. Is that the house?
No, that's like the we got the bus crashed and now we're all standing here
Oh, yeah, because all that is I think pre like recording. I think they should have just I think what um
Would have made my opinion better if they didn't lean so hard into like
The twist like you were saying like the guy is crazy and he just imagined all those people and shot at you
like why not hone in on the
Spiritual aspect instead of I I feel like that was the same thing a man of a damn
They're scared to tell like a supernatural horror story and they want to be based in reality
It has to have some kind of explanation people saying use a controller for me to press no buttons
Um, I don't think are you sure you want me to what are you talking about? All right, you're ready. Let's uh, here we go
it's time to uh
Do nothing because I I liked the
The lore better up until the end because man of a dan was like they're breathing in the gas
And if you accidentally talk to your co-op partner once you'll figure out the entire plot
Yeah, you do if all it takes is the other person you're playing with to go
Hey, I just like attacked you. It's like oh, that's the whole story ruined. Hey taylor
Help me get andrew up on his feet. Will you I don't remember anything. Who are you?
Okay, so andrew is talking to nobody right? Okay. I'm john. You're a college professor
You're taking a bus on a field trip, but that didn't work out so well. I got a question crash wasn't on
So why is he imagining these people? What's significant? Is this his family? This is his family, right?
As a character building exercise
Come on, we can do it. What if we just don't
So since you're like player one, yeah, I don't think my character's conversation is even happening
Oh, that's right flames all around us. It was like I have a split
That trail the others are on will come out down the road
So this is his dad
But wouldn't he know wouldn't he recognize them like as his dad and his like family and shit wouldn't he recognize them
Why can't we stay here? No, we could be here all night
Our best move is to get to the others amnesia towards town. See if we can find some help
The bus driver might come back. We should wait for him. The driver's done
What we should be doing gone into town for help. This is just this person's just listening to music
Okay, wait here all night then i'll go myself
Hey, i've already missed my first qt. Yeah, I missed two in a row professor, right? I got we got pushed into it
Anyways, no matter can we stick together? I don't want to wait on my own. Yes. He's right. We should all stick together
I got no signal either must be some kind of black spot or you didn't pay your last bill
You get that during the crash. Well, this is just the same as I I missed this one the first time
It's just the same gameplay. Yeah, it is except with added silence. Yeah, it's it's the same thing except with no
Uh, no extra commentary
He thinks he's smarter than us, but book smart is no good out here
He's all up himself acting like the big man on campus
No choice run that's from that's from being the hanging marks. Yeah, I mean I don't make it
Okay, when you get all the pieces put in front of you it makes sense, but that doesn't mean it's any good
It's just kind of like oh, it doesn't it doesn't really make sense. It's kind of just like he's crazy
Roll credits now, what do we do? I just the whole bus crashing thing and then the little hope shit
It's almost like they wrote the story and then added this part like the part that it's a guy with like problems afterwards
You sure as hell took your own sweet time. He's getting worried. I bet you were so who's this this gate has changed
Is that the brother can't get through? Uh, daniel you mean? Yeah, is that the brother? It's all photo of daniel from like
1917 or something like that think that's like the navy or something ready?
I'll push hard from my side ready three two one push holding out good for rusty chain not strong enough two
One push here. Let me have a shot
When no one else can do it three two one
What
That's how it's done what but it's just him trying to do it himself
Like so is this I assume all this is real, but it's just one person, right?
Yeah, you'd have to do that by yourself already concluded this conversation
By the way, if you just open the door
Why not just what's the point of the decisions made just open the just have them do like the one two three break it
What's the point of having any of that happen?
If it doesn't it doesn't matter. I'm sorry, but we really don't have time to be arguing
You'll stay here with me won't you
Looks like he ain't so keen after all if you got something to say to me spit it out
Do we all right? I just freaked out for a second. I thought like something wrong with the game
But you do you're doing to do nothing, right?
Okay
Let's everyone take a breath. So he's a bus driver. Whatever you say. Well, what did he crash into?
Did he run over the girl?
Remember it was like the girl the girl from his because wasn't he in the house at the beginning with the girl the girl
But he has a memory of her. Yeah, the girl burns
Can we please and he has a memory of her and inserts her back into the present?
So this so little hope is is a real town. It's not like a silent hill
So why is walking is are we just walking in circles?
Is he just walking in circles and this is just a normal town. Well, that's certainly shut you up
You don't know what's between the two of us. Well, yeah, we're let's believe
There's nothing that nothing is real because he's imagining
Keep out of our business. Okay
Based on the ending is it weird for me that that's like as
Just as simple as being just like oh, by the way, the whole thing was a dream, right?
Like oh every the whole the whole game was a dream keep moving. That's what that is
It's kind of what mana madan was too though
I'm going to hang out by the bus while you all do whatever you have because we just inhaled gas
You want to come along and wait install monsters? None of it was real. Okay, and then we got shot by the uh,
Military but here's the thing this puts so many
Unnecessary expectations on the third game because now guess what you and I are going to be like, all right
What's the fucking weird like dream twist? Is that a real person?
Rather than to be able to like enjoy the story. Whatever it is. They're all real but they're just like
He's just talking to himself
They're just his his people he met in his life. This is some very weird shit going on here
Yeah, parasol first he loses his pride then he loses his way
Andrew is the only person who's real but he's actually like 70 years old. Yeah, it's not possible. It's for some
Always gonna be fun here, but we've got better. So he just he still thinks he's like a teenager
Yeah, fucking around and tell me what's going on here. Is he got like injured together?
This is getting ridiculous
Indulge me
So he's not actually going anywhere. He's just like imagining them go somewhere because andrew's not going
And then he walks around and he imagines them walking back
He's also imagining his brother and sister going out we walk dead straight going. Yeah, that's true. So
How'd we end up back here?
Okay, let's try something
We'll all go together
We came from that direction. We must be able to go back that way
I want everyone to stay real close
No stragglers. Uh
You want to put us on a kid's line?
I do like the facial the animation. It's it's like a well made
Video game, you know what I mean? Like the actual character talking
Facial animations, it doesn't look bad. I'll be honest. I know this is an unpopular opinion
I don't mind qte's in these kind of games because they're supposed to be it's supposed to be just like a
Shit show anyway, admit that is a little odd
Mostly I played watch dogs three yesterday. See and this looks like
A thousand times better on the same thing. We are trapped. We can't leave here. Okay, calm down breathe
There's a rational explanation for what's happening
Maybe we all died in the crash
Yeah, nice theory, but i'm pretty sure we're all still alive and kicking. I think it looks all right
I think this looks good schooling us on creative writing not
Metaphysics, I know who i'd like to be it's uncanny valley, but it's still you this pissy little field trip
Better than a lot of the other games I see
That is way out of line
I had no way of knowing that damn bus would crash. You can't put that on me. Are you for fucking real?
Watch your tone. Will you I am doing my best to understand this just like you and the rest of us
It's probably he's his head is hurting or something
I think the animation looks pretty good. Someone else thinks they can do a better job
Step right up at least the facial animation isn't real
I don't feel like we rushed
Can everyone just shut up
Yeah, there he goes and then he's looking around helping us find help or getting us out of here
he's right
Bitching at each other isn't gonna play the other six sequels they have planned in the future with italics
Thank you. Uh, yeah, i'll be 41
Now let's be logical
The fog is between us. I don't think that's
Realistically going to release us and town so let's head that way
I don't get how heading further away from the bus helps. There is nothing on the bus
We can use to get help
In town, there will be people a working phone something
It pains me to admit but he's right. There's nowhere else we can go except into that damn town
Sounds like a plan to me
You're leaving me. All right. So now somebody said this in chat. Come on, let's go with them
Andrew just cuz doesn't do anything. He just kind of stands around and goes. Yeah, how'd you get it? I get it now
No biggie must have got it when the bus crashed. Oh, it's from like the 17 times. I got uh smokered in the last left for dead game
They can't have the fog unless andrew goes there. Why did you say we might all be dead? Oh, wait a minute. That's true
Is that that's true? Isn't it cable show about how your brain keeps going for a while after you?
You know you die forget about it what they said didn't really stack up
I don't like the look of that place at all. So, okay, what's with the cat though?
They won't ask for id this is a lot of like red herrings and they specifically go out of the way to be like
Do you think we're all dead? No, we're not because we know these dumb players are gonna say that hey over here
And we did
He's imagining this private. This is such a great idea. I did
Cat we should check it out cat is food. There could be a phone inside
I'll go in and take a look around and the point is to be ready. Yeah, this is just a bunch of red herrings in the game
We'll be right behind you
And it's it's kind of funny that the end, you know, what are we going with the whole little hope storyline?
Is there something between you just made up in his head?
We're really going to get into it. Well, yeah because he's going he's exploring little hope
And making up the backstory for me as he reads
the museum
Lore
That's like that's ridiculous
So that's that's another layer each of these little hope buildings reading a blurb and then he gets lore grabbed
And it vents like a
Backstory for it though. He's just he's just like creative writing inside of his own head
Okay, but but he's not here. Why is this conversation happening on screen if he's not here?
I need to know 100 percent. I can rely on you that you'll never let me down
We should catch up. So i'm in the andrew group and you're in the actually not happening group. So he's simultaneously
making up multiple conversations
50 to 100 feet away from each other
Someone in chat said that john is a creative writing professor laughing my ass off. Oh, that is true
But there there are specific portions where andrew is somewhere else and there's two people walking around like a mile away
Is how is he how's he making how does he know what's going on over there? How's he making that up?
So this dude is real and exists. This is tanya's boyfriend. Oh, you know, hold on dude
Pause it pause it. This is important. Um, we need to put we need to put like a thing on the screen
That just says like oh, hey, by the way, uh spoilers for the fucking whole game
We did and we're just talking about everything that happened
It's a bit late for that. Is it late for that pretty late. Hold on. Let me just do it
Because I feel like if it's like oh, what's what's this somebody's streaming this game?
Oh, they're right at the beginning of the game. Cool. That's the guy the guy's uh, he made it all up
I'm just gonna i'm just gonna put it on quick. Okay, let's go. Wait. What is this? How do I have four x files here?
All right, all right. You ready? There we go. Yep. Did you just put fuckface run again?
No, I said second playthrough spoiler talk
Oh my god, the title of my stream is that stupid little in-joke with like 10 people in pre-stream. Whatever
I mean, let's be fair
The game the game did come out today. All right, i'm good
It didn't release like six hours ago
So, I mean come on if you planned on playing this but I and you just open the stream
And the stream opens you get your fucking tostitos pizza roll ad and then all of a sudden it's like oh tostitos pizza rolls
Heat them up. And he made the whole thing up in his head. Yeah. Yeah, everyone's andrew
He made everything up. Don't you think you'd be like well fucking great. Thanks. Save me 30 bucks. No, that's true
All right, you ready? I can spend that 30 bucks on pizza rolls. How much is a bag of pizza rolls like 10 bucks 8 bucks?
Depends on the size of the bag. Hi there. How you doing?
These developers only cash flow is you and italics. Excuse me
But we're that's not even true. This is like a really this is a popular franchise people are buying this will it please
Come on. That's funny. What is
Okay
Uh that guy could have just solved the whole game
Yeah, he could have just elaborated. Yeah, show us a thick one tonight. So thick it's stopping us from leaving
Yeah, yeah, I know that feeling like right now he's just kind of egging us on maybe find a phone or something
Yeah, all right. Hold on, but don't come look at this
Come on. How about a game who's playing the darts?
Seriously, you want to throw darts? Oh, you're not listening to the oh hang on. Hang on. Hang on. Hang on. Hang on pause
But we got to start over like from this chapter
Because the last time we did manamadan, uh, if you're player one or player two you get to see the other
You're you're just gonna literally see the whole shit. You just saw for the entire game go the same
Like we flipped remember? Oh
Uh
You can restart it from this same chapter though. Okay. Yeah. All right
So you have to then you have to uh host the game. Oh, no, no, wait
It's like a wiimote thing. We're at that menu. We have to press
All right, let's let's swap. Let's go. Is it a wiimote thing?
Where like whoever presses the button first gets first player don't play alone
So do you have to invite me? Do we know that? Yeah, okay. Yeah, listen
Oh, you are invited
I got an invite
Oh cool
Okay, never mind. Uh, they made it worse. You actually I can't I
According to the devs. I have not ever played this game before my other news story or scene selection. Oh
All right, well, it's okay
Let's see if we can wiimote it
Okay
I'm gonna so I guess beware if you end up playing this game with a friend and then try and play it
Without them. Yeah, if you for some reason
Well, it is
I would have lost all progress like if we were halfway through and we stopped and then never played it again for some reason
We are doing shared story though. Maybe that's the reason why because you're sharing it with me, but I also bought it
Yeah, couldn't one person buy this game and then like steam
Link to someone else. Yeah, you can you can do remote play with this game. So why did we both buy it?
Because it's better than dealing with like
500 millisecond lag probably oh you can't
Oh, wait, wait, wait, hold on. Maybe you can't the thing pops up
When I when anytime you open the game don't you get the thing where it says remote play together
I get that in the corner. It's only for split screen. No, why would it pop up when I open this game?
That doesn't happen on every game. I open. Oh, here we go. All right, so if you what if you hit click first
I I don't think it matters, but i'll click because i'm just player two. Well game does have local co-op. Yeah, I think there's a
Yeah, there's a pass the controller. Yeah, so I guess you can do the you can do it that way
How did you pass the controller in mana madame?
I'm, not sure that passed the control was in mana madame. I think it was just shared story or solo. Maybe it was
Next game. No, this is it
Sorry, my leg bumped rb. Hey quit bumping. Oh, are we are we in hell?
Is the game trying to tell us something is this is this where is this where we pull the plug?
This might be a pull the plug
Can you do it? No
Time to rip pull plug
It's probably better that way because if we can't even swap we're just gonna see 100
The same thing anyways, unless we started a new game. Yeah, it was fun. It was but look
It's always enjoyable to play like a funny crazy scary game with friend. It just is
No, I mean, I I enjoyed the experience. I just wish it was better
True, but yeah, um
That's it
Uh
I
Thanks for playing taleks. It's always a pleasure. See you next year when we do the next one. Oh
Will there be a 2021? It's it's got a sequel. Yeah, that's gonna come out. Yeah, that's uh, it has to uh, that's taleks
Somebody one of the mods want to just span his uh channel, please
span it span, uh, and that was fun. Thank you everyone for uh for
Watching this shit. I I liked it and I didn't like it at the same time
Yeah, it's kind of it's in a weird spot, but I still am glad I enjoyed the experience
All right, just frozen screen on the last cutscene still
It was we had fun for five hours that that's that's a five hour
Experience the game was really four hours. We just kind of like that's why why was it only four who who else is playing this game?
That is taking six hours to beat you must just be looking at every single piece of material
all right, I gotta I gotta watch this quick video and then uh, i'm gonna end the stream but
Uh taleks good night. Thanks for playing. See you again next time
uh
Sorry everyone that um, you had to watch loser pov on derma's channel as he killed every single cow
I'm just kidding. It was fun
All right, take it easy, man. Bye. All right. Um, this is a spoiler for one of the endings, but holy shit
You weren't kidding. This is actually this is actually an ending. I can't fucking believe it. Are you shitting me?
Thank god. This didn't happen. Let's watch it by the way me watching
It does not mean a fluke diving accident the day before my high school graduation left me completely paralyzed
But a stem cell treatment helped me move my arms again. Why is this 12 minutes?
I thought this is supposed to be the ending why am I getting so many what's the five nights at freddy's among us ad
That was just every meme in a banner. Okay. Let me let me let me quit out of this
Uh, all right, let me get this bigger. So this is what could have happened. This is one of the endings by the way
Okay, here we go. Let's watch it get it out. Get it out of 144p. All right. I will all right. Let's see
Watching this does not mean I did it. It just we're watching what could have happened. I can't fucking believe it
I can't believe it. No way
I really dodged a bullet here. No way
Holy shit. I can't believe I was had to give a thousand subs
I can't fucking believe it
So what could have what could have gone differently with that would have happened if you didn't shoot the gun
Holy fucking shit. I almost didn't I almost didn't fire the gun. You don't shoot at vince then there's no cops
Thank god. I shot the gun
Here's the fucking best part about this
A bunch of you guys knew that was possible and were absolutely trying to push me towards the decisions that made it possible
Is that why when that came up everyone was like don't shoot him. Don't shoot. Don't shoot. Don't shoot
And the trial makes a difference too. That's ridiculous
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow for halloween vr. We're gonna start with the walking dead
game play that for a little while and move on to
You know it, you know, it's coming five nights at freddy's vr have to do it on
Have to do it on halloween and then maybe a couple other things too. It's halloween in four minutes for uh, yeah
Eastern time right happy halloween. We see you tomorrow. We see you tomorrow if we don't have a good halloween
Take care of yourself. Did you buy saints and sinners? Uh, I can tell you right now exactly what I bought
I have
Uh, let's see. It's whatever the I think I just bought the vr one
Is that due is it more than one version?
Uh, it says saints and sinners walking dead saints and sinners. That's the right one, right?
Uh raid vinny. Yeah, okay. Let's raid vinny. Sure. Sure. Sure. Sure. Let's go. I'll see you guys tomorrow
Good night. Thanks for watching
It's always fun to play with italics. We're probably gonna play some more stuff, too
We've talked about um playing one of the splinter cells together if we can get it to run
So it's a pleasure to have italics around
My throat is like annoying. I think I laughed way too hard
So it's just like hey, i'll see you guys later. Go say hello to vinny. Good night. Goodbye. Take care
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No. Oh shit the credits. They're fucking I forgot about the credits. It's gonna raid
It's gonna raid in 10 seconds. Oh shit. Okay. Uh, thanks. No, seriously. Thanks everybody for the subway
What about the money sort of this somebody gave money? Hold on. Let me do this quick
Go go go go go go go go go go come on
I have like 30 seconds to do this hurry
Okay, here it comes. Thank you everybody for supporting the stream all the subs all the gifted subs all the resubs you guys
Thank you. Seriously, it's going you know, it's gonna miss out
We're gonna miss everybody past g read the missed bits i'm i'm logging in right now. I I don't know why I was logged out
All right. Here we go. We had
Retro specter gave a shitload of subs chef's corner gave a shitload of subs
Look at me. Wait, this is from two months ago. Why is this happening? This is not recent. This is from two months ago
Thank you for the money. Thanks for the money