Fire ants everywhere. I'm going to die from fire ants. Where is the stupid treasure?
Wait, wait, wait. What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? Something, something,
something, something, something. God damn it.
Ah, fucking idiot. Six hours. What is that? Nothing. Well maybe, maybe you shouldn't have
lost the map. That would have been really smart. Blew out of my fucking hands. Wild dogs and
shit. What's that? I got something, got something. Wait, wait. Hold on. Is it? I always knew.
I always knew. Sometimes you just have to double check. What is that? That's the skull.
That's the skull. Hey, I found the skull. That's the skull that was on the map. That's
all I remember. That's the last thing I remember. Holy shit. Come on. Come on. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. Something in here. Something in there. Something in there. Oh shit. What is this?
This goes pretty deep. This goes pretty deep. What on earth is this? What the fuck is that?
What the fuck is this? This is huge. What is this? You guys see this? It's a very large
rock in here. By the way, have you guys had water in like a couple hours? You have? Alright,
we'll share it. There we are. God, this is really in there. Whatever it is. Holy shit.
I can't get it out. It's huge. Get out of here. Come on. Whoa. Don't want to lose the
hat. I didn't even say hello. How are you? Fucking in here is so bad. I'm going to tire
myself out. This is definitely not a treasure. Come on. Get it open. Come on. There it is.
Oh shit. I think I broke the shovel. Come on. This was in the ground. This is really,
really heavy. That could be from an ancient civilization. Is that it? It can't be. Hold
on a second. It's supposed to be cool, but it wasn't. What about over here? Sometimes
you need a little bit of intuition. What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that?
What's that? What's that? Promise, I'm older than 12. Something else in here. What's that?
There's more of this shit. Can you see this? Look it. Mom. Oh, you're not mom. Look at
the ground. What the heck are these? There's more. Hold on. There's more in there. There
are bees. Okay. All comedy aside, there are bees like swarming. This is how it ends. They're
like right in the eyes. Good thing I have glasses on. There's shit in the ground. Wait,
hold on a minute. Take these glasses to the front of my face. I could have sworn I got
a signal somewhere. Maybe in this vicinity here. I feel like Johnny is opening up. I
just got out of the hospital. My surgical gown. This is so tiring. You have no idea.
What else is in here? What is this? I don't think this is a rock. Is it a rock? It's probably
from the fucking Mayan times. What is it? Holy shoot. More rocks. I don't know if I
can do any more with the shovel. This is fucking tiring. That's a huge one. It's too tiring.
Give me one second. I'll be right back. I have to get something bigger than that. I got
something bigger than a shovel. Get in here. What's up with the big guns? It's in this
area here. I'm going to find that goddamn treasure and I'll be the first one. Sometimes
all it takes is my nice dig there right up. Why would I have even used the shovel for
any reason? Something right in there. Something in there. There's something in there. I don't
want to go backwards. Don't go that way. Something in there. Something in there. You see that?
That was a shit load of rocks. This place has got all these rocks. Should I do a wheelie?
Should I do a wheelie? Let's go. I can't believe. You know how to use that but you don't think
I can know everything? You don't think I know how to use one of these? I worked for 10 years
in the industry. Give me a break. I think there's something in here. There we go. Get
in there. That felt pretty good. That felt pretty good. Felt pretty good. Give me a hand.
Only if you're a trained professional like I am. Right here. Right here. There are bees.
There are bees and they're very angry. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good. It's like
the world's shittiest Disney ride. I paid to rent one of these to just have a personal
shitty Disney ride. There's something. I feel something solid. Something solid right on
over here. Shit. There's something solid right here. What is over there? I can't go down.
There's something in there. Something in there. Hold on. What is here? Oh shit. Red. I almost
got solid. Solid. Solid. No. What the? Do you see this? Do you see this? Do you see
that? I knew I fucking felt something. Hold on. Holy shit. It's a chest. Oh fuck. Broke
it and ripped off. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. You gotta be kidding me. This
must be what was on the map. It's gonna be filled with fucking dirt. Oh my god. Oh,
don't. There could be valuables in here. Come on. Oh. Wow. What's up? This is the
trap. One of those things that has stuff in it. This is just a full on actual treasure
chest. I got rocks. Do we? I or a scientist or something. Some kind of a scientist. You
can? Get somebody down here. There's a lot. There's some in here too. Give us one second.
I want to get this stuff ready to go. Can you get a guy? We'll be right back. Let's
get this stuff ready. I want to see what's in here. Well, well, well, well. Got everything
situated. Got my glasses off so I can take a look inside and see what's in here. I don't
know what's gonna be in here, but I'm very curious. Let's find out. It's just like a
Legend of Zelda. It should be like. Oh my god. There's a lot of shit in here. What is
in here? Okay, there's a letter. This looks like a letter. What does it say? Yeah, buddy.
You're a loving family. If you're reading this right now, I'm probably dead. Or you
stole it from me, in which case I want it back. But give it back if you took it, but
if I'm dead then you can keep it. But anyways, if you find this letter, you found my treasure
chest, you found all of my goodies that I've been keeping for the last 30 to 40 years.
There's some valuable stuff in here, and whoever found this, congratulations, you just went
up a whole tank of records. Absolutely no love to any of you. It's in my truest heart
of hearts that I really hope that at least some of you die trying to get this. I mean,
killing each other. I really hope that 10 of you fucking got here and had chainsaw and
firearms and are killing each other over this. And if I had to make any bets at all, it would
be Danny. I bet you Danny's the one holding this treasure chest right now. And if I'm
dead, who cares, I'm dead. So all in all, have a wonderful rest of your life with your new
found fortune, Grandpa. What a fucking maniac. Well, it wasn't Danny. What happened to him?
Anyways, interesting, Grandpa. I guess, thank you, we found it. Now what's in here though?
I saw some, I got a good look, let's see. Looks like we have various snack items. Dunkaroos.
There's like a time capsule. Capri Suns Kinder Joys. 3D Doritos. Oh, Gushers. Grandpa, I mean,
this would have been in the 90s, maybe this would have been alright, this would have been
cool, maybe you thought. But a bunch of people complained on Twitter, and all this shit came
back. Like, I think this is, can't you just buy this? Can't you buy Surge? And why would
you put this many Capri Suns in here? Like, did you just have too many? This is fucking
horrible. What is even in here? What is this? This is a Tamagotchi. Is it alive? Is this
alive? Can you see? Is it alive? I think it's still alive. Should I feed him? What do you
think? Oh, there's shit everywhere. He's covering his own shit. How do I feed him? I haven't
used one of these in a long time. 1.18 p.m. 1952? Didn't these come out in like 1996?
What are, whatever. I don't know what these are, but whatever. Wait a minute. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. My God. Grandpa, you did it. All the stupid 90s snacks, nobody gives
a shit about those. You can get those at the grocery store right now. Collectible Monster
card packs from 1997. If this is Pokemon. Oh, now I understand what he was doing. Oh,
my, get all the 3D Doritos. They came back and they don't even taste the same. All this
shit doesn't even taste the same. I have heard that Pokemon cards go for a shitload of money.
I've seen people open, if that's what's in there, that has to be what's in there. 1997.
That's a booster pack in there. Oh, my God. Why don't you come over and get a look at
this? Are you ready for the great fucking reveal? Collectible Monster card packs, holy
shit. Pokemon cards. What is this? What is Grotto Beasts? What is Grotto Beasts? Oh,
my fucking God. You picked? This shit didn't even go for like one full season on TV. In
fact, I think this company is liquidated. 1997. Yeah, they're jumping on the bandwagon
of Pokemon. Booster pack opening. Let's see what's in here because of Grotto Beasts. No
Charizard in here? Well, let's see what's in. Let's see what we got. Holy shit. Actually,
this is pretty good packaging. Wow. That's what's in here? Pretty cool. All right. Well,
let's get it open. Oh, that felt pretty nice. Fucking Grotto Beasts. Easy. Easy. Careful.
Careful. Careful. Don't handle these with care. Porcelain. That's, I mean, that's kind
of cool, I guess. Sweet Tooth. Sludge. Whoa. We got a Sludge. We got a Sludge. Does that
matter? Does this matter at all? Weenie Mutt. Should I be touching these? Should I not be
touching these? A Veggie Roo. Oh, that's actually kind of cool looking. These are actually fucking
cool. These are really cool. Razzle Puss. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait,
wait a minute. Look at this one. Look at this one. This one, this is, cut to my face. Quick,
quick, quick, quick, cut to my face. A Foil Razzle Puss. Oh my God. It's a Foil Razzle
Puss. Do you see that? Oh, this has got to be worth, that has to be, yeah. But it's not
worth, is it? What, we got Sir Grieves. Should I put that in something? These are fucking
cool. A Biogator. Eight Attack. Holy crap. That's, oh wait, sweet, whoa, whoa, this Sweet
Tooth has got a two. Look it. That's a, that's a Foil Sweet Tooth. Oh shit. No, it's flying
off the table. These aren't worth money. These might be worth money. That's going to get
lost in the fucking. Wait, where'd it go? You think I'm going to lose the Razzle Puss
that you're out of your mind? That's what the bag is for? Oh. Hold on, what else we
got? This, these are pretty actually kind of cool. Grotto Beasts. Who would have thought
that? I'm going to be more careful, hold on. Excellent packaging, I love this. Whoa. Oh
shit. That's a Bottled Knight? Bottled Nightmare. That looks kind of cool. A Meody. Sweet, oh
another Sweet Tooth, must be a common. Oh, that must be a common. Zapbit? Right now a
bunch of people just said, don't touch him. It's fine, it's all right. It's just fucking
Grotto Beasts. What do you care? Peep, I like Peep Peep. Peep Peep's really cool.
What's the damage? Heals all allies one HP at the beginning of each turn. Is that good?
An Ante-Bite. Swipe attack up to three, is this, this is actually pretty, this is kind
of cool. Oh god damn it. That, whoa whoa whoa, foil, foil, foil, foil alert, foil alert.
That's a foil bag ghost. You gotta be kidding me. Wow, this is really cool. Hey, um, this
company, this company doesn't exist anymore, right? You can look into it. I remember there
was one season on TV show, right? Something like that. Could you find out how much this
company's worth? If it even, if it even is still like for sale or anything. You get back
to me with the price, I'm curious. Dust Bunny? You see Dust Bunny? There you are. I love Dust
Bunny. Okay, okay, okay, all right, all right. This is a holographic sludge. I don't, okay,
I don't, should I not, don't touch it, just leave it here. I'm not gonna touch that. That
is my favorite character already. I don't even know what it is, but I love it. That's
a holographic foil sludge. Can you, can you get me something where I can actually put
this down on? Yeah, sure. Give me like a, give me the thing that they put them in. Like
a napkin. Do you have any napkins? I shouldn't be touching this like this. I should have
my gloves on. A napkin. Like a white napkin? A napkin, any napkin, any, hurry the fuck
up. God damn it. I gotta, I gotta seal it, man. I, I, you can't, I don't want to touch
it like that because then it's protected. I don't, it might be worth them. I don't know.
Who knows? I'm gonna put this back in the worthless chest of nothing. Shit. These are
like going in the dirt. People are probably having a panic attack right now. They're going
in the sand. I keep forgetting to put them down. Did I lose the holographic sludge? Did
I lose the holographic sludge? I don't see it here. Is it in the box? No. Where'd it
go? It actually blew away. I have to, I have to find that. It's not in my hand, right?
No. Somebody actually go look for that. Like I'm serious. Yeah, okay. Because I like actually
want that one. Like that's not like a part of like this joke or anything. I like want
that card. What do I look for? Is it, is it not even here? Did it go over, alright, well,
well that's okay. Well let's open another couple, let's open some more of them. We got
another pack of Grotto Beasts. I've seen people do this. This is big, big content. You got
it? It's not, this is, it's literally, oh it's, it's ours Charlie. It's ours Charlie.
I got a golden, knock this shit over. I, no wait, I put it in here. I put it in the box.
I put it in the box. I put it in the box. What are you guys saying? Zilly Wonka? It's
in the chest. It's in the chest. You're a dumbass. Whatever. We're going to keep going.
Put this in here. Put it over here. Here we are. You all, that's already a festive mimic
with a gold foil on it and I don't even know what that means. Oh my god. They keep, no!
Am I going to have to get a drill out here and start like pinning this stuff down? No,
don't ever open up the card packs on a windy day. This is what you all wanted to see. This
is what you wanted to see. This is what you wanted. Festive mimic. I'm going to hold onto
that one. Here's the thing about doing this. What else can I possibly say about what I'm
doing right now? You know what I mean? What else can I even possibly say? We found a company.
We can buy it. How much is it worth? Like $350,000. It's $350,000 for the... It's GrottoBeast.com
is what we found. GrottoBeast.net? .com. GrottoBeast.com. How much is it? $350,000. For the whole
IP. All of it. That's all the assets. Everything. Yeah, buy it. Buy it. Buy it right now. You
got access to my checking account. Get it. Yeah, buy it. Yeah, no, this is cool. This
is cool. I'll own it. Blademos. Holy shit. That's a lizard wizard? This one's got really
good speed. All right, let's do this the right way. Oh, wow. Toadstool. Wow. Birthday basher.
Wow. Optimal. This one's pretty cool. Look at this one. Optimal illusion. What's he got?
1-2-0-0 illusions with taunt. Grand finale. After reaching below 2HP, Optimal illusion
puts on a grand display, stunning all enemies for one round. I like this. This is fucking
cool. Did you get it? Did you buy it? You got it. It was that easy? Well, I mean, I
left a voicemail. All right, buy it. You're probably the only person that left a voicemail
at that company's voicemail in the last like 25 years, so that's fine. At least the number
was still connected. That's cool. All right, good. You say GrottoBeast.com? Yeah. All
right. Baroot. Baroot's cool. Jukeboxer. Oh, this is the... I love Jukeboxer. This is awesome.
And look at this one. Look, I love the festive mimic. That's unbelievable. How many more
packs do I have? Oh, dude, this is the rest of the damn stream. I don't care. And we got
a shitload. Hey, did you get ahold of a scientist? You got somebody, right? Okay. Because we
have... This rocks that I've never seen before. So I definitely don't want to see what the
deal is with those. This is now a card pack opening stream. Let's see what we got here.
Ooh, that's a bobbin. This is a common bobbin. That's a general festive mimic. I'm starting
to understand their names. That's a general porcelain. We saw that already. We saw that
with these. These are some repeats. Toy Rex. We're waiting for the foil. Toy Rex? Sneezy.
Sneezy sneezes. There's a booger on that one. There's a piece of food on that one. Oh! A
chroma nova! Oh, what the... No! No! No! No! No! Relax. What's it got for attack? Well,
this... Well, actually, holy shit. 877... 8779? Magic? This is the strongest card we've found
so far, and it's gold foil. All right, put that one in the clock. Because that one's
probably worth something. That's probably worth something, right? We got a common meowedy?
Oh, there's more. There's more. A storm flatty? Wow! Wow! Lick my... I'm gonna... And then
I'm gonna touch it, and I'm gonna touch my hand. I just heard eww. Somebody said eww.
That was pretty disgusting. All right, I think we got through these. All right, we got three
more packs of Grotto Beasts. Three more. Don't get too excited. So, I can't... Let me see
the chat for a sec. What does it say? He looks like he has a sunburn. Do I? Do I have a sunburn?
A little? What happened to his big stomach? He better not say anything fucked up. I got
a blaster. It's beautiful out here. Yeah, come on. We're just having a relaxing day when
we open up card packs. Oh, we got another Sneezy. That's another Sneezy. And another
bag ghost. Razzlepuss? That's a bee. Don't move. Get away from me. Is he gone? Ah, shoot!
No, I'm just kidding. Oh, a Razzlepuss. That's a holographic peep peep. We're gonna have
to really run around and collect all these things. Invasive Waves Strider. Holy shit,
that's awesome. Puddle Puppy. Another Biogator. A Weenie Mutt. Another Dust Bunny. A Toadstool.
That pack was alright. That pack was alright. Did somebody say next game? Yeah, let me
load up Yakuza. In the middle of the damn desert, man. What are you talking about? Next game.
I'm like, I'm... let me go to my computer. Oh, Yakuza Pog. He said Yakuza. Do you want
to say what? Do you want to say what? Hey, do you want to say what? GrotterBeast.com.
Do you want to say what? Ooh, ooh, let's see the pack. Oh shit, Glow Angel. Night Mite.
I'm waiting for a Gold Foil. Hi, Liar. Very cool. Zapbit. Here we go, here we go. This
is a holographic Zapbit. That looks so cool. I love this. Hylin Destroyer. Hypno Days.
Put an enemy to sleep for three rounds. That sounds pretty fucking awesome. XBlosion. That's
awesome. XBlosion. And then a... ooh. Hold on. That was... well, this is cool. How do
people do this? I'm asking honestly. I have to ask very honest questions. Do people open
like a hundred of these? I ran out of stuff to say like 15 minutes ago. All right, let's
go back. Glow Angel. Night Mite. Hi, Liar. I like the Zapbit though. Look at that shit.
Look at how awesome that is. Now that is a quality card. And I will be putting my fingerprints
all over it. Any more? We got two more packs and that's it. I just realized what I was
doing with my mouth. This is awesome. Grotto Beasts. And now I own this. I own it. It's
mine. I can do whatever I want with this now. Hmm. I wonder what that means. I wonder what
he's talking about. Let's get that open. What was it? Oh, we... People want to invest. You
want to invest? I have a chat over here. I have to walk. I would die for Proto Jammer.
Grotto Beasts Tournament incoming. God damn. We're going to clean all this up. They're
not going far. They're just going like right here. We've got to get the cleanup crew out
here after this. Ow. A slug. I feel like I'm like torturing people. Birthday Basher. Hi
Liar. Meowdy. These are all... I think we've got to repeat. Don't be seeing these around.
This is cool though. Veggie Roo. Peep Peep. Sludge. Holographic Optimal Illusion though.
That's really valuable. That's worth something. Last one. Damn it. There's one more here.
Dumpy. Stop littering. I'm going and picking it up. That's all that's over there. You don't
see over here. I'm putting all the... They're all going in here. Don't worry. I'm a litterer.
Fuck that. I ain't got a litter. Don't do that shit. Pick up after yourself. Oh, Crab
Jaw. This is the last pack. Dragosum. An Antibite. Oh, Proto Jammer. Somebody said that they
would die for this guy. I don't know who you are, but it's pretty cool. It's a really cool
card. Holographic Storm Platy. A Dragosum. A Toy Rex. And a Holographic Sir Grieves.
Excellent. All right. Coming up next. That's all of the card packs. Thank you, Grandpa,
for your worthless chest. But still, that was kind of a cool... That's a cool thing.
I don't own that company. There's other... I don't know. Whatever. We got a bunch of
rock. Did you see these? Look up here. These came out of the ground. I really... Do we
have... Do we have any ETA on the scientists? Yeah, just like two or three minutes. A few
minutes? There could be stuff inside of these. I have no idea. Why don't we break them open?
Sound like a good idea? You want to crush them? Yeah. All right. Let's get that set up. Let's
crush a bunch of geodes. Get a scientist. We'll be right back. After this short... Just
cut it before I look like an idiot. So, hello there. Welcome back. As you see, we have our
beautiful geodes on the table. And I'm joined by Josh from ScienceCenterNevada.org. Josh,
good to see you. Pleasure. By the way, I want to make this really clear. Not an actor. That
this is not like an actor. This is a scientist. This is a real scientist from ScienceCenterNevada.org.
So, first and important, very important. I want to make this really clear. Everybody
on site here has been tested for COVID within the last 24 hours. All negative. Very important.
That's why we're still trying to be a little socially distant and everything. But everyone
on site here has been tested for COVID negative in the last 24 hours. Very important. So,
I guess as a archaeologist, you could probably give us... Well, wait, wait, wait. This isn't
archaeology. It's not? No, we're dealing with rocks. Oh, okay. Archaeology people stuff.
Rock stuff, that's geology. So, this is not archaeology? Not at all. The title of the
stream is The Wonders of Archaeology and we have t-shirts that are being printed that
are archaeology t-shirts. You might have to cancel those and thanks a lot for that. Not
archaeology. All right. That's a common misconception, right? Yeah, I would say so. So, we're going
to break these open. Welcome to the stream. I hope you enjoyed the intros. So, each one
of these hopefully has something interesting in the middle. Let's find out. And over here,
we got one here, over here. Let's get our safety protection eye gear. Over here we have
a device. Now, this device is designed to open these. I think its original purpose is
to cut pipes. I think so, yeah. Oh, an understanding. So, how this works, we're going to be very
careful. We've been trained, sort of, in how to use it. So, we're going to try to open
as much of these as we can and see what we get. Eye protection gear, safety is number
one important. Let's get it open and see if we can get one to work. We have tested it
and we got it to work, but let's, live TV, right? Let's see what we can get. So, the
idea is you put the rock right in the middle and you wrap the chain around so it's taught
right down the middle. It looks like it's down the middle, right? Yep. And if we can
go like this, get it in there like that. So now, let's see if we can get this to break.
Are we ready to try our first rock? Are we good? Let's see what happens. Here we go.
It's time to break the first rock. Did I got it? Let me check it. I think we got it. We
got it. Oh, my God. That looks awesome. So, what is going on in here? So, what we have
here is a geode. And so, if you get up close there, in the space and inside the hollow,
those are quartz crystals. And so, each of these are individual quartz crystals growing
in there. Oh, my God. Can I see one of the half of these? I want to get this onto the
other camera. So, this is quartz. Quartz, yes. Can we see under here? Under this little
guy here? So, this isn't as hollow as some of them. Is there a reason why they're not
as hollow? Each one of them forms as an air bubble in a lava flow. And so, depending on
how much time there's been for water to pass through these voids, the minerals get bigger
and bigger and fill in the hole. Oh, all right. This one looks like it's a bit of a tapping.
And I know, I've seen the comments that I'm just like a little terrible version of him.
Look at me. This is the real deal here, okay? So, it worked. It worked. We were terrified
that it wasn't going to work. So, which one should we do next? What do you think? Let's
pick a random one. Just pick a random one? All right. Let's go for it. Let's do it again.
Let's get the chain up. We need to lift her up. So, this one's a little bigger. Let's
see how this one is. Like right there, maybe? Yeah, here we go. Get it right in the middle.
All right. That looks good. All right. You ready? This one's a little bigger. Here we go.
This one's done. Come on. Got it. Oh, that's awesome. Oh, whoa. Holy. So, those are really
clear quartz crystals, which tells us that that's a really pure mineral. So, that's why
you're getting kind of that glassy appearance of them. That looks incredible. Let's carefully
get this out of here. Oh, wow. That looks like the inside of a cave. This looks like a cave.
It's kind of like a mini cave, yeah. You're going to here? That one looks really,
didn't you see that one? This one looks awesome. There's like caverns in this one.
You get a good view? Look at those crystals. I have no idea what's going to happen with one
of these huge ones. This is really pretty. It's awesome. Quartz is actually one of the most common
minerals on the planet. So, these are some really pretty examples of them. All right. Let's grab
this guy here. This one. Something's rattling around him. Can you hear that? Can you pick that
up? Okay. What is in here? There's only one way to find out. That's right. Want to give me a hand
and hold this up for me? Thank you. There's something shaking around in here. What if there's
a bunch of snakes just came up? Maybe one more? Right there. Almost got it. Let's see if that
does it. It's right in the middle, right? Looks good. All right. You ready to go? Here we go.
Three, two, one. Get it. What? That's a good bowl. Cool. Oh, my God. So, why is this one like that?
So, the small minerals are in there because this one just hasn't had as much exposure to groundwater
to build the big minerals. And another interesting thing about this one is that this isn't just pure
quartz this time. I don't know how easy it is to see where you're at, but they're actually kind
of purplish. Yeah. And so, this is a variety of quartz called amethyst. Oh, this is amethyst. All
right. Cool. That's awesome. So, quartz is amethyst? Yep. Amethyst is a variety of quartz. It has a
little bit of iron in it. You just learned something right here. Let's get a good look.
This looks like almost like an ashtray. That's what it looks like. Like somebody just like
flicking cigarettes in here. That one was, this one's awesome. I love this one. Cool. Yeah.
All right. Should we do, let's do a couple. I'm trying to hold. This is like the ultimate stalling.
Wait, what are these over here? What are those? What do you mean? If you take a look at these
over here. No, what is it? You can just have it. I don't, I don't care. I don't know what it is.
All right. I don't know what it is. You can just have it. Let's do this one. Yeah. Is this some
rocks you can just take? I don't care. Thank you. Yeah. No problem. Let's get this one. This one
has like outside colors. Is there a reason why this one has like, like purple? Because these
are lava flows. There's probably a microscopic mineral in there called orthoclase. Orthoclase.
Sounds like a prescription drug. You're talking comedy and education. Let's get it in there.
This is what happens when you bring scientists on set.
No, this is awesome. You didn't think you were going to learn anything today.
It's a weekend. They think you're going to learn anything on the weekend. You want,
you, would you want to do the honors? Okay. All right, cool. All right, here we go. Ready?
Maybe one more. One more rung. It's not getting the tautness up here.
There. So maybe stick it in here. There we go. That should do it. Get in there. Get in there.
Get it. You get it. It's an awkward shape. All right, here we go. Ready? Let's see what's in the
purple lava rock. There it is. Carefully lift it out. Did it get it? Yep. What's that? Oh, wow.
So this one's like, this is black in there? Yeah, so that's a lot of the original lava rock.
So there's a couple different types of lavas in here. There's the pink stuff, which is called
rhyolite, and then there's the blackish stuff, which is more just a typical lava rock you'd
have in a barbecue or something. Then instead of quartz, this time we have, it looks like calcite
blades. Yeah, these are like flakes. Looks like salt flakes. Hey, Chad, do you guys want to get
a closer look? Do you guys want to get a closer look? I can barely even see that. Yeah, it looks
like salt. Like salt flakes. This is so cool. So it's a different type of water that's going
through this one versus the ones that we already opened up. Oh, okay. So when you mean different
types of water, do you mean like with different minerals in the water? Exactly. So different
dissolved minerals as the water's coming through. That's so cool. Science. Support your local
science projects and your local science organizations. Come on, look at this. How about
let's do, how about this? We'll do another big one. This one is meaty and this one's heavy too,
and you mentioned that the heavier the rock, it's kind of the more that could be inside of it,
right? More minerals that have grown in it, yeah. I'm like so excited. There's still so many to do
I love this. Let's go right down the middle here. Get it on there. That looks pretty good.
All right, you ready? Three, two, one. Oh, this one's tough.
There you go. All right. So this one is pretty pure quartz, but it does have a little purplish
tint to it. Yeah, this one. Yeah, this would be more amethyst, right? Yeah. This one looks
almost like the one, the really hollow one. Probably from the same family. Same place,
probably, yeah. Probably from the same exact mine, right? Because they pull these out of a mine.
Yep. Cool. I don't think that's, what? What? What are you, you're not supposed to eat rocks.
Why not? I do it all the time. All right. What about, this one's bumpy. This one's bumpy.
We'll try this one. I'll try. I'll save that one for later.
Really bumpy. This one's got bumps. So is there a reason why this is bumpy on the outside?
It's just a reflection of how they probably mined it out of the lava flow. Cool. I'm at,
that's, let me get it in the center. All right, ready? Three, two, one. Let's go.
Yeah. Whoa. That's a pretty one. That's a really pretty one. It's kind of wedged in there.
Wow. That looks unbelievable. So I think what we're looking at here is quartz again,
but because it's kind of that grayish color, that's a variety called smoky quartz.
What causes the smoky color in the quartz, the grayish color, is aluminum rather than the
iron that's in the amethyst. This one looks awesome. It almost looks like, it's dark too.
So you said quartz is the most common mineral in the world? On the surface of the planet. Yep.
Well, it sure does look pretty darn pretty. Let's do, let's do this one. Okay. Get it in there.
This one's big. All right, let's go for this. This one, why does this one look weird? Why does
this one look so interesting? I don't know. This is unlike the other ones we've seen. It's really
smooth. This one's really smooth. It's covered, it's got a lot of dirt on it. I've never seen
one like that before. Yeah, I know. This is really interesting. You ready? One, two, three.
What's in there? I'm not sure. Oh my God. It's Minecraft diamonds.
Wow. I can't believe it. It's even in a very cool packaging. It's even inside of a little bubble.
But that must be, that must be an air bubble. I'm going to defer to you on this one.
The water must have flowed over the air and created an air bubble inside of this rocket,
diamond rock. Wow. You see it? Get a closer look. Actually, this is really cool. It's like a claw.
Well, that's, that's a new one for me. You've never seen a Minecraft diamond?
No, that's first. You can get a good look. There it is. Preserved forever. Okay. Very cool.
All right. What about this? This guy is already like kind of, he's kind of already got a little.
It's begging for it. Yeah. It's ready. You're going to get a look at that. This one is like
already down the middle. So that's what we're going to do it. I can't believe we found Minecraft
diamonds. I can't either. Let's get it in there. All right. And on the count of three, I want you
to say one, two, three science. One, two, three. Guys are fucking clowns. Oh, wait, hold on.
It needs to be tighter. So you, you're, you run an organization. I do the Nevada science center
in downtown Henderson, Nevada. He was there. Two of them were very nice enough to come down here
and help us do all this. So support your local science centers, especially this one. You're ready?
Three, two, one. I didn't tell you to say it that time. It's still not tight enough.
Can be a little bit tighter. You might have to go like, come on, let's go. Science. There we are.
Change it up to this way. It's a little bumpy, so it has to be,
get his ass to get really taught. That's taught. All right. That'll do it.
Okay. One, two, three, science. Hey, one, two, three. Thank you. Excellent. There it goes.
More quartz. Really pretty quartz one. Oh, wow. This is deep. Yeah. That's got a really deep cavity
in there. Check this one out. If you look down in there, you can see some nice crystals too.
Oh, yeah. It's like buried in there. How does this even, how,
our world is so bizarre. How does this even happen?
When lava flow is making its way across the landscape, there's bubbles of gas in there.
And so when the lava flow freezes into a rock, the air bubbles to get stuck in there too.
We have such a bizarre planet. Like how would Doritos even be? Like it's just insane to me.
Some questions you better not answer. Let's do a big one. I think it's time for a big one.
What do you think? Do a big, we got three, we have two huge ones. Let's do a big one.
So originally we thought these were, may have been concrete, but they are not. It has been
confirmed that this is real. It is real. And can you explain why it's real? If you look closely,
you can actually see the air pockets that were around the main geode. And so that just shows
that there was lots of gas in this lava flow. And the geodes just happened to be the biggest,
biggest air voids that were in the rock. So should we, we should probably do it if we can
this way, right? Let's see if we can do it. My like $12 costume is starting to undo from the back.
All right, let's see. Right down the middle here.
Oh yeah. Let me hold the rock a little and then order of mouth. Thank you. It's a little
embarrassing. Is it embarrassing? Is it actually embarrassing? Oh, okay. All right. I think we got
it in a good spot. This is one of the big ones. This is the big ticket item right here. Are you
ready? Let's see if I can do this with my measly like worm arms. Here we go. Let's see if I can
get it to break. Is it going? Do it. Oh, it popped. Oh my God. I think your guests are in for a treat.
That looks insane from back here. Let's go ahead and hold the rock. Got it. Let's lift this out.
Careful. There we go. Oh my God. Wow. That's a beautiful amethyst geode. Look at, look at all,
look at all this in here. It's like a brain. It looks like the inside of somebody's head.
And you can see here there's a, it kind of goes from kind of a solid color to kind of a
clearish to the purple. That's the fluids through time changing as the, as the crystals,
as the crystals were growing in this geode. Wow. So what, what, what's going on down here? Like the,
kind of that, that gray. Like this stuff? Yeah. These are secondary minerals. And so these were
the first minerals to grow. And then there was obviously a second or not obviously, but I should
say there was a second phase of minerals growing. That's what these other ones are. It's like a
membrane. This is insane. That's all right. This is like, hold on to this one. Let's go. I want to
get, see if we can get this over here. Can we get like a good, can we get in there? See what's in
there? That looks awesome. It's an awesome purple too. Look at these. It's like, it's like a shark
fin. Well, that was worth it. That was absolutely worth it. That was awesome. All right. Should we
do a, I, I know this is going to be last, but like, my God, it's huge. Uh, let's, let's get a
couple here. We have like seven or eight more after this. All right. We're going to do rapid
fire. Let's see if we can get a couple. So what, what does your organization do? So we are a
research institution. So we'd go do geology, paleontology around the state of Nevada. And we
also do lots of educational outreach. So right now with COVID, we're doing lots of virtual field
trips. So just check out the website. That's so, that's so cool. You get to actually go on a
field trip, but with COVID you can't. So that's cool. Is this? Oh, one more. Virtual field trips.
There we go. One more. Get that one in there. Hey, there we go. Here we go.
Crush it. This is kind of, so this totally, this highlight is going to be total ASMR, isn't it?
Ooh. What happened? That is a, has like a shard coming out of the other half is empty. Yes. We've
got the smoky quartz in here again. So that gray variety of quartz, and then we have calcite growing
in here. Secondarily calcite, calcite, the white blady stuff. Oh, so that's a couple of different
phases, different types of fluids passing through this thing. This is so cool. Let's see that one.
Yeah. Let me get a closer with this one. This one has like a blade in it.
This is like the coolest thing I've ever done. This is like the most fun I've ever had in my life.
Look at that. Just like a blade going through it. Wow. And this is a huge display here.
All right. How about, oh, there's the other still over there. Let's get this little one.
Let's get this little guy. This one's also pretty dirty. Very dirty. Yeah, geodeform and all sorts
of different geologic processes. So all right, let's see what's in here. Ready? Let's do it.
And that, oh my God, those are, those are stardew valley seed packets. Ah, it's not that great.
That's too bad. It would be nice if there was some like fiery quartz in there or something.
And they're also the way that the water flows over the air creates a, this is a little bit
different process. A little bit different. We'll call it anthropogenic.
Yeah, this is anthropogenic, which means it kind of, you know, enclosed bubble. Of sorts. Of sorts.
But pog, stardew valley seed packets. It's a pretty pog champ. Wow. Oh, you didn't think there
was going to be comedy here. You didn't think there was going to be comedy. This is, my back is,
this is embarrassing. Wardrobe malfunction. Just hope it doesn't like fly down. That looks good.
Could be one more. I can't wait to do that huge one. That's going to be cool. I do, just by looking
at that, do you have any idea what could be in there? No, I mean, every single one of these is
a surprise. You never know until you pop them open. That's so cool. I could literally do this
every day, all day. Here we go. That one's also kind of like empty. That's the smoky quartz variety.
But this one obviously didn't have a whole lot of fluids pumping through it because the minerals
are really small and we got mostly hollow space. Yeah, it's almost like perfectly,
it's like a perfect circle inside. It's a perfect circle of just nothing. An air bubble in a rock.
An air, yeah, kind of like the stardew valley seed packets in the Minecraft diamonds that we
found earlier. It's really nothing like that. It could be. Oh, look, there it is, the Minecraft
diamonds. All right, we're getting, we're getting to, what we got, one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine. We've got, we'll do three more little ones and we're going to do this guy here.
That one, this is like, I can't wait to see what's in there. Oh, we also have that one too. Now this
one already has stuff. We're going to tape it this time. Are you going to tape it? Yeah. If you, if
you look closely, you can see kind of that texture on it. That's, it's quartz, but it's microscopic
quartz. It has some water in it. So it's called, yeah, so it's called agate. So if you hear somebody
talk about agate, it's just a special type of quartz. Oh, cool. Well, let's see if there's
any more inside. And this is a little, so this would break pretty easily. Famous last words.
This is about, watch this be harder than all of them. You guys having fun? I don't know what
camera's on. Snap it. Crotch. That's one of the coolest ones so far. Cool. Let me lift this up.
Wow. It's like, it's got like little tendrils. This is insane looking. Look at that. How does it,
why does this happen? This is a secondary type of quartz mineralization. And so it makes these
kind of weird finger like structures. It looks like a thread. They're delicate too. Even though
it's made out of the stuff that makes up the crust of our planet, it's actually a really delicate
mineral. So you could actually like break these pretty with your finger. I kind of don't want to.
I want to keep it intact. Let's get it underneath here. Underneath our, our patented microscopic
camber technology. Look at that. Cool. That's really cool. Look at this one. This one, they're
even finer on this one. And that's when we get lots of water interacting in our, in our geode.
Wow. That's so cool. That's probably, that's one of my favorite ones so far.
What is this? This one is, what's this one? Oh, it doesn't look like one of the geodes, does it?
Um, I mean, it's a little bit different shape. Well, no. Isn't that your teeth?
This is a, um, this is a smoky, a smoky granite. I can tell by the flavor.
Smoky granite with a hint, a dog peed on it. I think I'm going to be over by the crusher.
Okay. Dog peed on this probably like a couple years ago. I can smell the formaldehyde from the
dog pee. Okay. Yep. What, not formaldehyde. What's the word? Ammonia, right? Yeah. All right.
Let's do this one. Crushing machines. That was good. You want to try? Well, I'll take your word
for it. Okay. No, it's, it's, it's delicious. I guess you do need some silks in your diet.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Here we go. No not. Swing and a miss. Swing and a miss. Strike one. There we go.
See if we get any more, any more squid rocks. This one's tough.
Hold on. One more. There it is. That's a nice pretty quartz one again. You got some really
nice crystal faces, especially on this one right here. So would you, okay. So for all of us video
gamers out there, would you qualify this as like a common? Would you qualify the amethyst as like
kind of rare to see that? Like the purple? Um, in the world of quartz, I'd say amethyst is more of
a rare, but I would say like there's nothing more common than this. Okay. So what would you say is
like a like, wow, legendary status, like I can't believe that's in there. Legendary status would be
if we had some really nice sulfide minerals. Okay. So those are things like cobalite or things
like that, really brilliant blue colors. So is that possible in something in one of these?
Potentially. I mean, it just depends on what was in the groundwater that was going through.
So we got, how many, how many like card packs do we have left open before we get like our legendary?
Well, if it's anything like some of those games, at least another five to $700 worth. Apparently
we had Minecraft diamonds. We did get Minecraft diamonds. It's great. Uh, we got that guy there.
I keep forgetting to do that one. Uh, these two look cool. I'm getting sad that there's only like
five to 10 left to do. No, it can't. I, I just have to continue. I need to do this like every
minute of my life. It's like geologic Christmas. Let's get it in there. There it is. All right.
It's in a good spot. You want to do the honors on this one? Crunch. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Oh,
you got a squid rock squid. Okay. See the little finger courts in there. Oh, there's like tiny
little fingers. Oh, hold on to that one. Look at, look, can you see that? I'll put it in the
microscopic camera technology that we have double zoom technology. Can you see in there,
there is this really, really bizarre looking like swirl. Can you see it? I don't think you can see
it. There's like a little swirly at the very bottom of this one. I don't know if you can pick
it up. I think that's the agate. So I think you're getting the really water rich courts in there.
Yeah, it's really deep. This goes all the way in and look at the fingers on this one.
Get in there. See the tiny little like, uh, like, like flora or something, right? That's so awesome.
All right. Time for a big guy. Oh, this one is really, this one's really heavy.
This one is extraordinarily heavy. All right. Yeah. So we're, we're going to try to get this
long ways if it's possible. So that being that heavy is what kind of a sign is that?
I think we're going to have, it's going to be full. So. Oh wow. Hope we have enough chain to do them
all. Yeah. A little more slack. We're popping out over here. Oh man. Down maybe around here.
There. That looks good. Oh, this guy, this is going to work. We're good. We have just enough
chance. I don't know if we can, if we're going to be able to wait up to get your hammer for the next
month. There. All right. That's in. Oh wow. All right. This is it. Oh man. Here we go. You ready?
Oh God. All right. Come on. Cobalt blue, cobalt blue, cobalt blue. Everybody think it and we'll
get it. We need a legendary. Here we go. Come on. Oh, it doesn't want to do it. Oh, do we have any
score? We gotta go down one more rung. I could feel it too. It's about to go. Let's see if we
can get it up here. All right. Oh, that'll do it. Oh yeah. Here we go.
Crap. We might have to maybe this way. Oh, look at the score. It's right there.
Uh, can we get? Yeah. It'll probably be easier to get like two people to hold it.
Oh, thank God for production Jake. Also known as community Jake. All right. So that's right there.
There it is. All right. Lift it up a little. Get it in there. All right. Is that it? Maybe. Maybe.
Let's give it a try. Let's see if I can get it. Watch your hands. Yeah. This is it. This is it.
All right. We're good. We got to go. You got a good shot of this.
Oh, we might need a few people to help with this one. You want to, you want to,
you want to try to, we'll put some weight here. Oh, come on. It's so close. Yeah. Do it.
Come on. Break. Break. We're not breaking the tool. Are we?
Wow. Oh my God. Oh my God. Holy shit. That looks insane. You got to get this part up here.
Look at that. They sell that stuff in stores. They sell this stuff that you see that in the stores.
If you're born in February, this is your birthstone. What is that? It's amethyst? Uh-huh.
No cobalt. No cobalt, but that's pretty. That looks unbelievable.
Wow. These jaw. This is a display piece. That's what this is. Oh my goodness. Can
we get this out of here? That took so much. I wonder, can you see?
What we got? Can you see? Well, that's like, look at somebody's teeth.
That's beautiful.
Can you get in there, David? Look what I did, Bobby. How's it look?
Wow. We are probably going to need like three or four of us to pull that one.
That one is going to be very difficult. That's unbelievable. That's so cool. Oh, wow. All right.
Well, now let's relax a little bit and do a couple of the smaller ones. Look at this here.
So is there something that makes it more purple? It's just the amount of iron. It's actually just
microscopic amounts. Just that tiny little impurity can completely change the nature
and color of the mineral. Wow. And this has like blue under, what's the blue underneath?
To me, that looks a little bit like copper ore. So there was probably some copper mineralization
before the quartz came in. That goes to air, it turns that greenish color. Oh, look at that.
Yeah. They drop it on the ground. They put this on necklaces. You buy that and put it on a necklace.
That's so cool. All right. Let's move. Oh, this is heavy too. All right. Let's do a couple more.
That was by far the best one. And that was an explosion too. Did you get the explosion on camera?
Yeah. Oh yeah. Somebody slow mow that one. Just don't show our faces.
Oh, it's just like playing tug of war with a geode. All right. Right. Let's do this one.
That was very easy. And? Cool. Oh, more tendrils. One of those finger quartz structures.
Well, this one is even smaller. So what's the, is this just sand? What's the brown and...
Let me take a look. Yeah. Those are probably some sort of aluminum mineral would be my guess. Cool.
So how does it get in there? Again, this is all, everything that's in this
former air bubble has to get there through groundwater. So water just...
Yeah. There's all sorts of minerals in your groundwater.
Depending on where you live, it's different types of minerals. Look at this guy here.
Does the pink mean anything important? That's just the type of volcano,
volcanic eruption it came from. So that one has probably lots of quartz in it.
It's going to be quartz. I hope we get, I hope that one is filled with like blue,
legendary crystal. How many do we have left? Just a kind of naked eye. Only six left.
All right. And want to give this one a pull? Sure. Another one of the fingers.
Ooh. So is there a reason, can you see like the waves in there?
It's almost like a spiral. Oh, that's interesting. Yeah. What would cause a spiral like that? It's
just however the water was interacting with the substrate. So. So it's all water. Each one of
these air bubbles is its own little micro environment. So each one's going to be unique.
Yeah. So maybe this one can show up on the air. Well, I haven't looked at Chad in like an hour.
Oh no, not the spiral. Team Tendril. Team Tendril. Can you see? Let's get a look down here.
Okay. Yeah. I don't know if you can pick it up, but see like the center.
It just got like this weird spiral. That's awesome. The sadness is washing over me.
Get this up here. So just out of curiosity, if there was like
cobalt in here, would that, would that be worth anything? It'd be worth something in terms of
cobalt itself is a highly desirable mineral in metal because of what it does for technology.
And it's also desirable just as a collecting item too. Oh, he's coming to fix. Logos on here.
Wait, like Star Wars, Star Wars logo. I'm here to protect you. You're here to help me?
Cause this is, this is literally the bag costume of Poe from Star Wars.
Oh, that's what we're trying to be trying to protect me. Oh, thank you. I appreciate it.
Here we go. This is, this one's the thick one. It's tight. Wow. There we go. Maybe even more in
the center. I feel like this one's going to be a good one. Maybe move it a little. There we go.
This one's thick. Get in there. Right there. Right there. Right down the middle. Right there. All
right. That should be it. It's a process. There we go. All right. That's the money. That's the,
that's the money, right? Yeah, it is. Absolutely. Here we go. Oh, that one was hard. That was a
reason why the, oh, it's a nice pretty quartz one. It's like furry. Oh, those are just microscopic
or not microscopic, but they're just tiny little quartz crystals. Wow. This one, you can kind of
see that two stage growth again, where you got agate and then quartz crystals. Wow. Let me see
this one. Let's see if we can get this on another camera. I'm waiting for the blue. We might not get
it. These are still pretty spectacular. Yeah, these are awesome. Because correct me if I'm wrong,
but these could all be duds, right? There could be nothing in it. You never know when you get a
geode. Sometimes you crack them open and they're just still in their air pockets. So how hard are
we going to laugh when we open the huge one? It's just literally a rock. There's nothing in it.
That's part of the fun. That is part of the fun. Let's bring a couple of these baseball ones over.
All right. Here we go. This one should go pretty quickly.
Safety first as always. And let's give it a pull. Here we go. One, two, three. That looks interesting.
I saw like the brown. Oh, that is actually really interesting. We got some of those calcite blades
again. So team blade. Calcite's mineral. It makes up a limestone. Oh, so is this quartz still?
No, this is a different mineral. So that's limestone. Yep. This is in pretty form.
There's so many different kinds of rocks. Could you spend an entire lifetime
trying to like find it? No, it's like randomly generated. No two rocks are the same. No two rocks
are the same. And there are people that spend their entire careers out there looking for new
types of rocks and they're still naming new minerals. So there's stuff out there we don't
even know about yet. Involve in your local science community now. You see how cool this is? I wish,
I'm 35. If I was like 20, oh my God, I would start doing this. This is the coolest thing I've
ever done in my whole life. Let me get that situated. In there? Almost. All right. And again,
that's ScienceCenterNevada.org. Correct. Yes, come visit and our schedule of virtual field trips is
on there. Go take a virtual field trip. Think of how cool that would be. Go take a virtual field
trip. And they're at no cost to the public. It's free. Wait, hold on. I want to make that,
did you hear that? It was free. Don't panic. Passionate people. Support them. A little bit,
a little bit tighter. Here we go. This one was almost a dud, but we did get a couple minerals
in it. That's close to a dud, you're right. So a true dud would just be like the limestone. It'd
just be rock, yeah. Rock. I'm surprised we've had any that'll like that. No duds yet. Zero. No duds
at all. We don't have jinks at all. Yeah, it's going to be the big one. It has to be. The big
one's going to be a dud and I'm scared of it. You've already resigned yourself to it? Yeah,
because then if it's awesome, then we get to all be excited. I think that's called low expectations,
right? Yeah. Very low expectations, but very high reward if it is good. Here we go again.
Looks like snow. That's all agate in there. That's that water rich quartz. Get it under
the microscopic camera. You get a good look. Can I see the chat? What's it saying? Geode Andy?
Geode Andy. No, I think he's Andy. No, it's not Andy from Toy Story. You got that wrong. Oh wait,
I look like Andy from Toy Story. Oh my God.
Take this off. Get this off. It's a bandana. Get it off. Hey, did you know that every Andy,
no, every little kid in Toy Story is an Andy? Did you know that? They didn't want to animate
extra kids so they're all Andy. Look it up. That's a real thing. This is like bolted on my neck.
There we go. Geode Andy. I got it. Oh, another close dud. That's cool. Let's get like a little
slice. Little quartz crystals in there. That's really cool. I'm just looking at these on the
ground. It's like, that's awesome. All right, we are down to the final five regular ones. We
have no legendaries yet, which is, you know, whatever. And then we got this guy. This is
probably going to take like everybody on set. Let's do the last six. Oh wait, we have an extra one
here. Geode Andy. Come on, Rock. Oh, that might do it. Well, now that's different. What's the
orange? The orange is a lot of iron minerals. So this one's kind of a dud. Out of the shadow.
Now that's done. There's a little quartz crust. Oh, your half is way better. Oh, is my better?
Yeah, you got lots of little quartz crystals in there. Let's get a close-up. Oh, sorry.
What do we got for a stream time? How long have I been doing this for? I'm just like, I'm just
obsessed. Yeah, one hour and 50. Oh, cool. All right. This is awesome. All right, let's keep going.
Yeah, I'll get in there and do it after this. All right, here we go. Come on, Cobalt. Legendary.
This one's tight. Pretty amethyst one. The amethyst. Whoa, what's going on here?
What's at the bottom? That like weird like brown and beige. Yeah, you've got a different type of
quartz crystal starting to grow in there. So the agate grew inside the hole, then the amethyst grew,
and then there was water starting to come in again and there was a third phase of mineral growth
starting in there. But so here's a really good question for you. Oh, these look
they're like little triangles. Beautiful. I got a good question for you. How long does this take
to happen? Thousands of years. Thousands of years. If not millions, yeah. Millions or a thousand. Wow.
Let's get some detail on this one. Try to get the light to hit it. I'm not sure how well you can see
the sun is starting to change a little. What is that? Looks really good. Does it look good?
Look at those little triangles. Those are called the crystal faces. Crystal faces. Very cool.
All leading up to the final gigantic one, which we'll see. This is I think this is the smallest
one so far. This is a little guy. How heavy is it? I don't know. It's not bad. What do you think?
So again, the heavier this is, the more it could be inside.
I thought it was just burped right into the camera, which would have been weird.
I get it up there. And again, safety first. Workers gloves. Here we go. Team Tendril.
You've got another crewmate. That one was heavy because it was pretty full of minerals. Yeah.
It's a pretty one. These would look a little more clear too.
Oh, you want to get the detail of that other one, right? This one here.
Yeah. Right here. This one here. What was the orange rock you said?
It's probably some iron rich rock. Oftentimes you get lots of metals that are in lava flows.
This looks like a map. Like if I pressed M in a game,
I got to tie it back to the gamers. You know what I mean? I just saw like the cut.
I'm trying to catch the cut. I can see the monitor here. Take another one.
How's that look? Get a good shot of that. A snake head?
Tendril on the top. Oh, okay. Oh, it does. You're right. It does look like a snake.
Right there. Right at the top. Very cool. What are you guys saying? Crack rock.
Well, that's not what it is. All right. We got one, two, three, and that's it. And then we got to
bring it. We got to bring in the big guy. It's so funny when you said, is that the rock breaking
or is that the tool breaking? I can already see the quartz coming out of the edge here.
So this is going to be a quartz, Andy. Let me get a little bit more.
Very, very heavy quartz crack rock, Andy. Yeah, that one's a nice one. Nice pure quartz. You can
see the nice crystal faces in there glimmering in the sun. It's just about the water, right? So
when they like fill in deep into the middle, that just does that mean that they have more time?
More time. Exactly. More time for those minerals to grow and grow on top of each other and fill in
that void. Awesome. That's so cool. This is like, like rethinking my entire life choices here doing
this. I should have been a geologist. This is like, I get it. This is the coolest thing ever.
You know, after this one, I think I've got to get going before a place closes in town.
Okay. Yeah, that's fine. But after this one. Yeah, that's cool. Thanks for, seriously,
thanks for coming. You got something, you got to go somewhere. You got to be somewhere, right?
My pleasure. Science Center. We always aim to educate. Yeah. And again, that's
sciencecenternevada.org. They do field trips, virtual field trips, support them. Because honestly,
without them, this kind of doesn't happen because I don't know anything about what's inside of these
rocks. I'm just the clown that cracks the nuts. Here we go. Oh, go for it. Oh, do we got something
good? Pretty agate. Oh, this one's awesome. That nice cloudy texture. Oh, let's see like the,
that's cool. Looks like a pair of eyes. Let's get a close-up. I got, we got to get a close-up of this
one. What's that? No, it's purple. That's not blue. No, we don't have any legendaries, unfortunately.
Look at that. Nice. Beautiful. It's been a pleasure. Thank you for having me today. Yeah,
thank you. No, seriously, thank you for coming out here and doing this because this is impossible
without your help. So thank you so much. That's sciencecenternevada.org. Support your local
scientists, your local educators, please, for the love of God. Thank you for coming. Thank you. It's
been a pleasure. Seriously. Got somewhere to go. Let's go. We got two more. We got the big one
that's left. I'm gonna get the whole crew up in that last one. That was awesome. That was seriously
awesome. That's why you gotta get somebody that knows what they're talking about. Go like this.
Because, oh yeah, I could have done this stream and just, what am I gonna do? I'm gonna sit here
and go, whoa, whoa, oh, but I don't know anything. Here we go. Come on. Oh, that stayed in there.
That stuck around. All right, come on, come on, guy, guy, guy, guy. Remember what he said.
So this is the, this is the, I forgot everything. This is the mineral and then this is the quartz.
It's got smoky quartz in the center and then the water dissipated outside of the pores of the rock
and created, I gotta go back. I gotta get back. I gotta get back. I gotta figure out what else
is in here. I'm gonna get a legendary and he's not gonna be here. I'm gonna be like, okay,
enough stalling. Time to do the big one. Are we ready to try to do the big one?
Are you guys ready? Crack rock. Look at all these crack rock. It's not all crack.
This thing is, by the way, can we get a confirmed weight on this? It's 50 pounds.
This is 50 pounds. So whatever is in here,
it's, all right, it's already scored up here. I wonder, will the chain be big enough for this?
We can try. No, no, not at all. I think it is. Oh, we need a, we need one in person.
No, it's not long enough. Is it not long enough? No, we have to go the other way. All right.
God. I got the rock. You got the rock chain. Yeah. Come on. Come on. A little bit higher.
Should we try to get it a long way? It doesn't fit. The chain doesn't fit.
Maybe the, um, hold on. Can we do this? We could probably go like that. We can try. Like,
you know, like diagonal. Yeah, let's give it a shot. All right. So we go, I'll hold the rock.
So we go like this, maybe from like, can we get it like that? That may be tight enough.
No, it's not going to be tight enough. Well, it can be like a nuclear warhead.
If I hold it, can you get the chain? Actually, you know what? Here, try this. Okay. Let's go like
this. Hold the chain all the way out. Yep. Okay. Wrap it around. Okay. Okay. Is it around the whole
thing? What do you mean? Like if we go like this? Oh, uh huh. Can that make it? It's not even close.
Shit. Well, that's it. Streams up. No, I'm just kidding. Should we just hit it with a hammer?
Should we just smack this thing right? It's already scored right here. Sure. What do you think? Yeah,
should we go? Should we go horizontal or should we hit it with a hammer?
What do you guys think? Show auto. Why would auto be here? Chisel, chisel, just get the excavator.
I'm not going to break it. All right. Here we go. So I've been instructed. We got instructions.
So you're going to put this in the score. Okay. And then hit this with that and just smash it.
Smash it. Yeah. Tap it. Tap it. Are we ready to try this right in the score? Yeah. Just tap it.
Here we go. That's working. Yeah. Oh my goodness. Oh my God. Whoa. Hold on. Hold on. Wow. Look at
inside of there. Can you hold on? Let's go like this. He's more light. We got to turn it that way.
Turn toes here. Turn it this way. And then can you shoot this way, David? Shoot that way. Yeah.
I'm going to just carve it off. You got it? You got it? Yeah. Look at this one right here.
No blue, but still it's a rare. That's purple. That looks unbelievable. Oh my God. It's full.
It's like a Halloween candy bag full of these crystals. Honestly, this is like, hold on,
let me pick it up. I just ruined it. I picked it up and it broke in my hand. It was cool looking
and then I ruined it. Can you get it? This looks like the Mortal Kombat spike pit. Looks like a
shark's mouth. Yeah. It looks like a mouth. It really does look like a mouth. You're blocking
the light. Yeah. Just turn a little bit. I'm doing like limboing. There's a bee all right there.
Oh, it's a purple. They attracted it. They think it's a flower. Oh my God. All right.
Let me get one more look over here. This is the coolest thing ever. What do you guys think?
Pog rock. It looks like Jerma chomp. It does. It really does. I should have. All right. I'm
going to get it painted. This is going to get painted like Jerma chomp. That's so cool. That's
awesome. I'm going to hang this on my mantle. Well, this is a lot of fun. That was a ton of fun,
but that's really all we got planned. We opened up a shit load of geodes. We had
scientists come in and help us decipher what was going on. This is my favorite by far.
Look at this one. So cool. Awesome. I got treasures. I got cards. This stuff in this
treasure chest that I need to get like assessed. Some of these rocks need to get assessed. Yeah.
I'll see you guys later. That's the end of this stream. I'm going to go get some of this stuff
assessed. I got to see if I can make some money because look at all this.
I've got stuff in a chest. I've got geodes. I might make like $50,000 to $100,000 in the next
hour. Let's see if I can do it. Thank you for joining me. ScienceCenterNevada.org. Special thanks
to that team for coming out here and helping us do this. So awesome. I picked the wrong career
and I'll see you next time. Keep an eye on the stuff. I'm going to go get some shit assessed.
Have a wonderful rest of your day. I'm going to get the shovel.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello, sir. Welcome. How are you doing? Not too bad. What can I do for
you today? I'm doing fantastic. Thank you for asking. I have some trinkets here for you that
I would like to get assessed the value of. All right. That's what we do. That's what they do on
these programs. That is what we do here. They bring some cool stuff and we can make a deal,
right? I'll tell you what they're worth. Yeah. Tell me what you got here. Okay. So first of all,
you got to check out this guy right here. Okay. I don't know if that's potentially from the
Jurassic period or the Stegosaurus period. It's from some dinosaur period. Where did you come
across this piece? Digging in the ground. You found it yourself, huh? Yes. Digging in the ground.
Found it with a bunch of this other cool stuff. There's a story between. You don't need a story,
but that in particular is probably. Did you happen to notice that it was plastic at all?
No. Or that it said for pet use on it. But it feels kind of real. This is a completely
worthless piece. It's just a plastic bone. I ordered one for my dog yesterday. But don't
you have a guy? I'm not calling the guy for a plastic bone. Yeah, but you don't know that.
Do you have a plastic machine that you. It's all this is plastic. You don't know that that's what
that is. It's reflecting. Usually. I don't know if you've ever seen the TV shows, but usually you
call a guy. The guy comes in and looks at it and is like, oh, that's from the that's from Triceratops.
And then I you offer me $5000 for it. Well, let's let's find something worth calling.
OK, in that same room, look at these. These are rocks opened up like 30 of them.
Just at fresh openings. And how did you come across these ones in the ground to just in the
desert? Well, the the good news, these are some some beautiful geodes. So you did a great job
coming across these. The bad news is they're totally worthless. I'm not buying these.
People aren't coming into the shop looking for geodes. They just don't sell.
They don't. But OK, what about some of the big? We have a big one, too.
I'm not bringing that in here until you give me a price. They're rocks.
Yeah, but they're cool. They're really cool. They're awesome.
Maybe they make good gifts. You could try that.
It literally is no idea what it's talking about. I've seen stuff like this go for 500 bucks each.
You don't you're not going to take any of these even if I bring you the other ones.
I'm not interested in that. No, you don't want any of the rocks at all.
Not interested in rocks. What about the 90s snacks?
I've got we got Dunkaroos. I got these Kinder Joy stuff. This is old and they they make them. But
I got to say there's some there's some nostalgia here. I mean, I remember these snacks. These are
some these are some good snacks you got here. But something about snacks that that you dug up
just doesn't seem right. These these are also completely work.
A Blue Eyes White Dragon Yu-Gi-Oh original. This is I know this is worth at least something.
You have to have some kind of use for this. Let's take a look here. Is this has this been graded?
Yes, it's it's pounds per square inch 20. I'm not buying that. That's a lot. You're a liar.
You are a swindler and you're a liar. You know why? Because I looked this up before in the in
the garage when I was coming in here. This is worth at least $7.95 at least $10. I looked at
it before I got in here. Did it say you pay me? No, this is how much this card is worth at least
$10. I expect I expect you to take that for at least $15. I don't know what to tell you.
Because that was an insult that what you just did to me. Do you want the Tamagotchi?
Look at this. I haven't seen one of these. You're getting sleepy. I haven't seen one of these.
No, this stuff is not worthless. These look like little toys, sir. This stuff is not worth looking.
This stuff doesn't have any value. It didn't even hatch the egg. You don't even know what it could be
in there. It's random. Maybe you can come back after the egg hatches and it'll still be worthless.
What about these Stardew Valley seed packets? These what? Stardew Valley seed packets and
a Minecraft diamond. You know what Stardew Valley is, right? I don't speak French, sir.
You've never heard of Stardew Valley? I don't know any idea. Okay, what do you have? Let's take a
look at what you have here. We have some beautiful pieces here. Yeah, take a look. See if anything
strikes your fancy. You do have some pretty cool stuff actually. You got Elvis over here?
Oh, these coins too. All sorts of coins. Wow, this is actually really... What about this up here?
What's this? These are our newest arrival. Beautiful condition. We just checked through them
and take a look and see what you think. These are absolutely beautiful. They're heavy too. They
have a weight to them. That's how you can tell the value right there. Yeah, I knew that. That's why
I said that with you. Wow, these are... How much are these worth? These two pieces right now
we could probably let them go for 50,000. That's kind of on the high end. That would be quite a
steal on the high end, but it's okay. I did say that I wanted to invest in gold though. I did
mention that a long time ago. This would be a great way to get started. You think so? Absolutely.
Just hang on to these. Let them appreciate. They smell too. Is gold that was sent? Yes, it does.
That's the scent of gold right there. Holy smokes. You know what? I'm going to call my guy.
Come and get an assessment here. Over the phone. And it's my mom. It's like a pound.
Yeah, it looks good. He wouldn't... No, ma, he wouldn't take the Yu-Gi-Oh card.
I know it. I told him that. Okay, let me... 48? You think he'll take 48? Okay. All right. Yeah.
This guy's a moron. He has never even played Stardew Valley before. I know. Seriously. All right,
ma. All right. I love you too. Get ahold of your guy? That's very hard to reach my guy sometimes.
Did you say your mom? Is that right? Yeah. Well, she knows a lot. What did you say? Give me the
price again one more time. 50,000 for these pieces. Okay. Let me just want to make sure you
know I got it. Just so you know. Here it is. Just so you know I got it. I got it in my hand.
Well, okay. So this is the part where we do the thing. Can you do 38,000?
If we include all these items, I'd probably be willing to let it go for 49,999. 49,999. That's
5% off the first one you said? Something like that. Yeah. How about... Can you do...
Now that it's real, I'm really fucking nervous. Can you do 42,000? 44,000? 43,000?
I mean, these are great pieces. The best I could do would be probably 49,999.
You are. You are a tricky one. Deal. You got it. Deal. Let's make a deal.
I almost just yelled my mother's name. Here you go. You can count it too. You can make sure it's
all there. It's going to take a little while. Yeah. It's a step. You know what to do with it.
Yeah. Enjoy your new pieces, sir. Oh my God.
Yes. I'm going to... Should I turn it back to it? Wait. So I'm going to check the price of gold
right now. See if it went up. It went down? All right. Let's go. Whatever. You want to grab my phone?
Get out of my shop. Grab my phone. Thank you. You want to get Burger King? Don't use that part
because I don't want the people to know I ate it. I'm going to call my guy and I'm going to figure
out what the value that is because I'm going to get them in here and we'll make like they do on
the TV shows. Sounds good. I wanted you to do so badly. Just cut it right here. I wanted you so
badly to just call the guy in. It's good TV. I don't know why you don't understand that. I
would call the guy in if you had brought me these. You call the guy in for that. I don't
care what that is. The guy was just here. He's the one that evaluated these.
You just got to bring me something of value. Is he still in the parking lot? Give him that.