Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some more chivalry. Medieval combat. Oh, medieval warfare, would I say combat? That's not correct.
Playing as the knight right now with a big giant clunky two-hander. This is elimination right now, so if you die, you are permanently dead.
So you gotta be more careful than usual, and there's a lot of guys coming up here right now. Oh, my head smashed! Oh, did I get the hit?
At least I got the hit on him, that's all I care about. Don't have a shield, so I'm really vulnerable. Don't kill each other!
Wow, wow, I'm getting hit by my own teammates! Oh, get out of here, man. Whoa, dude, you're hitting me! What are you doing? What is this guy doing?
Dude, bro, you are swinging at the wrong person! That guy just didn't at least like... Alright, you know what, you're getting killed. Get the hell out of here.
You're getting destroyed, bro. What on earth are you doing? That guy was an imbecile!
In the corner here, a lot of blue guys. A lot of blue guys. Anybody come from behind? No, we're good, we're good. Hold your ground, man. Stand your ground.
Alright, get the guy that's running. Get the guy that's running. He's vulnerable, he's vulnerable. Look at him, he's like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
No! Oh, that guy. I opened... Oh, wow! Archer. Oh, this is scary. I don't have very much health, I'm regenerating it, though. That was not a good idea.
That guy's in trouble down here. Two on one! Oh, come on. Jeez. Oh, fake him out. Fake him out. Going for the run. Oh, I just missed.
How did I miss that? How on earth did I miss that? Too many things going on. Is there just one guy behind me? Why did I... What? What? What?
I'm gonna hop down and Wolverine-style hit this guy in his head. Ah, two on one. Ah, two on two. We can do this, man. Just be smart. Be smart. Be smart. Be smart.
Be smart. Be smart. Oh, they got a third coming. They got a third coming. Oh, is anyone behind us? Nope. This is a 4v2 situation here, man. We're in some trouble.
They're like hitting each other. Nice, nice. Oh, nice. Good job. Good job. Wow, we took on like four guys. Oh, you took on like four guys. Good job, dude.
Anybody left? Oh, they're storming him. Yeah, that's it. Nice job. We did it. We won that round. I love you. I'm going in this time. I'm going straight in. I'm going for the archers. Wow.
Oh, maybe not. Probably not. Ah, I missed. Go for the jab. Nice. Go for another jab. Go for an overhead. Go for an overhead. Go for a side swing on this bastard.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. Wait, how did I not kill him? I'm hitting the tree. I'm like chopping down a tree for firewood. Coming from behind. Crush. Oh, you're going to see better days.
How do you scream? Because that's hilarious. That is a long scream, man. That guy had some practice. He must be like a singer. Can I get up there? No.
Waiting on this guy to jump down. Me and my boy over here. Both got long swords. We both know what's going on. I don't see anybody. Oh, they're all back here. They're all getting crushed.
I have no idea. You are going to get smashed. Maybe not. I love how it's just like yeet. I feel like a Rockette. I can't even spam it. Oh, that's stupid.
My long blade has been in the generational families since the day my grandfather took the field of battle and missed his first overhead swing.
But then my grandfather took a swing from behind, blocked the incoming attack and swung and crushed and then died.
All right, so I'm going to shell cast this as if I were like in the medieval times. Here we go. And we have Brother Matthew attacking the swordsmith of the right side there.
We've got a couple at the side here. We've got lots of people fighting. Oh, what an absolutely brilliant blow on his chest. We have Governor Stevenson, even though Stevenson isn't even a medieval name, but it's OK.
So Governor Stevenson is attacking Walther Malfjau, which is the strongest knight they have. Stronger than any blue moon or green moon.
And he gets the kill on him. Absolutely fantastic with that blow. I sound like a golf guy. Like the guys that do the- no, they're killing each other.
Don't you throw things at me. I don't approve of that. Why don't you come down? Why don't you jump down? I will clump you.
I sure got that nice, pretty shield. Is your guy running by?
At the tree. Oh, you want to go? You want to go? Oh, you want to go with me? Is that what you said? You want to get stabbed? You want to get stabbed and you want to get swung at?
Oh, OK. Watch the right side. Come in with the blow. Oh, did I? Good. I didn't accidentally- where is he? Was it an archer? I think it- oh, wow, it was an archer.
Anybody left? Who's left? We got here. Oh, that's it. The mason order is victorious again.