VOD Watchers, I'm so glad I caught you this early. At one minute and- I'll shut up. What's
going on everybody? How you doing? Good morning. I'm not doing it again. No, I was- I- that was for
you guys to get really annoyed with. What if you have not finished the other VOD? Well, just save
them. Just save them for a rainy day. Why am I live right now? I'm like a- I'm a couple hours
early than typical, than usual. There are some new emotes. Some that I ripped from better uh,
Twitch TV. And some that are new. Hey, remember that emote that I said was going to be here?
Just about a year and two months ago? Well, I- there it is. Dermathing. Remember when I played
the thing last weekend? Wasn't that a really funny stream? It was- we had a bunch of fun.
Why are people getting banned? Too early. Too early. Leave. No, I'm- I'm not leaving. I remember
that like it was yesterday. Uh, dude. Okay, it was- uh, yes, it was yesterday. Are you all right?
Yeah, there's a look of me. There's also- I don't know why I enabled it, but there's also me ripping
a t-shirt off. Somebody's linked it and said, hey dude, enable this! Okay. When you guys get me
in one of those days where I'm incredibly impressionable, I'll just- I'll do anything.
I activated like five new emotes yesterday just because it was like, yeah, okay,
people told me to- yeah, I'll turn this one on. We're going to do more. Battle for Bikini Bottom
Rehydrated. And speaking of being hydrated, okay, let's do the complete opposite and drink a coffee.
Let's shrivel up. It's early though. It's like, oh, it's not even 10 o'clock in the morning.
Yeah, hydrate bot. Where's- where's shrivel bot? Where's the thing that says, hey, you haven't
drank water in over four hours? Don't do it! Turn to dust. What's today's sponsor? I don't
have sponsors. What are you talking about? I've been trying to drink more water. Trying to stay
more hydrated. You know, for a while I had an app on my phone that told me when to drink water.
I'm not kidding. I downloaded an app that told me when to drink water. It was a notification when
ding! Actually, that's a lie. It went like bloop! They made like this cool water sound. Like,
it's like, hey, it's time to drink! And the thing just got annoying because, you know,
you're supposed to drink like eight to ten glasses of water a day. Getting 10 notifications
a day is too much for me. Getting three notifications a day on my phone is too much for me.
Drink a pool. How many times have you guys had an app that gave you notifications that within
one time of it happening you went, nah, I'm fucking deleting this. I don't want this.
Because you were like in the middle of like- you were in the middle of like reading a newspaper
or something or you were in the middle of like a game or something like that and it just annoyed
you. No, whatever that is, turn it off. I never want to hear it again. It's like, well, I did that.
I wanted that. Oh, yeah. Notification. Yeah, that'd be cool. It'll notify me of something important.
Don't fucking do that ever again. Give me the phone. Give the fucking thing to me.
Where's the- there it is. Don't ever do that again, motherfucker.
What's wrong with humans? Why are we like this? The term of punching. I feel like that's going to
be used in a good way. Term of punching is a thing. Yeah, better Twitch TV. I got a hundred
dollars from KXZ. Thank you KXZ for the fucking hundred bucks. It's good to be back. Thank you.
That's 100 bucks. Derma Wild 2. Yeah, Derma Wild 2 is there. I didn't enable one or three. I just
did two. It's scary. Why not Derma Psycho? I don't know. Why do I have two? Wait, hold on a minute.
Why is there a save file here with 30 spatulas at 5 PM? And why is there one at 6 PM? Why is there
one a full hour later? This is an autosave. Did I- how long was this open? Which one's the real one?
I should do the one that was later, right? Wait, did I end the stream and just leave it at this
screen and just go like fuck off and eat? And then come back in an hour and go, oh,
this is definitely what happened. Well, welcome back to Bikini Bottom, guys. I'm your host.
All right. I won't do that this early. It's too early for that. It's too early to be a dickhead.
You know what I mean? Somebody knows what I mean. It's too early for like the- yeah, it is. All
right. What was the- where was I? Oh, Gula Good. Somebody said to go here because they said this
is a cool park. Sorry. Oh, this does look cool. I love the beach. It's the only thing I miss in
Vegas. No beach. You can use the bubble bash to move things. Okay. It's just- it's not the same.
There's no beach. What about Lake Mead? I'm not going to Lake Mead? What do you mean Lake Mead?
Lake Mead is like- there's like- isn't there like stores? Isn't there like a bunch of fucking dead
animals and like dead bodies in there and stuff? I don't want to go in there. It's true. I don't
know what the hell- I don't want to go into Lake Mead. The game's quiet. I'll turn it up.
This robot is called Monsoon. Watch out for his lightning attack. Can I kill him? One hit. One hit.
That was a farting and screaming compilation. What happened? What happened? What? What happened?
Wait, that's goo. Oh, okay. You can't even touch it? I mean, I understand if it goes above the waste,
right? But I can't even touch this shit. Oh, hey Larry. Do you look burned?
What's that mean in French? Oh my god, right? Oh my gosh.
Exactly. You can't spend a day at the beach without sunscreen. That sun is way too hot.
That means eat my ass in French. No, it doesn't. That robot is out on the island.
Nobody can get to him. What? Isn't there a song? Oh, eat my ass. What is this? How on earth could I
have missed such a sweet little succulent crab? What are you talking about? That would not be in
that Joe movie. SpongeBob, maybe you can use those sun reflectors to point the sun rays on that
robot. All right, let me pay attention. I need to pay attention to the game. If you can use the sun
reflectors. If you hit one of the buttons on the side of a lifeguard tower, the reflector will turn.
Connect all the towers and the light will shoot right out of the big reflector on the island.
This is pretty cool. Then all you have to do is swim out to the island and turn the big reflector
onto the real and live. Yeah, this is yeah, I'll stay here and protect the babes, but I can't swim.
Yes, how am I supposed to do this? And any of the character can like sandy swim.
All right, where's the first beam? All right, right here. First beam going. Push, push, push,
push, push. What are you talking about? Push, push. Who am I pushing? No, that's that's wrong.
It's gotta go this way. Like push the button. Yeah. Oh, I thought you meant. I thought you were like
push the thing out of the way, like move it, like turn it. Come on. I can't make that jump.
Yes, I can. Just jump better. I am jumping fine. I made it. All right. So what what side do I need
to press this one? No, no, no, no, no. Wrong. Okay, we got one, two, and then we got to go
from over there. Oh, there's a big cookie monster over there I can jump on. All right, cool.
He did it. Wrong. Cross the way. There we go. Okay. But now we go to that one and we got to
move it to over here. Imagine if you were at the beach and some pasty dude jumped on your fat belly.
All right. This problem. All right. It's probably a guy that has like one of those like bad
experiences with like a little kid at the beach where somebody like jumps to dive
to pick up like a ball and they just land right on your stomach. All right. Which one's missing?
Am I doing this right? What the fuck? No, I'm doing it wrong. I don't know. Aren't they all lit up?
Which one is currently being touched? This one to here. Wait, what does this thing say? Why is
there a sign here? You can get to the oh from the pier on the other side of the sea caves.
Well, shit. In this reach. I just woke up. Hey, good morning. All right. You can get to the pier
from the other side of the sea caves or something. Whatever. All right. Let's go. There's one that's
going to be lit across the goo lagoon. You won't be able to access it. Well, I got those accessed.
I'm ready to move. Somebody screamed because they were just like, dude, he keeps hitting the fucking
lightning tombs, whatever they're called. How many spats are just too early to say that word?
How many spatulas? That should be. I got to be Patrick for this. Is there a bus stop? I didn't
see one. Are you? Are you? No, I'm not even going to answer that. That's like so stupid. No. Just
who cares what character I am from Family Guy. I don't care. I'm not going to answer that.
Yeah. Hey, dude, I just want to know, are you a Peter or a Chris from Family Guy? Like who cares?
Who are you? What are you? That's what I want to know. Who are you?
Mrs. Pops. The children's balloons are carrying the children out of control.
I don't know, Mrs. Pops. It looks like they're having a lot of fun. Yes, too much fun if you ask me.
You can save the children by bubble bashing each of the balloons.
Okay, we're going to save the kids. All right. How many? What are they? Three?
Five. All right. Let's just look up. One, two, three over here. This game is fun. I like this game.
You know, I thought this was a racing game since it came out on like the PlayStation 2. I didn't
know this was this kind of game. I didn't even care to look. You know why? Because most all
cartoon licensed video games are car racing games. Why is this moving around? So it's like a
Spongebob battle for Bikini Bottom. It's like a combat cartoon Mario Kart racer. I don't want to
play it. I don't know why I didn't give it a chance. I hate that you weren't. Whoa, whoa, whoa. How
wrong you were. Yeah, I know. I didn't know this was like a Banjo Kazooie, but with Spongebob
characters. That's fucking awesome. Why didn't any of you guys tell me this? Dude, check it out.
Check out Spongebob Battle for Bikini Bottom. You'll love it. It's a sick racer. It's an awesome
racing game. And I'm like, I don't want to play that. What the hell? Oh shit. I didn't know that
one fell. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. No. Stop obstructing
my view. All right. Where are the other two? I'm not going to punch it. I promise.
Local viewer has 3000 viewers screaming. What did I scream? Oh, dirty sock. How many do I have? Nine.
One more dirty sock. Oh, there's a balloon kid over there. Uh, hold on. Wait, is the chat in
E mode only? No, it's not. Shit. The chat's not in E mode only mode. Oh no. It's just my chat.
They're not speaking to each other anymore. They're just communicating in symbols and images.
All right. Where is he? There's the last two. All right. Bounce up here.
Oh, I got it. Everybody. That's why it's so loud. Oh, by the way, I saw something the other day
and it was killing me. I want to play this and I don't know. Am I like a weird narcissist? A weird
like sicko egomaniac for wanting to play this? I'll show you the video. Hold on. Let me just get a
spatula. I was fucking laughing. I was like, why is this exist? Somebody made a mod for, uh,
Dark Messiah of Might and Magic. It's my face on the orcs and it's a bunch of random lines from me.
I was just like, why is this a thing? Hold on here. Look, let's watch this. Play it now. I'm
gonna, I'm gonna. It's the stupidest fucking thing ever. Like, where did you even get all these sound
files? Hold on. I gotta scroll down and get it. Sometimes I, yeah, sometimes I peruse the
gerber reddit and I just check out things that are going on every few weeks or something.
All right. Here it is. Let's watch this together. This video only has 700 views. What? How?
Unbelievable. This guy over here. Trash. I'm a fucking monster. Fuck out of here. Fuck you.
Oh my God, a human. Oh, sorry. This is fucked. Oh, I'm a fucking, I'm a fucking monster.
Play it, play it. I'll play it. I will. I promise I will at least run around for 20 minutes in this
mod. Play it now. Oh, I can't play it right now. All right. I got a spatula and then that wouldn't
even what I was trying to do. No, I want to play SpongeBob right now. I will do that really soon.
I promise. Beat the game with that mod. I already beat, I already beat that whole game and it was a
fucking joy. I wish I could just delete that from my brain and like play the whole thing again.
There's a human over there. Oh my God, a human. Somebody throws ice when I put ice on the ground.
Oh, so many puked. Well, I didn't do that. That wasn't my gameplay. Why am I saying that was me?
They didn't go in and edit the video of me playing it. What am I talking about? Can I make it from
here? She already puked. Okay, I want to go that way. Is that like a little, can I make this jump?
Shit, I don't think I can. No, what have I done? God damn it. What have I done? You've already been
there. I want to go across. How do I go across? Is there no way I can go from here to there? Is
it like a secret way for me to get to the other side of the lagoon over there? Or just go to the
right? Oh, I'll go that way. Okay. Call Sandy. Yeah, where's that? I need a bus stop. Oh, there's a
cookie monster. Holy shit. This is a classic Super Mario technique. Hey, look at that. There we go.
Oh, wait a minute. Get those. Call Sandy. Any opportunity I have to play with Sandy,
I'm just going to only be Sandy. But not yet. Let's see what a bubble friend says.
Have you seen one? Why? Yes, we were having a sandcastle contest and somebody put a golden
spatula on the top. All Sandy she's crying. I'm going to name it Fort Patty town the third
and Fort Patty town the third would have a big bake sale. Oh, can we talk about the secret
patty recipe by the way for a quick minute? Why is it so hard to figure out this plankton not know
what a fucking tomato is? I don't get it. Hey, I don't know. What's the secret formula?
It's a tomato and onion and some mayonnaise on it. You have you never been to a grocery store
plankton? Oh, okay. Should I not talk about this? The golden spatula. That should be easy to reach.
And then it's a crab patty. Perhaps you should see for yourself. Wait, it's a crabby patty. It's
actually made out of crab. So you tell me this motherfucker Mr. Krabs is running a restaurant
where he's grinding up his own fucking people and putting them in between hamburger buns.
Oh, that's kind of weird. Am I really late to this joke? I feel like I am right. I feel
like there's somebody made like a really funny like, Oh, Mr. Krabs. Can you believe that he's
makes us out of crabs. I'm like probably 1015 years late to this joke. Yeah, I'm a little
and the water is rising. Oh, what? Oh, what? Oh, what? Oh, what? Oh, it's still going.
Oh shit. Classic Super Mario technique. Watch it. Oh, very cool checkpoint.
Cross there. Can I just walk up here and get it?
They thought about it. They thought about it. You can't do it.
Do you think the guy that made the original ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding ding ding gets royalty still? You think that family has like fucking 25 islands.
like I'm the guy and my family's legacy is my great-great-grandmother made the
din din din din din din din din song and it's used in every piece of media
do it what's going on drown you can't copyright a baseline riff but there are
whole songs made about this you can you know you can all right do you think that
the guy that first made this song with like a guitar on the beach think he's
like wowed the fuck out of everybody back in like the 40s imagine hearing
this for the first time like a guy with a guitar on the beach and you he's just
like oh my second holy shit I got something big play that one again oh
all right yeah this is I'm gonna be fucking rich well I keep going and they
come up with a couple of cans yep and they start his drumbeat oh my god I'm
gonna create generational wealth okay cool but I want hit the cannon what the
fuck true the germa see the dabbing fish yet no I don't know I don't care so you
don't have to show me this next viral video there's a fish in the water that
pops up and goes like boom and does the dab and goes back in the water okay it's
probably like all over reddit right now I don't I don't care I do not I don't
have to say it what should you get for lunch I don't know something cheese
related you'll figure it out oh there's a spatula at the end of this cave I made
that it's the games controls are fucked up yeah I don't something that fucking
jump sticks all the time what the fuck yeah the jump sticking right now see
listen that's a huge fucking delay that's what I'm dealing with right now
you understand it's a fucking miracle I'm able to do this game oh shit oh you
got to go quick I should go this way or whoo there's a few ways to go all right
we're gonna go no we're not we're gonna go what happened okay if they die we're
hitting my head on the top did I give myself like a concussion what the fuck
was that I'm gonna come back that way somebody said you feeling all right yeah
okay all right easy don't fuck it up he's lying he's not feeling okay it's a
lie oh there's the spatula right there I need to drop that stalactite it's
because it hangs from the ceiling stalagmites are the ones that grew up in
the ground tight like it has to stick on the ceiling you get it oh shit do a
colonoscopy stream I'm not gonna do a colonoscopy stream is that how invasive
that is no that's incredibly invasive so there we go wrap that around no although
I wonder if like educationally yeah I could do that on Twitter just and put
very specifically put like bird documentary music in the background no
100% no sure no what I mean you sure no I'm sure about not doing that all right
I got it did I miss any any secret spatulas wait I wanted to do that part
over there it's just a classic collectathon plagiarizing what somebody
said yesterday day before two days ago no three it was four days ago up there
all right how do I get up there wait how do I get that hold on shit hold on
how do I get over there do I have to land on these little spikes oh okay I
need Patrick to freeze oh well damn it there's a bus stop outside I come back
in here there's two socks in here that Patrick can get remember be funny all
right there you go there you go there's your every 37 minutes this people minus
doing that hey what man's trash is another man's treasure as they say right
guys and this the first box well it's all right I have to get every single
item who are there with is a bus stop right here all right I'm gonna do
Patrick but do I have to be Patrick we're gonna be Sandy wait I can't be
Sandy why not sorry but the carnival is closed it's different every level oh
wait do I get to play as a Squidward a pesky robot has taken over me ticket
booth and worse me money if you help me get rid of that no good robot I'll give
you a big reward is it a spatula it is a spatula me boy who higher can don't
hire me whoa I just all right I got it now we've really started the encounter
boy now we've really started the encounter how many um how many
crunch berries do I need mr. Krabs 3,000 yes I'm getting all the green ones
they're worth five each all right what we throwing this
Oh whack a tiki oh shit all right let's go oh wait cheats cheat cheat cheat
there you go what but like somebody's gonna see me
walk over to the ski ball machine and walk over gently to the left of the
machine and slowly place the ski ball into the 110 times in a row I'm gonna
get in trouble for that I can I do this over and over again Wow I'm telling the
Chuck E. Cheese manager well you can't because they're bankrupt that's rude I
love that place I like genuinely liked that place a lot when I was younger that
place is great there was like pizza and shit like why what the fuck it's
horrible you got to eat pizza and hang out with your friends it was so much fun
half the machines didn't work the dollar bill machine to get money somehow used
Canadian for some reason nobody figured it out why joystick was missing from
five of the machines how do I turn this off we're gonna ride it you know if
it's worth a lot of money I bet you some I bet you some of those Five Nights at
Freddy's tokens are fucking worth a lot of money
Chuck E. Cheese token yes this part was like a secret where if I stay in here
long enough is there like a break one or ride one or go down like a Mario pipe
or anything he's has more subscribers than you oh yeah there are also like a
multi-million dollar conglomerate that had like entertainment capitals all
over the fucking cities yeah sorry I got less subscribers than a multi-media
conglomerate with like 15,000 fucking people that have worked for that company
oh I thought skeeble smudge Bob I thought skeeble sponge Bob needs the
bubble ball I can't just walk up go on no get off me I don't have the bubble
ball I'm not I'm Patrick Patrick doesn't have the bubble balls sponge Bob
has the bubble ball but stop oh yes okay okay what is what is considered
illegal all right I can stand right at the top left arrow I fell that doesn't
count it's actual balls come on come on come on can I get one point don't do the
thing that happens all the time where you roll it and it bounces off the back
and rolls back and then you have to do the stupid embarrassing thing where you
go I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry and it like rolls down the fucking entire
arcade sorry I'm sorry I just get bounced back on me he's pretending do I
look like I'm pretending it's I'm trying to get it in there yeah in there how
did it go backwards how did I throw it backwards okay I did it
price what am I what's the deal here
what he points to I mean I have to get four in a row why did the game just lag
like I was connecting no I wasn't pretending I was trying to get super
points I've maybe get it at least one just got invaded you're gonna stop what
am I not but I do I not get a spatula from this or something cool stop slow
down I got it and I was gonna get the one in the middle right there stop it
stop this act this is that one act about acting I'm trying to play skeeball try
harder all right I got them all right or 877 the best actor at cheating at a
heads game putting that on my acting resume oh it says here that you were in
the background in a McDonald's commercial okay cool you're a guy that
sneezes in in this in this is doctors show okay cool it also says here really
good at pretending to play video games on twitch and be bad at them oh show me
let's act show me and I then he I like pick I have I hover with my hands in the
air oh no oh shit guys I'm sorry oh more oh I fell off again oops oh no I fell
off and died oh this is the best acting I've ever seen hey guys like I can't
see it I can't see where it is where is it why are you guys saying blind ha ha
oh man me I'm doing that I'm going backwards I get this oh the active
magnificent the way that he pretended to look down at the water the way that he
thought he could grab the spatula oh I'm such a fan wait what's this
oh you know even higher wait there's a ha ha ha ha ha ha wait wait wait hey hey
it's all the way he caressed and grabbed gently and under the hook like
he thought he could grab it oh it's just it's it's immaculate
Patrick can't grab that this is for this is going down why is it going down why
is this going down why is this going down am I too heavy it's supposed to go
down I gotta am I too fat I gotta be Patrick all right no I gotta be um all
right let me go be spongebob for this I'm gonna get the spatula that's right
there I don't know why I thought I could jump on that I don't know why I'm not
gonna I thought I could like jump on that and then jump off of it in the
nominees for best actor in a lead role are Daniel Day Lewis for Abraham Lincoln
Steve Buscemi for Ronald Reagan Jeremy Elbertson for guy pretending at
children's game only three this year wait I want to grab that and the winner
the Oscar goes to and I'm just sitting there holding the fucking seat like oh
is it gonna be Steve Buscemi for Ronald Reagan and I'm just like yeah this is
the 12th time that see and he's walking up and I'm just like he goes to like
shake I like yeah like what what you were just what a category here and and
I'm just like die fucking put my hand in the air and I spot the other way and I
like out of here I supposed to actually just bonds on this this is my first
germistry hey welcome to the stream you know I like to think we do things
differently here can I stand on this I gotta be Patrick for this why can't I
just change on the fly where's the GTA hold down off the d-pad I didn't have to
get in a bus stop when I was playing as Michael all right now I'm gonna be
Patrick it's a journalist complaint no it isn't it's a regular complaint the
journalist complaint is just a complaint it still is just complaints so I gotta
go like this and then throw this don't get hit by anything right that's the part
this is this interesting puzzle only a sock for that one I think that's worth
more than a sock hey check that out bachelor 12 o'clock it's like pushed me
I need to do face cam wait look at that I said gonna get down there shit okay
like oh go go go go go go go go go eight seven six five four three two one
knockout we're going oh wait go back back back back go back go back go back
go back go back go back go back go back go back I wasn't looking who is it on
zero oh fuck it's on zero I thought it was on I thought it was gonna be one
zero not on zero like one more you know I mean all right I got what I wanted
those it's supposed to be bumper cars crush them I lost this much help
bumper boats cleared so so what oh there's a Patrick jumper over there
supposed to clear all the stuff with robots oh use the Patrick Tinker totter
to go to the island in Goo Lagoon Beach wait what oh shit okay this is the ah
lost progress I didn't I'm about to get it right here look at I have to be
spongebob though your save got wiped quiet quiet all right did it all right
now I go back and mr. Krabs gives me a spatula right but should I not do that I
should go back and do the rest of the other stuff over there right
hold on I gotta sneeze it's not gonna happen is it I couldn't say I couldn't
do it I tried to hit the button all right my something my stream deck is
fucked up sometimes I'll press one of the buttons and it won't do anything and
then it'll do so it'll do it like two or three presses later oh wait this is how
you supposed to do this part yeah what's he doing I saw the green so I
wanted to go get it Patrick can do some shit over here right
but I didn't couldn't do before bless you hey thanks the only person that said
that here is your reward 36 spatulas okay get out of here I go in here is there
anything else I can do it here I guess I could go I think I did everything here
all right with a slide I can't do the slide where's the slide start slides
right here whoo don't touch them just go near them
like anything at the end exit exit purple I didn't get either one of them
dude again it's gonna kill me fuck damn I'm so pissed off right now I thought I
had more than I was just gonna tank the hits because I figured I had more help
that's a lot of crunchies whatever whatever plans whatever I don't get it
I got it all right let's get out of here you already lost the Oscar stop you
missed the spatula go back to Larry yeah I know I know I've got Larry has a
spatula for me I'm just it's just waiting for me to come get I thought I
could make it whatever just go to the beginning rewind to Larry I know I know
I know I start to see how many spatulas are in an area who is only one more
connect the towers this one secret spatula that I have what's wrong with my
voice just warp to it hey Larry connected all the towers and now I did
everything in goo lagoon blue lagoon has been complex if it is one I don't know
what it is but you know I'll take a majority of those all right what's next
on the list I like this let's get out of here let's go back to Bikini Bottom
there's still three spatulas I have not gotten in Bikini Bottom I'm not gonna
100% is no CBD stream no no wait has special oh there's a special up there I
get up there it's 40 I got 40 oh I don't have 40 I'll have there what I have 38
37 entering rock bottom let's go it's the same joke no I just said that's that
I don't like this place home of strange creatures and souvenir t-shirts rock
bottom streamer what do you mean not rock bottom that's omega lol true
the robots have stolen priceless artwork from the museum if you can return it
to me get all the artwork questions you aren't prepared to handle the answer to
whoa all right there are six pieces of artwork there's candy here what was that
all about that doesn't enemy this is a sleepy time robots bun bob must sneak
carefully when near him or he will wake stab in the back time for a little
sleepy snake I got a bad what happens when you die like okay imagine like
just being asleep and die like what happens what happens oh just that just
open it up with that you know hey guys yeah we're gonna play spongebob battle
for bikini bottom stream number two yeah welcome to the stream and have lots of
fun collecting spatulas what happens when you die these platforms will
collapse unless spongebob sneaks across them very carefully got it I got lots of
these I should probably spend them just yeah there's a stealth level I don't know
about this one I don't know about this level I don't like sneaky stealth levels
we'll see if it changes my mind okay here we go this little scared the fuck
out of me when I was a kid did it why doesn't I know why because the big scary
robot that you have to sneak by I get it I get that I jump yes doesn't mean you
live I know how it work let's go
the robots are plundering rock bottoms museum but they've broken the roadway
leading up there you'll have to be clever and find another route to get in
what if I lick all these stamps and mail myself good work but perhaps being
sneaky would oh spongebob that'll never work I don't never work you'll suffocate
in the box that point oh wait okay okay does it matter if I don't sneak here can
I just kill him I just walked by him he activated shield or something if I don't
up ooh that's special rare away from me all right well there's this one there
was shirt oh yeah that's right hey oh Sandy I have to get Sandy and then she'll
be able to jump where's the bus stop I'm up there can't get up there okay well
over here just jump I can't just jump I won't make it go to hell I go to hell I
go to hell come on electro zap them but another one didn't have a snickers you're
not you that what you mean by that I know you didn't say that but I feel like
that's what you meant who am I done would you what would you classify me
all right we got more of these you're Dean dingus you're short let me tell you
something I can't wait to go to twitchcon like next year I'm gonna have
like five inch inserts and I'm gonna be like six feet tall I'm gonna fuck with
all of you I need to get the bus stop anybody see a bus stop anywhere for me
pull up to and Sandy how does that how do we're gonna go did you break your
back by trying to be taller I would say ban that person but okay let him let
him let him have it no no not punching no stop it's not what I meant whoa okay
now I know what happens if you get spotted purple in there ah okay so can
I what does this do what does this go this goes back okay that was dumb this
goes back here so now I can go this way press this button and what does that do
oh I activated another button there it is oh shit do I need to keep going fast
oops I've been the ball still saves down here
bullshit hey we're going up up up whoo
cannon destroyed now what um did that do for me
just got rid of the cannon I make this okay I can I didn't think I could make
them I go up why though why though why though why oh right I forgot he could do
this guys it's been like three days I forgot spongebob had that ability the
anytime don't say anything let him figure it out no help me I think I could
probably do it no all right so this is gonna go to where I get to jump from
here to here and then fight fight hey someone better make good use all these
holy shit sandy you almost blew it okay then we go ooh but spatula over there
too wait oh look at that okay um all right one thing to do one thing at a
time what do I do first I'm gonna do I feel bad that stuff like this because I
have like three or four places to go that all makes sense ah I want to go
over there okay I'm just gonna go this way you get the one that I know I need
to get reset no no no and he can't wait we go look what you've done you mean
get the puzzle piece who traveled to the museum all right I don't know no no no
not traveling to the museum I'm gonna go do the other sandy related tasks what
else gonna do is sandy get some of the paintings we are I didn't want to do
that but I guess I'm here wait this is gonna work out check this out ready this
will work out all right the spatula is over there so theoretically now this is
just my theory of mine I'm gonna go up high double jump I fucked it up hold on
you can't do it forever okay you can't do it forever I got it what you're
cheating that's why hold on wait just one fucking second can't jump on fuck it
fuck it all right done get me back up there and I'm gonna go hold on we need
to press a button I said what's this for get over there what is what's the
practical use of this well I mean nothing's as good as Texas barbecue
sauce so that's kind of unfair go up here again I get it oh I just have to
keep going return the museum's art get to the museum go in the museum all right
I'm just gonna go in the museum I guess I'm taking too much time running
around looking at stuff I'm just going to the museum stop what I'm going in the
museum I'm going to the museum as Sandy let's go I could go on that I could go
on that say warn me if that sponge kid comes back again okay this looks tricky
say warn me if that's why do I have to activate this with spongebob you're
pronouncing it wrong it's sponge it's spongebob right yeah yeah I do that I
deactivate it go back activate it activate the quest
here no this is my second job I work see now listen if you want to reach the
golden spatula you need to shut off the museum's security system you have to
iron those pants or are they wrinkle-free unlike you pay attention kid
this is serious stuff now if we don't get this robot thing resolved shady
shoals will shut down and I'll have to move back in with my wife and his four
screaming kids now you see that vent on the other side of the museum that's
where you exit the museum good luck kid hmm I just feel like this is what Popeye
and olive oil's kid would look like they have a half a kid it did no they didn't
I won't let you down barnacle boy who is Popeye you don't know Popeye is what
guys I'll give you I'll give you some help they use the same soundtrack in
spongebob that they do in Popeye same theme nautical theme why are you saying
what do you mean pop Popeye Popeye what am I saying Popeye Popeye all right guys
what wouldn't like a British person says like Popeye so I said pop did you hear
that he said pop Popeye it's not Popeye it's Popeye am I dead are you British
although I haven't I have an accent now I gotta go that way it's gonna be hard
I'm sorry this is gonna be hot hey what does he change stop what the fuck what
the fuck stop let go get off my brother fighting over a toy no I want to play
with it get off stop I fucking went too early you just got a combo yeah it takes
this time I'm not gonna get it smashed okay one two three four five six seven
do you see how long that takes get off of that that's not a classic Mario three
to four seconds that was like eight seconds talk under there holy shit why
is it even going only mode why is it eat boat only look oh this is wait get the
suck collect all the collective arms and these people are counting oh right
right right oh my goodness turn it back on turn it back on just for a minute
you'll still stop purple in there one two three four five six seven eight nine
10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 is so good 23 24 25 26 27 but when you
get to 27 just feels at all the tongue it feels so good 28 29 30 so glad I got
to get that out not any fucking distractions okay now actually don't turn
it on because now it's gonna be a shit show I have ruined the rest of the
stream for all you for all you like regular guys that just wanted to hang
out and watch and not like count to 500 I'm sorry that I just destroyed
everything I've ruined everything the whole stream is ruined now I'm sorry I
fucked up the rest of the whole day I gotta get up there you really did I know
I know I did it's okay I'll accept this one I'll accept it I'll accept it don't
nobody be mad at me though okay I don't like we feel I'm bad at me nobody be
mad at me okay I will take emote only mode off as long as everybody promises
not to be mad at me okay but don't be mad at me okay all right don't turn it
off yet but them really let them really marinate in this oh monsters that thing
emote is so ugly why am I following this trend lately with like the last few
emotes have just been oh never that like wicked ugly face about ugly Jeremy is a
Jeremy's wicked fucking ugly put that as an emote all right the next emote I put
up is gonna be like a wicked handsome face of mine it's gonna be called
German normal but like German looking good 39 39 oh these things break all
right all right okay okay okay okay what's up there a sock all right so you
guys there you go now you can't be mad at me you promised ruined it by the way
if you want to know what's on tap for tomorrow I've got the PlayStation 3 2012
Olympic Games the video game quite interesting if I do not complete
spongebob we'll finish it move on to the Olympics say that was not a hard jump a
how would I miss that I don't know I'm still angry sorry just don't just stop
being I told you not to be angry with you're a liar I'm lying about the like
Olympics are lying about that I'll finish spongebob I'll get there by the
end of the day tomorrow today I don't know whatever I got to get up there
quick cuz I got a jump don't ruin this for me this guy's ruining this way
ruined it like I've ruined it for me I can't get up there now yes I can use the
bubble bowl guys remember if it does it's the most accidental accidental pog
no all the way at the beginning wait I can go in here that was equivalent
exchange equivalent exchange for every action there must be an equal opposite
reaction behind me that's Newton's third law that's not alchemy the same fucking
thing yeah Newton smashed a piece of iron into his head over and over again
and he thought it was gonna make gold that have been like breathed on it or
something whatever his law was they were all fucking alchemists they all like
we're trying to turn iron and gold and they are yeah look at what I can do they
painted iron yellow and shit so people see I did that slamming fucking homemade
whiskey out of a fucking jar I need Sandy now I was looking at chat I was
looking I didn't think we were gonna be on a slide wait I want to be Sandy how
am I gonna get that up there I don't want to do this all right I'm not gonna
go for any skips just go for can I go backwards and go in there again just
get the all right I'm done just do the slide don't do anything stupid don't
make any jumps or anything
that's an interstellar joke I don't know what that means
trench of advanced darkness huh sounds dark okay Gary I'll be extra extra
careful meow hey Gary what do you say we go for an adventure
meow meow stop I go backwards now I can I go up the slide and go back let me do
the fucking dumb thing I want to do anybody feel like I'm doing that thing
in Mario Kart when you know you've got you're in last place and you got lapped
already and you turn around to go the wrong way to just drive into people in
first place because you're just fucking salty this should be a thing like
like he too should come over and just be like yeah I cut this shit after like 30
seconds if you have a wrong way thing on your screen for more than 10 seconds you
shouldn't be able to hold on all right well just now we could do it as Sandy
oh it's time to I'm gonna be spongebob oh what the hell all that time gone it
was all that time gone all that time the precious time mounted why you
pronouncing it wrong isn't his name is lucky to how am I saying it wrong
lucky to lock it to what is it this game's fucking too loud for me lock it
to
oh it's lucky to lucky to lock it to is it no it's not it's lucky to do I
actually have to be spongebob why even give me the opportunity to change well I
don't know but I'm I'm in trouble here how do I can't be spongebob X is
barbecue I love that stuff is the bus stop with the bus stop I passed it
oh he's so fucking stupid I'm gonna go I'll be back in like 20 minutes I got to
get up I gotta get up I can't watch him do it anymore I'll be back to our God
damn it Jeremy be back watch out sneaky leave leave you better not punch me that
2400 bungee where's it oh it's just a sock that's the sock but that was over
two thousand dollars for a sock no I would say that's not where I command you
to bring Sandy to me for this next job I can do that that I get up there how do
I get up there you go up yeah but I only want to help help crush you all under my
eyes to power what was that nothing say see those lasers they're okay I'll try
Oh I got it I got it I got it I think I got it I'm down okay calm down this is
fucking crazy exciting yep there was a narcissist he can't help but tell people
to look at him and well only one more painting and I get another spatula is
this the time of the stream when the dudes actually having like kind of a
fun time and he just always falls back to the like the oh he's gonna say like
this game sucks haha that way are we there yet I'm not sure have I arrived on
time it is what time is it is it is it Jeremy's playing a puzzle platforming
kind of game like platformer collecting game and he like oh this game fucking
sucks right like he makes that funny joke he does every time he plays a 3d
platformer sick of him you don't sound sober Jeremy are you okay yeah oh yes I
am I'm I'm as sober as a stone I missus puff has got a spatula for me pretty
good 5g sound stones yeah you are right this dudes on painkillers they're not
got it stop saying that so true but don't don't say that anymore I was the
last one yeah that one we got I need this one over over here right fuck am I
doing and where's that last one one two three okay so I gotta go that way oh
free clams I jump into that what the heck are do you trust a guy that says
heck oh the heck oh heck I say that a lot we trust you don't do that to me
why'd you move forward you don't do anything with the same vibe as sorcery
probably I would like to mean sorcery is fucking awesome I love that game all
right what did that plot I got to go to that platform with the red circle on it
what did that go where was that back here when is little move what I don't
know what you're saying I promised something it's another slide that's not
what did I wait what did I promise isn't this the beginning of the level what am
I looking for here did I miss it I'd be out there it is okay how do I get over
there have to be spongebob to get over there have to go around finish saw oh
I'm not gonna finish saw I'm just gonna walk through a shotgun thing again let
my head blow up what do you mean everybody leave I'm not gonna why would
I finish saw the game was very very very poor look how about this I'll play saw
two there's another one I don't think I can make this I guess I can hey just
wrangle I have to be alright I got the skip maybe I'll stay not sure maybe here
we are play ace attorney no no while I can't place attorney I wonder I won't do
it this is hmm I don't want to play this turn no I'm not playing a story I don't
want to there it is that's it no I don't want to play history I don't want you why
I don't want objection to that what the hell I just killed you doesn't care
about us I do I don't I fucked that up what I was trying to say is I just don't
I was trying to say I don't want to play it's attorney I was gonna say no I don't
want to play ace attorney oh whatever I stop stop it stop it stop it emote only
emote only quick before I have to be held accountable for my actions emote
only dude I think he's on drugs I am NOT all right stop I am NOT on drugs are
you're saying and I know you are I can see somebody put fireman as somebody
put like yeah like what's this was me like a fireman fireman like oh he's like
blaze it up like no stop that don't do that like 420 no stop that I fucking know
what you're doing I'll do that face where it's like his face is we get
fucked up because he's on like drugs and shit don't do that I know what you're
doing I don't like to see turn off emote only mode that they're fucking with me
turn it off you missed a spatula wait what I did not miss a spatula this chat
sucks don't say that because I just read that and now they think I said it
well I was gonna try but I say fuck it all right you know what's crazy I have
not even tried it once I have not done one yeah with shaking my throat I haven't
done it once because I'm afraid I'm scared I'm scared it's not gonna be good
enough and everyone's gonna minus 2 and be like holy shit that was so
embarrassing it's so bad I can you believe I haven't even attempted it's
been like 8 plus stream hours on this game and I haven't even attempted it it
has to be a record for a sponge Bob is on screen I'm gonna do it right where
are we out here oh this is this is the downtown spot like a spring breeze wait
a minute oh shit nice okay so you see the tracks go this way and they well
made it I can't hey mr. Krabs what are you doing well I could have sworn me I
saw a golden spatula here a minute ago but I think it fell down this chat
stand you I'm what down the slide it might have broken its leg I've got to
save it the heck go boy go save that poor spatula I'd be a different character
sand I got I'm gonna be sandy wait I press that button all right press the
button oh okay we gotta go now is this a kids game I don't know is Mario kids
game this Mario 60 okay is Mario Odyssey a kids game well yes it is all right
Mario Odyssey is a kids game let me just make sure I get that correct so
therefore all games that are platformers 3d platformers are kids games
right Simpsons hit and run yes no wrong no no what's a 3d platform move that is
like this that's not a kids game that bunker yes okay so take the one game
okay delete conquer what is it it's no game like doom that plays like this Dex
Dex is not a 3d platformer and what are you talking about it's a cartoon
character Dex is like a like a cartoon character and this is knee wait shit is
he just a guy code I was gonna say rabbit so did I go he was like a suit
does he have a British accent it's the guy go gecko isn't it
this gex have a British accent I was just talk no yes he does and by the way
to the one person that said plague lover no by the way I'm not talking about
right now I'm talking about like seven days ago like six days ago somebody said
hey plague lover and I was like yeah okay what do we got return the museum's
art lasers are fun and good for you wait I didn't get this I have to talk to
plankton told you you missed one I'm always gonna take a look okay now we go
back to the museum's art I'm just collecting I'm just collecting mad
spatulas I left no strange glowing stone unturned well now nice work spongebob
there's your reward 44 I got 40 now I can do that one with 40 I missed one not
on this task it's alright I can oh I can miss one I can miss one I've got to turn
in some socks to Patrick just do that yeah like why even do this okay I went
by these really fast and I saw I thought it said ambush Squidward like kill
Squidward all right let's go to here okay Patrick I've got a sock for you
I don't speak Italian every time doesn't it all right 45 nice how many socks do I
have seven should I buy another one from mr. Krabs oh yeah I was the one that's
40 and in there went to rock bottom sand mountain or oh there's one on top of
this this is a golden underwear a bit yeah let's go they all look like they
made it to ice cream I love this game ice cream cake material more important I
make that clear
sponge Bob's in for a rough ride and I'm back the button on his back he's got a
button on his back so we're gonna get dizzy
made himself dizzy he's down there me you just posted in post anything he's
not so hard wait I gotta be sandy for something I'm gonna swing around
probably I'm gonna die at least four times make sure I don't die once that's
the bar sound yep what is Sandy going to do to get sponge Bob unfrozen great
barrier reef
taking a beating out there great power your reef that could melt anything I
played third of the bosses in every spider-man video game I know how this
works oh come on come on land land okay now we have to instantly kills as an
instant kill or this one it's an instant kill what is sandy going to do to get
I don't know it was an instant kill so I have to stay on these and sometimes it's
not gonna be good sometimes it's not gonna be right all right where they
placed okay here we go don't touch it just okay so what can I lasso him can't
lasso him from here all right you just got to be good you just got to be good
you just got to be good smooth all right go down okay okay okay okay I can't get
over there oh yeah I know very funny very funny very funny we can see your
balls yeah very funny oh what kind of camera would I need to have here what
kind of camera angle and what what is just pointing down well I do that right
there right there yep I didn't get him am I dead no I get it okay so you have
to wait till he goes oh come on all right I get it I get it I get it I get it I
just just survive that's a lot explode oh that hurt hold on you touch it on the
ground oh yeah right that's some like Warcraft mage bullshit I happen to be
targeting you so the fucking frostbolt just followed you around three walls
quick go hit the router why oh my computer fucked up but I have a fucked
up computer
oh shit yeah I have dropped some frames so no the internet oh no the internet
problems are back oh yeah I'm sorry plankton the chum bucket lab is locked
up now I'm on fucking fiber that shit ain't happening anymore
just a little it's a couple of bumps sometimes it's all right oh okay I mean
so that's the boss to get to the third area security system I decided myself
it makes me so proud it was meant to keep out the hateful throngs of the
unwashed unfortunately I never figured I'd be on this side of it your stream is
down oh what the fuck so what are you gonna do plankton we of course meaning
you we're gonna have to go out there and get those golden spatulas or I'll never
get back into the chum bucket to regain control of my robots what was that oh I
said will I ever get back into the chum bucket to stay in all my parts yeah
something's fishy here like that all right now I get there there's
spatulas over here uh-huh I've been trying to get this one for the last like
three days you're gonna do that to me right now what wait hey because that
might you just put me in the same spot stop touching me that's not how you do
it
button oh shit he's getting fibered no no no no no don't worry it's not don't
worry super pinky shake on it I would if I had pinkies
here I'll blow you some yeah maybe later only attention spongebob this bubbles a
doozy paying my entire salary and attention when you're not moving press
this button and you'll blow a bubble that you can steer it flies through the
air aim carefully though you've only got a few seconds of flight time before the
bubble pops you move sorry wait okay wait it's underwear up there wait does
this count as me does this count as my body damn it I gotta get on top of the
wait hold on it's like yeah I'm just so so engrossed in the drones camera it's
like oh wait that's actually coming for me right 50 what is this
oh that was a lot help forest do I have 46 I don't know all right let's go I
want to go in the Krusty Krab 60 hit the buttons hold on I want to talk to Mr.
Krabs you don't look so good hit the buttons hold on I want to talk to Mr.
Krabs you gotta help me boy the Krusty Krab's been overrun by a bunch of them
hoodlum robots of yours they've booted me out and worse they've got hold me
beautiful shiny object see filing the Krusty Krab is there no end to their
evil what are we going to do mr. Krabs we meaning you are going to clear the
robots out get me back me restaurant and most importantly rescue me money okay
I'll handle it mr. crab are you ready kids
Oh don't do it was do I have to fucking hold on if it keeps up I'm gonna turn
off my fucking VPN I know that's what is happening trust me I know I really
probably should just miss the launch this guy over here fuck I missed he's
using Netflix to watch it and I did it I'll take my spatula I mean the one cool
thing is I've dropped 1,337 frames somebody is gonna be like happy about
that I think someone will be happy about it all right did I miss anything else
in here left left oh the left what's left something left destroy the whole
Krusty Krab I don't want to do that that's me I'll get these though remote
watches my hero academia with a VPN why would you need a VPN to watch my hero
academia VPN I did it where's my spatula you had me worried there for a bit boy
worried for me money of course here take this as your why would you need a
VPN to stream I don't I use it all right listen I use a VPN for the added extra
security and bullet point everyone I use it for bullet point number two and I use
it for bullet point number three on their website okay okay I got a spatula
all right let's go I bet he uses no I don't use that company I don't use that
company I don't use that company I don't use that company I don't use that
company denial well whatever I do whatever company you think I use sure I
use it how's that is that better he's a Chad VPN subscriber I feel like a new
sponge omega lol he does but what is this what do I do with why should I be
this it's I don't have 60 but wait a minute why is this I'm gonna be the ball
here for no reason I can't go in the boat school may I help you 40,000 shiny
objects 40,000 for what what does that do we get to watch a one full episode of
spongebob I feel like that's what's in there help all right let's go to 48
all right let's go to urban up in I got this zip forming right on top of my
above my upper lip it's driving me nuts it's under the skin and it just for here
yes whoa kitchen 75 authorities have confirmed that the robots running amok
through bikini bottom are indeed coming from the chum bucket yes right where
you're standing yes known for the cream and then stop on your children and stop
on your children's children this has been a bikini bottom news flash that's
fucked up old meme well up there up 34 man that's good one can't reach these
oh what I found behind the oven yeah cool excellent you found the Horatrix
this hurt yep go to Sand Mountain Sand Mountain Sand Mountain Sand Mountain
okay saying go back to the circle circle this a bunch of times it's like a secret
if I have to do like circle around a bunch of times wait sponge hold on a
minute
sicko we'd sleep comes to me so Bob can be found in sponge pogs that's a sponge
pog dream bubbles I'm surrounded by dream bubbles wonder what that means hey
thank you Vita for the tense ups welcome ten new subscribers to sure about it at
hives channel thank you Vita Vita impender of a row ten welcome new
germamites thanks Gary it does make me look more rugged doesn't it more tasks
well I could use more golden spatulas this is the best level in the game this is the
hardest level in the game is it the best level or is the hardest or is it both
you mean each dream bubble has a golden spatula in it well yes Gary I'll be
careful oh dear well I can already take a look already missed yeah you think
you're gonna be able to hide underwear oh I don't know why I thought that was
better what's an s-verb I don't know how do I get it from oh wait I'm gonna jump
on I go now now now now don't go now go now and then go now not now go back go
back go back Mario Sunshine yeah all right I'm gonna go back he's going to
rage I don't think I am here we go where's the double jump I've gone then
what if I go now this is gonna be hard wait you dick that was a dickhead thing
that was a dickhead thing I'm sorry that was a dickhead thing come on I was gonna
jump quick so should I just wait till he does his move all right I'm gonna wait
okay then you fire fire fire fire fire fire don't go and then when excuse me
um now there's about now this fucking puddle of mud there that doesn't fit on
there all right so you got to go quick don't wait just go you go literally
right now there it is how do I kill him how do I kill him we're going this way
how do I kill that guy okay he's dead now what now this moves oh shit
really that's not gonna work okay push it over there push it over and then jump
on it slowly oh come on dude I do what was this perception there okay hold on
wait I gotta get on it I'm going in front of it wait it's gonna slow okay
hold it slowly just goes down by itself I have to jump off from here how did I
not get that stay right there don't thank you if he okay we got that one now
we go this way is this a slide slow down don't go fast I need a checkpoint
that boy there we go and a thousand clams to open this door and it did
nothing oh wait a minute did that do I have to go in Sandy's dream house oh
shit yep I need that underwear thank you okay let's go in Sandy's dream house
soon guess things Sandy grows weed in there ha ha ha just kidding lol ha ha ha
all right let's go into Sandy's dream what the hell does everybody have their
own dream world oh dear wow your dream is massive everything in Texas is big
even dream the barbecue then you're just the right person to reach the spatula on
top of that golden acorn I'll try
I'll get that spatula faster than a Texas jackrabbit crossing a four-lane
highway all right I'm gonna go for it oh shit I don't know how am I going up this
slide what did I was that I was trying to do like I'm trying to be like
cheeky this is just a surf map yeah it is it's just like a TF2 or it's like a
CS go surf map and I was terrible at those I went right last time let's go
this way I just had Sandy have a dream of a manure wait a minute
2800 open this all right let's go
this is a commentary youtuber what are you talking about I was a commentary
youtuber for like six years
that's all I needed here what can I ever just dream normal dreams tricky tricky
I'll take that spatula now okay no it's ice I thought it was that goo stuff
there's a golden spatula on the other side if you can get me here that's kind
of two things I just sit here and do this shit if the stream wasn't on I'd
be doing the same thing I told you yeah Kim talks about this luck Kim will what
will be like in the other room and she'll just hear me in here just saying
the same like fucking ten words over and over guys that I would be doing this
more if the stream wasn't on I'm trying to not do it you know how many times I
would say but go get that go get that golden spatula golden spatula hold it I
would say like a thousand times I'm trying to not do it you're only getting
it sometimes I watched infinity war guys and I said I know what it's like to lose
I've spent like five days doing it over and over again and I was driving her
crazy all right I gotta finish the slide two ways to go
deceiving how's that me oh that guy gotta be the best bachelor at the end of
this right whoa whoa oh yeah whoa whoa wait go drag over there I'm going over
there doc now I've got to wait this is trampoline back here right wait what's
over here you gotta look around you gotta at least take a look and get there
no I can't this place is crazy what all right we're good getting thinner getting
a lot thinner turning into one of those coin games of the arcade that you push
it down that metal mechanic ism it has to land on the one spot whoa it just
threw me straight down this is long oh no checkpoint thank goodness gonna get
me this time maybe next time watch out for the cow it's gonna be right in my
face yes there it is nice okay cool there's that one does Sandy have any
more here across the dreamscape super bonds see any not have this where's it
go oh no don't put me up here have the other box all right just go no it's the
other way all right it's gotta go all right I know what way it goes now wait
isn't this gonna take me right do about this I think I'm just stuck right I'm
just Lee oh no no I can I know what I can do I know what I can do oh that's
what you guys when you saying teleport I thought you meant with the box all right
let's go get out of here he floats he floats there's one over there let's go
to it you guys are having a good day no I am well this sucks wait wait wait what
checkpoint huh I'm looking just down I need to look forward oh it's right there
wait I gotta get that what the fuck I got it so we can either go we can go in
Squidward's dream or we can go down here okay I'm going down here I said it
doesn't matter just go I'll get there nice okay I want to get all spongebob's
first go back I'm well I want to get all of spongebob's shit first there's one
right there you just call me a hater wait oh no fine I gotta go now oh fuck I
had an opportunity Patrick's dream wait box nice see I wanted to get this one
smells like all right I think I got all the spongebob one all right now that's
all the ones in like the open world let's go back here Patrick's dream I gotta
pass my test before you get this golden spatula very well sir challenge
accepted find it he's gonna it's gonna be on it behind a couch or something
it's gonna be right in front of him you're holding it yeah this is just like
a funny thing Patrick's dumb Patrick's stupid here look he hid it behind his
back that's hard yes I already saw the challenge you did you already gave it to
me why yeah why is Patrick in this weird solo space they're really dark and
scary and depressing in here why is Patrick at the pearly gates wake up it's
gonna be something it's gonna be secret right it's the four Kings yeah the only
thing we need in this room is
let's go back to Squidward's dream teleport teleport unit you want to know a word
that's fun to say teleport that's a fun radio word teleport teleport sources say
that he was teleporting around that's a guy if you're a news broadcaster or you
love to say that one I'm just saying that has a lot of confidence the the
consonants in the middle there make it fun to say in a radio sense it's old
material that's not all it's just that's every day that's everyday material
that's me mr. Krabs is dreaming of the Krusty Krab there's a lot of enemies
here a surprise I can't escape work anywhere lunch rush I better grab my
hat and get that spatula and get us out of here it's like a shiny golden
toothpick that holds together the bun of we don't have time for this all right
so just get up there climb the buns destroy the robot machine at the spatula
are you ready kids oh are you ready get to them I got it no don't even fight
them they're gonna keep respawning I kill them maybe all first oh I mean
surrounded I don't think I can I have to kill them wait wait well I know what
to do I know what to do come on man let's go in the bun I know to die no
to do I'm just shoot the I'm gonna rocket watch what I hit can't do it
they slow it's them all hey why that bun way the buns moving when they die a lot
of money how is that campfire camper hey you do it your way I'm gonna do it my
way my way is rocket okay we got an opportunity more wait all right is the
lettuce I'm going for that I'm going for it all right there's one down talk over
there okay one dad how are they shooting fire underwater I don't know this new
tuber it's gonna respond anything else happening here not really I kill more
of these little guys okay oh there's the lettuce okay there's that one I can do
them both president before waiting room nope nope nope get that out of your
head right now oh no no nope no I can't fucking believe it what did I do what
the fuck am I doing I don't know why I did that I don't know what I did I don't
know what the fuck I was doing I don't know what happened I seriously just like
fucking jumped off the edge I just was like trying to go fast I'm so mad right
now like what the hell just happened what happens I don't like a little too
early right now all right don't die to this shit stop oh this part sucks why
you're not blocking this don't block it sponge Bob okay no more fucking around
what you hit me why would I do that I'm okay you're using 2007 tactics I'm
trying to figure out what then we mean by that I'm staying up here where it's
safe this guy's got to die though I don't want him to respawn come on hurry
for the bubble huh spawning the bubble right when I get there stop camping all
right fine I'll go down there I won't camp anymore
yep I've done a lot of them thank you today I've done a lot of them I don't
like I guess I'm gonna look I'm pulling that out way too often I think is it
there okay squeezed a little too much air out of me get out of here okay don't
explode all right give me my spatula Squidward punk 56 looking good
by Squidward finally everybody wait by the Squidward okay let's keep going back
I I could have been almost minute what about the sock oh you missed a sock you
imbecile I look I had that can only pay attention to so many things I'll go get
it it's down here ten socks now Ruto run that's pretty good I like it give that
person a dude like what the fuck good Squidward's dream what was he doing over
in the other dream how many dreams he had boy covering your ears why does
Squidward's dream mr. Krabs is in it but in mr. Krabs his dream Squidward's in it
okay that's right that's what I'm saying
or at least it feels like it do you think you can make it across this sheet
of music to the golden spatula and Squidward's big nose don't worry mr.
Krabs I'll end this challenge on a high note good luck boy when you wake him up
try to wake him up I'm running out of aspirin this looks like hell okay how
much help is another slide it's not what is it then is this the theme song is it
gonna break ah I'm trying to go to who lives oh I got it I'm ready why don't
jump right into that oh shit okay hold on you gotta wait
somebody should be funny I'm trying to beat a game anyone has to pull like
magic magician sheets out of my hand well I'm trying to pick SpongeBob this
is a tricky level take some skill this shit oh I have to walk on it wait a
second do I have to walk on this shit bounce and okay it went away from me
you dick all right just wait wait for one revolution oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
dear get away to the middle don't go yet okay go now no why did I go that's the
worst time to go go back all right go now wait a minute what's that you dumb
fucking idiot wait for one revolution oh shit oh no there's a purple 57 I missed
a sock where I did right I'll get it where is it whatever whatever where is
it okay I gotta go this way a good thing I got the checkpoint where's it play a
triple-a game for fuck's sake the house this is a triple-a game this is
SpongeBob SquarePants it's a triple-a cartoon where's the sock oh above me
that trampoline right there I got it right here all right where is it over
there here we go we're good get me out I'm ready to come up pull me out oh come
on dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb I wanted to walk out the fucking front
door I'm going out the front door by the way what triple-a games have come
out that are worth playing besides ghosts of Shima does one come out in the
last three months all right what do I go how am I doing here okay I did it all I
got them all huh damn okay I I can't they all be like this wait there was
one small there was a section I didn't go to where was that it's like up here
isn't it talk talk talk talk talk I don't get every sock there's like a
portion that where does it where is it where is it yes you do I don't I don't
there was like a big cluster of these hold on that's the same exact spot got
the fuck up listen to us where's the sock I need a bigger view all right
where is it where is it it's in Sandy's dream oh nah nah that was fun all right
speaking of socks let's give it to Patrick cuz I have 10 yeah all right with
58 I unlock this 50 I go back to Patrick 59 what's your favorite subject
in school I didn't like any of it it's your honor is your honest answer I mean
maybe oh Sand Mountain everyone's been waiting you've been waiting all day for
sand mountain where sea creatures go to enjoy an afternoon of falling down big
cupcake 1500 1500 1500 okay am I glad you're here I need to borrow your
toothbrush again
oh yeah a lot of times I know you wouldn't mind that's disgusting what do
I care I'm a wreck anyways I try and get some exercise to run so does that
also imply that he breaks into Squidward's home and goes into his
bathroom and like takes a big shit and then brushes his teeth because of a
toothbrush no it's those blasted robots they've taken over the ski slopes how
can I ski with those ugly things beating everyone up listen Spongebob you've got
to help me I'm gonna lose my marbles if I don't get some it's implied if you keep
your marbles in a bag they don't get lost as often yeah and his shit I mean
you're talking about like Krabby Patties and jellyfish I don't think Spongebob
eats very much kale eats cheeseburgers all day doesn't eat anything else done
I'm eating you asshole I didn't say anything did I what did I say I said that
he doesn't eat very much like kale like you know if you know what I mean you
know what I mean barn like that it was I didn't say like maybe I did not kind of
not really he takes a giant shit that's what you said but that's not even like
gross lift ticket to guppy mound wait are there any things just here oh okay
wait so uh oh oh all right let's be standing she crushed everyone like a
plankton thing go go go go go go go I forgot everyone hates that I thought
we were gonna be so impressed when I did the doi doi doi thing you guys remember
that I'm like two years ago I thought it was gonna be so impressive everyone's
gonna be like well how the fuck is he doing that it's so cool I need to get
fun ball can I grab that find out how do I get Spongebob up there their bus stop
up here please do it please do it no we can Sandy do this no only Spongebob
right do it I can't do it people it's gonna piss off so many fucking people do
it do it who cares oh my god all right people that hate this just be ready here
it comes how do you do it no I can't I'm not gonna give you the story we've
already done this like three years ago
isn't there a safer way give me the tutorial no safety with you people hmm
I suppose you could bungee down wait would you like to pay $2,500 no I
wouldn't I already did it you're gonna be double pay okay so those I got two I
got 60 spatulas how many sponsors are in the game 100 120 somebody told me the
other day what was it I mean I have to be getting to game completion then huh
what's game completion 65 80 70 70 75 oh cuz the last door 75 all right we'll
probably get it today
I think we'll get there but if you can beat my time down the hill I'll give you
a golden spatula eat my time yeah 70 seconds I don't know what I just did I
don't know what I did like this bowling ball the snowball well this one's a
little tougher why did I say it louder I don't know all right don't get hit too
many times try to go on the right oh shit okay easy I got it fine when I turn
to miss his puppy snake that was not bad I'm spending a lot of these 40,000
I don't think I'm gonna have 40,000 I doubt I'm gonna have 40,000 of those
shells go to the theater that seems kind of impossible you got a grind is it
worth what if what's in there is it worth it do we actually get to see full
episode of SpongeBob it's not worth it spatula in here whoo this is a fake how
does this look fake the game story is a full episode kind of back to Sand
Mountain let's go this is pops this is pops where's mrs. pops very beginning of
level where's mrs. pops she bailed no she didn't when she like right here did
I've run by her no I didn't no I didn't where is she wouldn't she write the
beginning right at the beginning of the first mountain it was right in the door
I was supposed to go in the bucket basket box thank you 62 very nice all
right on to place number two whoa nice pretending thanks dude means a lot that
you think that thank you so this is everybody's favorite level why well what
is here that oh cuz it's a slide level I get it now I know everybody likes this
so much because it's just a bunch of slide like the wind and float like a
CB if you can beat my time down the hill I'll give you a golden spatula okay 110
seconds this time should have gone up top left damn it breakthrough no it's
okay wait eight snowmen I don't know that was a task shit oh fucking faster I
can't I'm holding up on the deep end I guess it's this way I feel like I'm going
back up the mountain they go the wrong way no this feels close closer than it
should be five four three two what hey I didn't go this way I didn't do the skip
just added time fucking wonderful great I should just went the right way I'm
gonna lose again yes go the right way I'm just gonna go the right way come on
going right I went left last time let's see if this helps 65 63 62 holy shit
that was weird right don't turn we'll go all right I got 41 what did I come here
last time 26 why did I lose why did he pop my tongue I gotta skip this is hard
damn okay that's worse yeah well I dub the snowman stop me in my tracks
completely I'm not hitting any boxes don't touch anything right don't touch
anything okay shit don't touch any snowman right side right the middle good
all right go go go all right four three two what the fuck matter I just need to
power through okay I can skip it I could skip that portion I can do it I can skip
that one I have to get on the rock oh come on bro oh come on bro you go off
the if you go off the track you fall you do you can't all right I'm going I got
it but lose it speed if I double jump let's go this way it's risky I jump I
don't know I can jump away I could jump down I think all right I can go down
from there I need some good skips right now skip anything here okay just go
straight down okay straight straight through great straight through the one
right here I got it I got it I've set six five four three two yeah I'm so I'm
so good so bad so good I'm bad I'm so good spatula and I get way I get two
spatulas this is sick German never sounds like a real human being what does
that mean I don't sound like a human being like a fake person more so than
any other streamer you fucking here on the internet how do I sound like a
fake person are you just so used to hearing fake people that are real person
like me a real guy sounds weird to you it's like a ventriloquist dummy so you
think I sound like when somebody's talking through the other guy and he's
trying to make his keepers lips together I'll give you a golden spatula if you
can beat my time so you guys think that I talk like this this is how I talk on a
regular basis oh it sure is cold outside how's the weather as my friend
drinks a full glass of water what are you talking about that's a really
irritating me today really irritating me today oh yeah I'm sorry I'm just kidding
I'm just kidding guys come on look at this you know I'm saying whoa whoa
why are they moving what did I do that for I was trying to like jump off the
side and be wicked cocky do it again
all right let's do it again when you get like paper Mario I don't
never I would like on July 30th the 2021 that's bullshit I like these though
they're hard I don't even need to skip my own I need to skip I'll get it that
really knocks you way far on the other side oh shit there's a sock I didn't get
it okay this is the one this is actually the one these levels are actually fun
though I mean if you put a racing segment in your game or a slide segment
it better be fun these are fun these are very very very fun
what the fuck did I do that for okay I'm safe left or right left only one way
left or right right smart um where's the exit I don't know I don't know where is
six five four three oh son of a gun wait how do I get out of here what is Sandy
no that's a good I'm gonna do it is Sandy that's a good call I get the
spatula though that's a spatula 55 I'm gonna be Sandy just follow the boulder
I will all right let's do it follow the I can't do it as Sandy thanks for the
jubade follow the boulder I will follow the boulder into my death I will follow
the boulder until I die you understand stop saying suboptimal I I know it's
suboptimal you have to remind me all right I'm gonna follow the boulder
wherever it goes I'm going to go no matter what even if it kills me even if
I die I'm going where it is follow the boulder oh look at this sock is it gonna
put me cool that probably shaved off at least 10 seconds I've wicked itchy face
what do I do don't go that way you see that bullshit yeah I get them all do I
have all these spatulas from slip slide mountain 66 there are nine more I got
them all here I did them all yeah this place was pretty cool yeah you're right
you guys were right okay now I have 60 all right but how many more areas are
there do the snowmen it's gonna be a sock I don't want it okay so 50 to go
that way 60 to go that way which one's more interesting help forest or this
one oh this one looks creepy flying Dutchman's graveyard yeah I want to go
here the graveyard of ships somewhere among these haunted mess he fearsome
there's a boss it's a great voice I love the voice here same actor yes
it's me SpongeBob sir I don't need any cookies but I'm not a shell scout look
kid I'm too disturbed to scare the bejesus out of your right now come back
later I'm too scared what's the matter it's these darn robots they've thrown me
off my own ship they have being thrown off your own ship is like having your
pants pulled down in front of casual acquaintances it's a sad sad thing no I
can't do I can't do a flying Dutchman I can't do it nobody can do that besides
that guy it was the worst impression ever it was not the worst impression ever
okay it wasn't they were so many worse ones over the years
available in a size three no but if you do this a golden activate the can be
your booty Bane Bane was good I don't know why everyone gives me so much shit
for my Bane I don't get it I seriously don't understand why is this such a bad
I don't understand why you'd that's fucking good that's good that's a good
that sounds like the guy in the movie that's the point of an impression
whether you like it or not that's what he sounds like in the movie he sounds
like that's what that's the I bet may have just been him there hey don't do
that okay we have Sandy we can get Sandy if we want if we want I want you
Harry because I dodge I dodge so let's start is there a bus stop I don't see
all right that's it I'm banned I'm banning omega welcome from my twitch chat
people have been way a laughing way too much I'm way too much fun and shit no
not here I don't want you to be fucking on here if that people have fun I want
to be silent oh shit there's a button in here what does this do and off the I do
have to like release that from the age or something get rid of the poison I
gotta come back here later give her the poison those three thousand clams great
I just wasted that turn the poison off well take a look at what that is got it
oh curious I can I can move that this TF2 music maybe a little come with the
invasion no well then I don't know what you mean then we go I gotta get Sandy
Sandy's wait I can turn this shit off that was risky everyone's having fun
again you know that makes me more angry than anything okay so can I can you go
all the way over here yeah yeah and then oh Danny is so strong and yes yes now I
can go down there let's go activate wait sock moving I don't like what it moves
get out of here hit it come on I need Sandy Sandy I need you right now for
this bullshit platforming is fun yeah I was the thing spawning these assholes
okay what that's no it's gonna kill me jump you can have fun sometimes any of
I'm gonna move this again I don't play TF2 anymore I don't because I've played
it like ten straight years say wicked wicked hates it I got what I got what I
wanted out of it I had a lot of fun and I I don't it's like reading a good book
you know like I've read the book a bunch of different times I made up different
voices for all the characters more than three or four times in my head I hate
these things he's stupid oh you know let's just cheese this right now I'll
get it whatever they get it no we'll get out of the way I'm trying to get out of
my get away from my camera I got in the way of the shot and the cameras bumped
him right in the fucking head oh is that it I guess the top of the mountain I
did wait see one later I've ever streamed ratchet and clank not not that I
wouldn't stream ratchet and clank I just haven't streamed ratchet like baby I've
definitely been into it before problem with ratchet and clank is there are so
many of them and they've remade them right once or twice that it's I don't
know which one to play which one do I play which is one because I'm not gonna
play like five ratchet and clank games I'm telling you that's not gonna happen
some people are the HD versions any good or they bad with a shitty with a
rushed I just go back play the original first one they're all awful you don't
think they're any good hilarious don't you have a platinum wisp to get people
spamming Bonzi buddy why is Bonzi buddy in this chat is it a raid it's a raid oh
shit who where who's rating me how come I don't see it on my thing this is a big
one this is a big one but it's kit boga are you shitting me this is a big one
holy shit hey well what's up everybody that's 13k people coming in right now oh
my god nobody link the slap thanks welcome everybody thank you kit it bug
everybody if you don't know he's uh he's actually he's really fucking funny I
like I've watched kit bogus like videos and streams and shit welcome everybody
we're playing spongebob battle for bikini bottom welcome I'm currently at
the end of the game there we got another hour or so left who was slapped no you're
not I'm at the end of the game this is I only need like ten more golden
spatulas before I got it he's doing his professional voice no I'm not no look
see I stopped don't get to the end he's doing his tuber voice I'm not doing the
tuber voice I promise you need seven more yeah that's not gonna take very long if
you're curious what I think I think this game is very good if you don't own this
game it's currently on steam and and whoa boy is it good people have compared
it I've heard some people describe it as a Mario Odyssey yeah I've heard that
somebody said that before I don't know who they were but I bet they were real
handsome it's fucking nothing like Mario Odyssey don't buy it if you think it's
Mario Odyssey am I gonna lose can I make that I feel like I haven't been over
have I been over here to do a wink I'm not gonna do a wink no I don't have any
clothes on I told you guys I was going back to pretty Vegas dreams and that
means like I don't wear clothes ever what the hell am I doing down here what
did I miss something I went all the way back around wait don't cam now you
stupid motherfucker hey stop we have new there's no people here oh shit wall run
where is the spatula oh shit I'm gonna lose no I'm not why do I game naked why
do you game clothes you know how free you are without the clothes on this part
is harder in the red why did it make it easier and then remake 2700 this is gonna
be a splash that's bachelor right has to be yep 68 put your cam on and show us
how you how free you are no I'd like to continue streaming on
twitch I'm gonna do this I get off you'll lie 30th naked stream okay how
long do you realistically think it would take if I will turn oh who cares
how long do you think it would realistically take if I turned on the
cam right now and I was naked and it wasn't even talking about it I was just
sitting here playing naked how long until I'm done you think it'd be more
than 30 seconds I think it would be like at least four to five minutes before
everyone there was like fucking red alert buttons going off at twitch HQ
you think it would take three hours no it would not it would take like two
minutes three hours it's just funny to think about that because oh so close
yeah what's wrong he does a big finish and that's what I fucked up there that
that big finish
what are you doing click link no I'm afraid to click I don't want to click
that this is I mean that's what that's just what I look like without a shirt
on that's just what I am that's that is exactly what it is I mean that's a fake
photo but that's you don't even need to imagine if that's real enough that's
exactly what I look like except one of mine one of my nipples slightly points
in another direction it used to piss me off so much when I used to lift I used
to get so angry both of so one of my nipples like points down and the other
one kind of points up like frog eyes and it really pisses me off I would sit in
the mirror just flexing just like fucking greased up and shit have you
gone like what the fuck cuz I would stop flexing it'd be like it just looks like
shit whoo the Dutchman ship show us
ahoy there sponge Bob swap the poop deck oh I already did that joke with Squidward
mr. Krabs yes well it's a good one though a nipple reveal oh yeah yeah here's
what you need to do destroy all the power generators on the robot ship once
the power is off you'll be able to shoot the Dutchman's cannons to destroy their
oh and there's talk up there too and I'm gonna be sandy yeah I make jokes like
that all the time and everybody makes fun of me because me fucking idiot and
stupid and once like punch me spongebob doesn't everybody loves him no they
don't never mind you guys are saying minus two okay never mind all right at
least you're consistent well I can't believe anyone would minus two spongebob
square pants I feel like you probably felt bad doing you probably sitting in
your chair going like consistency in my germa chat but are we inconsistent here
yeah that sounds about right that sounds about right any all you guys maybe some
of you new guys some of the new viewers wait can I get up there can't grab the
edge yes I can this is the best chat on twitch you know people give us a little
bit of shit I fit I feel like we get some shit but I think we have one of the
best chats on twitch I feel like we get a little bit of shit for this you're
wrong what didn't know every single streamer says this you know guys I gotta
tell you something I think we've got the best dream on twitch everybody thinks
that that's what just being proud of your son when he throws up on the
keyboard in computer class and gets an F now my son is fucking perfect my son's
did you do that no my dad did hey you want some germa dad lore using like the
sixth grade he puked on his he was in like a computer class and this is like
really really old shitty computers no wait I'm mixing two stories together my
dad didn't fucking puke on a computer computers didn't exist my father ate a
slice of pecan pie one time and he puked in class and he's never eaten a
slice of pecan pie ever again since he was like the fucking eighth grade or
something that's a true story I don't know where the computer came from like
he threw up on the computer I don't know where the computer part is somebody
puked on a computer that I know that's certain I know that's certain I know
somebody that like puked on a computer in fucking computer class and they had to
leave I just think it was one of my friends it wasn't me okay I'm dying I'm
dying here stop spawning on me no my father does not eat pecan pie he doesn't
like pecans at all because he ate a slice and he hated it or it made him sick
or something and he threw up in class all right I'm playing the video game now
before everybody leaves too late it's all right hey they'll hey they'll be
back tomorrow when we play the 2012 London Olympics do the skip that they'll
be back they'll come to the next one I'm getting really annoyed at this party
why can I not do this I'm staying I'm just gonna fire missiles out just shoot
him with missiles can I stand on this no you can't all right here we go I need
Sandy finally all right now get me the hell over there let's go I'll stop
Sandy thank goodness finally now let's go where they get the sponge from I'm
going back I'm gonna go back do I have to be SpongeBob stop stop stop stop stop
stop please please what the fuck are you doing I'm not wait people are yelling at
me what do you want to do please please please I don't know
makes his big speech urge me to do so okay I have to say I have to tell you
this this is I believe a second or third Nixon resignation speech that you guys
have deep faked me on urge me to do so but the interests of the nation must
always come before any personal considerations from the discussions I
have had with congressional and other leaders I have concluded that because of
the Watergate matter I might not have the support of the Congress that was
great thanks how many of those are we gonna watch
why is it always Nixon resigning all right I could stop stop stop I have to
pay attention right now I'm not gonna do this anymore bullshit I gotta get up
here and I go to pay attention to this where are they coming from and I reach
that I gotta get up there wait a minute can't walk this rope and get on the bus
resign I'm not resigning what smells like get on here wait how do I do that
with Sandy impeaching what how do I get Sandy up here no Sandy can't can't move
that right oh that's only spongebob but I can break these does that help me throw
the bubble then just switch I guess I could try that leave me alone wait it
doesn't okay hold on I thought it went right back up I have to step on it for
it to go up welcome to fucking hell now I couldn't I grab that well I tried I
yeah that didn't even give me an indicator there was no target you
watched you watched it happen on your screen I don't have to make anything up
I jumped towards it there was no indicator there's no targeting you saw
it happen don't punch me don't stop punching me snipe the generator you got
it all right here we go we're gonna go over and up my cannon right here I not
do this Sandy gotta be with Bob weird calling him Bob doesn't feel right all
right come on Bob gonna bring Bobby over here Robert yeah I'm gonna bring Robert
over here a little bit well that looks interesting I'll go do it they called
him sponge in the early episodes I think those fucking fall last cannon oh now
all cannons are ready to fire I'll get shot out of the air I get a soccer to
just keep going where's this button to press get the sock you think I should
how did I get that sock buttons on the other ship
how did I listen I have to do this all over again to go over there again all
because I wanted to go get the sock you know at least I got the sock that's
true across the bridge it's too dangerous I've ever eaten duck before
once or twice but I really didn't like it at all I think it's gross I don't
like it it's a little I'm not a fan it's too it's got a little bit of like a
gamey taste for me not into it plus I don't like how it's cut and I know
people really like this shit oh man it's so delicious when they it's like they
serve it up like they slice it raw kind of it's like just not cooked in the
middle it's just like seared on the outside looks like a piece of aji tuna
I don't I don't I like things fully cooked called rare now I don't we don't
yeah we've already had this conversation I don't like rare I don't like rare I
don't like I don't like anything rare did I miss something here why did that
is that all we had to do and just go talk to the Dutchman what if you like
and miss something they're shooting them out of the year shit I gotta go kill
those please reach it please reach it okay let's go that's fine
all right that's where that's fine that'll work there's a cutscene
you eat sushi sometimes
I like spicy tuna I like shrimp rolls I like eel I like salmon I'm what I'm I
like raw salmon like if it's in a row
I'll spy I'm gonna play said somebody just say play fall guys I'm going to you
will see that on this channel I guarantee it I saw his tail wait yep
keep hurting the ghost do it again it's not so bad now we're gonna float by hey
I wanted to play fall guys when I first saw the trailer it looks it looks fun it
looks like just a giant obstacle course with a hundred people is that what it's
like or am I wrong when we watch the trailer we watched it on this channel I
remember going oh I do let's play that so it's out so I do let's play that we
have reached time when that's ready to go we're not doing it tomorrow it was
very easy what is 71 only four more and I can get to the end of the game I gave
him two attacks 71 72 everyone I can feel it it's close how many bachelors
I've missed quite a few whoo tanker ahoy you had a loft there matey I'm missing
two I am sandy right now though let's take a quick look whoo tanker ah let's
go say I want to see the other area I don't want to get like 75 we're seeing
the other areas I haven't seen what was everybody yelling before I should be
working I've been doing this lately you've been highlighting my name and
yelling what's with the yelling all right this bit is the other area the
kelp forest is this the only other zone I haven't been to here we are in the kelp
forest an interesting area with many sites to see for those that don't get
channel point channel positive all you guys have like 60 million and this is
nothing to do with them how many socks do I have all right so I need three socks
and three hell I'm already dead I should probably get rid of that it's only 1200
to do that some of you guys could sit there and do that all day
first you just delete channel fine you could just store them forever in a vault
what's the first thing to do I can also buy one for mr. Krabs too so I
realistically only probably need to peach the streamer but we I feel like
a barely play with Patrick the whole game I need more pattern he motor only oh
you guys are in trouble a wrath of a god see I can't they keep Patrick has to go
tell spongebob to play the game hey spongebob lady over there wants to talk
to you I appreciate it third character that doesn't do anything driving class
isn't out here today is it no spongebob what why do you say that do you think
we'd have class out here just to hide from you I'm just gathering twigs for
the winter yes that's it I have a merit badge in twig gathering actually you
can help with something else these robots showed up and scared all the
students I mean campers off into the forest before the Ranger what a terrible
instructor thanks spongebob I'll make sure to give you a nice reward when you
found all of them so you like crashed and you you're like abandoned in the
jungle here how the fuck did you have this happen all right let's go save all
the kids one kid saved gotta make it up to the other kids this I'm going for it
grandma have you never driven a car you know with no road what the fuck all
right I'm playing a game hold on leave me alone for a minute all right
sock oh a camper I'm seeing the others over here you can't ignore us I'm not
ignoring you just choosing not to listen I want to be Patrick what you're
pretending to be a zero view streamer it's spongebob flatline yes some reason
they put that in it's kind of it's quite dark I didn't know this game was gonna
be so dark floating around okay yeah it is the half-life down kind of I think it
actually is these guys suck please do another time stamp treasure hunt I think
it's a little too late for that I'm not sure I have the ability to do that right
now I'm ready to help swap off your gamer
fucking make it a whole screen you want me to hop my gamer chair for a whole
stream what the fuck is wrong with you why are you even saying that
but me old brain couldn't figure out how to get them back up here I'm not
gonna say that anymore sure why not I need a good laugh there's a golden
spatula up there for you if you succeed oh boy mr. Krabs okay I'm done with this
fun let's go get these things wherever they are I guess we have to get on them
get on the bus clue stream oh and we've done stuff like that fast it kind of
doesn't work unless I pre-record the whole thing though time for a little
sleepy sneak you've just met the sponge in a time I need that prison low just
jumped on his head and it just fucking messed up everything do I have to jump
on his head all right every stream is pre-recorded most of them are I need to
be Patrick damn it this is what I'm talking about this is the bullshit I'm
talking about I needed to be Patrick you gotta throw that shit all right here we
go somebody be in that guy who's getting who's getting being boo-hoo we've
be ending that is it I'm gonna get the spatula right here because I've got
Patrick got it I got it if this is it I can do it I need to buy one from mr.
Krabs and then get this one and then I can go and beat the final boss where
should I go this level sucks leave this one okay he did it yeah I'm ready I have
I need three socks plus I feel like I've neglected this open world where's mr.
Krabs how much money okay I get forty nine hundred how much does it cost where
is he mr. Krabs by the Krusty Krab I'm sorry this this game's not this game's
not anatomically correct of where all the things are where is he there is okay
your treasure chests looking a bit like the boy do you think I've got bilge
water on the brain I ain't running a charity you know nine thousand all
right well where about what let me go back to one of the first areas like how
about downtown bikini bottom oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm missing three here I
need two more of those wheels looking for wheels pushing a simple button is
the most satisfying push push push push I see a sock up there okay hold on there's
some shit here I need to be sandy right see needle see needle there's another
level near the graveyard there is help place the boats the dream and the
graveyard is nothing else here we said that was literally one guy well okay
what about rock bottom Ellie fish fields out of all industrial park hmm
downtown bikini bottom the murmur layer Tom bucket lab Patrick 40 socks and do
that Sand Mountain got them all who lagoon beside oh I'm gonna do I'm
missing see needle is an area in bikini bottom what the hell is the sea needle
what I don't know what's the sea needle what is that it's in downtown oh I got a
downtown bikini bottom I like it cool where where where's downtown I'm gonna
get it so I need to go all right I remember I kind of remember there's a
trampoline I have to jump on where where's that trampoline he doesn't
remember I'm gonna try I'm using all my brain power to remember where that was
it was like a little little spot already already upset I'm already getting yelled
at means it must be right here okay I told you I knew I thought it was I get
look look look look look look look I got it shit all right
sandy can do a chop I don't have Sandy where's sandy where's the bus I need a
bus stop for sandy right there he's a lamp post they all the lamp
post look like bus stops all right please this is them please don't do this
bit where's the fucking bus stop why can't it just be the beginning of the
level why does that have to be a bus stop like on a roof why doesn't the
other bus stop up here on a bucket on the corner on the third roof where is
this fucking bus stop you don't need sandy how am I supposed to get over
there this is on the opposite side of the map just walk around all over the
road hi Larry what are the two at the very end this two that have to be over
here what are they go back to the road you're so close I go back I don't know
what the needle is I don't watch spongebob I saw the first like ten
episodes when he was making Krabby Patties I don't know this is where I
went to the space needle looking for like a space needle like the thing in
Seattle oh god come on that is what it is why can't I see from the map that's
what I'm looking for there you are someone's broken the sea needle that's
horrible the sea needle is the cradle of crochet corner somebody said how does
this guy have 9,000 viewers you have Gerber in your name get that area that
bullshit you watch yes yes it is but what's more important is that there are
Tiki's and shiny objects just outside the windows I thought it was something
I'm looking for like a building mr. Krabs how can you think of money at a
time like this easy I just clear my mind money money money so what do we have to
listen here boy you know that I'll give you golden spatulas if you bring me
shiny objects but I'm going to sweeten the deal if you can break all the Tiki's
here at the sea needle I'll give you a bonus golden spatula easy thing I've
done all day because they were laughing at you and calling you funny names what
kind of funny names you know spongebob but pants that's not very funny no but
they said your mom was ugly
Krabs break the myself you've got a deal all right break all the stuff II can't
go and eat up with you come with you oh does this count as breaking shit it does
wait I got a man I go one last box I break it yes I did everyone looks like
from up here you guys are like tourists get out of what are you doing here we go
another one break how did that hurt why are these hurting
shouldn't these hard to see it's hard to see it's hard to aim I got it wait I
need one of those I need one more of these everybody know where that is I
need one more of those things thank you for saving me this puzzle platform no
hit run that would be very very difficult do you not get any this is
like grabbing with the crane and the one with the candy in it the one that's
impossible to lose you just grab a bunch of like I mean yeah the candy in there's
gross it's like all smarties like who the fuck wants to eat those all day
nobody Marty's of the shit and I like them too but I mean you can only have
doses you can't have those every time doses yeah I'm saying like you can't
just eat smarties smarties and tootsie rolls from like 1993 smarties are great
up your urethra I didn't even know it was happening I didn't even know what
was happening okay I did it I've got 75 I'm ready to win this is what happens
this is why it's hard I can't read chat because like I'm paying attention to the
game and I'm like somebody said something and if I look over his way
we got loud idiot this is why I get into trouble this is what gets me in trouble
I can't do that I got all the wheels okay I got 75 dude but
SpongeBob you don't have a driver's license why is that it why can you type
that in the chat like you shouldn't be able to type that let alone be read it
you shouldn't be able to write that where's like the world of Warcraft name
filter like you wouldn't be able to name your world of Warcraft character up your
you wouldn't be able to do that I got 75 I'm ready for the final fucking
chapter he's endorsing censorship 75 how many do I have 75 are you ready it's
time to kick this game's ass plankton's laboratory I'm so glad I can leave soon
I'm so glad I'm gonna be leaving soon I gotta get away I have to run away I have
to run away okay but imagine writing that sentence oh yeah you just kind of
sit there just saying bullshit you're just saying nonsense like absolute
fucking nonsense it doesn't even matter you didn't even carry just wrote it
because you were like I'm gonna write that who cares
to set the switch to obey plankton I'm gonna go wait so we have to fight us
SpongeBob SpongeBob the final boss SpongeBob versus SpongeBob okay I wait
I see what to do I hit you in the green spot
try hit plankton yeah I'm gonna die he's bad I'm just I'm learning the
or should I say opportunity here I do with one hell I know what to do now do
it it looks like SpongeBob has an opportunity here that's the ticket and
robot is down fuck out of here
like SpongeBob has an opportunity here
come on Robert and here he comes goodbye how raw what I guess won't be winning
that way hey what had that right a dream about this get it in the hand all right
final phase I go in now nope nope nope nope it looks like SpongeBob has an
opportunity here this match is and tack on more and I have completed SpongeBob
and the battle for bikini bottom 76 I got a spatula for that plays this phase
too huge and wow he's got the muscle things just lifts his fist up and just
crushes him on earth I think we just this is it this is it it's gonna make it through
you to watch out for plankton he's gonna cause problems whoo there it is you're
gonna get all the all those things oh lots of spaghetti why you doing that what
I'm gonna jump on that come on SpongeBob what the hell trying to get out of the way
what I hit it back you'll just I didn't even you could do that it's been like 10
hours oh you it's time for you to pay we told you to parry yeah but you were just
like making funny jokes I don't know it was real I like this area though there is
pretty cool drop into my death I'm gonna give you an opportunity to do
anything plankton around yes he is you're cheating cheating how was this
cheating no I gotta knock it back that was a fucking failure by that again
this is a weird noise streamer I'm sorry I know and I go to what a moment to tell
you I didn't hit why is the camera doing this what are you doing stop I'm turning
all right where's Clinton do a monkey song I don't think I can do that on
command hey almost to the top we actually are at the top this is the top
still going oh okay where is he all right what did that do I just Star Wars
did you get it he's coming for me don't let him go over here they win that time
so somebody said time had hours and 18 minutes it was really fun how much is
this game surprise tag on this right now 30 bucks that's worth $30 yeah I didn't
do everything I missed like obviously like 10 to 20 bachelors I enjoyed my
time and I thought it was really fun thought it was really cute there's some
challenging areas that's what I would have done in the first episode of the
this makes me want to watch a bunch of spongebob I think they had a really good
slide mechanic all right that's a bad was a positive oh wait we get credits oh
I said slide mechanic and look there's a slide right here
Tony Hawk no this is all right I gotta go I gotta do everything with the slide
entrance shit okay all right here we go right here yes okay is there a game
that's just only slide levels what is it monkey ball yeah my monkey ball right
monkey ball shot should I play monkey ball for real and that's another problem
monkey ball there's like 30 of them and like only two of them are any good right
I have a dreamcast sitting right there that's ready but I get the one on dream
cast the two that are on dreamcast to play the new remade ones the GameCube
get it on the GameCube GameCube GameCube GameCube the way the one on dream cast
is not that's the original isn't it look at all those I gotta get up there here
we go here's the big one yeah I love slide levels there's so much fun arcade
is the original GameCube is just the port of the arcade how long would it
take to do like super monkey ball like the GameCube one that be a whole stream
or is that only like two hours depends that would be a whole stream and then
how bad you are well you know that does depend on the day doesn't it well this
was a lot of fun I've really enjoyed this I'm glad I finally played spongebob
battle for bikini bottom been too long I want to get in there shit I gotta do
that I gotta go down like the chute right there's anything else watch the
100% ending on YouTube it is a true ending to battle for bikini bottom is
fun about battle for key bottom secret 100% ending all right let's check it out
bro don't screw don't scream like a fucking pro all right we so we saw up to
here
Langton look out you got to see that again
What's the difference? There's like a minute left.
This isn't right. They're not children.
Hooray! There's the true ending. Battle for Bikini Bottom.
Yeah, I don't think I would have spent the next like seven or eight hours getting everything to see
the theme song played. I can watch the theme song on YouTube. Still cute though.
Can I leave? No, of course. Did I just ask Twitch chat if I should leave credits?
What am I thinking? Of course not. All these people did a really good job.
This person worked on Plankton. This person worked on
Sandy, Gary, Annie, Pop, Larry, Homer, Skorpun. Who are these people?
Oh, those are, okay. Was that like just, oh, that was EU?
Wait, can we hear all these voices? That has to exist in the game, right? Can I change my
language and just listen to like audio and see what's where the best SpongeBob is?
Okay, let's do French and let's go to the town.
The credits loop forever. Okay, let's go talk and let's just, let's take a look at the voices.
Okay, here we go. Let's see. This is French SpongeBob. Here we go.
Not bad. That's not bad. We need more dialogue though. We can talk to Squidward.
I like the, I wish Squidward would just speak French in the regular show.
Okay, pretty good. Italian.
Okay.
Oh, it's a little more high-pitched than Tom Kenny. Hold on. French was close. Let's see how,
sounds a little too smart. It's actually not bad. It's pretty good. It's close. German.
Patrick sounds, Patrick sounds close in German.
He just kind of sounds like Bilbo Baggins.
Look, if you replaced any of, you could replace it with any of these guys and I think it would sound
good. Okay, hold on. Spanish.
Squidward's freaking fantastic. That's fantastic Squidward.
I love Squidward. I love Spanish Squidward. All right, hold on.
Okay, I, I like the Spanish Squidward. I like Spanish SpongeBob as well.
All right, let's, what about Mr, whoa, whoa, whoa, what about Mr. Krabs?
We're gonna, we're gonna see Mr. Krabs, right? What about Sandy? What about Gary? All right.
All right, nice. What else we got? Polish.
Okay. Polish SpongeBob. I wish I, I need more lines for SpongeBob. Oh, Mr. Krabs. Yeah, yeah,
hold on.
Patrick doesn't sound stupid. He sounds cool. He sounds really cool. What about Plankton?
All right, Mr. Krabs. Polish Mr. Krabs.
That's good. That's good. Japanese. Here we go.
I, I like want this in the regular, in just like the English game.
Wait, that's Plankton?
Oh, it's cute.
SpongeBob sounds pretty good.
That's a, it's a different take on Plankton.
It does seem weird hearing Plankton talk like this. Okay, there's a lot.
Yeah.
German Plankton. Sure.
Oh,
all right. Let's do Japanese Patrick. You German Mr. Krabs.
Oh, Polish Squidward. All right. Look, I'm going to get out of here.
It's pretty good. That's, that's very good. It's very good.
Squidward. All right.
All right. All right. German Mr. Krabs.
Or German Sandy. Oh, we're going to do German Sandy and German Mr. Krabs. Go to Mermaid Man.
Japanese Sandy. His German.
All right. Japanese. They're, they're good. They're all pretty close.
All right. German Mr. Krabs. And then I'm out of here.
You go to Japanese Gary. All right. I'm going to do all, all language Gary. Okay.
What did he say? German Gary.
I like German SpongeBob. I wish we could get it.
That with all these different. All right. Japanese.
Okay. French. Not bad.
Italian Gary. Oh, they're the same. They're all the same.
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. I'm out of here. It wasn't a bit. It wasn't
until I figured it out after two. I'll see you guys tomorrow. We're going to do the Olympics.
We're going to do the 2012 Olympic games. I don't know that game might be terrible,
but I'm going to try to get the gold medal in at least 10 categories.
There are 35 different competitions. I'm going to go for it. Not Mario and Sonic.
It is the officially licensed 2012 London Olympic games. PlayStation three video game
movie night update. I have no idea. It's going to happen soon though. After tomorrow. I'll
probably have a really good day for it. I'll set the date tomorrow. So let's run the credits.
I think I got it fixed. At least I hope I did. What time tomorrow? Tomorrow we're going to start
more normal. Tomorrow's going to start around noon. Pacific 12 p.m. Pacific tomorrow. A little
bit more normal start started early today, but you know, sometimes you start early.
All right. Let's see if this worked. Hope it did. Thank you for joining me. Thanks for the
raid too. By the way, Kit Boga and all the people that came from the stream. Thanks.
I'm not sure how many of you still here, but if we see you again, we see you again.
Thanks for dropping by. Let's see if it works. And I try. I even fixed it too. I even fixed it.
It doesn't matter. It's just permanently broken. It's just broken. Very annoying.
Is this person even here? Is that was this person even here? Thank you. Shenro. The one person that
subscribed today. Thank you. Are you here? You're the only one. One sub streamer. How? All right.
They're here right now. This is really, really important. Shenro, when did you subscribe today?
When? Was it like 10 minutes ago? Was it like four hours ago? They left. It was at the start
of the stream. They didn't unsubscribe. Did they? They said it was autosubscribed. They said it did
it automatically. Is it them again? If it is, then I don't know what the fuck to do. It's just one
person. The ultimate one guy. Wait. No. Hold on. There's two. I got two of you now. No. Wait. I got
three. Three people. This is so broken. I can't even show it because it was removed from the
Derma Mustard website because he was doing some changes to it. I was making people sick.
There are the subs today. A lot of people fucking subscribed. They really did.
I got to get this fixed. I swear to God, I'm going to fix this up by tomorrow.
Thank you for the subs, everybody. Thank you for watching. Thank you. I want to make sure
to address really quickly. 100 bucks from Vilemi and 50 dollars from Big Bip. Big Bipper. Thank
you. Thank you both, you guys. 50 dollars and 100 bucks respectively there. Those of you that don't
know, I'm no longer doing end of the stream bit readings. It has been removed. Take more time
to be able to sit comfortably and do this on stream. To actually like do, you know. Well,
I'm going to play SpongeBob for six hours and I know I can sit here. So it gives me the time
to sit here and actually do those things. It is no longer here. And that'll be it. I will see you
guys tomorrow with the Olympics. Thanks again. Have a great rest of your night. We'll see you
tomorrow. Have a good night. I pressed it. I pressed it too early. Good night. See you tomorrow.
Uh, raid. All right. Before I end the streaming right now. Let's see.
Turn your cam up. I don't have a camera on.
Raid. Limey. Limey. Limey. Limey. Limey. Limey. Limey. Hold on. Wait. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Oh no. Let me. I'm sorry, I can't read. Playing Fall Guys? All right, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Let's raid Limey. I want you to prepare yourselves because I'm going to be playing
this game and I want you to give me all the damn secret techniques. Yeah sure, let's go.
Let's go spread him. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Make sure I get his name
Here we go
See you tomorrow. He ain't gonna care. Oh
That's all right
Well, I'm not like trying it. Yeah, that's all right. That's all fucking good
I'll see you guys tomorrow
All right. Bye