It was a little odd. For some reason my steam wouldn't connect. I had to like force quit it and then open it again.
Weird.
Anyways, hello.
Welcome back. I'm doing all right. I can't say I'm at 100% right now.
Because that would be a lie.
And you go ahead and make a new one. Dermal lied about being at 100%.
Because as the days progress here on this medication,
I feel like it's probably gonna get worse.
As we as we go forward over the next another five or six days.
Oh, end of the life. No, I'm fine. It's just
I'm I'm all right.
I can't this is one of those things you just can't talk about on stream and you just can't
just know
that
Like what the fuck? That's all you need to know.
But we're gonna continue our fear playthrough from yesterday.
I think we probably have an equal amount of time.
Left so I've been told this probably about four hours five hours maybe left in the game. We're just gonna do it today.
What happened? I missed it.
Uh, I guess i'll just talk about all right. Well
the nature of live broadcasting
and the nature of twitch and
Live stuff is people that were there yesterday may not be there tomorrow.
And the people that weren't there yesterday may be here today.
So it's um
That's people wonder why well, well you you've already talked about this like three times
well, it's because
You may not have been here two days ago. And if you were maybe your friend right there sitting at the table
May not have been here yesterday either
but um
Yeah, i'm on a couple of new medicines
i'm having some stomach issues that uh
I we think are completely unrelated
to
Uh, like colitis and stuff
So i'm trying some new stuff and what it does is it's causing me some discomfort
It discomfort in quotes
And I have to do it for a while. So the streams over the next week or so up until probably around halloween
Are gonna be shorter
But i'm gonna do more streams
That's pretty much the way it's gonna work. You're gonna get less time on stream, but you're gonna get more days streamed
There you go spread it around pass that around the lunchroom
And I don't really even need an intro here
Because we already know what's going on, but I do need to tweet something. So let me do that real quick
Spread the word
Well, don't spread don't spread it too much
Because it's not gonna be a it's not gonna be permanent
It's only gonna be for like a week or two
finishing
fear
I'm having a good time with this game though
If you didn't catch the stream yesterday
This is uh, this is a good one
And it really makes me want to play the other ones even though I know that i'm gonna be disappointed but still
It's the same company. It's the same franchise. Could it really be
worse
by that much
Two is all right. The three is the bad one
Fear two is all right fear two is fine. Okay, so fear three is not the same company monolith didn't do fear three
Okay. All right. All right
Fear two is good
All right, that's bad
I think I want to do them
Even if fear three sucks, you don't think we should do the three we don't believe we shouldn't do the trio
Well, I hate that game to a point where there's a meltdown on stream and I like quit the game halfway through. What do you think?
Is it not worth doing?
it may be
Never mind. You should play it. All right. Now we see where now we see where you're uh
Now we see where your true intentions lie
All right, let's go
Hi
Hi, it's me
So the last thing that happened
Let's break down the story here
scary girl
Find this guy
Kill that guy pretty fun game
Pretty much that's that's that's pretty much the plot of every horror game
All right, i'm going in
I I can't see anything you guys are saying. No fear three isn't a bad game. It's just not a good fear game
It's worth playing if you like fear one
We'll see
I should probably at least do fear two
But this I got all this stuff to do
There's a lot of games to play
All right, I apparently saved it
Where was I? Okay. Let me just check the audio level boom. That's really really loud for me, but it's probably all right for you
I can't tell is it really bad? All right play the expansions to fear one. All right
Maybe we'll do that too
Oh, I know why it's loud for me
Because I had to turn this up last night. Oh, it should be good for you
Check this out ready
That may have been too loud for you
Ow
Oh, i'm wasting ammo
Am I running?
Why am I not wait? Why am I going slow?
Oh, it's because i'm crouching. All right
Or how am I doing on health? Okay. I got how many health packs do I have?
The last thing I did. All right, right. Okay. I turned off the gas
from what I remember and then I
Yeah, no, I have to turn off the gas and then go up there
So the gas was over here
He didn't notice he was crouching
Yeah
Yeah, okay
All right. So this I went down but
No, this is why I came around
I didn't really pick the best place to stop
because
I kind of it's like i'm turned around here
I should have gotten the end of this section last night, but I just couldn't I couldn't do it
Does this take place after I didn't I turn it off already?
Did I pick the wrong save?
I may have picked the wrong save
What a chad
Really? I already got scared by this. Yeah. Yeah, I picked the wrong save
Like it's the wrong save that happened to me. Let me and do you remember what I said yesterday?
And I still feel the same way that ended the stream last night. That hurt me again
That was the one
Why did I pick this save?
No, I can't turn it off now
All right, where i'm fine. So that's turned off now. I'm gonna go up here. It hurt me it did
Keep out
I don't think it will
What the fuck is in here health facts health upgrade? All right. No, I don't want to go down
Wait charge up the flashlight
This is no, I need something with actual
What there's no I know no ammo in any of my guns
None of my weapons have ammo
Okay, so then now I can climb up the
Is this thing over here I can go through there or yeah, let's go through here
Because that's that
All right. Now I can go up the ladder
Oh
nice
Save it
Yeah, okay
This is where we stop
Yeah, I loaded the wrong safe. That's my bad. That's on me
This is the wrong safe
It's okay though. Don't worry because this is where this I remember
Stopping here
Let's go up
Uh, I guess we're gonna go over here
water
This is a water valve or is this a steam valve?
And I don't mean that I really don't mean that as a reference to any video game companies I actually mean like a
like a steamer
I I honestly did not mean that as like a that's this is a funny valve like valve joke
Like a company valve what is going on over here?
Okay, well the water's up
Am I killing somebody right now?
Yes
Oh, that was a good joke
Gay Ben
No, that's not what I was doing
Remember when that was like the funniest thing you could possibly say
You might it still might be I don't know. Did I get everything in here?
Wait, hold on
Okay, what what year do you guys think?
had the best
memes
Do you think it was like 2011 2012 2013?
I think i'm missing something here
2012 started a lot of fucking weird stuff
Can I swim?
Okay, i'm just gonna swim
2010 to 2015 I would even say probably
I'm, not sure I would put I don't know if I'd go as far as 2015. That's a little too far. I think
Turn it on turn it off. Oh shit. I just turned it on
What like shitty design that is down is not on down is off
Up is on like a light switch. That's universal. That's like go that's driving on the right side of the road in
America or on the left side of the road in europe like come on
Up is on down is off
Well that I did that now I'm just gonna go back
They are hard to turn on
Oh, that's why
Because you need to like put weight down to turn it on. All right. I just thought it was right. Whatever you're right
Up is off loser
Here we go checkpoint
There's probably gonna be fucking monsters and shit here now so I could be ready
I can now go through the door the elevator
Oh
Somebody else
Who the fuck is here?
Oh
What is happening to this guy's head?
Save him
There is no saving that one
Okay. Now I can go
Uh, wait, I can actually I can use this right? What if I want to go two one?
Can I use? Oh, all right
Stop
Okay, just how do I all right they're gone
Okay, intercept
Uh, did the elevator did the elevator just open behind us? I don't know. I don't care. I
I just you exploded
Wait, did he what did he say?
You exploded
Oh shit, you exploded
Oh, no
Oh shit
This game is fucking so fun
Okay, here we go shotgun. I like the shotgun the best
Although this thing sucks. It really does. It's just not very good
The hell are you doing?
Pick it up
What are you?
Hey
Okay, 65. What do I have the heels might as well use one
I feel like i've been completely just totally neglecting the pistols. I think I used it once in the first five minutes of the game
I feel kind of bad
You know what I mean? I feel like I wanted is it just bad
There's a lot of ammo and
That just scared me
All right, what's in here?
Anybody in here?
Okay, I don't know why my brain decided that this is what it was going to do
But I was going to hit control to see a hitman boom and look at points of interest
You know, it's it's the way that this looks this room is a hitman room. You know, you know, does that make any sense to anybody?
This is a hitman room
It it is that's why I wanted to do it it makes sense somebody's gonna be in here no computer computer
I was gonna close all the one but
I decided that was not worth my time
Look out. It's getting it's high voltage
Should I
That's new music
Oh
It's the human garfield. I forgot. All right
I love how human garfield has his own jokey like fairy tale music
Christ I thought I was a goner to you guys. The elevators are offline and those soldiers are everywhere
Feed him should I feed him security office and override the lockdown?
All right, let's feed him
That didn't feed him
He eats
Nobody move he usually eats him remember oops. Oh my god, he's just wearing a hat
Dude the whole the whole building just went up
Okay. Well, that was fun
override the security lockdown
You created a black hole
Somehow accidentally. All right, I got my shotgun
Yes, I did think that was a person for a second
It's a horror game. Come on. It's hard to not think the shadow is a monster
imagine getting hit right in the face by a absolutely more than eight to ten pound weight and just
Going like this
without even flinching
What a true chad
Uh, no guys, no
Oh
What's in there? Wait
I fucked up his toaster. Sorry
What somebody open the door?
No, that's a waste of a grenade. Come back
Saves come. Yeah. Let's try and see if it was good could contain the blast
Just
Okay, we already heard it so
Where is this security room then through here?
Somebody's gonna that guy getting eaten eaten in one of these he's gonna come somebody's gonna fall out of one of these
A monster or something a new enemy type
It's just completely and totally absolute
Oh shit
Good work
That guy was very unsure
What?
Wait, what is going on?
So I threw
I frisbeed in to the room. They couldn't see me. I they didn't they didn't know where I was quick
All right, I need uh
Where is he stop talk sit all clear. I didn't where was he? I don't even hear it
I want to stick this on one of his like butt cheeks
It's so important the music the music is
What
Okay
Uh, all right. I got him was he uh, that's cool. All right, but who cares?
I had to reload the fucking gun
That thing actually is not very good
It's not not very good. You have to shoot him like three times in the head
Just only use the shotgun. It's the best weapon in the whole game
Was that guy shooting at him?
I think he was shooting at him. I have no idea
That guy was on my team
He could have been
I'm stuck
How do they not see me that whole time?
He's trying to flank
He's running straight at me. He's flanking us
shit
I'm never gonna be able to
Hear them say that and not laugh at it
That's shit
What i'm looking for is i'm looking for three people in the same room four people and it's oh shit. Oh shit
Oh shit
I want to hear it four times in a row
That's the only thing I want what the fuck is that
There's a rocket launcher
I want to have five people in a room rocket launch explode. Oh shit explode. Oh shit
I want the pitch to keep going down
That'd be the ultimate video game laugh out loud moment for me
All right, let's go
Save it
We got two in a row
Can we get like four in a row?
Oh, uh, it's gonna take just dice thrown in the air
it's
What it's
You shoot three
Okay, this is too good to use right now
It's just it's I don't want to use this. It's too good
I wasted it. I know that's all right, though
I'll get more ammo for it and I will only use it. I thought it was a one shot. That's why
It's still open
What the fuck? Hello? Oh you
You're down there
No, no
Oh shit, nice throw. Oh shit
Why are you holding the gun like that?
Okay, I guess i'll take it
I know I can get in there. I'll get this way
Security room. Here we go. He performed final acrobatics before he died
Yes, i'm still on hard. Okay. Here we go. Who's coming in?
It's gonna why would you have the monitor here? It's gonna be a scary thing that runs by
Apparently not
All right, everything is been activated now we have to go back you can leave through here. All right, it's done
Nope, that is not gonna fucking happen 14 35 43
Dammit
It's got to be the detonate one
No
I have to do this once
It didn't I didn't even get it in
You motherfucker, I swear to god
There it's in
No
Quick run around to every floor and hit quick sprint up press every button on every floor on the way down running down the stairs
That'll fuck him. Why do I keep trusting that guy? That guy just disappears. He doesn't do anything else
He just runs away. All right
I was already in here. This is the way to go to where I just was so didn't know the door open
I'm certain that another door opened and then he turned off
That's so annoying
Can I even go over here? Oh shit
I do I have to meet him upstairs
Oh god. Dammit. I do
This come on. There's not a health upgrade here. Why would you have this here if there wasn't an upgrade? That's total
bullshit
What just happened? There's no cool music right now
I know what the fuck is a great
Seeing what happened
All right, we made it
Game saved. What's next? Sayonara sucker
It's very very quiet. That means something's gonna jump out. That's audio editing 101
Make the audience have to focus
On the fact that there's no audio go. Wait, why is it no then loud noise?
It doesn't open this looks like it's on
Perfect you again
Yeah
You almost didn't fit through the door you almost didn't fit through the door I get the last lap
Can I destroy it? Let's just hide
Why is that in here? Why does that exist?
Yo, you left you cactus. I don't think he cares. All right, so let's uh go in here
No, no
Jesus
So I can't go this way now. There's no make sure don't miss this like no what the fuck's happening
Okay, go back. Okay. Well
uh
It's a retro stream
Uh-oh
Why why yeah, why is my why is my bit rate so low right now? These graphics suck
Why is this happening?
Oh, I think I have a setting
I think there's a new setting on like on obs now
Where if you if your internet sucks, it doesn't drop frames it drops your bit rate. I wonder this that's interesting
It's 2007 all over again
That's better. Yeah, it was like a it was like a pretty revolutionary thing that they were working on
I remember I talked to somebody at twitchcon about it
But the real question is how long I wonder
Do we just kind of slowly come back?
Um, let me just do one thing. Let me just look at this real quick. I want to see if this is actually
If that's what's actually happening. I saved it. Hold on. Let me just check something
That's very very cool
Let me just see if that's what it's doing
maybe
Because this is for as happening in like real time
This is so strange
I didn't think this was on any of the other obs's though
Because I don't think this is enabled
What what's this link you guys are spamming?
That's what this looked like
Oh my god
That looked like I made it a clay
I think that is what's happening though
You know, i'm just gonna say that's what's happening
And we're just gonna go back to playing the game because it looks like it's climbing back to like four or five six thousand now
interesting
What did it hit?
Dude, that is a that is an amazing feature that they came up with though. That's that's
insanely awesome
Because like you won't your stream won't turn the fuck off anymore
That's so awesome
Thank god for smart people making smart things in technology
all right
This is actually the the the bit rate that I used to stream at I used to stream at this exact bit rate at like
4,800
So this is like this is actually uh, twitch.tv slash germa985 from like 2016
Can I activate it?
Why can I not turn that on?
Warning video cameras are operating on these premises good
Automatic
How could you tell
All right. I'm going for this is what these are for
Excuse me, excuse me
I
Huh? What?
Never mind. Those things suck
I can't even see where this thing is now. Where did it blow up?
That was that was
I can't I can't save scum. Just go
There's too many health packs
Okay, so
See what we do here on germa985 was we make sure that we show everybody our best and our worst
This is the mario tennis stream
All right
We started out all right
And then I started like swearing at people and making fun of people on mario tennis and everybody really hated it and it went right
Down, but I want to make sure everyone knows that we don't do that shit
We show the worst that we have but we also show the fucking big recoveries that we have too
This is from the tony hawk pro skater 2 stream
Where I was playing really poorly and everybody was like making fun of me and everyone made fun of me
And then I pulled off a one million point trick and made a ton of great jokes in a row
You can always salvage it. Don't throw it away
and then this one is uh
That that one's tesla. I just I just always want to keep track of it because I trade it
Okay, so
No, i'm not doing any chin faces anymore because I know how bad I look
Don't die
I'm doing curve at the frog. Why won't these explode?
Pull them next to it. Well, what the what it shouldn't explode
I need more health now
I have a click saved about five minutes. I'm supposed to make a macro for that
I'm supposed to make a macro for every time I throw a grenade. It saves the game
Okay, uh, let's go that way
Right electricity off. There we go. Oh, no, I don't like that
No more turrets
That's a good thing
Does that let me open the doors? No
Okay, I think what three hours have gone by
in-game
No, none of these open
That just turned off the turrets. That's it didn't do anything else
That's that nothing else here. All right, i'm gonna go this way
Maybe now I can keep going
further through uh, what's this way
Could go that way. I'll go up
We're down. No, i'll go down
I haven't been over here yet
health upgrade
No, germ is so smart. He can see time
Um, I can't see time
I can see the system that we have created as humans
To be aware of its passing
There's a difference
I turned it off. I turned it off
Am I missing? Oh god, i'm in trouble
I'm just
Did I get it? I thought I turned this shit off
Just throw a grenade
What do you mean just throw a grenade? The last two times i've thrown a grenade into it. They've magically disappeared
A regular grenade would bounce off of it and come back and kill me
I can't use the rockets because I I might need it for something
like this
Like this scenario. This is the scenario
Is this what hackers do?
When they put like this is like pulling up to a red light next to a guy in a Lamborghini. Is it like
All right. You ready? Let's go fine
What's he doing? Is he in yet?
I hope I I hope I can just push this guy off like an edge. You know what I mean?
I don't want to like kill this guy. I just want to push him over like a cliff
Maybe kill him probably maybe
I can't activate that. So let's just go
Wait one two secrets
Remember that kills people
Well, it depends. I don't know
There's a difference
A click guys a kind of pushing somebody over an edge off a cliff
could mean
like on the top of a playground slide or
Like grand canyon, you know what I mean? It's off the edge
I just want to push him off a slide. That's what I meant
That's a slide not a cliff. Oh, we could argue semantics here
What is a cliff? What could it be? Like what is an edge? What is like a pushing somebody off of off an edge mean?
Cliff is a well cliff is not a man-made
Why is he running around?
I don't understand what this guy's game is. There's people
There's like a whole agency of of weird super soldiers that are killing us and trying to kill everybody and there's
All this awful shit going on. There's a little scary girl
and
Why is he running away from me?
Let me ask a question. It's been like six hours in the game. Can you cook grenades?
Yes
No
We're about to find out
You cannot
Otherwise this would have exploded
So we're just gonna have to use this thing
Here we go
Still there
Is it gone? Oh my god, and he's six rockets
Well, that's unfortunate. I can't open this
No, no easter egg to get a soda. I get to I get to push him over an edge
I get to push him down the cliff
I get to do that
I am gonna he's gonna say his last line and i'm gonna push him down the laundry chute. I get to do what i've wanted
I get to do it
I can't wait
Oh, come on. He made it in wonderful. I don't get to do my fun thing that I wanted to do so bad
That's very disappointing. Let's take a look over here anything that's over here that I need to do
Oh shit, just hold on. Yeah, he's stuck in that vent
Just fill that thing with chocolate syrup and you got the first half of the Willy Wonka movie
All right, that's good
Just open the fucking vent
Wait
Why are these here?
Okay
All right, that's gone
I think i'm by it by this point
How are you still aiming down here? What?
Well, that's a that's a crock of shit
No
Here comes a jupiter storm
Watch out left or right. Uh, let's go right first right looked shorter. Good call
Uh-oh
Um, is it one of those things?
You love cocaine
I would advise on not doing that anymore
I don't think it's not very good for you. I would not do that anymore
Clip that yeah
I would advise on not doing any
Thing like that. It's not good for you. It's not good for you
Eat a fucking banana. Okay, eat a banana
What did he just jump out of the ceiling?
He did
Roger. Oh, no, that was roger
That was one of his friends
I have one bullet left in this thing. Um, I need a new gun
I'm in trouble here
What all right, I'm I have one health pack left
Where'd it go? Good
Uh any other ammo or anything? I need a new gun
Ooh, perfect a boost to my reaction speed thing
Turn the flashlight off. There's probably more
Um, was he destroying one of those turrets? Got him
Any more kill that light?
All right. I have to replace the I gotta replace the no this thing replace this
I don't the nail gun isn't really that good. It takes too much
Even if you headshot it takes like three headshots sometimes
That's too much
It should be two one
So this is now I can use this not yet. I will be using it though to go up or down
Wait a minute. He can shoot through the glass. Okay. Give me some weapons here
This thing doesn't come into this room, right?
Where is he?
Holy
Oh
Come on get in here
I can pick him up. I can pick him up. I can pick him up
Here's the plan
You ready for the plan? Okay, pull him over here put a gigantic trap for him
He i'm gonna pull him into this room
He's gonna be all the way back here
Get this out a gigantic trap. This guy is fucking dead
There he is. Okay. How are you? Good to see you
Now you're dead
See you in hell
Now why is the music still going?
All right, I guess i'm out of here
It wasn't even hard. It just took all of my stuff. Wait this ammo
I mean, I'm going this is the last the final boss is up here. That's where i'm going. That's a specific noise
that little like
What is that from? I don't know. It's
Oh, it's gonna kill me
It's from mario 64
No, it's not is it really?
Okay
Good. I have a hundred now
100 armor save it
What's in here another one of those things?
That's you're probably gonna have to fight like a few of them. Wait. All right. I haven't been in here yet
Right
There it is
No
Why did I not break that? I should have fucking known
Really?
That's the point. That's why i'm doing this see
Because I know that I was there
All right, we got water. Let's go given the game is too scary. Please change it
Nah, this is nah, it's not it's not that bad. It's scary but
Nah ready? It's gonna go
Do it do it
Come on. I'm really off with these predictions today
Amnesia is better than this. Well, I mean this is not like a it's not supposed
Okay
This is like a shooter game though. That's I mean, it's it. Hey, you don't you can't talk smack about fear
I'm this is like a really cool game. I really like this game
And it's like scary, but this is
This old it's not like brand new
See omega lull omega lull l cool
I actually really like this game. I think it's really good. I think it still holds up
This many years later
Is it toxic gas in here too?
Why would you have a button to press that does that
Is bill back down there? Okay, you might be getting a call from bill. He's a fucking asshole
Ask you guys a serious question
What was the last time you left or listened to a voice mail?
What's the last time you left a voicemail? It's been a while. I think
Everybody knows that nobody checks their voicemails. So nobody leaves voicemails
Every time I get to a point where I really need to tell somebody something. I got to talk to this person
By the time I leave a voicemail for you if you're not available right now
I'm just gonna text you and i'll i'll you'll see that first before you'll listen to a voicemail
voicemail is is really just
As you know, I don't have a reason to do it
I think like maybe if you like call the doctor or something to like leave but even still you just call again
You call like at 8 a.m. The next morning and y'all you get through to somebody
I don't really leave them anymore
And I don't listen to them either
Somebody could literally leave me a voicemail
that says
Uh, mr. Albertson, this is
Uh free money giveaway incorporated. We have a check with your name on it. There's no quit
Literally, this is no questions asked you get a million dollars if you just call me back
This I that's it
It's just a full taxed one lump set payment
And it's there's three doctors and two scientists in the room to make sure it's legit and a police officer and a tax attorney
Police call me back within seven days and you'll get it and I I wouldn't get it
I would get that voicemail if that voicemail was left, uh, like yesterday
I would listen to that voicemail
in
July of 2020
When I go through and delete every voicemail that's saved in my iphone
Check now what if it's there?
Well, it's too late. Anyways, if it's there. No, it's too late. Anyways
Check now. No, I definitely don't have one
See now a great joke for this stream if I had thought about that beforehand
Was to have a voicemail on my phone of that what I just told you and it's like at the end it says
end of message received on
may
Oh, well, all right. Let me let me make sure I got everything that I need here. I've full everything
I don't think there's anything else in here. So i'm going to go the way that I'm supposed to go this way
And here this would be an even funnier thing to do
Is have that voicemail a different version of it like six or seven different times over the course of like a full year
Like I had a really good chance
Stop stop what missed lore?
This is scary girl and you're in the facility there
Pitch that around
Look, I won't miss this
It's not even in there. I don't want that
Uh, is this where the here we go. Where are they?
Wait, am I gonna
I'm not gonna like poison them. Am I?
Oh, I
Do they know where it is?
Who are these people?
It's a turret. Don't come in the room with the
Why would you go in the room with the turret?
Oh shoot. It's a turret in there
Everybody go in everybody running at the same time
No, you won't
Yeah, yeah
Who where?
It's a turret
There's a turret in there
What's with the cactus? I feel like this isn't a cactus theme
In this uh game. Okay, what about down here? What?
All right, but who was this did somebody fall off
And they're just like oh, oh well resume patrol
These guys know these guys aren't on the same team. Okay, that's good to know
Any secrets?
What the hell is the atc doing? Okay. Let's sneak around up here
A lot of ammo gonna be up there definitely put up the shotgun again. It's best weapons
You heard my gun
You didn't just hear my gun. Did you?
Okay
Uh, look at how many people are up here. This is ridiculous
Find him
Well, you did you found me?
A lot of blood a lot of blood here
A lot of blood missed lore missed lore
What I got five? I don't know what's over here. Is that this the way that I have to go?
I guess
Tell us the lore to mist
I
Couldn't do that
I couldn't do that
I don't know mist as you wake up on an island and you have to figure out why you woke up on the island and then
I guess leave the island
Is that somewhat accurate?
at least
slightly accurate
I couldn't stop
That may have just ended the stream. I sneezed the shit my pants. Kidding
Where is he? Oh health. I want that
nice health
upgrade
lore
He's no, i'm not
Sure, don't skip lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore
Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore. Don't skip lore
Instead of their doom a war is coming. I've seen it in my dreams
Fire sweeping over the earth bodies in the streets cities turn to dust
retaliation
This guy's doing a really great job of doing the random voice lines that play
When you spawn for the first time in a league of legends game as a champion
It's kind of all he does
fucked up medical stuff fucked up medical stuff
Who you know, the game starts to get hairy when there's a bunch of fucked up medical stuff
Like what are they? What are they doing in here?
All right, I got the upgrade. Wait, is this something else? I just ruined this gear
Stop stop it. What is that?
Wait, what?
I have to slow down
He did like a push-up
What how would you know it's me what if I was one of your colleagues what i'm trying to hide
That was not even slowed down but it sounded like it was
They all of them have been so far the whole game. They've been
That one was not slowed down. It was not during a slow down period. It was just
shit
God damn it. This is I love this game. What a fun game
Looks like we missed the party
If anything has taught me anything in my whole life
Ever since the talkback came out from home alone
If you slow anybody's voice down by 30 or 40 percent, it's funny every time
The talk boy the talk back. Yeah, the talk boy
Everybody had everybody had a talk boy
What what do you mean heads?
He dropped it on the how did you
How did you do that?
That's impossible
They all sound like orcs like ogres
Yes, they do
uh
Ogre
Oh my god. Oh, it looks like we missed the party
All right, let's is lauren here if there's lauren here. I'm gonna intentionally skip it
No
What what are they fighting?
I'm helping
Hey
He fucking he was trying to get away
He was going like
He was trying to like shitting backwards just run. Why are you doing that?
Instead of like like sliding backwards turn and sprint
Oh my god
My doctor is gonna be mad at me
I'm supposed to be just like taking it easy
I'm sorry doc. I I couldn't help it
But you should have seen what the guy did
He flew up. I I the guy was going this way and then he got magnetized his face to the wall and blood splattered
He's gonna be like what the fuck are you talking about?
Oh
Show him the cliff
Doc, you gotta see this. It's fucking hilarious
Yeah, you don't understand the guy was magnetized and his head hit the wall and blood went there and he like flew this way
And the other guy went oh shit really really slow because time was slowed down
And then he stepped back with his being exploded. It's gonna be like jeremy. Um, I would like maybe to refer you
It's like what?
Yeah, and then we have this that that 15 000 seagulls were saved
Oh, it's a big guy
No, it's not skee ball. God. Damn it
Okay, I feel like i'm playing against my little brother in an online multiplayer game
And he doesn't really understand how to actually play an fps correctly
And i'm just trying to give him an opportunity to to like think he's doing a good job
Oh shit, it's that was fun
Move your camera
No, I can't there's nothing up there for you to see
There's all bullshit up there. There's nothing up there
How do I can't move it because then if I move it it'll go in the wrong spot
I know i'm not gonna move it. I'm not going to that's final. That's final. That's my final word
I'm not going to move it not moving it
locate alice wade
bc
We've got funny music. No, that's not
All right. This is my shot. This is my shot. This is my shot. I have to make this work
Why would you throw a?
Shit
Why would you throw a grenade?
Because you saw light over here
Oh, oh, I threw it whoops I screwed that up. Oh shit. Oh my god. This game is fucking ridiculous
Oh, he knows what he did immediately after throwing oops
Really what was that explosion?
Can I say I want to see it can I see that I want to see it
I need to see the grenade. Oh shit that I have to somebody has it right and I don't
I need to see it
I can hear his intestines melting. I just want to watch it
You know if you see a really awesome part of the movie and you want to just rewind it and see the that part again
Mashed banana. What the fuck is this? Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
I just I just need to see it
No, not this one
Not this one
The one that just happened
When he throws the grenade down the hall
Oh here it is. Here it is. Okay. Here it is. I just want to see it. Just give me a sec
Why would you throw a the best part about this one is you can't really hear him but it's on the screen
Here show us you just no, I just want to see it
We're back to our regularly scheduled program
Whoa?
You want to fucking go you want to try this?
You want to do it like this? Good
Can you throw it? Can you get it in here?
Get a grenade in here get a grenade in here. You can do it. No terrible
Fucking awful your buddy
I want your buddy to do it one of you. Come on
If I won't move you get it in here do it get it in here. No, not very good
This is just the dunk tank again. I gotta be up a little higher. Come on up here
I don't have any heels left
What?
He ran out of ammo. Let's go. I need heels. I need a heel. There we go
Any more in here? Give me something else. Give me some more. Give me some more lore
skip
Pistol, no
No pistols
I already got these cool
Are you are you checking it out? Your first instinct is to throw a grenade
I thought he was aiming up here
Fuck that's a big guy. Did you throw a grenade? I don't know. All right, it's time
Fire every single
Weapon at that man. Do it hurry unbelievable. He shot me through a wall
Flat flashlight
I'm gonna die
Hold on. Is there health pack?
There's probably one secret health pack that I didn't get
And I need it bad
I definitely don't need it. I don't need it. I need it
Damn it. I'm in trouble
He's gonna do wait, what do you mean? It's gonna despawn. What are you talking about?
What's gonna despawn?
despawn
That big guy dropped Excalibur
Well, what the I don't give a shit
I can't use it. Anyways, that's that's not how Excalibur works
You don't just pick up Excalibur and go this is neat and use it. Nice peek. It sucks
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Where are you? Where are you?
This is why I don't play games like BR he could be in any of these bushes
I have no idea and he could see me and I don't know where he is. I don't know where he is
No, but he's an awful player. He just installed the game like an hour ago. Yeah, I I don't br
I don't I don't br. I don't do it
Flying low. Oh my god
How does it one way you do that? You're watching the stream
There's no other way that's possible
Trouble here. Let's go. Let's go
Oh duck
Oh
No
I gotta stick them. This guy sucks
Go, what are you doing? Did I get hit by it? What the hell hit me?
I'm fucked
I'm in deep shit right now walk forward shoot it with the gun
Um, i've shot him with the gun a thousand times. He's not here yet
Shoot it until it dies
That's good advice god, how did I use all my heels already? Why how could you not make that jump? That's
Ridiculous get it get it get it pick it up. What the fuck is happening?
What is this? Oh fuck. Hold on. I'm gonna be squad
Kelpax. Oh
Oh, he was he freaked me out so bad
I don't know why he was freaking me out
Okay
I have to make it into that fucking room, but this time if you have this if you have the detonator out
You can't pick up any items
Okay, here we go new strategy
Start walking down here. Is this stupid enough to work? All right. All right. All right. All right
No
Pick it up. See you later. We can't hit him sir. He's behind a glass door
No, he's just watching your life. Oh, this is not good. Oh shit
That's my line
Okay, don't use this that's for emergencies only
Uh, okay. I thought this was like a google satellite image of like a warehouse and roads and stuff. I was like, where is that?
All right, let's go
What's the next step here?
Computer no
No out here into the left
Take out the assault rifle. Let's get the most range. Let's get the most range on everything else
Up here and through that door sure thing
I get more
Wait, kill the lights
Why would you kill the lights?
How can you see me in the dark? Do you have night vision?
No, he can't see me
I just like proved that he
He cut himself off
Get down. Oh shit
All right, let's help kind of up against the clock with health here
I need some better
Skill so I don't keep losing
I'll turn the lights back on for god's sake
They were sitting in the dark now, that's embarrassing they were huddled together terrified god
Nothing else
No, we should turn it off again. Is that the guy standing?
He uh, you think I have attention problems
I have to stop laughing at this. I have to like
You throw a grenade in a dark room
Oh
Pretty awful. Okay health. It's strange. There's a piece of shit. That's all the health that's here. Let's go
75 hp
Is not enough hp, especially when you're playing on hard mode
It's dangerous. That's where I just was
Hey, look at this
ooh
Nothing here. Well
Um, there's nothing I can interact with in here. That seems a little strange. It's like the only place I can go
Out the window because I was just down there wasn't I or was I not down there?
Maybe I wasn't down here. I guess I wasn't down here
interval seven
Redirection nothing. Okay, cool locate alice's office. I believe it's probably here somewhere. Look at a computer
There it is. I'm not skipping it
Except for me because i'm the third or i'm the first. No first is the girl
Second is fetal third is me
I mean
Come on, do I do I need to spell it out for you?
Okay
No health packs. That's not good
Why?
scary
scary thing
There we go handsome minds good
Uh, oh, okay. That was kind of creepy
Oops, looks like we're getting in
Is human garfield dead? I don't think I don't think so. It's possible. I would assume we'll see
That character again. All right, here's some lore. This sounds real important
received on
june
3rd
1991 no, I think if you if you work in a in like a corporate environment, you have to listen to your voicemails every morning
Don't you?
That's how it works
I want to get that. What is it? Where's this ringing phone?
Was it not even in this room?
I would have loved to have seen whatever scary thing was in here, but the venetian blinds prevented me from going in
Are you serious? Really?
I could just go into the door. Where's this phone?
This is fucking driving me crazy
Proteus i'm gonna find the other guy's office. It's not it break room. I mean we'll get in apparently, right?
No, not yet. We could do that later. I need to get health. Where's this fucking phone?
Oh, well, maybe in another lifetime. I'll get it. Oh it fell crap
Wow, it fell this way
Uh
Efficiency is not more important than safety. How much further do I have to go?
Hey, okay. There's a supernatural force blocking the door. Nice supply room health
Give me something else something more than that. No, no, no, there's nowhere else. I can go up here
Fine, I could go up. Let me just see what happens if I go up
Good thing I went up
Surprised there's no uh upgrade up here. That definitely is
somewhere, right
Nope climb it climb it down
All right, let's find what was this guy's name to find the other this other guy's office
All right. Well, we're at a checkpoint good and then pick up the phone in his office
Wait, these soldiers are eating people
I don't think that's what's going on
Why would somebody those guys are not eating people are they?
Was that ever implied?
I'm not sure that's the case
Oh, what the fucking hell
I'm not going over there
Doesn't read the lore starts asking what's happening
What I mean, I I know what's happening
We've listened to all the lore. I missed one lore. We listened to you
Not really. It was that one time when the guy was talking about um
Uh, like why are you not?
Talking to me. I'm trying to call you
What anybody left? I think that's it
I see you up there
Oh, and here's another thing though about like the lore every time that I open up like a piece of lore or listen to lore
I look over and somebody writes l omega lul re
You gotta talk to those people not me
No, that that's that that's it's not me. What you heard the face break
Ow, okay
That was a little odd
Turn the light off just use the door like a regular human, please
All right, let's go
There it is
Oh, they heard them. They heard the message
that like
Who's shooting me from where?
No, you can't somebody finally gets it somebody gets it i'm actually surprised by that
I don't want to i'm not gonna i'm not gonna shoot that guy weird. I got owned
Um, why is there an alarm going off right now?
flashlight off
Data no already picked up everything over here
Why does this shit make you laugh but fuck doesn't because they don't they they don't say fuck all the time
Scott
Case in point that's why it's funnier. I think that's it, right?
I still live I have to go to
Let me see where where where where where was I?
I got turned around
This door doesn't open
So I have to go away through here. There we go. Is that door open?
Can I go through here?
Come on
There we go
It doesn't really do anything for me. Just kind of wraps back around
Uh, uh, yeah, I know i've wanted to go in that other room though
I got the health pack
All right. Uh, where the fuck am I supposed to be going though?
locate the this guy's office
I have not found this office yet. Somehow is it not in here?
I don't I shouldn't go down
Was there a room that I didn't go in up here?
He's just walking over dead bodies
You should have read the lore
Was I in the red area?
I just didn't go in the right spot
Well, we'll try it again
So this is where I was before
So this is like the middle room that goes through here's like a little break room
I guess I mean have I gone through here?
Yeah, because this is a circle
Yeah, this this whole this whole corner is just a circle
Is there a door here?
Or do I have to go down?
Because this is actually just a circle
Oh, here we go. There's still a spot here
I feel like I need to get in there
All right
Where is your phone?
Okay. Am I in your office?
I don't think I am
What why did you do that? Jesus?
What's your status?
Uh, well, I don't know somebody made a mistake is the status whatever that is
Okay
Activate
All the doors are now open
Oh that goes into that other room. Okay. I know what that is
Okay, I want to explore a little
A little bit see if I can get some more stuff
Like this
Okay, I got the full one. I'm gonna actually use that for a little while
What about this?
Ooh
It's turret time. I think I did it. How do I get out? So that takes care of that
Now I just to go back there and go in that room easy. Yeah. Well, just get a checkpoint anyways
Okay, this is back this way
There's one of the first doors back here
All right
What is this?
There it is and everybody's gone
I get the place to myself for the first time ever
That's hurry up music. I guess we're just gonna go
Why does it want me to go so fast? What does it want from me?
um
Faster, but why did it start here?
Um move move move, but there's nowhere to go
It wants you to slide kick the bodies
Oh, come on. Who heard that?
Is somebody up here? This has to be opened. Yeah, I think I can't do shit up here
I gotta go the other way. Holy fuck
You lived
Wait, I thought he was a chair. Okay. Uh, nothing nothing nothing
I don't hate anxiety music in games. It makes me feel like I I have to rush
Good not bad. Let's go now. We got new music
Why is the soundtrack just kicking in for the first time ever right now?
What?
Why
Why did he say that?
Oh shit
Wait, why is he why why did he move all this stuff?
The squad check it. That's some there's some problems in that troop
Shut your fucking mouth
Wait
Where are they?
What the fuck are they using for a weapon? It's inside my head
I it's inside my brain when they fire it. It's firing in my head
I'm trying
What was that noise?
That was the
That was an arcade, you know when you walk by the arcade
Do you want to know that sound that's the most the most quintessential arcade sound effect?
I'm gonna see if I can do it
You'll know exactly what I mean when I do this when you're walking by an arcade or there's an arcade near you or you're in an
Arcade and you hear this sound
That's the only sound that's the number one thing you pull from an arcade
And I don't even know what machine that is
I it's at every I don't know what it is. You just never know what that sound is
But you know what it's there every time
It's funny because i've never played a game of the arcade that made that sound
But i've heard it every time
Why?
Where should I go?
I wish I we just gotta I wish we just gotta shut the fuck up right there
There's nobody here
This this blood did he hit his head?
Oh, he's over here now
Oh shit
He's
No, that's I want to do better than that the blind boomer
Why was there blood here?
You understand there's blood
I want whatever the gun they have I want it
What the fuck is this? It's a shotgun
That's not that doesn't make any sense. That's impossible
What do you have for a gun?
So they were shooting from back here
like this
With a shotgun and it was like I was being sniped in the head
Cactus. Yep
Good call. Thanks
It's the deluxe dlc. No, wait a minute. Okay
All right. I got I got three hills now
I'm all right
Check it out
Is there a door up here?
I got his arm
Somebody come on
You gotta go through this
through the hole
without slo-mo
Just bang through the hole
He's not gonna move he's actually he's not going to move. He's not gonna move. He's not gonna move
Why are they getting so defensive now? They weren't they weren't doing this before
He's
It's not gonna help you
It's it's a couch
Somebody back here does not want to take orders
These guys are fucked
They hate each other now. What happened? They hate each other. How do you win three?
Oh
No, where is he? What the fuck I am
You're strong. You're very strong big guy
Let's go
Oh nice
Oh, I just took a health pack though. It's okay. Sorry. It's no matter. Oh you idiot
What in the name of god?
What? I'm almost dead, man
He's just waiting for me. Oh my god. He's got a skeleton gun
Refill didn't think that was gonna work
Let him sleep. He's a skeleton inside of there. Who the fuck is this? Oh, that's um, one of them. That's uh,
Giving up on being rescued
Let's you got all these voice bales
Fall joke
You're not one of them
Sorry gotta go
Oh, oh mega lol. I gotta go
You're not one of them. I'd pretty much given up on being rescued. Okay
Hello, I need to get to my dad
Some kind of classified facility. I've never heard of it
There isn't even a street address just utm coordinates. The entrances are all hidden, but I have pass codes
All right
Let's open it. You mean a helicopter?
Can we drive instead my car's downstairs in the parking garage? Let's go car plus one letter grade kind of check point
All right. What?
No way. I'm not going anywhere until I know he's okay
Hello
I get okay. I'm like I get like so adb bored like such random things
All right, let's go. I'm ready
No, stop. Just go. All right. Here we go. Go we need to escort to the roof for evacuation
Can you handle a weapon?
How do I get to the roof? Oh you actually have collision too. This is gonna be great
You have to go up
Just go up
It's good call
mess
What a mess
Where are you going?
Get over here. Oh, you're concerned about that
Where did she go?
Okay, where is she?
All right, don't
Get the fuck over here. You're freaking me out
Okay, hopefully just she just teleports with me
So, yeah
Who said that?
Excuse me
Oh my god
All right, save tuber
That was not a tuber reaction. That was an actual. Oh my god reaction
I have to go back to like the elevators
Let's go
up to the roof
In in you don't mess around do you?
Nope. Why are all the floors lighting up?
Hey somebody's pressing the she was about to say
She was about to say the thing that I said earlier so it's pressing all the buttons
so fucking
Some little some little shit's going down and pressing all the buttons. Why are all the floors lighting up?
Uh, somebody's pressing the call buttons get ready
Wait closed
What do you mean closed what are you talking about closed
It's not voice activated lady, all right, I gotta be ready floors lighting up get ready
No, that's not what I wanted to do
So close it
Close it you have to close it
I'm gonna bring people in here with me
See if we can get some friends in here
I know this is kind of
What do you mean this sucks
One hell
What's going on what happened to the power, uh, I don't know what oh
Hey, that was a late reaction
Okay, I did I turn it back on oh no, she's dead
Can't open this soft line. We're just gonna move
Save it. Hmm. Hmm. Can I make it under definitely not going up?
I turned it off
What what the difference from last time
What's the difference between the last fucking first time that I did it
That's it
That motherfucker heard me stand up creaky knees apparently. Let's go. Let's go
Did this game sorts code get leaked?
I don't know that's
Dead hit that's kind of bad
Supply room. Damn it. It got leaked like this. The actual source code got leaked. That's kind of that's not good
After it was released though
There you are. How did we get separated? How did you get out the power going out in the elevator?
Then the next thing I knew I was arriving on the top floor and you were gone
You should have a visual on the eback chopper
Great. Well
I am not waiting here. My dad's in danger
I
I'm laughing. I'm not laughing at the explosion. I'm laughing at the
shit
Just okay. I need to I want to look this time
Well
What I thought it just exploded
No, right
All right. Hold on that guy's so bloody
Where's the other guy?
What an idiot what a moron, all right, let's go i'm supposed to cut her off
Whatever flashlight
How did we have the same idea every time
He fucking made it
Whoa
Pretty good. I have to cut her off. So I have to go down there. I think but there could be a health pack
And that's much more important to me
than game progress
Absolutely ridiculous
Which elevator this one? No. Oh, come on. I can't get in there
Let's just have to go down
This guy's voice change he's not he doesn't have the accent
He used to talk like this and he's like that's it not anymore
He just happens to have an accent
You you could have said something
Oh look another character that is unarmed
unarmored and surrounded by lanister swords
Come with me
I don't care as long as one person as long as one person gets that. I don't care
Like two people will know what that is. I don't that's good for me. I don't care. It wasn't
Well, I thought you guys I thought better of you guys you didn't get it you didn't get it
Just didn't get it
Don't you know there are two ways to make everybody angry in chat make a rick and morty reference or say the word game of thrones
I think it's a guaranteed way to make everybody angry
Do a do a game of thrones reference and everybody will start screaming
It's like the new rick and morty
Remember like season one rick and morty everybody loved it and thought it was like a funny show
And then they the show kept going and everyone was like, I hate that show game of thrones season one and two
Oh everybody, that's the best show on tv now. Everybody hates that show
It's weird. Yeah, that's it's very simple very simple process
Fucking master manipulator. Sorry. All right. I'm going over here master manipulator, but
Can't fucking follow simple directions
You know, we have our weaknesses
master manipulator as a
Fairly
Sore sense of direction as you see very clearly
Oh, but once I get out of here, I will put you in a scenario that
You'll be very upset that you got it and make you angry and maybe eventually if I could figure it out
I don't know how I even got in here in the first place. I don't fucking remember
I actually don't remember how I got in here
Found it. What's another one? What's another show or movie or something that everyone like really liked
And then everybody hates now. I'm trying to think
Dexter
Yeah, maybe
I guess the real moral of that story is if you don't want the word
Or if reference to your show to make everybody like puke in their mouths and hate everything about your show
Is to just only have five seasons ever of a television show
I think that's what it is
Think of every tv show that had that had like less than five seasons people remember it very fondly
Okay, let's go
Five is too many
House had eight seasons house did
Get a little weird at the last like two or three seasons though. You know what I mean?
I if house was five four or five seasons, I think it would have been fine
But then you were you run into a family guy scenario where family guy had like three or four seasons and everybody loves that
Fucking those seasons best. Wow. That's the most that's the most funny the most hysterical show on television
Oh my god, I wish they would bring it back bring back family guy. It was so good everybody
Oh, it's my favorite fucking tv show. Please bring it back fox, please god
It's on adult swim now. Everybody loves this fucking show
And then they do 10 more seasons and now here we are everybody that everyone hates that show. It's it's weird how that happens
Because they went too long. They did it too long. They went too long
Simpsons was only good bad. Yeah, but here's the thing
Like south park is still good
What about that inch?
Now we're fighting robots. Okay
No, it isn't what?
I think south park is still doing like still making fun funny shit
Chat thinks nothing is good. Is that that's another thing too. Do you guys like anything?
Does anybody does anybody on twitch like anything?
I mean, I have a lot of things that I don't like but I feel like
Does anybody enjoy anything anymore?
Hold show that I already have that what's your favorite? What's your favorite tv show?
And don't say dream of that night five because we already know that one. Should I go in here? He took my answer
Wait, let me let me let me pay attention for one second
I want to make sure I don't miss any like heels or something
mash
All right. Yeah, it's
It's probably actually your stream
Well, thanks
uh
You know, i'm of the opinion we've got we've got like too much media now
It's like it's
With you could just open up netflix
And watch every television show ever
You got like netflix hulu
hbo now
You've got so many shows and so many movies
It used to be you had to wait until that shit was on cable television
once a week
Now it's just every every two weeks. There's like five new netflix movies
Where the fuck do these come from?
And they're all bad
This is a 75 year old opinion
I don't think so. I it's just like there's this a lot. Hold on aliens
Can I turn those into a skeleton? That'd be cool
Everything's in color nowadays
No, there's a lot of options
Oh, yeah, do you see me?
He's too fast
A minute it's making the arcade sound
Oh i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead in that scenario I gotta pull out the other gun
What was the last time I saved it?
Why am I all the way back here?
Are you serious?
Why are they aliens? No, it's not it's this way. I think they're just robot drone attack
things
I didn't save
Sorry
Always sunny is actually hilarious. Yes, it is
I mean, there's definitely this this
There are shows that are still good
You know what I mean?
It really does feel like if if everybody loves your show
More than five to eight years later. Everybody doesn't like your show
All right, here we go
That's why i'm telling you guys i'm i'm getting close
I'm getting close to being over that like 10 year seasons
When are you guys gonna start hating this show?
I just didn't even get a chance
Was that one of the robots that just said that
Okay, save it here
Now really yeah, really when we already kind of had this conversation before about like, oh, yeah after spree it was just like come on
That's my favorite episode. It will always be my favorite episode
It was the helicopter
shit
I got plenty of heels
Uh, let's get a safe right here. I think that's a good idea
All right, let's go
You know, I had to do it. Okay
The word, uh
Okay
No, all right
Oh, I could be here all day. I could do this fucking for like an hour
Watch this
I'm just gonna drop a grenade
They are right
Uh-oh, they're okay
Holy shit that guy that's the guy in the squad that invited the two guys to play and he's really good at the game
Those other two just were doing it because they wanted to make their friend happy
I'll get him this time. I'll get him
There's nobody alive
Nobody's alive to say that
What
Do nice room nice room
Watch your stuff. I know i'm trying to like stifle it. I'm trying
It's going all right. It's going all right. I'm fine. I'm going okay
I think we're fine
Don't shit yourself laughing. I won't I won't i'll be okay
Okay, let's see
I don't think there's anything else. Wait, should I go downstairs?
Can I go all the way down?
Have I ever shit myself laughing? No
I've never shit. I knew I should have went down
No, I have a lot of control over my
lower half
Don't worry
I have I have a very good amount of control
So many messages is this guy left. I think I just I I scared myself doing that a little bit
I think I scared a lot of you too
Stay down and and there was even an oh shit in there. I'm not sure you're paying attention. I love that so much
It's like my favorite thing
They planned this they did all that and the guy still
still was
Confused to have been played this game health packs
No, I got him. I got him didn't I I got five
I think I got one
Can't turn it off. Sorry
What what's oh I thought he was
Okay, I thought it was pointing over there at something
I can't get I can't get him off. He's stuck there forever. That's okay
What was the explosion it didn't hurt him
Jesus
I did. Yeah
Yeah
You gotta let me try out now
Psycho
Cover up anything else in here?
No, I killed like can I use the elevator now? I should be able to power's back on
Do my best joker laugh?
um
Maybe like maybe later like and why by later? I mean like like a few weeks
You got out
What?
Wait
No
Why is she going so fast?
So what she's going up to the roof right now
Is she gonna try to run me over with her car?
Oh god, I hope so
I'll be ready
Is she gonna try to kill me with your car? Do I have to walk up to the?
I have to i'm not gonna get there before her she's in like a porsche
Yeah, run up there. Maybe you'll get there before she does
uh
All right
I've had enough
No, how did I miss my crosshair was right on his body
You've soiled it
Yeah, I did. You're right. I did. I soiled it
I soiled it
Goodbye
Done deal. Don't I can take I put that away now. Let's get the assault rifle up
Lots of health. I hope it's a car boss. Please be a car boss
I would be so happy if it was a
Fight the lady in the porsche
Holy shit. There's a lot of people over there
Ah
That guy snuck all the way around. All right, i'm gonna keep it out. No, we're doing grenade
Grenade i'm gonna throw it. There's a lot of people over there this way
This game is epic
Yes, it is
You're right. It is
They don't even know
Nothing. Oh, hold on. What about the truck?
Ooh refills
I don't really need any of them. Um
Hold on
Let's check
No, let's go
turn the corner
g2
How do I
That's not gonna do anything man
Holy shit. Is that how you stop getting hurt from a grenade?
I do not have any
I'm gonna have to use the electric gun
See ya
That electric gun is pretty good
What did you have?
Don't want it
Dude, don't
Don't do that people
Good. I think i've made it to the top
Right. Damn it. No secret
I have to look at that
Well, hold on. I can't alt tab when I alt tab the game will crash if I don't do it in a very specific way
this way
Oh, I did it I did it
Why there
No car bus
I really thought we were that was we were gonna get out of there
You know what I mean?
It looks okay, but the pilot's dead and jen's banged up pretty bad
I'll live we're fine. It'll be a while before I can ice skate again. Yeah, we're fine. We have dialogue
You sure you want to send him alone? These guys ain't fucking around
By the time backup reaches you we're still a couple of clicks away from the ramama compound
So you're gonna have to get there on foot
Hope it's true. Oh, it's true
It's true
She'll be okay. It's you i'm worried about
Okay, let's go
Can't go in there
Can't go in here kind of a creepy place though. I thought that was a person folded in half
I looked over. I thought that was their legs in the shoes and that was their body like folded up
Okay, i'm getting condemned vibes from this place
That game is great
What a great game that was
You didn't finish the second one. I didn't I never finished the second one. Are you sure?
Uh, yeah, I did
Yeah, I did
I think he threw
Okay, I think the guy just stepped on his friend. All right, let's get the shotgun going
Stuff in this room probably
Both of them
Oh, I got them both
Is he dead? I think so
What am I looking for in here the enemy patrols?
I'm just walking
What is going on?
uninhabitable
Hello, is this guy dead?
No, okay itchy face itchy face. Not good lethal shoulder injury go through here this way
Uninhabitable, I can't get in. Come on. Really? So how do I get through here? I gotta go all the way around
Can I make it through here?
I mean I can
Not really
Should maybe go down the hole
Because I can go
What is that fucking explosion?
Oh, I do have to go down there. Okay
All right, I see the health pack
You idiot that might soft lock me. Oh my god. What are these guys? Seriously you motherfuckers?
great, all right
I could be
Guy was right here. Don't throw a grenade, please. He was good. He was gonna say it
He was gonna say it. I stopped him from saying it. He was supposed to say
Uh-oh
Whatever it is. It's big
Oh dear
You all right. Oh my god, he can run through we can break through all the walls
Holy shit. I i'm gonna use this whole damn thing
Holy god. Oh
I only have five more shots out of this thing. It's like the most powerful gun in the game and that took so long
Holy shit. Okay
Well, maybe I can get out of here now. What did he destroy?
Wait a minute
Where is this? Okay. Now this is the right way
Watch there be two of those things. There's gonna be two of those things
What happened it's that motherfucker right there
I
Don't know what they were looking at there, but
It wasn't me
Where is he right there? Is that is that him? Is that the guy who the fuck it is?
Well, they all have one
I want I wish I'd be going that room and get all that ammo. That'd be great. All right
We have to make a jump here. Is that not where you go?
Um, is there a little thing maybe thing on the right because of that I think that's what I have to do
Just yeah, it's right there in the nova you got to stand on like the brick part sticking out
Oh fuck, whoa, he went the other way
God damn it. That sucks. Do I really have to restart this again?
I don't think I can't cross over here. So is it really just that simple?
No, it's not is it? I don't think I can do this
That looks like you stand there and jump to there
Is that don't admit that's maybe not what you're supposed to do
I don't think you're supposed to do that
But I did it. I got a lot of ammo for this thing
Okay, um, I need to start using that
I'm just target practice
Let's go
Who else is here?
Anybody else?
Oh, wow. Look at you
That's what I get for talking shit. I don't why am I talking?
Helpax no
All right, here we go
Where's the southern guy? There's three of them and then there's another guy over here somewhere up on the roof. I think okay
Anybody else? Oh
Okay, that was a bad place to save the game, but it's okay save it right here. Nobody else, right?
Don't just pop out of the window and shoot me in the head, please
Yeah, what's one person? Oh, no, how scary? Why is this so scary?
That was they had they played specific music to be
Scared of that guy. He's what he's playing this on easy. This is on hard
What's with all the meat? I can't see shit in here. He flew up so fast
That the top of the door guillotined his head. That was fucked up. These are oh, give me that
These are the guys with the lightning the electric guns
That's pretty great. How much do I have now?
Nice, that's awesome
Where is he the fuck is he? Where is he?
I heard check it out. So where is he?
I'm gonna run right into him accidentally over here. He's over there. What what is he talking?
I thought he was talking
I was trying to listen to him. I thought he was having that conversation with the guy
He was a blackhawk helicopter crashed
There's a health thing in there
Is he alive?
Found him. He was outside on the side. This place sucks. All right, give me the uh upgrade
170 health seems pretty good. Doesn't it? Okay, let's go get in there. All right
Oh this she is the girl that drive drove off in her car. I should liquidate you right now
Wait, somebody behind you no flashlight somebody in here
What what happened? What happened?
What?
Dead
No, that was just a pot and a piece of cardboard no, not this
I took damage in my dream. That's bullshit. That does not that's not how it works damn. Yeah, I took damage in my dream
That's not how that you can't get hurt in your dreams. Yes, you can
Yeah, maybe if you like are having a dream about something and you like punch yourself in the face in the dream, maybe
If you like roll around and like roll out of bed and hit your head on your night table next to you then yeah
If you like sleepwalk making eggs and you put your hand in the pan
Yeah
I don't want to go that way
Wait, there might be a health back in here. What the hell was that?
Give him back
That is the exact tv that I used to hide under my blanket and watch wwf wrestling when I was younger
the exact television
That's not the right gun. All right, let's move now
Why do they do that every time
It's almost like they the game knows when I press the grenade button
Not this time
That's fucking ridiculous
Oh
Okay, let me slow down
this in my brain
There was no
Possible fucking way that there was going to be another person inside of that truck
Impossible. Oh, no, I can't get in
Checkpoint good two health packs. What are you preparing me for?
What are you preparing me for?
It's important, let's I just want to see if it's possible to get hit by
Okay, so I needed to make sure I didn't want to see if it was possible did I just drop that
Does anybody know what happened?
I'm camping
Spawn camping of spawn camp
Uh
Who the fuck are you oh that's so funny
What the fuck hello idiot
Uh-oh, it's like a it's one of those
Okay
Spawn killing. Oh, it's gonna make me laugh every fucking time
Oh, okay, I would laugh if they just kept spawning
Like why wouldn't they be able to get out
To just hold just hold down left mouse button one of you will kill me
Even when there's a hacker. Oh, you can just hold left mouse button out the door
Uh
There's more in there now
Were there four in there last time?
Okay, that's that I want to be like in that perspective
I've been in that perspective before that perspective is just a guy
going
Speed hacking back and forth and just holding down the mouse button that auto aims to your head
And all of us just like oh, no
Hold on wait, wait, just pocket medic me uber me uber me. We'll get out. We'll get out just just everybody took five medics
I know what that's like
It was bullshit. All right, I got full armor. I don't want it something's about to happen here. So i'm gonna
I don't know. So i'm just gonna bust through
Yeah, look at all these health packs. They're giving me this is gonna be fight against something
through here
No, really?
i'm surprised
Oh, right. Okay, we're going over the fence. You can't jump it
There's a door right here
It's the revenge of the
Where is it going?
backing up
You still alive
I think that guy fell in the window
Yeah, I think I didn't know what the fuck he was doing
Checked the back of that car. I was too focused on that guy
Anything else? No
Largest concentration. This is gonna be fun. Now, isn't it?
scaffoldings
Okay, nothing down here. It's not I don't get to be a badass like I was told
Save it here
Uh, I need to use the bathroom. I've got to use the bathroom. I gotta pee
So let me say let me get in a spot on the corner here
I'll be right back. I have to use the bathroom in game. No, like in real life
I'll be right back
All right
I have returned
Hello, so I feel like we're getting to the uh
The last leg of a game if I were to take a guess I would say this is probably it
Eliminate enemy patrols
This is another sniper section
Oh, no another fucking car
It was a whole squad in there. They were ready. They're sitting in the back. Let's go. We're gonna do it
We're gonna kill this motherfucker
I don't know what the driver
Is doing
Why?
Would you do that?
It's like hey, uh
That tom tom he's right there
Tom you're still going tom. You're going over the cliff
Okay, he knows we're fighting. You know what? I've noticed a lot more in this part of the game here
Not a whole lot of enemy talking
I think they're
I think they're trying to focus
Well, two can play at that game. I just won't talk either
Uh, never mind they're talking
That is
Unbelievable that he still was able to get that off
He got 10
Seven or eight bullets in his arm and his body and he still pulled it off his angle even changed
What happened? Oh, there was a tank right there. Nice. He's still left by the legs
All right. I gotta get up. Hold on check check check check check check
Check we're good
check
Get up one health back
Did he just dodge it
He went like this
Holy shit, man
I can't what I go from here. I gotta jump from here to there
Okay, I have to jump. No, I don't it's right here
The health upgrade. Yeah, I know i'll get it
I think I have to go around for the health upgrade like this
Can I see?
Well, it's not a health upgrade but
still good
Uh, I do want to go up here and see if there's anything over here though. We'll check there is
Body armor is nice, but I don't really this doesn't open right now
Nothing no fall damage, right?
Let's go
Down or around probably around first
Spawn camp are they just sitting in there waiting for me to do something?
All right. I'm gonna surround
I'm gonna surround the uh outside with stickies
And the second I see the door open to right click
And then watch the chat room and watch everybody in that spawn
Talk about how much of a piece of shit I am
That's gonna open right?
All right. I'm taking a gamble that this is going to open. That's just a gamble. I'm just i'm playing the odds
Okay, i'm just playing odds. I can pick them up if it doesn't happen. There's also a health upgrade over there. I think
Okay, so you can open
It might it actually might they might have to turn something on and all of a sudden boom it opens
Doesn't look like it that happens though. Just
Know that I was thinking about it. Let's make this smart
Wait, wait, don't do it yet. He's almost here. You're not gonna. Why do you guys always do this? Oh
You all right. You're actually pretty smart. Everyone else is stupid. Never mind. You're all idiots. You're idiots. So
No, not you guys. I'm no
I'll put words in my mouth. That's not what I said
It's not what I said. I mean it is what I said but I wasn't referring I was referring to these
These idiots
Okay, let's save it here
Somebody's mad in that room
Can I get him to come out?
Is he stuck? I think he's stuck in the wall. Um, I can't open the door
Well, I don't think I have to worry about that guy anymore
Okay, I heard a grunt and that
There was a loud grunt and then he stopped moving and his leg was sticking out of the wall
Wait, that's not you, is it?
You guys are the worst all right back to the shotgun
Mama. Oh, he didn't get stuck. He just walked back behind this way
And he walked the whole time
He walked a long way a very long way
It was actually in my favor though
I'm gonna use it
I need some big heavy weapons
There's a lot of those big guys now
So i'm gonna use it
on the big guys
Okay, this is
She's close now
Presence is strong here. Thanks for the info
nothing down
Who touched wait a heavy? No, i'm i'm just talking like straight up
like heavy
like a heavy gun
Like heavy weapons not the heavy weapons guy. Well, I mean a heavy weapons guy uses heavy weapons
Really?
What the fuck that guy's not it's so accurate with these
How is that guy not dead?
Okay
I need someone to explain how that guy's alive
I need someone to tell me what happened and why uh, where is he now?
He didn't but I shot him with
I killed him. What the fuck does he have for a gun?
Hold on. Okay. He has a repeating cannon
So these guys are much they're they're much harder. All right, I gotta bring out the real thing here
He's that's not gonna hit me. It's not gonna hit me. You're in a room by yourself
Oh, no your leg
Your leg is hurt
All right this thing look at this. I love what we dove out of the way too. Okay, let's check it
Is this thing gonna be good?
We'll try it
Repeating cannon nice. Okay, that gave me a lot of ammo for this
Very cool. Let's let's shoot somebody with this and see what happens good
Good up the ladder. This is the best weapon in the game
Uh, I wonder what it does
I'm looking forward to shooting my first person directly at the chest
This is where uh the little door that I couldn't go through earlier
Patrol
In more ways than one I think
Okay, I need that bad
Uh, do I have shark? Yeah, I got plenty of shark
It's very funny
I mean i'm just i'm just i'm just saying
I mean i'm just saying
Do I have any regular? Okay. I got a lot of regular grenades
It's a little too quiet
I knew it was quiet
I don't like that outcome. That's better
Okay, I actually like the shotgun for this better
Where is he?
There he is
Default shotgun is just the best weapon
No matter what scenario
It's just the best
That was a good face plant on the corner
All right. All right. All right
Where is he?
No, I think that's it
Nice work get banned for grenade spam. Keep at it. Keep at it. Keep at it. I'm coming. I'm coming
Is
Why did he go back? Come on. Come on. Come on
Come on, come on. Come on. Come on this way
Don't de aggro to your original spot. Yeah
I need that. I need you to step on that. I need this
Okay, i'm getting high ground here
Oh fuck
God damn it hit me right in the face. Now what you cheesed him?
How else are you supposed to kill those guys without cheesing them? That's the whole point
The entire point is to cheese that because it that it's impossible you you have to have to cheese that
Got it. That's probably a third one, too
I thought that was a gun. It's an arm
And I thought that was a frying pan
But it's a tire with a thing sticking out of it. I wasn't even gonna say anything, but I guess I just did
No healing sticks
This is the guy that beat yeah
I beat dark souls 3 on stream and i'm incredibly proud of it
and the dlc
That's not even an achievement anymore. He's here
Like I want to hear that conversation
I didn't know they were behind me at this point. It's okay. I want to hear that whole conversation
That's unbelievable how the fuck
Would you even rip around?
Yeah, okay. Yep. Come on out. Everything's fine. We got him that fucker's dead
Shoot him this way. Okay, it's time to just use my tried and true
He's here
He's talking to me like actually me or
I mean if i'm in that scenario and this super like
He's like sprinting around speed hacking and then just i'm gonna be like hey man
nice
What are you doing later? You want to like hang out?
I I guess I don't uh, no you did it good work
We're gonna do
And then when he and then be like, yeah, nice job when he's not looking
And then be like I did it. Where do I go? Oh if I have to touch what the hell is that what?
Okay
I guess you have this
Whole area back here. I don't have any at full health. So that's good. What is this attached to?
I get um
Kick some ass. Okay
Uh, so we can go down here
I was just in here. Oh, wait
I didn't look at this
No
I guess I don't need to do anything there. What about through here? It's like an elevator up there or something
Is this two skylights?
That just leads to this one
I'm getting nerd neck. Am I?
I feel like I have to do something with this
Can't like drop it
Obviously I have to get up there
Question is how?
Why can't I open?
This door didn't open last time
Why is it open now?
I I hope I tried to open it. I pressed I did you can go back and look. I really did. I promise
I did I really did
All right, let's go left
health upgrade
Yeah
What do I sound scared?
Um, i'm not scared. Um
Well, i'm a little i'm a little flush and queasy
But that's for other reasons
Did I just fall?
Who was that?
Uh
Here we go again
Hey, okay. I'm alive
And did I I didn't even go anywhere
Cool. You wasted ammo
Well, I they would have killed me
Thank you
incursion
locate ah
locate
wait
That didn't do anything
Dead dead
I'm glad you regenerate
To at least 25 that would be so
Awful if you didn't buy this on hard. It really doesn't matter
Because if you get shot like two or three times on hard you just die
So maybe that doesn't matter. That's no that's not an alarm, right?
Wait, just check the like health packs
I don't I I am in
The market for them. Here we are
And go that way
And go up here
Nothing. Okay
Let's check over this way
Multiple ways to go
I'm just gonna go through the vent
Oh, what are the oh nice. I haven't had these in a long time
I can't all right. Can I break this one?
I can't go through this
All right, let's just two grenades fine
Okay, let's go down
I don't think there's much else for me to do here
Still no health
Wait hidden. Nope. Hi guys
It's the last thing you're ever gonna say
Are you it's it's uh, it's garfield's human garfield
Do I get to kill human garfield now?
I really hope I do
Hey
Remember me
I'm coming for you
You don't have very much time remaining
That sucks. Let's go. I'm gonna pull out. What am I gonna do? Yeah. No. Yeah
It's part of the best. Let's do it
Best gun in the game that I do under the power of one guy
One guy
Can seriously change everything that's right attack me during a cutscene fucking coward
Coward attacks me during war coward. He's peeking around the side
Yeah, and now i'm gonna i'm gonna make your life a living hell. I'm killing you with the scary gun
Yeah, that is that is I was gonna say the same thing. He took the words right out of my mouth
That's really fucked up. Okay
Let's go up
Go up and can I crawl over?
I think I can crawl over the whole thing
Oh, that's sick. Nice
All right
I'm gonna drop in on him
Spider-man meets fear. Why would it be spider-man? He's not in here again
When is the final confrontation gonna be with this guy?
He keeps just barely getting away
Come on. I mean i'm gonna do what i'm gonna do. It's me. It's my life
so i'm gonna decide what I
I decided to shoot that guy because he was he was dangerous to me
These are all explosive
Yes
All right full health pretty much
That's all I need
Just like my father when we used to play
mario brothers
see my dad
was not like necessarily really great at video games, but we had the regular nintendo
and
What he would tell us to do we had regular just super mario brothers, right?
And he would tell us if we got him to the last level
with five lives
That he would beat the game for us because we couldn't do it
So we would always just try to get to the end and get have five lives and hand and be like dad
Dad, you have to beat the game. We got five lives at bowser's castle
And he'd come over be like, all right, excuse me. Let me sit down and he would do it every time
But we had to have five lives though because there was a couple places where he knew he was gonna die like three or four times
Uh, how do I I guess we're going this way
Gamer dad it was only with that though. It was only with mario brothers
He didn't really play anything else
It was it was pretty wonderful
But he wouldn't beat the game for us
What?
I had nothing to do with that one
Uh-oh
Okay, we're gonna have to do this strategically
One more I could use the force to find out what the fuck this thing is back in the regular shotgun, please
Gentlemen not a very good hiding
Oh, it's not explosive. Come on
He saw it was a silent under the breath of shit
You did there you're the one that killed me. You're the one that finally got rid of me. You finally killed me
Outplayed me completely
Shit I love this game so much
It's so
That's so stupid
Which way oh my god, what a fucking fun game
Uh, these guys are
I feel bad
What the fuck
Why is he not skeleton? Oh, no, no, no, no
Panicking I panicked like a lot a lot
Whoa
More health, right? That's not a terrible place to be in
I'm gonna die down here
Turn off the light
Reload the gun
And get ready for that and we're gonna do a wall bounce here
No, I don't think I need to
He backed into it. He stepped. Uh, you idiot
Did you kill everybody too? You did nice work
He's over here. Did I overthrow that?
I got him. I got that guy. I really did
What's over here?
Nothing. Okay
What in here? No
You're locking me in
They're locking me in
Fine. I'll just go down the sewer
I'm your favorite centipede streamer
Okay down we go, okay, I did that on purpose because I did I took a lot of damage for no reason
That was pretty brutal
Sorry about that. All right
Oh shit, he's coming down here. Goodbye. What was that? All right, there's the little shortcut
Get out of here
Up and under let's go
All right, there's traps everywhere just activate them
Shit, I may have fucked that up. It's all right
Well, whatever. I'm just gonna walk this way. Anyways
You check it out. I don't want to go over there
Couple of dopes
Somebody needs to make a fire extinguisher smash super cut
It's just available for me. So I do it and then turn this
No, i'm not exactly sure what that did, but it did something. So let's go up
It's just a
It's just a thing that I know
You know what I mean? It's routine
In a game with scary jump scares and all kinds of weird fucked up enemies. This is routine for me. It's comfortable
Okay, I can't go anywhere
Is it kill me
Unless I don't fuck it up. I'll be fine
Here we go. Costco is garbage tier pizza
Why would you eat Costco pizza?
Is it good?
I don't know
Because it's good
It's pizza tier list. It's good and cheap
I thought Costco is where you go buy like 40 tubes of toothpaste
No, hey, I wanted to do that
Why is it on tv?
That was so anticlimactic
He just like
I just wanted to do I want to do what needs to be done. Come on like that guy can't like get thrown into like a
One of like the silos or something
Well, yes, we're gonna slide kick his corpse off. Yes, that's don't worry
You think i'm not going to do that
Those things open every time
Those notebooks just go like that when you go near them
It's actually really strange
He's gonna be like hero
Come over here
There's one last thing I need to tell you right? Why is he like happy?
The only way in
Is to divert power to the door. Divert power to the vault door
I can't
You can't slide him off
One last meal for you
Still hungry
Why did I die from that? All right, tell me again
The only way in
Is to divert power to the door
Okay, i'll see if I can divert some power
You hang tight guy that'll be dead when I get back lying down further on his back and not breathing
see
Oh, i'm gonna go down this way
nothing
What the fuck do you keep doing that so well?
I'm gonna die
He's throwing another one. He's trying to throw another one
Turn off the flashlight
What is that? Oh, I guess I got health
Okay
Here we go
I'm taking this out. This thing is
You fucker
Really? All right. I need to start using the other gun. Did you drop one of these two? Didn't you? I guess not
All right. This thing's gotta be used
Get the fire extinguishers. No, i'm over that. No
I don't do that anymore
Say right
nice
Yeah, i'm over that i'm more into the magic notebook's opening though
I want to open those
fucking
Fire extinguishers are old news guys
Do we have power?
Is that what that means?
We're connected
We have a signal
Maybe I can't believe I used to do that shit
Embarrassing. Oh, let's just go check it. I thought that was damn it
Do I have to do both sides?
I mean that was a pretty elaborate
Thing that happened. Is it open? This does not look like it's open
It is not I have to do them both
So let's go this side. Did I go down here already? Did I was there on this side?
Yeah, it's already are they connected is both both sides the same thing
Do I have that right? Do I just have to do something else down there?
Or do I have to actually go to the other side and this is the side that I was on before
This went the wrong way. Yeah, that's what i'm figuring
so
Theoretically now i'm on the other side
No, i'm not
Am I? I'm fucking confused
What the fuck am I doing?
uh
Okay, so
They are connected
They're they're they are connected
so
I have to go back down to where I was before
Because they would that that device was down there. So
I don't it's not about two different sides. It's just going back down there and
pressing more buttons
Because I went right last time
Okay. Yeah, I thought I had to go like on the other side and there was another one of these
All right. This is double yellow
We have both the yellow switches in
Whatever the
Whatever that means
so now
Is that enough? Does that open another door to do the blue ones now?
I don't know
Or is that just power?
Well, this door is the two yellow now. I gotta find the two blue. All right, that's what you gotta do
All right, is he alive? Anybody else alive up here? I don't believe so
No, you're dead
Just making sure you're actually dead
Does that say caution no, this guy used to be my favorite fire extinguisher smasher
Sure, whatever you say. Let's get up there if I can
So I need to get up there. But what's secret? Is it great right there?
oh
Nice
I didn't know there's a magic notebook up there fucking sick
He's over this game. No, no, I'm not. I really am not i'm just a little drained
But that has nothing to do with the game it has to do with me
oh
Every fucking time it's awesome
Oh, there's other magic books
All right. So now
This is two yellow so I can open it
Nice
Hey, look at me. I'm up here
I hear something. Finally. I have two health. I haven't had two health packs in probably an
What is in the wall? All right long range think I can get it. No
I don't like it matters
Somebody somebody threw a grenade
And it hit me right in the head
I'm stuck in i'm stuck right now
I don't like that outcome
Fucking the grenades the grenades I got double tapped. I'm just going in fuck it
out of my way
What does he have for a weapon?
No, I don't want the outcome here. All right, let's go. Um, i'm actually done fucking around
That's fun. Where's the guy with the rocket launcher? He got I think it's serious there for a second even though I took two health packs
Streamer dies to grenade and goes bald
one of these days
Here's the real here. Listen, this is important one of these days
You know, let's say I stream for like another let's say I keep streaming for like another five to ten years
right
There's going to be a scenario where i'm going to actually be truly bald
Like an m on the top of my head back here
And you guys are gonna have so much fun
I want this up. Isn't that too yellow?
Um, i'm gonna go up. Can I even go up anymore?
nice
confused
Glitch it out and get up there
Because this door doesn't open I get up here. So why can't I get this door open?
Is there a problem with this? Why can't I open the toilet room? That means I have to go back through
Where do I go? No one tell him. Wait, maybe no one tell him
All right, is this blue?
Blue blue
She's not in there. Line like round, right? Here blue is not ready. Where is it?
Wait, wait, wait, what's going on there? What is this in the way? What do you mean? We'll fucking get rid of it. Okay
There we go. We got dated upload get it uploaded. Get over here. That's it. Now plug the damn thing in
Be on shoulder
Will you guys relax and then I gotta go through that door
Blue blue, right? There it is
Cool. Let's go
Now I need red
Red and red and that's it. You have bees all over your skin
Shit, I should probably go to the doctor
Cool. All right. So that leads me to now. I need to go back to the door
That I just was at because that won't open
But now it should open now. I wonder if my hypothesis is going to be correct
It is okay. Well
Hey, hey, why is it why is it just dust out of here? All right, i've had enough of this
I hate these things
How the fuck you rely you're supposed to kill these things without them
arcade machining you
I like that. Okay, nice. This thing's not even that bad. They're fine
I remember when I thought that was fun
memories
It's like looking at an old photo
No, I don't where are the items?
That's new
What's in there? Who knows?
We'll never know till I go this way
I'll take that heal, please. Thank you
pretzel germa
What do you mean pretzel pretzel is the rocket launcher? I don't think I want it
No, fuck that thing. Okay
So what is this for
Something to do with this
What do I need to do with this thing?
I tried shooting it
Is something else here wouldn't grab if I put some barrels in here?
Shoot the ones that explode
Get inside
Okay, get inside
That's a lot but whatever I hear those
stupid robots
They're in like the ceiling
Did I go in
Maybe I should go in I need to get up there. Can I just walk over there? I sure can
I was trying to get superpowers
All right. We're good
No, I shouldn't uh, I didn't mean to do that
I wanted to get a good view
This door is gonna open
They're all done. I went I created this I finished
You want superpowers dude? I can try to get you some
Not today
All right, i'm gonna do my best
That's it to go through the door now
These people aren't even real
Hey
There are four pylons damage the reactor
What about you what are you gonna do I guess he's just gonna die there yeah, okay
Contact from here on be careful of this wave guy. Not only no, well, he doesn't have a super shotgun. I do
What does he have?
mustache and a big brain
Good luck
You take walls down with this thing
All right. Well, what about here we go. I don't i'm gonna save this i'm gonna use the default shotgun
It's my bread and butter. You guys know that
Build them all i'm not this shit again. You still don't know do you?
What you are?
Why here what's the first thing you remember?
It's the joker given name. That's the joker. Where were you born history? I don't know. Where was I born?
You and the same mother
Okay, can you tell me the story without me having to shoot ghosts? You must have sensed it
Like just tell me see in your mind, but perhaps you can see into hers
Life of waking from mind yourself
And another will set her free
Damn it
Can we rain check? I don't have any grenades
What but what happened this soldier's just been watching just oh shit
That's the real time to say that is right now. I just fucking hurt myself
I thought this is a dream
What do I have my weapons?
Just this okay
Shit, it's fucked up
You probably shouldn't shoot the volatile ball of destructive gas
Hey, hey open up. It's me
Actually be more like this. It'd be like
You can't hear me
Oh, no
Get away from me. Get away from me
I do appreciate the golem run. It has to be in every horror movie. What's that?
Smoke over here. What does it do? Uh
Who opened up the portal to hell a lot of damage there?
You did you did this? Okay, just lying around. Let's use the pistol for the first time ever
Yeah, i'll use the pistol. It's like kind of fun to shoot. It's only taken me until the last
20 minutes of the game to realize it's a fun weapon. It's not as good as the super shotgun
Which way this way
Nope escape and destroy expose and destroy reactor cells to sabotage energy pylons
Hey, that doesn't that doesn't cause damage
Shoot all the yellow spots
Uh, am I getting in close?
Can I do it?
Okay, go
Uh-oh
What the hell?
I'm almost dead
Give me health pack. Give me a health pack right here
Uh-oh
That way that way that way that way that way
Let's go. They're gonna get in right? They're gonna get in here
Hey
How are you guys all right, how's everybody doing i've had quite a day who just gave up a hundred dollars freddy dread
Just gave ten thousand seven hundred fifty bits germa. I'm scared
Well, thank you for your more than hundred dollars an insane amount of bits
motherfucker
Hey
duck
Go around it. That's child. That's it. Let's go
Give me out. All right, where are they coming from? All surrounded awesome
Uh, oh fuck. Oh fuck where they're going. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
Get away from me
Where am I?
Hey, did I do it? Okay, i'm going
Shit. Oh shit. Oh my god. They're everywhere
Did I miss a health pack fucking dumb person just jumped back down
No, i'm fine. Okay, go
Don't break i'm almost out of bullets
I'm almost out of bullets and then I have to use the shotgun that hurts me
Nope, i'm gonna
No
I didn't want to have a temper tantrum. Like where is it?
I've been able to do this the whole game
I've been able to punch the whole game
No
Oh, but there's so much fun things I could have done
Where's the gun? What happened to the gun? There's like two guns. I want
The other one what I don't even know where it is. It exploded and flew away. That's great
Okay, whatever. I'm just gonna put this on for now
There's nothing around
Yeah, I put that's doesn't hurt right? There's a lot of weapons here
Close the portals
This gun is too good, but I don't I can't get close with it
I almost just fell through that
You've got to be kidding me
I'm supposed to fall through that the machine gun god one of these is like this day to jump now
Now this is a way scarier game than the last
Seven to eight straight hours of this game. I've tried so hard to forget
You were born in this place
Place I was there
This place
That's me
Making those noises
You will be back to the box. Okay
Let's leave
Rick did I do it? That doesn't seem right
That's not right that's incorrect that doesn't seem like the right uh, can I get back in the room go back in this room?
Go quick. Go get in the bathtub
Go get in the bathtub. That's what you're supposed to do. Go get in the bathtub
I think i'm dead massive explosion detected by a Hannibal 3 spy satellite in the vicinity of classified
Silly moments before signal was lost efforts to reestablish link on successful status of fear operative unknown
I'm
Since the explosion
What happened to us?
What how is that epilogue
epilogue
We just we just watched it
mushroom cloud and then
The ring lady went in the end of the helicopter
It's got to set us up for fear, too
The helicopter you're on got attacked again
attacked again
Yeah
Either the how long are the expansions?
Are they a couple hours each or how do they play out?
Four hours. That's not bad
well
So here's here's what we're going to do for the next
Uh a few days
I'm not going to be streaming tomorrow
But we are going to go
Stop falling over. We are going to do uh, I originally was going to do today yesterday
And then saturday sunday, but we're going to do saturday sunday monday
so
We'll instead of doing four days. We'll do like five for the last six days
And what's on the list?
There are a few things actually there's rhythm games, which i'm probably going to break up the horror stuff
But we are eventually going to make our way to this
This is siren for the playstation 2
and
Last of the probably the horror games that i'm going to put at least some significant time in
Is this one?
We've got some interesting stuff for sure
The thing in siren are probably the how we're going to round out and then the halloween stream
Now that's a yeah, i've heard i've never played this
That game is hard as sin. Well, it's all right
You guys can help me
You guys can help me out in these ones. So don't worry, but i'm not streaming tomorrow
i'm just gonna try to gain some energy
and hopefully
by
The end of this week. I'll be a little bit more
Used to me having to use this medication
Because i'm really only going to be on it for another probably four or five days
so
Yeah, do less cocaine
Yes, and by less i mean you mean zero and by zero you mean never
Yeah, i'm really i'm just doing less cocaine over the last of the next few weeks
Jesus christ
Jerma strikes me as an e guy
No, jerma should strike you as a guy that likes salad and bananas
He likes eating salads and bananas and sometimes he has like captain crunch sometimes
What?
I like I don't do drugs. That's what i'm saying. I don't do drugs
I don't do drugs
That's not true. I'm on them right now
Oh
I mean like prescription
for prescription
Hey, thanks for watching everybody
I'll see you. Uh on the next one
Not tomorrow, but the next day and the next day and then we'll do three days in a row after tomorrow
i'm gonna spend most of tomorrow just
Trying to energize again
I've just been so tired. This
It's definitely the med this medicine is making me so fucking exhausted. I don't even know why it shouldn't
I just broke all my bones
But you do what you gotta do, right?
Someone just wrote good
What's wrong with some of you guys?
Why?
All right
Uh, i'll see you guys on
No, what's today? Hold on. Let me look at the let me look at the actual what I want to do
Yeah, so tuesday wednesday friday saturday sunday
Yeah, that sounds good to me
and then
I gotta hold on. I gotta really plan this out because
If I do saturday sunday monday
And then maybe
Because the halloween stream is going to take a few days to set up
So now that there'll be plenty of time to do at least
Because before how the halloween stream i'll be live how many more times
See one two three
We'll get some rhythm games done
And then it'd be like one or two
Or one day there two days off there
And then like one two, three four. Yeah, there's definitely plenty of time to do at least one. All right. Let me ask you then
So I can plan this
What would you rather see over the course of a couple of streams?
the thing or siren
because
There's only really one of them that I could do and get it done
I would assume
I'm gonna do a straw poll right now where there's still people here
If I can do them both I will if I can if I can make that happen
But i'm pretty sure both these games are at least 12 to 15 plus hours long
And look if if it's not interesting I could you know
And move on
They both are gonna be interesting
just because I you know, I did a little bit of research to see
What's the thing the thing?
Is the sequel to the movie?
It's actually I believe it is actual canon
This is like what they did for a sequel
The thing is a sequel to the actual the thing movie and this is still very close
Yeah, you have like a squad in this game and you have to control everybody's emotions
People sometimes don't trust you. They think that you're the thing instead. It just seems like a
fun experience at least for a couple of streams
And siren from my understanding
Is a game where you control multiple?
protagonists
You choose a protagonist that you want to play
For that particular chapter or something, right?
They both seem pretty interesting
And siren siren is going to be probably much scarier than the thing. The thing is going to be more
third person creepy gross
Action game whereas siren is I believe an actual horror scary game
But uh, i'm i'm gonna call this here in a second if you have not decided if you've not picked
I suggest you do because it is very close
They're both horror games
They both are technically horror games
But I think siren is just a
scarier game
And the thing is more actiony
The thing is probably more like fear was
All right. Can you re-vote? What do you mean re-vote?
re-vote
You didn't know what the games were
Wait, so if you didn't know what they were, why did you pick one?
I said, what would you rather see me play this or this? It's like, ah this one, but it's like, all right. Well
Shut up, just let me re-vote
They're both very good apparently so don't worry and i'm gonna play
I didn't get them to not play them. I just which one would you which one would you rather see first?
All right. All right. That's it. That's it. We're doing the thing
That's the one we're gonna be doing the thing
And the siren will happen
Probably immediately after it. Let me change my vote
mad face
No, wait, you'll see them both. Don't worry
What is this
All right
I love this game. All right, I'll give my my final thoughts on the urgent of the fear
No, not the the it's not the thing. It's it's not the fear on fear
That was very good. It was just fun
And that's all you want out of a video game. Yeah, I just it's it was just fun
They got a little repetitive in a couple places, but it was still fun. I still liked it
Good stuff. All right. Let's do the
Let's do the bits
Have them open here from earlier
And if you take it off, we'll see you again this weekend
for a
Saturday Sunday and then monday extravaganza three days in a row will do
But I thought no, it was great. I loved in nearly every second of playing fear
It was great
And the oh shit stuff is is it gonna be stuck there forever in my brain?
All right. We'll see you on uh on Saturday if you're leaving
Thanks for joining us
And for the rest of you, we've got a few things to talk about we've got some bits to do
Let's go back to earlier today
We had 300 bits from
kore
Who says hello, mr streamer. Hope you're feeling good today
Uh, it's cool. You're doing eu friendly streams now. Also, do you think you'll play planet zoo when it comes out?
Uh, absolutely
I just didn't want to play the beta because I wanted to do the complete game
I didn't want to be limited by anything and that that's not I
Hold on this top sub gifter thing is just all fucked up. I'm gonna change it
Okay, here we go. Let's try it again. If it's still me. All right, if this is still me i'm going to uninstall stream labs. OBS
All right, it's gone
Okay, it's gone. All right. Uh, but anyways
Yeah, planet zoo. I just
Limited in the sense that I it's not like oh i'm so good at these games and i'm so talented
And so creative with all of my my I look at my habitats. I've no
But I just want all the animals. I just want to I just want access to everything
And that's coming out soon, isn't it?
What are the rhythm games gonna be? They've got a parapher the rapper parapher the rapper too. I'm jammer lamby buster groove
guitaro man
and uh
What's the other one? It's like one more
Is at least uh one more that I have?
Yeah, all great games. Yeah guitaro man is god tier. Oh, yeah
And guess what?
I've never played it
I saw it in stores. I've seen people play it. I've never held the controller in my hand and played guitaro man
So it's gonna be blind
Can't wait, but yeah, i've dialed the streams back a couple hours just because I know
that living in pacific
Daylight time still whatever it is
Streams get late for everybody. So I don't want to start at like four o'clock anymore starting around one or two is much better
For everybody me included
So yeah, i'm happy that people think it's a good start
Sad vega. Thanks for the 250
Your voicemail question is nonsense. I left one about 10 minutes ago and got a call back
I do it for a living we have people like you you make our lives hell
We have our tickets open sitting there forever because they never pick up and they never reply
You wanted our help. Why won't you return our calls you monster?
But here's the thing
I got no, I have no excuse. You're right. It's it's not nice. You're right
Uh, but I it's everybody. It's everybody. It's everyone. It's not just me
When I brought that up, I I I think 3 000 people all said that they do the same thing
So it's a it's a whole it's an us problem
You know
Until we find out a way to have
Voicemails be you know what voicemails will be gone in 10 years. Anyways, doesn't matter
You'll be able to get a text message and it'll just be read in your brain
You'll get like tts text messages
You can just turn them on
So yeah, the voicemails will won't exist in like another probably 10 20 years
So your job will get way easier
Hey, just a sad boy. Thanks for 300 bits. No message. Just
300 bits. Thank you. Uh, thank you. Emmanuel depressed. Thanks for the 500 bits
German, I know the stock trading joke is a thing
But do you still dabble in stocks and if so, what kind of stocks do you buy and any stock trading tips from the richest streamer on earth?
Okay, thanks
I'm of the opinion that you should never take trading advice from anyone because everybody's guessing
You just have to try to use your best judgment on what you think
If you're gonna just kind of play around with like a little bit of money and don't ever use
That much money when you play when you like trade
Is not don't do that. If you want to have like a little robin hood account or something where you
Mess around with like 30 40 50 bucks or something, but don't don't like all right
I guess i'll buy 10 grand worth of
Apple and then it's just it's gonna maybe it'll go up tomorrow
Uh, but if anyone ever tells you let me let me tell you something. I got so many let me tell you
I know everything about the stock market. I got this I got that I I you know, I got this chart
I've got this let me tell you that's you gotta buy this one. No, just go just eat a banana
He's talking to his past self
Banana stocks
And maybe you'll calm down
And maybe you'll get the right amount of potassium
I don't think you guys realize just how
many problems
are solvable
With a banana just by consuming a banana
That is the world's
Most versatile fruit it does everything he's saying invest in no i'm not saying to invest in but no, why would you do that?
oh
w
Oh, why did I read that?
I hate bananas. I used to too
I did
I don't know why I read that but
No, here's the one thing that you need that i've realized over the last five to ten years
you can't
You can't tell people what to do with their money like because then you almost become responsible
For if that something goes wrong
You know what I mean? Let's just say for instance and i'm gonna put a huge gigantic asterisk on here
This is a joke scenario. This is not real
And the following sentences are are fabricated
If I told you to go right now hey, yeah, yeah, I got some tips for you jack open up um
Yeah, you really should get into I mean honestly seriously like whole foods is starting to really take off amazon
Like you really probably should start to buy a little bit of the amazon stock
So, uh, once like the big whole foods earnings call happens, uh, you know go up
Maybe for probably like five ten percent sell it on the next day
If that doesn't happen
I
I've just made an enemy, you know, what if that doesn't happen?
I did that so I will never tell anybody what they should buy
investment wise
Except you know if you were talking about that bitcoin and I still wouldn't
bitcoin
Invest in vault going no. Yeah, I
But long story short, yeah, yeah, I can't I don't want to tell you what to do with your investments. Just do your research
If you think a company is worth investing in
Really look into it and see what their plans are on the future see what you what you think they're going to do
And if you think it's worth it
Don't let anybody else try to tell you that unless this person
No, you just can't you can't if you have a financial advisor then you have a stock portfolio then yeah
Then trust what that person does
Because you're it's you're that's your financial advisor
Not the guy on the subway
You understand?
anyways
Uh where we are here. Thank you fitty for the 500 bits. You're the best
You're honestly the fucking best term. I thank you for being you. Can I get some germa hearts in the chat?
Well, thank you. That's incredibly kind of you
Thank you fitty
Thanks for the 500 bits
Thank you apple shift. Thanks for the 250. Hey, I just got hired for my first job ever, which is really exciting
But it's also bittersweet since I have to miss most streams from now on
Depending on what my work schedule will look like
Maybe they'll let me listen to them while I stack boxes
Let's cross our fingers
But in the meantime, let's go vaude gang
Well, uh congratulations on getting your first job
Hopefully you learn some stuff
Hopefully make some money
and yeah, I mean
depending on what you do
if um
Maybe they will just let you just kind of hang out with like some uh ear pods in or whatever
but if not then
Whenever you decide to show up if you feel like coming out and hanging out here. Yeah
Oh, you want to watch the vods. There's a lot of people to do that too. So
thank you for
watching for as long as you have
and
Make sure you do your work though. Like, you know, but I I scream a lot on this stream
He's talking about stacking boxes. I don't want you to have like a 50 pound box in your hand
And I scream something and he like drop it
I don't want you to get like hurt
But thank you. Congratulations on the job
Stephunky checking next to the 300 bits for all the new viewers in chat
Don't worry. Jerma has an inside joke where he acts really stupid and doesn't understand something. Yeah, I know right
All the all the new viewers they they'll figure it out. You know, it's just like a funny
It's a it's a yellow bell moment where we just
Where am I?
Where the where the fuck am I? Oh, this is another hallway. I'm in a circle. Fuck
And everybody laughs wicked hard and then I look in the camera and I go
And I wink
And then the stream turns off
And I lie in bed and I look at the ceiling
and I go how
Fuck did I walk in a circle?
seven
fucking
times
And I squeeze my eyes for like to squeeze my eyes real tight to try to like block out the memory. I'm just like, yeah
Yeah
Blink. All right, it's gone
He's crying
And then I take a nice bath
You're like ren from ren and stimpy. I you know, i've always really connected with ren
Do the voice
See, no, nobody can there's one person that can do that voice and it's billy west. No one else can
That reminds me. I need to go back and watch
The old ren and stimpies they tried to bring it back and it was just a disaster
The original ren and stimpy
Is just so bizarre
and interesting
Billy west is in the chat. Holy are you serious?
What's up? I'm a huge fan
I'm a huge fan pog champ. No, don't I can't talk like that pog. No. Um
What's up? Hey, i'm a big fan of yours. You're really really cool
You I loved you in all the in future rama and doug
Uh pog, uh
uh
Thanks for coming if you're coming to the stream. I appreciate everything you do
He left
I'll be all right. I'll get over it. I'll take a fucking banana bath a banana banana bath is when you have a banana flavored
Banana scented bath
This is a cool outro. Yes, it is
No
All right, i'm gonna stop blinking
Okay, all right stuff
Okay, we're good
so
Uh, thank you to cvfd
For the thousand bits. Hey jerma yesterday. You said you had to drink some nasty medicine. Yes
That reminded me of the time. I had to drink steroids from my leg stuff was disgusting
I lost my appetite for a few days, but I couldn't get over the taste out of my mouth
Yeah, it's it's it's kind of similar
Uh, I two two two times a day morning and night. I have to drink
this
gross thick
Dick sugary liquid
It's disgusting
It is not appealing at all
it's just
the word is just
vile
and it's
Kind of just like fucking me all up
prescribed maple syrup
Yeah, weirdly
Dunkin donuts coffee, but yeah, it's it's it's annoying but
You know like you gotta do what you gotta do
Hold, you know as well drinking it that makes it worse for me
because my brain
dials up a thousand percent
You know what this tastes like you know what that tastes like, you know what that tastes like
It's disgusting. You know what that's it. You know what this tastes like and i'm just like, I know
I know what it tastes like. I know I know. Yeah, you do. Yeah, you do
You know what I tell you know what it tastes like and it makes it worse
Especially because it's like it's consistency too
Uh-uh, I just have to do it get a turkey baster and shoot his tongue on your throat
No, it's two at number one. It's very thick and number two. I don't really want like gag and puke
I can't oh i've got bananas
I can't you know what i'm gonna do listen to this shit. I'm about to blow your mind right now
Let me tell you something. Let me tell you a secret
Take six bananas
Chop them up peel them make sure they're ripe
Chop them up into little you know, maybe half inch circles
Put them in the freezer a few hours later when they're frozen
Take them out
Put them into a blender
blend them up
smooth
Take them out of the blender now that they are
banana ice cream
Scoop it up
Put it into a bowl
And eat it if you want to add a little bit you maybe you know, sometimes if you want to get a little
A little fun with it. You can add like a scoop of vanilla ice cream
You could add a scoop of chocolate ice cream
You could add a
little bit of your favorite
Other like strawberries, maybe you could add like a couple of strawberries
Maybe some yogurt somebody said that sounds disgusting. It's really difficult for me not not to ban you permanently from the channel
I mean like i'm hovering and I it's i've never done that before but that's
It's close
Saved you. Okay, just make banana bread if you've never had it before
I would like you to not
Talk smack about it until you eat it
It is the most intensely delicious banana ice cream and it's not even ice cream
It's so much better for you, too
Can you repeat repeat the instructions? I wasn't listening. Well, that's unfortunate because
You should have listened to the tutorial germa. Why didn't you why didn't you know that f was open door?
Why weren't you paying attention germa?
He hates us
Okay
Let's keep going. We only got a little bit more to do
but anyways, uh
Six bananas chop chop chop chop chop make sure they're ripe freeze them
Take them out of the freezer when they're done about
Three to two to four of some with three or four hours depending on your freezer
I don't know how powerful it is. You might have like a blast chiller. I don't know that
I don't even have one of those
Don't put it in there. Uh, but if you I don't know why I even brought that up
Three or four hours in the freezer take them out put them in the blender blend it up until completely smooth
No chunky bullshit wait till it's smooth. It might take a little while
Add a scoop of vanilla ice cream if you feel like it you don't have to this is on you
Add a scoop of chocolate ice cream if you feel like it that's on you not on me
add whoa
Add two or three full tablespoon like
Of peanut butter
Blend it up. There you go. Done. I want that's that's your homework for the next day
I want all of you to have a banana
a whipped up frozen banana with maybe a little bit of peanut butter in it
or a little bit of uh, like vanilla or chocolate ice cream or just
Just straight up and I want you to come back and we want to I want to discuss this. It's your homework
Eat six. No, not you don't eat six bananas in one sitting. That's just to make enough to eat it a few times
I'm gonna make it and i'm gonna show it to you on stream and I want us all to show it
at the same time
but anyways
Uh s10w update. Thank you slow update for the 250
Hey germa back again to wish you a happy halloween. Unfortunately last stream I caught was the carnival
Which by the way is my favorite stream ever now, but I couldn't watch it because of work and stuff
But i'm happy to say i'm back to donating and supporting you
Peace and love peace and love ps. What's your favorite horror game?
Just asking
Probably outlast or resident evil 2 or the first six hours of resident evil 7
Something like that
resident evil 4
Didn't scare me as much as resident evil 2
Did especially the remake and we're talking straight up scary how what's my favorite horror like how what there's a couple of criteria there?
Yeah, resident evil is not that scary. There's a few times in resident evil the the regenerator the regenerators
Were terrifying the first few times you see them
In fact, I would put the regenerators up
As some of the scariest enemies I think i've played that were in a game
Number one the number one scariest enemy the most intensely terrifying
enemy experience
Has to be misdirected. It has to be at this point
it just was
just the stress
and the the walking around and the fact that
Because a lot of scenarios like that
It happens for a little bit and then you don't see them anymore. It doesn't happen anymore
It's a thing that happens for a 30 minute period during the course of the game
That motherfucker
does not
Leave you the fuck alone
It's horrible
It's so stressful and so scary and just design wise. He's just a really interesting designed character
I mean just like it's just a huge guy. It's just a huge guy
with a
little top hat on and an overcoat so
It's cool. But yeah
I actually think that resident evil 2 we're getting close here to the end of the year
Resident evil 2 might be the best game of the year
Yeah, I think so. It's gonna be close
Sekiro, I wouldn't put sekiro there
At least for me
I would put sekiro somewhere
Probably in the top like five
But I think uh, I think resident evil 2 is the best game i've played this year in regards to just total like the whole thing
goose game
That's funny you say that because I probably would put that somewhere in the top like five or top ten
What came out this year?
Let me think what like came out this year like actual games that released this year
Came out this year
Smash came out, but I wouldn't put that up
It was cool. It was good, but I don't kingdom hearts 3 I didn't even play it like I don't want to
Let's see
Kingdom hearts 3
Crackdown to 3
Anthem which I know metro exodus. I didn't play it devil may cry 5. I want to play it
Sekiro mortal kombat 11
Didn't play it
Control didn't play it
It's it's it's resident evil 2
And unless something else comes out, I think
What came out for nintendo?
Mario maker 2
Death stranding is coming out. Yeah
Let's see what else even really even like indie wise let me think of what I
You know what I have what I do
I have to go
Anytime that there's like an end of the year scenario
It's like what what did I actually really like at the end of the year?
I go back to my steam purchase history and go to the year
And then look at what what I played
Yeah, it's resident evil 2
at least now
big spender
No, it's that I just want to I just need to remind myself what I bought in 2019
And please do hey do do not criticize my steam spending habits all of us
Almost everybody in this channel right now is like addicted to steam
And buying steam games is everybody here. Maybe some of you don't
I've been I have like I think I have
I don't even know how many games I have i've had
I'm trying to think I maybe okay. I could look
Every steam sale that happens people just buy them
You just do
That's how it was and that's how it will be when they even now but they used to do
Five years ago. It was a big deal when a game was 75% off
Oh there. There's a bundle. Here's the entire ubisoft bundle. It's
75% off. It's normally like
165 dollars
Okay, I guess i'll own every single ubisoft game
I guess
You buy games. You don't even play them that I have not done that for very very many ago
most of the I would say almost all of the games that i've purchased they're games that i've wanted to play
and even if they weren't
They're games that I eventually did for at least enough time to understand if I really cared about it
I get bored of games like halfway through that happens to me all the time, too
You know a lot of you guys will ask like oh, how come you won't stream a game more than three four or five times
It's because that I don't really play very very many games
For more than like three four or five sessions
It's not really necessarily a stream thing like well, I don't want the view counts to drop
No, it's more of
It's I lose attention on stuff more than halfway through
That's why playing games like uh back in the day like playing tf2
And playing diablo 2 and some of these other games that I was obsessed with
It didn't matter how much time you spent you could play it for an hour or you could play it for 10
It didn't matter you're gonna play it regardless
And they had a game has not really come along
That has done that to me
Where oh i'm just gonna turn it on for like two hours and that's I just that's what I want to do today
That's not really happening. And I think that one of the reasons why is because a lot of that
Has a lot of those markets have kind of turned into
Like br markets like a lot like fortnite apex and I just don't
I don't really care about those games. They don't do it for me at all
I can understand why br is an interesting experience. I just cannot stomach it. I just can't do it
German won't even give a no to stalker
What is with the stalker thing?
I played like I played stalker what a call of prep yet
I played it for like a stream or two and then I like it was like three years ago
God damn it. Like is he ever gonna finish stalker?
We haven't seen a stalker episode in three years
It's been a long time. That's even that's back
Like I've been I was living in massachusetts still
He's not gonna play tony hawks pro skater
Yeah, but that's just kind of how I play games anyways, too
I'll get it when I play a game
This is how you guys know that I actually like something like really like a game
Really?
I oh that was kind of fun. Oh, this is kind of interesting
No, no, no, like truly enjoy and fully appreciate a video game
If I want to finish it on stream because that means I really just want to play it
and
I want to I have I live stream don't I?
lifeline clock tower three
Yeah, all right. Hold on. There's a couple of variables here though
Sometimes you just have to get to the end
Because you have to
There's no other reason I was not going to see
After the first six seven eight hours of clock tower three
I was not going to turn that stream off
And then turn on clock tower three again. I knew it so we had to see it through that night
He's playing it out of obligation
Well obligation to knee I want needing to see
How it ends because I know that I will not go back to it. It'll come out of the playstation 2
It'll go in a box and then it'll turn into one of those scenarios where oh, yeah, I guess um
Yeah, I did finish clock tower three and sometimes maybe sometime. I don't know
I'm gonna clock tower three and uh find a way
You know scary monsters and try to get away from it
I mean, maybe maybe one day
Get scared of them. Maybe
No, I i'm not gonna go back to it. So I had to do you have to do it sometimes but
Let's finish the bits
We're getting we're getting into some tangents here that
I love getting I love getting on tangents. I do
It's like one of my favorite things
You just got your andy marco in the mail
And you're watching the stream
With the andy marco. Oh, fuck. Yeah
Hell, yeah, they're very cute. They're very great
That company is amazing
If you guys ever have
anything that you need
For anything to do with robotics
They sell all kinds of stuff
And they are a company full of wonderful wonderful wonderful people actually like just great people
andy mark
the
the folks
That helped produce the carnival stream
They made the robots
They're awesome read bits, please. I'm i'm doing it. I'm doing it. Look you guys what you gotta go to bed
Wait, you gotta go to sleep
Imagine sleeping
Sleepy chat. It's late
I mean, it's is it though. What time is it eight nine ten? Uh, it's a little late. It's a little bit late
s l omega l
Slow, so that's not even correct
anyways
Uh, thank you to kimmel for the 250
Hey, have you ever been watching this since tf2 day is glad to give back for all the amazing content. Keep it coming
I plan to I plan to read the bits. My mom is screaming
Well, then you probably you probably should get off the computer
And go find out what that's about
Lovely carver. Thanks for the
2500 bits
25 dollars. Thank you. Hey germa been watching you for about six years or so. I just recently took a big exam
Think uh, like cpa exams
And in the middle of the testing area, which is dead silent
I started thinking of the greedy grinner and your no emotion bit and burst into laughter
They kicked me out and I failed the exam
No, they say unsubscribed that's not good
That kind of reminds me that reminds me of a story
That reminds me of a nice long winded story that i'm gonna go on up on here
One time I took a picture. No, no, just listen to me one time. I took a picture
Of my friend. We were he was in the back seat. We were on a road trip
And he was sleeping
and I just took a picture of his sleeping face because
He was snoring really loudly
and it was like, oh my god, why is he sleeping so loudly and
I just took he was just like his mouth
His mouth was just open
and his like eyes it looked just like insane so
Eventually, he he woke up and we looked he was I was like look at how he was sleeping
He was like, oh shit like what the fuck
And seriously for the next week for the next week. I was at the grocery store
I was
Driving around
And I would just see the image of him his face
And I would start laughing hysterically. I remember being at the checkout at a grocery store
and just
Do decide there's there's no reason for me to think about this image and this is absolutely absolutely like seven or eight days later
Had to be
and started laughing
uncontrollably in the checkout and just kept going
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just i'm definitely really funny happened
And I remember the lady just being like, yeah, she was kind of laughing too
But this photo I don't I don't have it anymore, but it's
It's fucking funny
Patrick Bateman what?
No, not it wasn't she was like she thought she thought it was funny
I wasn't guys. I wasn't being like a fucking weirdo. I wasn't like
No, I was just laughing going i'm sorry that something really funny happened and i'm just trying to just trying to get through it
You know, it's sometimes it pops in your head. She's like
It's contagious. This is funny
Actually crazy. No, it's it was funny
Her friends told no her friends told her told me she told her friends later that there was a serial killer in the store
No, that's not what happened
Okay
Good story. Let's move on
You guys
Okay
Good. All right. Good one. Yeah
good stuff
Hey, thank you though. Appreciate the 25. Thank you. Thank you. Uh,
anonymous for the 300 bits
I can't look at chat right now you guys being too funny. Okay
Uh, hey germa, it's the animal rescue guy who used to stream the ducks
Until his computer broke
Just want to say i've gotten so many nice messages from your community even after the computer broke
Oh also, remember you chose a duckling and named it bilbo
Well, that ducks the tamest duck out of the hundreds
He follows any person through the yard and loves to cuddle
Here's a real
real
Short bit of him if you want to see thanks for all you do that isn't that just fucking adorable
Let's see
Let's take a look. How can I it's on instagram. So this is what happens
Can I pull this right now into here? Come on
Come on guin can I do it?
every time
Come on get in here. So i'm trying to throw it on the big screen
Uh, I should be able to get it
Let's go like this and we can actually go over to here now
Why none of these working why is this playing was this the last thing that I put on my browser source
It has to be
Oh, I gotta get an update I have an update
Uh, all right, let's watch this video
This one there it is
Not that one this one this one these are apparently this is the ducks
So this is what happens every time I walk through the yard
There it is
It's me
Hello
Why are you not paying attention to me what are you doing bilbo?
That's so cute
Bilbo, that's awesome
Thank you for sharing that that was great
And that's the that's the duck that I named it out of all the ducks out of the hundreds of ducks
That's the best one. This is what you said. That's the the most well-behaved the most lovable the most interesting
That's pretty good pick. I think
of millions of ducks
Keep telling yourself that hey, I don't have to tell myself that somebody else told me that I don't have to tell myself that
But I will continue to do that in the mirror later on this evening, but thank you though. Seriously. That was uh, anonilous
Bring back the duck stream
Hey potato chief. Thanks for the 700 bits derma. Just turned 26 today. Here's your cut of the birthday money. Happy birthday
It's hard to imagine. You're almost 30 years older than me
Anyways, love the streams and I hope you're feeling better soon. Okay for a second. I thought you were four
That's like that's that's very advanced
A computer knowledge for a four-year-old, but no happy birthday. Hope you have a good one
Hope you had a good one. I'm not sure what time it is for you now
But thank you. Thanks for the 700 bits
Uh cassio plead thanks for the 500 bits. Hey germy. It's my 20th birthday today 26th birthday and then 20th birthday here
back to back
Uh, I had a very shitty day. Please give auto a pat for me. I'm sorry to hear that
You want your birthday to be a good day? Hope hopefully it turns around
Sorry to hear that but happy birthday
Take care of yourself. Can we get a few germa heart birthday man, please?
feels germa birthday heart man, please
But thank you for the 500 bits
Take care. Appreciate it
Vilemi. Thanks for the thousand bits
Hey germa, I don't know if you've confirmed this yet. I haven't been able to get to your streams very often
But is there a set date for the next green screen stream? No
There's not going to be a set date for it until I start to pull
um
Suggestions in a new discord channel and that will happen after halloween
So after halloween because we already have two channels open right now that people are doing stuff in so
At some point after halloween, you'll see that channel pop up and that stream is going to happen in november. So
It'll probably be early
One of the first or second weeks of november, I would assume but thank you so much
See 4g. Thanks for the 250 rhythm games means
Hatsune miku's stream debut, right?
right
Wrong, but thanks for the 250 appreciate it. Oh, no jerma pluto
No, not now. I don't know not now and maybe not ever. I don't know
But thank you though. I'll take the suggestion
Thank you. Uh
argnator
For the 300 bits
Hey jerma, thanks for playing fear. It's one of my favorite games and you butchered it to near perfection
I did. All right. I got I walked in a alright. Hold on
I've walked in a circle like a few times
And that was it. I did. All right. I did. I did. All right
It was fun. I didn't come on. Come on. I did fine. I did
Fun, would you consider getting a perm so you'd be curly? No curly didn't have hair. That's not even what you said
Uh, thank you. You need there's no bits here. You just wrote that in chat. Thank you
Why would you read a perm comment, I don't know but no I uh
It was great. I can see why it's a lot of people's favorite games from
a while back
Hey, I it probably would be one of mine too if I played it 10 15 years ago
I hope your stomach gets an order and your energy can be restored
So we can get more chunky delicious 15 hour play the whole game. Not a joke clock tower three type streams
Tell stir to get well soon, too
Thank you
um
I mean dark wood the last dark wood stream was almost 12 hours
I started to lose my fucking mind at the end of that one doing more this
Doing more than 12 15 hour streams. I they they they kill me. I can't do them
I can't
Sometimes you can do
I don't know how people do it. I really don't
Trap joke grenade joke fall joke dying joke pretending joke
Uh, why is why do people think that I'm pretending?
I'm for days pretending like, you know how difficult it would be to pretend to do all that shit
It would take like three times the amount of work
to pretend
Pretending not to pretend
Can you imagine setting up elaborate ways for you to step in like bear traps and that's what you're doing
imagine like falling off a cliff like
And pretending to do that more than like five times
Can you imagine lul? Yeah, this is phil jokes. No
No, it's it's called not paying attention to my surroundings
I should I should get
like my old guidance counselor from like the fucking ninth grade on the phone and ask them a few questions
Do you think it would be odd if I were to?
Put down something and then forget I put it down
No, no, in fact, uh, we had to give you a pen every day because you would bring a pen to school
And you would not leave the
You would not leave school with a with a pen
I've lost books before guys. I've lost textbooks
Teachers would give me stuff and I just wouldn't it would never come back. Oh, yeah
I'm gonna get along. I'm gonna loan you this pen. I want this one back. Okay
I don't have it. Where'd it go? I don't know
Where where is the pen? I don't know
I don't have
Okay. Well, here's another one. Don't lose this one
Thanks. I don't have it anymore. I just handed you the pen. I don't know. I just gave it to you
Did you eat it?
Maybe and then I like smile
And I got a bunch of like wood in my teeth
And then we got to commercial
Oh, well, that would be a funny show
if you call like
Jerma just doesn't get it
Everybody hates jerma
bad pilot
Bad pilot he said did you say bad pilot? Did you guys know that young sheldon exists as a television show?
That makes 500 fucking million dollars
Wait, wait, wait a minute. It's not it's not about making a good show
It would be about making as much money
as possible
Yeah, you should see you should see the huge
Grin I got right now. Did he just call out big bang theory?
No, no, I called out
Almost all network television at the same time cut his mic. How original
Jerma is big bang tier comedy
Here's the difference though. Uh, I don't I don't pump in audience members
Okay, if you want to go that far
That means that you that means that you've left at the big bang theory then
Oh, wait, wait, wait, we can't have that. We can't have that
Oh, oh
Big bang theory sucks. You know, actually
An old college professor told me one time
That saying that something sucks
is
You can't ever say something sucks
If it if it makes
that much money
Because that means that more people
Think it does not
But then think it does
Your professor sucks
Yeah
Popularity does not equal quality. No, it doesn't but uh, but I mean
Yeah, now that I think about it that guy
Yeah, that guy that guy was only my professor for like six months and he had replaced
shit
I'm kidding. All right. All right. No, i'm not i'm not fucking around
I love fucking around but we've got a job to do
Play fear 2 right now. Why would I do that?
All right, that's it. Let's get the credits on
I'll see you guys on uh
saturday
See you on saturday
Here comes the credits. Thanks for subbing everybody
Appreciate all the support as always
The stream gets a lot of it. So thank you. Seriously
We fuck around a lot. I talk a lot of
bullshit all the time
but
real real real
Thank you for continuing to
Uh, let me live this fucking life
Each and every one of you. Thank you so much. Seriously
It means a lot, but while we see that we still have a handful of bits to do
We had creamy sensation gave 500 bits planning to do anything on halloween. Hope we get to see a lot of monka s moments
Yes, there's going to be an elaborate halloween stream
uh
Probably on halloween day, I would assume
They will be a halloween stream. Yes
It's gonna be a lot going on there
It's gonna be a secret slime action part of that stream
Go check out the discord go to the secret slime discussion stream so you can see exactly what is going to happen there
Should be fun, but thank you for the 500 bits. Thank you grump clump for the 300 bits grump clump
One of my mods
Can you tell my friend he did a great job on his video?
Teehee
Thanks
That video was
incredible
Oh, they forgot to link it. Oh
He just lied
Well, I didn't say it just
The message just said hey, can you say that he did a good job on this video?
Sure, I what video I was like, all right, you did a great job on this video was great
All right. Let's let me see what this is. This is called frog. Somebody get that please. Nobody get the fucking door, please
Stream will be popping soon
Did I lie about that video or was it as a great video? So
What are you guys talking about?
What do you mean? I'm not watching the frog compilation. No, everyone was just yelling at me to go to bed
And hey hurry up and finish the bits
But let's watch a frog compilation
Why not? Thank you grump clump. Thanks for the 300 bits
Slow update. Thanks for the 250. Hey jerma just quick update on my last donation
I was going to donate a lot more until I saw jerma sour and now i'm not only i'm not donating
But i'm suing for emotional damages
Uh happy to watch you again. See you next time. You know why that emotes there, right?
Because I said out loud if that emote was not there within 24 hours, I would do a 24 hour stream
That emote is only there so I would not have to do a 24 hour stream
Came pretty close. Yeah, it was about an hour and a half before the stream started that it was there
Smelly boy. Thanks for the 250. Hi jerma been loving your content so far this spooky season
My question is you ever been in the shower looked up towards the nozzle and just let a bunch of water fill your mouth for no
Reason and spit it out all the time. Yeah
I mean that that happens at least two or three times
I was gonna say a stream that happens two or three times a shower without a doubt
And my favorite part is you know, you do that and then you piss in the shower. That's like the best part
Thanks for the 250
Thank you water
For the 1500 bits
Hey jerma been watching your youtube channel for years first time twitch viewer and I cannot thank you enough for all the laughs
You've done more than more good than you can imagine and have truly changed not only mine
But many others lives for the better. Thanks for being you
longtime fan water
Thank you. Welcome to the twitch channel. I still have as much fun as I did
Here at the same amount that I had on the youtube channel. I have a lot of fun
Thank you so much for the 1500 bits and thanks for hanging out and I need to just quickly turn to the chat and then just say
that
peeing in the shower
Is one of those weird things that everybody says
It talks shit about and says that's ridiculous unbelievable what the fucking god disgusting what a psycho
And you do it every single day
I don't know why people are like this
Is there a reason why people?
pretend
that they do not pee in the shower is it's one of those things that people just
You're disgusting. You're gross and then you're like groggy in the morning and you just look down and you're just like pee into the drain
Nobody knows I did that but me it's just pipes. What's the difference? What do you mean? How does it smell?
You don't look
You don't you don't pee into a hot shower
You open up the door
You turn the shower on
And you pee into the shower
Okay, my stomach hurts there's a perfectly good toilet right behind you
But you don't give a shit for some reason
Oh
No, i'm fucking kidding, but i'm just
I'm seeing it in my head
I'm watching the thing i'm saying that i'm conveying is real
And i'm imagining what you're seeing in your head and it's making me laugh fucking hard
Because the second I start talking about it, you just people just start
It's it's I
What if i'm kidding no, I
No, I do not pee into the shower from outside the shower. I do it while i'm in there like a normal person
Define in like i'm talking in you're standing in. All right, we're not gonna even go over this
Everybody does this shit and everybody pretends like they don't do it and the and like the and like the three of you that actually
Don't do this
Good work because you're you're amongst a sea of liars right now. What about the sink? No, no, no, excuse me
There are lines you didn't know absolutely not why do people pretend that they don't take their shirts off to poo
That's another mystery. Do you guys okay? No, we're not gonna go here
But just know that for the longest time I was I used to actually I still kind of do it sometimes
I completely naked to take a shit like i'm talking not even socks
You know how difficult it is to go to the bathroom in a public bathroom
When you have to take off every single article of clothing including your shoes and socks
It's impossible
I'm saying I i've never done that. That's too hard
Uh, what the fuck is happening? Why is the credits?
Okay
uh
Can you imagine walking into like a public bathroom and you go into like wash your hands?
And you see like draped over the top of the stall like a shirt
Pants underwear socks and the shit and the guy's shoes are out in front of the stall
What the fuck is going on in here
God, all right. Let's get out of here. Thanks everybody
Oh fuck. I closed the website
I closed the website because do people still call them websites?
But you just say like I closed my tab or my site. Do you say website still?
There's no cool
New way to say that
Window. Yeah, there you go. You close the window. You don't close the website. You close the window
All right, let's finish this
Thanks for sticking around
We have
Uh, just a couple more to do. Thank you. Havegun for the 250. Hey germa
If you ever if you enjoyed sphere you might want to give a shogo
Mobile armor division a look. It's pretty fun 90s shooter by monolith monolith made a lot of great games
I wonder what they're doing now after shadow war. Thank you. Vilemi for the
2000 bits. Thank you 20 bucks here total. I'm not addicted to buying games. I'm just addicted to giving germa bits
You don't have to do that
But thank you regardless and then they say at this point we really need the germa psycho emote fine
I don't know the germa psycho emote has has to be that image
On something. I don't know. I have to find one
Which face is it going to be? I don't know
If it's not ready by saturday we get no i'm not doing that again
But it'll probably be there on saturday, but i'm not giving up. No i'm not doing that
I could not do a 24-hour stream right now, even if I lost that bet
I'm too screwed up right now
On this medication, so i'm actually surprised i'm able to be here for this long
It's actually because I i've been eating very light today
That's probably why so this stream was really not supposed to be more than like four or five hours long
But i've been okay. I felt alright, so i'm cool to hang out
But they will be one soon
Finally stefunky chicken. Thanks for the 400 bits. Did you get my other bit message?
If not, I just said the thing was a tricky game where if you don't manage it correctly, you can soft lock yourself
It's fun when you know what you're doing, uh plan on two or three save files where
Two of them get soft locked. I would assume this is the one right here. Let's see
Yeah, i'll find one some of these are good
I'll get a good one. I'll get a i'll get a damn good one
Wait, no now it sounds like I don't think kim is funny
I like this one
It'll probably be this one
Yeah, but that's not this is not even germa psycho
Look, that's not germa psycho
That's fucking that's like germa deranged
That's germa scary. That's not the same thing. I'll find one
Use the deep fake we'll see
But that is gonna be it. I'll see you guys later
Have a fantastic
Next day. I'll see you guys
Very soon. What do you mean? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
What are you waiting for?
What's the matter? What are we waiting for?
Okay, you can go. Oh, thanks
What did kim what's the first thing kim said to me?
um
I don't know like
uh
She said I was a she said I was a c minus
Yeah, I remember I was like, oh what would what would you give me for like that? That's not the first thing though. That's like
and after like a
maybe like five days four or five days of uh
Of like hanging out. I was like, what would you give me for like a letter grade?
And i'm like I I would give you an a like I give you an a
She's like you get a c minus
And then wait, whoa, whoa, whoa this story. There's a small little hold on interestingly enough
After another I mean it was a joke
It was she was making a joke and I laughed at it because she knows that I think the things are funny
You know, we laughed
And then a few weeks later. I asked again. Hey, what was what was that? What that did I increase?
Mike would my was still beta c minus
Nope, I went up to a b plus
and now
What is it now?
Kim's here now kim's in the chat. What does it know? I mean like it's it's been three. It's been like almost three years
What does it know?
What no
Come on, you're supposed to say
You get an a
You get an a plus
And then everybody goes oh
And I go, oh
I just got dunked on a b a b plus is great
That means solid
very good
Not too good where you're like trying too hard, you know, like a b plus is perfect
I think b plus is the best grade you could possibly get
It'd be an a if you weren't bald
Oh my god
There's context for what kim just said. Okay, she
I don't okay. Listen, I gotta I have to I gotta explain this one because I can't leave after that
Like a bombshell like that one. I don't have any tattoos kim has a lot so
She was referring to I don't have any tattoos. I want you to get a tattoo and uh, no that's not gonna happen
The only tattoo I'd ever get would be the fucking venom symbol on my shoulder. I almost got that tattoo by the way
I was potentially hours from getting the venom symbol across my entire left shoulder
Thank god, I didn't do that because now i'm gonna get it on my chest where it belongs
Hey anonymous skifter. Thanks for the five community subs
Appreciate that and that's it. I will see you guys on saturday. It's over. It is over
Goodbye. Good night
See you saturday. I missed did I miss bits? What do you mean? Where from where no, I got them all
I don't see any from I missed you missed my bits
Did you was it did you give 250?
It's not highlighted
Where is it? Where is it? This should have everything
So, oh, yeah, so yeah, you it was right at the beginning
So I I saw kore was here
I wonder why that didn't get picked up because kore's is the first one
Well, i'm sorry about that
uh, I
Didn't see it
But that was from c
Uh from
I fuck up this i'm gonna fuck your name up bad
See zexen s
or
zexen zexen s
Thank you for the 500 bits. It is here. Yeah. No, it's here
Uh, oh it actually shows you how to pronounce it
Chexen
Chexen s okay. Hope you're feeling better soon. My man
I've been watching you since your early youtube days and your streams are always a gateway to having a better day
My birthday was last saturday and I missed your stream, but I wanted to say my girlfriend got me a super cool gift
She printed all your twitch emotes as stickers and they're so cool. That's awesome
My favorites are germa boomer and germa chomp. Thanks for all the entertainment. That's lovely
Thank you for the 500 bits. Sorry. I missed it earlier, but it was not on here before
Strangely enough, but yeah a happy birthday. Thanks for the 500 bits and that's a really really adorable awesome gift
Thank you. Well, thank you for the 500 bits and that you know you that's your gift not mine
All right
I will see you guys on saturday. I'm still gonna be fucked up from this medicine
So hopefully we don't have any issues during that stream because that will be i'll be on it for about three four full days
And I it takes
a good
Two plus days to have it really get into your system apparently
So, I don't know. We'll find out
We'll just cross that bridge when we do
Have a wonderful wonderful friday
See you saturday