I don't know. I have no idea what happened. I told like to reverse countdown.
And my fucking stream just turned on. So that's the new feature. Okay. Yep. I'll see you later.
I guess I have to do something. I don't know. I wasn't playing on stream for like another four hours.
All right. Yep. Hey, what's happening everybody? Welcome to the stream.
Oh, we're starting. This is when I, this is when I'm starting. Stream in orbit soon.
All right. Uh, actually give me one second. I need to move a few windows. See you in a minute or two.
All right. So today we're doing something, uh, kind of just came out of the blue for no reason
last week. Just decided that this is what we're going to do today and probably tomorrow too.
Depends on how much fun everybody thinks this is. I think it's going to be fun. We're going to do
heroes of might and magic three. I know it's kind of odd that it was just white. Wait, why are you
playing this right now? Well, it just kind of came up. I remembered how much I loved this game
and we're going to play it. This is going to be a real comfortable stream.
Now I'm going to be passing out blankets and, uh, eye masks over the course of this stream flight.
Feel free. By the way, they're all, they're all, um, $6. So, I mean, I'm not going to be passing
them out. I mean, you're going to be paying for them as I walk by in the aisle. Don't make,
don't make any loud noises. Are you like, no, no, you can't like make like a loud noise,
like on any transportation. Don't make any loud noises and just watch the screen. We will be
arriving in Amsterdam in about 12 hours. So have a good trip here. Stream trip. Why are we going to
Amsterdam? It was the first, it was first like city and like European place I could think of
in the 10 seconds I was reaching for one. But yeah, we're going to play. Uh, this is a classic
game. Uh, a lot of people are going to be confused when we first play cause there's a lot going on
in the game. And I even don't know a shitload of the stuff that's going on in this game.
I loved this game when I was a kid, when I was a teenager and I didn't even fucking understand
any of the nuances and the complex systems that could potentially be in the game. I just clicked
on stuff and I had fun and I have a basic understanding and I haven't played in a long
time. So we're going in with like 14 year old brain into 34 year old body and then
teleport to 2019. So why don't we just show it on the screen so you can see what it looks
like. There it is. Here is a might and magic. Let's get the music turned on. It's a pretty
good soundtrack. One, two, three. It's Mr. Worldwide over here. Yeah. I know you're getting loud.
You're getting loud. Quiet down. There's no dancing in the aisles either. I'm seeing,
I'm seeing dancing, please. You're not dancing. Sit down in your seats. Stop. Okay. Fucking dumb
plane that would be. And you're like just on a plane or like a, like a nine hour plane and
you're just sitting in your seat with your iPad and people are just fucking dancing.
You'd just be like, sit down. All right. Here we go. I think there's a campaign in the game,
but I don't know if I'm going to do it. I feel like I'd rather do one of the random scenarios
because I've never clicked this button. I've played this game dozens and dozens of times
over years. I've never selected this button. I think we can keep it that way. So this is
random scenario. This is all for one. Let's see available scenarios because you can do random
map. You can do random scenarios and they all are different completely. You can have up to like
eight people in a game. There's no multiplayer on this one, unfortunately,
because it is the old version. Rush the capital. I want to play. I want to play. Let us in. You
can't, what do you mean let us in? This is not pirated version. I bought this from good old games.
Don't pirate this. Buy it. It's good. It's worth your $10. I don't think we can smart click this.
Let's just find an interesting one. Do this Warlords. I'll read them for you. All right.
Here we go. I'm going to read, how many are there? I'm not going to read them all. That's too many.
Let's find one that I think is cool and then I'll read it out loud. Let us click. The bubble
won't even be here. If you click here, you're going to click here and here and here. No,
I'm clicking one. A brave new world. A great upheaval shook the very foundations of the world,
breaking apart continents and dividing territories in new ways. After the earth stood still once
more, the people crawled out from their hiding places. They began to rebuild in this brave new
world. No one's clicking. Sit down in your seats. Yada, yada, yada. No one's clicking on my screen.
Okay. No one's clicking once and we need to do map size. Let's do like medium. This is the first,
okay. This is the first scenario. I just need to show you guys how to play. Here,
like how about this one? Like deluge. I need to get back into the swinging thing.
Pick elbow. All right. I could do that. This world ain't big enough. No, no, no. This is
going to be too hard. All right. Here we go. I'm just going to do random scenario. Here we go.
I'm going for it. Um, let's go for, uh, I don't know. Let's, um, roll the dice. Here we go. One,
two, three. Start, starting here. Just to visit. Emerald Isles. Step by step. Harsh winter. Uh,
rumble in the bogs. Carpe diem. Seize the day. A few years back, the gods decided they no longer
wanted any part in this world. Now there is total anarchy. Everybody blames everyone else for the
gods abandoning them while sitting in the throne room. You decided you were the only person fit to
rule. Carpe diem. Here we go. Uh, lose, defeat everybody, kill everybody. And we've got player,
uh, difficulty is on 160%. I don't want that. I just want it on like a hundred percent or just
right in the middle. What does this mean? I don't know what that means. I know what that means. I
don't know what this one means. I'm not going all the way up here. 130. Rumble. Rumble in the bogs.
It's difficulty scaling. So this should just be right in the middle. 130. I'll take it. I'm not
going to max it. I'm not for the first one. All right, here we go. Ready? What about advanced
options? Oh shit. Hold on. Starting town. Oh, that's important. This is important. This is me.
I need to pick my flag. Which flag do I want to be? Do I want to be red, blue, um, sand, green,
orange, or purple? Green. All right. Starting town. Uh, we can pick starting towns here. I think
we should just do, should we just do, what do you think? Who should I be? Who should I start as?
Should I be? Oh, here we go. Okay. That's all I needed to see. All right. Uh, where do I want to
go? Town alignment. Castle. Associated creatures. Pipeman, archer, griffin, uh, the swordsman,
the monk, the cavalier, and the angel. There's, okay, so this is kind of standard fantasy, uh,
knights and archers and griffins. This one is more fan, like fantasy creatures like dwarves and
elves and centaurs and unicorns. Uh, this is the tower. So is this, this is like a fantasy
styled creatures. Gremlin, gargoyle, golem, mage, genie. I think I want this one. This inferno is a
little geared more towards like high fantasy. So you have imp, uh, gog, hellhound, demon,
pit fiend. That's kind of cool. Necropolis. I don't have any other way to describe anything.
Um, this is a, I don't know. I like this one though. Skeletons, lich, black, uh, black knight,
bone dragon, harpy beholder, medusa, goblin. These are like orcs, gnoll, lizard van, serpent fly,
firebird, elementals. All right. I think I'm going to go with the gremlins. I think so.
The tower. We get gremlins. We get stone golems. We get mages. Oh, should I need a new? Hmm. I
like this one. That's just the, you took a photo of me and I'm not photogenic and I wasn't ready
for it. And that's how we look at every picture. Torosar. I need a better name. So we rename. I
don't think we can rename Torosar. I think that's good. Everybody else can be random. That's fine.
We don't need to do any of this. That's where we're going to start. Everyone else's computer
and we're on normal difficulty. Three, two, one. It is your belief that the gods didn't
abandon their people, but the people have abandoned their gods. To bring the gods back,
you must make the people believe in the gods again by force if necessary. Here is your castle. This
is where you stand. This is your stronghold. Here's the map. It goes eons and eons and light years
away from you. You step out of the castle and you see, I'm not going to narrate this whole thing.
So here's my magic. If you want to know how this works, do not be deceived by this initial
overworld map. Oh, it's a click game and you click around and you, oh, look at that. Oh, it's fun.
No, no, there's way more than that. There's a whole full combat system, 2D and potentially 3D.
This is an isometric 3D. The game works based around exploring and getting stronger and leveling
up and leveling up your creatures and having thousands of them and having them fight. I hope
you're ready for the best fucking game you will ever see ever in your entire life on this channel.
Here we go. So let's go look at the castle. This is our, where we are right now. This is who we
have. We have the fucking random, I like hate this guy already. So we have 31 gremlins. They're like
jesters. Okay. They, uh, 31 of them. We've got three stone golems. There are 16 available gremlins
right now. That's too many gremlins to have. No, I want like 500 of them. Not playing as the
skeletons. Dropped. Well, this is the first scenario. We can play more scenarios. I'm excited.
I'm like, emotions are overwhelming me right now. How this works is these are all the monsters we
can eventually make. Eventually we can have just giant guy with like a lightsaber. It's awesome.
The genies, the mages, stone gargoyles. This is a lot of cool things. And these are the most,
obviously, most powerful units you can make. But for the purposes of what's happening here,
this is your tree. Yep. It's a tree. All of these have a function and they all cost a certain amount
of resources. So for instance, the blacksmith, uh, the blacksmith provides your armies with
ammo carts. Okay. Well that's a thousand gold and five wood. I got 15 wood. You get resources by
claiming territory or by trading it or by finding it. Are we understanding here? You can upgrade
your tower. You can upgrade your buildings and bases many, many times. This is a cool mobile ad
stream. Now I'm just taking it slow because people are going to have a lot of questions.
Let's do it very good. Okay. Golem factory. The golem factory allows you to recruit stone golems.
It's five wood, five, um, hair balls and $2,000. I'm going to get that because I want to be able
to start having goblins, goblins. Here we go. There it is right there. Six of these are recruited a
week. I can buy six per week. It's 900 bucks. As you see, I'm going to buy them. I'm going to
recruit them right now. Here we go. See now we got a nine. If you don't leave anything here,
your castle can be claimed by other people. So if I don't have, for instance, if I can put, um,
like, oh, let's put, uh, you can split them up too. So I'm going to leave, uh, I'll leave like two,
I'll leave two of these guys here. Now they're going to get wiped out of the castle that has
ever breached. Who cares, right? I don't need anybody defending the castle right now. I'm
going to just take everybody. But this is where you do most of your maintenance. Now you probably,
oh, that was fucking awesome, Jeremy. Like, holy shit, that was the fucking coolest thing you've
ever shown us. I know. So here we go. Ready? You go by, uh, you can only go a certain amount of
paces per turn, right? So here's how far I can move. Every single one of these things is
interactable and they have consequences. They have choices. There are a pack of wood elves here and
there's something behind them. A monolith one-way entrance. I don't even know what the fuck that is.
I have no idea what that is. I wish I could tell you what that was. I don't know if I'm,
a pack of wood elves, we might be able to kill them. I don't know. Maybe I'll try.
First of all, let's pick up this, uh, this treasure chest. Oh, after scouring the area,
you fall upon a hidden treasure trash. You may take the gold or distribute it to the
peasants for experience. Which do you choose? This is important because you can take money
and be able to buy things, or you can take experience, which levels up your hero,
which then lets you put skill points in, which lets you do more, better things.
I think I'm going to do experience. You have to pick this every time. Let's pick experience.
Bingo. Taurosar is now level two alchemist. Spell power plus one. Or, well, no, this is,
you can pick one of these two. You can pick either advanced tactics or basic ballistics.
I don't know what those are. Just sit on. Advanced tactics allow you to rearrange your troops just
before combat within five hex rows of the commanding hero. Fuck man. That sounds pretty
good. Basic ballistics gives control of the catapult to the hero, allowing aim shots with
increased damage. That's if you're breaching buildings, if you're breaching towers. Um,
I don't know. They both sound pretty good. I would probably say basic ballistics because that's
how you really take over capsules very well. You sound so excited. I love this game. This is like
one of my favorite things ever. This, this is like, uh, yeah, this is what like a sponsored stream
would sound like. But this is like a, I'm sponsoring this game. You know what I mean?
Like I'm sponsoring this stream. It's me. I'm going to do ballistics. You know what I'm saying?
This is me sponsoring this game. They're not sponsoring me. I'm sponsoring them. I bought
this game for 10 bucks and I'm telling you to play it. All right. So we've got a scholar here.
Ooh, I don't know what to do because I only get a certain amount of things I can do per turn.
Remember, this is very important. Everybody listen to me and stop talking during class.
Oh, Dave, back there. We don't, there's no food allowed in the classroom. And, uh, Karen, Karen,
you like to pass notes, huh? Is that what you're doing? Oh, let's see. Let me see that. Let me see
that. Thank you. What does it say? Oh, the teacher's ass is fucking huge. I wonder how he fits
at his desk. He probably desperately needs two seats for one for each, each ass cheek.
Fucking funny. Sit down. Every single one of you is coming after school for detention.
What, you didn't do anything? Doesn't matter. You all have to think about what you've done.
Unbelievable. Okay. So let's go to the windmill. Ready? Ready?
The windmill had five, um, whatever that is. That's all that was there. Sometimes it could
be something bad. Sometimes it could be a scenario. All right. Should I talk to the scholar?
As you ride into a clearing, you notice a university scholar resting his horse.
He agrees to teach you some of what he knows before setting off. Basic fire magic. I think
we just got easy mode right here. Basic. Can I learn that though? Okay. So what do I hold? Let me
see. Basic fire magic. Cast fire spells at a reduced cost. Ooh, but I don't know any spells
though. Where's my spell book? I don't think I have any, uh, spells. Where's the spell book? I know
it's like a certain button you press. I don't remember. I'll figure it out. Anyways. Okay.
Here's some wood. That was six wood. These don't respond by the way. There's seven, um, crystals.
Do you think I'm prepared to do this? What if I just lose? Uh, I'm, I'm out of time. I can't,
my turn is over. So as you can see, I can't go anywhere else. The only way it would be possible
for me to do anything else is if I had another hero, which you can recruit. They cost money.
By the way, that windmill sound is a, is somebody, is a page turning sound effect
that has been looped over and over again. Some, it's really pretty interesting. All right. So
uh, I can go to the kingdom. We can see the whole world. We don't really do much of that
right now. I can end my turn. That's all I can do. I'm done. End turn. Right. Ooh. Okay. It's our
turn again. Everybody else has moved. Everybody else has done something. Let's go to the shrine
of magic thought land mine. What does that mean? Land mine. I just exploded. I feel like I want
to try to fight this guy. Who do I have in mind? I got, I know I've got plenty of people. Let's
see if I can do it. Here we go. What? Why, why didn't I get to fight? What just happened? Um,
what, why did that happen? That's not supposed to happen. That's not, I'm okay. I'm telling you
that was absolutely not supposed to. I've auto combat on. Why would nine golems and 31 goblins
lose to six archers? Even in an auto scenario and Taurasara is dead. He's abandoned me. What?
Okay. What's, okay. It's it. I'm really confused in the, yeah. Okay. I need to, I need to let go
in the settings and turn that off. Okay. That's part of the HD mod. This is, I don't have the
HD mod. This is just from good old games. All right. But anyways, more importantly, um,
the hero with a higher tactic skill can arrange their armies before any combat begins. So before
combat begins, I can move, as you see, I've got these slots here. I'm going to try to get behind
this because that can give me line of sight. I don't have any ranged, so I'm kind of, I might
just be fucked anyways. Uh, we're just going to move forward and it's now my turn. They don't have
any active spells. Their, their morale is whatever. Fuck them. Damage three to five.
As long as I can, I might actually lose here. I actually might lose here. All right. That looks
fine. This is bad. This is going to be bad. I'm going to lose. I'm, I'm fucked. I just wanted to
show you what combat looked like. I might be able to do it. I might, it's possible. What about, do
I have any spells? Magic arrow. He can't, I can't do it. Yeah, I can. Here we go. All right. I killed
two of them. I'm going to go for it. They're going to kill these. This is bad. I'm going
right down to the bottom here. Come on. No, he's dead. I gotta do it again. The hero might be able
to do this. It's very possible. Come on. Here we go. All right. So once you get to this point
where I can actually get close enough to attack, you can get in there and choose any angles you
really want to from whatever hex you want to do. I'm going to do from here. Sometimes I have,
they can retaliate and when they retaliate, it does a certain amount of percentage of damage.
We're going to go right here. He's trying to run away. That's fine. We'll get under here.
These guys are stronger. Remember, let me slow this in. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Yeah. All
right. All right. Slow down the animations. It was going like really fast. Come on. Stay alive. I
don't want to use any spells. I have to. All right. Take them out and then get yourself over here.
He's alive. Very good. And that's a victory. A glorious victory for Valorant in combat.
Taurasar receives 250 experience. And here are your attackers and here's your defenders of 16
archers. We lost almost every single person. But did we? We're still all right. Remember,
every week you get more. They're back at the town. See? Ready? They're currently,
how do I get a good view of that? View towns. Okay. This is my only town that I have.
I think I actually have to physically go in here to see it. Don't I? I thought I,
can I just go look? Kingdom overview. Okay. See it here. Creatures available. So right.
It's, I can, I can go get 16 ramlins, but I need to get, okay, this is gold. Let's get it.
That was a thousand gold. Pretty cool. I don't know what this is. I'm kind of scared to click
it because I have, I have four, I have four golems and if there's like a monster in there,
I'm dead. There we go. Okay. So you don't have to be, your hero doesn't have to go in.
Here's our town. This is who's available to recruit. There's none here because they have,
it's by week. You can actually recruit all available creatures. Now let's see what we got.
Tavern. I can get another hero, but I don't think I want to do that because I'm,
I don't want to spread myself out. Arch Magi throw magic with a precision greater than most archers.
So we have a wizard and necromancer that are available to hire. You can get astral or nimbus
and that is a necromancer. Get the necromancer, but I'm not going to take the necromancer out.
I don't want to get too many heroes. That's 2,500 bucks. All right. Fine. We don't want to,
remember money is, money's important. I just bumped the mic. I know. So we have skeletons
and walking dead. That's what he starts with and we may as well. Um, just it's, that's a lot of
money, but recruit and we're going to, we're going to stack this guy. So he's got three, uh,
different creatures. I don't think any of these are ranged. And now as you see, here's the window.
I have two different options to where I want to go. I might just throw this guy away. Let's just go
and let's go in the portal. What I ended up over here. All right. Uh, this is somebody's kingdom.
This just took me right to the front door of somebody's house. Should I go in? Is there
anybody in there? There's nobody even here. There's like two frogs guarding this place.
I'm taking this one. I'm at, I'm out of turns. All right. There's like literally one frog here.
Let's go through here. I'm going to go this way with this guy because there's a pack of hobgoblins.
Let's get the ore. Let's get some gems. Another scenario where I can do, let's level them up.
Didn't level up. Okay. That's fine. Warrior's tomb, not visited. Go in there.
Okay. You have come upon the resting place of a nameless warrior. Do you wish to search the
tomb? Don't do it. Don't. Should I go in there? What if there's like gold in there? I don't have,
but my, I don't have my creatures. Like I, let's go for it. Reluctantly, your troops enter the
tomb, finding the vial of lifeblood, but such a despicable act has ruined your army's morale.
Oh damn. This item increases the health of all your units by plus two. Holy shit. That's pretty
great. Actually everyone has plus two health. So you mean, oh wait, 16 plus two. What do you mean?
No. So those of you that are still maybe a little confused, if you're not, then you know, that's
fine. But for the people that don't get it. So there are 16 gremlins in here. It looks like one
on the screen, but it's 16. So that means 16 times six instead of 16 times four. See six at 15 health
every, each, all of them. You know what I'm saying? Just want to just, just get you unaware
of what's happening. You know, just so you can see. All right. Well that was a good, that was
pretty good outcome. Let's get going. I'm out of time, I think. Let's end this turn. All right.
Do you think I can do this? Should I just, I, I don't think I can kill this one frog. Frog didn't
build. I gotta go in and turn that off. I don't want to see the outcome. So there's 13 frogs
and I've got, let's move forward a little bit here. This, yeah, cause this said this is going
to get launched. I have, remember the basic military, whatever basic ballistics. This is
why you have it. Because you want to take down walls. I wouldn't be able to do anything if I
didn't have this. Here come the frogs. They're coming out the front door. Why are you coming
out the front door? All right. Back it up. Cause he'll waste a turn. Okay. Can I just kill him?
All right. These things, these things are really weak. I'm probably just going to retaliate and
win. Uh, I don't think he can do anything. They just wait. Oh, fuck. He's good. He's
trying to kill it. Can he destroy that? Fucking frogs. 565 experience. Apply batteries out. Yes.
There we go. All right. Level three alchemist. Defense plus one. Everybody in the party gets
plus one. And then I can do basic archery or advanced tactics. Um, let's see. Basic archery
increases damage done by range attacking creatures by 10%. I don't have any, but it's
probably going to do to get it. Cause I'll probably eventually have some monsters of archery. And now
here we are. I can now recruit. Oh yeah. This is mine now. How much do these cost?
We've got a tavern town hall fort. I can level one ranger. No, no, not a one heroes right now.
Harpies. All right. How much is it to recruit all these? It's a lot of money, but I could deck
him out. Beholders. Are these ranged? What do you think Chuck? I'm just taking them. Let's do it.
Let's get off a nice little army here. I mean the frogs suck, but it's okay.
Get more frogmen. Uh, I have to wait till they, um, grow. All right. So I have Evernight and
Stronggale. Evernight is the other castle that I own. All right. We're going to hang out here.
Let's see. Should I buy something? What can I upgrade? Marketplace Citadel.
Including a 50% increase to base creature growth. The Citadel adds a keep and other terrain
obstacles in a town's defense. So I can increase the growth portal of summoning. You can recruit
creatures from an externally flogged flagged dwelling. Uh, blacksmith is, you can make the
list as mushroom rings. The mushroom rings increase Troglodyte production by seven per week.
I think we should do that. By the way, you can only do one, you can only build once per week.
So we're going to get some more frog recruits. I can no longer do anything here, but back here
I also, I don't want to bleed my money completely. That's the thing. You have to be careful.
Citadel. Uh, and just in case somebody comes, I'm going to get the Citadel. I'm going to build the
Citadel. More base creature growth. This is getting, ah, spells. I need spells. This is the spell
tower. And then in here, summon boat. Summons an existing friendly unoccupied boat from anywhere
in the world to your location. Chances for success at 50%. Dispel, magic arrow, slow. Okay. So I have
to bring somebody in here. I have my mage who's currently the necromancer. Does that count?
All right. Well, I'm, it's a new day. Spell points. Let's go, let's bring you in here.
Oh no, actually you're on the other side of the world. Sulfur. Uh, a little hut. Would you
like to recruit halflings? 15 halflings. Join your army. Nice place that they'd like to be.
Shrine of Magic. No longer have. Ooh, this crest is up there. Let me go. Did I go to this windmill?
Yeah, I did. Visited. Learn landmine. I wanted to go, what did I want to go, up or down? Um, let's go
up because this is mine here. So if you take a look at this, you see that this scattered stuff,
like the scattered ore all over the place, this is an actual like ore pit, which when you claim
these, you just, it will generate resources. So there's a pack of hobgoblins here. Who's in,
who's in this party enough? Oh, I want to, let me just disable this shit. How do I, um,
no, no, no, don't quit. Where's the menu? I just want to get rid of this quick,
get rid of quick combat. Okay. Yeah, there we go. Quick combat disabled. So save the game.
Oh yeah, that's right. You have to do manual saves. Save game. Auto save. Uh,
we're just going to name it first map. First map saved successfully. Here we go.
Pack of hobgoblins. Here we go. They want to fight. They can move a lot. They can move very
long way. Eight. This is like, I got enough. Unfortunately, I'm, I don't know if I'm going
to be able to, let me see my spells. Shield. Shield's a selected unit reducing the amount
of damage received from hand to hand attacks. I think I'm going to do that to you because
that's where they're going. And I mean, you're not going to be able to move anywhere. He's going to
make it. So might as well just move forward. Uh, you on the other hand, you're going to be,
was he going to cleaver? Oh fuck. I thought I was controlling him. I'm an idiot. No, I'm not.
That's fine. No, he's going for you. Bad. Okay, go in there. Oh, you had nothing. What did he just
do? Shield. Luck. What did he just do? Oh, these guys, they kind of suck. Skeletons are good.
Okay, we're good. That was low morale. Okay, right, right, right. We lost five little gremlins. It's
all right. 75 experience and they could just access to this ore pit. Two every day. Forever,
unless somebody else claims this. So there's nothing else up here. Wait, artifact.
Stoic Watchman. What's that? What's a stoic watchman? This figure increases your eagle eye
skill by 10%. I don't even know what that is. That's hidden back here. All right, so that's all
back here. I have no more things to do. I mean, I guess it could. I only have 50. What do I have? 5600?
5600. No, we just got to end the turns. All right, day four. So I have learned summoned boat.
Although I don't really know for what reason that is.
Kind of went this way, but I want to get the treasure. Um, I'll take the money this time.
Oh, shit. A pack of Gorgons. I don't think I'll be able to beat that. Yeah, I'm not going to chance
that one. So Seer's Hut. In order to travel through these dangerous lands, my envoy needs
more backup. I hear 60 halflings and 12 trolls are excellent guards. If you were to bring them to me,
I would be deeply grateful. Huh. Well, I have, I have a few of them. I don't have a whole lot.
I need 60 halflings and 12 trolls. Uh, rally flag. That's out of turn. Let's go back to the
worlds here. All right. So I got 8600. Level two, Citadel Marketplace. You can buy and sell
resources. You exchange things back and forth. That's pretty good. Uh, lookout tower extends
a visible distance around your city. That's pretty good too. Uh, allows you to recruit
stone gargoyles. I feel like I'd want this upgraded workshop. Uh, master gremlins are available.
Wall of Knowledge increases any hero's knowledge by plus one if they visit. Uh, I'm going to go
with this. I'm going to go with the Citadel. It's, I mean, you need to have like walls,
so they can just walk right in. What's the library? More spells. Yeah. Let's, uh, what do
I need for the city hall? City hall allows you to purchase town structures and earns your kingdom
2000 gold per day. I need a marketplace and a blacksmith. I probably should just get the
marketplace. Yeah. Let's just, let's just start that process. So as you see here, I can, you know,
for instance, um, I think this changes week to week depending on certain outcomes and certain
seasons. Some things can be worth more money. So here's the resources available to trade. So I can
do, you know, I could trade gems for gold. I can trade, you know, crystals for wood and the ratio
as you see is not very good, but yeah, it's pretty cool. It's pretty cool. So that exists now. Let's
go to the other one. Anything, nobody to recruit. What can I do here? I need to, hmm, 5000. I don't
think I have, I don't really have enough to do this. The Academy of Battle Scholars teaches new
skills to any hero once. Pillar of Eyes. The Pillar of Eyes allows you to recruit evil eyes.
What is this? You can recruit Medusas with this one. Yeah, this will 2000. I'll get 4,000 per day.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to just get two city halls. Let's just go to the marketplace.
Starting to run out of resources here though. All right, let's go. Oh shit. Oh fuck. Oh no.
Okay, this, he's come, that's my house. He's got, he, this is, this is another player.
Uh, he's, he's gonna take me over. He's trying to take, what, what does he have?
I have, pretty decent, what does he have? Several, a horde of skeletons. Uh, what is his stuff?
I can't, I don't know. Destroy him? Kill him. He's got a horde of skeletons. This is probably
gonna be bad. All right, I'm going for it. No, I'm not. He's gonna take the castle. I'm not prepared
for him. I'm just gonna, yeah, I'm gonna go in. Everybody to the battle stations. Wait, I can't,
can I not place him up here? There we go. Okay. Um, can I recruit anybody? Is anybody available?
There's nobody available. Uh, should I make something and recruit someone? I don't do,
I don't have enough. 2010 and five. I don't have enough money. No, I don't have enough of,
what is it, ore? What am I missing? Wood. Fuck. I need to build the citadel. Quick. Okay, yeah,
I need, I need to add terrain obstacles. Pull up the bridge. Let's go. Wait, hold on. I'm gonna
send reinforcements. Uh, hold on. Blacksmith. I don't know what, I need wood. I gotta go fucking
find wood. How do I need to make wood? Plus one gem every day. I need wood. I need goddamn wood.
But the exchange rate's probably so bad. Let's go to the market. Okay, wood. I need wood.
And I'm gonna give money. I just like fucking almost restarted my computer, I think,
because I just elbowed my, this is so stupid. Supply and demand. Bullshit. Look at that. What
about hay? No, these are all such bad exchange rates. God damn it. No, nothing I can do. No.
How many, how much wood do I have? I need four, right? Uh, trade the M&Ms. No, no, I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. I'm not gonna, I have good troops here. I've got good people here.
I've got, they're garrisoned up and they're ready to go behind walls. Let's just do it. You're out
here. Rally the, rally the troops. I got some luck. I got some morale. Wood. How much is it?
Eight wood. Oh yeah, eight wood. And I got some spell, I got eight spell points. Done. We don't
have to end there. Learning stone. Mercury. All right, don't, don't do anything crazy here. Just
get more mercury. I can't, there's an alchemist's lab. What's this thing? Learning stone. Nimbus is
now a level two necromancer. Advanced necromancy or basic wisdom allows 20% of the creatures killed
in combat to be brought back from the dead as skeletons. Basic wisdom allows your hero to learn
third level spells. I mean, yeah. Now we're a real necromancer. I don't have much more wiggle room
here. All right, I need to be ready. So let's go back here. Um, I got, I take the wood. What was
I gonna build with this wood? Blacksmith. Cause then I can do city hall. Yeah. Blacksmith and then
city hall. This is five wood and this is 5,000. Ammo carts. There it is. Blacksmith. Only visiting
heroes may use the blacksmith and then next week I can do a city hall. Cause I already built
something here. It's just at the front fucking door. God damn it. All right. I'm ready. Ready?
Three, two, one. He backed off. He took all my fucking shit though. He took, I was going to get
all this stuff, which that was my stuff. We just ran away for no reason. I just like panicked,
but nothing. Kill him? He's got, how much is a horde? 50 to a hundred? It's a lot. He's
unsuspecting. Got him. I, seven. I told you it was like a hundred. I told you it was a hundred.
All right. What is he? Harpy. Harpies can probably move real fast. All right. I got to play this
smart. The hobbits. I think can you cast like spells? They can't go through the rocks. I'm
terrified of this person. Protect the frog at all costs. Now this is okay. This would be fine.
All right. You ready? I'm ready. Let's get a spell out here. I got magic arrow on, on the whites
or on the skeletons. It has to be 59. It does 10 every time. I'm staying where I am. Defend.
It's not great range, but it's enough. That's bad. Oh fuck. Okay. Hold on. Oh, the hobbits are
ranged. I don't have any, I can't do any of those spells. Who's priority right now?
Probably the whites. Look at the damage. Not bad. All right. Should I, should I just throw like these
fucking green onions up here? Should I just make the green onions go forward first?
Okay. Here we go. Oh God. That hurts. That hurts. No, not a good opportunity. They have good attack,
but I don't want to just throw them up there. They'll get hurt. Stay here. Defend. Spell. Defend.
Good opportunity here. Good. Oh, oh no. They're getting closer. They're getting closer. Um,
it's all right. The green onions are dead. Four. Oh, it's getting close. Here we go.
Should I go for the whites or should I go for the skeletons? I think I got to go for the whites,
but there's so many more skeletons though. Get in there. Oh, oh no. He's creeping up.
Come on. Let's go naked guy. I'm thinking Harpy's defense. Damage one to four.
Damage one to three. I got to whittle down the skeletons. They're 28. I'm going for the whites.
That's a great power to have. Come on. I'm going to try. Maybe I should back you up.
I think I'm going to go back. Yes! All right. Move the hobbits. They need to stay alive.
Uh, we're going to have, okay, we're going to have to have naked guy versus half naked guy.
Ah, they do a lot of damage. All right. Here we go. Should I? I think, I think it's time to
sacrifice you. I'm going to fly down here. I don't have any spell points. I'm out of mana.
Out of mana. 24. 20. I can't really run. Just, uh oh. Keep fighting over here. He's a pretty good
tank. Okay. Here we go. Ready? 10 skeletons left. Eight. Four. Yes! This is a victory here. This is
a good victory. Um, I can't go that far. Let's get it closer so I can do it next time. The enemy,
no, the enemy's fled. He ran away with one guy. Okay. Where did he, where did he flee? No, he's
dead. He literally disintegrated. Yeah, he's dead. He's gone. He abandoned the cause. Okay,
because I didn't kill him. I win. Good fight. Good victory. You all deserve a raise. Spell scroll.
Just as you bend to pick up the old parchment, you hear something move behind you.
Turning around, you notice some marksmen in the trees. You are not really sure why,
but you get the feeling that if you pick up the parchment, they will attack.
Do you want to pick up the parchment? I don't, not after fighting all that. I don't have enough,
it'll still be there. No, it'll be there. I, I, I, uh, we're gonna, I, no. What do we got over here?
So we've got this already. A pack of stone goblins. I got a pretty decent crew, right?
Damage four to five. Damage three. Damage two to three. These guys are slow and they can't move
very far. Shield everybody up. Well, not yet. Hold on. None of them are ranged. I mean,
this thing actually is pretty strong. Should I run? The cowardly Nimbus flees from battle.
What? Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait a minute. Is he dead?
Where is he? I, I didn't know that's what happened. It's been a while. I didn't know
that when you retreat, they just delete themselves. Okay, so I'm not going to fight you. A pack of
gogs. I don't know if I can do that either. Would you like to recruit gremlins? 16 gremlins join
your army. Nice. And there's a chest here. After scouring the area, you fall upon a hidden chest
containing the ancient artifact Mystic Orb of Mana. What is that? This orb helps you recover
three extra spell points per day. Nice. Pretty nice. Although I can't get this stuff, unfortunately.
I kind of need to just go down to the other. I'm too, I'm too weak to do any of that. All right,
we got it. I think I can do citadels, right? In City Hall. 2,000 extra gold per day. Do it.
5,000. Bingo. Our growth has increased. The capital building is the new one. Pretty nice,
although I'm out of resources though. This can also be done. No, I need a blacksmith. I don't
have enough wood, but I think I'm just going to trade for it with one of my like pots because I
want to be able to do this stuff next week. Blacksmith. I need to deck this place out.
New turn. Weirdly enough, I've only seen that one person. Aren't there like four or five people
on this map? 60 halflings in there. I'm just gonna head down here. I'm gonna have to use
that whole day to do this though. All right, almost done with the first week almost.
Which brings us to here. I don't think I can get over here. There's just that.
Red Keymaster's tent is being guarded by a pack of Gorgons. They're probably really strong though.
PvP versus viewers. I don't have the new version. This is the old GOG version. There's no
multiplayer. It's unfortunate because the new version is kind of all fucked up and
messed up in a lot of places. The new, the old version is way better, but doesn't have
like multiplayer capabilities. But wait, the good old, the GOG one does it. Isn't it like land?
Sea Chest. Where's my spell book? Should I get in the boat? No, no, no, I need it. Okay,
we're almost done with the first week. I can recruit some people. Well, yeah, not, not yet,
not yet. That's a pretty good idea, but hold on. I, I don't have any money for anything.
I could do the Citadel here. Resource silo. Citadel. I'm just gonna run out of money.
I probably should Citadel this. Stone. No, give me this. Nine per week. I'll get eight. I'll get
more. Four thousand gold. Looks all right. Okay, let's go over here. Portal of Summoning. I don't
know what that means. The Harpy Loft allows you to recruit Harpy Hags. So what do I have? I have
these, uh, these Harpies, regular Harpies. I can upgrade the Harpies and then we get new, better
ones next week. I'm going for it. There they are. Harpy Hags and regular Harpies. Two different
versions. Damage one to four. Attack six six, six five. And these are much faster. Strike and return
and no enemy retaliation on the upgraded ones. That's pretty good. All right, we'll see it next
week. First week is about to be complete. I don't have anything else I can do. Astrologers proclaim
week of the Condor. All dwellings increase population. All right, let's take a look at what
that does. Nice. So we've got a lot of options here. I've got 6,000 gold. Should I just pull
everybody? 3750 for 18 Gargoyles, 17 Comedy Gremlins, and six Naked Guys. I think that's
pretty good. Recruit them all. You guys can stay there for now. Let's go over here. Let's recruit
all here. I don't fucking have any money. I need to, oh shit. I need to, okay, I gotta go.
Let's fill, fill that up. Come here. Ah, damn it. I, ah. No, it's gotta, this is a pretty decent team
so far. 44, nine, 18, six and six. These guys are strong. These guys are strong. So now, shouldn't,
can I do this? Uh, I have to spend, yeah, I might as well just do it. So now I have better Harpies
here. No, just, you sit around for a minute until I get a little bit more money. Because I'm gonna
have you go into the ocean. You've got enough troops where you're, of course, to be reckoned
with here. We got, uh, Witch Hut. This will have to be next week. I don't have any money to do
anything so let's keep going. What? It didn't take too long for you to realize that people will not
bow down to a new god as easily as you might like. Fine. You tell yourself, if it's a war they want,
it's a war they're going to get. Who did I say that to? Witch's Hut.
An ancient witch living in a strange hut welcomes you, teaching you offense for her own
indestructible purposes. I learned basic offense. Thanks. Increases all hand-to-hand damage
inflicted by the hero's troops by 10 percent. In, what did I say? No Marauders. You really need to
get these. I got a lot of troops. 20 spell points. I think I can take them. The no more
marauders awed by the power of your forces begin to scatter. Do you wish to pursue and engage them?
Let them run. In awe at the, of in awe at the absolute size of this unit. Two wood a day. That's
good. I need it. Money or Mr. Experience. Nice. Level three. Expert Necromancy or buyer magic.
Expert Necromancy allows 30 percent of the creatures killed in combat to be brought back
from the dead as skeletons. I mean this, why would I do anything else at this point?
This is the like the Resurrector. Okay cool. I don't think I want to do anything else. I want
to do a boat with you. How much money do I have now? All right I can do this. I don't, I want to
do upgraded tags. So if I pull everybody, these hags? Yes they are. Okay. Recruit them. Get them all.
All right. Wait before it snow. I don't have any more money but I want to summon the boat over here.
How do I summon the boat? Where's my spell book? That's one thing I do. There it is. Cast a spell.
Summon boat. That spell costs eight spell points. We have six. God damn it. I only have six points?
Well you can just, you hang out here and just take care of the castle for a while.
Next day. What do I have for, all right so we're going down this way. Hutter the Magi.
You enter a rickety hut and talk to the magician who lives there. He tells you a place near and
far which may aid you in your journey. Oh shit. Oh shit. Look at that. Look at these things. Bears.
The coliseum. He's just revealing everything for us. Look at this dude. Holy fuck. Thanks man. All
right so let's see. Where am I now? I am right here. So if we go down there is, we got a shipyard.
A lot of stuff. There's some wraiths. There's a gem factory. Golem factory. Subterranean rocks.
There's a little ship out here. There's the eye. Let's just go down here first. Actually this is
like the top. Let me see. There's another castle over here. Let me just see what it is. What is
this? University. Your hero's footsteps echo through the quiet halls of this ancient university.
A clerk informs you that while here your hero may receive instruction on the following subjects.
Offense. Logistics. Learning. First aid. You cannot learn first aid. This will cost 2,000 gold.
Basic logistics. Increase your hero's movement points over land so you get to move 10% more
each turn. Or basic learning. 5% more experience. But it's also all my money. 10% more movement per
turn or 5% more overall experience. Tuition for learning basic logistics is 2,000 gold. Let's do
it. Hey, um, why don't I just do them both? No, not free. Should I do them both? Oh, I can't. Right,
okay. I thought it was already in real time updating that. Well, okay, I can move more.
I couldn't really build anything in 1,000 gold. How many spell points do I have? What do you have
for spell points? Eight. All right, let's go. It's time. Cast the boat. We're getting that chest in
the middle of the ocean. Boat. What? Oh, it's a 50% chance. Well, go back to bed. Get some sleep.
We'll try again tomorrow. Uh-oh. That guy just killed somebody. Where's that person? I think
they're on a different continent. All right, things are getting interesting. Take a nap and
go again. All right, so there we go. We got War Machine Factory. Oh, damn. Recruit Ballistas.
Ah, they're so expensive, but they're so powerful. Give me one. Can I not do it? No, I can do it.
Look at this shit. I want like a ton of these. Worth it. I'm taking the money. Den of Thieves,
or do I go up to the Harpy Hags? Look at that. A pack of Silver Pegasi. Protecting a gold mine.
Let's go this way. Den of Thieves. Oh, this just tells you about...
So here we go. Number of towns. Oh, shit. Artifacts. Kingdom. Army. Income.
So I'm the green flag, right? Best hero. Personality. Human. What is that? Is that a goat?
Best monster is my Beholders. This is cool, though, because it can show you just how...
That's interesting. All right, so we know how to be careful. A pack of mummies.
And a sulfur. There's a Coliseum here. Arena. Thousand experience. I'll take it. Thanks for
1000 HP. That's all we can do for now. All right, how's the other guy doing? Two spell points. It's
not... You know what? Fuck it. We got places to be. Just... I want that sea chest. So bad.
Ugh. Somebody right here. No, it's me. Go for the cow. I don't know if I can do it. Oh no,
I can go for the... I'll go for the scroll. Okay, here we go. I've got a decent army here. I've got,
like, pretty good hags. You get the feeling that if you pick up this parchment, they're going to
attack. Oh my god. What have I done? Uh, this is impossible. I won't be this... Must be something
pretty good, yeah. Um... Retreat, but... But I'm gonna lose everybody anyways. Everybody hide.
These guys are magicians. They're gonna fucking kill everybody. No, I'm not setting the frogs
out. I'm gonna see if this is even doable. I don't have any fucking spell points. Uh...
This is... That's a... Guys, these guys have crossbows. This guy's dead. Dude, he just is.
And I could retreat and then redo, but it's over. Might as well try to take as many out as I can.
I'm gonna stay back here though. Oh, this is bad. Very bad. I didn't even kill one of them.
Pop its attention. Send out the frogs. No, I like these guys. At least... Let's try to take a piece
off before we go down. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No rewind. I'm not gonna save, scum. That was an
outcome that... I went for the item. I went for the spell scroll and it was like, hey, be careful.
And I got fucking wrecked. That's just the way it is. It's okay. It's all right. It's okay. This is
the guy. This is the guy that's level like three. He knows what he's doing. He's got a great military
here of undead creatures. He's got more spell points. This guy's way better. All right, I'll
get a new one. We'll get a better hero. For instance. Like, take a look. Ready? Uh, where's
the tavern? Yeah, I mean, already I like these two more. This is a death knight. Or should we get
this guy? Thane or Volkiel? I'm going with Thane. All right. Alchemist. Wait, don't we already have
an alchemist? We know we did. Thane. I mean, I kind of need Thane. But death knight is like...
Let's just wait. Let's compare them. So death knight starts with... Okay, hold on. So death
knight starts with the skeletons and the the wraiths. This is necromancy and artillery.
Specializes in vampires. Okay. This is gargoyles and gremlins. Is an advanced scholar. Has a bunch
of points and specializes in genies. Hmm. This is a scholar. We have a necromancer already.
I'm going to go with the genie. You hang out there for a while. You're gonna have two? Yeah,
I know. I just want to spread it out a little bit. Don't bite off more than I can chew.
They're starting... We're starting to get to the stage where people are starting to move around.
Oh! No! They have a terrible... They have a shit army though. This army sucks. This army sucks.
What do I kill first? These guys are terrible. I can't even attack the skeletons.
I can't... I can't go that far. Okay. Skeletons. You're not going to get in here. This is an
impenetrable fort. You're not getting in. I'll kill you all before you get in here.
Good thing we took the magician. Oh boy, they can... They can fucking throw in here. Oh fuck.
Oh no, they can get in here. Oh, eat shit. We're fine. Everything's fine. Yes! Just stay behind
the walls. Ow! All right, get in there and then get out. Whoa! What? Wait, what happened? Why did
he die? He landed in the pit. That's not fair. He got boiled in the oil.
Shit. I just bought you. You would take 2,500 gold. Do not apply... I have to... I can't just
redo every battle. You can't just redo every single time. It was dumb. Yeah, but now I learned.
Don't worry. I'll get it back. Guys, don't worry. I'll get it back. That was a dumb mistake.
Rewind? Was it dumb? Is that a fucking mistake?
All right, let's go. All right, it's the only time I'm going to rewind in the whole day.
I promise. Just don't land in boiling oil. All right, kill this motherfucker. All right,
everyone can just defend. Defend, defend. Take him out. I've got my Medusa archers.
Do not let him in here. All right, everybody defend. I'm gonna lose the gremlins. Are you
gonna burn in the oil? You can't get in here, can you? I'm not doing that. Ow. Oh fuck. They
have to die now. Yes. Thane received 722 experience. We have pushed them back. The
person is collecting all my stuff. That person is taking all the things that I want. A pack of
mummies. Add some sulfur. Mine. Save the game. Okay. I wonder if a pack of mummies will be able
to take me on. This is a pretty good crew here. I mean, like, really? What do they got? Nothing.
I think they're ranged, though. No, they're not ranged. All right. Good to know.
Move the gremlins forward. I don't think I need to cast any spells here.
They have Curse. I forget what Curse does. I'll have a homeless second here. Stone skin,
shield, magic arrow. Just lame it out in the corner. Let's try magic arrow on you. Holy shit.
Okay. These guys are pretty tough. Skeletons, move in. Butchers. Butchers, move in. Naked guys,
move in. I wanted more of these. All right, here we go. I'm gonna get a little bounce back here.
Get it. Oof. It's all right. We're doing fine. Right in front of you. In fact, stone skin,
defense, shield. Hmm. Which one's better? They both do the same kind of thing, right? Dispel.
Slow. We'll do stone skin. Yeah, we're fine. Move in. We got three more. Uh-oh.
Cursed? Yeah, he's cursed. Oh, they're both cursed. What does the curse do, though? Cursed duration
three rounds. Spells affecting the army. What does it do? I think we'll be fine. It's one down.
Skeletons coming up from the back. And butchers coming up from the left. Okay, we're good. Level
four. Advanced eagle eye or water magic. Spell power plus one. Advanced eagle eye gives your
hero a 50% chance to learn any spell up to third level used in combat. Or allows your hero to cast
water spells at a reduced cost. 50% chance to learn any spell up to third level. What does that mean?
I mean, maybe we should just try it. All right, one soul for a day is not going to come from here.
Let me see. What does that, what does that do? Spell. It's just all learn from the enemy here.
Okay, I see. That's interesting. That's pretty cool. All right, what do I want to do now?
I have this. Let's see. 35, 33, 15, 6, 6. Pack of wood elves. I don't have any range, though.
I think I'm going to avoid them for now. Yeah, I'll avoid them for now. Let's get the chest.
Experience. Level up. That's all right. Get the crystals. Idle of fortune.
It's awesome. I can't, I don't think I can go here unless these are dead. Is Stain still alive?
Yes. All right, Thane. Just hang out there for now. I'm going to recruit the frogs.
Okay, I don't think I can do much. Nobody to recruit. Go on. That guy's in a boat.
Where they're getting a lot of stuff done on their turns. Pack of nomads. I'm so timid. Idle
of fortune. You found an ancient and weathered stone. Idle. Kissing it is supposed to bring
luck or happiness. So you do. This stone is very cold. Got more morale. Gems. Silver wing tower.
There's nobody here. Shit's fucking empty. I'll take it. It's empty. All right, let's
gonna relax here. And you got gremlins. I'll take them. I got 59 gremlins. This is an actual
empty town though. I already have a fort. 2000 gold per day. I could have just a huge income.
Marketplace. Go for it. Get a marketplace up here. Hang out in there for now. 4000 gold.
Mage guild one scholar. Okay, hold on a minute. Allows you to recruit evil eyes. Yes. Oh damn.
Okay, what's the difference? Beholders evil eyes. So beholder is just that. This is no melee penalty.
10 attack, 8 defense. Just better. Shoots 24 shots. 3 to 5. 3 to 5 health. It's just better
in every way. Eyes for days. I have upgrades here. All right, looking good. Citadel. Let's go for it.
More growth. Now I gotta relax. You gotta upgrade the gremlins? Yeah, I'm...
Yeah, I know. You're right. Hold on. I'm scared that something bad's gonna happen.
Look at this person getting all the fucking stuff in the ocean. That's what I wanted to do.
No. What do I got? 4600 workshop. Master gremlins. Okay, here we go. They're just like
Fantasia monsters. All right, so this is 3344. Oh, they're ranged. They can be ranged. Okay,
damage one to two. Yeah, these are better. I gotta upgrade. I gotta bring people in here.
Who has all the gremlins? You do. You have a lot of these just like shitty gremlins.
Blacksmith. Let's get that city hall up. Only visiting heroes may use the blacksmith.
I can't like use that? I guess I don't have anything to use it. All right, what else? Anything
else in here? Upgrade the warren. Infernal frogs. Oh, okay. Immune to blinding. Okay,
so they attack five four. They're just better. One to three. Health. Have more health.
So they turn from green onions into like Triceratops or Stegosaurus or whatever.
Okay, that looks good. Good luck. Increased attack. So we got some upgraded frogs.
Now, I need to start moving around. You have such shit. You have such bad,
you I could move around though. We have to, we have to do something. I gotta get some,
I gotta move around here. At least one of these things. Let's go to the windmill.
Three gems. We're in the windmill. Okay. Lots of sin to our captains. I'm too afraid to
pursue. Packing nomads. I think I could take them. Let's go. All right, this is a lot though.
These guys are fucking strong, aren't they? I mean, kind of, kind of, but it's all right.
All right, we're good. Defend here. I don't want to just give them a free hit. I don't think they
can make it. They're not going to make it. He's not going to make it. Wait for them. This guy
though will be here in time. He will make it. Just get up there. Nice. There you go. There you go.
There you go. There you go. There you go. Not going to make it. He made it. Blocked. Holy shit.
You fucking hero. What an absolute fucking monster of a unit. No, he's all right. He's all right.
All right. What we got? Gargoyles. Let's go down here. There's only three down here. Bang.
Bang. Crap around the side. Yeah, we're good. We're good. This is not that bad. I can't believe
that didn't kill you. You really want to get rid of the gremlins, huh? Yeah, that's it. Say what?
Okay. I was scared for that for some reason. 420 experience. That'll give us the one crystal a day.
Pack of wood elves. I should be able to take them as well. I still have plenty of points. I got
plenty of people. I should be able to get these wood elves, but they've ranged. That's the only
thing that concerns me. No, let's just park it right here. I need like to get the other hero going,
but he just, you can't do any exploring with this group of fucking idiots. Is uh,
necromancy automatic? I think it is. Let's keep going. Oh no. Again? They're going to take it.
Again? Not again. What do we got here? Whose ranged? The whites. Oh man. Ah man. I can't get
over there. I have just the towers, but he's going to cast spells and kill the violet.
I have such a small crew. This is bad. Uh, not good. Very bad. Very bad. Very bad. Very bad. Very bad.
Very bad. Very bad. It's over. It's over. Yeah. I just have to accept the defeat here.
He's going to just shoot. Oh, he's going to shoot through every time. How much, how many
spell points does he have? Yeah, I'm dead. Yeah, that's it. Game over. Oh, it was my like younger
brother, Thane. Came to attack Thane's. Thane came to get Thane's stuff. Thane versus Thane.
Astrologers proclaim week of the badger. All dwellings have increased population.
That's why we need to like, ah, this is going to have to be our real stronghold.
I spread myself a little too thin here. All right. What about this? This is a good place. Let's
really upgrade this stuff. Obsidian gargoyles, iron golems, can recruit mages. How much is this?
Let's get some mages and 1800 recruit everybody. No, not yet. Not yet. Mages are damn good.
But I'm not going to get them yet because I have to upgrade these guys. Let's get at least the
mages. Yeah, these guys are awesome. And let's pull up the gremlins because we already have,
obviously, the upgrade there. Get them all. That's all I can afford.
Fuck, I'm out of money. They're going to attack the city from the portal.
Fuck, they're going to come for that town next week from this portal. I've got four wizards
protecting it. I don't have any money. I should have fucking taken the money before in the
beginning. I've got to start to fucking cash in something here. I have to try to make something
happen. Do you wish to pursue him? No, let him run. I want to go into the arena. You enter the arena
and face a pack of vicious lions. You handily defeat them to the wild cheers of the crowd.
Impressed by your skill, the age trainer of gladiators agrees to train you in a skill of
your choice, plus two attack or plus two defense. This could be the run saver right here.
Attack. That's pretty damn good. Oh, there's defense. I don't have any.
Okay, that was good. That was good. I need a hero. Lots of harpy hags, lots of centaur captains.
The university is over here. The war machine factory. I don't know. A pack of silver pegasi.
Can I get them? I might be able to kill them. Don't come attack me, please. Don't come attack
me. Don't come. What happened? What? Where was that? It was a scripted event. It was just a
scenario event. I had to pay like somebody robbed me taxes. Oh, that was actual taxes. I needed that
money this week, this day. So bad. Fuck. Okay, well, here we go. I would have just bought another one
of these. I need the money. I need the money. I need the money. I have to recruit people.
Lots of, no, not lots of Harpies. Let's get the gold. 600 temple. Got some luck. All right. More
gold and a pack of silver pegasi during like Christmas or something. This is bad. I can't do
it. What about the harpy hags? I might be able to get the Harpies. There's an obelisk right here.
I'm not sure what I want to do here. Lots of harpy hags. No. I'm fucked. I'm so fucked. I just need
to just dial up the defense. Recruit. No, not yet. Hold on. Obsidian gargoyles. There we go. All
right. Pull them in. Let's see the difference. Speed. They're just faster. Okay. Now how much
money do I got? 13. Recruit as many as I can. I have 1300. Come on. Recruit. Wait, what?
Oh, okay. I can't afford it. I have to at least have something here. I have 30 gold. Fuck. I'm
in so much trouble. Why do they have to take all my money? I was just getting ready. Guys like
sailing the seven goddamn seas. Okay. 3000. Recruit everybody. There we go. I have now the
obsidian gargoyles, a bunch of magic remlins. This is at least protected. This one-way portal
is an awful danger. Can I close it? Can I close this portal? This guy? Okay. Should I just go fuck
this guy up? Lots of skeletons. Lots of frogs. I'm going to buy a new hero and we're going to storm
the castle and I'm going to take it back. I need somebody in here though. Look at that picture.
Level one knight or level one wizard? I think that's the first thing I'm doing.
Don't go in that portal. He's looking at it. I can tell. Go up there and- go up there and get
your ass kicked. Go take that squirrel and die. Please go up there. He doesn't know.
What's over here? I can go over here and go down. Let's go to the imp cache. This has been- have I
visited this yet? I don't think so. Don't come in here. Don't go in the portal. Don't go in the
portal. Oh. Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Somebody else came. Oh god. Purple just came up
and just murdered him. Go up there and die. He's going to go touch it. What do you have?
He's got like treants and griffins and mutants and- oh no. Okay. Take the castle now. Take the
castle now. All right. Here we go. Ready? Let's get level one genie. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah. Upgrade him. We're going to get the castle. We're gonna just put the walls up.
Okay. We need to upgrade these guys. Oh Jesus, man. 64 of them. Stone garg upgrade. Dude. All
right. I'm ready. Let's go. Let's go get the castle. Well, there's nobody in it. There's nobody in here.
It's mine. Sucker. Hey, thanks for the fucking upgrades. You dummy. You're not going to get
over here. Yeah. I don't have- how do I get money? But hold on. How do I- can I-
I'm going to exchange something because I need- I need money. Hold on. I got a lot of-
Uh, hold on. This is important. I need castle. I need 5,000 gold. How do I get five grand
right now? Go to the market. I want- no, no. I want this. What do I get for this? Okay. I
can do it. I can do it. I can do it. Hold on. What's the- what's the best one? What's the most
expensive? Gems? 100. 50. 100. 100. They're all 100. Okay. I think I could get rid of
some pots. Sell the red crayons. 10. I don't think I need mercury for anything right now.
I need to get to 5,000. I need wood. What about the- okay, what about sulfur? I could do 10
sulfur, 10 pots, 10 ore, which is 3,000. I'm going for it. I have to. Selective blindness.
I did it. Okay. We're gonna do- I don't have enough wood. Wait. What do you mean? I fucking
need 10 wood. Wait before- hold on. Before I go any further. Hold on, Ed. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
important. Oh! Eat shit game. Eat shit game. Eat shit game. I'm gonna win this. I'm gonna- I'm
gonna hold the castle. All right. What's more important? Restore spell points with the gems
and the- can I get the gem factory? No, not yet. I'm gonna go to the imp cache.
You found an imp cache. Do you wish to attack the guards? The portal near your base is one way.
Where- they're out. Okay, this is a different scenario here. Hold on. They're just weak. It's
okay. I'm gonna go for bottom right. Bottom left. Yeah, I'll win this. It's a lot of imps, but
they're not- they're not strong enough. You just got to go twice. That was bullshit.
No, they ain't gonna win. The retaliation alone. Let me see here. Magic arrow. Let's just try to
just melt one of these. I'm gonna just melt the guy over here. Absolutely melt it. Okay, just
attack the thing right next to you. Should kill it. Things weak as hell. Skeletons go down here.
I better get something good for this. I don't need to waste my magic here. Yeah, gargoyles.
Yeah, same thing down here. Skeletons are really good. I can't wait to upgrade them.
Right here. Just move over here. Drop them. Come on. Get this one up. Hopefully there's a bunch of
money in here because that was actually to solve every problem I have. Dude, they're doing so good.
Doing so good. Gremlins are doing really good. All right. 800 experience. 200 imps dead. All right.
Lost some people, but it's okay. All right. Level five necromancer. Expert eagle eye or basic wisdom.
I learned attack plus one. That's good. 60% chance to learn any spell up to fourth level used in
combat. Or I can actually learn third level spells. That's, yeah, that's better.
Having defeated the imps, you discover four mercury and two thousand gold. I have done it.
I've done it. Got it. I've done it. Good. I still need wood. Is there any wood down here?
Oh, it's like a shipyard. There's no wood though. Well, let me just, I can visit this once a day
anyways. So I might as well just, I don't think I can do anything else. Shrine of magic gesture.
Remove obstacle. I just learned. Nice. Okay. Cool. Very cool. Very cool. All right. But this
lumber here, somebody's right outside the door. I gotta remember that. It's important to remember.
Okay. Wait, wait. Which door? So this is a one way entrance. So that person can't even get over here,
but they can go here. So I need to build. I need 10 wood. I noticed. Yeah, no, I know that. I've read
it in the chat a few times. No, I know. I knew that. I knew that like 20, 15, 20 minutes ago.
Yeah, I know. I didn't know that before that, but no, I read. I read that. I did. I'm concerned.
We both went through it. So no one's, there's nobody going to live through this. This scenario
here is no one is going, no one's going to live through this. Like I have to get on the boat.
So it's either take it or don't. I need wood. I need wood. I'm willing to spend.
What am I willing to spend? That's the best. It's just three. I could give some sulfur. I need how
much? I need 10. I could do six sulfur. I could do nine. I need one more. We could do gems. Okay.
I will now have two arrow towers, fortified defenses and doubled growth. Bring it on.
Just hang out in here. Don't move. Save the game. That's a good idea. Okay. I'm fucking nervous
because I can't like, that's really nice of you to build that for the purple guy just to take it.
I still have a couple of cities. I'm going to piss my pants. I'll be right back. Two minutes.
Here we go. All right. So I've got no money. I've got defenses. I've got a very large amount of
people that are going to try to come kill me. This does not bode well. Let's go. There you go. Bring
it on. Or go up top of the spell book and get killed. Here we go. Okay. 160 fucking eight. Look
at that. I got, they shot three times. All right. I got an opportunity. Here we go. All right. Let
me think about this for a second. I just dropped all their hobbits are gone immediately. Chained
lightning. Chained lightning strikes four units. Will this bounce around? If I do it right here,
is this going to be catastrophic? What do I start it on? Are we over here? Oh, that's not very good.
Oh, that's not very good. Oh, that's not very good. Defend. I can't do anything with you unless
somebody gets closer. Ah, okay. I got to kill these archers, but it's not going to be good.
There's so many centaurs. I think I have to go for the centaurs.
Mm. No, I got to go for you. The oil could get them. That's not a whole lot. It's not doing a
lot of damage. 27. Fuck. Oh, come on. Fire it. Kill them. They're getting in. They got in. They got
in. They got in. They got in. Quick. Go this way. What do I do? She got in. Spells. Stone skin.
Stone skin. Stone skin. Get in there. Oh, I'm dead. Oh, we're dead. This is very bad.
17. I got to kill the immediate threat. Kill the immediate threat. Come on. They can't get in yet.
15. Oh, shit. This is so bad. I'm dead. It's game over. That's it. They got, they breached. The
Pegasus breached. There's not much else I can do. I mean, I get to spell. No, I don't have any
points. I don't have any points left. We just die. Maybe next time. It's not over yet, but it will be
very soon. We just have to try to kill the Pegasus. My only hope is sincerely that the archers on top
will do a lot of damage here. Don't surrender. Just get up here. I got three archers. They're
going in the mud. They only have 12. Dammit. Not good. Now they're outlandish. Bad. One hit.
One hit kill. 149. Instantly kill. Oh, no. That's it. I got nothing left. I got nothing left.
Oh, fuck. Oh, well. I tried. All I got is you. 5,000 gold. Gone. It's not over. It's not over.
I still have a bustling city here. Not over. This thing. I just have this for the fucking
gold at this point. I need a mage tower level one. I need money. It's not over. It's not over.
There's still plenty of possibilities. I'm going to try to get over here. I'm just going to refill
my points. There's like a pack of dwarves. I can get rid of them. Would you look at that?
A group of battle dwarves with a desire for greater glory wish to join you. Yes, I accept.
Well, that could have just potentially changed everything. 7, 12, 7, 22 health. Shipyard. Boat.
All right. Things are looking up. There's nobody in this area, right? Better not be. No, it's just
me. Changed everything again. Summon boat. That was the different character. I don't have that
ability. Holy fuck. I can summon boat. I thought that was a different character. It's this guy.
This is the guy that has the boat ability. All right. I know what I'm doing. Here we go. Don't
kill me. There's somebody dangerously close to where I am. All right. Get the gold. Lots of
walking dead. And then a golem factory. Don't pursue. Golem factory. Much to your dismay,
the golem factory is guarded by a pack of gold golems. Do you wish to fight the guards?
I don't think that's wise. That would be very unwise. Give me the boat. I have 20 points.
Summon boat. God damn it. Do it again. Summon a boat. I got heads twice.
Fuck. This strange eye turns and studies you as you approach. After a few moments,
it returns to its slow scan of the area. You can't help it feel like someone or something
is using the eye to spy from another location. There's a shipwreck survivor right here.
Come on. I got to get over here. Look at all this. There's so much stuff untapped potential
over here. I need that fucking boat. Now. All right. I've got some money. Resource silo. More
gems. Increase obsidian and gargoyle production by four. Wall of knowledge. Let's get it. Yeah.
More growth. Better troops. Don't kill me, please. I give up on this one. All right. You know what?
This one. How many? How much is it? No, not even worth it. You can just have them if you take it.
There's nothing here. This place sucks. This is the one that I don't care about. I already
took all this shit, but this is going to get cleaned. This motherfucker's just sailing the
seven seas. I can't afford a boat. How can I not afford a boat? I have $9,000. Wood?
But okay, so riddle me this. Does summon boat. Summons an existing, friendly, unoccupied boat.
Oh god damn it. I need to have, I need to have a boat first. How much is a boat?
How much is a boat? I need a castle. $5,010.10. I'm building a castle. I need to get to this
capital. $4,000 gold a day. I need to, I just need things. Where's the market? What do I need?
It's so much and not worth it. Terrible exchange rate. Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, four.
I need to, I need to start upgrading. Bad. Two more. Sell some of my bitcoins?
Oh, what do you mean? They, I don't have any of these. Two more wood. I'm going to just take it
from here. No, I'm not. I'm just depleting my resources. These are so necessary. All right.
Castle. Adds two arrow towers. Fortifies town defenses, doubles creature growth. Build it.
I can now, $10,000 for a capital building. I need a lumber mill. I need wood. I need a lumber mill.
This is what, that's it. This gives me like one wood a day. Where is there a lumber mill? I need
that fucking boat. I think I'm going to go attack this guy. Over this guy. Lots of gogs. Pack of
stone golems. I'm starting to go in the goblin factory. What do you think? Should I try to do
this? Wow. Whoever green is, he sucks. If I just did the, I didn't, I don't know how much it is for
a boat. Is it ten wood? I'm giving myself a restart point because if this is just horrible,
then I'm just restarting again. Go. Fuck, okay. So it's, this won't be, I don't think this will be
horrible. Shield. Magic arrow. Who's more dangerous here? Down here. I can't reach it though.
Oh, he's magic immune? Oh shit! I, uh, they're both magic immune. Whatever, it's fine. What do I have
right now? Gargoyle. How far can they walk? They can walk kind of far. I do have the dwarves.
All right, dwarves are going in the bottom. Not enough. Good. Okay. I have no range. I have hue
though. Uh, you defend. You also defend. No, go up like a little bit. You go down here to back up
the dwarves. Nice shot. All right. Gargoyle time. Stay here. Nice. Okay. Dwarves. This is where you
wanted to join a better cause. Pretty good tank. Stay with it. No! Good. Just, I gotta go for it.
Five. Go for the one that's damaged.
Get the skeletons down here. There's 50 of these guys. You're next in line. In fact, you wrap around
here. Four left. Oh, there they go. There they go. There they go. They fought for glory. Bring in the
skeletons. 49 versus four. Big damage here. Very good. And I mean very good. Nice. You're just trying
to take a plate space at this point. Gargoyles are dead here. Good. That's what I wanted you to do.
All right. Bring in the gremlins from top left. Kill this. Done. All right. It's almost impossible
for me to lose this. This better be worth it. Surrounded by all sides. Six. Go this way. 49
skeletons. This thing is so strong. Imagine having like more than 20 of these. It'd be
unbeatable. Almost, gremlins are almost dead. Thank god. 810 experience. The golem factory is
now no longer defended. Oh. Oh. My god. Okay. How much money do I have? Fruit, iron, golem.
I can bring in a bunch. Bring them all in. Can I, how much can I have? This is diamond golems.
I definitely want at least two of these. Diamond. Gold golems. Just how many, okay I got one more
slot. No actually I don't. I, because these are stone. I can get them all. At least, okay I can
fill it up. That's good. Two diamond. Three gold. Seven stone now. I spent all my money. That's okay.
These guys are so tough. Now I can go up here and get this now. For sure. Guaranteed. Now it's time
to save for a boat and hope I don't get attacked. I don't like where that guy's going. I don't like
the boats that you're on. Astrologist proclaim week of the wyvern monarch. Wyvern monarch growth
plus five. Well I don't have those. Lots of people to recruit but I don't have the money.
I could get another hero. No don't do that. I need money. I need wood. Save the game. Looks good so
far. Lots of rates. I have a great team here. I mean I'm going hard. Let's go. Oh fuck you.
Fucking goddamn taxes again. I'm broke still. Go on. Come on over here. You ain't got nothing.
Um I don't think you can make it. I'm gonna defend. Maybe actually defend with most everybody. Let's
put you guys out there. Put the skeletons out here too. Uh yeah because I don't want to lose any of
these guys. I want them to be incredibly safe. Drains enemy mana. Let's see if I can do something
here. Be slow. Let's see if this works. Not bad. Uh defend. I don't want them going out there.
It's okay. This is pretty good so far. All right we've got diamond. Diamond go and I this might
be a one hit kill. Not really but it was still pretty good. Yeah I have just these slow moving
assholes. The skeletons are the best. They just truly are. Look at this. They're so good.
Don't hit the diamond. Thank you. Only lost a few skeletons. Here we go. Knowledge plus one.
Basic resistance. Basic resistance endows a hero's troops with five percent magic resistance.
Yeah take it. Here we go. Now I get some good. What is this? One a day. Well I could probably
do this now. Although let me get the points. It's 30. What are we doing? All the taxes took
all my money so I can't do anything. We got this. The imp cash. I've got 3500. We're gonna go up
to just the warm machine factory. The Harpies. I think I can take them. Or the cent. No.
Let me take a look at the map because I need to start to move out somewhere. I own that stuff.
I really just I need. What about up here? Pack of stone golems. Okay I can do this.
I can get up here. We can get the this stuff here. Yeah move up here. This is the good old
games version. This is not the HD remaster. This is the good old games version with the community
HD patch. I need 10 000 gold to do that. I don't have that yet unfortunately. Oh that stuff he's
getting. I need to get out there. The tomb. Did not go to the windmill yet. Take the three.
Uh this is the rally flag. I can grab this. Walking morale up. Might as well touch it.
Okay I'm ready. A pack of golems. I have a pack of golems too. Let's go. They're just clearing all
the... I'm dead. Pack of stone golems. Nine and nine. I mean I'm gonna win. I'm gonna keep the
skeletons back here. I really want to just have... I want to attack first so then everybody defend.
Yeah I don't want to I don't want to be the one that gets hit. Let them come to us
like that. All right you are gonna go... Let's just overwhelm this one. Overwhelm this guy with
everybody. He's running away. He's going down here. Overwhelm. You stay back. Uh oh not good.
You gotta... We gotta get up there. Fuck. You go up there. Lock. Get rid of this one.
Three versus... There we go. We should do it. One more. Fuck. He's come with my skeletons. I know he
is. Why am I holding back the skeletons? Because I can... If I if I don't lose any skeletons I can
have like a hundred of them. Remember anytime one point is ticked off there's a chance that it adds
to my skeleton stack. So I mean I'm just I'm going like skeletons. We're good. Actually probably
good to get. No not worth it. So I have 49 now. I only lost three people. I should maybe have some
more. Let's see what I got now. 53 skeletons now. Alchemist's lab. I've already visited this.
Bingo. I now have one of those a day and then there's something... Artifact. What is it? Gog.
Got some gremlins. Is it gog? Scary. I don't know if I can fight this. I don't know what a gog is.
They're ranged. Lots of gogs. I do. Resource silo. Lookout tower.
Alter bushes. Genies. Genies or capital building? Genies.
Okay capital. I'll have a decent amount to recruit after this. I don't want to... I can't... I don't
want to waste money here. Get one city ready to go. He's coming. No. This guy's clear. That orange
is clearing out. Oh fuck. He got in a boat. He got in a boat. This guy got in a boat. Where's he
going? He could go down here and then... Oh no he's in a boat. He finally got one. He's gonna go down
and he's gonna come over here and he's gonna meet me over here. I'm fucked. Okay I gotta be ready
for this. Is it worth trying to get this artifact? I have some decent army. Let's go. This is not
that... there's only 11 of them. Yeah they're weak. Get up there. Checkmate in five turns. No we got
this. I'm gonna... I'm just gonna move the skeletons up there anyways. Ballista. Nice. Yeah it is.
Hopefully that that artifact I'm hoping is a uh a table turner if you know what I mean. Go this way.
One hit kill. Not quite. Almost a one hit kill. Good job. You can just sit here. Nice. Lost a couple
of skeletons but that's all right. There it is. Cape of Velocity. What does it do? Warn about the
shoulders. This cape increases the combat speed of all your units by plus two. I mean it's all right.
That's okay. That's pretty good. I can move more. That's good. Backpack. I don't have any backpack.
Nothing else up here. I'm delaying the inevitable. Here we go. Capital. Chris your kingdom to 4,000
gold a day. It's done. Now I need to upgrade. Uh this has already been done. This has already
been done. I need to do the Golem Factory. Do that another time. Speaking of Golem Factories,
I want to go back to the Golem Factory and hopefully I'll have 10 by then. I'll have 10
by then. Because I'm scared of the guy on the damn boat. I don't know where he's gonna go.
It's so scary. Someone's gonna be waiting for me down here.
This is so close. Look at how close he is. He's in the boat right there.
Uh 10. I have 10. I'm not gonna be able to make it. Not even close. Castle. Taravan. Wall of Nod.
Lookout Tower. Resource silo. One gem. Golden Pavilion. Or the genies. Genies or the uh nagas.
Probably nagas. They're the ultimate unit. No no no. Giants are the ultimate unit.
We'll go genie. Okay genie now available. 13 to 16 damage. That's pretty good. They're available.
I've got 10 wood. Don't worry I know I just spent five but trust me it's gonna take me at least
like four or five days to even get down here. If we get a new week we'll have a ton of people.
All right I'm ready. Here we go. He's going down to the islands.
Fuck. He's gonna get all this shit before I am. All dwellings increase population again.
Come on. Give me to the boat. I'm so close. What do I got? I have so many people to recruit. How
much is it? 95 80. I have so many recruits. Save the money. I'm gonna just get barely down here.
This guy's gonna take all the cool shit. Let's go. That's all I can do. Just don't go to this
cool island. I want to go to the island. He's on the island. Oh he's on the island right now.
They're scooping up fucking taxes. Wow. Why? What the fuck? What? They took all my wood. I had
you took all my wood. Damn it. I'm so disappointed right now. I gotta go for it. I have to.
This is too much money. I'm not using gold. Yeah but this is every cent I have. Just to get seven
I can get one two three. Give me the boat now. Boat please. That's it. It was only a thousand.
Give me a boat. Get in the boat. We're in the boat. Boys and girls we've made it. We're gonna go rescue
this person. I have no more turn points. He don't come over here. Oh he's on the island. That's my
island. That's my island survivor. I've been looking forward to this. You pulled a shipwreck
survivor from certain death in an unforgiving ocean. Grateful he rewards you for your act of
kindness by giving you the crown of the supreme magi. While on your head this item increases your
knowledge by plus four. That's a lot of points. 70 spell points. Favorable winds. Rock. Chip.
Where do I go? But he's on here too. What does he have? Stryker the death knight. What do you got?
Oh he's dead. He's fucking dead. Look at this shit. He's got nothing. He's so depleted. Let's go get
him. This dude is fucked. He's got nothing. He has like three zombies. Stay here. I have no more. I
got him. Don't leave here. There he goes. There he goes. He's right here. Did he get it? No. Where is
he? Where did this motherfucker go? Is he inside? That's his boat right there. He knows I'm coming
for him. Coming for you. Hey is that uh your boat back here? Oh fancy seeing you here. Oh so you're
gonna go in that? There's a bunch of uh orcs in there. You're dead. Bye. The mistake was taking
this. Do you see how many times this castle has changed hands? Like five times at least. This is
just a dead zone here. I will kill you. You have one person? This must... I mean this is a scout.
This is just a scout. Yeah. You've captured an enemy artifact. Endless bag of gold and bow of
elven cherry wood. It took like 15 grand. When equipped the endless bag of gold increases your income by
750 a day. This bow increases your archery by five percent. What a mistake that was. That guy is
fucking dead. All right. I don't know if I want to do attack this yet and I got a boat too. So I got
money. Very important. Let me take this place over. This place. Wait what's in here? Oh boy. He's on
his way over here. This guy's dangerous. Um look at this shit. There's stuff back here. Red border
gate. There's like a troll bridge. I probably need to just get on the boat and get out of here. Let
me just go to the arena. There's nothing else down here. I'm not going to go in here.
Ding dong. That's two attack. I think I need defense. I have zero defense guys. It's very
necessary. Give me the shipyard. Mine. He's not going to be able to move. He's going to anchor up
here and he's going to be stuck. So I got an opportunity. I can leave. Why did I do that?
Because he can't move when he lands. I'm getting in there and I'm getting the gold.
Okay. Artifacts. Merchants. For a nominal fee you can purchase artifacts from the merchants.
Lookout tower. Super genies. Yeah. Upgraded genies. Master genie and recruit genies. What's the
difference? Hates effreet. Spellcaster. Random benefit. Pretty good. This is still uncontested
somehow. All right. He's gonna he's not gonna have enough points to do anything. Here he comes in
the boat again. He's going all he's going around. See he might take this castle but okay do I have
enough? He's not coming for me I don't think. I think I can get in there and get out. Where's the
boat? What happened to the boat that was right here? I can get in and get out. He summoned the
boat. Oh fuck. No I know my boat's right here but like he's he must have summoned it back.
Summon it? Should I summon it from him? No but I can get in this one. I'm going for it. Fuck it.
I can't let you pass. You should seek a key master tent. Like that? What about the troll bridge?
Much to your dismay the troll bridge is guarded by several trolls. Do you want to fight?
No. No. Go back to my like war machine factory. I'm gonna recruit more golems. No I am not going
for it. All right it's time to get another hero. Wizard or necromancer. I kind of want like a knight.
Especially hypnotize. Animate dead. Just have two necromancers? Yeah. Level three. Wait who the
fuck is this person? What? Wait. Phant? Wasn't this guy an enemy? Oh he's a deserter. He deserted.
That's so funny. He deserted and we hired him. No loyalty at all. Holy shit. All right do you think
I should just deck him out with all my money? Fuck yeah. I'm gonna spend every set of golems.
He's pretty fucking strong though. All right like we can't just have one hero.
This guy has a lot. The master genies. These are really good. I'm okay with this. No where's uh
where's he? He's got the glyph of gallantry. We're out by one. He has the first aid tent. Heals
everybody in each round. Okay what does he have for spells? Summon boat. Great. Animate dead.
Increased effect of animate dead. Okay I'm gonna keep him here for now. Let's move on. I need to
go check out the golems. Oh there he is. Did he fight? Okay he had to fight. This is empty.
Dude I don't know. I'm not doing that again. He's getting so much more money though.
I'm not gonna fall for it. He did it like the same thing to this guy.
Let him take on the trolls. Let him fight everything and then I'm gonna clean him up.
10 wood. Nice. Hold on a minute. Wait wait wait wait wait. Is there anything else over here?
Freelancer's guild. There's a bunch of stuff down here. Dwarven treasury.
Anchor up first. I got a turn. All right what do we got? Library. Uh upgraded golem factory.
Or it's time to get. Yeah this guy is gonna. This is the best unit I can make. Get him both.
This person is really ready to go. I could upgrade it too. Hopefully the person doesn't fall. Go
fight the trolls in the bridge. No. All dwellings increase population. We get a condor. 5,000. What
do we got? I can get a couple of these. I can get. Yeah let's just get the ones. Let's recruit
more golems. All right. I feel pretty safe. I'm gonna get back in that boat and I'm gonna
explore over here. I feel safe. Get more. I mean I just want to just sit here
and farm them. Farm these guys. All right let's go. Farm golems for 10 straight turns. I feel like
I'm gonna lose something. War taxes. No it's only it's per week. It's not every day. It's every week.
Sorry. Unfortunately guys. I'm gonna go exploring. I'm gonna go down here. Or should I fight the
trolls? Queens. Oh man. I can make naga queens. I can make it fully upgraded. I just can't afford
it right this second. Let's go. He's gonna be right in my way. Uncharted territory. Hold on a minute here.
Dead. Boat-to-boat combat. 28. You ain't got nothing. Get on over there. Walk the plank.
They're gonna have to do the same thing. Ow. He ran away. He wasn't gonna deal with that. He
abandoned his post. Goodbye. Cowards. Coward. So what is over here? A lot of uncharted territory.
What about up there? Should I check this? Oh there's a shipwreck. Let's check this out.
Shipwreck. Let's check it. Resource silo. Let's upgrade some stuff. This is the best thing that I can make.
I'm bringing in so many people. I'm just spending so much money. I've got so many people.
I'm going to win. The turtle wins the race. Did you see the end of that movie?
Pirate ship creaks eerily as it's pushed against rocks. Do you wish to search the shipwreck?
Yes. Morale down. Search it, yeah. Nothing in there? Whoa. Okay. I'm gonna be unstoppable.
Uh oh. Red. I haven't seen red or blue. Mermaids. Luck. Increased luck.
Anything else? Oh. Turn around. I've gotten too greedy. I thought there was shit over here.
Should I board him? Let's see what he does. I think red is the actually one to be afraid of.
No this is very heavily guarded right now. I'm going down here.
Do I have everything that I can? 99, 66, 39, 23, 24, 15, 6. Unstoppable. Could have another hero too.
Yeah I could have another hero. Um maybe I'm absolutely gonna pick like this weird frog guy.
All right who am I gonna give you? You're gonna you're gonna go off on your own adventure.
Um you don't get anybody. Have this one person farm golems. That would be
useful. All right you go off on an adventure. In fact, no I can't fit a bolt in the boat.
You gotta make your way over here. I need like two boats. Head down here. Okay let's move on.
That's where I'm going. Blue just hanging out right there. Can I see what he has?
The Freelancer's Guild. I feel like there's something good there.
Let's land. A lot of shit over here. I don't know where we got you. Let's see. What do you want to do
here? Go back. You go to the Golem Hut. We got there available. Uh we're almost at the next week.
You can take some. We also have Ewan here who I could bring you out. But should this be the
Stax Defender? Level one Alchemist or the Edamon the Burning Guy. Specialty Golems.
Specialty Golems. Should she just take a bunch? Just take the Golems? Just take them all. I mean
she is the Golem like queen. All right you take the Golems. Have fun. All right let's go. Five
gems. Witch Hut. Basic Offense. What does the specialty do? Increases the attack and defense
skills of any stone or iron Golems for each level attained after third level.
Xena. It's a frog guy. You kind of uh you're kind of like useless at this point.
Anything else to upgrade? Golem Factory. Probably should just have. I probably should have done
that before. Send her back. Waste of a turn but whatever. Oh yeah I'll put frog guy in a boat.
Send him somewhere. All right we'll do that after. Go back. Upgrade these guys. 41 iron Golems
and let's buy as many people as we can. I can leave. I got this. These are so good.
I all right I got enough Golem. No just yeah we're gonna go. I got 41 iron Golems. Here we go.
Time to start with you. We've got Shipyard. I mean do I should just buy it? Own it? Does it really
matter? We got Freelancer's Guild. Please inspect our find. Whereas if you feel like offering a trade
click on the items you wish to trade for. Oh I see. I can give you two iron Golems for one wood.
Oh get the fuck out of here. No thanks. Try and learn third level spell. Frost Ring.
Lots of holders. It's a gold mine. I think I could take them. We got uh idle fortune. Let's get it.
What about you? I want to get you shipping out here. I can't buy a boat but I will next turn.
Out of money comes taxes of course. Frost Ring. Magic Arrow is 50 points. There's a lot of them
but are they are they magic resistant? Not bad. We can take them. Oof that hurt.
Get in there. Got this. Spread them out a little bit. You go forward here. Yeah we're good. I need
I should meet that lady somewhere in the middle and transfer the golems to her.
Although there's no bonus for these golems unfortunately right?
This way. One last gremlin remains. I think that gremlin's gonna stay alive.
These things have we've gonna lose our skeleton stack I think. Although we should get some more.
Lost 29 skeletons. Ton of experience though. Ooh fourth level spells. Basic earth magic. I need
to go and learn some spells. Four gems. One a day. Good. All right let's go this way. Thousand
experience. This is this guy's capital. Purple. Not strong enough to take that yet. All right golem
lady needs to go down to golem center. Right here. We need to get wood. We need boats. I need a ton
of shit. Yeah the second city. I mean no one's coming near this. This has been untouched. Maybe
it's time to put some resources into this and actually make it. But I don't have any money,
I don't have any resources. I need wood. Can't do anything with it right now. You cannot get a boat
so I can't do anything with you. You may as well just sit here. All right gold mine. Den of thieves.
I'm actually interested in right now. Here we go. Best hero. Number of towns. Red. So red is
oh jesus wyverns. Everybody has something really strong.
I'm terrible on defense but I'm powerful in everything else. Now this dude has a legit red
dragon. Look at that face. I have the best income. Good to know. All right homestead. Purple. Let's
take all this shit away from purple. Do it next turn. Don't have enough for a boat. So you two
just gonna have to sit here. Let's go back this way. Lookout tower. A lot of knowledge. This cloud
temple. I need it's just my resources are so depleted. I'm just gonna have to keep going.
What is this on? This is just on pc. It's on windows 10. Good old games. It works perfectly
fine. There's an HD patch. You don't have to get the HD remaster. The HD remaster on steam
is unfortunately I guess doesn't have any of the expansion packs. Doesn't have any added content.
It's a thousand gold a day. Medusa stores. Homestead. Recruit wood elves. Yeah Medusa stores.
This is probably Medusa's. I don't have enough. All right it might be time to upgrade this to the
town. What are we gonna get here? Tavern for a fort. City hall. I need tavern and mage guild.
Taverns. No that's wood. Resource silo. Mage. It's all wood. I need the wood.
No not until I get a boat. Although I might as well just. I'll take 85 of these. Why not?
At least there's somebody there. Resource silo is five. Five thousand. What do I have? I have plenty.
Yeah let's build the resource silo. I can do it on both. Resource silo. Five thousand and five.
Do it again. That's plus two gems a day. Just waiting for the goddamn wood so I can get this
person in a boat and send him. How much are you? Not quite enough to get these. All right let's go.
I'm about to be at the stage where I'm gonna. Uh-oh. Oh fuck. That guy just landed.
Oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Not my two scouts. Nine.
Boat. Give me his boat. See you later motherfucker. All right. I mean I've got. I've got 47 iron
golems. I'm gonna get out of here with this lady. Stalem. He has a horde. Horde. Horde. He has like
hundreds of people. Body block him. I can't body block him. It's all right. We still have
uh Professor Thant. Guys no one's taking this castle. Not with Professor Thant. Okay what's
the Medusa stores? What happened? Oh somebody already took it. I got scared for a second. All
right let's go this way. The windmill. Already visited that. Already went to the dead thieves.
Let's go to the dwarven treasury. We found a dwarven treasury. Do you wish to attack the guards?
What? What? What'd I just do? 20% magic resist. I have an 80% chance to hit you with that.
That was bullshit. It's all right. You take this one on. Good. Look at that. That's a ton of damage.
Uh I think I'm just gonna split up into the four corners. Take the skeletons
up here. All right you. Both you guys kill this one.
Yeah you're getting counter-attacked every five seconds. Yeah you're trying to run away.
Uh who do I want to shoot at? Probably probably you. And then you uh go up and help the skeletons.
I don't care about this guy. He's gonna die. Here you just go up. Save this guy. He's fine.
He's the body blocker. He is official body blocker.
Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead. A lot of dwarves here. There better be a ton of good shit in here.
I'm gonna be very upset. No get away from my archers. He's strong. All right run away. No fuck.
I thought I had the other guy selected. I had. I thought I had that this guy was selected.
I'm fine. There. See. Just kill him.
All right you got one dwarf left. Not a big deal. Costly battle. It's fine.
There it is. 2,000 experience. That's a lot. I did lose some but you know that was. There's
a hundred dwarves guys. Advanced resistance. Yes. Having defeated the battle dwarves you
discover five crystals and 5,000 gold. It's actually exactly what I needed. Here's an obelisk.
Um I don't know what to do here though. Unfortunately this is not good. This is not
good at all. Nobody else to recruit. I kind of have to run away or sacrifice myself.
I got the guy on the boat but he might just. Okay. Perfect scenario is he turns around
and is pissed that I took the boat and fights me. There's nowhere for me to go. Hide. Hide.
What is the hide? He has a full turn coming up. Bring Thant out. Should I bring Thant out and
just have him just run down here? I could do that. Are you ready for this? Let's go. Oh you're dead.
You ran right by me. All right. Obelisk. What the hell? Puzzle map. What is this? Puzzle map?
What do I do with this? I have missing pieces or. Hmm. I need all the pieces. I don't have it.
All right. We have some some shit going down. So expert. I didn't say I was an expert. I
said I'd played this when I was a young kid. I don't know if that does. All right. Uh warrior's
tomb. Let's keep going. What is this one? Haste. That's a good spell. Warrior's tomb. Mushrooms.
Let's just get a view here. Oh fuck. Uh oh. All right. This is a fight. This is a fight to end
all fights. What do you think? Is it time? Is it time to get to go nuts? I'll get a lot of
experience with this one. Here we go. Skeleton horde versus very powerful genies and very powerful
queens. Okay. We've got. Let me take a look here. Genie. Genie can move very very fluidly.
We've got bloodlust. Curse. Protection from fire. Increase the hand-to-hand damage inflicted by the
selected unit. Cause the selected enemy unit to inflict minimum damage in combat.
The spell will affect nobody. Okay. What about bloodlust? Should I give bloodlust to the genie?
Well bloodlust to the uh to the naga queens. Stone skin. How long does it last? Just for the whole
the whole thing. Bloodlust on the naga queens. We're gonna get these guys in a favorable position.
I'm gonna say like right here. Same deal. Get you guys in a favorable position.
All right. We've got the naga queens. On you up here probably. Let's get like up here.
Oh that hurts. All right. You're ranged. Nice. That does a lot. Just get you guys up there.
You're just like a shield essentially at this point. I need the mages. Who else is ranged? Nice.
Beautiful. Oh I thought that was gonna do it. Vampire. All right. Going for the queens. Genie
time. Now spell cast a random benefit. He can pretty much go anywhere in the map. I wonder if
I should just take out the lich. I think I can get the lich with the gremlins. I mean I could buff.
Cast a spell on obsidian gargoyles. Cast a spell on the naga queens. How would I get shield?
66. I'm going for a I think we'll go for the the wraiths. Oh that was easy. Trying to kill
this. Oh fuck. That was bad. All right. I'm gonna go with the queens up here. Big unit versus big
unit. Let's go. What did that do? How much did he kill? Get rid of this guy. Did one. I mean this
thing is insane. So once this is done it's it's over. Okay. I gotta play smart here. I can't
curse anybody. Maybe bloodlust on on genie. I'm gonna do more like stone skin on the naga.
Curse? I don't think I can. I can't curse anybody. I'm gonna do stone skin on
on naga. All right. We gotta we gotta focus on this dude here.
Two black knight stone. Good. This thing has to die. Genie. Should I just buff the queen again?
Should we just buff the fuck out of the queens? I think I can kill it.
Yes. All right. We're good. 62 versus uh with 10. Five. It's in the bag.
Yeah this is the bag. I ain't got nothing. I win. Ran away. I lost. Not very much.
Level four. Advanced wisdom. Fourth level spells or basic water magic. It's a good thing I had this
guy. Let's do water magic. All right. Cool. All right. Back to bed. That's all I wanted you to do.
I wanted to go get more minions. You on the other hand. Uh there's a boat there now. I have a scout.
I can do two boats. Not yet. You need to go exploring.
Just search. Yes. Nothing there. Got nothing in there.
You have you got a lot of stuff too. Make another boat. I think I'm gonna do two boats here. Yeah.
Let's go. Let's get in there. Opportunity down here. Middle thing in the castle. I can do the
trolls maybe. How are we doing on resources? Wall of knowledge. How much is this? Five and a
thousand. Yeah. Just build it. Let's go. Plus one knowledge. Anybody that goes in. I've got able to
recruit. All right. Let's go. Uh oh. I'm on the defensive now. Who came in? Oh shit. It's purple.
Who did you attack? Oh I'm down there. I don't. This is bad. You've got unicorns. Shit. This is
not good. This is this is a losing battle. 100. It's the same guy with the 100 plus centaurs. Um
but I could probably take a few people out and then run away. This is so many crystal things to
lose. Oh no. Wait. What does surrender do? What's the difference? I'm just gonna. I mean I'm just
gonna. I bet. Apparently I'm just gonna run. Here we go. Surrender lets you keep your army for a
price. Oh no. Fuck that. Thankfully this guy doesn't have the whole army.
I lose badly in both scenarios. How much is it to surrender? I wonder like what do I have to pay?
Coward. But at least I keep the artifacts. He's back. I had a lot of artifacts on that guy. I'm
gonna lose him. We're good. Okay. Now you. Well this is our new main anyways. One knowledge.
Give me your shit. Come outside please. All right. Level eight versus level four.
I mean I guess we could. He's level eight. Should I just give him everything?
Maybe I'll just give him everything because he's level eight. Ballista. I can only have one.
Ballista. I can do the ten. This is a glyph of gallantry. Mara by one or health of all units.
No that's way better. Okay. Fant has better. I'm gonna keep Fant on defense. In fact I want to
Okay. You've already visited. I gotta get something else here though. Oh yeah the gold.
Gold. Gold. Give me the bag. Switch the bag. That'll be forever protected. Oh I can actually take
this. Because now I gave him the bag of gold. Very nice. Very nice. So Fant. Get back in here.
It is your job. I think I have to move you. He is the one that will defend this castle. Get in here.
Summon boat. Dispel. Slow. Stone skin. Um can I learn any of these? I have to upgrade it. Yeah
it's level one. What is that? Thousand. It just costs resources. All right. We'll switch it out.
We have. You have a lot of good people now. You're forced to be reckoned with completely.
Uh I'm looking. Hopefully I can recruit something. I could get some more golems.
All right. I'm going back down. All right. We got boats. You have 47 golems. I wonder if I can
fight the trolls with these. I'm kind of scared to do that. Yeah what is Nimbus's specialty? That's
a good question. Specialty is eagle eye. She's five percent per level bonus to eagle eye skill
percentage. What about you? What's your specialty? Eagle eye again. This dude sucks. This dude's only
purpose is to like walk around and look at stuff. Nobody even here.
Claim that castle. It's mine. You are gonna go. Who's over here? You a shipyard. Avoid that. Go
down here. You know what I'm saying? Like up this way maybe. Or down here. Let's go down here.
He's taking everything back. Wood elf growth plus five dwellings increase population.
Damn it. I'm so annoyed. Right at the last day they came back.
That sucks. Why does this guy always pre-record his screams? It's just easier that way. I actually
weirdly enough. We can bring this up now. I'm actually like 52 years old. By the time you're
seeing this. I've recorded like eight or nine thousand like six hour sessions and I batch
uploaded all of them and they're all scheduled to go. I'm actually like 50. I've been doing this. I
did this like I don't know maybe 30 like 20 years ago or so. It's kind of I guess that kind of they
can come out. Sirens. What did that say? A bunch of people dove out of a bunch of people drowned
themselves. That's great. I lost half my army. That sucks. Let's go with plus two attack. I don't
get in there so bad and I can't do anything about that either. No this dude's gonna have to go
explore over on this side. They're already showing these to me. Castle ship. Go take it. I don't think
I can. I have like 40 frogs. I don't think they're gonna be good enough. Yeah they have much better
units that I do. I'll just get down here. I think I can handle this up here now. Yeah I can handle
this. I'm going up here. That's a gold mine. That's a mercenary camp. Let's go for it. War machine
factory. I already have one of these. Lots of harpy hags. That will be the next thing I do.
Speaking of doing. Level two. Remove obstacle lightning bolt. Disrupting ray and fortune.
Cool. Other town. I don't have enough money. Let's go. All the purple is over here on the right side.
There's the fucking taxes again. Goose eggs. Zero everywhere. What do you guys have? Pack several
lots. Pack. I could kill this one. I do have a lot of gems. Gotta have a lot of gem. I have more gem
buildings than I have anything else. All right you just keep going over here.
Damn it. All right harpy hags. Do not engage. They're afraid. Touch the obelisk. Puzzle map.
Don't have them all unfortunately. Lots of captains. Centaur captains. I wonder if I can do it.
Don't engage. They're afraid. Recruit stone gargoyles. How many do I have? No I don't want that.
Now this is where it's going to get hard. These are absolutely going to attack me.
Morale increased. Lots of silver. Pegas high. They scatter. I'm so powerful. A thousand more a day.
Nice. Awesome. And I'll go to the mercenary camp up here and get all this stuff.
Now what the hell am I going to do with you? I'm just going to put you. This is just a scout.
Head this way. I mean he's definitely, he's dead. He's dead.
Uh oh. They got a bone dragon. Time to die. Four. You killed fucking 33. 25 to 50 damage.
That's insane. Let's go this way. Ow. Hey you. Get that motherfucker out of here.
Lots of, they're going to run away too. All right. Look at all this shit up here. We got mercenary camp.
Plus one attack. A thousand experience. Expert resistance. That's huge.
20 magic resistance. A thousand gold or 500 experience. We're going to do the experience
I think. Both of them. 1500 experience. Level 10. Expert wisdom. Basic learning.
That seems like the expert wisdom or basic learning.
Are they the same kind of thing? Level fifth level spells. I got to go back and do this.
Expert wisdom. Wisdom and learning. High wisdom, low intelligence.
Should I be, should I learn? No, that's just experience. But
all right. We're going to do the basic learning. All right. I've cleaned this out.
This guy's pretty strong now. My only concern is now with the unguarded couple of places here is
someone's going to be coming here. You just landed. What do you got? That's not good. Purple is going
to be coming up this way. I have to bring you back to the castle. You can just go like Magellan this
way. There's nothing over here. Don't even tell me there's nothing here. Artifact merchant. Library.
Lookout tower. I can do that. No, that's 10,000. Let's just recruit some people. I'm going to spend
the money. Just in case for some reason he gets here. Let's go. Depends on what Purple's going to
do. Oh no. He got it. Did he just go in the boat? He's taking everything. What am I doing out here?
There's nothing even out. This just rocks. Oh shit. Holy crap. This just rocks and shit.
He took all my stuff. Where are you? Throng Horde Horde Swarm Horde Pack. Is this a fight?
I mean this must be like 300. No, no, no, no, no, no. This is going to be a battle at the castle,
I think. I'm not going to be able to make it back. I'm not going to be able to make it back in time.
No, we're okay. This is a pretty decent defense.
See what happens. Thank God. What an idiot. Yes. Oh, he didn't do anything. He just turned around.
He got scared. Come on. I have to wait another turn to do this? Give me my stuff back. It's mine,
not yours. I just ruined everything. I just fucking ruined everything. He can kill me now
because of a goddamn gold mine or a gem mine. Whatever the hell it was. I'm dead.
If he decides to turn around and attack me, I'm dead. Oh, thank God he went the other way.
I'm excited about this though. This is completely uncharted territory.
Whoa, this is a dragon utopia. You stand before the dragon utopia, a place off limits to mere
humans. Do you wish to violate this rule and challenge the dragons to a fight? I don't think
I do, but that's cool that it's down here. I could probably recruit like next level dragons down here.
Save scum it and just see what it is. I couldn't go back in. The cursor wouldn't let me do it
because I was already standing on the space. I was standing on the one spot where I was
allowed to do it, so I had to move. Let's do it again. I already learned that. I already learned
that. Let's go. I'm actually not afraid anymore. He already cleaned this all out. I feel like,
no, I'm going to go back and I'm going to keep, I'm going to recruit more. Yeah,
I'm going to take all these guys because I want to be unbeatable over here. All right, I need
a, I need 20 wood. What is this? Five wood? It's not worth it. I need the wood. City hall. I need mage
and yeah, but I just, I'm going to burn all my wood. Whatever. Nobody claims this.
Yeah, tax day is coming up. You're right. Well, you're just stuck down here now. I was,
I just forgot. I was supposed to just go look in there, but I saved it. It don't matter.
I, I'm all right. Whatever. If I like, okay, if I went in there and I died,
I would have had to do like that whole last turn again. I don't know. Whatever. It don't matter.
Like do you really want me to like redo the last whole turn? There's no way I'm doing this.
Well, it's every kind of dragon. What do they have stats? 40 to 50, 40. No, you've got to come in
here with like a hundred at least dead. Well, there it is. That's a cool little thing though.
That's an interesting little like secret. All right. I was going to go up here.
I was going to do this. I want more minions and then I'm taking you on a boat and we're going
to try to kill somebody. I'm going to try to wipe somebody up. Just coming up this turn coming up.
All right. No, it was this one over here. Tavern. You have made us very pleased. Good.
Now you have to just get out of here. You just, oh, I hate that. I have to do this shit.
All right. I want mage tower level three. I need six pots. I can get that right now.
Learn spells. Level three. What else we got? We got air shield, destroy undead, force field.
Let's bring them in and we're going to look at this. So many. So many. I don't know. Should
I take them all? I'll be unstoppable. All right. Let's learn a spell. So destroy undead. Attempts
to destroy any undead creatures in the battlefield. Force field. Place a small force field on the
battlefield at a point specified by the caster. Destroy undead sounds really good. Shield is a
selected unit reducing the amount of damage received from ranged attacks. That's really good
too. Maybe destroy undead. So now how do I put a spell on? I'm curious because how do I get it on
here? Right click? Or being like the book? Or do I just do what is good? Oh, you auto learn them.
Okay. That makes sense. Let's, let me just make sure. All right. Cool. So you just get them all.
All right. Uh, we're at the end of the week. I'm going to wait. I'm going to recruit and then I'm,
this is the character that is, Nimbus is going to kill everyone. I'm going to take them
on a journey to wipe out every opponent. I've upgraded all my dudes. I'm ready for a fucking
bloodbath. Anything else I can get up here that has been taken from me? Let's go to the windmill.
Just three, six crystals. Might as well take it. All right. I'm good like this. Uh, I guess I could.
I need, no, I don't have any resources for it. Let's go. Here comes a new week. All dwellings
increase population. Unfortunately, you're just stuck back here for an undetermined amount of time.
All right. Money. Recruit everyone. I am now a real ruler. I've got a lot of people.
A very scary amount. I have very highly skilled people. I don't know if I want the skeletons.
18 queens. All right. I need 20 wood. I have to do the mage guild and then the city hall.
All right. I can't do it yet, but I am ready. The question is, should I, hmm, should I take
this fucking place over? It's mine. Get it. Take it from orange. Go take all this stuff and then
summon a boat down here. I think I could take this. I think I could kill them both and then take a
boat. It's either that or the other scenario is I could go here. All right. So run down here.
Go try to kill the dragons. Oh, that's so scary. If I go kill the dragons, I have nobody available
to defend my only remaining two structures. The troll bridge. Yeah. But then you'll have dragons.
Yeah. I need to build up defenses too. I've got to go like wipe somebody. I've got to go kill
somebody. I've got to get up here. He's like right here. I could take this. Take this. Kill him.
Go to the troll bridge. Let's just wait. I got to get this guy on a boat anyway. So let's get in a
boat. All right. Let's go. Blue is not sure what he wants to do. There's the taxes. Didn't have
anything anyways. So far away. It just takes forever for you to get over here. Okay. How many points?
I got 100 points. I could go to the golem factory, which there are. Who should I get?
What do you think? Two diamond or three gold? Why not both? I don't have enough room for both.
I don't. Yeah. I only have one slot. Diamond? Yeah. Diamond's probably better.
Gold's more cost effective, but diamond is almost unheard of from spells.
Oh boy. This is iron, right? Okay. Pretty good group. Let's see if I can summon a boat.
Well, you have a boat. Should I just trade? You want to trade boats?
Just. Boy, they've been so fucked with wood this whole game. Uh oh. You going to the dragon?
This guy's heading to like the dragon's den.
I got to get away from you. Nobody in here. Well, I don't think I can fight you
although you don't really have anything that scary. We have packs small. No. He's going to
go die to the dragons. Let me see if I can get a boat here because there's a couple of boats.
Summoned boat. Do you not have summoned boat? Fuck. You don't have summoned boat.
Well, I'm just going to have to wait till you bring it up here. I clicked the wrong button.
Oh, there it is. Did I get it? How do I cast it? Not from the inventory. I can't just. I have to.
That's not. That is not the spell book. I thought it was failed to summon a boat.
I thought I could do it from both places. Uh, I, is this even possible? I, I,
is there even a friendly boat? This is why I have one friend. Let me go.
There are no boats to some and I just wasted fucking points. Just bring it over here.
He's going to the dragon. He's going to die. He's actually going to die. He has no idea.
Switch the boat. Come here. Oh, damn it. No, I was right there. No. Oh, fuck. I, oh, whatever.
Get to do another turn anyways. Oh, you're dead. You're dead. You're dead. We're going to do the
old switcheroo. Watch this. Put him in this boat. You think it's this person in the boat.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me all your stuff. What do you have? All right. Now you go on the
boat and he's going to attack the boat and be like, holy shit. This guy's unbeatable pack. Lots
thrown. He's got dragons. He has bucket red dragons, but he only has packs of the other ones.
Wait for him on land. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do because this is like,
I could die to save it. I'm just going to go in the boat. He's not, he's going to avoid me.
Look, this lady's, he's not going to attack. But what if he does? I can't attack him from here.
He actually is going to the dragon. He doesn't have enough to do that.
So make sure he doesn't get them. In fact, here, do you want to take these?
Take these. I just got some more of them. You can have them. Oh, no, no, no. I got them. No,
nevermind. What do you think? Should I fight it? Should I go for it? Okay. Who is priority here?
14. That's not that big of a deal. I think that's the only range unit they have.
180 health. Jesus. This is the one that's going to be the horrible, horrible, horrible problem.
I don't have curse frost ring lightning bolt 135. Oh my God. I can lightning bolt the dragon
dragon immune immune to spells one through three. That's horrible. Lightning bolt the centaurs.
I'm going to lightning bolt the centaurs. I think see if I can kill like 30 of them.
That's not 30 of them. That's not 30 of them. That was like seven.
The genie. Who should I buff? I'm going to buff somebody with the genie. Who should I buff?
Who should be buffed? Um, somebody with range probably. Fire shield. All right.
Nobody move. Nobody move. Where should I throw this at? Probably the ranged. Get rid of the ranged.
Ranged. The ranged is gone. Okay. Now I just have to worry about the pegasus and shit.
All right. You're expendable. Get on the plank. You are also expendable. You go. Oh,
you should have gone on the other plank. It's just the golems. They're supposed to be doing this.
Morale going down. Here we go. What does the dragon just fell over and died?
All right. Here come. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh, please. Shit. You suck. Oh no. Oh no.
I think we're good. We're fine. Genie. Who? What's the genie doing? I need to the dragon
to just sit back here. Uh, kill the dragon. Buff the naga. Frenzy. Oh, how many just died?
Twelve. No, it's fine. I thought that was 103 died. Just kill the dragon. Holy shit,
he was pathetic. That was wicked easy. This is the scary part. Oh no, it's not scary at all. I'm
fucking unbeatable. Unstoppable. Nobody can beat me. It's game over. Doesn't matter. I win.
4000 experience. You learned ice bolt. Basic sorcery. 5% more damage. I like it. We're good
to go. Didn't lose very much. I'm going to go sack their kingdom now. Here we go. Is that, oh,
yeah. Is that red? Oh, you got some, you got some shit over here, don't you? Where do I want to go?
What's the destination? I wonder. I could kill this. I could go here and clean up this hole.
I'm going here. Fight the dragons. Um, I'm actually, yeah, I'm going to, I'm going to do,
I'm going to change this up a little bit here. I don't, I want to get rid of, um, this. I'm not
going to, uh, I kind of, Nimbus is not going to die. Nimbus is going to be fine because I want
skeletons. Yeah, I can, I can, let me, let me just transfer and hold on. Come here. Skeletons are
actually really important. I need a space for them. Okay. I'm ready. Let's go kill the trolls.
I have a lot of money too. Let's not forget that I should probably be buying things.
Level four, I don't have any pots, but what about over here?
Mage go level one. That is required for the city hall. I could just, I could take these and upgrade
them too. All right. City hall is next. Did he die? I don't think he went in. He didn't go in yet.
Here we go. Who is here? Trolls. Should I just, is there a reason for me to do this?
I don't think there's a reason for me to fight this. Well, I'm going to buff the wizards. Slow.
See? Oh wait, I can, no, I don't, I don't want them though. Damn it. Ah, that's too bad. No,
I don't want them. Wasn't even worth hiring. I have 80 points now. All right. Let's go claim
this shit. I'm going to take it. There's a, just this one, there's a bug in here.
There's a single bug. You can just, oh, am I going to have you do? I don't know. Go defend the other
one. Go defend this one. Let's go back here and learn some spells and shit. City hall. That's more
money. I could spend some of this money too. Yeah. She can bring the, she can be the goblin transfer.
Did that guy even go in there? I think he chickened out. Gold dragon growth plus five
new week. All right, here we go. Take this castle. 17 bugs. Just get the fuck in there. Thank you.
Lost a couple of gnomes, but that's fine. Mine. Excellent. Okay. We're going to get a hero here to
defend and then I'm going to recruit all these people. Pretty sick. That's decent. That's pretty
decent defense. And we've got level three death knight. Uh, I, yeah. Why can I not recruit you?
It's because I'm in the way. Call of Valhalla. Let me, let me move out of the way.
There we go. I've got a good defense here now. We got, uh, let's see. Yep. This is good. I'm going to
escape town, flee from defending upgrade cliff nest, Thunderbirds. The specialty is
liches. I don't think I have access to them in here though. Not yet. Cyclops, behemoth, ogre,
orc tower. I can make more chieftains. Yeah. Let's get it. So upgrade these two chieftains
two to five, two to five. It's arranged as well. That's good. And you stay there. I do have a pretty
good supply of these things. Fort requires, uh, let's do, I don't think, no, I can't do it yet.
I don't, I capital needs. I just need a bunch of fucking ore. What is it to make the, um, I need a
fort. No, I'm kind of behind. All right. I have secured island in the middle. I'm ready to get in
the boat. This is protected. I don't have a problem here. I'm ready to keep going. You are on your way
to this castle over here. Don't stop. Thank you. Isn't there somebody? Okay. You're still in here.
This castle is now also defended and protected completely in a good spot. Taxes. You headed here.
Get the, this way. You're good. Cloud temple. I need this. I've just, give me more wood. Come here.
All right. Here's my thought process here. Yeah. I'm going to wipe this up. Purple's done. This is
purple's base. It's over. I'm claiming this land. You're about to lose. I'm about to take over purple.
Can't do anything else. Everything is fortified. Yeah, you're running. We just came out. Okay.
I'm not concerned at all, but I am going to save it because, you know, why not?
We've already seen this. I will take that. Thank you. It's a one a day. I'm going right on your
front door. Take the castle. Okay. They've got the unicorns. They've got not very, this is not that
bad. It's just a question of getting rid of these. Destroy undead. Don't have any undead.
Air shield. I feel like I could give this to somebody or maybe I should just blood lust
lightning bolt, ice bolt, force field, lightning bolt. I wonder if I should just lightning bolt
the archers here. Just see what it does. It's pretty good. I'm going to buff. Who do I want
to buff here? Probably the one of the ranged, probably like the mage or the, yeah, the mage,
I think prayer. Okay. The gargoyles can get in. I can get in for the gargoyle. I wonder if I should
get in. Not right now. What I'm saying, like jump over in a minute, get in, hit and get out.
I wonder if it's something I should do. I'm going to try it. Mages. Holy shit. That was devastating.
I cannot get in with the naga. So I'm just going to hold. They so desperately want to get review.
Nobody else can do anything. I'm going to put people up in front though.
Skeletons just get up here and just take damage. Can I come out the front door?
They're coming out. He's coming out the front door. Brave. I did not expect that. I thought
they were going to stay in the walls. They're coming outside. Okay. This just got a little
more hairy. I'm staying with Clint. Okay. Now I'm going to buff the naga. Buff naga. Okay.
Naga is buffed. Now I'm going in. Fuck it. Let's go. Got it. Okay. Dwarves, I think. Yeah.
This is, these are so powerful when you have a stack of them. Let's see if I can wipe this out.
Holy shit. That was insane. I can't get cocky though because all it takes is
thousand damage. Good. I'm sticking. I'm going to, I'm going to just, I don't know.
I kind of have to just, just fight it. It's in front of you. I'm going to lose all the gremlins.
Reinforce. Wow. These guys are so strong. Okay. Here come the centaurs.
Good to go again. Not good. Holy fuck.
I can taste victory. I can smell it. There's only a few things left. I'm going to get the castle.
Purple is no more. I can't go anywhere. So I'm just going to hang out right here.
This thing is very strong. Oh, I think it's like stone skin.
Don't want to lose any more of you. Yeah. Having this many. These, these are, they're upgraded too.
Can I go for a one hit kill? What do you think? Oh, no, that was a bad idea.
Oh, that was a really bad idea. That was a bad, bad idea. This thing is so strong. It's okay.
It's almost done. Kill it. Why are you so strong? No. The siege.
The battle has been won. Almost 10,000 experience. Lost 165 gremlins, 73 gargoyles, 10 magicians,
eight genies, two naga queens, seven skeletons. You have captured an enemy artifact, the tome
of earth magic. This heavy book contains all spells in the school of earth magic.
It must be equipped for those spells to be available. Expert wisdom or advanced sorcery.
Level spells, 10% more damage. Get to go again. Knowledge plus one, advanced logistics,
20% more movement speed. Damn. Advanced offense, all hand to hand by 20% more damage.
Claimed. Mara Shen. Look at this place. Thank you. I appreciate it. We're decking this place out.
You already have a castle. You don't have a capital yet. Wait, do we have a capital?
Is this thing already, what's this? Mystic pond. Produce a small random number of resources every
week. Yeah, give it to me. I need to get in there. No recruits left. So there's green dragon that's
available soon. I'm gonna have you defend here for a little bit because I mean I just did this.
Purple probably has one more stronghold that's down here. How many skeletons did I get for that?
85 skeletons. That's a lot. I'm not confident with this group though because I just lost so many.
Maybe hire a new hero to take care of this place. I have a lot of just strongholds.
I have to click on this one. You stay here. I want to have somebody available in each base.
Here's the book. Where can the book go? The book has to replace something.
Wait, does it? Yeah, it does. Okay, so you got this bone cruiser archery skill by 5%.
That's nothing. Bang. We now know every single earth spell in the game.
I want to know what they look like. Oh my god. What? Allow you to summon earth elementals. Once
cast, no other elemental may be summoned. This almost feels like hacks. Cheat codes. Implosion.
It inflicts massive damage to a single creature stack. Meteor shower. Resurrection. This is insane.
Sorrow. Well, I think that's our... I think we win. I need to get some more here. I gotta get more
units here. That was a major victory, but we suffered major losses. Let's continue the
exploration down here. How much money do I got? Can I do anything? I need to get these goddamn
giants. 10, 10, 10. I'm gonna be getting a lot of income though. I could trade the gems. Yeah,
I could, but that's not very much. I guess it is. Gems for wood. 10, 20 gems. Let's get more. 10
more. So I have... no, hold on. So that means 24 wood. I need 10 ore, which I don't have.
I have four. I have six. All right, let's get those fucking giants.
Giants. 150 health, 40 to 60 damage. Oh, I need gems to recruit. I can only recruit one a week.
Well, time to start the collection of two per week. Let me take a look at them again. Mind spell
immunity. They're very, very expensive. All right, I don't need them this second. I just want to make
sure I could get them. That leaves us with... I have 14 wood, which is enough. What's something
else I want to do? No, what was the other thing I wanted to do before I left? Upgrade the cliff
nest. I need... what do I need for this? Five more ore, which I have. Five... what do I miss in here?
Can't afford it. Oh, okay, I do need five. I need five ore. I was looking down here for some reason.
All right, let's get some ore. What do I have to trade? Crystals. How many do I need? Five or ten?
Did I not go... oh, shit, right. I didn't shake the hand. Cliff nest. Thunderbirds. Golden birds. Nice.
All right, so 15 health, 60. What's the difference? Speed. Chief. Gold birds. Lightning strike. Oh,
that's different. Okay, cool. I think I'm in a pretty good spot. I think I'm in a pretty good
spot right now. I'm pretty confident. Let's get this stuff claimed again. More gold. Get this homestead.
Want that. Okay, what have we got? Still the same weak lookout tower. I mean, I could just build it
just because. But no, that's precious wood. Let's do another upgrade to this one here. Cyclops cave.
I need the ogre fort. 20 wood. 20 and 20. Two things that I don't have.
I mean, it's gonna wipe me out, but let's get eight. And then what about this? This is not
bad exchange right now. What do I need? Three. I mean, 20 and 20, right? Fuck, I need money.
I don't have any favorable. No, it's all good. I'll just wait. We're not at the end of the week yet. I
can afford it. Tax day. Tax day is coming up. Not right now. I still have a couple of days.
16,000. No, wrong place. Upgrade the ogre fort. No, this is a regular fort.
From where is it here? All right. Yeah. Just try to come get me now. All right, that's good.
You are continuing your path. I've already done this. What do I have for points?
Upgraded my points. There's the Dwarven treasury. It's been deserted. I've been to the obelisk
already, but I'm gonna take another turn. Do I have enough pieces? No. All right. Uncharted
territory for the first time. The warrior's tomb. Do I wish to search the tomb? I do.
Oh no, that's not good. What happened? Did I just get super morale decrease? Sulfur. Very bad morale.
Minus three from the warrior tomb. Dicks. All right, what have I got? This is the last day
before the new week in taxes, so let me see if I can build something. I need to spend this money.
What about this new town? Maybe I should save money. Fountain of Fortune. Enchanted Springs.
Ooh. Yeah, let's get it. Which is silver pegasi. All right, here comes a new week.
Notice how purple is painful. Like the rabbit. Move you around. Plus one luck for the next battle.
There's another. Uh-oh. This is purple's last defense. Ammo carts. Unlimited ammunition.
Should I get the ammunition one? Do I already have one of these? I don't know if I'm confident to
get in there. Get the tent. I think I already have one. Just get it, yeah. I've got everything,
though. Um, you've got several. Lots. Lots. Pack several. Few. It might not be a good idea.
I could probably do it, but I don't have the range, I don't think. I'm not confident.
But I do have money and we have a ton of new recruits. Oh, you have every earth spell. Yeah,
that's true. I could just like earthquake them. Should I delete these? Yeah, just dismiss these
idiots. Or yeah, just get out of here. Here we go. 26,003 to get all this stuff. This is turning
into another great army. There's three giants. What does it take to upgrade the giants?
25,030. I can do this in another turn or two. I'll be able to do it. I'll have unstoppable units.
Let's just recruit everybody just to do it. Yeah, bring them all in. Oh, okay, hold on. Wait.
Skeletons. No, that's good. I'm running out of money, though.
Oh, here's the taxes. What are you doing over here? He's coming for blood. I think he's coming.
He's going for it. I think he's going for it. I need to upgrade somebody. I have chieftains,
wolf riders, or hobgoblins. No, I already have a wolf pen. 1,005 and five. I need some more wood.
Terrible exchange. Awful exchange, right? This is bad. I'm gonna need five, so I have what? Two.
Do I have enough money to do this? 1,400. All right, they are now wolf raiders.
I'm gonna lose the talent. I might not. I may not. This is a really good defense.
This game's 20 years old and it holds up really well. Yeah, it's just the classic,
you know? It's just a very, very, very fun game. You can go so elaborate with this game. I mean,
sorry, keep bumping the mic. This is, I think, four players in a medium-sized map. You can do
extra large with eight people and you can put it on very fucking hard. I saved, see? Look.
I'll do it again. See, right now I have the difficulty on normal. The map difficulty is
normal and then I have like the player difficulty on like, what's that, like one notch up,
essentially. You can really just bring it up or down. You can make the game real fucking hard.
I wonder if I should go for this. Let me just see what's down here. All right, there's a mine.
There's a couple of things. I'm just gonna go outside his front door. I'm gonna take everything
in his front door. Would you like to recruit centaurs? 14 centaurs join your army. I didn't
mean that to be like a horse, but like, I mean, I'll take them. I had a spot for him. I'm right
outside of his door. I'm just waiting out here. All right, here comes a fight because you look
like you're coming over here. How are we doing? We're all right. We got enough at least for a
standoff here. Take it. I can't move anymore. I have to wait till next turn. Let's see what he does.
There he comes. He's going for it. He's coming with everything he has. This is his entire army.
He's pissed. We took his city and now he's like, fuck this. I'm coming with 300 centaurs.
Uh, all right. Death ripple. Curse bloodlust. Curse. Disrupting ray. I could do bloodlust or
just lightning bolt. Throw curse. Yeah. Curse the archers. Curse the archer. But they're gonna just
gonna fly in. I think he's gonna take the castle. Maybe not. Curse the archers so they don't do any
damage. And then I just gotta, I gotta sit in here. I can't go anywhere. I can't just jump out there.
No. That's too many centaurs. Hopefully at least the archers will take care of it.
Do I even have any ranged at all? I don't think I have any. Besides the towers. Well,
they're gonna make their way over here. I wish I could just throw an axe at you.
No. Hurts. Okay. No, this is ranged. This is ranged. It's an axe thrower. Ugh. I don't know.
Right, the front door. Try to just throw. Or should I go for the archer? This is gonna be,
it's not great. But once she gets in, she's gonna fly over the gate. Fuck. Come on. No.
The gates have been breached. This is bad. Gates are open. All right. It's time. I'm gonna go
bloodlust. Either bloodlust or earth magic. This is not the same person. This is a different person.
Different hero. Am I out of mana? No, that's not good. Can I do anything? I'm fucked.
Ah, I have to just go out and start fighting. Who do I want to try to take out first?
It's not completely over yet. Not yet. Really the only real major scary thing is this guy and this
guy. And the archers too. I gotta go in. It's 57 trees. Yeah, this is bad. Well, at least I put up
a defense. I'm gonna just gonna fly in and see if we can take out some of the centaurs. Damage
through health. I mean, these things are good. They're trying to kill the thunderbirds immediately.
I could probably take out a bunch of these though. There's so many of them.
Ah. I could fly up here and just go for the archers. But I can only fly this far. See if I can
make something happen. All right, you didn't like that. Holy shit. That was not good. All right.
Just get the fuck out here. Game over. Ah. I can't hurt... I can't do anything.
You got... You can't hurt everything. Might as well just whack this thing.
No. They don't stand a chance. Why do they have to piss purple off?
Well, I don't mind losing this because it's not like there's a lot here.
I can get it back. Plus, dude, I'm about to go destroy his whole... He's only gonna have one place.
He spends all of his money to get his revenge and that's fine. I could care less. I'm standing
outside his front door. I just bought this guy yesterday. See, look at this. Several few lots,
pack several, pack few. I think I can get in there. And then I have this down here and this
is definitely decked out. This place has to be. I got all the best spells in the game. Let's go for
it. Oh, that did a lot of damage. All right, here we go. Earth. Earth elemental or implosion.
Should I implode the dragon? I'm gonna fucking implode the dragon. Excuse me. Sorry, but I'm
about to kill at least two of you. That does so much damage and two of them have been removed.
That's how you can tell that this thing is fucking crazy. I'm all right with this, though. I got
a good... What's the damage on... I wonder if I should buff somebody. Let's just go in.
They don't do that much damage. 13 to 16, not worth it. Haste on the mage. What the hell are
you doing to me? Come on, come on out the front door. I'm gonna kill the dragon before you get
out of here. Fucking morale. Whatever. All right, beat him up. Punch him right in the face.
Go for the dragons? Or should I just remove the... Go for the dragon. Everybody. Everybody
focus on the dragons. I'm so glad these skeletons are just taking the damage here. They're just
eating this. Thank God. They ate that whole thing. All right, Genie. You gotta get one hit. That's
all I ask. Hit one time. One hit. Yes. The immediate threat is not the unicorn. I think it's... Is it
the unicorn? I don't know. Is it the... The Medusa's probably? Got it. All right, I gotta get the
gargoyles up front. You did... That was a big mistake. Front door not open. All right, let's
implode. There's more danger, I see. Let's see. Three to seven. Two to three. Let's... I'm just...
I'm gonna implode the archers. I have taken your castle. It's mine. With minimal loss. Overkill.
I wanted to like assert my dominance here. Genie should end this in one hit. Nimbus versus the
gold dragons. Didn't... I lost a bunch of skeletons, but here we go. Let's see how decked out this
place is. Holy shit. Hey, thanks. Thanks for like the decked out house. Castle. Fountain of Fortune.
Enchanted Springs. Unicorn glade. War unicorns. Yep. Yeah, thanks for the house. And thanks for the
new hero that I'm going to have that is going to be decked out. Who's it going to be?
Out Mr. Heretic. Probably the heretic. So I don't care if I lost that place. Basic pathfinding has
been found out. Chris's morale. Finally I get some more stuff to claim. Two wood a day. Thank God.
Now let's get another hero. The heretic. And let's at least recruit a bunch of these.
I have a gold dragon now. Pretty awesome. Where are we in the week? I have no money now.
Purple has holed up here. Look at this. Is that? No, that's my boat. I'm gonna say where's purple?
I think it's time to bring out the... Let me get some more money first.
Let's see where the purple has one remaining boat coming this way.
Hey. You motherfucker. I'm coming to take my castle back. No, you're not. In fact,
I'm going to hang out here because I'm stacking this place. A thousand experience. That's good.
Centaur stables. What does that lead to? Yeah, I'll take some centaurs. Check out the windmill.
All right. Let's just hang out over here. I got 12,000 gold. Let's get a bunch of stuff.
It's like imps kind of taking up space here. You know what? Here, I'll trade you next week.
Blue keeps on going back and forth to the dragon cave. What are you doing? Should I go over there
or should I not go over there? I don't know. Should I go? Should I stay? He's coming back.
I'm gonna have to wait for him here. He's gonna come back. I'm just gonna get some money.
Here he comes. Oh, wait a minute. He went the other way. Oh, fuck. I forgot about this castle.
He went the other direction. Oh, no. He got word from the scouts. They only got one person. Oh,
you fucking idiot. God damn it. You're dead, man. I completely fucking forgot. Oh, that sucks.
I just have to get a decent group together here. Come here. Let me give the...
Come here. That's his only force. He's just taking it all over the world. Okay. I want...
I'm sending you... Hold on. Let me look at this. You get out of here for a minute.
I need to look. Let's see. What's better? Send Nimbus home to restock. It just takes so long.
I'm on the other side of the world at this point. It's empty now. He just... He's leaving every
castle empty. I have like five castles and like four... The one he attacks is the one that doesn't
have fucking things in it. Everything else... Look it. Everywhere else has stuff. He's just hanging
out over here. You're a pain in my ass. Maybe we should just both go get him. Meet him on the open
field. Not yet. I need to like have the correct... Shit. I'm gonna recruit all these fucking people.
Here we go. All right. Bang. 93 centaur captains. That's really good. Let me see what you got on
you. You got like this... I'm just gonna send you to like your death. I definitely want the dragon
and the centaur captains. It's the imps. The imps are fucking this whole thing up.
All right. Come here. I'm dumping the imps. We're both going up there. You guys just stay here.
93 captains. Now what do we have here? Centaurs... I'm gonna trade him the centaur captains.
So he has 93 captains. 16 naga queens. Should I trade out the skeletons for the dragon?
Skeletons for the dragon or skeletons for the pegasus? I feel like I really want the pegasus
though. But what do I give up? The golems? Trinket's a good... Golems are a good wall
though. But now I have the centaur captains. Wait. Hold on. Let me look. Damage 2 to 3. Health 10,
12. I mean, not that much. They're not that great. It's not worth using a slot for one unit.
No, but I mean it's got 250 health. There are 93 centaur captains in here and they all have 10
health. You know what I mean? Like I need like two or three dragons and it's immune to spells.
There's 93 of them though. The archers too would be good. They have pretty good damage.
This is an unbelievable unit. This is an unbelievable unit.
The gargoyles probably for the trance. Does this... We need... We got range here.
Send in Kallad to soften them up. We're gonna go together. All right. Yeah. We're gonna send
in like this little imp first. He's gonna take out like four of them. He's gonna take out a bunch of
them and then I'm gonna... Like dad's gonna come in and clean it up. I think that's good as it is.
All right. Out of money. I'm ready for the actual purple battle because then these... Look at
they both these castles are empty. He's got nobody there. Not one person. Not one person.
He's just a riding castle. He's riding around with the castle on his back. It's time. Soften
him up. Let's go. Uh oh. Blue's coming in. Here we go. He's coming down here.
This is it for purple. It is because look it. Blue's coming in to take this free castle and
then this is it. Purple will be wiped out from the game. Purple is not going to exist anymore
after this. There's gonna be three people left. Do you have any of this shit? I don't think he
even has this. It's just fine to take one. Wait. Hold on. Do you have... All right. Just soften
them up. You'll be good. I'm going in. All right. I have like these these two booger enemies.
I'm gonna hang out back here just for a minute because like I... What if he doesn't... Somebody's
gonna come from the other side and take this castle. All right. There goes that one.
Wait. There's an energy elemental grove. Is that purple? What the fuck are you doing over here?
Where does purple have another castle? Down here? No. Impossible. All right. Go fucking go get him.
You're good. He's not gonna come back. Creeping up. Let's go. Blue is down. Brown has just been
in the top left. There's the taxes. Okay. You dick. Save the game. Go get him.
Purple does not have anything left. All right. Let's go. Charge. You want to go? It's time to go.
Hypnotize. Put an enemy unit temporarily under your control. I don't even have enough points
for this. Do you have any points? Ice bolt. Ice bolt on the archers. You just open the front door.
What a mistake. I'm going... Should I... I'm going in? This wasn't even worth doing. I can't soften
him up. He's got like about 500 people. It's because he's in the castle too. Damn it. You just...
Damn it. I need like a fucking... I need like a thousand people. I need more like range and...
I need a ton of archers. I need to stack ranged on somebody. Who do we have here? We have more units.
I got two more dragons. Okay. I got more dragons. More archers. I'm just gonna play
the turtle game for a minute here. Look at all this too. I gotta start to get this out here.
Delete the booger units. Yeah. I'm just... Get rid of these things. You guys suck. Get out of here.
Yeah. Goodbye. All right. Come back. Everybody back. Back it up. This way. Where does this go?
One-way entrance. What does that monolith exit end up? I can teleport? I have teleport?
Oh, this is all earth. Town portal. The nearest friendly town. The town must be unoccupied.
Oh my god. View earth. I mean... All right. Hold on. This is important. You... All right. I gotta...
Just... New turn. I gotta get everybody in buildings because I don't want to teleport you here
because you're right next to it. They exit to the one that's orange up here. Yeah, but that... I
don't want to be up here. All right. I gotta get a plan. The plan is I need to get you in this building.
Nobody attack me, please. Okay. You have to get in here. First of all, let's get this correct.
Three dragons. Sixty. Okay. I've got a little group of, like, idiots.
I'm gonna stack them all. So do I just... What do you have? Yeah. Bring them... Just bring them all
back. Bring them all back. Because I need to... Come here. There we go. 123, 19. Now you get the
fuck back in here like that. You're not... I know. I know. You must delete the skeletons.
All right. 44 arches. I just need to... I need to think about this for a second.
You've got... Pegasus are really good. Maybe trade the iron golems at this point.
So now I can teleport to the nearest town, which is here, I think. Because I get in here and I
remove this hero from the town, right? And actually, no, I don't want him to... I don't
want him to go here. There's nothing here worth taking. The nearest town is the one you're at.
Yeah, but it didn't say that... That as long as this town must be unoccupied,
teleport to the nearest friendly town, the town must be unoccupied. So if a town is occupied,
will it take me to the next one? That's not how it works. Will that work? Yeah, you just take
a hero out, right? So I want to go here because there's a lot... Yeah, I gotta get up here. Look
at all these recruits. All right, so first action of teleportation is this. We're going up here.
There's giants here too. There's... All right, I gotta fucking think about this shit. You... Okay.
Will you go into this town? This one is also occupied. They all are, right? Unoccupied,
occupied, occupied. Cast a spell. Town portal. Stop. Take the units out too. Okay, I'm out.
Spell. Town portal. Here we go. Save it. All right. Town portal. Here we go. What? Too tired. Oh,
he's coming down. He's ignoring me. Okay. Town portal. Do you want to teleport to the Emerald
Moor? Which one is that? No, I don't want to teleport here. God damn it. Do I actually have
to go all the way over here? That's... I have to actually travel that far? Shit. Put a hero in front
of the town. You mean like... Wait, what is this? One... Lot and lot. I could get it right now.
So you said what you're saying. If I go in here and I go like this...
Let's see what happens. Okay, so he's selected. Nearest town occupied. Spell failed. Yeah,
unfortunately. All right, I'm ready to start doing this shit again. Golems. I kind of want the
dragons, but I wonder if I just replace the dragons with golems. I got three of them now.
That's a lot of health. And then go up and take the town. Bring the archers with me probably too.
So I need archers. Who doesn't need to come on this trip? Leave the trance. Get the golems over
Pegasus. I think that I'll be able to get this town up there. Health 30. Health 35. Damage 345.
They're both really good. The unicorns are insane too. They only have so many slots. All right,
I'll keep this here for now. I'm going to go take that town back. Purple is going to turn around
and that's fine. Whatever. Get back up here. Now the question is, upgrade the tit- to get to titans.
Yes, I can now have titans. I have lots to recruit. This is Swiss Silverwing. Silverwing is down
there. Okay, so I'm going to recruit a bunch of stuff. I can only do that many. You just go back
in here because like there's no reason for you to be out here anymore. Go up there. There's a titan.
You can just take the iron golems. You're going to be just hanging out here anyways.
Titan has ranged attacks. Yeah, and I'm going to upgrade the other ones that I have too.
I cannot. I'm out of mine. Just hang out there for now. Okay, everybody relax. Let's go. Okay,
you are down here now. Where are you going? Uh oh. This city sucks. The city is going to fall. It
just has like 200 little trolls. Maybe he's not going to come that far. It's going to take him a
couple turns. He's not going to take this one. That's for sure. All right, give me back my
fucking town, please. How much can I make more recruits? No, stop, stop. Two titans. Yeah,
you're not going to take this. He ain't going to make it. Here comes Brown, finally.
Brown's making his way over here now. Give me this. What do you got? You don't got anything here.
Let's go. Give me it back. All right, dragon. Go in here and instantly kill them. Thank you.
Stone skin. 111 dead. Done in a second. Just cast a lightning bolt.
Just wait. Give me my castle back. Expert offense or advanced learning. Expert offense, I think.
30%. My home. I got it back. Okay, this is where we're going to leave. First, let's walk in there.
That'd be nice. Archers are going up. Centaurs are going up. When's the new week? It's coming up.
Dragons are staying. Staying, staying, staying, staying. The reason why I'm doing this is because
I want to just feed a ton of these units into here. What's the building? What's the town hall?
Treasury. 10% interest in gold through green dragons. Everything else is enchanted. Let's
do this just to get it. New week is coming up. We get taxes coming in. End of the stream. What
are you talking about? All right, so they're in there. You're here. We got enough. We got more
stuff to recruit. Just keep dumping. 68. More money. I keep forgetting to do that first.
Let him in. Let him in. Please let me in there at the front door.
He's coming over here. I only have like three RC cars. Please, they're gonna kill me.
It'll be fine. There's nobody even on here. It's this guy. He's not gonna make it. That's
more than a full turn. He ain't gonna make it. We got a new week. Let's go. Somebody got killed.
Brown just killed somebody. Okay, here he comes. All right. 12,000. Let's upgrade these giants.
God, that's so expensive. I have five of them. I need more money. Camp him in the city.
All right. What about the... okay. Wizards. Uh, other wizards. 68, 48, 18, 27, 19, 18,
40. Okay, this is pretty good. I can't buy anything else. I don't have any money.
All I can do now is hope and pray because now I can go. But let's see. What we got down here?
We've got a bunch of... we got so many units to buy. There's so many that it's... I'm getting
overwhelmed by the amount of units that I can purchase. I need another day to go by.
I have a lot of sulfur though. Can I get a good exchange on sulfur? Not really. That's a pretty
bad exchange. Although I can... I mean, I could... I think it's time to take you. I gotta make the
journey back. I can get two more dragons. I think five dragons. Here's the plan. Five dragons?
Yeah, he's just like running back and forth like on a route. Yeah, I'm gonna get you two more
dragons. Because it's a new week, I'm gonna get five gold dragons and now I'm just gonna get some
money. I'm protected at least enough where no one's gonna kill me. I'm protected completely.
Here he comes. Stupid fucking taxes. There he is. Here he comes. He's coming in. I gotta be ready.
He's coming in. This is my... guys, this is the main city. So if this falls, it's gonna be really
sad. What do I need for this? I need the library. I don't have a fucking library. Why did I not
build a library? Seven titans. Seven goddamn titans. Am I gonna lose with seven titans?
He didn't have like... I have seven fucking titans. I feel like I've just been playing against purple
this whole game while the other two just build up their resources forever. Just give me my damn
dragon. Here we go. If we lose, we lose. Whatever. Here he comes. Okay, this is it. I got like mines
and shit. Let's go. What do we got? Wizard. Buff the titan. We're good for spells. Force field.
Animate the dead. Destroy undead. Lightning bolt. How much do I have any points? 80 points versus
50. That's so many, but I can do it. I'm thinking put a curse on their archer or a curse on their
pegasus. The pegasus is gonna fly right over. My pegasus has to die. Okay, curse on the archer.
And then I'm gonna buff... I'm gonna buff the titan. All in on titan. Here we go. Yes! Okay,
that's... for being that far away, that's very, very good. That is exceptionally good. I ain't
moving anybody. Step on the mine. Idiot. How many archers are here? I can't tell. This is gonna be
all in on titan. No, don't move. Let them hurt themselves. That hurts so much. That hurts so
much. That sucked. Do I stand at the front door? I think I have to stand at the front door. They're
gonna kill them. They can't get in yet, but I'm gonna get at the front door. I'm going right here.
Okay, now it's the... the magi. I just gotta go for the archers. 29. How many treants? 70 fucking
three treants. 73! I'm never gonna kill 73 of these. Who's up? Genie. Titan. All in.
Cross the map. No. Holy shit, that was fucking insane. I just killed a hundred. I killed almost
one fucking hundred of them. All right, all in on titan. That's all that matters. I wonder,
do I fly you out here just to be a pain in the ass? Or not yet. I think I'm gonna curse the...
I'm gonna curse the pegasus because this next turn she's flying over. She's gonna fly over
this next turn. Fly the gargoyle over the archers? Yeah. Let's go on. Force field. I don't know. I'm
scared. What does the force field do? I've never used it. I'm gonna play... I'm gonna do Stuart
Smart. Here we go. These two are now worthless. Now I'm going in. This is it. These are my two
strongest units. It's fine. Pegasus is gonna be dead. Almost left. Nine pegasus die. Yep,
that was a good distraction. I'm okay with this. He's not coming in now.
Oh shit, he's in. Not the genie! This is bad. Destroy Undead. I'll give it a try.
How many are left? I can't tell. Is it five? I can only shoot. Like, the... No, no, what are you doing?
I thought it was gonna... What? I thought it was a range. It's all in on the goddamn titan. It's
still possible. Destroy Undead. It fucking barely did shit. All in on titan. How many are fucking
left? What? Oh my god, there's too many of them. There's so many of them. Are you trying to tell
me that seven fucking upgraded titans cannot kill a fucking pegasus? Are you... Eat my fucking...
Ah! I'm actually upset right now. There's only 15 of you. Get over here. Don't step on a landmine.
Come on, titan. I know you can do this. I'm fucking certain you can do it. You can do it. You
can do it. Stay alive. Stay alive. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it.
Bleh! No! This is just too fucking goddamn. I lost everything. The army was just so enormous.
Whatever. We have a new home now. God damn it. I mean, I've got like five fucking thousand enemies.
Fuck! Who do I have down here? Who's even up here? I gotta go... Okay, I've gotta bring you up here.
Grab this shit. Let me go in here. I need... I'm going to get... I can get five... It doesn't
matter how many dragons I have. Gold dragons. Five gold dragons. Could I go up there and kill
them now that it's softened? I don't know. I mean, it's... Look, it's gonna take me fucking like
a week to get back over there. There's nothing in there. He just... He's just running around.
This dude just put a thousand people on one guy and has just been walking around in circles.
That's what I should have done from the very beginning. I shouldn't even have bought any more
houses. Yeah, he has access to make titans now. Why would I even take like Elsa's castle for any
reason? Just put five thousand people on one guy. What was I thinking? He's going to come take this
now. I can't even upgrade this. I don't have any money. What was I thinking? Well, I can teleport
if I teleport. I can only teleport here. We've tested that like three times.
I mean, I could just try to go and retake it. What's up there? All right, I'm taking the
captains. I'm taking the archers. We're going to get some more. I'm going to get... Pegasus,
let's just put everybody on here. I'm going to go through and recruit. So when I... On the way back
up, I'll fill this up. I probably should leave... What are these? Health 20. No, these are better.
I just need money. I just need money. Like, very, very badly. Like, so bad. All right,
well, here comes another one. All right, 8,000 golds all I have.
That's just not enough. There are like 100... I guess I could get like 70 archers and like
180, 200-something centaurs. Who sent out you a page to Melee? I didn't mean to,
because that would mean I have... Let's see. This is just a lost cause here at this point,
that one. Go through the red portal and just use the town portal. Yeah, but if I go through
the red portal, I just end up right here. Oh, do I end up here? Which one do I go through?
And then use the town portal to get to like here, but then I still have to go all the way across
here if I want to take it. I want to stop here and grab that furry because, I mean, I don't have
enough enemies. I definitely don't have enough to take that on, because I can't take any of
this shit. So I'm just going to go with this. I'm going to go recruit and see if I can get
anything done. Because there's a ton up here. No, no, just give me the... give me archers.
Give me these, because that's a lot of archers to have. How many pegasus do I have on this guy?
Pegasus and unicorns. All right, yeah, just... I'm making a pit stop
right up here. And then I'm gonna walk up here. Go through the portal? Well, if I go through the
portal, I'm gonna have to teleport back to here anyways. I'm going up here. This will put me at
at least 100 plus. What do I have for points right now? Again, I'm maxed out. That's good.
Back up again to recruit more. Just keep time going. No, no, go in the building.
Oh, for the love of god. All right, this is this is where we do it. So I'm gonna report right change
out. Maybe the mages? No, I need that. They're ranged too. 29. I don't have that. I can't upgrade
those. Can I upgrade these? I can make this a capital. And all right, so that's 141. 29 pegasus.
16 queens. Five gold dragons. Who do we leave behind here? Or do we just
stack the ranged instead of the golems? Because there's a lot. There's a decent amount here.
Maybe the genies. 18 to 22. 110 versus like just not enough of them. Yeah, they're too high value.
I think I could probably get away with this and then make another person here.
I'm gonna try with this. I think this is good. Maybe I'll, yeah. I do need more range. I need
more like just picking people off. That means one, two. Yeah, 141 centaurs. All right. This is,
this is like the last hurrah here. If I can't make this done, I think this is gonna be good.
Like, this is it. I'm going for it. Give me a damn boat. I'm going back. I'm not. I mean,
this is free, but I don't want it. Look at all this. Get in the boat. I'm going up here.
I'm not close enough to summon one yet. I'm going back to take my home back.
There you are. Are you gonna meet me out on the open field? Is this what this is?
Lots hoard. Several. He, look, he kind of replaced all his shit. Did he leave anything in here?
He kind of didn't. He, I think he may have spread himself out a little too much.
No, that's Luna. What happened to Ares? He stole my shit. And here he comes for this one. I'm
fucked. I am so fucked. Teleport home. I'll end up over here. This'll be, this is the closest one.
He's just in here. See what happened was early. I just was learning how to play the game again
and I like bled myself out so hard. This is going to be really hard to come back. I think
I'm going to go for it though. We'll try. Uh, summon boat. I'm going to go for it.
Whatever. It's like a thousand gold. Just give me a damn boat.
Here they come. Coming to take my castle. They're just going to take it. There's nothing I can do
about it. I'm so far behind at this point that if this, I, I'm going to be screwed. What can I do?
Um, magic arrow. Let's try to kill some centaurs. That's really all I can do.
Where did they get in? Oh, this is already broken. Fuck. Fight to the very end. Um, yeah, that was,
that person just killed a hundred, almost two hundred. Yeah, this is unbeatable.
Can I shoot it up like myself? Just take it. Take it. Run around in a circle with you. A
five million. Why would you do that? That was BM. I just got fucking BM. That just got roped in
Hearthstone. Oh, thanks. I had a shot there like an hour ago. Oh, it's like six hours. I fucking had
it too. And they're both up here. I'm screwed. You're using my own men against me. I meet you
on the open field. I could probably take you. Is there nobody? I can do it. I could probably take
God damn it. I have to do another goddamn fucking turn. I need to take out the other person down
here and let go this way. This only, the only way this works is if like somebody else is doing shit
down here and I like, I have to wrap around. I have to. This is, this is not, that's not a bad
crew here. Although I probably would rather have, now this is all right because there's a bunch of
territory over here. I'm going to go this way. No one's coming down here. Give me this shit back.
It's mine. Come and get me. And over here. Let's go Seer's Hut. Halflings and Trolls. I don't have
that. I'm sorry. Take the Mercury. You take back our city please. You can get it. Really just stacked
it up. You knew I was coming. Pack lots, few, few, several, several lots. I can do it and I'm taking
my fucking home back in and I'm gonna fucking upgrade everybody. I have a lot. This is a really
like decent, I got Dragons. It's coming back down. All right. Lots of those mages. Several few. He's
got Titans. Give me back my fucking house. It's mine. Give it to me. Let's do it. Implode. Implode
on that Titan. Fly. Should I fly the fucking dragon in? These are my Titans. Dragons should just
completely just obliterate the uh probably the Titan. Who are these mages? How many mages do
they have? 32 of these mages back here. Obliterate mages? Yeah not yet. Not yet. I can't buff the
dragon. Why not? Oh Immune Dispel is right. Okay. Kill the genies. Titan's dead. Titan's down. Genie
next. Genies. Almost dead. I'm going in. I'm flying in. Taking out the elders. Both genies. Elders.
Get in there. Elders dead. I get to go twice. Genie dead. Dragon. Obliterate. Genie. Buff. Pegasus.
Pegasus. Attack. Take. I got my house back. I've got my home back. My home is returned to me. I
get it back and then I'm going to stack and I'm going hunting. Come on out here. I only lost a few
people. Archers. Some Pegasi. Give me my goddamn house back. All right. Back in business. Artifact
merchant. Too bad. I have no growth here. This thing. He already used it. Now the question is
let's keep looking over here. I got that already. This way. Now I start. This is where the stack
begins. I'm gonna stack genies and mages by the way. I got elders now. Just get in here and hang
up. This is where this is redemption here. Uh hold on. I want to pick that up. Give me this.
All right. Here we go. He's coming back. He's coming back. He's saying to himself, oh how dare
you horde horde lots pack horde pack. He's coming back. Open field. Can I take him in an open field?
What do you think? Back. Back. Back. Into the castle. Into the castle. I'm just tracking horde
dead. On an open field dead. Oh fuck. Uh I'm I don't know what to do. I'm freaking out. All right.
Morale increase. Witch hut. You just slowly acquire stuff. Stables. Hut of the Magi.
He tells you places near and far. We're gonna get some more reveal on the maps. We already did it.
Bring in the breastplate stretcher. So I don't know what that is. The breastplate stretcher. I
I'm fucking getting tired. I'm ready. I'm I'm kind of scared because okay I'm gonna tell you
something. If I lose here. If Cinderella's castle goes down. I'm fucked. I'm not gonna be able to
win this game. This is it. He's coming for me. This is the battle. I can't recruit anybody.
There's nothing else to do. I can do mage guild level five. No. Let him come. Let him come. Let
him come. Level five. Air elemental. Water elemental. Berserk. The targeted unit will randomly attack
the nearest unit be it friend or foe. Oh that's fucking pretty great. He would put your life
savings on Ares. Mistake. He's coming in. We'll see. He's pissed. Bring it on. No he gave up.
I'm going after him. I'm just I'm just fucking gonna go after him. No I'm not. I'm taking my
castle back. Stupid. You want to meet in the fucking open field? I'll do it. What do you think? I'll
wait right here for you. Oh shit. Oops. What is this? Refugee camp? Where's he going? He
went by me. I'm fucking gonna kill him. Imp growth. Familiar growth. All dwellings increase.
They're on an open field. Let's go. Dragon. This is why I want to do it in an open field. Obliterate
immediately. Who's the biggest threat? Five dragons. No no no. Implode. Implode. Fucking
instantly kill. Destroy. Implode. Implode on the naga queens. Berserk on the naga queen.
Berserk on the naga queen. You're all dead. Dragon. Obliterate elders. Straight ahead. Pegasus.
Um I'm gonna go up here. Just to stay away from the uh the naga queen. What the heck way? I can do
this though. Why can I buff? I couldn't buff him before. I'm gonna buff the archers. Down my way.
This is the revenge arc. I'm fucking pissed. First it's purple and then it's blue.
What do I do here? Naga queen. Beautiful. Bye. I win. Didn't lose anybody. Everyone's alive.
See you later. What was that Ares? Do you want to come up here? Do you have something you want to
say? You good? What was this? Star Axis. Plus one spell power. Take this back. Not yet. I'm good. I'm
going for my fucking town again. I'm gonna claim all the resources. I was so. I was pissed. I was
pissed. That's how you knew it was time to go. You know what I'm saying? That's how you just. I was.
It's time to go. I'm sorry. Did I. I'm sorry Romeo. Did I kill Juliet? Come back. I'm waiting for you
right here. He's. Holy shit. He's mad. Tan has been vanquished. Wait. What? Tan's dead. How?
Who killed Tan? Tan's dead. Plus one defense. Who wiped off Tan during this whole thing? Orange?
So it's orange, blue, purple's about to be done. This is purple's last stronghold. Ares is running
away. I'm gonna have control. Wait. Where are you going? You sailing over here. You motherfucker.
That's fine. I got my guy down here. I gotta. I gotta claim all this shit back. Give me my sulfur
factory. Give me. All right. Get back. Get back. Get back. Get back. He's coming. He's coming. He's
coming. He's coming. Blue has the dragons. It don't matter. I'll have ten. I will. I will
destroy him. Which way is he going? I think he's. Let's just see where he goes. And then I'm. I'm
gonna have another. I can recruit. I will. Hold on. Hold on a second. Let me just see where this guy's
going. He's coming over here. Okay. You're going for it, aren't you? He's going for it. He's going
for it. He's going for it. He really wants it. Can I teleport from here to there? Check this shit out.
You are fucking dead. I cannot wait to do this. Am I close enough to this one? This was. This is. This
is uh. Marishen. Uh. There's nobody in here. Except for me. Hi. I'll take some more of these,
please. Did you. Were you coming over here? Were you. You like on your way over here?
That's fine, man. In an open field. Thank god I found that fucking artifact. Time to die.
Oh my god. He has 19 bone dragons. Oh my god. That's a lot. He has 20 bone dragons.
All right. I'm gonna frenzy bloodlust on that. Will it work? Was. Will Berserk work on you?
Are you immune to spells? Berserk. Oh. We gotta go in hard. I got five to the liches here.
Go in. I gotta go in hard immediately. Who the Pegasus going for? This is very important.
Vampires? Oh. Genie? You know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna move these guys up a little bit.
Oh no. That's just a super buff. Holy fuck. I blamed the fucking spell in the beginning.
Oh my god. No. It was a spell in the beginning. It was a spell in the beginning. It ruined
everything. He is destroying me. The spell in the beginning ruined everything. I could have given it
to the anybody else. How did you get 20 of these? How did you get 20 bone dragons? You have
no castles. He doesn't even have a castle. How do you get 20 of these? It's like 500,000 gold.
He's got no land. He's got no money. How many liches? 30? At this point, I'm just screwed.
We gotta just go. We gotta try to wipe some out. We gotta try to hurt something. Holy shit, man.
You gotta be kidding me. 20 fucking goddamn bone dragons. Did you find these? I had like a
million gold lying around somewhere in a hole somewhere. I buried it. I lose. The only way
it's as possible is if I can berserk like somebody over here. I berserk, right? On...
I don't know. Who can I even do this to? The unicorns? The trees? See if that works.
And then I'm gonna try to buff. I don't fucking know. I don't have anybody left to do this to.
Archers? I think he's cleansed everybody. One of the fucking dragons. That's a horse. That's dog
shit. That is impossible. I just saw this guy like a week ago and you didn't have 19 bone dragons.
I'm dead. 150 health each. Fucking 25 to 50 damage. I really thought I was gonna win this one.
Fuck. I can't even. That's unfucking believable. I was like so confident to pack a bone dragon.
Shove those bone dragons up your ass. You fucking dick. I don't even know if this is winnable.
Maybe I shouldn't even go after him. I'm not sure I can even do this.
Let me try one thing. Let's see. Hold on. Okay. I'm talking about potentially. What about like an
elemental? A berserk implosion. This does 577 damage. I could implode the dragon which would
take like five or six of them away. Maybe like four? Five? Three. All right. It's very clear
that the dragons have to die. So what? Okay. 150, 2550, 250, 40 to 50. I might just do dragon to
dragon here. I'm gonna die but maybe I should hold back. No. The dragon's gonna fly over here.
If I leave him. I mean I'm gonna sacrifice this dragon right now essentially. Five versus 16. They
have more HP but I mean maybe I'll really kill a couple. Let's just see what happens. 16, 13,
four. All right. This is not a bad strategy so far. I'm gonna berserk this guy right here probably
or this one. I'm not going anywhere yet. Berserk the trident probably then. Undead spell. Well the
last time I did undead spell it only killed one person. Remember I tried it already and it only
killed like it only took away one person. It affects everybody. We'll see. Let me try it.
Um I don't think I want to go in with anybody right now but what's the what's the play here?
I wonder. I'm not sure I go in. They're gonna attack the dragon but I could go after the uh
the unicorns. 110, 18, 22. Let's see if I. I'm just going in for the vampires.
It sounds like clan. 57, 48. All right now I've got the genie. The genie should really buff up
the ranged. That sucks. I need to be. Well let's just do this. Frenzy. Good. I'm just gonna move up.
Of course you do that. No dude. No. No way. No way. I have to berserk somebody at the very beginning.
Otherwise this is. I will never win this in a million years.
Somebody has to get berserked immediately. Let's see what I can do here.
It could be possible if I berserk somebody right at the start. Let's see. Let me try it now.
Let me put because this might be a wash. Let's do the undead thing.
Destroy undead. I don't think it killed anybody. Nobody died. So everybody's saying I had to do
that. I hope you see what happened. These guys are actually the bad. I wonder if I berserk.
Let me see who I can even berserk because I'll try that at the beginning. This is too much.
What level is this hero? Destroyed. All right. God damn it. He's so powerful. It's not fair how
powerful you are. You shouldn't be this powerful. Okay. Berserk the tree. I can berserk the unicorn
or I can berserk the treant. Nobody else can be berserked. The trees will last a lot longer but
the unicorn might do more. Let's try the unicorn. It worked. All right. Now. Now I'm going for the
dragon. Unicorn's also going to go for the dragon. Or do I just not move? Just nobody move?
Should I buff him? Nobody move. Everybody just sit here. Did he cleanse it? No. No, this is no way.
This is impossible. There's only one way this is possible and I need to get like 25 dragons.
This is unwinnable. I have to just turtle for five weeks. It's not doable. I got it. I was so
overconfident too. That's the worst part about this. He's going to get this town again.
All right. I need a dragon. We're going to meet in the middle here. We're going to do a dragon trade.
What do I have? I have five dragons. Honestly, I need to like maybe I could win from the castle.
No, because the dragon can just fly over it. How many dragons can I have here now? There's two there.
I have two that can be recruited. Two on him. So two, four. I'll have like nine dragons.
Get some more archers. Get more of these. More pegasus. Do I not have the upgraded ones?
I could get more of these too. Just get them just to get them. Okay. So I have two more dragons.
If he's going to take this. What do I do with the guys that are here right now?
You're just going to. I mean, I may as well. I'm so screwed. I'm just going to have to go back
down here and just get more. Admit defeat? Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. I'm not done yet. I still
have plenty of property. I just need to get to the right spot. I can trade some units here.
I have a lot of this guy can just be like a good unit trader. I've conquered all this over here.
He's going to go take the castle. Whatever. Take it. I don't care. There he goes. He'll get it.
Whatever. Nineteen bone dragons. I saw you like less than two weeks ago. Motherfucker. I can't
believe. Well, I could do. This is a good opportunity to just. Maybe I can wipe up some
unicorns. What level are you? The computer just like gave him all this random shit. He didn't do
anything for this. He just. They gave him to him. Well, here's the thing. He might leave some of
these here, which is a good thing. Maybe I can. I might be just. Maybe I'll just be able to turn
around. You know, you like leave the vampires and the fucking. Okay. Whatever. What do you leave
there? All right. He left some. He left a bunch of shit here. He left the unicorns. He left his
trance. No, he still has so many. Not worth it. Stick with the plan. Stick to the plan. Come here.
Seven dragons. More centaurs. I need to upgrade these pegasuses. Do I not have it? Can I? I
waste my treasure reef. Silver pegasi. There it is. I want to upgrade these too. I need to upgrade
the archers. I'm going to just sit down here and fucking turtle. He's blocked off the path of escape.
Well, this is my final stand. If I'm dead, then I'm dead. And it was really fun. This game's fucking
awesome. So if this is it, this is it. If he's like, he's like fucking coming down here to kill me,
then that's it. And I'll have to just say, well, what do you know? Oh well. No, here he comes.
He's coming down here. He's coming to get us. We have to everybody. I'm parking him in the front.
Yeah. I'm going to be inside. And then this, uh, Kalad guy is going to be standing at the front door.
Okay. Nine dragons, 116 archers, 293 centaurs, 58, 16, 38. Like this is, this is so ridiculous.
Like I have to be able to put up a defense. The genies instead of, I need genies instead of the
dwarfs. You could recruit heroes across the map and start a new era and conquer the other dudes.
Yeah. But I have like a personal vendetta right now. Can anything else be upgraded?
Treasury, 10% interest, fortune, luck of the garrison and the hero by two. Let's do it.
They're coming in. So let's trade with you. You can take the dwarfs. I will take the pegasus. I
will take these. Okay. Go back in there. Unicorns. Okay. Now I think he's back to you. Okay. Get back
in here. Get up here. Hold on. I need to like switch this out. This is such a joke. I can't
believe I'm doing this. All right. Well, here we go. I've got, this is my army. He's going to be
outside 119. This is just, he's just here. I also have this still, but it's the only other thing I
got. Park yourself in here. Almost 10 dragons. So I have so many people. Like I just got to stay
behind the walls and just try to fight. Can you put both in the castle? I don't think you can.
I mean, no, he could just stand right outside the door. Okay. Here comes our inevitable defeat.
Let him in the castle and then run away with the teleport spell. But then I would just go all the
way back and it repeats again. And then I just have to go like, what's even blue doing? This is
orange is only place. I don't think this guy's moved. Has orange moved the whole, I don't think
he can leave. He can't even leave. He's just over here. God damn it. Well, whatever. It was, it was
fun. Let's see what happens. Red is still a player. Here he comes. Okay. There he goes. Three. I got
one Titan here. It's possible that I could make it to week seven. Look at all the purple. Purple
had nothing. Like a week ago. And now all of a sudden you have everything. Did you just do
something over here? Like tan died and you picked up all the houses for free. I already know what
that did. It's inevitable. Maybe he'll go this way and I can buy a few more dragons. I want to
like start over the scenario. Here comes the other guy. Oh, this is, this is the, this is,
it's over. This is my other stronghold. I'm about to be wiped out. I'm actually about to
be completely removed from the game. Quick kill the king. Throw a bolt at the king's head.
I've been restarting my scenario because I suck at this game. Oh man. I mean, it's, it's a pretty,
it's not, the game's not necessarily easy. That is a lot of fun though. How do they have these units?
I don't know. He came into a fucking like trust or something. Somehow he, maybe when he, you know
what might've happened? So you know I said tan was defeated. He may have just stumbled upon tan's
last building and then took all of tan's money because tan, I figured it out. This is what happened.
So tan wasn't doing anything all game. It was just stockpiling money and stockpiling resources.
So he took over tan because tan was just a fucking moron. It was like walking in circles.
And took all of his money and all of his stuff like Monopoly style and then just built like
30 dragons. I think that's what happened. I think, like that was fucking absurd.
Why didn't I do that? I mean this is my first game coming back from, you know, a while. Purple.
I can feel, yes! Okay. My last stand is now higher. I can get more dragons. 10 dragons.
That's all I can afford. Wait, I can sell all my resources. Okay, hold on. Okay, I want money.
I'm willing to give you this. Wow, this is bad. No, I need those. What do I need for dragon?
Crystals. I need two crystals. I have two crystals. It's time to like, I'm liquidating.
No, no. Get, here. I'm gonna liquidate my entire, uh, yeah. It's liquidation time. This is it.
He's knocking on my front door. I'm the last remaining Monopoly player. 40. Sell gold for
gold. What? Wood. Look at how bad of a trade-off this is. I'm the last remaining fucking Monopoly
player. I'm gonna at least give a go out with a bang. 11 dragons. 88. I have fucking 323 of
these. That has to be worth something. No more money. Liquidate everything else. Just liquidate
everything. I have to. It's over. This is the end. If I win, then I beat the, I beat the hardest
fucking guy on the map. We'll see. What can I buy? Treants, probably. It's probably better.
Yep. That's it. I have 100 bucks. I have 101 dollars. Good luck, everybody. This is our final
stand. Here we go. Blue and red have just been fighting. This is what happens in these games.
And here it comes. And he walked by us. He's just toying with me. I have zero resources. I have
nothing. Just come over here and fight me. Engage him. Fight the open battle with this guy. This is
gonna be embarrassingly awful. If I can kill. You wanna know what the plan here is? You wanna know
exactly what I'm doing? The plan is, try to at least get rid of one or two bone dragons. That's
it. I can't even cast these. You guys level one. I like fucked it up from the very beginning.
It's alright though. Like, it's the first time I've played in a while. You know,
sometimes you just gotta learn. This is a seven hour learning experience. Good. Come over here.
Send in the dwarves. All I care about is just hurting this dragon. Kill one. Yes. Okay, he got
one. Try to get a couple more. Just try. Get this down to like 15. And then I got like 11 dragons.
Fine, come up here. Ooh, that's pretty good. 17. It's getting... did a good job. I just realized
that was a hare. Is that hare? That's alright. He lost two dragons. This is a castle, right? Yes.
Okay. I just was making sure. It's time. Can we hold this off? I ain't coming out. No, no, he sent
it in his shitty. It's her again. They're like, look at, they're just like, they're just so fun
together. This is my final castle. Come on. Bring it. Do it. Do it. End me. End my misery.
I'm getting out. Let's go. I'm killing her. You're fucking dead. And this time I'm killing her. You
know what I mean? Like, if there's one thing I'm going to do, I'm going to make sure, I'm going to
make sure that she's dead. Going for the fucking dwarves immediately. Instakill. No. You know what?
Fucking... what do I want to do here? This is going to be embarrassing. It is going to be awful.
Just inferno. No, I don't want to spend that many points. I don't even need to do that. The dragon
will kill them all in one hit. Don't let her run. Let's kill the archers and then buff. Don't not
retreat. Please let me just have one victory. Let me like kill your wife or your friend.
Dead. Now we can turn around. I got you. I got your feet. Warn on the feet. This item increases
your knowledge and power by plus one. Leveled up. More damage sorcery. What are you gonna say
about that? Huh? What are you gonna do about it? What are you gonna do about it? A whole lot of
nothing. Is it on? I put it on. I'm out though. Maybe now he's gonna turn around. No, he's not
turning around yet. He's leaving. No. Why are you leaving? Don't do this to me. Fuck. I'm just,
am I gonna, you know what? I got a better idea. I'm abandoning my home next week.
God damn it. What do I do? I just, I thought that was gonna be it. Um, I'm gonna go kill Orange.
Orange is dead. Watch this shit. You ready? I'm gonna, I'm gonna wipe out Orange right now.
I think I can do it. And I'm gonna take all of his money. Let's get in there.
We're going for, if I can't kill Purple, I'm going for Orange. Berserk. Berserk on the manticores.
I'm gonna win. I'm gonna take this castle. And I'm gonna sit here for fucking a year.
Just you wait. Just get the dragon in now. Everybody get in. Get in now. Everybody get in.
Don't give him a second. Buff. Manticore. Oh, what's that? Now you're gonna fight the dragon, huh?
Dead. Good, they're killing each other. Thank god. Okay. How many dragons do I have left? Get
them up here. Archers to, who's that? I can't see who's up here. The minotaurs. Or the, who's left?
Or maybe the, um, Medusas, yeah. I can't get in though. That door's gonna open.
Give me all his money. What do we think? Maybe I should kill the Medusas or should I go right
for the minotaur? Minotaur. 12 minotaurs dead. I'm gonna berserk somebody else. Berserk on the,
I wonder who I should do this to. Probably the manticore again. Or on the minotaurs. They
haven't attacked yet. Or on the lich? I can't. He's undead. I can't. You can't do it on undead.
Maybe the Medusas. Or maybe the Harpies and they'll fly over and just kill themselves.
Or, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm gonna, I'm gonna implode. I'm just gonna obliterate completely.
Always implode. Implosion on, um, on the manticore. Just melt them. There we go. Okay, great. Good,
good, good. Minotaur, attack. Six minotaurs dead. I just burnt my own people. I got this. I'm gonna
win. Okay, I get to go again. Do it twice. I can't get in there. I can't go anywhere. Get the dragon
out. He's, I can't. How many dragons? Five? Versus five? No, kill him. I can do it. Okay, I'm gonna
get him out. Bad move. No, you can go back. Okay, hold on. Kill the minotaurs. Where's resurrect?
Resurrection. I can't do it to the dragon. I'm gonna implode again. I can't do it to anybody.
I should have left the fucking dragon in. I should have left the dragon inside. How many
left? Five? There's only one more minotaur left. Kill it. I can't even get in here.
I got this. I'm gonna win. All right, it's open. Dragon to manticore. This manticore has to die.
How many points left? 69 points. Implode. It's all right. The dragon's fine because everything's
fine. I can't move. I have to kill this manticore right now with my dragon. These walls have to
collapse. Manticore. Got it. I win. I have to win. I win. Go in with the genie.
I get the dragon still in here. I can't get in, unfortunately. There's nothing I can do.
Burn. 29 harpies dead. 22 harpies dead. That's so close, but the others can't do anything.
Implode. I don't have any more points. I only have four. Magic arrow. I'm gonna take it.
Hopefully this is all of orange. 15, 1, game over. Ah, fuck. He's too big. I got
17,000 experience. Oh my god. I got torso of legion and spell scroll. This item when
equipped by a hero in a town increases the growth of your fourth level units by three per week.
And this scroll contains the dimension door spell, which is added into your spell book for as long
as you carry the scroll. More experience. Yeah. Expert sorcery. 15% more damage. Yes.
Orange has been vanquished. I killed him. He was stuck here. What did I get? Did I get anything?
I killed orange. He was just sitting here. What do I get for killing orange? I beat him. I won.
I did it. I killed orange. I don't get anything. Uh, 224 skeletons. I still have this house. Who's
in here? There's nobody here. Uh, now what? Orange's gone. Tana's gone. Now I'm the new orange.
Oh, I see. Because I can't leave. That's why he was up here for so long. Because he ran out of places.
So he didn't have another castle and he was stuck here.
That's fucking hilarious. So I actually just went up here for no reason because orange didn't give
me anything for losing. And he was actually just stuck here for eternity. All right. What's the
spell? Let's see what it is. Visions. Uh, what was it called? The dimension something. I think it
has to be my inventory. Oh, let's just put it on. So it's on. So what is it called?
Dimension door. Once per day, you may teleport your hero to a visible unoccupied location on
the map. Hey, was it worth it? You tell me at this point, because I, um, I absolutely would not have
gotten the dimension door. Rolled up your fourth level units by three per week. Here's your eagle
eye skill. I feel like, I don't, I feel like this is much better. What eagle eye skill by 10%.
I'll put this on. I want more growth or extra spell points per day. This is really good. This
is really good. That's really good. All right. As the new orange, I'm going to turtle here.
This training is going to be like fucking very long. What do we have in here? Man of vortex.
I don't have any resources though, guys. This place sucks. How the fuck did you not upgrade any of
this? You were sitting here for like three months. You didn't upgrade anything. What an idiot. So
I'm just going to teleport and take stuff and teleport back. Finally something worthy. I shall
send word immediately to the border guard that you'll be allowed to pass. Okay. All right. So
I'm going to take this dickhead and we're going to go resource hunting. That's all you are for
is just to get resources. Even as a one a day, you can just kind of chill in the tent. No, wait a
minute. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I can teleport. I'm going to teleport over here. Oh my God. Fuck.
13, not enough. All right. Just, I'm going to look at all this shit that purple has now.
This is not, I'll never win. Look at the map. I don't even know what's over here.
Purple has everything. He's got like a bunch of, look at all the, his heroes now.
He's got like five heroes. All of them have dragons.
A lot, lots of bone dragons. It's not a pack anymore. There's probably 30 dragons there now.
I will, there's no way I can win this. I mean, okay. You remember World of Warcraft 3,
how you would play that person online, that you would wipe them out and you'd be clearly,
you're going to win the game. Very clearly. You won. And they build like five farms in random
places on the map. That's what I'm doing. I still have a gold mine and a town hall that I built just
to be an asshole, just somewhere. And he's just looking for me. Run out the clock from five months
we've been doing this. And this is just on, well, okay. What's it on? It's on the normal difficulty
with like a 30% like increase in difficulty on the actual game, right? There's still imps over
here. I lose. I'm not going to be able to do this. I can make some more dragons, but I don't,
I could just make dragons and I don't have enough money. It's over. I lose. I lose. I lose. There's
nothing I can do. He has so much. I didn't even get to have my last stand. Here he comes. He's
about to put me in perpetual fucking nightmare mode. Run. Run away. Don't. Oh, he's going to,
he's trying to stick me in purgatory, but he doesn't know that I can teleport. You don't know
shit. 260 points. Are you ready for this? Asshole. Get the castle. Mine. And going down. In fact,
I'm going to teleport tomorrow and take another one. I'm going to teleport over here and then I'm
going to teleport like over here. Well, I have to be able to see it. Nevermind. I'm going to get
a ball. What? What? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Yeah. How did you get that? There was nobody
there. There wasn't anyone even there. That's so stupid. Oh, God damn it. He's stuck. He's stuck.
It's there. He's not going to be able to get out. He's not going to be able to leave. I have a
chance. He's got all of his best units here. I'm going to fucking win the game. Boys and girls,
let's go. I'm ready. I'm fucking pumped right now. All right. Let's go. Pick up some resources
along the way. He can't leave. Go get all the land back. He's just going to pack a few, a few
lots pack. You should tele-frag them. Give me the dragons. Hold on. Let's see what happens.
Is there a way that I can make them all go in the portal? Blue has finally made it over here.
Oh shit. Fuck it. Yeah, take over all this stuff. Fight each other. Kill them. You fight down there
while I take everything up top. I'm going to do this very slowly. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Take it all. Then I'm going to know what I'm doing. Here he goes. This is awesome. I'm so happy right
now. What else can I take going this way? I can get the sulfur. Yep. Okay. Keep going.
Why are you coming down to me? Why are you going down to me? Uh-oh. Teleport. This, I can't
so stupid. He's got nothing in there. Where is he? He's up there. Oh, it's blue.
No, I needed these dragons. I was going to come back and get them. Um,
Vexant Icebolt. He has all, I think, the best units, at least top tier units, all in each slot.
It's all, they all can fly. Might as well, um, just go out the front door.
Meet them all in the open field. It's not like I can do about this.
Maybe I can take out one or two, but it don't matter. He's got some cool monsters, though.
One dwarf. Why is it one, one, one, one? This seems weird. The thing is, though, when I had my
original, my like 11 dragons, my 300 centaurs, I probably could have done this. This would have
been a good fight. I would have won without much of a problem. It was just purple. Purple somehow
just amassed a fortune, amassed a ton of money. Well, kill the genies. Yes, we're back home.
Genie versus genie. Good attack of dragon mistake. I have 245 skeletons, though.
Maybe I'll get lucky and I will get like a thousand skeletons, right? Two thousand experience.
Got my capital back, what's in here? All right, I can get it. I can get some titans, I think.
Two titans. I can get some more of these. What else? Genies? No genies.
I can fill up on these. 45. I could get a bunch of these. No, I've got one titan. What do you got?
Few pack, several throng, lots of hoard. Guys, guys, I can beat this. I can win. I can win right
now. I can, I can kill this person right now. Go ahead, fight each other down here. Let's go.
You got nothing. What do you got? I'm just, I'm going right. We're not wasting a second.
I'm gonna obliterate. Where is it? I have so many spells. Where is obliterate? Where is it?
Obliterate. Implosion, not obliterate. You know what I'm saying. Obliterate. Ares is stuck in
the corner. I might actually be able to do this as long as I can, like, kind of...
Why am I flocking with the archer? I'm losing it. I'm losing my fucking mind.
Okay, that's pretty good. Pretty good, pretty good, pretty good. All right, so now let's take it back
this way. I've got some titans. I've got, I can, I'm gonna teleport this and watch this shit. I'm
gonna teleport over here and then I'm gonna go down and I'm gonna get blue and I'm gonna get
fucking red. I'm gonna kill red. Listen to me. What's wrong with me? I'm like fucking freaking out.
He's turning mad. That's great. Okay, would like to recruit gremlins? No, just, this is all I got.
Yeah, blue is, I have to scoop up. I gotta go around. I have to scoop up. I'm not gonna leave
this place undefended. This one is, all right, hold on a minute. I need money. He can't do anything.
He's fucked. He's screwed. This is perfect. That's so awesome. More crystals. All right,
let me get the lumberyard. This is so stupid. Uh oh. They're getting in their boats. All right,
I got all the resources. Now let's get over here and I'm gonna teleport this way.
Although, how am I doing on, I feel like I should, I'm gonna get some more genies.
I'm gonna get four titans. More of these. Let's not rush here. Hold on. I can't believe I've done this
camp. This is like random campaign for fucking seven and a half hours. Should I just farm titans?
266 skeletons. Three more mages. Yeah, I'm just gonna sit out here, man. I'm gonna be the biggest
piece of shit ever. I'm gonna be the biggest fucking piece of crap ever. I'm just gonna skip
every single turn. What is gonna speed click? Purple on land? Uh, he's dead. Archers,
hoard a pet. You're dead. Get over here. Let's go. I'll kill you all. He's coming up. Okay, he's
dead. I got better dragons. Berserk on the dragon. Kill the archers. Get the fuck out of here.
I just burnt the fucking tent down.
I win. Slowly but surely, I'm going to kill all of purple and I'm gonna win.
It's a war of attrition at this point. I'm gonna win. I'm gonna get a balcony pick with a handsome
guy. Remember, are you seriously bringing another guy over here? Several packs, several fused,
several. They keep respawning and coming back to me. This is fucking awesome. I need more money
though. My resources aren't terrible. All right, here's what I'm gonna do. Okay, I'm gonna go.
That came out of nowhere. I'm gonna come over. I'm gonna teleport over here. I'm going this way
and I'm gonna go swoop by red. I still have a ton of units. I'm one more week and then I'm
gonna teleport over there. Somebody's coming over here though. Oh, they have to fucking do
that right now. It's this guy. I can't, I don't know if I can leave yet because if I teleport here,
I can swoop around. I don't even have this viewed. Stupid tax bullshit. No, I gotta wait another day.
Here you come. Here you come. Okay, I gotta be ready for this. What do you think? Two titans and
then replace the skeletons. I need, I don't have any money. I need two crystal, I need, okay, I need
two like nerds. 5,000. 5,000 gold. I have, I need, all right, okay, here we go. I'm gonna sell some
shit. Where's the market here? Down here? What the fuck is it? Artifact merchant? What the hell is this?
Defense, growth, cot, mercury. No. Where's the merchant down here? Did he fucking have one?
Am I insane? Where is it? Okay, I want this. I'll give you crystals.
All right, this is a good troop of people. I need a capital too. Fuck, I do. You're right. I gotta
kill this person though. They keep sending them up here. What is that? A behemoth? Target enemy's
defense is reduced by 40%. This is like a chad orc. Not that scary actually. Just go for the
berserk on the behemoth. Why are they on his legs? Got it, okay, and then we're gonna go right over
to the magi's. No, yeah, no, that's too close. Down here, the birds. One hit kill. Buff, buff.
Nice. Titan. Up top. Wolves. Magi. Defend. Ooh, got it. I win again.
No, I need to make a citadel. Stop making people. Make some genies. All right, that's it. I need a
citadel. He keeps retreating and you're killing the useless units. Well, the units don't stick around.
5300. Does this have a citadel? It doesn't have... Okay, I need... I'm gonna have two more capitals
here. Okay, I just gotta get to 20,000 gold. Everybody leave me the fuck alone. Nobody come
up here. Purple. I just killed like three of purple's heroes. 10,000. Let's get it right here.
Capital building. 4,000 gold a day. See you next week. 8,000 now. We're getting there.
We're getting there and I'm going to stack titans. It's gonna be embarrassing how many I have. At
least 30. I gotta get the wood. I'll go with this one. It's still mine. Am I gonna do anything with
the other dude? Yes. Uh, but first I need to get that other building. I need to get a capital in
that other, uh, castle, so. Imp growth, familiar growth. So I need a capital in here. All right,
already is one. I can't build more than one capital. Oh shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. I can't do it.
Shit. Oh well. Oh shit. I don't know. Oh, I need the money though so bad.
God damn it. Two more titans. I got it. It's still going. I'm not going to bed. No, I don't care.
Oh god damn it, man. Shit, I can't believe this motherfucker is coming over after me. Oh shit.
What the fuck am I doing? I got the sulfur for free. I'm just gonna sit here and grind.
This stream is never going to end. But here's the worst part, guys. Let's say this is like a 12 hour
stream. Okay. I have to eventually go over here. Otherwise I don't win. You know, understand? I
eventually everything, all everything ends at Ares. I'm going in there with 50 titans. It's
the only way to win. I'm telling you, this is the strategy here. All right. Let me, let me hang out
in here. That's eight titans. I just need money. Look at how much stuff this area to buy. Get the
reveal map spell? Do I even have one? Oh, it's tax day. Bullshit. Lookout tower. I don't have five
wood. I have to go on an expedition. It's inevitable. I have to. Anybody up here? I
don't see anybody up here. I have to go on an expedition. I'm teleporting over here. I can
always go back. Puzzle pieces. Witch hut. Okay, we got a rally point. Lock up. A thousand experience
right here. Oh! Uh oh. He ain't gonna come at me. That's the other guy that's really strong.
No, he's not here. Okay. What can I do? He's not going to come after me. I'm strong.
I want a new save. Whoa, what? Did Red just kill somebody? Did he just kill Purple?
What does he have in there? What? Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, what? Oh, he brought a boat.
He brought a boat. He brought a fucking boat over here. Boat. Not good. I have to turn around, I
think. But there's an island. But I've already been to this island. What are you doing? Wait,
but there's an island. Yeah, the middle island. I've been to a thousand times. No, go back. Back,
back, back, back. Ares is back. Oh my god. Okay, for a second. I thought this was 68 dragons.
I can take this. I'm thinking of implosion. Implosion on the angels or I wonder on the
zealots or the archers. Yeah, that was an absolute destructive thing that I just did. Thank god.
All right. 5200. 40 to 5250. No, I gotta I gotta whittle. I gotta blow you down.
I don't think I go anywhere. Unless me going. Damn. That was not what I thought was gonna happen.
Can I buff you? Okay, good. Magic mirror. Who do I throw this at? Angels. Oh, they can fucking fly.
This is terrible. This is really bad. Angel has to die now. Dragons are dead. I got no more dragons
anymore. They're gone. We gotta go twice. That sucks. Oh my god. I'm exiting the game. This is
not part of the plan. Not part of the plan. No, I'm not doing it. I had to fight the one dickhead
on the in the ocean. Watch this be the only thing he has. Angel's dead. Uh, those things are strong.
We got 200. Let's just go in the back here. It's gonna be good. 36. Okay, Genie.
Genie's just he's right in front of you. You have to try and you got nothing.
15 to eight. You keep going. Nice. All right, if there's something substantial that I get from this,
then I'm gonna redo it. You know, if I get like the the chest piece of immortality or something,
then maybe because I'm gonna I think I'm gonna win. Pretty good bait here. That's it for the
horses. You take care of this. That's it. 10,000 experience. Defense expert learning and nothing.
Here comes fucking Ares. Um, here's the thing though. This is I could get rid of red.
I could delete red right now. I don't think red has another castle.
This is empty. There's nothing in here. Unless unless there's something down here.
No, that's not part of the plan. Load game. This is before I even teleported over, right?
No, it's not. What the hell is going on? No, wrong one. Okay, so this is where I I'm gonna go back.
We're gonna teleport back. So then if I don't do that, let's see where the timeline is.
He still gets in the boat. Red is now here, which now red is gonna end up potentially taking this
castle. At least I got the resources. All right, teleport over here to walk. Okay, so get up here.
Back it up. Really want more dragons, but I don't think don't have any access to them.
It sucks. What do I have access to over here? Unfortunately, it's the same place. It's the same
place. It's not different. I'm gonna have to just like master gremlins, naga queens. I mean,
I'm gonna have to do something here. I could send somebody down here, but he's here. I really want
that back. There's nothing there except he's here. He's got dragons. Double of the same production
is not bad. No, that's not. Yeah, that's true. I'm gonna send a scout out next week. I'm gonna
send a scout out to try to get blue. At least that castle on the right. And I'll start him here and
get him, try to get him down here. There's nothing, there's nobody here. I can just get that back.
Or this one for day five. Still have the dragons. Titans. I'll have 10 titans. Still have all this
stuff up here. All right, let's go. Let's do that plan. Here we go. Wizard or Death Knight. He has
an artifact. What is it? What's the artifact? Knowledge and power by three. Let's give you
just a couple of these things to go out with. I will keep the other ones that are for this building
here. Go out this way. Grab a boat. Get the hell out of here. Basic scouting. This one definitely.
Arena. This is where I get some points. I'm not gonna move. I'm gonna stay here.
Oh, fuck. He's coming my way. What does he got? Is this the same red that I fought before? I beat
him. Yep, it is. All right, well, I'm getting in. I need a new hero. I might have to meet you halfway.
I think I'm gonna have to meet them halfway. Yep, I'm gonna focus the zealots. We're not on,
there's no planks here. No, I, you know, I'll make another, I'll make another hero.
And I'm gonna send this hero off. Absolutely this one. One knowledge. Okay, so then let's give you
this. I'm gonna give you something. I'll give you some something just to get this to be out there
and just be alright. Back it in here. I want you behind the walls. You need to go recruit shit.
Find your way around. Just walk by this guy. And I need to get in the boat and I'm gonna go down.
I'm gonna go down here. I want nothing to do with you, man.
All right, same deal with you. Down this way. Here we go. Let's see what happens.
He's coming in for a fight. All right, he wants to get rid of this guy. All right, well, this is
good bait. This is really good bait. I'm okay with this. It gets rid of the centaurs and it
makes him not attack the house. Everyone's just gonna die. This is wasted money. I know. Fuck,
you're right. I just... I didn't think he was gonna fucking... I thought he was gonna...
I didn't think he was gonna fucking come back and kill me. I thought he was gonna...
Okay, he's gonna go back to back. Back to back and kill everybody. Hey, remember that money that I
lost? I'm just... I got... I can't even... I shouldn't even spend any money on any other towns
because this is not possible to beat unless I have an equal or better force, which I can't do.
I can't. It's... I can't do it. I have to... I'm gonna... I don't give a shit. Just take it all.
I'm gonna just turtle the fuck out of one place and just get 25 titans and then win. Damn it.
I need to stop, like, putting money into three or four different places. I just need to do it
in one place. This whole... this same scenario is gonna play out over and over again. Or I just
lose because he keeps going to the capital. God damn it. Let's... I want to see what happens.
I made, like, three other heroes. I should have just sat in my fucking castle and just banked
money and then had, like, a bunch of people. I'm making that same mistake again. Well, the only
reason why I thought I was gonna win is because I thought Ares was stuck forever, but then it
didn't matter because then Red decided to grow a brain and move from this island to over here.
It's taken him eight hours to get here. What were you doing all this time? All right, let's see.
Let's... let's check this new scenario. Let's see what happens now. I need to, like, build this
place up. All right, this is what I was doing, right? Naga Queens. I can now make them here,
which is good. I can now get them to be made here. I'm going to do Cloud Temple. So I need
Author of Wishes. I don't have... I have no money to make anything else. What did I just say? No,
no, no, but I... but I made... I made, like, three new heroes. I spent, like, almost 10 grand on new
heroes. I'm not doing that. I'm just spent... like, I'm just trying to recruit people now. You know
what I mean? Like, see, I can have... make the genies. And now we go again. I've got a plan,
and his same scenario. He keeps coming back. All right, I can do this now. Author of Wishes,
and then we can do them here. Now I can make upgraded genies. And by the way, like, delete
this guy. What is that? What... that guy serves no purpose. All right, even more. And then we're
going to dump them together, and this guy's going to just ride his horse off a cliff, for all I care.
Okay, looks all right. Okay, let's go. Save it. Okay, here we go. So here comes Red. If I'm behind
my walls, he won't kill me. Here comes Ares. Everyone is recruited from here. This place is
looking all right. Okay, now Cloud Temple. I need 5,000 gold. I also need 10 wood, 10 ore, and 10
marbles. So I just need some wood. And then we can start generating titans here. So let's just make
as many of these as we can. I have to cash right now. I kind of have to get out here. If he... I
kind of have to get out and, like, get the wood again. All right, first of all, get in the castle,
because if he comes over to the castle, I'm going to die. So what do I do with these? I said I wasn't
going to make another hero. Do I just delete them? I think I have to just delete them. Yeah, I have
to dismiss them. I'm not going to use them. Sell them for resources. Yeah, that's a good idea.
Where is that building? Where is that building? Do I even have it here? Resource silo? No.
What is it called? Do I have it in this town? No, the tavern. Um, a blacksmith? No. I don't think I
have it here. Stronghold is the only faction that gets a building to sell units. Ah, damn it.
It's only on the orc stronghold. Well, oh well. Wait, what? What do you mean I do have it?
Where is it? No, just kidding. Thanks. Skeletons aren't worth it. Just delete the skeletons?
I feel like the skeletons can be pretty good sometimes, though. It's not worth making a new
hero and just having him just go die. I'm just gonna dismiss them. I'm just gonna dismiss them.
Three, two, one. I'm doing it. Has chap been right before? Quite a few times, actually. Yeah, they
have. They've been right before. Okay. How are we doing here? I need wood. I'm gonna take back the
fucking wood. Where is he? Go get wood. I need this. Just don't pop out of nowhere and kill me.
You know how upset I'll be if that happens? I don't have the new, the new genie, right?
I can get these guys. Okay. Starting to build a decent army on the other side here. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I can beat them. I'm gonna go hard on the zealots. The angels, they have so many
good fucking units. I think it's go hard on zealots. Start off with implosion on the zealots
or should I berserk? Berserk the zealots? There's so many options. Either berserk the zealots,
implode the zealots. How's their attack? 10 to 12, 7 to 10, 2 to 3, 15 to 25. I could do that.
They do way more damage. Yeah, I think I'm gonna berserk the, um, the capital right here. They do
more damage. And then I'm just gonna go hard on the zealots. With dragon and with titan.
Ah! Get out of here! You're ruining everything! Because I'm gonna deplete all my fucking forces
on this! This is like the same thing that happened. Except at a different part of the map. They just,
I just don't, I didn't do it. It was the first three hours of the game. I just didn't get
everything in the right position. I was still trying to learn and remember how to play.
And I fucking peed on myself. All right, well, get up here. I at least need to have somebody fight.
And then I'm back to square one again. And then there's two or three other people that have
huge armies. I think this is a retreat and give up. I think I'll lose here. I don't think it's
possible that I can win. Even if I beat this, I, what am I gonna do? I'm behind in troops and
resources by like a hundred percent. I can win this fight, but then we start all over again where
it's like, oh, here comes Ares with his 30 dragons. I'm fucked. Well, it was fun. Use spells? I couldn't
use spells. This is the first round I've been able to use spells up until last time. We're
going to berserk again. Let's berserk the angels, get rid of them, fight each other, kill each other.
Okay. Good. So put the skeletons. That's perfect. Very good. Go carve up the angel. This is a
victory. He's melted the skeletons. Holy shit. Kind of in trouble here. Whoa. Well, that's not good.
Angel's dead. I'm going to wrap back around here and they retreated. 10,000 experience. I used
blind. Cannot move, cause a counterattack at half its normal attack strength. Let's get expert
learning. So now I, what the hell am I going to do now? I need more Titans. Crystals back here.
Two more Titans. Oh, they can only get one. I feel like we are probably going to be in a never-ending
loop. I'm almost certain of it actually. Epic 72 hour campaign. Now I'm essentially treading water
at this point because they just has so much great stuff. I'm going to give it like another week
or a couple of weeks and we'll see. Cause I just not really generating enough money.
And if I send people, it's almost like I'm constantly swimming upstream. And I think, yeah,
I just have to, I think I just have to take somebody. I got, I'm going to get, I'll get 10
Titans. And I think I just have to, I have to go down here and just try to steal something. Just
try to get something. Let us recruit what we can recruit. And then I'm going to go from there. So
let's do it. There are 18 of these over here. So what I'm going to do, I'm, what am I going to do
here? Let's just see, let's just see what happens. We've been going for like over eight hours now.
It's probably time to wind it down. It's like midnight Pacific. I'm like too addicted to being
in a never ending circle, but it's all good. Let's do this. I'm just going to recruit
whatever's left here and then I'm going to head down. I need to wait a day. Of course it's tax day.
That's great. 10 Titans. There we go. I hate that. There's still a few more in here. I've got to
wait. I can, if I'm going to give it a real try, I'm going to wait, go until a year has passed.
That'll be like another, probably eight and a half hours. It's month six. I don't think
I'm going to do that. All right. Wizards. All right. Almost ready to go. I'm actually going to
bring the other Naga Queens over. Don't even tell me he's fucking coming to get me. Oh,
this is you motherfucker. No, let me have my, don't you dare. I need to like deliver these guys. Oh,
God damn it. I need to just deliver people to here. Just do something else for a minute.
Do not come over here. Just do anything else for fucking five seconds. One more turn. Don't even
come over here. Thank, what? Special goddamn delivery. What happened? He's got 21 dragons and
a hundred liches, a hundred trees. This was never winnable anyway. He's just progressively
gotten better and I've been treading water. No, it's not possible, but I'm going to go out with
a bang and he's going to come get me and I'll let him take the fucking castle like a goddamn.
He's unbeatable. Come on, let's do it. And end by like eight to 10 hours streamer with me being
fucking humiliated. Let's go. I'm going to sit up here. They have too many. He's right outside
the castle. This is it. It's over. He's going to take his, his cheating dragons. Is there,
is there a way after this match is over? Can I go like to a replay and see how the fuck you got
these? Why would it be a reaction? Yeah, I know. Aha. You lost a unicorn. He's not even going to
come get me, is he? All right. I'll just be a piece of shit. What are you going to do?
You're going to come get me? This is it. The last stand before I actually lose.
I lose the game. Oh, this is so sad. This is so sad to me. I was so pumped and excited.
I have to get my revenge. I have to get my revenge tomorrow. I've, I'm so sad. I'm very sad right now.
I actually really am. Damn it. I really thought I had it. Okay. All right. This is fun. This was
fun. It was. Who do I even, what do I even do here? Berserk on. I can't even do that. I have to
implode somebody or let me try one of the other. No, no, no. You know what? Let's get an earth
elemental out here. Oh, this thing sucks. Nevermind. Going for the dragon. Holy shit.
Wow. Wait a minute. Wow. That was very, very, very, very good. Should I go out there and kill
the dragon? Six dragons dead. Waste. No, he's just got too many good. I could kill, at least let me
kill the dragons. Let me just get rid of these dragons. I hate them. All right. Titans. Five
dragons perish. What's going on? Oh, you're dispelling all the mines. That's kind of ridiculous.
If I kill the bone dragons, this is a victory. There's only, there's only four left.
I win. That's a victory for me. No, not my city. Not my capital.
Oh, I want to play again. This time I'm going to do much better and I'm going to be prepared,
but not tonight. 23. I will come back stronger. There goes everything. Is that me?
No, what? They even do this to you? That sucks. Oh, no, it hurts. I'm like actually,
ugh. No, I'm not doing round two right now. I'm just going to have, I'm going to have mayhem
for tomorrow. Team alignments. No teams. Maybe we should do teams. What do you think? Tomorrow
should be like four on four. Eight teams. Large map. Cause I mean, obviously it's eight people.
I'm going to keep it at that 130%. I think that's, that's good. It's fair.
Monster strength. What was it? It was on strong and it's a random map template.
Normal water. Or should we do pre-made scenarios? You have to prove. No water means no boats to
worry about. That's true. Always build second level rebuild library. I don't know what that means.
This is all. We can do this tomorrow. We'll set it up. Uh, yeah, that's going to be it. Unfortunately,
uh, I ran around in a circle for the last like three hours, but it was still a lot of fun. It's
exactly like I remember. I have a sour taste in my mouth, but I will turn it into sweet candy
tomorrow. Going for a win tomorrow. And then after tomorrow, after tomorrow, I am going to
take a little bit of time off. I have to do my colonoscopy. I'm going to be kind of miserable
over the next few days. I'm not going to be able to eat very much, but that will be it.
I will see you tomorrow around the same time between three and four Pacific. Thank you for
watching. This was Heroes of Might Magic 3, an old favorite of mine. Hopefully you guys thought
it was fun because I know there was maybe people said, oh, maybe not. I wonder. I've never seen
that before. Is it boring? Is it not boring? But I think we definitely can do another stream on this
and we'll do it tomorrow. This game is fucking awesome. It's very fun. It's very intense
and I will see you tomorrow for the next part. Thanks again for watching. We're going to do the
bits and subs when I return because I need to use the bath. I'm not going to pee. Much love to you
if you take it off. Maybe you'll step by tomorrow. See you soon. I'll be right back. Okay, so let's go
back to a long time ago, almost a whole day away. We're going to go back to Gnarly. Thanks for the
six dollars. Gnarly 62. Thanks man. Appreciate the comfort. My pleasure. Thanks for watching.
Thank you for the six dollars. Appreciate it. Thank you. Some guy. Thanks for the 15 dollars.
I don't have any message. Here's a dog. A dog. Is it a dog running after a guy? That's not Otto.
No, it's a different dog. Show Otto. No, Otto I think is probably asleep because it's
midnight. I don't think Otto is awake at the moment. Otto attacking Ares. Nah, let Otto sleep.
Otto doesn't need to be awoken. But thank you for the 15 dollars some guy. Thanks. Appreciate the dog
run video. Thank you. Thank you warm like biscuits for the 10 bucks. 15 dollars and 10 dollars right
after earlier today. Jerm, I've been watching you since early TF2 days and I have to thank you for
all the laughs and joy you have brought me through the years. I've had pretty dark nights and your
videos always made them a little easier. So thank you. Thank you. I love Team Fortress. I loved
making YouTube videos. I'm very very happy that people enjoyed them and thought they were fun
and may have helped them forget about some shit in their life. You know what I'm saying? That's
that means a lot. Thank you for the 10 dollars. Thank you for the fucking incredibly kind message.
Much love to you. Thank you warm like biscuits. Really appreciate it. Multi trip thank you for
the three bucks. Good god this is such a geeky nerd neck game. It just made me crack my neck to
make sure that I was not sitting inappropriately. Thank you for the three dollars. Thank you Matt
P.T. or Piety for the 250. Thrilled to see you playing Heroes of Might and Magic 3. Some of my
earliest memories as a kid are sitting on my mom's lap and watching her play Might and Magic
and Heroes of Might and Magic on her computer. Then abusing the hell out of cheats when I started
playing myself since I was so bad at it. I joined right as you were complaining about losing a battle
and loaded a save to redo it. That's the German we all know and love. I want to watch from the
beginning so I'll be checking out the recording later. Keep being a cool guy. Thank you. I do have
very fond memories of this game but okay maybe we can put uh maybe tomorrow I won't do any
rewinds but I'm just trying to get back in the swing thing trying to remember how to play the
game trying to remember how things work. Now I got like a good idea of how things are working again.
It's been like 15 years. Maybe we don't do rewinds tomorrow. Maybe we just have to accept our fate.
What is the worst sound of 2019?
Fight the article that says yeah fight the article that says let me find an article fight the
article that says yeah what the fuck thank you for the 250 though appreciate it matt
Freudian weapon thanks for the three bucks cheer 300 no message thank you for three dollars
Onicus thanks for the ten dollars thank you Onicus dude just want to show a little bit of
support been watching your videos for years just starting to come to streams thank you for all the
laps thank you Onicus really appreciate the ten dollars appreciate the support thanks for watching
for that much time I'm super thankful that people years later still think that this channel is fun
you know if you watch the same thing for a few years maybe sometimes you can kind of get sick
of it or something you don't really like anymore so floored that people have been able to think
this is still fun and cool and interesting over the last few years if you've been around for that
long or five years whatever you always say you're going then stick around for an hour
well when a stream ends and this is going to be changing once i have lower down makes the new
graphics when i say a stream is ending i really mean the stream is transitioning into a
like 30 to 45 minute hangout session where we just hang out so the stream is technically over
but it still goes on for a little while yeah yeah it's the game yeah the gaming is done
and i go through the messages that came through over the course of the
evening i don't i'm not sure how maybe how new you are or how many streams you've caught but i don't
read uh subs or donations or anything like that on stream i will stop for something major you know
if somebody gives you know five ten twenty community subs obviously that's a that's a
big deal it's a lot of money or like 50 bucks or 100 bucks it's like that's a that's a big deal
but um for the most part i just can we kind of just do the broadcast and then we do a little
hangout session afterwards gamer cool down yeah there'll be a new screen this won't say stream
over uh in a week or so i'll have uh some new graphics some new music so it will not just be
over it'll say something else but it seems to have been working pretty well over the last couple
of years i heavily enjoyed i like doing it it takes a lot of the stress and the um kind of
need to stay on top of things like subs and donations i like this better let's just focus
on the stream and then have like a good 45 minute session to go over everything how does dna work
um you swab a thing in your mouth and then you uh import it uh but thank you to profit rocket
for the five dolls hey germa long time fan first time giving you bits i've poorly animated part
of one of your streams hope you get a chance to see it thanks for all the laughs let's feel
wrong button let's look at it okay poorly animated neither do i i don't fucking agree with you
about this no neither do i let's put this on this is he said if i poorly animated you doing
a portion of this stream let's see what it is
no neither do i i don't fucking agree with you my browser go yeah you're an idiot an
imbecile i'm sorry but i disagree no you should not be trusted ever absolutely sure about this
no neither do i i don't fucking agree with you yeah you're an idiot an imbecile
no you should not be trusted ever no you get out of my house how about that you i invited you over
here you took the fucking bus here lady that's not right yeah and you asked for directions and i try
to give you directions no yes it is because i gave you directions earlier and you didn't care
yes it was what happened so stop fucking interrupting me that is what happened so stop
fucking interrupting me yes it is you knocked on my door and you asked for fucking directions
are you following me do you understand what i mean
i'm really sure about this no neither do i i don't fucking agree with you i don't i
i don't even fucking like i i guess i vaguely remember that
that was fucking funny though thank you so much for that that was pretty good
i missed the english tutorial channel didn't somebody say that they removed every video for
some reason did we cause that to happen weren't there like a hundred views of per video on that
channel why did this community viewing those videos get them removed i don't understand who
else watched them didn't each yeah every single one of the videos on that channel had less than
100 views it's odd i don't know why that's but uh thank you that was profit rocket for the five
dolls and that uh little animation little moving comic book thank you for that uh
smelly boy thanks for the 250 aries is basically hannibal also he needs to be in the next rumble
yeah i'm gonna give him zero stats i'm gonna eliminate him first i feel so i feel so unfulfilled
i need to win tomorrow i didn't cheat i may have rewound a few times but i wasn't gonna cheat to
win i have to win for real but thank you smelly boy thank you clowers clowers clowers v clowers
for the 250 thank you lads bought jupiter's have been flooding the market recently liquidate all
of your germa jupiter and germa jupiter for germa jupiter 3 and 4 and invest exclusively in germa
saturn now i have a feeling germa saturn will be the next big thing please trust me because germa
985 himself is reading this right now and he wouldn't lie to you germa wouldn't lie that
should be another one germa told the truth about x where are those i need some of those
thanks for the 250 though and we only have a couple more so let's get the credits on screen
get them up there roll them about to reach the over a um just about under nine hours
cool i like just doing this sometimes i feel like i've gotten so comfy that i like just sitting
here and playing a game it's fun i like just sitting here and making units i'm getting more
comfortable with these streams do you remember how rare it was when i would have a stream like
maybe like a year or two ago did i ever have a stream like two years ago that went over four or
five hours i don't think ever i used to play yeah max four hours but that was a lot of fun
i know that near the end there we got a little late so sorry we're kind of pushing the midnight
oil here now you read bits for four hours not anymore we've only been here for like 20 minutes
that's why i raised the minimum these have been going pretty smoothly too i think that was a good
call i think it was a good idea hey i wanted to ask you something for the longest time could you
play a three-minute ad no no i'm not going to play ads i'll play ads tomorrow i promise
but thank you everybody for watching i hope you really liked it i mean i know i'm
not the best like strategy and kind of management player but it really is such an old favorite of
mine especially when i was younger so hopefully you enjoyed it maybe you'll stick around for
tomorrow if you're around we'll try it again uh there's still a couple more bits to do there's
buttery uh buttery raven thanks for the bits this game is making me cry real tears
it was my childhood yeah uh thanks for watching there's a lot of cool shit in the game
there's mods too i have one of the community mods for hd and some bug fixes maybe if if people like
this and people want to see more of it if we could do it again with some mods or change it up or
maybe i'll try to get multiplayer to work i think that i might have to get the other version
thanks for your tears uh but thank you to all the subs everybody there's about you know almost a
whole day here tons of you guys came in and subbed thank you much love to you and finally we had
uh espada escarlata for the 250 have one bit for every point of iq you fucking legend
250 iq that's high i would remove like 110 points i would know way more than that i would
remove 135 points i think that's more accurate and then finally the jack thanks for the 250 from
the jack so you get nothing you lose good day sir i did lose but that means i'm gonna come back
stronger than ever that was a lot of fun thanks for watching i'll see you tomorrow tomorrow is
the last stream for a few days i'm hopefully i can come back here without being too messed up on like
colonoscopy drugs so tomorrow and then i'll see you after tomorrow uh well technically thursday so
friday saturday and maybe sunday i might be off i'm gonna be pretty miserable so after tomorrow
we'll talk about it again but you'll see me on probably monday have a great rest of your night
thank you for watching i'm gonna do stream legends if you i would like to use it if you'd
like to if you play and you mess around before or after streams i'm about to turn it on i can't
wait for the butt stream stay tuned for the colonoscopy stream um i cannot even open my
extensions menu for some reason oh also good news another day of no real internet problems
this was just under nine hours and i only have 1300 drop frames which is
it's pretty typical that's very normal cross your fingers that we're through the woods on that one
it's been a few days now and with this twitch having problems i can't like open my extension
manager all right it's open now here we go ready three two one open your presence and there you go
yips are out what's a colonoscopy colon i'll answer that real quickly before i go
a colonoscopy is you are put under sedation and they do an endoscopy they do they put a camera
in a place that sun don't shine and they examine your entire intestinal tract
they scope your colon yes the elbow all of it yes the whole thing do it without sedation i
actually didn't want to do it with sedation but this practice that i'm going to i asked him about
it and they do not do no sedation colonoscopies the reason why i said i didn't want sedation is
because i've done two sigmoidoscopies before without sedation they don't really do them
and a colonoscopy is sort of just a sigmoidoscopy 2.0 it's just longer so i've done them before and
i just i don't like like anesthetic drugs they i think fuck with you but uh we'll see i'm just
i'm doing it for a couple of reasons there's a preventative reason why i want you know just
want to make sure i've never really had like a full on complete colonoscopy before it's good to
do because obviously my condition that i've had over the last decade so a new place i want to
get re-evaluated i've had some issues the last year so i'm just gonna go in you know do what you
got to do and i should be fine don't worry about i have the best colon it's the largest colon no
inch colon you got into my colon that's so stupid somebody wrote that i had i just had a
monka lul does that exist should i like make that a thing i made that up don't forget that
all right good night guys i will see you tomorrow have a great rest of your night take care