All right, so with the remaining time that we'll have here, let's do some lists. Anybody have
any special requests? Because this was fun yesterday. Remaining time in quotes. Yeah, well, I mean,
I usually only stream for five to seven hours, depending. All right, let me get that on the
screen. We can find one. Snacks. Is there a snack one? Candy. Ooh, that's a good one. I'll do candy.
Anybody got a good candy one? Taco Bell menu tier. What? Do these even exist?
Do the Soulsborne games? This is easy. Yeah, I can do this one in my sleep. Do I even need to have a
tier list open for this? I could just say them. Dark Souls bosses. That's kind of cool. All right,
let's get, I want you to be able to see this shit. And window capture. Please do. And what's that?
What? How is that the window? That is not the right window. That is not the right window.
Oh, here we go. All right, so I'll do some quick. Do I actually go get a T or am I a faker? Ooh,
there is a Dark Souls boss one, is there? Yeah, we'll do this one first. Now, is this supposed
to be hard or which one I thought was the coolest? Hold on. I don't want to have any Hulu ads.
Bring this down. Holy fuck, there's so many. I don't even remember that this is too many icons.
I don't, I can't do this by icon only. I'm sorry, guys. This is like picking a champion in Dota.
I don't know. I don't remember who any of these are. Holy shit. Uh, well, how do I get this on?
I can't even get this on the screen. Do it one at a time. Okay, I'm gonna do, I'm gonna do it
really slow. One at a time. That's a decent spot for it to be right where you can see S. All right,
so let's get this off. Let's get me back on here like this. Hey, what's happening? Okay, um,
I have to change. Hold on. Why is this? This is fucked up. Okay, let me, wait, I'm not doing
this for cleanup detail anymore. That's a lie. All right, here we go. Uh, so this is, I don't,
who is this? Who is that? You guys gonna have to help me here. Clean my ears? Did, they should
be cleaned now? Who is that? I'm not gonna be able to do this. I'm gonna, I'm gonna find my
favorite boss. That's all that matters. Bloodborne's not on this list. Never mind. Okay, um, I'm not,
I can't do this one. What is this? Germania? Germania. All right, we'll try it. Give this
like that. Okay, so what is Germania? Germania tier list maker? Oh, Jesus Christ. It's like picking
a chip in a dota again. All right, who, were there really this many people? All right, I can do this.
The pencil doesn't even get a slot apparently. I can do this. I can do this. All right, let's go.
Now, this is not about how strong a character is. Remember, this is like who I think is the coolest
character. Not the strongest, just who's the, who's the best character. We'll go, Pac-Man,
it has to be somewhere at least at A, S, or A. Uh, the egg. What does Z mean? Let's put egg at F
for now. It's the spy, like D. Um, all the bia's have to be down in the same spot. Like they can't,
what, is one bia cooler than the other? This is a bia, that's not Mario, that's a bia.
Santa, I mean that's just Santa Claus, it's stupid. Elvis is just Elvis. Who is this? Oh, this is
Captain Old Bones. Up here somewhere. Danny DeVito. This is the chicken. The Easter Bunny, F. Like F,
like below F, like the pencil. Count Chocula is somewhere in A. Dick Dashley Richard is B.
The Magician is definitely somewhere in C. All the serial characters are going to be probably on one
list. Yeah, now I have to change this list a little bit. Yeah, because they're all stupid,
and they all go on the same. There's a complete different serial tier, I think,
and it's definitely like up here. Yeah, that's good. That's definitely, and then in the serial
tier I will determine who I think is the coolest. Baldcoin, probably, probably like F. Baldcoin
sucks. I mean it just glows, that's any one, so it's not fair. This is, it should be a president's
tier too. Dr. Roker is at least A. Orson Welles? Earthworm Jim A is the wine guy. Not a serial
character, but definitely cooler than like the egg. All like video game characters also have to,
besides Pac-Man, because you're up there. And yes, I get to put Pac-Man at S because
in the Smash Brothers games he's like a D, so he gets to go up there on mine.
He gets to be S in my one. Okay. What? Pac-Man belongs up there. All video game characters are
going to have to be on the same tier too, because this is a shitload of them. And all humans, all
real humans, I think should be on the same category too. All right, let's get it, I'm going to put,
I'm going to make it, let's call it humans. Because this D. F. Humans. Look, there are too
many like just real people. Why is it just a normal picture of his face? All right, who
else is just a regular person? Why is a spy on here twice? Oh, the PSVR absolutely goes up.
I love this character. A. Mime belongs down with pencil. What's going on? Why they're like,
everything's duplicated. What? Why are there three, four, everything's twice?
It's broken. It's all right. I can do it. All right, Burger Boy. Yeah, another big down here.
Miserable Mikey. Absolutely belongs up around. Well, hold on. Yeah, that's accurate. Speaking,
this needs to be moved up. Glue Man. Yep. Glue Man goes up to S. I'm going to put like at least
two. Is this a? Yeah, I can't tell. I think it is. The green screen belongs up there.
Can't be stopped. So this is just a human. What is that? B. B. C. D. B. B. B. C. B. D. B. What is
that? B. D. D. B. B. What does that stand for? Yeah, Batman. I don't, I don't even remember
making this. So it's down here. Bootleg Duck Dynasty. Yeah, Batman. Holy shit. All right.
The egg is already up there, right? No. The movie of the movies characters. Yeah, they belong up
here. The pencil is just in the pencil category because it's the pencil. Chicken belongs way up
here around B. Disco Diaper is probably B. Hitman is a, is a, no, Hitman. No, it's a character.
It's just Hitman. There's nothing special. It's just, Oh look, he's bald guy with the suit on.
No, get rid of it. What was that? It was a giant rat. There's two giant rats though. Which one's
cooler? There are two chickens. Where's the other chicken? There are two chickens. Where? On the
list? There are two eggs. There are two chickens and two eggs. Egg one. Chicken one. Okay, there
there are two eggs. Where's the other chicken? Who the fuck is that? Oh, that's Ma, that's Kyle.
Yeah, that character is pretty cool. Jack's Jerma goes up here. No, no, that's too much. What does
this say? Monopoly guy D. Wizard Mike is already up there. The mime's already up there. Dick
Richard's up there. Boo is up there. That's just a person. This is Gabe Newell. Where's Gabe? Gabe
Newell is already up there. Yeah, but B. Birdboy's there. I don't think president number seven,
whatever his name is. No, down there. This looks good. This is James Madison. I think so.
Granny from the Vumps. Well, okay, here, there is just like a Vumps. Let's just,
we can collectively use them. Chocula's under cereal. Let's just get all the cereal characters
out here. Tony the Tiger's there. Cheese Nips is up here. Oh, no, that's Cheese It's. Definitely
somewhere in S. Isn't this, this is the same, this is a different pose of the same person.
Frank Pizza? Frank Pizza is not that great. Not a human, though. Does Danny DeVito, all right,
the two-person horse. I love that character so much. Human Lord Zaraxos, I mean, just because of his
lower quality. Needs to be somewhere up here. Another president, right? James Giraffe? James
Gar, oh, okay. Other presidents. Is Dr. Roker up here? Yep. This is another, another, yeah,
but he's already there. I think this is like Star version one. Winston is the, another one guy.
Are there only two cereal characters? Oh, there's what? Cheese Nips down there. There's so many
people. This is the Archmage. Let's see. Captain Crunch is, is double S tier. Yeah. Demon Grandpa
is pretty high for me. It just is. Demon Grandpa is like S for me. Mr. Sneak Man is probably A.
There's Paul Bearer, who would definitely be up around B. He's a classic. I don't know what this
is. Can somebody refresh my memory of what this is? No rewinds. Oh, ah, eh. There's the Apple.
Definitely down here somewhere. Easy Pete. Easy Pete belongs, uh, at least in A somewhere.
There's somebody with a diaper on. I don't know who that is. I swear to God, there's like 10
cereal characters. Did I only make like three? No serpents. All right, what about this is the
Anor Lander? Somewhere in, somewhere in A. I like this list so far, but I'm going to make a couple
changes. There's the Wirehead guy. I could recognize, I could recognize that vest anywhere.
See. Captain Crunch, there you are. You are a cereal character, but you are like,
one of the best characters ever. Benjamin Franklin is a pres, is a person, president,
but, uh, I mean, this motherfucker invented electricity, so you have to be up here.
Carl Griffinstede, uh, probably somewhere like around here. There's a lot of Cs, but there are
a lot of C list characters. The EMT. EMT belongs in the human category, but it's going to be like high
Z. Disco Diaper's already up there, right? I thought so. Yeah, right here. It's like two
different images. Okay, the movies that are up there. I don't know who this is. This Andrew
Jackery Jack. Eh, somewhere in D. The Heavy Weapons guy. Oh, okay. Probably should be right next to
the spy. That would make, that makes the most sense. Here is, uh, from Lethal League, Mr. Candyman.
I put you in the high Cs here. Anybody else that I didn't put in here? I don't know who this is.
I think that's a mistake. I don't think that person's on here. Sluggo, right? Did I get
German Moon? Not yet. Oh, and this is, uh, IRL, uh, 3D CGI Pac-Man. Right. We have
cartoon Pac-Man, but we also have like 3D CGI, like made for like the movie version of Pac-Man,
which I think is way better. Censored. Yeah, that character sucks. Danny DeVito is not up there.
He's just a fucking human. All right. I think that's everybody, at least on this list. I can
move some stuff around now. This is, this is most of them. The VR guy. Oh, that's the VR guy. I love
that character. Yeah, definitely belongs up here. Up here. Oh, nice. I'm not changing that. He's not,
he's not coming down for mess. Did I get this guy? Did he try another guy? I don't think so. No,
I did. All right. Who am I missing anybody? The PSVR is up here already. Yeah. There are two Danny
DeVitos. Oh, okay. Yeah. This one, one inhuman. Okay. No 30s milkman. If a 30s milkman belongs
down here anyways, doesn't matter. Now I have to make the real one. I can already tell you
it's going to look like this. No tooth goblin. So what we have available, two-person horse is
probably my moment. I don't know why I have an accent now. Missing German moon. Yeah, you belong
definitely like on B. All right. Two-person horse is my favorite character, I think, out of any of
them ever. I've made my final decision on this. The loom man, Pac-Man, Mr. Cheez-It, Steven Grandpa.
Yeah, but bring him down. He doesn't belong up there. Neither do I. Hmm. I think that's it for
the yeses. Then you got Earthworm Jim, Dr. Elker, PSVR. Hmm. Easy Pete, I think, stays there. Disco
diaper comes up. German moon comes up. I go down. Winston goes down very, very much so. All the way
down to Lake Sea. They're doing the same pose. I'm all right with this. Maybe, oh, hold on.
I would put myself in front of Gabe Newell, but I'm not going to do that. Okay. Miserable Mikey
comes forward. Annalander goes down. Mr. Sneak Band takes that place. Jake Richard goes down.
Okay, I think, I think that's it. Now it's, no, now it is, now it's good. I think I'm going to bring
the, okay. Yeah, I know. People are saying, oh, whoa, hold on. Gabe Newell, I mean, what,
Gabe Newell's not like the, besides like the VR headset stuff. Gabe Newell used to be like all over
the place, used to be like everywhere. He used to be on interviews and talking and he was like a
front runner in like the gaming industry. Now he kind of just does his thing, right? Did I get a
cut on my hand? Put Gabe in the human spot, but he's almost, he's almost like otherworldly. He's,
right? All right, if Danny DeVito is going to be down in the human spot, then, then he should too.
He is a human, just a person, but he's a person that's not a president. That's important. I'm
not done. Hold on, I got to move these around. Just, they're all, everyone's freaking out about
this. Just hold on. I'm going to fix it. Just hold on. Don't worry. It's going to be fine.
Gabe, Gabe Newell, just because you're on the human list doesn't mean you're like bottom tier.
It just means you're, you're a human and we have to put the humans in the right place.
All right. Where was I? B? B looks pretty good. B minus streamer. I'm a B plus streamer now.
All right, let's go see. Magician stays there. Orson Welles stays there. Candyman comes up. Wine
Guy replaces, hit the tree. The movies actually goes in front here. The egg goes up in front
there. Egg goes actually in front of the movies. Orson Welles stays there. The bumps take over
that spot. Candyman comes down. Wirehead moves over the spot that was occupied by the Wine Guy.
This is kind of just a person. So, you know, not, not that interesting with the characters.
Cool. And it's funny, but this context here, Winston goes down here. Benjamin Franklin.
Okay. I'm all right with this, I think. Orson Welles is a human, right? It is a human that's
not a president. In fact, all humans, all humans that exist in real life or have existed in real
life are going down here. And then we'll have, they'll have their separate list. Benjamin Franklin
has to come down here. All people that are real people. Shit. That means Dr. Ocker has to come
down. Captain Crunch is not a person. Captain Crunch is a fucking cartoon character. He's not
a real guy. He's a serial. Fuck. You're right. You're right. They have to be on the same playing
field. No, but there's the other serial. Where's Woody the Woodpecker? Whatever his name is.
The Cuckoo Bird. Hey, I don't see him down here. No, the serial characters don't need their own
list because this is where they belong. I'm removing the serial character list.
Okay. That's good. Remove the human? Oh, there are too many. I can't, I can't put, I can't put like
fucking James Madison up here. Like, no, they don't, they exist on their own plane. Two-person
horse is a human. That is a horse. That is a, no, it's not. That is two horse pieces.
Jerm is a human. All right. All right. I'm getting rid of that. I'll get rid of it.
I'm just, I am just categorizing people. Like, oh, you're a human. You're a serial character.
You're a cartoon character. That's not a tier list. That's just what are they? All right. I'm
getting rid of the humans. You go back here. You, I still don't think I would put you any higher than
that. But they, all the humans would be like C anyways. I'm gonna have to get them all in C
and then move them around. No, I mean, like, James Madison sucks. Like, the characters are stupid.
Both of these two presidents characters are filler content. It is the equivalent of a
filler episode of a TV show. Van Buren rocks. That's right. You can love the filler episode.
I love some filler episodes. It doesn't mean that they're not filler episodes.
They, they're filler episodes. That like sucks too. It was just like,
all the presidents are like down at the bottom here. Make the humans row F. No, that isn't,
no. Z is F. I'm changing Z to F. This is F. What are you doing? Excuse me. F. That is just F.
I'm just gonna remove the human tier. Star. I'm just, I'm, this is not final yet. Hold on,
everybody. No rewinds. Belongs in D. And then Orson Welles belongs probably up here. Okay,
let's get her to the human tier. Now we can work with this. Okay. Do you guys understand why I had
a human tier in the first place? Because now you're making me rate my friends. That, you
understand? Having everybody in the human tier. Oh, well, aren't they like MLC stealth? There's
definitely like cooler than boo. No, but boo is better than a talent. This is why I wanted to
avoid that. Star belongs up. You're making me rate my friends. I'm doing a friend tier. No, yeah,
that's Gabe Newell. Never mind. All right, the friends of friends. The friend, that's the friend
tier. What? Oh, fuck. What's going on? Hey, what's going on? Is that it? Okay. All right.
Now I'm going to rename this to D. What are you doing? What are you doing? D. Okay. All right,
so now I'm ready. We did B. I'm happy with that. C. C is, I think, pretty good. Friends. Doesn't
matter where any of them are. Doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. They're all friends. And they're
all cool. And I like, they're all fun. And I like them. Okay, cool. None of this list does not mean
however high anybody is, that they're cooler or liked more. This is just a non description list
of people that not from any particular order are just on the list. Okay, there you go. And I'm
going to put the friends down here because they are not, they are not part of this. They're,
they're down here. They, they're down there because this is like, this is the pencil tier
and this is friends. So they're just in a separate category. The pencil tier is not
part of A, B, C, D, S, D, E, F. Okay. It's just the pencil tier. The friend here is,
is not part of the, of this, of this stuff here. Okay. Now that we've got that situated,
A, B, A, B, C, D. Okay. D is going to be hard. I'm going to have to change some of this around.
Okay. This is going to be hard. They, they're all so bad. All the BS have to be at the bottom.
This is too many of them. Santa should, should be like over here. Maybe DeVito should be here.
Apple is like a little bit closer up just because Cheese Nips is like just a shit character, but
it's fun. That's another BI down here. Okay. I'm not, I don't hate this so far. All right.
Does anybody need to come down or up from F? Maybe the F. Okay. These are the, that's it.
It's done. I'm happy with it. This is D plus. I would put Frank Pizza in a D plus.
Vault coins probably at the bottom here. Not that I don't like vault coin, but
maybe up here. The apple should be up here. James, no, James Garfield is a president down here.
Andrew Jackereject is also a, also president, right? But the coolest one out of, out of all
the characters, because it's just, this is, it's like, I made him in Fallout. So it works. It
still works. Joop, Joop, Joop, Joop, Joop, Joop. What's going on? Where's Batboy? Down with pencil.
I do need to find out what the worst character that I ever is though. That's important. Okay.
Let's see. The Monopoly guy's got to come up way up here. I think that's all right. All right.
We did that. Looks pretty clean. The worst character ever. It's the mime. It is. There's no
context to this channel. There's no joke. At least these, like the sensor bar, Garfield,
Hitman. I played Hitman and it was fun. This is like a monster of a bunch of different other
characters that I had. Sluggo is, he's been around. The pencil sucks, but the Easter bunny. Oh,
it's going to be close. Okay. But the mime is not, what's the mime? This is a mime.
There's no joke there. It's just a mime. Every single character on this list came from
something or was made for a reason. This is another filler episode, but this is the kind
of filler episode that you tell your friends to skip. You say, don't watch that one. You can
just skip that one. Some filler episodes are great. That one, not so much. The pencil is,
I don't think the pencil belongs down here. I'm changing this category.
Let's look at that. Look at that. Look at how, look at that. Look through the eraser and the
length and the top. This is, that's a, it's a fun, that's fun. It doesn't belong down here.
It doesn't deserve its own category. I don't think so. Better than, it's better than a PM
and Danny DeVito and Sam and all the presidents. Okay. But who is the least worst character?
Just because I don't know who this is. I don't know. I'm going to put it down here.
No, but Hitman is just Hitman. I'm done. That's it. From the available characters. That's it.
Where does, take a screenshot. The pencil isn't in pencil tier. Yeah, I know.
It's missing key characters, but we, but I still did it. There. Just terrible.
Demon Lord's Araxas should not be grouped up with the mortals.
That's fine. Where's the snack one? Where's the next one? Snacks? Cereals? Oh, fuck yeah.
Cereals. Let's do cereals. Oh, fuck yeah. Does this have them all? I don't, I don't think it has
them all. Let me, let me, let me, let me, let me sniff this list for a second. No. Is there a
better one? Is there one with more? Is there one with more? This one best cereals? Is this one
better? All right. That's, that's more. That's better. Okay. I think I'm ready. All cereals.
There's, there's another one. I can't right click it. I can't click it. I can't click it. I got it.
All right. Hold on. Everybody relax. Hold on. This is all serious. Oh my God. S S S A B C D
Probably trash. What is that? Why? Why? How would that not be? Never had it. You're just guessing.
You're just saying that it's trash. I never had this before. Well, I also think that's trash.
That's not how it works. I'm deleting this one. Like, no, that's, that's, I've never had it
or it's trash. Here we go. Oh, this is a shredded wheat. Never had this. Shredded wheat. No, I never
had it. Frosted chocolate strawberry. I never had it. When it's going to go when, as they come in.
Frosted chocolate strawberry. Frosted shredded wheat chocolate. Shredded wheat. Shredded wheat.
Shredded wheat. Cheerios on crunch. Oat crunch. I've never had it. Cookie crisp. Now is this 1996
cookie crisp or is this 2019 cookie crisp? That's a big difference. 1995 cookie crisp is up here.
2019 cookie crisp is down here. I'm going to assume by the box art that this is like later,
like 2010 plus. Belongs down here. Maple bacon donuts. Who the fuck buys that cereal?
I don't think anyone's ever purchased that. Why would you buy that? Maple bacon donut cereal.
That's like between Captain Crunch, Cheerios. So you got Cheerios, Captain Crunch, Lucky Charms,
like Raisin Bran. Maple bacon donut. That's, you never, why would you pick this one? I've never,
no it's probably trash. Chicken and waffles. What are these? This is the same bullshit.
People might think this is unpopular opinion here. This is the same bullshit of potato chip
flavorings. Are we going down that road with cereals now? Oh this is ketchup mustard pickles
and dipped in acid and fiery red tomato. No, like I don't want that. Just give me fucking sour
cream and onion. Well this is mesquite barbecue chili lime bacon. All right. This is BLT flavored
potato. This is BLT flavored potato chips. That makes no sense. So it's a it's a mayonnaise and
lettuce flavored potato chip. Oh yeah you get the chicken and waffles cereal. We're going too far.
This cereal is called Good Friends. Cocoa Puffs. I'm gonna start at a B. Put it on the friend tier.
Wheaties. I don't buy, I don't buy Wheaties. I don't read Wheaties. Reese's Buffs.
See you later. Trix. See you later. Alphabet's never had it. These are apple cinnamon Cheerios.
They're okay. Apple cinnamon toast crunch. It's a fucking dumb potato chip flavoring.
Banana nut Cheerios. That sounds pretty good. Boo Berry. Up at B. Chips Ahoy. I've had it a
couple times but it was all right. Cinnamon toast crunch is god tier. Yes. Apple cinnamon toast
crunch is not god tier. Have you had it? I've had it. I've had it. Why is apple cinnamon Cheerios
C tier? Because that's Cheerios with apple cinnamon. This is this is fucking french
toast with cinnamon and apples on it. Which is actually fucking really really good.
Uh Kix. I used to love Kix actually. Kix and Pops. Is Pops on here? Blueberry Cheerios.
Now get this get this green ketchup. I don't want it. Shredded wheat. I don't I haven't I don't eat
these. Cocoa Pebbles. The thing about Cocoa, I'm gonna do both these right now. Cocoa Pebbles and
Fruity Pebbles. Um are we talking about the first 30 seconds? Or are we talking about the rest of
the time you eat the cereal? Because once you once you pour the milk in and you eat the cereal
it's like it's S. S. S. But after about 25 seconds it becomes something you want to just throw in the
trash. They just become hard boogers that you're eating. It's just individual boogers. That's what
they turn into. The shit that you pull out of your nose is what each every single pebble turns into
in about two minutes. I'm sorry but that's just I'm telling you how I feel. That's a big deal with
cereal. It is. Eat them dry. No eat them dry is like eating glass. No those can move. I'm just I
need to I have to see it first. Is this another one of those things where it's just it's doing
them all again twice? Why is it why am I happening to me? Golden Oreo. I've had Oreo always before
but not these ones. What's the difference? Marshmallow Fruity Pebbles. I'm gonna bump this up
just because. No I've never had it never mind. That sounds pretty good. Nilla. Never had it.
Nutter Butter Cereal. This is another thing with cereals is they just have they just put
cookies in a bowl. Cookie Crisp. Yeah I understand but I that's not that's not like good.
Putting putting like cookies in a bowl with milk on them. That's not a breakfast. Maybe that's why
they changed the recipe. Oreo Ore is they're very good though. They are insanely good. Peanut
Butter Fruity Pebbles. They're all gonna be on the same. They're not I can't get over it.
This is is this real? There's only one place you should ever put a Sour Patch Kid in your
fucking mouth and that's at a movie theater. A cereal for this shit. You better eat that at
the movie theater or there's no reason to buy that. Oh yeah that goes up here. They mass produced
they had to produce that. They had to been enough interest in that for them to make like 500,000
boxes of this. I don't need to taste it. Bran Flakes. I don't think we've ever had this brand
before. Honeycomb. I think I've had it a few times. It was all right. Cheerios Ancient Grains.
That's why that says ancient grains. Is that supposed to mean it's healthier because it's
using old spices or something? Or does it mean ancient grains like we've been storing them for
a long time? I haven't had it. Cheerios Protein. Never had them. Chex. I'm gonna have to I'm gonna
oh I don't buy Chex. I don't eat Chex. No. Belongs on the floor in your bathroom not in a cereal.
This tile motherfucking cereal. Get out of here. All right here we go. Chocolate Cheerios.
Um that doesn't sound very good but I haven't had them. Now this is Chocolate Lucky Charms.
I have had these I think once. They weren't as good as the regular ones. I like the regular
ones better but they weren't bad. We'll keep them here for now. Chocolate Toast Crunch.
That just doesn't make it. Cinnamon Toast Crunch. Chocolate Toast Crunch. What is Chocolate Toast?
Chocolate Toast to me is I guess when you when you Nutella on your toast or something.
Is that what it's supposed to taste like? Not for me. Cheerios Cereal. I haven't had it. Here we go.
Cinnamon Toast Crunch. It belongs up here. Nothing's est here yet. Not yet but it could be very soon.
Count Chocula is up here somewhere in C I think. Cotton Candy Crunch. That sounds disgusting but
I'm gonna buy it at the grocery store tomorrow. That sounds truly awful but I'm gonna get it.
Crunch Berries belongs up here and what what's with this? Wait oh this is the different trick.
Okay one of these tricks is I'm I know this. Okay so these the two tricks is one of them was
we want a healthier cereal and we want less dye in our cereals and we want it to be healthier and
no more colorings and make it like less sugar and then they did that as this one and and then
everybody had it and said no I don't want that give me the fucking colors back give me like the
sugar back and so they they ditched that and started doing the old one again. That's what
happened right? There was such an outcry about how gross and not colorful and not yummy and delicious
and sugary that this one was. The healthy one that everybody wanted. Give us a healthier alternative
to tricks. I want no food dye. Okay well here's one without food dye. Oh that looks like bird poo.
Give me the other one. I have never had it though. Fucking consumerists. Frank and Berry is it's
all right. I have two tricks is on the list. Yeah I know that that's the different the different
versions. This is this is the the new the one that the healthy one right. Go look it up that happened.
French Toast Crunch is better than Cinnamon Toast Crunch. In fact it might be the first S.
I think so. It's okay to be wrong. French Toast Crunch is insane. It's it's insane. It's really
good. That's really good. Cinnamon Toast Crunch is fucking good too. Cinnamon Toast Crunch is really
really good. I just think that French Toast Crunch is a little bit better. Just a little.
Cocoa Wheats. Never had it. Total. I've actually never eaten total. Frosted Cheerios.
Oh they're gross. I've had them a few times. It's not they're not good. They're not good.
Just eat Frosted Flakes. It's Frosted Flakes are better. They feel better in your mouth. They crunch
better. I don't like them. If you like them I'm glad you do. Maybe it's D-. I don't it doesn't
belong on like the movie candy box. Yeah but I'm not a big fan. Fruity Cheerios. Chocolate Peanut
Butter Cheerios. Haven't had them. Now here's a the issue here. This is Golden Crisp but where's
Smacks? Because they're the same cereal. One of them is just way better. And do you know which one
it is? Which one is way better? I'm glad we have some intelligent people in this chat. Smacks are
way better. So these are coming up at probably around like D plus C minus. Smacks are going to
be up at like B. Golden Grahams suffer from the same problem that Fruity Pebbles suffer from and
they get soggy in about 10 seconds. I have eaten Golden Grahams before and they taste great but
Golden Grahams are the worst offender for that. You will pour your milk on these fucking things.
Turn around to go get a spoon. Turn back around and it's porridge. It just did. I can't. I don't.
It's got to be crunchy. I don't eat cereal dry. I don't do that. But you have to do with Golden
Grahams and with some of these others. This is a tactic. I mean I did this a lot when I was in
college. Is you get a mug of milk and what you do is you have like a drinking mug. Take whatever
cereal you want. Sprinkle a little bit on the top. Like make a little top layer of cereal on top of
the milk in your cup and just like sip it and crunch it and stuff. Therefore you can keep putting
a top layer. Sip, crunch, top layer, sip, crunch. It works out really well. It's the only way I can
really eat those. Otherwise that's too much work. But then I get soggy cereal. I don't want to eat
that. Every time I get to the end of the... When you get like halfway down and it's just...
When your cereal goes like this, that's not good. You don't want to eat that. It's
it's not appetizing. Just eat it faster. No, you don't eat... What do you mean eat it faster?
No, you don't just wolf down food as fast as you can. I got to do this before I get soggy.
No, you want to eat and enjoy your meal. I don't eat cereal dry. I eat it wet with milk.
I usually put almond milk on it and that's not because I... That's a stomach and intestinal issue
that's not like a, oh I prefer whole milk. I just... I drink almond milk but I put almond milk on
because it's a stomach problem. Okay, okay. Lucky Charms Frosted Flakes. What? That's real?
Frosted Flakes Lucky Charms? I need to get these too. It's gonna... No way. I didn't make a new list.
I gotta add Roblo. This is called... This is gonna be the get next time at the grocery store list.
Yeah, like just order this. Wait, there's another one too, right? Okay. Any others on here that I
like... Do I want to eat? This is the next time I go to the grocery store. I'm gonna get these.
No, I'm not eating Sour Patch Kids. All right, Grape Nuts. I've not really had them. All right.
Honey Bunches of Oats. The only one I've had is with strawberries and it's very good.
I would put it somewhere in like high C, maybe low B. The rest of them I have not had.
Honey Bunches are good. Yeah, the Honey Bunches of Oats with strawberries. That's the one I've
ordered. The rest of these, yeah, I've never had them before. There's so many cereals.
Honey Bunches of Oats S'mores and Almonds. Get that. Kicks is already up here, isn't it?
Isn't Kicks already up here? It's just... What's the difference?
Honey Kicks versus what's this Kicks? Chocolate? Oh, no. I just had regular Kicks.
I've never had chocolate Kicks before. I don't know. All right, here we go. Time for a staple.
Here come the staples. Honey Nut Cheerios belongs up here. I would say Honey Nut Cheerios is...
There's so many options now that it's like hard to put that higher. All right. Where was I?
Honey Nut Cheerios Medley Crunch. I don't know if that is five or one. No. Honey Bunches of Oats.
This one, I haven't had it. Raisin Bran Crunch. Get that one. I've always wanted to eat it and
never have it. Frosted Flakes. They go up here. Just regular Frosted Flakes. No bullshit. Tony
the Tiger. They taste good. They're really, really, really yummy. They've been around for like 150
years. Like blacksmiths used to fucking eat this when they were making swords. So it belongs up
here. Crave. I don't think it's as high as A, but it's all right. Crave is like a little...
Crave is like a little disgusting though. It gets gross. Like anything that is filled with something
else. Something crunchy filled with this. It's usually... It's very hit or miss. I'm going to
put it below 2019 Cookie Crisp, I think. It's still good though. Still... And what is this doing all
the way down here? I'm going to put this one down because it's kind of taken up too much space.
You know that I haven't had these. Fruit Loops with Marshmallows. Man, they really are adding
marshmallows to everything, huh? Never had it. I don't really want it though. Frosted Crispies.
That's not the only SS tier that... Where is it? Is it on here? Where is Rice Crispy Treats
cereal? That's the highest on the whole list. It's mostly all cereals. There's no Rice Crispy
Treats cereal. Can I just pretend? Blind. Am I blind? Where is it? Rice Crispy Treats. It's
purple. Oh, fuck yeah. Rice Crispy Treats cereal is unstoppable. It is insane. What do you mean he
doesn't know? What do I not know? What's wrong with it? What's wrong with it? Rice Crispy Treats cereal
is so bad. No, it's not. So this is Frosted Crispies. Never had it. Apple Jacks is very...
It's very boring to me. It's boring. It's very boring. It doesn't do it for me. Now I've had
Frosted Mini Wheats. I've had the regular ones, just the default ones, which are these, right?
And they're pretty good. These I would eat dry. It's one of the only cereals I would eat dry
because you kind of have to. They're very good. It's good with milk. Yeah, I know it is, but I
would eat these dry. Why am I watching this? I don't even eat cereal. Cocoa Crispies last longer
than Cocoa Pebbles, so they're better. Measelicks. I don't know what it is. Frosted Mini
Wheats. I don't have, never had them. They're like little bites. Never had them.
Different flavors of little mini bites. All brand have never had any of these. Pops. Here we go.
The second of our S tier is Pops. Wait a minute. A Cracklin' Oat Bran. No, that's an old people's
cereal. Chocolate Frosted Flakes. I've never... Get them. Rice Crispies. They're too... That's
too default for me. I wouldn't... I would never... It's not trash, but I would never order them
because they're not... They're just too boring. Crispicks. Never had it. Some other weird version
of Crave that I've never had. Smart Start. Never had it. Raisin Bran. Belongs.
Somewhere up here, and I would say B. Not quite as good as a Cinnamon Toast Crunch, but it's still
good. Kicks. That's regular kicks, right? Yeah. This is just regular kicks, but these are great.
They're definitely at least A or B. I'm gonna put them in B for now. Any of these Maple Cheerios?
Mm-mm. Fruit Brute. Wait a minute. Hold on. There's an Oops All Berries. Get this. Is it... Is it
All Crunch Berries one? Oops All Berries. All right. I'm gonna put this in line of like where...
What I want the most. Captain Crunch is the best cereal. It is. It is the best cereal you can
possibly eat. There are... There are no other cereals that are worth eating more than just
regular Captain Crunch. None. Some of them come close, as you see. Not close enough. I just
teleport myself back to when I was like 12, and every one of those individual deep like earthy
corn tastes like starchy sweet flavorings. I know. I can feel it right now. I know what it
tastes like right now. I can taste it right now. Can you taste things in your head? I can taste
that right now. Perfect. I can... I feel it. Is it another one of those? Okay. Regular Cheerios.
I just don't... I want to... I don't want to... They're not bad. Look. I would put them high on D.
But they're... No. I don't... Look. You can get like... When there's... Okay. When there are
Honey Nut Maple Chocolate Frosted Oreos, why would you get the regular Cheerios? I don't know.
I mean, I guess they're... It's just... It's just cereal. Interesting. Because I'll like the...
I don't think I would even... If some... You know how people say,
oh, I wouldn't order it. But if you gave it to me and you're like, hey, you want a bowl of Cheerios?
I'd say, yeah. I don't think I would say yes. That's one of those scenarios. Like,
you got anything else in a very not disrespectful way. Oh, you want some Cheerios? Cheerios?
Like Mustard Box Cheerios? Or what are you talking about? Oh, yeah. Just Cheerios. I'm not a baby.
That's baby food. That's what babies eat. I'm a man. It's baby food. It's very good baby food.
It's really good for you. But I'm old. I'm too old for Cheerios. Or like the guy with the salt
and pepper hair that's sitting there eating the bowl, talking to what I assume is his like
five-year-old daughter. What are you doing, Dad? I'm just working on my cholesterol, honey.
And then the commercial ends. Doesn't matter. That's the whole commercial.
Those are the two scenarios. Which, by the way, I could tell you. I know that like, oh, eating
Cheerios every day will lower your cholesterol. But no, no, no. That's not what it is. It's eating
Cheerios every day and having a good healthy lifestyle could lower your cholesterol. Right.
Okay. Yeah. Hey, don't eat a Big Mac. You won't clog your arteries. Okay. If you stop smoking
cigarettes, you might be able to run faster in a couple of years. All right. That's good to know.
So be healthy. All right. What's the point? The point is that it's just like, eat lettuce
and be healthier and you'll be healthier. It's not the lettuce that's doing it. It's the fact
that you live in a healthier lifestyle. Just be healthy. Yeah. Cheerios. Just be healthy, forehead.
Replace the fucking heart here with like the forehead. Drink dried sugar. What is this one?
I don't know. What's this one? Lucky Charms Magical Unicorn. Is Lucky Charms on here already?
It's not. Is there like just a regular Lucky Charms? I don't see the regular Lucky Charms anywhere.
Well, I'm just gonna say this is regular Lucky Charms. What is the cereal string?
Never. Lucky Charms, you just avoid all the fucking cheerio bits and you eat the marshmallows.
Everybody does that. And you end up with like 30 to 40 pieces of soggy, just beige cardboard that's
in the bottom. And you just like, you don't feel bad. You're like, eh, I kind of feel bad I didn't
eat that. It's all right. Peanut Butter Crunch is also up here pretty high. I would say somewhere,
I think it's better than Crunch Bears. But is it better than Frosted Flakes?
They both are. Frosted Flakes belongs down here. Okay. Just making sure. All right.
Fruit Loops. Regular Fruit Loops. I'm like, have I blinked? My eyes are getting so dry and watery
and hard. That was a complete oxymoron. My eyes are getting really dry. Fruit Loops.
Better than blueberry, but they're not. They're okay. They're all right.
Multi-Grain Cheerios. Somebody said if I didn't put this at at least A, they were going to
unsubscribe. I'm sorry. I don't, I've had them a bunch of times. They're just, they're just
regular Oreos. No, why do I keep saying Oreos? They're just regular Cheerios,
but some of them taste like pumpernickel bread. It's not a bad thing, but I don't
put fresh honey on them. But I'm like, I hope you're not, I hope you're still here.
Look, I put, I didn't put them down below in the trash category. I put them like right here.
They're definitely better than blueberry. In fact, blueberry should be at the bottom of D.
Like I, I don't even know. That's only up there because he's friends with Count Chocula.
You know what I mean? He's like, he's like sapping some of the clout from Count Chocula.
That's the only reason why he's there. I'm going to, he's coming down. This is like part of Count
Chocula's entourage. Where's the other one? Yeah. The Count Chocula entourage is not as good as
Count Chocula. It's cereal nepotism. Yes, that is exactly right. So we're going to put Count
Chocula where you belong. These are both the same cereal. They just tell you, it just, they just say
it's a different flavor on the box. All they have to pay for is like the art and the boxwork. Yeah,
no. I mean, Frankenberry is kind of good. I would say of like the Count Chocula fucking like princes,
Frankenberry is next in line for throne, I think. Once Count Chocula gets like fucking killed,
it's like next in line. Here comes Frankenberry. Cereal nobility. Yeah. Once like the throne gets
overthrown, like the English come in, then yeah, Frankenberry. I don't, I've never had any of these.
Apple Jacks is the same thing as Apple Jacks. They're the same cereal. So this comes back down
to here to right. It's the same cereal. There are so many like cinnamon toast, cinnamon apple
jack. There's so many of those. Everybody has their own version of cinnamon crusty apple crusts
that it's hard. They blend together and they all have a green box. They have a green and red box.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Green and red box, cinnamon, apple, apple cinnamon flavoring.
Hold on a minute here. Wait, wait, wait. Apple cinnamon toast crunch is green box,
green and red. Apple Cheerios, apple cinnamon is green box.
Come on. They're all, they're all green boxes with red letters and they're all
apple fucking cinnamon flavoring. Sour Patch. Apple, it's too much apple. It's too sour.
Don't you get it? Apples are sour. It's a green apple, green box. That was great. J. Jonah Jameson.
Yummy Mummy. I don't, I don't want it. All right. I definitely, I've never had it before,
but I don't think I want like, I'm not tall enough to see over the table frosted flakes.
It's supposed to be big and strong. That's, what's that saying? What's this? Rice,
Rice Krispies. What is that? That better be an apple fucking flavoring. Is it apple cinnamon?
Tell me it is. Tell me that's apple fucking cinnamon. I've had frosted flakes with marshmallows.
They're very bad. Too sugary. Way too sugary. Frosted flakes are so sugary to begin with.
And then the flavor from the marshmallow, it's too much. It is. I was so excited for these.
I remember being like, holy shit, that's so awesome. And it's just too much. It's too fucking much.
It's worse than movie theater food. No, it's not. I have, I'm, look, I'm just placing them
right now and then I'm going to go through and we're going to figure it out. Yeah. These,
they're not, they're not that good. They really aren't. Not, not to me. I've never had these.
Kellogg's corn flakes. Well, Kellogg's corn flakes, I don't think are trash,
but they're just unfinished frosted flakes. They're default character creator cereal. So
I'm going to, they have to be below frosted flakes. They're not bad though. Corn flakes are good. Like
just corn is good. When it's mashed up and like mob, like rocked up, it's when it's smushed up
and then hardened and baked. I don't know how they make cereal. How do they make cereal?
How do you, they take, they take corn and they crush it up and like smash it up into a paste
and they like smear it over a long baking sheet and then they put it in the oven and then they
hit it with a fucking hammer when it comes out and then they put that in a box. I don't know how they
made, I don't know how, I don't know how corn flakes are made. It's just magic. I don't know.
You're exactly right. Thank you. It's good to be right. Why is front? No, okay. Should this
belong on the movie theater tray? They're not good, but anything compared to Sour Patch Kids
has to be terrible. In fact, this is so bad that it almost needs its own tier because I'm afraid
to put anything else down here because it is a direct correlation and almost competitor
to how gross this cereal is. Okay. Carrot Cheerios. I've never had them. What is that?
Peach Cheerios. Okay. Running out of fucking fruits to like make your cereal themed after.
Fiber one. I don't eat any of these. I don't, I've never had any of them.
Never had any of them. Boys and girls. Yoink. Can I do his voice? Can I do the voice? Let me,
hey, let me, hold on. Hey kids, have some smack cereal. Oh yeah, smack cereal. Is that close?
Let's find out. How do I, I need to give me like a video right now. It's something like that.
Everybody have one. What? Let me, I'll just do it. What? Oh, everybody have one.
Everybody got one. Smack cereal ad. Here we go. Hey, what do kids think about my catalog smacks?
Sorry, Digga. I think we all have to agree. They look kind of weird.
Very scary. Scary looking. Honey smacks are the fun tasting part of a.
No, no, no, no, no, no. That's not the right one. Here's another, here's, here we go.
I had it close. No, I can't do it. It's been too long. I've been talking for too long.
Just do Mark Simpson. Pretend I did it. I had it right. Raisin Bran. I already put Raisin Bran,
but what's his frosted flakes? Banana cream. Holy, really? Get that tomorrow.
Banana cream frosted flakes. That sounds really good. Wild berry fruit loops.
You just change the food dye and that's all you did. I don't want it.
None of these. I'm not going to order them. I don't want them. These are doubles anyway,
so don't matter. Pop tart cereal. I'm not interested. I really am not at all. I'm not interested. I'm
not. I know people are going to be mad about that. Lucio? Lucio O's? You can, can you,
you can buy, this is like on the shelves? What are, what are they? Is it like Cheerios?
It's a gamer cereal. I've never had it and I don't think I'm going to buy it. I've never seen that
before. That's probably only in select locations. Strawberry crispies. I kind of have to try those.
Peeps cereal. Goodbye. Get out. Out. Out. Peep. No. Awful. Raisin bran crunch. Is that just regular
raisin bran crunch? Because it's really good if it is. I lost it. There it is. No. Where is it?
I lost it. Where'd it go? Where the fuck did it just go? Raisin bran crunch. Second row?
That's the third row. That's not the second row. This is up here in A. It's awesome. Raisin bran.
Red, white, and blue crunch. Is this like a Fourth of July crunch?
I've never had it, but I mean it's crunch berries, right? Sprinkled donut crunch. Sprinkled don't.
All right, get that tomorrow. I want to try that. That sounds weird. What is that? Strawberry,
strawberry what? Why is this upside down? Why does it look like it's a packet that you
rip? Is this like a cereal bar? Strawberry, what does that say? Is this a cereal bar? Is this a
cereal cereal? Yeah, no holiday crunch. That's strange. It's just a bag. Well, I don't really
want that. I don't know what that is. Strawberry cheesecake crunch or whatever. Same with this one.
What is it? Sugar cookie toast crunch. No, that's bullshit. You can't call everything French toast.
Toast crunch. Candy corn toast crunch. Sugar cookie toast crunch. French toast crunch.
Is it toast or is it a cookie? What the fuck is it? Just have it be sugar toast crunch or cookie
toast. Sugar toast. Buttered toast crunch. That's a better name. Like why? Sugar cookie toast crunch.
Peanut butter pops. I never had them. Hostess has a honey bun cereal. Oh, that's gross.
A bunch of mini honey buns. You've eaten one honey bun before? They're delicious and then you get a
stomach ache. While you're eating it, it's the best thing ever, but then for some reason you just
feel bad. I'm going to try it. Wait, the little powdered doughnuts? Is this cereal? Oh my god.
I want to try that too. I'm going to try these. Sardine toast crunch. Pumpkin spice.
No, I don't want like a latte cereal. Okay, the rest of these I haven't had, so say goodbye to
these. This is what we should be concerned with up here. Try them on stream. I mean, I could.
There's a lot there. How many cereals am I buying? I have to eliminate some for that list.
All right, most importantly, let's see. Captain Crunch is definitely up there. Rice crispy
treat cereal is definitely up there. Too best. French toast crunch. Honey made s'mores and
honey smacks? I don't think belongs there. Reese's puffs I think are up there too. A high two.
I would say Captain Crunch peanut butter crunch is a superior peanut butter flavored peanut
buttery kind of cereal than Reese's puffs. I like the flavor of the peanut butter from the Captain
Crunch one. Trix is not better than any of these. Cinnamon toast crunch is probably better than
pops. Raisin band crunch is probably better than pops. Pops is probably better than crunch berries,
but honey smacks are probably better than crunch berries, and Trix are not better than
crunch berries. Therefore, this list is correct. Raisin band's gonna drop. Raisin brand's dropping
down. Raisin brand crunch is already up there. This is the cooler one. Again, this is the unfinished
one. Oh, this is regular Trix. This is fruity shapes Trix. Which one's better? Fruity shapes.
Get this out of here. Honey nut cherry is the worst. That's a B minus though. That's still very
good. Would I put cocoa puffs in front of Frosted Flakes? No, I wouldn't. I would not. Justify Trix
being higher than a C, because Froot Loops are a C, and Trix are just a 10 times better version
of Froot Loops. It's the same cereal except that this one's just better. The reverse is true.
Thank you Concrete Car for the five community subs. I think I missed subs earlier too. I was
too engrossed. But thank you Concrete Car for the five community subs. Thank you.
Fruity Pebbles, Froot Loops, and Trix are all the same market. They're all the
sugary, fruity cereals that don't taste like fruit. They taste kind of just like candy.
These ones taste like candy. These ones taste like bread. And these ones taste like sugary,
yummy fruits. Now do you want a bread flavored fruit snack? Or do you want, you know, like a
candy? Or do you want a lighter, crispier, not even close? Back in the medieval days we ate
bread cereal. No, back in the medieval days you ate like an onion and like you put an onion
into a boiling bowl of water and like ripped up a bunch of bread and put it in there too and boiled
it for like four hours. Sometimes there'd be a rabbit in there. And that was a, that was awesome
if you had that. That's a French onion soup. Where do you think it came from?
All right. I, I am not going to let Chad influence me. I think Trix is a very, very
just good cereal. I would put Trix up here with, changing my mind. This belongs in front of Trix.
It does. It really does. I'm not going to let you, I'm not going to let you guys
influence me. It's still, that went from an A minus to a B plus, vice versa. Oreo O's,
it's just too much though. They're very good, but you can only eat one bowl of Oreo O's a week,
or it's too much. And for that reason, I'm up. But they're very, very, very good. I've never had
these before. Why are they up here? Get them tomorrow. Banana, banana nut Cheerios, banana
cream frosted flakes. Okay. This is how I do these lists. Are Trix better than Cocoa Puffs?
Yes or no. Are Trix better than Kix? Both got the, they've got the same name. They both
have Ix in their name. Which one is the better Ix? Trix. Are Kix better than Honey Bunches of
Oats with strawberries? No. Are Kix better than Mini Wheats? Frosted Mini Wheats? Yes.
Are Frosted Mini Wheats better than Honey Nut Cheerios? No. Are Frosted Mini Wheats better
than Oreo O's? Yes. There's your list. B. Done. Is Co-chocula? I don't need to say it. You just,
you know the rule. Okay. Is Cocoa Puffs better than Lucky Charms? Yes. Is Lucky Charms better
than Honey Bunches of O's? No. Is Honey Bunches of O's better than Lucky Charms? Yes. Okay.
It was, it was the branding. The branding fucked with me. It's the branding. It's the same brand.
It's the same thing. This is, this is a, this is a knockoff of each other. Some, you could have a
lawsuit. One of them could sue the other one. They've got the same opening mouth. They've got
the same, like zoom in. They've got the same, like it, somebody could get sued. It's the same
branding box that fucked up my brain. I've been on this single list for an hour. It's very important.
This is an incredibly important list. Why are Rice Krispies S.S. tier? That is Rice Krispies
Treats Cereal. That's not just regular Rice Krispies. Regular Rice Krispies is down here.
That's a Rice Krispies Treats Cereal. Okay. I think I'm happy with this. I think, yeah. Now it's
Krave is, no. Chips Ahoy. It's just Cookie Krisp, but with an exclamation point on it.
Honeycomb is good. Fruit Loops, no. Get them down here. Golden Crisp is probably better than these.
Apple Cinnamon Toast. I don't like those, but they're not, I wouldn't put them down here.
Maybe I would. I think I would. I don't eat these. Like I, I don't know why I'm putting them up here.
All right. One step at a time here. All right. So we got another thing that I just figured out
right here. Count Chocolate is just a much better version of Lucky Charms. It's just, it's like this,
it's like the, it's like the yin and the yang of cereals. It's, I like this one better. What are we
talking about? Count Chocolate is like little fucking pieces with marshmallows. This is little
pieces with marshmallows. They're the original little pieces with marshmallows cereal. Count
Chocula had the, the, the crispy little like bready pieces and the marshmallows. Lucky Charms had the
crispy little bready pieces in the marshmallows. What other cereal had that? What other cereal had
the marshmallows with the, the crispy puffs? Those are the two originals. One of them's chocolate.
Yeah. That's why I said it's, it's like the opposite, but they're like this, they're the
same like cereal, but one is opposite of the other. It's like a mirror. These are the original
fucking characters. Yeah. They've, yeah. They've got like, they add marshmallows to every cereal now.
Oh dear. Fruity Pebbles with marshmallows. Oh, Frosted Flakes with marshmallows.
This is the original too. Sorry guys. That's the way it is. I like the, this one better. Donut
Steel? What's Donut Steel? Imagine thinking Kix is a B, but Fruity Pebbles is a D.
It's the soggiest fucking cereal in the world. I wanted to do a third party test to see what
the soggiest damn cereal is. It's going to be Fruity Pebbles. I like my cereal soggy. It's,
is this your tier list? Whose tier list is this? I like it like this. Whose list is this?
It's my list. This is not your list. Go make your list. I would love to see it. This is my
cereal list. I don't like my cereal soggy. Therefore Fruity Pebbles is down here. What's,
what's going on here? Whose list is this? Getting me heated over fucking sugar in a box.
It's all dog shit anyways. From A to B, from S to D, these are all, you don't eat a banana.
Eat a fucking fruit. Have a salad for breakfast. Don't eat these. Don't eat Cocoa Puffs for
breakfast. What the fuck? Why would you do that? Eat an apple. Eat a pear. They're all like the same
tier. Just stretched out a little. See these, these aren't even on here. Because I'm a degenerate
fuck that doesn't eat the good ones. This, this is like just an accordion of bad cereals.
And that's why I, the Captain Crunch is the best. Cut his bike. I got blueberries on this list. Okay.
If you want to criticize something, criticize the fact that I don't eat like whole grain cereals.
All like these good nice whole grain oat cereals are down at the fucking bottom. I've never had
them, but I've eaten the fucking Captain Crunch entourage like a thousand times. Somebody just
gave subs. Thank you modest narcissist for the five community subs. Like brand flakes.
You should be more concerned at my, like I am between the ages of eight and thirteen cereals.
We, that, that should be more concerning. Actually, well honey, honey, not Cheerios.
And regular Cheerios, if I was a responsible functioning adult would be up here.
But no, it's down here. Anyways, I'm going to go on with my cereal list. That just made me think
about my health a little bit. So these are going to get bumped up a little. That made me concerned
about my list. Just wanted to move them up just a little bit because I'm a little concerned about
my health now about like Crunch Berry, Captain Crunch. It makes up at least every top tier
at least once. I probably should bump up multi-grain Cheerios a little. Yeah, pops are on here.
Come on. Putting higher cereals up on your list is not going to improve your health.
All right. Now that we've cleared that up, we've gotten that out of the way. Let's, let's continue.
Put these on the order list because I don't want them. Oreos at B is a travesty.
I'm drinking coffee at 10 o'clock at night. Health. I know you, I know you love some of these cereals.
I do too. And for that reason, I'm just, I'm kidding. I'm kidding. D tier. Now,
Lucky Charms really is not that good. Multi-grain Cheerios and Cornflakes are definitely not better
than, than Raisin Brin. Cornflakes actually should be somewhere down here.
Crave should be down here. I think this is the new recipe. I don't like it. All right. I'm happy
with this. Now I am. Now I am. Now I'm, now, now I'm happy with this. Now I am. Yeah, I think so.
Okay. This is the D list. This is cereals that I, I still think are all right, but I don't really
buy because they're just, they're too much of a pain in the ass to eat or they're too bland for me.
Guys, I gotta say something here. Real important. I put Fruity Pebbles down on the D list.
I didn't scream in your mother's face. It's, it's the same. I took, I'm finishing my list.
Wheaties. They're fine. Coconut. Fruity Pebbles. I don't want them. I don't want these. What are
they? Oh, the Tweedledee and Tweedledum. They can stay where they are. Golden Grahams. Probably a
little bit better. Probably Golden Grahams is probably better than all these. You know what?
Golden Grahams is definitely better than all of these two. I, I was, I went, I jumped that too
quick. Golden Grahams is really, really good. The only issue I have is like they get soggy in 10
seconds, but the 10 seconds that you get to eat them, they're fucking, they're really, they're good.
It belongs up here. Why is Cheerios a D? No, no, it belongs there. That's like D minus though.
I would probably rather eat Cheerios. Yeah, I'd rather eat Cheerios than Frosted Cheerios.
Hell-conscious guy. Notice how, noticing pattern. I just don't really like Cheerios.
Really that much at all. Rice Krispies are probably better than these two meme cereals.
It's weird because I've probably eaten these two cereals less than the amount of times I've seen
it on Adult Swim. So there's, there's a reason why it's down here. Apple Jacks is A tier.
For you, maybe. But hmm. Foot Captain Crunch in the trash tier. Where's the Mario cereal? The
Mario cereal wasn't on here. If you watch the commercial for Apple Jacks, it'll be S tier.
I think that's the list. I think that's it. These, this is a pretty, look,
look at the first three rows. The, here's the thing. Everybody's first two or three rows are
going to be kind of similar. Everybody, every other cereal in like B to D is super personal
opinion. It's all just personal opinion, right? Everybody fucking knows. Everybody on earth knows
that Cinnamon Toast Crunch is a great cereal. Raisin Bran Crunch is a great cereal. Pops,
Smacks, Crunch Berries, Frosted Flakes, these are all A. Everybody knows that. Everybody knows that.
This down here is what you get to, like personal opinion. Pops is a, how could you not, Pops,
Pops is one of the most unique cereals. It's, Honey Smacks and Pops are not just
toasted fucking corn with marshmallows in it. It's not just like a circle that tastes like bread.
Honey Smacks tastes wildly different than anything else. Pops tastes really wildly different than
anything else. Captain Crunch tastes wildly different than anything. Let me tell you what
cereals taste exactly the same, okay? Ready for me to blow up this whole scenario here?
These are the cereals that taste exact identical to each other. Ready? These, one, two, these two.
You know, the idea is that they all taste, they all taste pretty similar except for like three of
them. These two, these two, these three, these like four, all the Cheerios that have different
like fucking seasoning packets on them. It's still Cheerios. They still taste the same. This is just
a mirror. Look, they taste different. That's all I need to know. Crave is too low. All right,
you know, somebody said Crave is too low. It's going up here. Honey Smacks tastes
different than anything else. Do a cigarette tier list. Oh yeah, marbles. They're all belonging to
trash. Can I put them all down here? All right, please, can we just agree? Can we agree on
something? This is, guys, this is a cereal list. This is like British Parliament right now.
Can we all agree on one thing? Sour Patch Kids cereals should be removed from shelves.
Like we, come on, like why would it be there? That's like why? And peeps, that's what, no.
And these are just not very good. But Sour Patch Kids, we can all agree on that. I'm good. I got
my list. I'm happy with it. I think it's good for me. That's my, those are my favorite cereals.
In the comments section below, write out your favorite cereals. What is this? Annoying Orange
characters. I'm not doing that one. Pasta rankings. Ben and Jerry's ice cream flavors. I don't think
I've had enough of them to be able to give an opinion. Fruit tier list. All right, do you
got a fruit? I'll give you the fruit tier list. I will. What is it? Is there actually like a big,
a nice good fruit tier list? I'll do it. I'm gonna do it quick. Jelly Belly flavors. Don't even need
the list. Every single one F. Toasted Marshmallow S. Pick them all out and put the other, like just
give them to somebody else for like a present. Take, here's the tactic. Take out all the toasted
marshmallow ones, eat them, reseal it and give it to somebody for a present. All right, fruit tier
list. I'm getting linked to a lot of these. Give me the one with like the most amount of options.
Okay, let's link that. All right, this is apparently for, get a screenshot of that.
Oh, you know, get a screenshot of that because I get a screenshot of this because I need to know
what I'm gonna get tomorrow. Especially this part. The list is too big. So now that you got that
screenshot, thank you. Here's the actual list. There you go. Okay, this is fruits coming up.
Okay, this one shouldn't be too hard. This is only mainstream fruits. I didn't, I wasn't aware that
they were underground. It's like indie dev fruits. Sorry, these are, well we're only doing AAA fruits
today. Okay, I am a citrus kind of guy. People are gonna get so mad about this stuff.
I'm just like opening up all avenues of attack is what I'm doing. Boy, hold on a minute. This is
important. Is this eating the fruit? Or is this the flavor of the fruit? Well, is it eating the
fruit? Because some fruits taste all right, but they're gross to me. Eating it. Okay, fuck,
because I think I love oranges. I love orange juice. I just, I don't like eating an orange.
I think they're disgusting eating them. You get like orange gristle. I hate oranges. I hate eating
oranges. The white like gristle. That's gonna change everything. I'm gonna go with flavor.
Like the way that it tastes. I don't, what's this one? Is that a tomato? What is that? I don't know
what that fruit is. It's a pumpkin. That's not a pumpkin. Lemons are the best fruits.
Lemon is fucking unbelievable. Guess what? So is, no I'm changing that. Pineapple is my favorite
fruit. Lemon is my favorite like fruit flavor. Lemon and water. A squeeze of lemon. Lemon
flavoring. That like tart, sour, citrusy lemon flavor is my favorite flavor besides pineapple.
I am a, I am a, I'm a like kind of fruit guy. It's got to be like citrusy and fresh,
refreshing. I'm gonna make a lot of people mad with a couple of these. Disgusting. Absolutely
fucking revolting. Not because these, how many times, eating berries. You, it's like eating sand.
You crunch on this like, like a fucking hard sand. Try and blend them up. It doesn't work.
You're drinking sand. You're eating sand. Those seeds in berries are the most obnoxious things.
It's like eating fucking popcorn kernels. You said flavor. I did say flavor, but sometimes you
got to think about like the horrible experiences you've had. I've had a horrible experience eating
blackberries before, right, over raspberries. What are these? Yeah, I've had a horrible experience
eating these. Flavor-wise, they're good, but I can't. I'm gonna leave them there for now.
Cherries. Bananas. Bananas and smoothies are amazing. Bananas, they're great. I love letting
bananas rot, almost to the point where they're rotting, and then eat them. Some of you people
will know what I'm talking about. Some of you guys here will know. Right before the banana starts to
get really, really kind of ripe, overripe, is when I'd like to eat them the most. Uh, and by the way,
where's your mother? Because I'm gonna scream in her face. What are these? Watermelon. Ew,
ew, gross, gross, gross, gross, gross. Worst. How do I have, no, where's the worst? I gotta make like,
disgusting tier. I have to make awful tier. Add a row below. No, no, no, no, no. Disg- awful, awful,
awful. Hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate. F. Grapefruits taste like stomach acid.
You know how, so my mother used to eat these. My mother would cut a grapefruit in half,
and she would put a little, uh, spork with, you know, the spoon that has little, little, uh,
ridges on top, and she would eat it half a grapefruit. And it's like, oh, okay, you're
gonna eat half a grapefruit. But every time before she went in with it, you know, went in with the
spoon, she would cover the top of the half with sugar. And apparently that was like the way to
make it taste like, worth eating out of the half. If you have to add sugar to fruit, I don't think
it's worth eating. You have to add something on top. Well, it would only taste good if I put
fucking a bunch of salt on it. No. Grapefruit juice is also disgusting.
I'm sorry, I'm upsetting a lot of people, but that's the way it is. Where's kiwi? Done. What is this
corn? What is that? Lime? Weirdly enough, lime not as good as lemon to me. Belongs up there. What is
that, coconut? Actually, I hate coconut. I love coconut juice. I like coconut milk, coconut water,
but coconut. I don't really like coconut eating it. It's gonna be bad. What the fuck is this?
Is it ice cream? Is that Oreo? Is that cookies and cream ice cream? I've never, I've never eaten that.
Grapes? Grapes can be up here as long as they're frozen. I don't like eating regular grapes.
If they're frozen, I like them. But the reason why I don't like eating grapes is because my brother
told me a story one time about how, uh, watch out when you eat grapes because there could be
spiders in them. And that just freaked me out enough to put them down to be. But frozen grapes,
I think are amazing. Strawberry? Eh. Are you ready to have everybody hate me? I'm gonna get off camera
for this one. Apples suck. There's only one apple that I actually will eat willingly, and that's a
Macintosh apple. Soft flesh apples. I heard something over there. What was that? It has to
be crispy. I don't look, I don't like apple pie. I don't like apple fritters. I don't like apple
jacks. I don't like cinnamon apple cereal. I don't like apple. I don't like apple pie. I don't like
anything with cooked apples in it because every time I eat something with cooked apples, if it's
apple pie, oh, whoa, oozy, yummy, hot apple pie. I love that filling until you get the piece of the
apple and it's like an old person sucking up a fucking prune. It's like a slippery slug, a hot
slug that you... No, disgusting. I don't like that. I don't like it. I'm sorry. I'll eat Macintosh
apples. I like blueberry iced coffee. Blueberries are right here. I just put it at A. Hot apples
taste like a warm slug. I don't want to eat, I don't want to do that. I would eat a Macintosh
apple right now if you brought it in here. I'd be like, okay, this is great. I like this. I like
being able to like, and it's pretty juicy and flows down your face. I will say the green apples
are better than red apples. Melon, listen, melon is the fruit that you dig around in the fruit cup
to eat the fruit that you want to eat. Once you run out of the good ones, you go,
oh, well, I guess there's melon in here. I just, I just saw it for the first time tonight. I saw
go to hell. Go to hell. What is this? Oh, is this a Clementine? Tangerine. All right. This is
important. Nectarine. Oh, this is peach. This one's nectarine, right? Nectarine belongs up here.
Peach is really close behind. In fact, nectarine may have to take the spot of watermelon.
Nectarines are incredible. You want, remember I told you like the Macintosh apple, when you bite
into it, it's like that, if you get a ripe nectarine, the thing, it's as if somebody
fucking just like sprayed, like sprayed a hose in your face. It's like, it's incredible. It's,
it's okay. Nectarines are what gushers the fruit snack we're trying to emulate very poorly, very
badly. You get that like super soft bite with that flow of like fruit juice down into your mouth.
Oh my God. I'm good. Where's the list that I can put this on and get these tomorrow at the grocery
store? Peaches are gross. Peaches are not, I don't think peaches are as good as nectarines.
I still think they're good though. Sometimes I pretend to be like a bee when I eat them too.
Like this is like, this is, this is what like a bee did this. And I'm like taste, I'm like eating
like nature bee. Like I'm a bee, like a nectar. Pears, it depends on what kind of pear, but I
usually like pears. Pears are better than apples. I don't know if I, yeah, pears, I probably eat
blueberries over pears. The rest of these, I don't know what these are. This is other orange. This is,
I don't know what that is. What is this one? Is it papaya? This is a mango? Which one's a mango?
What's the corn one? It's a permission, permission, permission. What is it?
I don't, I don't really, I'm not like into it. Mango and papaya, which one of these is which?
I like mango salsa. I don't eat mangoes though. A little too slimy for me, a little too slippery
and slimy. When you like cut into, you have like mango slices, it's like covered in ice. You like
pick it up, it just slips out of you, it's too slimy and slippery. I do like, I do like, I need
some more down at sea. Okay, let's do it. Best fruit on earth is a pineapple. Fresh cored pineapple
that is ripe. It cannot be compared to anything, anything. It's every single thing you want in a
fruit. It's really good for you. It's really fucking delicious. It's got an incredibly distinct flavor
and it has an enzyme in it that eats your fucking flesh from the inside out.
Fucking sick. That's like cool. Bad ass, right? Kiwis on the other hand are lighter. I could eat
like five of these and be like, oh that was pretty good. Cut them up into little tiny thin slices,
like I'm talking like deli thin. Lay them out and just pick them up and eat them like little
cucumbers. They're great. You can eat the skin. I don't, too fuzzy, too, too fuzzy for me.
But I do love kiwis, so I think that that's good for me. Two of the best fruits. Lemons is just
top tier flavor for me. I would put nectarine in front of it, but I'm not going to because I
drink lemon water all the time. If I drink a glass of water, I usually have a little lemon squeezer
and I just squeeze like a half a lemon in the water and drink it sometimes, maybe like once in a while.
I just like that. I like the taste. I like the way it makes you feel.
Where do plums go? Plums are down here, but they might not be there forever. This is just
a preliminary. I had to do it. So yeah, watermelons. As you can tell by this list,
I'm really into those fruits that are really easy to bite into. So you bite into them and
your teeth just kind of melt right there. It's like having like meat off the bone, like a barb,
like a smoked brisket. These two are the smoked brisket of the fruit world. It's tender,
your teeth go right through it, and it's just juicy and delicious. Yes, that's why they're up
here. Peach is pretty close, but I like nectarines better than peach. We already described that. This
is tangerines. I would probably put tangerines down this way. More close. No, this is orange.
Tangerines are already down there. I like orange probably more than banana, but I like blueberry
more than I like banana, and I like banana more than I like pear. Strawberry and lime.
This is where you get into... I like it. I would eat it every day. I would. I would eat any of
these pretty much any day. Cherries, too much work. You know what I mean? Too much work. You
got to eat it. You don't swallow the fucking seed. There's a giant core in the middle,
and you got to work around it, and then spit it out. What do you do with it? Spit it out in your
hand? Too much work. I'm not like a big cherry flavor kind of person. Just pull it out on your
date. Oh, so what is it that you do for work again? I'm a scientist. I work for NASA. What?
No, come on. What is this one again? I don't remember. That's why it's down here. It's a
mango, papaya. Decent flavoring. I like the flavorings better than these.
Look, seed does not mean bad. Seed does not mean bad. Seed is fine. I like cherry coke,
and I like grenadine syrup, but that's bullshit tier. That's not real. Now here we go.
Raspberries are definitely... I really don't even know what the cookies and cream thing
even tastes like, so I can't even really put it on the list, but it's not F because I don't
really know. I definitely would rather eat all of these before I would eat an apple.
You gave me a choice. You said, hey, here's a bunch of raspberries or apples. Eat one.
I would be like, oh, raspberry. I'll take one. I avoid these at all costs. In fact,
that's how it should look. I think that's pretty accurate for me. Where's the pomegranate? It's not
on this list. Although pomegranate would be somewhere in front of cherry because I feel
like they're like... Plus pomegranate, the inside of it looks fucking weird. It's weird. It's like
a bunch of strange scattered egg sacs inside with seeds in it, like spiders. There's spiders in
there. Those could be spider eggs. That's all I know. My brother told me that one time. That's
why I can't eat it. Okay, so there it is. Any more brain busters? Cheeses? I'll do cheeses.
How long is this stream? We're still going. Have I eaten enough cheeses for this to work?
I'm not going to do annoying orange characters. They're all annoying. Is there just one bar that
just is annoying on it? Do soda. I could all do soda. Give me a good soda one. Chips? We'll do
soda. I'm talking a good soda one. Let's check this one out. Soda. That was fruits. Here comes
soda. Oh, this is a lot. Okay, I do appreciate they have it all set up already. The trash and
I don't care. I haven't had it. I don't care. Let's go. This is... I don't think I've had that,
but I love 7-Up. 7-Up I think is better than Sprite by a pretty decent margin, I think.
Dr. Pepper has fallen off from me in recent years. A&W root beer is the best root beer. Cream soda,
I used to love it, but I think it's disgusting now. When I was 15, 16, 17 years old, I was obsessed
with this stuff. But now it almost just tastes like... it just tastes like they got halfway
through and they stopped making the soda. They added the water, the carbonation, and a bunch of
sugar caramely kind of sugar flavor, and then they didn't. They stopped. There needs to be
something else. It's weird. It doesn't do it for me anymore. Barks root beer. I don't know if it's
better than A&W, but it's still all right. That's how we drink it. Barks is good. Is this some water?
What is that? This is just water? If it's water, then I'm gonna... I'm just gonna pretend this is
water. It belongs up here. I have an ad. I don't know what that is. There's no way you could never
in your whole life have never tried water. You getting water accidentally in your mouth in the
shower counts. There's no way anyone's never had water. You'd be dead. You would just die.
You would just turn into bones. It'd be dead. I don't really know what that is, so it's off the
list. Is this iced tea? I wish there was like a zoom in button. What is this? Is this iced tea?
This is not breast milk. I like... What does it say? It's called balls? I don't know what this is.
Balls. I don't... I don't know what this is either. Canada Dry ginger ale goes up here. I'm... This
is gonna be a deliberation here. It's gonna take me a while. Oh, fuck. Uh-oh. This is the real one
right here. Where does Pepsi go? Coke's better than Pepsi. Sorry. Like 44% of you now think that
I'm like talking to the devil every night before I go to bed. I now pray to the devil every night
before I go to sleep. To half of you guys know. Is this like steak sauce? Dads? Uh, no. Cherry
Coke? Not as good as regular Coke. Um, this is like... What is this? Like espresso Coke?
I don't think I've ever had that. Get this shit out of here. Stop drinking this. Honest to God.
Get the fuck out of here. Diet fucking Coke. Diet Pepsi. Just... No. Get... Don't stop. Don't...
Don't drink them anymore. No. A&W cream soda is better than this. Don't drink that anymore.
Like, I'm looking out for your health. Anymore diet sodas on this list? Do you see any? Because
they're going in the trash. These are just... These are fucking awful too. The Minute Maid
lemonade in the fucking jar. No, no, no. They're bad. No. These lemonades in the fucking... That
come out of the bottle are so over sweetened. It tastes like syrup. It's like lemon syrup. It's
not even like fucking... It's not even like drinking like refreshing, like, quencher. It's syrup.
You could cut this like three times. This is a lemonade concentrate. That's not lemonade.
You can make four lemonades out of this. Tastes good, but just save some money. Buy one of those
and then just cut it with water. Like at least 40% of it. It'll... You'll be like, oh wow, that's not
even that much of a difference. Trying to say I'm looking out for you. But both of them...
If this were... If this were younger teenage me, this would be up here. I am a sucker for
Shirley Temples. Mountain Dew Code Red is as close to a bottled Shirley Temple as you can get.
I love... If Shirley Temple was on here, I would put it up an S tier. They're so good,
but they're just so bad for you. But this is probably... Probably truly belongs somewhere down
here. Sprite. I actually prefer Sprite over any of the other amber drinks at this point,
besides root beer. Like I said, Dr. Pepper has fallen off a little bit for me.
This is... These are meme sodas. I don't want them. What is... Is this the same thing? Is this
vanilla Coke? Isn't this vanilla Coke too? They're both the same one, right?
Is this one different? Wait, is this the orange Coke? Is this the orange one? If it's the orange
one, it's going somewhere very specific. This is Coke Orange? Confirmed? This is Coke... Confirmed
Coke Orange? Confirmed Coke Orange? It's awful. Pepsi's already up there. RC Cola is... May as
well just be the same thing as all the other ones. But it's like the worst one of them all, I guess.
But it's cheaper though, right? Maybe I would drink it. Mellow Yellow is Mountain Dew.
And speaking of Mountain Dew, do you know where this has gone? Into the trash. This other Mountain
Dew. Crush Orange Soda. Somewhere up here. Sierra Mist. Somewhere up here. I don't know. What does
this one say? I don't... What's this one? Chucky Cheese? Chucky Cheese Soda? Wait, this is Baja?
This is Baja Blast? That's... It's better. It's good. Zoom in. No, I'm trying to exercise my eyes.
Chucky Cheese Soda. I've never had it. Fanta. Fanta is just kind of Orange Crush, but it's...
They're both essentially identical. There's no differences. I think one of them is a little
more syrupy. I think Fanta is a little syrupy for me. So I'll probably put it down. I don't
think I really want it. I'd rather get a Crush. I really don't like a Grape Soda. If I'm going
to get a Crush, it's going to be the Orange variant, not the Grape one. So I'm not a big fan
of Orange Grape Soda. I don't know what this is. This looks like Strawberry Soda, but I've never
had it. Jolt Cola. Don't drink it. Stop being fucking aware of it. Is this Cigarette Ashes in
Water? Oh, no. It's IVC Root Beer? Is this the Cream Soda? I haven't had this one before.
IVC Root Beer, though, is pretty good. I don't know if it's better than like... It's probably
on the same level as Barks. And these should be down a little more. I think I would rather
have like a Vanilla Coke than like a Root Beer. Although, I would probably... I would rather have...
Now, wait a minute. This is very specific. It's not in the can. I would rather have the Glass
Bottle IVC Root Beer than the can of Coke. I think so, because that doesn't come in a can.
Yeah, I would put normal vanilla in the trash. I like vanilla. What's wrong with vanilla Coke?
I like it. It's good. I don't drink it all the time, but sometimes you just... you're looking
for it and you want it. Squirt has not been available, I don't think, for like 25 years, so
Surge is another meme soda. I've never had it. Why is this an eBay listing? That's the best picture
you can find? Storm Soda. I've never had it. Mellow Yellow is... I think it's better than Mountain Dew,
but not by very much. I don't think it's better. Hold on. It's definitely better than this.
It's the Star Wars flavor. The rest of these are kind of the same... wait, but it's bottles. Ah,
I get it. Yeah, all right. So I'd rather have a bottle of Coke than a can of Coke.
Bottom tier for me is plastic bottles. Plastic Bottle Coke. Plastic Bottle Pepsi
is F tier. Can Coke, Bottle Coke is better for me. Plastic Bottle... no, I just... if I can...
I don't want it. It's going in the trash. I would never... I cannot think of any scenario ever,
and I mean actually ever, that I would buy a Plastic Bottle Pepsi. I wouldn't. I wouldn't do it.
That has to go in the trash. It's... I mean, Pepsi is obviously... I would drink Pepsi.
I wouldn't avoid Pepsi. That's fine. Whatever. But I'm not going to buy a plastic fucking bottle of
Pepsi. Look at chat. What? You have vanilla Coke in the trash. The one next to Coke is regular
caffeine free. I thought this was the orange one. What? You have vanilla in the trash. Orange isn't
on here. Well, I'm just going to pretend that's what they are. No, in my... that's fine. This is
vanilla Coke. This is orange Coke. It's in the trash. That's fine. We can use our own list.
Here, look. This is vanilla, and just pretend that this is orange Coke. It's caffeine free Coke.
That's fine. I would put it in here anyways. Just, yeah, play pretend. All right. Hold on.
I'm missing some stuff here. What is that? Oh, okay. Bottle of Coke versus Bottle of IVC Root
Beer. Probably Bottle of Coke. Especially if it's like frosty. If there's like still like
white frosty shit all over it. And, ah, yeah. Only if it has the white frosty shit all over it.
Otherwise, it's not as good. While I'm holding that in my hand, it has to burn me. It has to be
like this is too fucking cold to even hold my hands. That's Mexican Coke. That's fine. Yeah,
that's even actually even better. Pib Extra. I don't care. Oh, this is ginger beer, right?
This stuff is actually pretty good. This is pretty good. I will put this up here.
That's good stuff. A&W gives me a stomach ache. Is this a bottle of Pepsi or is this a special
Pepsi? I think that's just a glass bottle of Pepsi. I would... no, I'd rather have these two.
Crystal Pepsi is a funny laugh out loud ecto cooler 90s kids thing. I don't care. This is...
what is this? Oh, this is one of those... this is one of those Japanese sodas, right? This is the
thing where you like you punch the thing down and like bloop! Like the flavor goes in. It is, right?
Okay. These are okay. These... I don't know if I... it's weird though. You don't really ever have an
opportunity to drink these. Like why do you drink soda or liquid? Oh, I'm thirsty. I want to quench
my thirst. This is more like a game than it is like drinking a soda. It's more like a, oh look
at how cool that looks. Not like I can't wait to drink a Coke right now. It's like, yeah, it's fun.
That's... but I would put Baja Blast in that same category. I don't like go... I don't drink Baja
Blast, but if you go to Taco Bell, it's like, oh, the like teal green one. Yeah, I'll take that one.
Oh yeah, this is fun. It's for fun. These are the ones for fun, and they belong up at sea.
There's no other scenario where I get this. Plus, I don't think you even get them. Can of Pepsi?
Doesn't it... I mean, what's the... made with real sugar? This is a joke. This is... this is just like
the look... look at how healthy we are when we're not healthy at all. Doesn't matter. Made with real
sugar this time. It's still... it's still a Pepsi. You know, it probably is better than the regular
one. Okay, what is this one? Is this Diet? That looks like Diet to me, and it's making me angry,
so it's going down here. Now, the rest of these... I've had Jones Soda before, but I'm not... I don't
think I've had these enough to really have an opinion on it. Some of these. This one... this is
pretty good. This is the orange one, right? There's like a lemon lime. Yeah, these are okay. These are
good. These aren't bad. I'm just trying to remember how much better they are than the other ones.
I distinctly remember these being very good. Like, potentially like best, but I don't... I haven't had
them enough times to be able to have... that's not in my memory. I know they're good, but I know
exactly what a 7-Up tastes like. I can... I can describe it to you. It's the only one that's going
up there. 7-Up is the best soda in the world. It is. This is the... really the only ginger ale on the
list. Canada Dry is up there too. Those of you that disagree with this, that's okay. That's all
right, but just... you got to listen. The next time that you go on an airplane, please, if they have
it, get a 7-Up with that airplane ice. It enhances the flavor by 45%. Airplane ice and 7-Up... something
about it. I don't know what it is. It's fucking really good. Because I don't know what's on that
ice. I don't know if this is like... if that's... it might be toilet water. It could be toilet water ice,
but there's some combination of like airplane toilet water ice and 7-Up that make it magical.
It is by far the best soda I would drink it if... and then it's not everywhere either. That's the
thing. See, all these dickheads... these guys are everywhere. 7-Up is not in every single store.
You can get a Pepsi literally anywhere. You could get a Pepsi at the doctor's office if you really
want it to. A 7-Up is a treat. You see it in the cooler and you go, oh fuck, they got 7-Up here.
Give me... give me like seven of them. And you like stuff it in your fucking arm and go to the
checkout. We buy it at the grocery store. That's not fun. I can get 7-Up at my dentist office.
There's a reason why 7-Up is hard to find. It's because it's just selling out. People are just
buying so many of them. Because it's the best airplane soda. You know how many people fly on
airplanes every day? How many... okay, somebody calculate how many people are flying on an airplane
today? And how many of those people are drinking a 7-Up right now? It's got to be a lot. There are
like 5,000 airplanes that are flying around right now. That's at least... how many passengers are on
an airplane? Like a typical... like an Airbus or a 747 or whatever. There's probably like three... two
or three hundred people on a plane? Something like that. 100 people? 200? So 200 times 5,000.
That's five, 10, 20, 25... that's like... let's just say there's like 200... let's just say there's like
400,000 people flying around the plane right now. And like 40% of that... you got like 20... there's
like probably 190,000 people drinking a 7-Up right now on an airplane. Definitely. More than that.
Where do they get those numbers? I don't know. This is like... I'm just... I'm just spitballing.
This is an open spitball platform here. I don't... I don't got a... I don't got a guy over there
with like four laptops and like two fucking Google searches open.
Hey, what... how many people are on a plane today? No, it's just me. It's just me and you. And all
these gross teeth rotting beverages. There's nobody else. Just the two of us. Times a couple...
a hundred or a thousand people. Water is the S tier? Yeah, but it's not listed on here.
All right, let's go back. This is our... these... I remember... these are really, really good, but I
can't put them above anything else. I don't think I've ever had these. I've never had sausage soda
before, I don't think. All right. Nope. Wait. Make sure I look good. Okay. 7-Up I think is the best
on this list. Canada Dry and NW both A tier. Might have to move... not as good. Close. Too...
too sugary, I think, to me. I just... I just tried it. I just tried it in my internal mind, and I
think it was too sugary. These are all very sugary. Very, very sweet. Um, I think this is good. I don't
think I need to change anything. Although, let me put all the diet ones at the very bottom.
Because this is diet, right? It's like diet cherry vanilla Dr. Pepper, right?
Yeah, definitely. Like, diet Pepsi is probably the worst drink. Cherry Pepsi is in the trash?
Yeah. Yeah, it is. I have had this before. I've had this before. No, I'm not. I don't like the cherry...
like, cherry Coke is all right, but no, it's not up there very high.
Cherry Coke is okay. I don't remember this being something that I really liked.
Done. They're just... done. I'm happy with it. Meats. Why is there meats? There's a Taco Bell menu
one. I don't even need to do it. There's only one item that belongs up anywhere. You already know
what it is. You want to do meats? All right, I'll do meats. I'm not doing Jell-O. They're all gross.
Oh, there's chips. This one's all right, too. I'll do that after. What the fuck is this?
G Fuel Tier List? Where does Kool-Aid Packets and Pixie Sticks fall on that list?
All right, well, it's a meat one. I'll take the meat one. Cheez-Its.
There we go. Meat. Let's try meat. Did I fuck it up? Meats. Okay, this is perfect. This is fine.
I've had all of these, I think, although I can't really determine what some of them are.
Uh, bacon is the first one here, and bacon is good, but it's also a meme food.
Bacon is one of those things that, for some reason, the internet got ahold of it
and became, like, the coolest fucking thing in the world. Putting bacon on something
made it cool, even if it wasn't cool at all. Bacon. Oh, whoa! You put bacon on that sandwich.
Yeah, it's become a big thing. Like, bacon. Okay, let me tell you something. Bacon and the word,
like, epic, are the same word, right? If you put bacon on something, it makes it epic.
That's just what happens. Nothing wrong with that. There's no problem with it. It's just,
that's what, that's just the kind of what happened. I don't find it to be like this god meat
that people started putting on their ice cream. I don't, I don't think so. I think it's good.
I like bacon a lot. I eat it all the time, but it's not like, I put bacon on this, therefore,
now it's the best. It's awesome. No, it's just bacon. I just eat it. Bacon is a condiment to me.
It's not really, it's a side. It's a condiment. It's like putting mustard on your hamburger.
You don't, like, oh, hey, guys. Hey, so today, come on in for dinner. I made a bacon. What? No,
it's, it goes on stuff. It's a side. Yeah, but it's, I'm being a hipster. Wouldn't I be being
a hipster if I said that bacon is fucking so awesome, epic, cool? That's mainstream.
Well, you're really going to not like this. Am I still a hipster? Is this salmon? Done. Done.
Sausage? Wait, chicken? What's this? Fried chicken? What's the difference? Isn't this
chicken? Is that turkey? Wait, is that a turkey? That's a turkey. No, no, no, no. That doesn't go
up there. This is pork. This is like a hamburger patty. Hold on. Oh, I'm going to make people angry
with this. I know I am. It's a ham. I don't like ham. Not really. I think it's, yeah, it's a, I'm
not a big fan. Also, not a big fan of steak. I do like ribs. I would rather eat a steak than ham,
though. These ribs. Hold on. I just need to get it on the plate first. I, everybody, hold on. I need
to just get it on the plate. What is that? Is that like white fish, like cod or haddock or something?
What is it? I would put that up here. So I'll put sausage here. No. Okay. Is this, what is that?
Is that lamb? What is this? Brisket? That's, is that brisket? Doesn't look like brisket.
Is it brisket? That's turkey. No, that's turkey. Maybe it's duck. That, is that duck? That's chicken.
So what's that? Why is it like different? Is it like fried chicken and regular chicken?
It's, yeah, it's unclear. I'll take, I'll take a salmon and a 7-up, please. Pork chops? So then
what is this, though? I don't know what that is. I think this is duck. I'm going to say that's duck.
Okay, now hold on. Would I rather eat ham or duck? No. I don't like duck. That's too gamey. I don't
like it. Would I rather eat like pork cutlets or cutlets over steak? I would eat cutlets. Sausage
over, yeah, I like, I like sausage. Hamburger over, this is, is this, what is this? Is this chicken
cutlet? This is pork cutlet right here. So that's chicken cutlet. Is this chicken cutlet? Is this
pork cutlet? I'm going to say this is pork cutlet and this is chicken cutlet just from my brain,
and they could be wrong. I'm pretty sure that pork is this one. I would rather eat a hamburger
than pork. Yes, I probably would. Bacon, it's just a fucking condiment. I'm putting it on the list.
I'm just going to be condiments. How can you put like bacon over a hamburger? It's, that's not,
this is mustard. Would I rather eat, I'd rather eat chicken,
turkey, salmon. I think this is good. Tofu, I find to be just something I never want to have.
It's weird. It's, I just don't, I don't like it. I really don't. I actually really don't like soy,
like anything, really at all. I don't like soy milk. I don't like soy, like tofu. I don't like,
it's just that I don't like it. It doesn't do it for me. But I do, I do also not like steak.
I wouldn't order steak at a restaurant. If I had an opportunity, it would be something up here.
It wouldn't be a steak. No, I'd rather eat steak than ham. But I'm a, I'm a, I'm a fly and fish
kind of person. Salmon is probably my favorite meat. Or, you know, turkey probably would be my
favorite if it was easy to get all the time and easy to make. Salmon is really easy to make.
Turkey's not easy to make. If you want to make like a fucking Thanksgiving turkey, it takes like
a day to make it. You can make this in five minutes. Would I rather have like a piece of
cod or a hamburger? Hamburger. It's still up here though, but does it, but yeah, no,
yep, no. Learn to cook turkey. You forgot forehead. Salmon, turkey, chicken, hamburger meat,
whitefish, chicken cutlets, bacon, bacon, ribs, sausage, pork cutlets, and then steak, ham,
duck, and tofu. Bring it on. What's next? Why are ribs and steak so low? I'm not a big red meat fan.
I like burgers and I like meatballs. And that's kind of it. Game of Thrones characters? No,
that's like spoilers. Not seeing one I want to do yet. Best pop tarts? It's s'mores pop tarts.
Discussion over. Chips. Chips is a good one. I'll do chips. Is this the full list here? This doesn't
look like a full list to me. Is this a full list? This is not. This is not enough on here.
Ultra tier? No. Epic American chips. That's not, you just made that. You just made that.
Is bacon on there? Epic American chips. Yeah, this is, this is a, I want a bigger list.
Why do I feel like this is a smaller list? Like you gave, you gave me a bunch of like
Smash Brothers clones. Is this, is this, this is not in a variety here. It's just all Cheetos,
Doritos and Lay's. Where are the Pringles? Okay. Where are the Munchos? I don't see them on this
list. Chip tiers. I got another one. Hold on. All right. Hold on. This is a little bit more.
They're on this list. All right. I think this is the one. Combos are on here too. All right.
This is better. This is better. Yeah, this is better. All right. Right. We got baked Lay's on
here. Baked Lay's not on here. Yeah, no baked Lay's, no Cape Cod. What's this one? Do snacks? Wait,
you can add? Can I add stuff? Cape Cod are Zoomer chips. Cape Cod has been a chip
brand since I was like fucking four years old. Zoomer chips. Is this one better? All right. Okay.
Cape Cod is a Redditor chip. Oh, this is the list we're doing because I already know which one is
this. Oh yeah. Yeah. Holy shit. Those things are amazing. You never had those before. Don't let the,
don't let the title fool you. These are fucking amazing. They're so good. With baked Lay's,
it's going to be a fight up here. It's going to be a, it's going to be a brawl up in this,
in the S-rank. I can't have more than one or two, but it's going to be a fight up there.
Goldfish is definitely A or B tier. Where are those munchos? No munchos on this list, huh?
Fuck. No. This is going to be a fight up here. I, hold on. It's actually going to be easier to
go bottom up with this. These taste like dog food. All Lay's brand that are not baked Lay's go down
in D because they're fine. They're fine. But once you eat two thirds of the bag, you're just left
with a greasy fucking bread crumbs. The bag is full and it's this fucking big. The bag is huge.
Down here are the chips. Here's the layer of ones that have not been sat on by like a fat
guy on a plane. Making lots of plane references today. Under there is just bread crumbs. I'm sorry.
I do like, but look, I'm not a Lay's hater. I got baked Lay's up in the best chips that I've ever
had. It's the classic ones. It's the classic, just greasy ones. Any more of those? Cause they're going
right there. Bugles, F. No, I don't like them. Bugles tastes like cereal without any like sugar
on them. They just taste like, like just did nothing. It just has, it tastes like air.
It's just eating dry air. I eat dry air every day here anyways in Vegas. I also really, really do
not like the Ruffles brand, like the Ruffles. No, I don't like these either. Tostitos. This is an
interesting thing here because Tostitos are nothing without salsa or queso. So I don't know if they
belong on this list. Are these just standard default, just eat tortilla chips out of the bag
or am I implying that I'm eating these with salsa or queso? Are we implying that I'm enjoying them
with salsa? Just the chip, just alone without the chip, without it. Well then, I mean, I would never
do that. I would never eat Tostitos unless I was dipping it in some type of viscous fluid that had
like a spicy or cheesy flavor to it. No, I would not do that. I'm not going to do that. Why would
I do that? I'm just not going to do that, regardless of how they taste. I'm sorry. These are the ones
that taste, which are the, we're the dog food ones. Yeah, no, these are all the Frito heavily
flavored. That's a heavy spice, heavy flavoring. They're just cat food, dog food. I can't eat them.
Regular Fritos though, those are, those are good. Hey, can you focus here? Come on, what's going on?
Camera. Focus. We're just the default Doritos. There they are. This is going to take some
revisions. Doritos Jacked. I don't, I wouldn't, I don't want these. I would never buy them.
This is like Doritos Chili Lime. I would never buy them. I like Cool Ranch less than I like
the regular Doritos. I just wouldn't buy, I don't, I'm not going to eat, I'm not going to eat these.
I am actually a sucker for these. I love the compilations. Pretzel Cheese Squares.
Like Sun Chip, I love because you get a little bit of everything. So I like having that. Although
I would never buy these. In fact, this is at the very bottom. All Sun Chips are at the very bottom.
Yeah, they are. No, I dare, once you eat one of these, if I had one, then I would be done.
Eating more than three, four, five, or six Sun Chips, they just start, it doesn't, it just starts
to taste strange. If it's my first chip, this is up here, but it's eating like at least, I'm going
to say like a half, like a couple dozen. I wouldn't sit down and eat a whole bag of these. I would eat
a whole bag. In fact, I've done it before many times. I have gotten the normal regular size
Bake Lays and I'm talking within the last couple of weeks. Now I'm like, oh, I've done that before.
Like, no, I did this like two weeks ago. I ate the whole bag. I do it all the time.
I wouldn't do that with these. Um, which, what are these? Which one of these?
Moldy Doritos. I don't, I don't, I wouldn't get them. I don't know. It's like something all over.
Cheetos. Um, I would put Cheetos up in it. The regular, like the asymmetrical Cheetos.
I like more than the puff ones. So yeah. Flamin' Hot. I'm not a fan. I'd rather just give me the
regular ones. Flamin' Hot. Not only does Flamin' Hot taste worse to me, but it increases the amount
of shit on your hands by at least twice, two or three times. I will eat Flamin' Hot Cheetos.
You fucking have to wash your hands. It's awful. And I don't know why that's considered a good
thing. Oh dude, like I got so much Cheeto, like the Flamin' Hot dust on my hands. Why don't they
make it so it's not, they're not like that. Nobody wants to do that. Where can you eat those? Where
can you reliably eat Flamin' Hot Cheetos? You have to be like in your bathroom. It's part of the
trademark. Dirty hands. But it's something with Flamin' Hot. The regular Cheetos don't really,
they do that a little bit. But you may as well have like fucking murdered somebody after you eat
Flamin' Hot Cheetos. You're like a blood all over you. And no, I'm not going to lick the, like,
you know what the fucking hands have been on a daily basis? You want to talk about like, like
getting sick and how we need to be more health conscious? Yeah. Put your hands as far down in
your mouth as you can over and over again. That's a great idea. No, that's like so like bizarre.
You got to like, yeah, you got to wash your hands. But what if you're not in your bathroom? What if
you're walking down the street with a bag of Flamin' Hot Cheetos? Okay, you've eaten like 20
of them now. What do you do? What do you do? You're walking around, where are you? What do you do?
You, yeah. And then you go like this. That's better. Or like, yeah, that's better. That's
sanitary. Just pour the bag in your mouth. Eat them with chopsticks. These do that, but these do that
way more. Therefore, they're at the bottom of the list. Chex Mix, mid-tier. I like this style more
than I like Chex Mix. I don't really like Chex. Combos are really good, but combos are actually
also like really bad too. You can only get these at like gas stations. So there's something going
on there. Goldfish Flavor Blasted is just the same complaint that I have about, ow, my hand.
That hurts so fucking much. That hurt a lot. And I'm gonna complain about it. Flavor Blasted
Goldfish are the same thing as Flamin' Hot Cheetos. They just put extra dust on it and
it's just give me the regular ones. Those ones are better. Funyuns are okay in small doses.
They're pretty good, although I wouldn't, I don't think I'd put them at B. Cheez-Its are definitely
a little, they're up here. Now this is, is this Tabasco? Spicy? Because if those are the ones
they belong up here. I'm not a big fan of any of the other early Cheez-It Brains. I like the hot
ones. I like the super toasty ones and I like the regular ones. Cheetos Puffs, again, like I said,
I would rather have these, the regular ones, the asymmetrical crunchy ones over the puffy cloudy
ones. Oh, those are White Cheddar. Yeah, that may, this may have been a mistake. They belong up here.
The White Cheddar ones are actually insane. Again, this is like Flamin' Hot Cheeto. Just,
oh yeah. Do we have a chip? Yes, we do. Do we also have an evil version of those chips?
We better. Chesters? One of these? I don't know what these are. No, they're the fries, the little
like, like little hot fries. Where are the hot fries? Why are they not in here? Okay, can I pretend
that these are the actual hot fries? But can I also pretend that they are the regular cheesy ones,
not the hot ones? Because that's not on this list. I'm not going to put these up anywhere high.
I'm pretending that these are the original fries. I don't need to pretend. Are they on here? No,
not on here. Okay, so that this is, this is hot. These are the regular mild hot fries.
These go up here. Yeah, they have, they have regular ones. Oh yeah. They're insane. They're
amazing. They're everything you love about the hot ones, except they're not hot. Just add them. Yeah,
yeah, the Andy Caps. Andy Caps is the one I'm talking about. I don't know what these are. What's
going on in here? Taco flavored Doritos? I don't, I don't, I don't think I would want to get those.
Gordettas. This looks like a little combo mix thing. I think I've had it a few times,
but I don't really remember. It kind of, it's the same thing as Chex next to me, my brain.
Salt, salt and vinegar chips are really bad. Just tastes like rotten potato chips.
It tastes like potato chips that the bag was open. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It just, they're,
they're just, they're just pee. It's just urine chips. That's just what I think of. I'm sorry.
It just, it's just urine potato chips. That's, that's it. And that's all I have to say.
I really, really dialed up the polarization here in chat, and I didn't mean to, but I just,
I'm being honest. I'm just being honest. I am fucking fuming. I personally disagree,
but I understand and respect your opinion. All right, we've got Pringles here. There's no normal
Pringles somehow. There's just sour cream and onion Pringles and pizza Pringles, which I don't
really like either one of them. In fact, regular Pringles, I think, are not even the best ones.
I think cheddar Pringles. I think are my favorite. Honey mustard Pringles. I've never had them.
Those sound good. They sound pretty good. Honey mustard Pringles. I would rather eat any Pringles
over any Lay's though. That's for sure. Kettle cooked Lay's. I mean, we already have the,
I mean, these, I wouldn't even, I don't want these. These are essentially the same idea,
except these ones have barbecue sauce on them. These ones are just better.
Um, pork skins. I've never had these before. I actually need to put like another, hold on,
let me do another row of, I've never had this before because this is at least, at least
six of these that I have actually really never eaten. Never had. I've never had these Doritos.
I've never had whatever these are. I don't, I've never had them. I don't know if I've ever had
these. I have this weird memory of me eating them, but I don't think so. Uh, the rest of these,
I've never had these pork skins. I've never had like these hot and spicy. I've seen these before
because they always say that they're two dollars. It's printed on the bag everywhere,
but I never had them. I've never had these. I've never had these and these are bad. It's just,
it's like, it's just, it's maybe, you eat saltines. It's just a saltine 2.0.
I don't know. What are these? Potato sticks? I don't think I've ever had those.
So let's start from the bottom. Which one of these that I really don't like what I've,
what I want to eat the most? Probably these. No, I don't, I wouldn't, I wouldn't choose those over
any of these. Probably, probably Bugles because it's, oh look, it's weird and I haven't had these
in 10 years and oh wow, I can't believe they have these here. That would be the only reason.
These are the Doritos flavors. I would probably try them. Like I've had them a couple times.
It would be like, ah, I guess, okay, if there was like, if there was a Doritos shortage
and I really wanted Doritos and I had to get them, I had to eat them, it would be those.
I don't want this, the hot Mr. Munchies. The Tostitos would be all the way, all the way at
the bottom. Triscuits Tostitos would be at the very bottom because it just, you need all those,
you can't enjoy triscuits without like a piece of cheese or a piece of pepperoni on it. We,
this is implied and this is, I asked you guys this. Eating Tostitos without salsa is just,
I don't, it's just a cracker. Eating triscuits without like a pepperoni on it or like a little,
like a spread or some, or like a dip is, I wouldn't want to do, I wouldn't do that.
I wouldn't, I'm sorry, I just wouldn't do it. Crackers are good, but if I'm at the grocery
store I'm not going to go. Triscuits, get them in the cart. I can't wait to eat a handful of those,
like 20 of them today, right now. I'm, no. Do I know how pepperoni is made?
I don't know, some guy, some, some guy in a pizza restaurant, like sings and then they,
they just appear on the plate I guess. I don't know. Lime Tostitos are the worst.
Um, are these, these, these are original. When I put chips in the sandwich, I used to do that
until I got hurt. I used to put potato chips in my tuna sandwich until one day I took a bite
and it literally like pierced up into my mouth and I said that I'm never going to do that again.
It hurt me. I got hurt. Okay, so that's, this is done. I would not want to eat these.
I really don't like salt and vinegar. I really don't. Okay, the D. These are ones that I would
eat, but I wouldn't choose, right? I would eat these, but I wouldn't choose these. That's where
I put D. Fuck, I wouldn't choose any of these. These are all on the same level, so do not be
fooled by this list going kind of descending down this way. No, they're all the same. I wouldn't get
any of these. I would eat them, but I wouldn't. No, they're all in the same tier for me. All of
them. Okay, moving on. Now, this is things that I would pick on a rainy day. If it was rainy outside
and I was like, it's fucking raining out. I want to get a snack or something. This is one of those.
This is like it's sunny out. This is like a rainy shitty day. I think Bake Lays just goes in the
front just because I would eat Bake Lays no matter what. I would eat combos way before I would eat
Chex mixes, I think. Yeah, that's good. Yep. I like, I love nachos, Doritos. I don't love Fritos,
though. This is like a wow, I really like these. I don't really, I don't really like Fritos. This is
a problem. Yeah, this is a problem. I would, yeah, I would choose Cool Ranch over Barbecue Bake Lays,
I think. I would eat Fritos over, no, I wouldn't. That's accurate. Yeah, I would definitely choose
Fritos over Chex Mix. This is, I don't think I need to change anything here. This is where it's
going to get hard. All right, this is the difficult part, trying to decide which actually is my
favorite, like snack. These two are up here. Goldfish come down a little. In fact, I would
choose, I would choose nacho Doritos over Goldfish. Very small margin, though. Would I choose Cheez-Its
over Doritos? These are scary. The reason why Goldfish are so scary is because I buy the bucket.
Do you know the giant, like fucking high school milk carton? I buy the big one, the one that's
supposed to feed like 40 people, and you just, you sit there and you're watching TV or a movie,
and you eat like 25 people's worth of servings in those, they're dangerous. Why do I have Cape
Cod so high if I don't like Kettle Chips? I love Kettle Chips. I just, I just don't like the, the
bar, I just really don't like barbecue, uh, Lay's Kettle Chips. I wouldn't like choose these. I don't,
I don't like, I'm not a big like barbecue chip fan, if that's been clear, I guess. The only reason
why these are up here is because they're baked. You have garbage tastes. Why are Baked Lay's an S?
Because Baked Lay's have my favorite chip. And Smartfood is actually about to go up because I'm
trying to figure out how, what my top three are going to be, and then me just sitting here,
I figured it out. Why is your opinion different than mine? Smartfood is fucking delicious. It's
that, it's white cheddar popcorn. Remember when everybody freaked out when white cheddar Cheez-Its
were over here? What? What? Smartfood is white cheddar popcorn. It's insane. Come on. Smartfood,
there's got to be some people that agree here. It's fake popcorn. It's just, I don't know why
a company would make fake popcorn when popcorn is the world's cheapest thing to produce. Why would
you fake something? It would probably cost more money to fake than to make popcorn. What do you
think is in there? No, I think it's plastic. It would be like four dollars a bag. It's bones.
Popcorn. Popcorn. Pop popcorn. There? Are we happy? What would you put up on S? I'm just curious.
Sun Chips? The only place where Sun Chips belong are in a big bowl at a fucking retirees party.
And guess what? I really hate to say this to you, but that bowl is going to be just as full
six hours later when parties are. What else? What do you want? What do you want up there?
What do you want up there? Funyuns? I've got nothing on Funyuns. They're actually pretty good.
I told you this wasn't going to be easy. Don't even come talk shit about rolled golds.
I will delete the stream. I will turn the stream off and delete it. I will delete the VOD.
And then I'll re-upload the VOD on YouTube and edit that part out of you guys talking about it.
If you don't think rolled golds, pretzels belong up here, then I'm sorry. You and I have an
extreme disagreement. You like cheese. You just like cheese. Smart food. White cheddar.
That's not accurate. Cheetah. In fact, I'm seeing something right now that I don't like.
I would choose goldfish over Cheetos so that it doesn't belong down there. I actually would
probably rather eat like 30 people's worth of goldfish over cheeses. Oh, he's climbing.
He's climbing up there. What's the next Mortal Kombat contestant? What's up? Rolled gold?
Was it Shang Tsung? Oh, he's taking them on. He's done. I would rather eat goldfish than rolled
golds. What we got left? We got fuck. We got Goro and then we got Shao Kahn. I would rather eat the
hot fries though. It's not S tier. It's not. It's very close. I'm having second thoughts about
those like Andy Capps fries because if you look at the back of those fries, this is like fucking
500 ingredients. It's something crazy. The amount of shit that's on the back of that container
is like too much. It's like laundry detergent amount of shit that's in there,
but they're fucking good. Wow. You're so healthy. Were you present for the cereal segment an hour
ago? I was not. Check that out. There's plenty of cereals in there that people thought I was like
a fucking eight-year-old for liking. Done. Done. It's done. Wait. Done. Am I okay with that? I'm
okay with that. Done. Done. Done. Now it's done. Utz is not on the list. I know it's unfortunate.
Munchos aren't on this list either. Munchos would have been up here. See, the reason why SmartFood
is here is because Munchos are not on the list. I am replacing Munchos with SmartFood. SmartFood
would be down here, but it has to be up here because I have memories. Baked Lays I get every
single time I go to the grocery store. Every single time. They're the perfect little snack.
I love them. Veggie straws. There are people that are Mr. Healthy talking shit to me right now,
but if you've never had these before, they're so light and you could eat a thousand of them.
They're really good. Try it one time. And a Goldfish is just a classic. That's a classic
snack. It has to be up there. You can take a handful of these straws and just they're very
crunchy. They're very, very light. It's not vegetables. It's like potato starch. They're
really good. They cost too much. They are kind of expensive, aren't they? Finalists. Veggie straws
start tasting bad the more that you eat them. If I try Takis, you'll get veggie straws. If it's
available, I don't know if Las Vegas grocery stores stock Takis. I've never seen them before.
Amazon Prime them. Oh yeah, you can do that. You can look just like Amazon. But what,
I'm just going to Amazon a bag of chips? I would have to get like a box of them.
I'm like, you're going to tell me I'm going to Amazon Prime two-day shipping, a bag of chips.
That's like, I'm going to go to the grocery store for that. Overnight. No, that's like
Postmating or Uber Eatsing a Gatorade. No, I'm not going to do that. All right,
we got any more? I'll do, I've been going for a long time here. Okay, we'll do,
time is getting late. We'll do one more. One more. One more decent one. It's been about,
what, seven and a half, eight hours or so? It's been a while. Video game, what is this? Video
game tier list? Oh, like consoles? I'll do a console list. This sounds good. Is this a good,
we got a good one? Like a full console list? All games, every game list. Door handles? All right,
let's see what this one is. Video game consoles. Okay, we'll do this one. We can do this again.
We can do, I have fun doing these. This is fun. This is not, I'm not, I'm not enjoying this.
This is great. I'm having a good time. This is like the new GeoGuessr for the next like three weeks.
All right, so I'm a Super Nintendo, I'm a Nintendo person. I wasn't like a, I wasn't a Sega person
when I was younger, so take that bias into account. All right, where are we? Super Nintendo,
there it is. The best console that's ever been made. I need F tier because this thing was just
looking at the sun. Add a row below and needs to be like F. Or like, I need to make another one
that's like I never played it. So this is F, F, and I need to be, come on, capital. F and then I
never played or didn't own. No, I never played because I played some of these and never owned
them. No, I never played. Never played. This is, color has to change. All right, we're good.
What are you guys saying? How many consoles did I own? Well, we're gonna do those first. We're
gonna do the consoles that I actually owned. Original, is this original Game Boy? I mean,
Game Boy. For what it was, it was really good. It was one of the first real mobile kind of platforms.
The original Game Boy I loved. Belongs on B. Is this like a slip and slide or is this a console?
I don't know what this is. This looks like a jumpy house. I probably never played. What is this? What
are these? Genesis. I thought the Genesis wasn't very good. It was the sounds of the Genesis that
did it for me. Didn't have good sound effects. All the sounds and the music in Genesis all had that
weird like, you know, those, you guys know what I'm talking about. I know at least some of you do.
Super Nintendo had superior sound because Super Nintendo obviously that they got their sound
from Sony. Sony helped them make the sound. That's why the chip, the sound chip is so much better
than the Sega Genesis. I wonder how many of you guys knew that one? False? That's not false.
All right, so what is this? I don't know what that is. And this is like another version of the
Super Nintendo. This is, is that, that's not Atari. Is that Atari? No, this is Atari down here.
Regular Nintendo is up here. Nintendo 64 is up here at S. The regular Xbox I'm going to put
over here. Xbox 360 goes down here because the thing was junk. And I mean like hardware wise.
All you need, there's a video of the guy cracking the egg in the fucking radiator, man.
Come on. This, the thing was a D. Gamecube. Hold on. This is important. Is this the Wii U? Definitely
F. Um, is it a game and watch? I never had one. PlayStation 1. Oh, here comes the fight up here.
Dreamcast fucking sucks. Laughing my ass off. It's definitely a C. Well, the Dreamcast fucking
sucks. LMAO. I will never forget that. I like, I sometimes, I'll be in the shower and I will just
think of the all lowercase text. The Dreamcast fucking sucks. LMAO. I will never forget it.
It's burned forever in my brain and it makes me laugh in the shower. This is the Ouya? Is that the
Ouya? The Ouya? Did this thing even release? Wait, aren't these things worth like 500 bucks now
because like nobody has them anymore? These things are worth a shitload now, right? I swear to God,
I thought, I heard that that Ouya is like a collector's item because they're just liquidated.
It's the beanie baby of consoles. Switch is really good. It's just, it is. I had my doubts at first
and I like, I was a kind of, I was kind of a shit talker at first, but it's, it's pretty,
it's pretty great. PS2 is just one of the, there's so many good consoles. Well, let's get rid of the
dumb ones. Is that a, where's the Sega CD? Virtual Boy F. Is this a Sega Master System? The thing was
pretty cool actually. I had one of these, but we're talking about the best. PS3 was, PS3 wasn't really
that good. It was, it was, but I mean, these two just, they had a bunch of problems. I think we'd
like to forget about just how many issues this generation of consoles really truly had. They were
kind of dog shit. The hardware and the, some great games came out, but the consoles were just kind of
bad. There was a lot of issues. It wasn't the, yeah, the PS3 was like 500, 600 bucks at launch.
Wasn't it something crazy? The Wii. The Wii was fucking awesome. It was. It was 599 bucks.
It was great. You know how much, how much time I got out of my Wii? So much, so much time.
Yeah, I did, how much time did I get out of my like PlayStation 3, you know, or my Xbox 360? I got
time out of it, but this was the console that you just dumped days into because there was so much
fun stuff you could do. I played hit the fucking ball with the baseball bat for like every day.
I played Wii Sports every fucking day for like a year. You know how many times I played like
Viking on Xbox 360 once and I turned it off in two hours? Where's the PS4? Where's the Xbox One?
In fact, it's really strong. It's struggling right now to not put this up here.
The PS4 is so good. It's so good. It is fucking, it's so good. The amount of
exclusive games that they've come up with on this damn thing. The interface is just, it's,
it's really, really fucking good console. It really is. But is it better than PS1 or the PS2?
I got every, I got every PlayStation on here. I just, I got every PS, I got every,
all the PlayStations are on here. That has to go up. It has to. It's too good.
There's like 5,000 games for the PS2. I did it. I'm not going back on it. PS4 is,
it's done everything right. The PlayStation has done almost everything right,
except for a couple of like bumps. Just think of, you gotta, I'm thinking of games and like
hardware and shit. Think of the games that have come out on PS4 and then go like 10 years ago
and be like, okay, what are the, there's been some ridiculous games that they put out over
the last like four or five years. Too many handhelds. The PS2, I know, I know. God damn it.
Super Nintendo is never going to change. It's going to be number one. I'm trying to think
the games that I played on PS2 and they changed everything. The Master System was cool. The
Dreamcast was cool in the Genesis and the Master System, but it wasn't better than the GameCube,
don't worry. But let me get some other stuff on here. All these may as well just be empty boxes.
That, what is this thing? I don't, it's just a Super Nintendo. It's like the new version.
All these other ones. Wait, is this the phone? Which one of these, which one of these is the
end gauge? Is this the end gauge? That's F. That was what a disaster. Okay, this is Game Boy Advance.
I like the DS better than the Game Boy Advance. Although this is the 3DS, so I mean the 3DS is just
a better version of the DS. It's just a bigger screen in 3D. I'm not, I'm not a handheld player.
I'm not, I don't, I'm not a handheld player. Remember, they're good, but I don't, I don't,
I don't play them. Let me come back to this. Where's the game gear? Game gear. Where is it?
Right here? That's a game gear, right? F. F. PSP. Is there, is the PSP down here? Because that's an
F too. Why is a game gear an F? Because it took like eight AA batteries and in the ride to grandmas
you'd have to replace them. It's not, it wasn't very good. Where is it? Is this the PSP?
This is the Vita? I'll give Vita a D because it made itself relevant for like a couple years.
There's a PSP. F. No, wait, I played Grand Theft Auto on this and it was, it was pretty fun. Okay,
no, that's a D. High D. No, that's a C. Not better than the DS. Yeah, I played, I played the GTA
in that and it was like the first time I've ever experienced like a good like full open 3D GTA type
game on like a handheld and it's the first time they did it. So yeah, whatever. Liberty City Stories,
whatever it was. Yeah, it belongs there. Okay. But thank fucking God. I would not have remembered
it. I would have, okay, here's the funny part of what just happened. If that was a thing and I did
this again, this list would probably would be completely different. This would be the same
up here, but all these would be completely, it would be completely different because I'd have
to think about every individual one again. All right. I don't, I never, I don't, this is the,
this is the Canada console. I don't know what that is. I don't play it. I don't know what it is.
Where's the, where's the Atari? Atari changed the world. So we're going to use, we're going to put,
Atari deserves to be somewhere in B. Without the Atari, there is no Dreamcast and without
no Dreamcast, there is no Game Boy. Without no Game Boy, there is no GameCube. Without no GameCube,
there is no Wii. Without no Atari, there is no PS4. Therefore, it has to be here, holding the
anchor down at B. Where's the Phillips CDI? And are we certain that these are not the same console
taken at a different angle? The photo. I think they are. I don't know what they are. What is this? Is
this like, this, is this the 32X? Yeah, this is the 32X, isn't it? 32X was just a Genesis 2.0. Or is
that the Sega CD? They did a weird thing. Sega had a strange console thing where it was like the
32X and the CD-I were the same console, right? Something weird. What happened? What the fuck was
that? Did my internet drop? That's weird. It says I did not drop any frames. That's,
that was weird. Chat just stopped moving and it didn't say I dropped any frames.
Weird. That's weird. All right, moving on. What is this? Is this, is this the Jaguar?
I never played the Jaguar. What is this thing? I feel like I don't know what any of these are.
This is, I don't know, this is like something I would see this in like a 70s. I think this is
in Space Odyssey. This is, it's old. It's really old. You can tell because it has like cigarette
fucking stain on it. Somebody smoked in their house. This is like a cigarette console.
Old as fuck. That's fine. I don't know what it is. I don't know what this thing is.
I don't know what this is either. What is that? What are all these? I didn't, none of, I don't have
any recollection at all of playing any of these. So what are these two handhelds? What is, what is
this handheld right here? The Apple Pippin. The Apple Pippin? That's what the console was named?
Why would you name your console after the weakest character in Lord of the Rings?
Why is it not like the Apple Gimli or like the Apple Aragorn? Because Pippin is a type of apple.
Apple Gandalf. People would have bought it. What the fuck is this? The Apple Gandalf. I would have
bought it. I would have bought it just to have one because it's fucking stupid. This is the game
rectangle. Nobody knows what this is. What's this one? This is the Wonder Swan. Okay. Is this the
Neo Geo? I never played any of these. All right. Let's go up. Oh, by the way, just in case anybody
was curious, just in case anyone needed to know, Pink is doing a two, two for $49 bra, get one,
get to buy one. These ads, I thought I had an ad thing on them. All right. They just keep like
popping in my face. They're doing like the mobile game thing where just every like 10 seconds,
they just reload the ad to get an impression. All right. What do we got? Oh, I don't like this
decision. I'm changing it. No, I'm not. I really do believe that's one of the best consoles. Is it?
No, that's better. Is it that right? That's correct. Yeah. This is, this is good. Wait. No,
no, no, no. Hold on. Switch is not better than the regular Nintendo. Switch is better than the Wii,
I think. Switch is better than the Wii. Yes, it is. It's going to have more shelf life. Look,
it'll last a long time. It'll last like 15 years. The GameCube better than the Game Boy. Atari better
than the Dreamcast. Way more influential. Microsoft really not doing very well, huh?
No Microsoft stuff is above C for me. That's weird. This is much lower. I, you know what? I
actually really didn't hate the 360. This just had a lot of hardware problems. The Xbox One is,
it's so close to F, I think. If Wii U is F+, Xbox One is close. They just, they really just
dropped the fucking ball so hard. It's just not very good. I don't think I would put that down
here though. It's just barely there. It's sad. I haven't used, I have an Xbox One. Well, actually,
not anymore. I fucking gave it away. I gave it away. That's right. I don't have it anymore.
Yeah, I haven't used it. I didn't use it for like a couple of years. It just sat in my closet. I had
no reason to turn it on. So I just, I just wiped it and gave it away. Yeah, I forgot that I even
had it. All right, so hold on. Let me, I got B that seems correct to me. Where's the DS? DS should
be up here. Not this one though. No, I feel like they're like the same thing though. If I put like
the DS at B, I want like that to be at B2, then do it. Yeah, but it may as well just be the same
thing. Okay, this is B. This is one, two, three, four, five. This is B5. This is B5 too. The Xbox
better than the Genesis. The PSP was, I can't in, I can't a good conscious say that.
That the Xbox 360 was worse than the PSP. That feels wrong. I think it belongs like this. That's
fair because it wasn't bad. It was, it wasn't bad. Just was, it was just kind of normal.
That's, I'm good with this. All right, PS3 Master System, the Vita, which is the worst console
that I wouldn't buy or wouldn't want to play. No, it's the Xbox, it's Xbox One. It is. If you
handed me a Vita right now, I'd say, oh, okay, I guess, yeah, I'll play something. Whatever,
this is dumb, but I don't really, it's not dumb, but like I don't, okay, fine. If you handed me
an Xbox One and said, hey, play something, I'd be like, just take it back. Same thing with the
Game Boy Advance. I'd be like, okay, this is why you're handing me this. Master System 2, it's just
like, hey dude, here's a Master System. Check it out. There's like four games that were worth
playing on here. They've been re-released like twice. If Xbox 360 is up here, PS3 has to be
up here, but lower. And the original Xbox is going down here. This is fair. GBA does not belong in D,
but I don't, I don't, I don't have anywhere to put it because I can't reliably tell you
that I would rather play the Game Boy Advance than like the,
than like the fucking say, oh, hey, how are you? Hey, sorry. My internet turned off.
It's not like that's a normal occurrence every day. That's so out of the ordinary. I'm shocked
that it happened. It's absolutely shocking. What the fuck is going on? It's, it's, it's 12 15.
It's midnight. What is happening that the internet would just turn off? It's midnight.
Oh, those people playing Call of Duty. No, everyone's asleep. What's, what day is it today?
What date? What is, what day is it right now? It's fucking Thursday at 12 Pacific. Why would
the internet just turn off? Anyways, new face. No, I don't, I don't, I don't want to touch my
face with my like dirty hands. All right. Where were we? Let's finish this up before I get turned
off again. Computers, man, I swear to God, electricity under the ground and shit. All right.
What was I, it was a Game Boy Advance. I'll put it up here, but that means I have to downgrade
the Sega CD because Sega CD was dumb. It was real dumb, but it had a lot of fun novelty.
We played every single Sega CD game on this stream a couple of years ago, whatever, right?
It was, it was fantastic. What, what a fun time that was. What a fun time that was, but I would,
I would be disappointed if that was the console that I owned like 20 years ago.
Is this the Sega Saturn? Oh, that's the Saturn. I did not know that. Okay. That belongs over here.
Nevermind. No. Okay. Here's the question. What had less shit on it? What, what had less stuff
to do? The Sega Saturn or the Xbox One? Both had like a tiny library of stuff. What had less stuff
to do? It was, yeah, it had to have been said. There was like 12, it was like 16 games were
released for the Sega Saturn. I don't think more than 20 to 30 games released for that console,
right? Like 30? That's at least like 200 games for the Xbox One. All right. I think that's good.
Now down here, what is the worst console that I've ever played? I've never played the Ouya,
but I mean, like, come on. Whatever. I'll just, I'll just pretend it's down there. What's the worst?
It's the N-Gage. The N, it's the N-Gage. Like, what, it, it had no purpose. But the Wii U is
worse than the Virtual Boy? No, the Wii U at least didn't give you a headache. You got actual physical
damage done to your brain when you used this for more than an hour or two. This didn't damage
your brain. This one did. Move the switch to S. I've, I was fighting with that for a long time.
I like this. I like this already. No, don't, I don't, I'm questioning now. There you go.
There is your list. The, do a German tier list list. Which of my tier lists is the best?
You're going down too many layers there. You sure the PS1 is better? Better is not enough is the
right word. But PS1 was just a lot of influential stuff. A ton of great games, a ton of, like,
their series got their start on it. Super Nintendo, it can't beat it. It's the best console ever made.
It's just, you just like cheese. All right, guys. I think that's going to be it. I'm sorry
we had so many problems today, but it was really bad today. And it wasn't even bad in a sense of
we, it wasn't even dropping frames. It was just dropping everything. The whole thing would just
turn off. That sucks. So sorry about that. It's like, I think that's like four or five mods.
Not much I can do. I knew they were doing maintenance. They were doing something. They
were up, they were upgrading the node or something. They were doing something. So who knows? Maybe they
either fucked something up or maybe it's one of those scenarios where they're still working on it
because it was, the internet here was turned off for like eight hours or so. Six hours or so I think
yesterday, last night going into today. So I don't know. Why is the switch so high? Because
for the longest time, and I'm talking more than 15 to 20 years, I have been searching and hoping
for an entertainment device to take into the bathroom with me for my 40 minute shit.
I used to bring my computer into the bathroom and plug it in and like set up a desk in the bathroom
and sit there. I used to, it was bad. I used to sit, I used to bring my computer into the bathroom,
set it up on like a stand up pop up table, and then plug everything in and sit on the toilet
for a long, long fucking time. And even after I was done, I didn't, because like what a pain
in the ass that was to get it all in there. So my legs, my legs would start to tingle.
I would sit there for an extra like 25 minutes and I would have to like, I would be getting like
tingly legs because I was sitting there for too long. And that's what maybe had to get up.
I think I remember my mother at the time fighting this and eventually just being like,
whatever. Like you do, you, if you're gonna do it, if you're gonna do that, then go for it.
I think at first she's just like, what, what do you bring? Why are you doing all that? Why are
you bringing all that stuff into the bathroom? It's like, uh, because I wanted, I just, I'm like
working. I don't know, I was an idiot. No, no, no, I'm going to turn off. I'm going to turn off.
Listen to me before I go, before I turn off, I want to do the bits, but it's going to be
fucked up. Hold on. All right. Long story short, I can bring the switch into the bathroom and I can
shit on it and keep, and keep my hands close and not have to worry about my legs tingling.
So I can get up whenever I want and put it over. Okay. Done. My internet is going to turn off.
So let's try to get some of these bits done before we get shut off. Done. Let's get the, no, not BRB.
I will see you guys later. The next time you're going to see me, I've got some work to do
on a certain stream. So you will see me after this weekend. I'll be back on what day is it?
I will be back on Sunday. So it is right now it is Thursday. I'll be back on Sunday. There's a couple
of things I want to try to get started. I want to try to do a few things on, I want to try to set up
the Where's Waldo stream. So I'm going to work on that and see if we can get like a good announcement
I can make next week to set that all up. If you don't know what I'm talking about, you'll know
very soon. I also am obviously going to work on the other stream too. So I will see you guys on
Sunday. Sunday, Sunday, Sunday. But for now, let me see, let me try to get through these bits before
the internet turns off. And if it does, I'm sorry if I miss your bits or your subs. It's kind of out
of my control at this point, but I'm going to try. We're going to rapid fire these, which usually
means I'm going to do it much slower than normal. And some of these may have been broken up. I hope
not. Let me actually get this open. But thank you for joining me. It was a lot of fun. That
kind of a long one. Playing with Star was a lot of fun. It's fun teaching him how to clean a house.
We'll raid Vinnie. I'll raid Vinnie after this. That sounds about right. All right, so let's go
down earlier to today when it's just, I want to see where this cuts off because I, the stream
turned on and turned off like five times. Let me make sure this is correct. I think it is. And
earlier, I think because the stream turned off, I missed a couple of big donations and I want to
make sure I touch upon them. So at some point when the stream was having problems, Lady Wild
Moonchild gave $50. Vinnie is going to end in 30 minutes. Okay. Well, it's late.
That's okay. We can, we can hold the raids off then. And let's wait, is Joel streaming?
Raid Joel. All right, we'll raid Joel after this. Well, let's see who's streaming. It's late. Let
me get through this. Let me, let me get through the bits. And I don't really want to speed through
these because that's kind of rude. I hate doing that because right now I'm like kind of up against
the wire here with the internet. But thank you Lady Wild Moonchild for $50. I finally got a job
after recovering from a chronic illness. Your streams always cheered me up in a darker moment.
So I wanted to share some of my first paycheck with you for seeing me through hard times.
Thank you Jerma for the great content and for facilitating such an amazing community.
Well, I'm really, really, really glad to hear that you're recovering from
whatever it is. Thank you for the huge $50 drop. It's a lot of money for anybody to give anybody.
So thank you for that. And thank you for being part of this community
because without engaged, engaging people like yourself, it's, it would be kind of boring,
you know? So having a bunch of really, really fun, interesting people around is good. Very good.
Thank you for the $50. We also had $10 from Fahita Meat. Thank you Fahita Meat for the 10 bucks.
Look on the bright side, Jerma. You being short means you are the last one to get hit when it
rains. You still get hit at the same time. When it starts to rain, everybody gets hit at the same
time. It's an extra 0.0023 milliseconds. It's not a big deal. Thank you for $3 to Valentura.
And there's a big boop. Ha ha. Big boop. Thank you for the $3. Thank you Freudian Weapon for
the $5.56. They just say hello. Hello. Oh, they're from the soundboard. Right. Hello.
Thank you for the $5.56. We also had $5 from Infectious Frostbite. They say silent viewer
here. Love the streams. Keep it up. Will do. Thank you so much for the $5. I'm going to keep going.
Keep streaming. Thank you to AzzyDreamer for the $3. Hey Jerma, long time fan, second time
donator. Funny enough, I've actually followed your Twitch channel ever since you beat Deltarune on
stream. This is- and beating Jevil first try. I forgot to put that part in. This is just the
first time I had both the free time and money to contribute to a live stream. Don't worry,
I'll still be here regardless of whether or not you play Deltarune again. Oh, here we go.
P.S. Your battle with Jevil still gives me chills to this day. What a god of a gamer. Seriously.
Thank you. Sometimes I turn it off.
Jerma's stretch. Oh god. But thank you AzzyDreamer. And I really appreciate it. Thanks for the three
bucks. Uh, Devakitty thanks for the $2.50. Hey Jerma, tell the star his apartment is a jungle
story. Also, holy shit, cereal is a fucking excuse to sell kids candy for breakfast.
I don't- I don't- I remember. I think his heater was broken and it was just pumping hot air
into his apartment forever. And it was- you couldn't even be in it. It was like 85 degrees
in his room. It was something like that. Is that- that might not even be accurate. I know
it's something like that. Something was like wrong with his heater. 200. It was a fun stream,
Jerma. But I genuinely hope your- holy shit. Uh, thank you, the funky chicken for the $5.
Hey Jerma, I made this uh faux movie trailer using green screen and other stuff. Be cool
if you showed it. I think what I'm probably gonna do, because there still are green screens that
trickle in and little videos that trickle in. I think it's time. It's time to set aside
stream time for these. Instead-