Hey, how you doing everybody? Welcome to another day. I streamed yesterday but I had to
kind of take a little short there. Cut it a little short because I wasn't feeling well and I have a
cough. It's a deep cough. It's inside my body. Like it would be coming from somewhere else.
Outside. It's an outside cough. It hasn't gotten better. It's actually gotten a little worse.
And that's the unfortunate thing. I woke up this morning. I was a little slow.
I'm a little fatigued. But I don't give a shit because Sekiro came up. I've been waiting for
this game for a long time. So I don't care how bad I'm going to be coughing. I'm going to be mutant.
I'm playing this fucking game now because come on. What am I going to do? I'll wait like a few days.
No, no, no. Yeah, there's mucus but it's fine. The Drake no, no, no face.
But yeah, we're going to start Sekiro. I'm going in completely blind like we did Dark Souls 3.
We'll see how we do. I've heard it's a lot different. I've heard that the game
should not be played even remotely like a Dark Souls game. It emphasizes blocking and parries,
not dodge rolling. So I'm looking forward to this. Early boy. Yeah, we're a little, we are.
And I wasn't feeling great and I didn't want to just see, let it progress even more over the
next three or four hours. I took some DayQuil. Go back to bed. No, I'm staying right here.
It's Christmas morning for somebody that likes the game company from Software. Christmas only
comes once every four years with this company. When was Dark Souls 3? 2015, 2016, 17, 18, 19.
So Christmas comes once every three years. Thanks for the early stream. Yeah. How long
do you think I'm going to be streaming today? I don't know. It really depends on a couple of
factors. It depends on first of all how physically do I feel and if I get stuck on the tutorial boss
for the first like four hours. I don't know. I've been playing it since release and it might be
too hard. That's what I keep hearing. I keep hearing the game is too hard. I'm, I can't wait.
Your immune system is compromised because you're a vegan. Uh, I had a chicken sandwich last night
just for the record, you know. And there it is. God, I'm so excited for this. I wish I felt better.
I wish I physically didn't feel so fucking awful, but it doesn't matter. Everything's going to be
fine. I'm going to get the video game placebo effect and I'm going to start feeling way better
in about 10 seconds. This is Sekiro. Shadows die twice. Not like you haven't seen this intro
like 50 times. I'm one of like 16,000 people streaming this game right now. I was actually
going to type, we're talking to the pre-stream chat. I was going to title this stream in all
capitals. Please click mine. Don't scroll down. Click mine. I played Dark Souls. I actually played
Dark Souls. It's going to be in all caps. I actually changed. I went in here and I changed.
I'm curious as to how this is going to play out because for two reasons, right? I got an Xbox One
controller plugged in and I don't like the bumpers on the Xbox controller. So what I did is I changed
attack to right trigger and prosthetic tool to right bumper and guard to left trigger. I wonder
if that's going to be bad or not. I'm actually considering making attack X. I'm thinking about
you can use PS4 controllers. Yeah, but I heard there was issues with it.
And the button prompts screw me up too because the button prompts don't change to PS4.
Yeah, we'll try. I'm just going to play like this and see how it is. If I need to change it,
I'll change it, right? I'm stalling. I know that that top right. Did you see that auto save top
right thing? It's been so long since I've seen that. Set it to English. Yeah, it's on English
already. All right, here we go. It's been so long since I've played a software, a piece of software
developed by From Software. Blood on, subtitles on, HUD. This is all fine. This audio I think is at a
decent level. Software from From Software, yes. The game is meant to be played in Japanese.
We'll just go back and forth. Every like five minutes I'll switch it.
All right, cutscene. Here comes the opening cutscene.
In the closing years of the Sengoku era, Japan was consumed by perpetual conflict.
Takes place in Japan. The fires of war raged on, spreading deep.
Oh, nice shot. Was that bad or good? It has a germa hair. I gotta get comfortable.
This game is supposed to be the hardest game ever made. What is the hardest game?
Oh my god, shut up. No, no, not you, me.
We did it. Master swordsman Isshin Ashina staged a bloody coup and wrested control of the land.
What the what? What's the matter, stray? Nothing left to lose. Well, don't grab it by that.
Don't you understand? You gotta hand somebody a pair of scissors the other way and hand them
handle side, not blade side. From the battlefield, betraying relentlessly.
It's like kindergarten safety 101. Went on to become a master shinobi.
Was never for the shinobi. As your father, my master is as of today.
Defend him with your life. If he's taken, bring him back.
I'm sweating right now. I really am. I'm disgusting. I don't know if that's because
I might have a fever. I don't know. I'm going to say it's because I'm really excited for
Sekiro. Shadow's done twice. After Isshin's coup, the Ashina clan was on the brink of collapse.
And the shinobi, known as Wolf, had lost everything. Both the man who took him in
and the boy he had sworn to protect. Is that engine? Is that from? So I haven't seen any
gameplay. I've been pretty good about keeping away from it. I've seen like maybe I saw I think I saw
like the original teaser trailer, but not any. Hey, there's 10 straight minutes of gameplay.
This could be a strategy game or a puzzle game and I wouldn't even know.
Shinobi. Every minute is at least as hard as pinwheel. Good luck. Okay. That's good to know.
Thanks for the tip. Nice. All right. Here we go. Let's begin. Let's check the movement first.
That's really important. Is that the? Oh, it's the dodge roll. Nice. Yeah, everyone said the game was
way harder, but the funny thing is, is this is like, this is 400 dodge frames. Is it? Where's the
dodge? All right. No, don't miss anything. Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to pay close attention.
Portamental letter. A letter thrown into a well. Kuro's wolf. Your destiny awaits you at the moon
view tower. Escape from the well and find the tower bathed in moonlight. Moonlit greatsword
will be at the base. Even without a blade, you can reach it, stay silent, stay vigilant.
So escape the well. Okay. First that you can swim in this game. I didn't just fall straight through
into the, out of the map. Interesting. Uh, that's new. So I could go this way or that way. Can I
dive? I wonder if there's a dive button. What's over here? I got to turn the lights off in my room.
That's important. Whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm in the menu now. Hold on. Now it's, it's one, it's one
third in the afternoon, but the lights are coming off. This game has actual menus, apparently. There
we go. Now I can see a little better. The equipment menu allows you to change your currently equipped
quick items. There are five slots available to equip and switch out quick items as needed, right?
Okay. So it's just like Dark Souls. You have this, these are your inventory slots or equipment slots.
Interesting. All right. Unseen aid, vitality, attack power. We only got, we only got two stats
in this whole game. Vitality and attack power. Items currently in possession can be viewed
through the inventory menu. Okay. So this is my items. There's the idle. Let's see. I'm going to
read. Okay. Let's see. No, no, no. Don't touch that. A small palm-sized wooden Buddha can be
used repeatedly held by the wolf. Ever since he was saved by his father, its corners are rounded
with use. This Buddha is used to return home. It will return the user to the last visited sculptor's
idol or dilapidated temple. And I can use this as many times as I want. So this is a homeward bone
with an infinite value. Really unlimited bone. Yeah. Okay. All right. So, um, am I missing
something over here? Did you wall jump? No, nothing here. Maybe there's something like over here
eventually. Is this just like Mario 64? It was made by the, uh, I think the same exact developer
from Nintendo. I was, I know that was not funny, but you know, look, I'm sick today.
That is really cool though. And you keep just having a jump in general that I don't have to
be sprinting and then press like the left thumbstick in. What? Okay. Yeah. Well, that's
jump in air near to do a wall jump. Don't even tell me that you can even feel like Spider-Man
in this game. No. I mean, yeah, kind of. Oh, I just want to go so slow. If I'm sorry, if you thought
this is going to be like a fast playthrough of a guy like, yeah, let me just get to like the first
boss now. No, no, no. I just, I want to look at everything. I want to experience the game very
slowly. What if I just died? Thank God there's no fall damage. Otherwise that would have been death
number one. I need a weapon. Also another thing that I need to change. I need to change the,
no, maybe not. I'll get used to it. All right. We can go backwards or we can go.
All right. I got to like relax. I haven't even played the game yet. Let's go this way first.
No. Holy shit. Tug wall. You toggle it. Okay. I can go the other way. This is a shimmy.
You can peek around a corner. All right. Well, there's an enemy right there.
Stealth. Stealth. Advance without being seen by crouching in bushes or moving under floors.
You do not have a sword at the moment. You stealth to avoid enemies and head to the moon view tower.
You are about to be seen. Warning markers appear above enemy's heads. Oh man. This is a stealth
game. So, okay. Crouch. Well, you can see me. I'm in a bush. Okay. Let's just keep going.
Let's hang off the ledge. This feels like I shouldn't be able to do this.
Drop down. No, that's gonna kill me. Just let's go through the corn. Underfloor. Wolf can slip
into tight spaces such as beneath floors when crouched. You can go beneath floors. Like under
there. Okay. But what if I'm missing items? There's probably like an item I can go get over here.
Did I just do it? Oh, let me see. Because that's... Is there something else I can do?
No, I mean that's clearly going under the floor, but is there anything else I can do?
There's so many hidden fucking things in this game. No, I'm just gonna go.
I tried to do the infinite eye frame dodge. Died in the... Well, I'm just... I'm so conservative
of missing something. I'm just gonna go. Yeah, I'm just gonna go. Look, there's like an item over
there. I might go back. Am I never... Wait, am I never gonna be able to come back here again? Are
you sure? I figure this might have been a different way to go, but maybe not. There's nothing here.
All right, that's... I'm gonna call that strike one. The check is three strikes today. That was one
guy. No, I'm just gonna go. I'm just so happy that I get to play this right now. Under tight spaces.
That death doesn't count. All right, I got the eave drop there. Spider webs. Let's just go. So,
I'm assuming that's the tower, right? How much can I move without actually being seen, I wonder?
It's yellow and then it turns red, right? What about over here? No. Let's listen. Hole in the wall.
I mean, really. But you're not Sekiro. I'm Sekiro. I can do it easily. All right, so now...
Well, they got two... Oh, they face... Can I go down here? Can I just drop down there? I mean,
obviously, I have to go down there. I wonder how sensitive their hearing is. That's beautiful.
Oh, imagine living there. Jeremy never played a video game in his life. Elbertson. No, I just
don't know. In some stealth games, it's very sensitive. Their hearing or how close you get.
All right, I can jump this. I would have been very embarrassed if I died right there.
Uh, jump and in the air to ledge hang. Jump ledge hang. Is there a sprint? Okay, hold on.
There's a hole in the wall up here. Oh, there it is. Nothing else. What about a guy up there?
I don't see nothing. What about down here? No items. Oh, what does that mean? Not sturdy?
There's the hole facing the cliff. All right, I think we found our first character of the game.
Is this gonna alert enemies or something? No. First boss. Hey, no spoilers. That's strike two.
Even if it's incorrect. He just fucking flops me. Oh, that's a sword. Okay, I thought it was a pipe.
My shinobi, in accordance with the bond of lord and retainer,
you will I hereby welcome you to Sakura. Thanks for dying in the tutorial. But I was exploring
the controls. That doesn't count. As you command. The Kusa Bimaru, a katana given by Kuro, the divine
heir and heirloom of the Hirata family. A cadet branch descended from Ashino. Once thought lost,
it has found its way back into the hands of the wolf. The name Kusa Bimaru beseeches a shinobi's
role is to kill, but even a shinobi must not forget mercy. A mantra of the blade itself may manifest.
All right, weapon. All right, so this is the hub world. This is where I level up with my souls.
Loyal wolf, I see you are wounded. I have something that may help. Do you get it?
Okay, healing gourd. A gourd filled with vitality restoring medicine. Restoring, resting refills
the gourd. Okay. Made by an apprentice of the extraordinary Dr. Dogen. Though it is strange
that the gourd's medicinal waters refill automatically. The seeds within may hold the
secret to how it works. I could turn my mouse upside down because it's gonna keep doing that.
I'm gonna like put it on my desk and like upside down. Okay, so I have a estus kind of.
I'm not gonna change the audio to Spanish.
We got an escort mission.
I ask you to find that secret passage. Once you find it, signal me with a read whistle.
You got one of those? Like you used to long ago. I will join you as soon as I hear it.
All right, healing, using quick. You can cycle through various quick items to
and use each according to the situation, right? If you've taken damage, you can recover vitality
with the healing gourd. So use quick item and then cycle. Wait, so the use item is now up.
Oh, okay. I gotta actually put it on here though. Oh boy. I gotta change that. Yeah,
that's gonna screw with me the whole game. Let's go into binding here. So let's see.
Action is, this is action. There's a lot of, okay, use item. X is Y bound to anything?
Cycle prosthetic tool. Shit. I might have to get used to that.
Because drinking like the Estes is always that face button, whether it's square or X to me.
Somebody said rebind Y to up. Because that's a cycle prosthetic tool that's probably better
than Y, I would think. Use item, I'm going to say X and then action and collect loot, I'm going to
do Y. Because I will never ever get used to that. My muscle memory, my brain has different bindings
because of it. Yeah, but it doesn't matter. It really doesn't matter. Hitting X to heal is
something I will never be able to not do. So then Y is now my interaction button, which that's fine.
That's getting the car in GTA, right? That's interact. I can do that. There's a secret passage
beneath the moat bridge that can take us out of the castle. Find the secret passage beneath the
moat bridge so that we may escape Ashina Castle. When you've reached it, give the signal. I'll come
as soon as I hear a good whistle. So let's, how do I refill the gourd?
Didn't tell me that one. Smartass. All right, let's go upstairs. Nice physics. Look at that. Item.
Pellet. Medicinal pellets that slowly restore vitality. A secret treatment passed down for
generations in these lands. Records say it has been used in battle since times long gone
and lent to the famed resilience of Ashina warriors. A pill case full of these pellets would also serve
as a battle charm. Oops, I just broke it. Okay. One pellet. Is this a chest? Let me look at that
again. So pellet. Slowly restore vitality. Vitality is a stat. Huh. Okay. So, but vitality is not
health. No, it is health. Okay. All right. Okay. I'm thinking too hard about it. Well, I'm just
basing every, all my knowledge on from software. I thought maybe it was something to help with,
like a status effect or something. All right, let's go. And here we go. I just, I just opened
up the gates to Yharnam. Posture and death blows. A shinobi aims to break an opponent's posture.
Attacking an enemy is one way to achieve this. When an enemy's posture breaks, he is vulnerable
to a shinobi death blow. So right trigger is, I mapped it to that. Right trigger after breaking
posture is a death blow. So that's kind of like a, a, like a parry into a death blow or a
visceral attack would be more towards Bloodborne, I would say. So breaking an opponent's posture.
Here we go. First enemy. Is there a two-handed or is it, is it only one-handed? How does this work?
Let's see what happens. Do I have a dodge? Okay. Oh, I got two people at the same time. Let's just,
let's go. Let's go. Oh yeah. That's posture, right? Okay. Oh, I see. That's a different bar.
It's a separate bar underneath the health. Whoa. All right. Well, uh, okay. So there's two,
there's a health bar and then a posture bar. Does stamina exist anymore?
Wait a minute. There's no stamina. Holy shit. That changes everything. Let me go take, uh,
nothing else over there, right? Wow. All right. That's so cool. Oh my God. Yes. All right. Let's
go. Come here. Wait. Sometimes relentless attack is not enough to break an enemy's posture.
Deflecting enemy attacks is another way to damage their posture. A master shinobi uses
a combination of deflect and attack to achieve swift victory. Left trigger the moment an attack
lands is deflect. Let's give it a try. Let me see what it looks like. Okay.
There it is. So then you go immediately into it. So it's not as much a parry as it is. Okay.
I get it. So you get to treat it as a, that actually, that feels really good actually.
That feels fucking great. I'm not going to lie. All right. Two guys that way. Let's go up here.
Anything hidden? No, that's just where I came from. I guess I think I have to go that way.
Lock on. Yeah. By locking on targets. Yeah. While locked in, you can change with, uh, R.
It's much easier to attack and deflect and perform other combat actions with people that are in
front of you. All right. I guess I'm just going to go in that door. Let's see if I can get some
perfect lock ons here. Perfect parries. That's so what is that? I got one of those bars too.
Perfect lock on. So I, this is on PC. PC with an Xbox one controller. Is there a sprint?
One. Oh, you can instantly kill people. You just insta kill. Oh, where is he? This is leader,
leader. What? This is a boss already? A counter slash can be performed immediately after
deflecting. Yeah. That's what I was doing. This allows you to deal posture damage without giving
the enemy time to recover. Counter slash. So it is just sword play, huh? Let's see if I can.
He's got a big long swing. So that's his posture up there. Some powerful opponents require multiple
death blows to be killed. The number of death blows required to kill an enemy is shown by the
red circular markers above their vitality bar. So you got to do a death blow to kill bosses. You got
it. Ooh, that hurt. Watch my posture. That hurt. Back it up, back it up, back it up. I don't want
to break. Whoa. My posture just got increased by a shit load right there. So if I hold down block,
my posture goes back to normal. Okay. Whoa. Oh, he's going to break my posture. Shit. Okay.
Who's going to break first? You. Oh no. Oh no. He's almost broken. Oh, don't treat it like Dark
Souls. Oh no. Wow. That's a, that's different. That's very different. So, all right. If your
posture breaks, then you can die, but you could break their posture as well. All right. I'm,
I'm starting to understand how this works. Well, I'm already right there. Is there stagger? I want
to help pick up a stagger. But I don't lose posture when I attack. Okay. There is a stagger.
All right. I see. I kick because you can do that little block at any time. I'm, I'm using it as,
I got to remove the Dark Souls from my brain because a parry in Dark Souls takes a few seconds.
You know what I mean? Do it again. Am I dead? What? I'm going down again. Okay. I'm starting
to figure out what I'm doing here. So once he gets to that red area, you got to hit him
another couple of times. So here's another pellet. Okay. Interesting, interesting, interesting stuff.
I'm not going to heal yet. Wait, what else is over here? You're going to say that 20 times an hour
for the next three days. You know, it's, I'm starting to figure it out. You know,
we've got first boss done. You know, I'm starting to figure it out. Interesting. The mechanics are
pretty cool. I'm just starting to figure out like kind of how that works. Three bosses down.
Cool mechanic, but I, I'm not sure I completely understand it yet. It's very fun though. 45
minutes from completing the game. Yeah. I think I'm really comfortable getting comfortable now,
maybe on a second play through. I feel like I can do something here. No, it's yeah. You're,
it's offense and defense at the same time, which is something that you're not used to. Ash gripped
into a hardened clump, throw it at an enemy to temporarily distract them. The snow falls thick
and thus the hearth runs thick with ash. So you can throw dust in somebody's eyes. All right.
Unless we got here this down. Should I go in? Oops. What about the doors that were just over here?
Let me go in the doors. Can I open this or can it not be opened? Like, oh, it doesn't. Here we go.
Cannot open from this side. You know what that means. That means fall down here and
no, it doesn't. I almost did that. You almost just left. All right. I'm going to go up there
actually under the bridge, right? That's the bridge. Let's see what's over this way.
Should I be still thing in air near wall, wall jump, and then hang on ledge? Yeah. What's that?
Oh, I can each run with it. It's guarded now. What's that thing? What is this little weirdo
that's just sitting here digging? Uh, this is an, it's an enemy. What do I do about this?
What the fuck? Okay. Near edge. Um, who was that? I don't know who that person even was
or why they were here. It's the egg. Is this going to kill me? Oh, an item. Look. Oh, look at that.
What is it? Pellets. I should probably put these on the heart bar and the ash here too. So pellets
heal. All right. Oh, you got more rocks. Let me just take a gander across the way and make sure
I didn't miss anything. I mean this shit over there, but fuck it. Let's just go the way we're
going. Uh, any enemies? There's going to be something down here, right? Like right here.
No. What is this? Nothing. This appears to be at the escape route called the divine air with the
no, I found it. Okay. Hold on. No, no, no, no, not yet. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is there something else I can grab or do? Is this death? If I fall down this?
Hold on. You can't grab that. All right. Well, can I, hopefully I can grab this again. I need,
I need to know. Oh, it's not water. What the fuck is that? Okay. It's just a lizard.
Oh my God. That wasn't even, I don't even know if that was hostile.
I don't even know if that enemy was hostile. I'm sorry. I'm coughing. Anything else?
Yeah. I don't think I, I don't, I don't need to be doing that, but I'm going to, I don't want to just
blow through that part. Let me look up here. I feel like it's probably another pellet or something.
Maybe, maybe not. No, no, I can go here. Nothing else, right? No, not really. Just want to look.
No, I think we're good. I think we're good to go. Nothing else over here. That much of a fall might
kill you though. Still in the canyon. Oh, I'm taking my sweet ass time. You better believe it.
Although I might have to go all the way around again. Yeah. Well, at least I got to see the
lizard, right? You're supposed to ride the geckos. I don't know if I believe that, but
jumping around is really fun though. Here leads us to this ledge, which can I make a jump from here?
Oh my God. What just happened? All right. Well, that's, that's actually a really good thing
because I was almost just drinking that Estus because I pressed, my brain was pressing X.
Instead of Y. Okay, let's go. I should be able to get them from here. That looks good. Although,
what about over there? Oh shit, hold on. I think I, a shit load of money just came in.
We just gave 50 fucking dollars. Let me see what was. Oh, my mouse is up here, right?
Ow. Uh, Katz Beanie, thanks for 50 bucks. Thank you so much, Katz Beanie. 5000 bits.
There's a lot I would like to say to you, Jerm, but I just keep it, Jerma short.
I love your VR streams and your Dark Souls streams. I'm always happy to watch you stream
and thank you for being yourself. Uh, that's, that's really fucking kind of you. If you like
the Dark Souls streams, then you probably like this one too, because this is by the same company.
Thank you for your extreme generosity. You have 50 dollars. It means a lot.
Much love to you. Thanks for sticking around. 5000 bits. There's nothing I can do here. That
was Katz Beanie, by the way. All right. Blow the whistle. Are we in E mode only? What's going on
with chat today? Is it because it's Sekiro? People just lose their minds over a game like this?
You found it. Now, let us leave this place. Yes, my lord. To think that this is the only way
to run from the faded bloodline is the answer. No, is, are we in escort quest?
Escort quest territory. Get the mouse off the screen. There we go. All right.
Run away.
I didn't even mean to do that. I'm sorry.
All right. If I walked back out there, it was like jumping up on walls again. Hey,
let me just check the verticality of the game. See how it is. All right. That looks cool.
Where's the note that says welcome? Get good, right? Last we stood together was your uncle's
funeral. Lord Genichiro. Genichiro. I'll just hand the sword. Hey, you take this. You try.
It's like we have two lives. You can't beat him. I'll give it a go. Oh boy. One v one.
Is it going to have a huge boss bar underneath at the bottom? I hope so.
Uh, not necessarily. Oh God. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I didn't heal
yet. I didn't heal. I need to heal first. All right. Let's do it. So let's tap, tap.
What the hell was that? That little like, what the fuck does that mean? I am so confused.
I gotta back up. What the fuck? Why am I getting like a Batman indicator?
What the? Oh, I think, oh, that's supposed to happen.
That's how you become Sekiro. He turns and he says to the kid, it should have been you.
Is that all the Shinobi? The divine air will be coming with me. You were supposed to go first.
I would have seen the Batman indicators and then I would have fucking ran.
We're about to see, this is the E3 teaser. I thought he was doing that to his leg.
Oh, pale blood, you say? No matter. Just think it all and be a bad dream.
Don't mind the beeps. I'm just going to mute. Looks like death is not your fate just yet.
All right. The Shinobi prosthetic, the artificial arm of a Shinobi passed down by the sculptor,
a replica of a human arm fitted with a variety of mechanisms,
apparently designed with a modification in mind, with modification in mind.
Well, if there is a number of cuts and is stained thick with blood and oil,
it has been impeccably maintained. Interesting. Okay.
What do you call yourself? The eyes of a wolf who has failed in his duties.
Or so it seems to me. That is not your concern.
Spoken like a true Shinobi. This dude is huge.
Dialogue options of how you got here. Ask about your new arm. How'd you get here?
What am I here? All I did was drag you here.
Didn't even know if I was dragging a corpse. Go get eaten, vile dogs.
When was I asleep? Some time has passed since I found you.
I see. However, your master,
yet lives. He's being held prisoner in Ashina Castle.
They will soon make use of his bloodline. I wonder if this is the hub.
Looking at you, I'm sure you appreciate the value it has.
Okay. Ask about your bloodline. What did you mean when you said they'll
make use of his bloodline? I don't know much about him,
except the dragon's heritage. There's a special kind of blood by that name,
and that blood runs through your master's veins.
Of the Divine Heir? Someone's after him.
Might be that the strange things happening to your body
have something to do with that. All right.
Might as well ask. What did you do to me?
That is what I call the Shinobi Prosthetic. A fitting fang for a one-armed wolf.
You're getting to where I have where I reached. Gonna beat the game myself.
See you later, Teramo. See you later, Pat. Enjoy the game.
It seems really fucking cool.
Any Shinobi tools. Shinobi tools.
I see this device. You catch on quick.
So this is kind of like a blacksmith. If you give me Shinobi tools,
I'll find a way to Shinobi Prosthetic. I appreciate its worth.
I've said too much. Go now. You're quite the strange one.
Huge amount of money just came in again.
Other peculiar visitors have come to this temple.
Oh, let me just get to the end of the sequence.
There's one in the clearing to the right of the gate,
leading off the temple grounds.
Two strangers in strange circumstances.
To the right of the gate, okay.
You too might get alarmed.
All right, so I got the Shinobi Prosthetic.
Hold on one sec.
I don't know why this keeps doing this.
There we go. That's better.
Juno Upsetto gave $50.
Thank you so much Juno Upsetto.
Two very, very large monetary contributions back to back here within 10 minutes.
So, that's a fucking lot. Thanks guys.
Juno, you say, you say, I've been under the weather recently.
Guess it couldn't help to spread a bit of positivity.
Love you guys. Jerma Heart.
Hell yeah, thank you. Sorry you're not feeling well.
Neither am I.
Unfortunately, I don't know why it seems whenever I get sick
or you guys get sick, I get sick too. It's weird.
But, welcome to the hub world.
This is probably what this is.
I'd be surprised if it wasn't.
On Sculptor's Idol.
Commune. Commune with Sculptor's Idol.
Sculptor's Idol serve as a checkpoint and can be found throughout the area.
It's like a bonfire.
Completely replenish vitality and restore one's
one use of resurrection.
One use of, additionally quick items and spirit emblems in storage
would be added to your current inventory.
With some exceptions, resting will also revive defeated enemies.
Uh, okay.
So, I get, I get, I get, I get.
Resurrection. Unseen aid.
30%.
My, my god.
Shadows die twice. Yeah, that makes sense.
Uh, um, what, what have you done?
Die, die 335.
That's 225.
That is an uncountable amount of damage.
That is an uncountable amount of money.
Thank you for the 225 bucks.
They say, don't know what to say, but here, laughing my ass off, take it.
Okay.
I guess I'll take it.
That's a fucking ridiculous amount of money, die.
Thank you.
Holy shit.
Streamer can't count to 225.
Well, I can, but that's uncountable.
Another NPC coming in here.
Jesus.
No, it isn't. It's uncountable.
But thank you, die.
My god.
That's fucking insane.
Okay, so what does she do?
Oh.
You got any more of them?
Is it weird that anytime somebody says that I'm a doctor, I don't believe them.
I just got, trust me, I'm a doctored.
The medicinal waters in this gourd spring forth on their own.
Even after being emptied, you will find it full again after a short rest.
Yes.
Is there a way to improve it?
Bring me gourd seeds.
Gourd seeds?
Yes, medicinal waters grow from gourd seeds.
Adding new seeds will increase the volume of these medicinal waters.
If you find any, bring them to me.
Alright.
Okay, do I have one?
Oh, I don't have any.
Hold on, what else do you got?
I'm glad you've come. I'd like to make a request.
Request?
Please show me your face.
What?
This white mark.
Is it a birthmark?
No.
That's a correct reaction.
What?
I have to show my face again.
Okay, anything else?
Receive the dragon's heritage.
Hmm.
Oh, yes.
Okay, just making sure there's nothing else?
Yes, right. That don't do anything funny.
Yeah, I won't.
Alright, so we've got our place of rest right here.
And then we can go this way, or we can go that way.
Now, the question is, which way is correct?
Grappling hook.
The shinobi prosthetic grappling hook allows access to normally unreachable places and a chance to take the high ground.
Nearby grapple points are designated with a circular symbol.
When this symbol turns green, the grapple point is within reach.
And I've got a left bumper.
That's so cool. Hold on.
Let's just take a look.
Might as well try it.
Well, that's awesome. Can I do it?
Does it have to have an indicator there, or can I just do it whenever?
I guess I can just do it.
Okay, this is Ashina Outskirts.
I wonder if this is where I need to be.
Maybe.
Sculptor's Idol travel.
You can now instantly travel between Sculptor's Idols that have already been communed with.
Travel can be accessed via the Sculptor's Idol travel menu.
So, any of them.
So, okay, that's good.
This goes to important places.
So this is the, yeah, Outskirts.
There's the dilapidated temple.
This is the temple, and the Outskirts is really all I have.
I love how important places is here.
Alright, so we've got a bonfire.
Let us...let's just go.
Can I grapple that?
What about down there?
Can I make that? If I jump and grapple, am I gonna die?
I need to test.
Should I test it?
No, you can't! You can't, Spider-Man!
It was worth a try.
I didn't die, though, somehow.
There's definitely something I can do over there.
But, for the sake of progress, let's just see what happens.
Go this way.
Uh, I can go to the building here.
This is too much freedom!
Oh, I could just go that way.
What about this guy?
Stealth deathblow.
You can perform stealth deathblows on opponents unaware of your presence.
So you can Batman people.
So the plunging deathblow is one of these performed when leaping at an unaware enemy from the high ground.
So you jump and then swing.
Once you are locked on.
Let's try it.
Awesome.
And then there's loot. Enemies drop loot such as items and money.
Multiple enemies can be looted at once.
Really.
And from a distance away.
Items found in the world are different than loot in that they must be approached to be picked up.
Press and hold Y to acquire loot.
Press Y near world item to pick up.
So there's just like a money grabber.
Interesting.
Some pellets.
And you can only have three of these, alright?
Alright, what about down here?
Let's go...
Nothing.
I'm gonna go across that bridge, though.
Can I make that jump?
Come on. I can grab that from here.
Really?
Come on.
You can go up, down, around.
One could get lost simply just doing basic tasks right now.
Ceramic shard.
A piece of pottery that breaks with a satisfying crack.
Throw it at an enemy to draw their attention.
I feel like for the stealth portion of this game, some of this stuff is gonna be fairly important.
And why would they give that to me right now?
Okay.
I was gonna say.
Wait a minute.
Can I just do this?
Fuck.
I'm trying to jump down.
You know what I was trying to do.
He jumped backwards.
What a pro.
Alright, let's go.
Fuck this, man.
Just go up here and drop down on somebody.
Whoa!
You are just flurrying right now.
I wanna get that guy from jumping down.
Wait. Grab the items. Very important.
It's a huge jump when you jump off of one of those ledges.
You launch.
Let's get this guy.
So this is a currency.
Odd.
There is some sort of currency thing.
What?
Okay. I thought I was gonna fall.
Alright.
Oh my god, guys.
Oh my god.
This is so much money.
Oh fuck, there's a guy right here.
Can I stealth kill him?
Can anybody see this?
No. Alright, hold on.
GuyDude
GuyDudeSM
or GuyDudesm
just gave a $250
on top of the $225
that Dai gave earlier.
Oh my god, guys.
Thank you, Guy. GuyDude.
Hey there. Not much to say. Just want to donate to probably the only streamer
or YouTuber I watch nowadays.
Thanks for being a big inspiration.
UWU.
I don't even know how much money that was.
It's uncountable. Anything over $225?
But holy shit, guys. Seriously.
Thank you, GuyDude, for the $250 fucking dollars.
What an insane amount of money
to receive in one second.
My goodness.
Hold on.
I only have $225 fingers.
Alright, what about this guy? Is that a...
What if I just surprise this dude?
Ready? Watch this.
Oh, he has a gun.
Bullets and...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Who's here?
AshGryptant? Yeah, I know what that is.
I can deflect bullets,
but more importantly...
That was actually kind of scary.
There's an item over here that I missed.
So how do you deflect a bullet?
Ungo Sugar.
Sugar candy made in Sun Phao temple.
Sustaining Ungo's blessing.
Temporarily reduces vitality damage
taken from physical attacks.
Bite the candy
and take the Ungo stance
to impart its inhuman benediction.
By doing so, you endure the excess karma
of man from the spirits within.
They spread this candy across Ashina
so it's like a defense candy.
I wonder how long it lasts for.
I've got so many items.
I wanted to take a look up here.
Let's get up there.
And up this way.
You can just climb on houses.
Ah, I see an item.
Item that I missed over here.
More sugar.
Cool, alright, let's go.
You can, Spider-Man.
You just have to be close enough.
Oops, that's not death, right?
No, it's not.
Can I get up there?
Is there anything on top of this house?
Don't fall.
That's not another
50 plus dollar donation, right?
There's not much else I can do up here.
It is.
The Reno just gave 50 dollars too.
I'm going to stop playing because I'm a bad gamer
and was starting to rage.
Can't wait to watch this happen to you.
Anyway, I'm enjoying the stream thus far.
Good luck. Thank you so much, Reno.
I am ready to
get absolutely fucking shit on.
But I'm taking my time.
I don't want to just blow through it.
I really appreciate
the 50 dollars
on top of all the other money that has come in.
You guys are too much.
Alright, dog. This is a soul staple.
Now I'm going to deal with the dog.
Let's deal with the dog like this.
Oh fuck.
He's dead?
Oh shit.
The dog
I killed the dog in one hit.
Is that a checkpoint?
Wow.
Alright, cool.
Dog down.
Why can I grab that? I'm getting the checkpoint first.
Bonfire found.
Sculptor's idol found.
Crest.
Travel.
Can you travel to every single one?
Yeah, you can.
So this is the gate path.
Let's get the idol.
Another ceramic shard. Who's this?
It's a dog.
Oh right, right, right.
I respawned the enemies.
Oh shit.
I'm forgetting the most important mechanic
in any of these games?
Really?
Of all the things to screw up.
Oh my god.
What an idiot.
Hmm. Let me think.
Name two things that happen in every
souls game.
You die and enemies respawn.
Oh. I'm not going to make that mistake again.
Dogs can't even get up here.
Who cares? Who's this?
Uhhhh.
A mechanical device made by
the mechanical genius Dogen.
Can be fit into the shinobi prosthetic
to become a working tool.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
As well as palm sides, a surprising number of
shuriken can fit into the shuriken wheel.
As the edges were designed for stacking,
find example of what can be achieved
when one matches mechanical finesse with a shinobi's
talent. So I got a
part. They can't be used on their own
by giving them to the sculptor. They can be
fitted into the prosthetic. You can quickly return
to the sculptor via travel from a sculptor's idol
or use the homeward bone.
Interesting.
Let's just go put it in now.
I feel like I need to do that now. I have an upgrade
mechanic. Might as well
use it.
Get up there.
Get up on top. Thank you.
Fucking consumerism.
What?
I got something for you. Fucking consumerism.
I don't even know where that came from. Why did I
read that?
I don't know why I read that.
Seems you know this prosthetic
very well.
It used to be mine.
The more demonic my sculptures
will become, give it here.
I'll fit that tool
for you.
Fit new tool.
There's a little menu here.
Regular shinobi tools found in the world
can be specifically adapted to the shinobi
prosthetic with the fit prosthetic
tool.
So loaded
shuriken.
Polish
costs spirit embers.
Spirit embers?
Pull a shuriken loaded into the wheel
and launch at a target in a single flowing
motion. The swiftly thrown shuriken
damages enemy vitality and posture.
Particularly against those with a tendency
to take to the air.
Alright. Loaded shuriken.
Okay. So is
that on there?
Another fifty bucks.
Fifty dollars from
Koopa Troopa.
Hey Jerma, I thought this was the right time to donate
to. You have offered me and my brother so much
entertainment. I thought it was time to give back.
Thanks for everything and enjoy the game.
Thank you so much for the fifty
dollars. Happy you
and your brother can enjoy
the streams and videos and stuff. Thank you so much.
Seriously.
Big money today. I know. Apparently.
Prosthetic tool. Prosthetic tools
are shinobi tools adapted for use. There should be prosthetics.
I have a shuriken now.
So equipment menu and then using
them is spirit emblems.
So a prosthetic tool is right bumper.
Let's see here.
So I have prosthetic
tool slots. There are three slots available.
On the equipment selection
screen the controls can be viewed through Y.
Okay.
So I have the loaded shuriken
and that's all I can do now.
So that should be right bumper
is how to use this.
What is this?
You see the kind-faced Buddha there?
That isn't one of mine.
It was carved by the true
sculptor. The true sculptor.
A man must confront what is inside
of him. It can probably
be of help. Confront what
is inside him? Anger.
Sadness. Or perhaps
old memories of times
long gone.
I wonder if we can do something with this.
Spiral. So now
I guess it's time
spirit emblems
are required
to activate prosthetic tools and are consumed
each time these abilities are used.
They can be obtained from defeated
enemies in the world and purchased from
sculptor's idols.
If you pass near them they will find their way to you.
Interesting.
I wonder if this is
Derma's crying right now. What?
So you can only use this twice.
Before you have to redo it.
Interesting. Purchase spirit
emblems.
Two out of fifteen.
How much do they cost? Ten bucks?
What? Shit.
I don't even know how this works. I wonder if I should
buy a couple of these?
Not yet. Prayer bead.
What is the unseen aid?
Thirty percent. I have no idea
what it means. Let's just keep going. I've got no idea
what's going on. I just got
two thousand dollars. Don't be so stingy.
Oh yeah. That's just fucking
consumerism. Wait.
I can get up there. Oops. Oops.
Oops. Oops.
No. No. Can't stay
up there.
I just Mario jumped on his head.
No. Go up here.
Alright. We're fine.
Fucking consumerism.
They'll forget about me in a second.
Can I grab that?
They don't know I'm here, right?
Is there like an aggro range or something?
There's a giant
turkey. What? Why? Wait. Hold on a minute.
There's an enemy chickens?
Giant chickens?
No.
Why are there huge chickens?
And why did I
just murder it for no reason?
That's
so dumb. I love it.
Alright. We're just circling back around.
That's the best enemy
in any Souls game, I think.
Personally speaking here.
I'm so glad there are giant chickens.
Look at that. Let's go over there.
This isn't a Souls game. I know. I know. I know. I know.
Alright.
Guy right there. That is a
super bad guy. So I need to be
prepared. So let's go like
this. Let's wrap around.
Does he see me? Can he see
me? There's an item over here.
Watch out for that super bad guy.
Okay. Still hidden.
It's full of ash.
Oh. He sees me.
Alright. This is the first time we're going to get to see this.
Some enemies use unguardable
perilous attacks,
signified with a danger symbol.
When these occur, watch carefully
and try to respond properly as each
type requires a specific response.
As thrust
deflect,
jump, or
a grab.
What do they mean by sweep? So sweeping
attack. I'm assuming from left to right.
Thrust is straightforward.
Grab is a grab. Okay.
Let me just take him and figure this out.
Sweep is jump.
Like that?
That's what that means, right? Let me see.
Oops-a-daisy.
Alright. I get it.
That's sweep.
What the hell does
that mean though?
So you can interrupt it though too.
I think.
What about my... Should I use my
weapon thing?
Let's see. Don't even let him do it.
Don't even let him do it. Oh shit.
Oh fuck. No, no, no, no.
Okay. That symbol right there fucked me
up. Jesus.
Safety roll.
Alright. So I thought I had...
To stay down after being...
To stay down after being knocked to the ground
surely means death. Safety roll can be used to quickly
recover from being knocked down or posture
broken.
A will be a safety roll.
So what it was...
I'm trying to remember the controls for that.
Oh wow.
That was a fucking weird move.
Oh shit. I'm in trouble.
I'm dead. What the hell was that?
He did this little like...
He did a little tiny kick.
Wait.
Die or resurrect? Why do I have...
What?
Hold on. Why do I have a fucking arcade
continue screen? Should I come back?
Resurrect.
I get to die two times. That's the title of the game.
What?
The Divine Heir's Blood grants the ability to return
from the dead using Resurrective Power.
One charge is always
restored by resting at a Sculptor's
Idol, killing enemies restoring
additional charges.
Resurrection becomes unusable immediately
after using it for killing enemies will make it available
again. Alright.
So when you kill
people you get to charge your
comeback to life bar.
Shadows die twice.
If sometimes. If they've killed enough people.
Okay. Let's go.
That's a different move.
Oh my god. I'm gonna die again. Do I get...
Do shadows refill my health thing?
That's a grab.
Right. Okay. Grab is different.
Holy shit.
Back it up. Jesus Christ!
I'm almost out of posture.
I had it too.
I'm dead. I'm dead. Safety roll. Safety roll.
Oh fuck man!
When he swings that... You gotta...
Fuck!
So you don't want to take that many hits.
I gotta get back to my full posture
again.
Oh fuck. I'm dead.
Oh boy.
Shadows die
thrice. Alright.
Let's see what happens here. Experience
toward the next skill point
and current Sen in hand are
halved upon death.
Sends them money. Everything lost is
gone for good.
There are no known means to escape this
loss. However, through the grace of the gods
or Buddha it may not be impossible.
So wait a minute.
When you die
you lose half of everything.
And there is no go back and pick up
your money.
Oh shit. Really?
Wow. 44!
Oh!
No!
You lose forever!
Give me...
Just don't die. Apparently
I have no more pellets. Alright.
Let's get back over there.
Now that I've...
Scripted. Scripted death.
Is the chicken back? Just don't aggro the chicken.
Let's do this again.
Wait a second. Alright. Shadows only die
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Get up there.
No. Nevermind. Let's go. Let's go. Fuck it. I'm ready.
Watch that
fucking sword.
Who broke?
Me or him? Oh come on. What?
He's so close.
Let's go.
Ugh.
Fuck me. You're not doing that. Break him!
Break him! Alright. See you later.
A loose prayer bead. Offering
four of them in a sculptor's idol will increase
maximum vitality and posture.
Apparently the wolf has
one bead. Oh. That's leveling up.
Gotta see.
Do you reckon he practices these noises
in front of the bathroom mirror?
Like what?
So a seed from the healing waters
give to Emma to increase the maximum
uses of the healing board.
Right. There it is.
I hope you can't
lose these, right? I would
hope not. It would be pretty bad if you could.
But anyways, let's take a look
up here. Make sure I don't miss anything.
Doesn't look like I missed anything.
Yes I did. Shadows
check both ways.
AKA twice before crossing the street.
The pellet though. Alright.
Well, that guy's not gonna respawn.
He's like a super enemy. I'm gonna go back.
Good one, somebody said.
I actually left. See? Good.
The enhanced physical attributes option
has been unlocked in the sculptor's idol menu.
You can spend four prayer
beads to create a prayer necklace
which will permanently increase
your vitality and posture.
I need four.
Well, let's just go get
our gourd
upgraded.
So, what do those bar...
What does the thing in the lower left?
See that pizza pie with the hat
with the pizza slice taken out of it?
What is that timer?
It's your resurrection pizza, okay.
Of course.
It's a FromSoftware game, of course.
If they give you the option to just die,
there's some reason why you shouldn't resurrect.
Right? Okay, here.
If you could just resurrect,
there wouldn't be a
like, battlefield-style
just die button.
Okay, cool.
So, I have a question.
So, when you die,
right, does it matter
if you resurrect or not, do you still
lose half of all your shit no matter
what, or does the resurrection
stop the halving
of your stuff?
No. You don't lose shit
when you... Okay, so there's two sides
there. There's definitely gonna be
some kind of penalty for resurrecting.
But the penalty for not resurrecting is losing half
your shit. Okay.
I didn't... Hold on. I didn't
go this way at all. What is over here?
This is
an NPC that I haven't even talked to.
Your name? Won't tell me.
But you do have the look of a skilled
shinobi. A shinobi.
Or perhaps.
Sir, please heed
my humble request. Face me
in battle.
I wasn't
ready for that.
Wait a minute, this is like a from
software game. Should I let this guy kill me?
Should I not have done that to this guy?
Oh.
Is that it? Are we friends now?
Do I get to have your house?
He's... Not wrong.
He's kind of morbid, but okay.
Yeah.
I guess.
He's just bored.
Let's do it again.
Training.
Practice the basics of evasion.
Practice the basics of attacking.
What's the flex?
This is cool.
Sometimes relentless attack is not enough.
You have deflecting enemies' attacks, damages their posture.
Do three death blows.
I'm dead. I'm back.
I will.
I didn't even know you could do this.
Hold on. You can.
So there is a hold down
in charge. Alright.
Basics of attacking.
I stand as your opponent.
An enemy with broken
posture is vulnerable
to three death blows.
Yes, yes, yes.
Kid. Kid.
I wonder if eventually
I can get... I'm probably going to get some posture breaking
stuff.
Right. I'm going to get a
thing that costs 10
emblems to use and it's going to break like
50% posture or something. Alright. Step dodge.
We didn't really even learn this.
I stand as your opponent.
It allows you to avoid attacks. Dodging won't compromise
enemy posture but may help
avoid damage.
Evade enemy attacks and then attack and
perform three death blows.
Yes, I will.
I like how the animation of the death blow can happen
in front or behind. It's cool.
Kid. Kid.
Spend the whole stream killing this
one guy. So you can
feel good.
I think it's about time we tried
something closer to a real fight.
Come at me with the intent to kill.
No better way to prepare
for the real thing. What's wrong?
Why do you go to such lengths?
Half to pass the time.
And the other half... Expert training.
I want to loosen that
furrowed brow of yours.
Alright. Enough talk.
Sorry. Let's begin.
Free combat is now available.
Begin free combat. Fundamentals.
Now. Let's begin.
Yes.
You got more?
Practice what you've learned. Sure thing.
Fine. I'll just break you.
I'll break you.
Again.
So when they go for a grab
they don't get attacked. New training
is available. What?
Counter...
This is a...
This is going to be a
consecutive deflection.
I stand as your opponent.
Okay. Deflecting once
doesn't always mean an enemy will stop attacking.
Consecutive attacks can be countered with
consecutive deflections. Which can
greatly damage enemy posture.
Deflect all enemy attacks.
And before three death blows.
Let's see what happens here.
Three, four...
You gotta get it though. You gotta time it.
So it's...
That's going to be so hard
later on.
Imagine some of the bosses later on
that you're going to have to do that like ten times
in a row. Alright. Vitality
and posture.
You might as well just practice now.
The lower one's vitality the slower their posture
recovery is. This is good to know.
For enemies with seemingly unbreakable
posture use techniques such as
dodge.
Counterattack reduces their vitality.
Making their posture easier to break.
Ah.
Okay.
So...
Alright. This is very important
information. So
if somebody has high health
you're not going to ever be able to break
their posture if they're hard to break through.
So you have to get their health
down by dodging
or by hurting them. Not by
going blow to blow with the sword.
To a point where you can bring down
their posture. I would have
been raging at
this later on.
Why does this guy have such high posture?
Game's fucking broken.
So it's good that I did this.
So they recover posture slowly.
Oh that's so much better.
Yeah look at that.
You can just swing it on like once or twice.
Yeah.
That is a huge piece of information
that you need to know.
How bad it is. I'm glad I figured this out.
Alright let's come back to the
back out here please. I don't want to
phase out.
I did not see this tutorial.
This guy's actually fairly easy just to
walk by and never see.
It doesn't lower their posture, only their posture regeneration.
Yeah but that's still a big deal though.
I'm going to do it all. Countering
thrust attacks.
You can kill through vitality
as well as long as you can hit them
I guess somewhere in their back or a place where they can't
block.
Thrust attacks cannot be guarded
but they can be countered by deflecting
or step dodging to the side.
Okay I was kind of panicking when I saw this before.
So if you do a side
dodge you can counter.
Or if you deflect.
Or do a step dodge.
Alright so there you go. So before I thought you had to
Okay.
You can also block it too.
It's the right time that is.
You've got to be perfect. I'm not certain
I'm confident in being able to deflect
that especially if it goes right for you
and you can't block it.
Maybe.
What happens if this guy kills you?
You take his place.
This is important. Sweep attacks.
Sweep attacks cannot be guarded
or deflected. They must be jumped over
to be avoided.
Jump kicking an enemy during sweep attacks
deals heavy posture
damage. Perfect.
Often leading directly to a
death blow. Also great to know.
So jump in mid-air near the enemy
jump kick and it does a ton of posture damage.
Let's take a look.
Oh it's no. Alright
hold on a minute. It's just A twice.
Right.
Holy shit.
If I knew that before.
That last boss
that little mini boss that I fought.
That general. I would have killed him in probably
15 seconds.
Again.
How far? Okay you've got to be
close though. You can't do
it from that far away.
Again.
So the easiest way
to remember that is sweep is
AA. Thrust is
dodge or deflect.
And grab is dodge.
Let's do it again. Free combat.
What do you got? Back up this way.
Come on.
You're too far away. Oh
okay. I've got to get that right.
Ooh. It's hard to tell
sometimes. Ooh.
Thrust. Thrust is deflect
or dodge. You know what? I'm going to do dodge.
If I see that and I know it's a thrust
I'm going to dodge.
Yeah the sword comes up to the
head.
Oh easier on me.
Apologize.
I'm so sorry
sir. I don't mean to kill you.
I've killed him like 12 times.
Give thanks or apologize. I feel like this is important.
Maybe I'm going to say sorry.
Give thanks or apologize.
Give thanks or apologize. One false
move and this could go wrong.
Apologize. Bloodthirsty
streamer.
What?
Okay.
So
that's the training. What about talking?
What is that? From left?
A from laugh?
Yep.
It's in every game. Wait.
Something interesting in the box?
What's in the box? Items that become
unavailable elsewhere end up in the offering box.
When the box is
illuminated it means an item has found its way inside.
Items can be obtained by inspecting the box
and offering money.
The box is empty. Okay.
First P?
I think it's time for the first P
of the day.
Two hours. Two hours per P.
See you in like two minutes.
Who the fuck would sub to German?
You? You're subbed.
There's $50
from a minute, two minutes ago.
Toshiro.tv just gave $50.
You guys are showering me with fucking
money tonight. Holy shit.
Thank you. How do you feel knowing you
can hurricane Rana in From Software
games? Very satisfying
to do these moves.
A green shower.
Seriously, I don't even know
what to say. Thank you everybody.
This is an absolute shitload of money.
Thank you. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
That's all I can say.
I can't believe it.
Let's hope you're enjoying the stream.
Speaking of the stream. Do you ever go to bed soaking
wet? Oh.
Do you ever go to bed soaking wet? I do not.
I do not go to bed soaking wet.
Cool. So we learned some tactics, some
techniques. Things that are good to know.
Let's continue the
journey. Didn't I get a better
healing gourd? Healing gourd.
There we go. Purchase
travel enhance. I don't have it.
Can I lose these prayer beads?
I'm scared I'm going to lose the prayer beads.
Turn on the Japanese
dialogue for a cutscene or two.
Alright. After
I beat
the first boss. I'll do it.
Which will be in like 15 minutes. I'm fucking being
the first try.
Back to it. This is where the
we just sit right here. This guy doesn't respawn.
I don't think.
Progress.
Why do you cough then mute the mic?
Well, because it's hard to
suppress a cough and I have to reach forward
and press button
here on my stream deck.
So what happens is I end up getting like
a quarter of it out before I have to press this button
here to mute. So it's hard to
sometimes predict it's
going to happen. Mute and then do it. I've done it
you probably heard a few
times it just go dead silent because I caught it early.
I am trying to
squelch that though.
I do apologize if it's annoying.
Okay.
Trees. Look at all these places to jump to.
All right. What we got? One guy.
Crows. We're going to go
crow route. Maybe.
I'm not quite close enough to that.
I can go this way.
I have to see what's going on with
these crows.
Light coin purse. Before it's filled with
a small amount of sen it can be used to acquire
the sen inside. Has a somewhat
satisfying weight to it.
I'm not opening that.
Oh my god.
Oh.
I was trying to jump.
Somebody has a gun.
Who has the gun? That's
guy. Boy there's a lot of people here.
Which one has the gun?
I'm not even locked onto him.
That guy. No. I think he doesn't
have a gun. Shit.
Oh my
god. There's too many people.
Actually too many people.
Aggro the whole entire
fucking city.
So unlike other
From Software games. No I was just
locked onto that guy.
It's actually really hard to fight more than one
person at a time. Before you could kind of
just get like a big weapon and just swing it in a circle
and kill five people. Oh my god.
Somebody just gave 20 community subs.
Come here. No wrong guy.
I wanted to lock onto the guy in front of me.
Why the hell would I want to lock onto the guy
behind him? I can't see
shit. Oh fuck I'm dead.
Come on. Swing. Come on.
Swing.
There's still somebody with a gun.
Alright. Who gave the 20 community subs?
Seriously. I
missed it. Those gift subs
just crashed the app on my
phone. It's Bob.
It's Bob time.
Thank you Bob. And thank
you for your time. Alright.
I gotta get up. I'm killing this
guy. Can I like stealth
grab him or something?
I guess. I guess so.
That whizzed right by my head.
I'm just gonna take it.
Cause it...
Oh what?
I didn't. No.
I was trying to. I was gonna
block it. I couldn't even see him.
Should I resurrect?
Oh I don't know what this means. I don't know
how bad this is. No I'm just dying.
This is gonna be bad for me to resurrect this
many times in the beginning of the game.
I'm so scared to resurrect.
Alright. Well this time I don't want
to aggro the entire
camp. Death is worse.
I don't know
that yet. I still have the coin
purse. So I'm good. Alright.
Let's jump down here in stealth.
I don't think it's a penalty for resurrecting.
Where's the
guy with the shoot you in the head
sniper rifle?
There's an item over there. He's right there.
Alright. I'm gonna wrap around. This is what I'm gonna do.
Go on over there. I'm gonna jump on the
tree. Can they see me
on top of them? Do they have the ability
to look up in the air?
Let's eavesdrop.
I want that item down here.
What? Where was my
Well can't you do a stealth takedown?
I thought it was a stealth
takedown. Huh?
Alright. It's just a fucking vase.
I thought if you jumped off of the
of a perch you could
do a apparently
not. Alright. Well that's good to know.
So I'm gonna go. Let's just keep
wait there's a guy right there. Three
people there. There's the whole
camp. I can take that guy out.
And nobody over here right?
Holy shit this guy's
huge. Alright.
No don't do that. I had to get
the big dude with the mallard. Only one
guy saw that. This guy.
Okay.
There's an item in here too. I'm being
followed.
I don't got time to fucking care about this right now
but you can get more
items. Ooh. What's this?
Ooh. Ooh.
I don't know. Who saw me?
Who has a gun shooting at me? It's that person.
Reloading. That was a really
quick reload by the way.
Just take them all out.
I got too greedy there.
Just drink. I don't want to do that again.
What? How did I not deflect that?
You're making me look bad.
I almost cleared the whole
area. I feel like I should use some of this shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
There's a lot to look at here.
Don't fall off that.
Why would you let me go over there?
Don't want to miss anything
like something over here. Right?
No. Why are you
here? Why are you making me
think there's something over there?
Typical from. See what I mean?
Is that an enemy?
I think it's an NPC.
It is an NPC but who is this?
It's just a chicken.
Chicken.
Alright, we're fine.
I am going to sneak in here though.
Look at this free shit.
Coin purse.
Nice. Now the question is
is the person up top an NPC?
And are they going to get startled if I jump up here?
Let's just see what happens.
They have a marker over them so
I'm going to assume you're friendly.
For now.
Have you seen...
I'm not your son.
Sorry.
She reminds me of one of those bloodborne enemies that has the lanterns.
Or what if I just pretend I'm
the son?
If I don't say anything to her.
She thinks I'm her kid.
If I talk it
takes it all down away.
Oh.
Got it.
Okay.
Anything else?
Huh.
Alright.
Sprint push off cliff.
I can talk to that person too.
What do you have to say?
Uh...
I can...
What if I say nothing?
Am I just going to be silent
protagonist in this stream?
I feel like I should say something.
Yes.
Do you have any prayer beads?
Oh.
This is the son.
Okay.
So should I offer it?
Probably should go back.
Offer it to Buddha, come back, and then...
Yeah, but I need another checkpoint though.
That was hell getting through that.
That was such a pain in the ass.
There's so many enemies here.
Where's the illusory wall to give me
a new bonfire?
There might be one right here.
Of course, right when I walk down here.
I can go up, but...
Is there like a...
Can I do that?
How do you do that?
Oh, the ceramics. Right, right, right.
That's how you do...
That's a big guy.
That guy has a bed post.
Watch out for the giant guy with the bed post.
No, I cannot whistle. I don't know how.
I'm going to throw a ceramic over here.
I might as well use them.
You don't see the other zeros.
Alright, so...
What's the range on that?
I'm just going to pull him. Fuck it.
The guy with the bed post. That's a cannon.
That's a mortar.
Now the guy with the mortar knows I exist.
Wonderful.
That's just fantastic.
That's fantastic.
He doesn't see me over here, right?
Yes, he doesn't.
He doesn't.
Alright, we've got to move.
I've got to plan.
Maybe he'll stop. I'll take this.
Sugar, more sugar.
The high Senpu priest
gave this candy to a band of short
but adept assassins.
Suppresses sound and presence for a time
making the user harder to detect.
So it's a stealth candy.
Bite the candy and take the
gachin stance to impart
its inhuman benediction.
Once hired guards, now extensions of the monks
will in their quest for undeath. So it's a stealth candy.
Apparently somebody can see me over here.
I don't know who. Who can see me?
I don't know.
Let's go.
I almost just fell off.
I'm going to grab that tree.
It's not safe. Please.
Okay, we're fine. I wonder if he gave up
shooting. I can sneak behind
him. Nobody else over here, right?
I'm going for it. He's not stupid
enough to turn around and just fire the cannon at my face, right?
Black gunpowder.
Material used in alchemical
prosthetic tool upgrades, including those
of an explosive and occultic nature.
Even the most mundane form
of gunpowder has a wide variety of applications.
So
gunpowder. Let's go ahead and take
out the two people in the front door.
You know, like LOL.
What you meant to say is just
fucking do that and do it again.
Nice.
How many healing? I don't have any healing left.
I just have pellets, which is
bad. Oh, whoa.
Wait a minute. What's that? Look at all that.
Look at all that shit.
I got to get over there.
How do I get there? Can I? Come on.
Is it the first cookie bug in the game?
No. A cookie bug's even
in this game. I don't think there are
those bugs are even in this game.
Possession balloon.
A people balloon filled with fountainhead water
with the blessing of fortune.
If one pops this vibrant green balloon,
those as water flashes
will have a higher chance of obtaining items.
So it's like magic find.
Magic find.
Two magic find balloons.
Another item over here.
Any more? Iron.
Basic reinforcement.
Maybe this is
like the shards, possibly.
I don't even know
what the hell I'm going right now.
What did I do?
Where did I end up? I'm going all
the way around the mountain.
I guess we're going to
keep going this way. Whoa.
Can those rocks fall? Is there a
better place for me to go from here?
Can I hug this wall? Please.
I hate when it does
that. I keep thinking I'm going to fall off.
Absolutely gorgeous.
It's a gorgeous game. Gorgeous.
Uh...
Spider-Man? Maybe a
Spider-Man scenario? I'm going to try!
Oh!
That could have been bad.
I would have lost half my HP.
It seems
so much bigger
than any of their previous games.
It's open. It's huge.
There's a lot to explore. It's almost overwhelming.
Because of how big this is.
And how much you can see.
There's a lot of people over here, so hold on.
Oh! Give me, give me, give me!
Thank God.
It's all the vertical movement. Yeah.
There's a lot of it. Alright, let me go back
to the town and
see what he has to say about this bell
thing. Great Canadian
Fuck Club. Ten community subs.
Back at it again. With the
major community subs.
Thank you so much, Great Canadian.
Let's find out what we can do with this.
What is it? Seems to be
your battle sense has returned.
You're more like a shinobi
than before. If
only a little. Take this.
A book of secrets
that details a variety of techniques
grants the ability to learn
shinobi style skills.
Within this text are the
innermost secrets of the shinobi arts.
Such as attacks performed in the air
and hiding one's body to avoid
detection.
What is it? What?
Shinobi techniques
recorded within are fighting techniques
that cannot be performed
by samurai.
Whether you make use of them or not
is up to you. Shinobi
aren't the only ones with their
own fighting techniques.
So now
skills. Owning
an esoteric text of a combat style
will allow its skills to be acquired in the
sculptor's idle skill menu.
Each enemy defeated provides skill
experience. Skill points are acquired
once enough
experience is gained which can be spent
to unlock skills. Some skills can
also be learned by obtaining items or defeating
enemies.
So there actually is just a level up bar in the game.
Harmony Accord thanks to the five community
subs. Thank you.
Subs rolling in.
This is the...
Is this the...
What the hell is he telling me?
I've seen you.
Do I have any new tools? I have gunpowder? No.
All right.
So this is Prey.
What does this do?
Close your eyes.
Hear the bell speak to you.
DLC area?
Someone just said sorta.
The bell's chime
will stir your
thoughts. Waken
from their slumber.
Day one
DLC. Three years
ago.
So wait am I...
I'm in like a dream world? Dream
world.
Yeah. New
skills.
Oh boy there's a skill tree.
Spend skill points
in the skill menu. New combat styles can be
learned through obtaining texts for each
style.
There are three types. Combat
arts, shinobi martial arts,
and latent skills.
Combat arts must be equipped to be used
in combat. Shinobi martial arts and latent skills are always
in effect upon being acquired.
So this is a
combat art. Whirlwind slash.
So this is available. This is not
available. Counter thrust
attacks. This is all. I guess
I'm just gonna do this.
Why wouldn't I just get this right now?
Whirlwind slash. But do I only get
a certain amount of these books?
Or points or something.
Enables one to counter enemy thrust attacks by
stomping down on an enemy's weapon.
Nearly impossible to perceive the speed
of a thrust, but not for the sharp eyes of
a shinobi.
Okay. I'm just gonna
get the first one. So how do I do
that? Maybe I can go back to the training guy?
I like the idea of hitting multiple
people. Okay combat arts are special
attack skills based on the strengths of the fighting
style they belong to. They
must be equipped in the equipment menu.
And can be learned
through the skill menu or found in special texts.
So left trigger
while holding. Right trigger while holding
left trigger is the
combat art. Let's go put it on.
You can only have one on at a time.
Oh there it is. Okay.
So it's
just both at the same time.
Alright so you can hold it. Just
hold it and bang. It doesn't
cost anything.
That's a pretty cool move though. That's actually
fantastic. I'm gonna love that. I'm gonna
love it. Somebody said play conquer
is bad for a day.
No.
Like right now?
I don't think that's gonna happen.
Hirata Estate.
I feel like I probably shouldn't be
here right now. But for the sake
of just seeing what's here I'm gonna go over here.
Can I go up? No. Guy
right there. I gotta try my
new move on somebody.
Oh this is somebody. I don't even know how it works.
I'm just starting to barely
understand the mechanics of the game.
Sorry. Alright. Anybody
over there? I could probably sneak up on
this dude. Well I'm not gonna sneak up
on that guy.
Should have paid more attention.
Dowsing Powder. Treating burns.
Reduces burn damage
and
you put it all over here and it makes you not
be burned. Let's go.
What a dude. Alright.
Nice job.
I'll give you credit. You did try to burn it.
Wait!
No it's not. Oh my god.
My whole body hurts.
Thank god you can't die by going in the water
in this game. I'm pressing A instead
of Y to pick shit up. Look at this thing.
I don't
know. Look at how big this turtle's
neck is. No that's not alive.
I thought that turtle was alive.
I was gonna say that is a fucked up looking
turtle. Can I...I can't...
Tre...Treasure Carp
Scale. Wait this is the
cookie bug. This is the new
bug from...Alright.
Bring it to somebody who knows what they're doing
and you can...Alright that's cool.
So it's a cookie fish now.
Look at that. Wouldn't even come over here
if it wasn't for the cookie fish.
Another one. Nice.
How far can you go? Is there an invisible wall?
Yeah.
Look at the other side. I don't think I can make it up there.
You can't grab that ledge? Yes
you can. You can't.
What are you dumb? Did I miss anything
over here? There's more shit over there though.
What are you dumb?
Let me get down here first.
There's like pirate boats over here with items.
Huh? Who?
Oh. You. Alright fine. Come down here.
Okay. Two seconds. Are you gonna come over here
or...You're not gonna aggro everyone
by doing this right? That'd be really
bad. Please don't.
You lost me. Good. That's a big
animal. Regular dog?
Just regular dog.
This guy's still finding
me. There's no fashion
Sekiro. Well that's
unfortunate. I'm one of these
magic find items.
I'm intrigued to go check over here.
Can I get up there? No? Could you
effectively just go all the way around and skip the whole thing?
Another coin purse.
Ooh! Secret fish.
No! No!
That was brutal. Who just? Was the fish just talking
to me?
Why? What?
Oh creepy.
Purchase items with scales.
Mask fragment.
Withered red
gourd.
Curved withered red gourd filled with medicinal water.
The gourd's medicine refills upon
rest. Reduces burn
buildup and slightly increases burn resistance.
It cannot heal the burn status
of its
divine grass. So this is a full
heal. So
this is a consumable though.
It's a scale to eat this and it's gone.
The original must have been broken
into several pieces and this fragment appears to be
the right side of the mask.
So this is a combat art floating passage.
Unleash attacks in a flowing
dance-like form, overwhelming enemies
in a furor of
graceful aggression.
What does the mask do? No idea.
Bring me some scales next time.
No Wikipedia to help us.
We just gotta play.
That's really cool though. What a cool character.
Uh, fish?
What was it? I just got
What was it? Did I lose my opportunity?
I gotta get out of the water.
Who is aggroing to me?
Let's get up here.
No I can't.
There it is. There it is.
Come here. Come on.
No. Damn it.
I gotta get up here and just wait.
Come on.
I need to kill you. You gotta come on.
Fishing quest. I know.
Really. There it is.
He's not at the surface though. I think he used to
actually pop up because I can't really hit him.
Drive the shuriken.
That's a good idea.
Because he's deep down there.
It just makes him go
real fast. I might just have to watch him
wait until he gets up. Hopefully he comes
back. It seems like he'll have to come
up a little higher to the surface.
Back? Just wait.
He gets a little closer.
I'm gonna leap out and smash him.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Come on. Just scream and charge him.
That's not gonna work.
Come to London. I've always wanted to
go to Europe. I'm not sure he's gonna get up.
He's gonna be right here.
Here we go. Here we go. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck no. What?
How do I swing down?
I couldn't get it.
It's almost like I see him
slashing this way. I don't think you can
do that. Is there a way I can
swing down?
Maybe like that.
I hit the rod.
I don't buy that. Let me try doing that
combat art too. Come on.
I have to catch this fish. It's gonna drive me crazy.
There he is. Alright.
I'm gonna do the combat art too. I can't even see him.
I might have to just wait a little longer.
Just wait even longer.
He goes by here. He starts to come up a little bit.
This is just a fishing stream.
At the moment, yeah.
Alright. This is what happened last time.
He came up a little.
I saw it at him. Everybody just don't move.
Where'd he go?
Where'd he go? What?
Oh shit. How did he go by me?
Shallow water.
Fuck it. I'm going for it.
Got him. Nice.
Alright. Cool. I feel
complete.
Shut up, Oscar.
There might be another one.
Might as well check, right?
I can't see anymore.
There was one under here.
I'm gonna get the great rod. There is no great rod.
Just the great rod.
That's a lot of dogs up there.
I think I'm gonna just pull this guy.
No. How am I gonna effectively do this?
I gotta go around.
I just got three dogs with me.
Have I thought about visiting Singapore?
I wanna go everywhere.
But I wanna turn like 40 first.
You know? I wanna be one of those boomers
that just travels the world when he's like 45.
The guy with the three dogs
is right up here.
Maybe fighting's not the answer sometimes.
I can't grab that from here.
Okay. Here's the plan. Ready?
I'm gonna go in. I'm gonna do the weapon art
to all the dogs at the same time.
Nobody sees me yet. Perfect.
Oh shit.
That's the burn meter.
He got me with the burn. Really?
I'm burning now.
Fuck. Yeah.
I touched every...
Oh. I'm so mad about that.
Yeah. Resistance gauge.
There are two items which suppress the gauge
and cure, and I'm on fire.
I don't think I can get rid of this
until... How long does this last?
I dodged into every single one of those
somehow. It's definitely not that bad.
Enemies doused in oil easily set alight
causing them to take additional vitality
even from fire attacks.
Oil and they burn.
You got it.
Now, let me just get rid of this guy too.
I love games where stomping and dropping
actually works. Yeah.
And then it's pretty cool.
Nothing else.
I completely forgot this is almost a secondary
area that I don't have to be in right now.
My brain...
This is the next part of the game in my brain.
Why did I press down? Maybe it is.
Let's take a rest.
I'm good. 59 out of 15.
More ceramic shards.
Alright.
Is he screaming to let
everybody in or... That's a big
yell, right? Okay. Well, whatever.
Just come over here.
Is he opening the door? That door just
can't open. They just know that something's
going on over here. They can't do anything about it though.
I'm fine with that. Alright. Let's get out.
Alright. Any enemies down here?
No. Let's just check.
Ladder. Wall.
Just an item on a tree.
Ooh, thanks. I don't even know what it was.
What the hell was it?
You are so infected.
What? You mean me in real
life? I would agree with you. Something's wrong with me.
There's more sugar.
So this is... You take less damage.
This is just the damaged candy.
Three... Okay. It's in storage.
I need to save those
for bosses. I'm not taking those during regular
encounters. You want me to jump?
The only point of entry is up
here. So...
Remember I can go that way.
Ooh.
Let's be easy. Let's be easy.
Easy. Easy. Can I e-drop?
These guys talk to each other?
Who's more dangerous? I don't know.
Guy with the bow. Somebody's
looking at me. I left my favorite
YouTuber streamer.
I think it's streamer now.
Almost exclusively.
Doesn't open from this side. For now.
Streamtuber.
Um... Three.
Guy with the burn. That looks like
a shortcut. I wonder...
Let's go up this way.
Can I climb there?
I'll go down this way. Let's go.
Watch this. Ready? This is gonna be
so cool. Nevermind. More
sugar. Boosts attack power.
So this is a...
The fighting... The red sugar
is the fight sugar.
Wait. What's that? Three people.
Ah. Easy.
Climb up there. Come on. Give me a
point of access. Got no
access right there to climb? Come
on. How? There's gotta be
something I can jump up to. Not even the
tree? You're killing me.
I don't know what I'm doing right now,
but it's stupid, whatever it is.
I was just trying to
find a place to grapple.
I can't get on this house.
I thought I could. Alright, let's just talk.
Because you just gotta go in.
Watch out for this guy.
You're almost broken. That's great.
That was a Smash Brothers sound effect?
I don't even know what you're
talking about.
Some pellets. Good.
That'll help. They were dogs
though. Thought I could get over
there. Thought I could be cheeky about that.
Whoa!
I'm stuck on something there.
Did that guy just say waza?
Like the old Budweiser commercial?
Ooh! That hurts.
Alright.
Oh no, no, no.
Bad. Very bad.
Relax. This guy with a
bow and arrow or something over here.
I gotta go. I'm back on top of the house, please.
Actually, maybe not.
That's probably bad. I don't know.
I need to get the item in here.
Oh, come on.
With this accuracy.
I'm talking on the roof. Alright.
Fuck this guy.
Where are you locking on, game?
Holy shit,
a lot of people. Easy.
Fuck.
Just trying to do the art.
Ah!
Damn it, I didn't time it right.
That guy was shit-faced.
Yeah, he was pretty drunk.
Although, I'm kind of hurting for
health here.
Just one more guy, I think.
I feel bad for that guy.
But still, sometimes you gotta...
I hear another dog somewhere.
Burn powder.
In this room? No.
Okay, there we go. Pellet.
More items. Couple here.
This is the money pellet.
Flame barrel.
An iron barrel that spews fire?
Ooh! A new prosthetic.
It's difficult to control
the rage-filled red eyes
with the power of man alone.
A fire-based weapon could be a means of resisting them.
They're said to fear fire
above all else.
Well, I now have a new
toy to play with. I'm gonna heal.
There's another item over here.
I haven't used this once.
Just see what it does.
Every time I play one of these games, I just never use
the items that they give me.
And I end up with a thousand of them in my inventory.
Keep going.
Let's see what it does.
Looks like a distractor. That's actually
really good.
Phenomenal, actually.
Oh.
Worthless bastards.
Hello.
You are...
a shinobi, if...
if I have mistaken.
Take the shinobi axe
from the temple
and split it into
skulls wide open.
Please.
For a second, I thought you said, like, hug him.
Oh, okay.
Sorry that you died.
See anything?
Will he see me if I pop out here?
What is that?
Oh, he's trolling.
Alright, so something going on in there.
I'm gonna kill these guys.
There's more stuff over here, too.
There's an NPC over there. Alright, wait.
Let me get the... there's an item this way.
Let me just get up there.
Pick it up. Whatever it is.
Chicken. Another sugar.
So this reduces posture damage
taken. There's a lot of these candies.
Ah, hey, look at that.
I did it. I opened up
the shortcut. Remember this?
I remember.
Let's go
refill our stuff.
I also kind of want to...
I want to go see what this new toy
is. New toy?
Yeah.
That's how you go lucid, man.
Hey, next time you're in that
zone, look in a mirror
to get even more lucid.
Flip a couple of light switches. Look at a clock.
You'll get deeper into lucidity.
Actually, by the way, don't ever look at a mirror
if you're in a dream. It's terrifying.
You look like the Scream monster.
The guy from Scream with the Scream mask on.
It's horrible. Your brain doesn't
understand how to decipher
a mirror if you're in a dream. Try it.
If you want to be scared.
Alright, deals fire,
damage to enemies in a short range blast
while burning.
So let's create it.
I can have three of these, right? You've never seen
a mirror in your dream? I'm telling you, if you want
to scare the shit out of yourself,
if you ever find yourself lucid
in a dream, go look in a mirror.
You will probably immediately wake up
because it's going to be a horror movie.
Okay, let's see.
Let's equip it. So this
costs three spirit emblems.
Whoa.
That's cool.
I kind of want to just try it. It's a cool way to switch.
Alright.
Back to it. Let's rest up.
Thermal lucid.
No.
What about skills? Okay, I can do...
Wait a minute. Mid-air
deflection. Allows one to
guard against or deflect enemy attacks
in mid-air.
That sounds pretty great. What's this one?
A Shinobi's Karma
body. Max spirit
emblems. Interesting.
What about down here? Let me look at what some
of these do. That's cool.
Run and slide. Allows one to
slide into a crouch position while
sprinting. Sprint through an
area and slide into cover or otherwise out
of view. Easily deceives
an enemy's eyes. Reduces an enemy's
ability to perceive those who are in stealth.
I kind of like being able to deflect
in the air.
But I'm going to hold on.
Not yet.
Am I still in Anor Londo?
I don't know how you could classify
this area. You could classify
this area as...I'm not sure.
I'm going to try this move though.
Ready? Let's see what that
does. Short range, right?
So it's kind of just like a blast.
Pretty long line there too.
You've got to be
real close. That's...
It's a dodge. And then
from the dodge you've got to be ready to go
and get hit.
Alright, let's skip this.
He tried to backstep. Yeah, I did.
You're right. Alright, he's going to go through the door.
That's now open.
I can just probably sneak around here, right?
Don't need to fight anything.
There's your pyromancy. Yeah.
Pretty much. I can't get there from here.
Come on.
Come on. It's right there.
I can't reach the roof here.
What are you thinking?
Wait. Yes I can.
Game doesn't suck.
What do you know? We
carry on. Alright, there was an
NPC.
There's a chicken. Well, I'm
going to go over here.
I bumped into everything in his house.
He's just kind of standing there going
well, you know, somebody
fucked up my house. Destroyed all
my stuff.
Sucks. I don't even know
what the hell he's looking at.
Way! Way!
Way!
Wait, you can come this way?
Somehow, instinctively, for no reason
started to try to attack with R1.
Which
that's a long time.
You are
hard to parry.
Jesus.
Oh my
Lord. Where? God. Come on.
Fuck me. I feel like trapped in the corner
over here. With two different elevations.
You know what I mean? Like boom, boom.
Oh, fuck off, game.
He's PG.
No, not right now.
What's in here? Ooh, a secret.
There's the axe.
Fuck off, game. Means game sucks.
No. It means fuck off
for that moment. I found the axe.
It's another tool. Less for cutting
and more for breaking things with its weight.
Once the favorite weapon of a shinobi, known as
the bounding monkey
of the sunken valley, he was lost along with his left
arm. Okay, so
there's another two tools here.
That's pretty cool. Wasn't there
somebody just walking over here looking at this?
It was an NPC.
Maybe not. Well, let's get rid of the
chicken. If I die to this chicken, I swear
to god.
You killed my brothers!
Don't make jokes here because I actually could die.
Oh, no.
So god damn it, please.
Please not the chicken. Please.
There's another one in there.
That's king chicken.
Do they live in this house?
Stop! You violated the law!
Can I stealth kill this chicken?
Come on,
let me stealth kill him.
No! Something has to be in this
house. Why would this be here?
There's nothing in the chicken house.
Really? Yes, there is.
More sugar. What about the people
that were back here?
I think they're still here. Yeah, see?
Okay. So this is the way to go
to progress. It's just straight through.
I cleaned up everything.
Now, speaking of cleaning,
let's clean up some
braid matter off
of our sword.
What is that lit up for?
Amnesium?
He's not bad.
He's highly skilled.
Just let me do one more taken.
Just one more, I swear. That'll be it.
We can put it in
feudal Japan.
Please write the script. Please.
Yes.
We've got a blood-borne window NPC.
Trader. Hey.
You. You're the young master
Shinobi. Yes.
What good are you? Wait.
Tell me you didn't leave. The timing of their
attack was perfect. Yes.
I hope. I would love if
you heard like...
And then it made like the soul collection
noise that like...
I hope you die
twice. I hope
you die twice.
Well,
let's see what's going on
over here.
Okay.
May the force be with you.
You as well. So everyone's kind of just
locked away right now.
And may the force be with you. And also with you.
Can I open the door?
Will that alert the horde? Oh, wait.
Right. They're just standing out there.
You can just hear me.
I think I heard something behind this door.
Maybe.
All right. Let's go for a drop-down kill.
Get the big guy
first, I'd say.
Yeah. Big guy first.
Hiya! Hiya!
I can't do that with the cold.
I was doing fucks.
I'm gonna say it this way.
No. You just gotta... No.
No. No. No.
Come on. Just one at a time.
Let me just throw... I'm gonna... Come here.
On the back. Bring it on.
Can you deflect that?
I haven't even attempted to.
It does burn you though.
This dude's got a shield.
How do you break shields?
Come on down the stairs.
One shield at a time.
Please.
You're so slow.
You're so slow!
Get down here! What an idiot.
He's almost broken.
Just... Really?
Fine. Fuck it.
Oh my God!
Why do you have so much reach?
What am I supposed to do against this guy?
Um... Dodge around him?
And hit him in the back, probably?
Deflect and then break it eventually?
What is this idiot?
I think I just got hurt by stepping on a piece of metal.
It's a big thrust.
Push.
That hurts a lot.
I feel like there's a way easier way to do this.
Yeah, I just gotta wait till they go...
Get out of the way.
Come on. Do something.
One of you do something.
Before I go mad.
Of course it does!
Hey, let's do a puppet show for him!
Fuck you!
He killed me again. I swear to fucking God.
Ugh!
Burn!
Use jump.
He blocks it.
Ow!
What the fuck?
What?
Unseen aid.
I have to use the axe that I just got.
I'm getting a break.
Half of skill, experience, and scent are lost upon death, but there is a way to avoid this on rare occasions.
Through the unseen aid of gods and Buddha, one may be spared this loss.
The chances of receiving unseen aid can be seen in the pause menu.
So I have to go get the dumb axe to break the shield.
Otherwise they just do a puppet show for five minutes.
So wait a minute.
Okay, acquired skills, right?
Unseen aid. So there's a 30% chance that when you die twice, you get to come back without losing anything.
So I didn't lose anything.
Alright.
Let me go put on the mandatory item.
He just lost a lot of respect.
Don't call him Pinshield.
Look, how was I supposed to...
I gotta like put this axe on.
One strike and easily turn a wooden shield into splinters.
Ugh.
That's such dog shit.
What?
A book of secrets that details a variety of techniques for use with Shinobi prosthetic.
Grants the ability to learn prosthetic skills.
You can also use it as a weapon.
A variety of techniques for use with Shinobi prosthetic.
Grants the ability to learn prosthetic style skills.
Okay.
um thanks for everything i mean wait wait don't just skip it so it's too emblem to do it big
strike breaks shields very cool let's get it on there i'm ready i'm ready to go and fight the enemy
but first let's see i have two points there's another skeletonry prosthetic arts
i should have a martial art that allows one to perform a forward dashing sword slice after
using a certain prosthetic tools allowing one to close distance on enemies instantly
oh so you can throw a shuriken and then dive in that sounds really great actually uses the grappling
hook to launch oneself add an enemy and use that momentum to perform a rolling sword attack
oh that sounds actually really fun i mean that's the ability to grapple into and do the spider-man
move to people i'm doing it what does that open up here nightjar slash
spinning leap attack that can quickly close or create distance from foes
use the weight of the massive shuriken to add force to the blow so you just leap forward what's
this one of course the healing effects of recovery items that's almost necessary in these games
oh okay i'm ready necessary yeah all right let's go skip this bullshit get to the shield guys
break their shields break their necks doesn't matter to me bring it on do something what okay
good already done i was pressing the wrong button that's all right yay i'm very happy now very happy
happier than i've ever been i can go to that tree but for what this is kind of just here for no
reason i kind of you can swim yeah i know you can swim but let's just see i'm not i'm not rushing
through it you know let's just take a look i'm here the goal is not to get to the end as fast
as possible the goal is to enjoy the experience so let's just see if there's anything over here
there is what was that oh scale no that's just an angry fish no scale the mad fish
there's a tree here though what would this be here for um i there's somebody in here can i eavesdrop
on this person come on come on i'm right here really are you just weirdly pushed against the
wall where i can't do this if anyone's gonna get out they're only going to use this cave
don't let a single racket this cave this is the way to get out i don't love this guy brand
i didn't know there were this many people only two people were talking oh this is bad news now
oh it's so slow
guy with the bow gotta go now that's so important
it's so hard to time that in a game that's a thousand miles per hour in fighting
watching the guy slowly swing his fucking stick at you these two left
my god it's like he comes he's in slow motion where am i going all right there's like there's
a wizard down here why is there a wizard over here i don't know what to do about this should
i fight uh fight the wizard uh the thrust holy shit i'm gonna die wow
oh
holy shit this guy's insane did i just get a scripted wizard death
your death is not your fate just yet you died twice game over
wrought essence somewhere a pained cough rings out continuously the man who coughs
zealously sculpt statues of buddha to avoid being consumed by the building flames owning
this item reduces one's chance of receiving unseen aid wrought essence timid mane so wait they're
like dying or one with the power of the dragon's heritage dies the more a sickness known as dragon
rot spreads through the world if one known to the wolf is coughing and wheezing it's likely they are
afflicted with dragon rot the more wrought essence wolf has the lower the chance of receiving unseen
aid okay what's wrong dragon rot the stagnation overflows spreads the disease that leads eventually
death what you don't need to worry about me i'm not normal you see the more that i die the more
ask him about the rest i got so shit on by that guy he just attacked so many times in a row
have you seen the sculptor lately yes he's all i know is what dogan told me long ago
that the dragon's heritage can bestow the power of resurrection however it is not any ordinary
it kills everybody else needs to stagnation which will eventually reach a point where it
overflow this causes those who do not have the power to become sick a disease known as dragon
rot he knew much about it but even so he was so there is a penalty for using a cure forgive me
is there a way to treat this dragon rot i do not know it must be stopped i am unsure
for dying but the first step is to look through my mentor's research and see if i can discover
a way thank you just don't die easy i'm gonna lose i'm gonna have zero dollars by the end of
this playthrough i bet you anything i bet you i have five cents when this is all said and done
all right i feel like i probably shouldn't i need to go down and fight the wizard again
i mean how am i gonna just not have that happen uh shit try it again i have dragon rot let's keep
moving nice knowing you same two idiots okay back where i was before i'm gonna get embarrassed
again here um all right hold on grab this should i go that way i feel like i'm i have to get my
revenge even if it means killing every single person in the town by dragon rot i'm gonna die
like 30 times here i have to get my revenge on this guy i don't even know where the hell that was
where the fuck was that remember was down here yeah no it wasn't no yeah it was okay
all right all right all right this time don't fuck it all up forget about see i came in here
with a bunch of issues stealth kill this guy and then go get the wizard who can see me that makes
no who is even looking at me hey yeah you're trying to tell me the fish down there is is
seeing me right now the fish yeah let's go i wonder what's the wizard vulnerable to oh my god what
am i doing what this there's too many fucking people here what was are you serious how was
i ever gonna do that i don't even know where i'm going right now i'm so lost where we even was that
executive wall jump where why am i doing this hello um am i supposed to be here
okay i don't know where this is because i got another sculptor's idol uh any items that i can
get the fire looks beautiful that's too busy paying attention to how wonderful looking your game world
was from software and you put an archer right next to me that's a lot of people oh my nice eagle
eye of course the guy with the fucking eagle eye really he has no line of sight on me he can't see
me and he's just shooting the wall that's unbelievable they shoot so much faster too
now i'm fucked oh i'm fucked here fighting more than one enemy in this game
there's like no way good luck what i got predicted i got predicted
holy shit oh my fucking god
come on why i i didn't know it was gonna happen you don't even have like one second of immunity
you don't have like a half second of immunity all right i can have a different approach to this
because this seems almost almost undoable you're gonna have to pick people up one by one you can't
you can't just walk up there no way give me my other tools i'm gonna have to do a pole here
i could do one or two at a time i need more than that that's an uh-uh let's go
if it didn't matter jesus i didn't see you
and i knew he's gonna shoot at me too
you fuck you all right so far so good watch out for hawkeye don't i have to grapple move to
music stop which means i'm safe almost not completely almost born that's burn powder
there's a lot of fire here something tells me i'm probably gonna need to use this
i gotta get my inventory ready is that maybe just go through the house almost incompatible
divine confetti made for driving away apparitions the paper is made ceremoniously
whereby pulp is spread thin using water from the exalted fountain head so this is to be able to hit
ghosts why is there you swing through this wall the whole the game's getting a full letter grade
downgrade anymore i see something oh that's just more of that okay no more enemies there's a bunch
of shit illusory wall i didn't clear everything over here though i'm gonna get spotted by something
maybe not it's down here nothing uh is there more i guess i can go this way
i don't know there's even more of these idiots over here well i'm gonna have to start pulling
people is sakiro the bad guy or the good guy he's an anti-hero he could be anything no no no calm
down i bumped into a fucking piece of plastic let's get a pirate here
i figured these guys out you just gotta get that lunge and insta-kill them i i'm not opening one of
those coin sacks try me until i'm gonna until i need them um who's drunk who's drunk joe's with
a drunkard i think i may have bumped out an economy um i well he certainly is drunk yeah
he certainly had a fuse to drink do i have to fight everybody in here
uh is he gonna do we all fight i'm confused right now it what is he doing is he stuck
so this is not a scenario where uh joe's who the drunkard comes out and kills everybody
and invites him that i miss that did i miss a cut scene i may have missed cuts i find him in the
hallway um this is bad this is very bad uh are you sure i don't get a like gun in this game
because that's how i would see completing this well got to deal with it right
as long as he stays stuck on stairs and shit i can care less who's next just me and you um all
right let's see what you got what moves do you got you got an acid spit he spits it two times
that lingers for a while too so this guy can be anti-poison that doesn't really hurt him
so wow that's a push okay he drinks i'm almost dead that was uh i could have gone a little better
shit i don't even know how i even happened i he like got stuck in the wall and then i had to
fight like six people i thought i was like if i ran into the middle it was gonna do like a
cut scene or something apparently not let me just see how that is supposed to work
yeah under a potential normal circumstance hold on so i'm realizing right now this whole this area
sucks can i just run by these guys or do i have to deal with this every time
like this gotta be a way i can jump over that again i can just run
how am i supposed to deal with this part and it's just kind of stealth to take out everybody
what oh hi hi there you want really come on i'm talking to an npc
i'm gonna kill the npc accidentally this is oh my god can i i just want to hear what the fuck
this guy has to say let me explain i want one of you guys to go to med school become a doctor
and explain how i was not locked onto that guy what happened go be a scientist go do game go
do like 50 years of game development and then figure out what just happened right there
are you gonna fund it my controller has low battery my controller doesn't have low battery
it's plugged into the wall or whatever into the computer it doesn't have low battery who's
fighting me oh my god fuck this area i'm gonna come back and
fucking slit this guy's throat when i'm like 15 levels higher no fuck this place
this place sucks there was another way i could go it's just they just just throw up like fucking
20 enemies in a fire zone and then a big fat guy comes out and drinks no i need i want to hear
what that guy has to say i want to listen i want to hear the npc can i get over there through this
way i have to be able to right i swear to god if this is one of those scenarios where i have to go
get like another weapon art thing and i just fucking i throw like a grenade at him or something
and he instantly dies i'm gonna be upset i don't think i can jump over that okay where is he let's
listen to this guy let's get away from these people hide wait just deflect where are they
they're gonna come over here and yeah there they are he's gonna shoot me through the bush
it's just one guy and he still has his sights on that's fine just talk to me so i can figure out
what i need to do here there's definitely something to do i have to like pull a lever
and a big log is gonna come crashing down from a tree that's right i can't move when you're in a
conversation with an npc they've made five of these games you can move when talking to people what
is to protect me yeah you can do something about it please never forgive me should i fail
i found the secret i found the way i found the way i found the way to do it all right we fight
together me and this guy i knew there was something weird going on but why didn't he uh
i hope he doesn't get his ass kicked wait wait wait wait wait can he just beat him for me
no no no no no he's gonna die i i wasn't prepared for this he's gonna get it like three
times and die what is the lock on doing why is the lock on this is i i don't like this lock on
very much i'm gonna be completely honest here it like keeps taking itself off of people he's dead
are you kidding me this is on by default no it's not oh fuck off game
kill all the minions then recruit the guy i didn't even know that's what it did
oh god that voice is gonna kill me he doesn't have fire i don't have any healing left or anything
either all right so i i know i have a basic understanding of how to fight
i'm gonna clear the people that are over here and then recruit them and then fight
be lucky that you can give one hit on see if i can
kill this dude i'm trying well that's a grab i somehow got
me poison spit i wonder if fire will work here even if i get a good dodge
do you want to grab oh you gotta just dodge those here we go i can pause the game all right let me see
get all this shit out of here i don't even i can't even yeah i have a healing pellet
um all right oil oil and then burn them maybe i wonder i'm gonna try covering with oil and burn
him what he doesn't drink he's coming in oil can i do anything oh it kind of does
man this oh yeah i try to ignite his alcohol breath maybe um i have this like sinking feeling
that i'm not supposed to be in this area i don't know how true that is i have a feeling i skipped
too much and i'm way over my head pretty sure because there was like two areas that i
i feel like i shouldn't be here right now i'm gonna give this one last try before going back
something about this just feels harder than it should feel at least in regards to like how many
enemies are here how many healing gourds i have i don't like to heal this is so many people here
it almost i don't feel like these people should even be here this place is burning what are you
doing here this this like ramped up to a thousand let me see if i can just clear this
i forget it every time
let me burn ah fuck this area uh no no no i'm fighting five six people at the same time
not right now i'm going to be on fucking zone no thanks uh where was it over here right
i'm gonna come back when i have like another attack power i was gonna bang my head against
the ceiling because i'm so damn tall all right there was a couple of places that was over here
right because i remember being like oh i got this and i went back and i that whole area was me
dropping the bell so this is where i was going progressing kind of normally through the game
oh okay i'm all right
oh funny and money you see this you hear about that i got only one pellet though like i can just
see me hello not broken your guard yet how is that possible i hear the loud sound take his health
i hear who's making this noise uh it's a it's another boss really oh shit
chained ogre he's tied up to her grab attacks cannot be deflected there's no way to avoid
taking serious damage once grab enemy grab attacks can be evaded with a well-timed step
dodge even the strongest attacks are useless if they don't make contact
oh that was the exact same animation and energy as okay i'm gonna stop talking because i can't do
it and speak at the same time especially the blacksmith and dark souls one all right now i'll be
quiet i'm dead instantly this is insane insane what that's not a dodge that's not a time oh my you
got to be kidding me that's not dodge i don't think i even want to attempt to dodge that i'm
just gonna fucking i don't even know i don't even know still kill that guy let me try this again
she's not already up okay let's try this again i don't even honestly whoa i just saw an indicator
on his head there that was much faster you seriously have got to be kidding me what why
are you over here is i'm like fighting somebody i'm currently in the middle of something why are
you here what i feel like i need to start just dying i'm gonna everyone's gonna i'm gonna kill
everybody should i just keep from i feel like i shouldn't be fucking resurrecting just to die again
wealth wrong button that's so quick i'm dead
he has like two different lunges he has a really like quick one that's the power bomb
and then he has a longer one which is the instant kill okay so let's try this again clear the trash
here
there's one more guy he's like up here can i get up there from over here
of course you can't fucking get it unless you start the encounter
don't get too overzealous here
grab again do it away don't believe me get this bolt motherfucker out of here no get greedy
for the burn again you gotta wait for the grab you gotta watch it elbow drop
i was just gonna drop it off the fucking ledge
why does he have elbow drops wwe ogre he's like the rock did they chain him up and like
fucking clockwork orange's eyes in front of like the attitude arrow all right got prayer beads a
loose prayer bead offering for them will increase okay two beads okay new medicine rank they wanted
to learn such techniques to be gravely injured time and time again by worthy opponents nice
i did it that was fun i didn't even have to complain that much about that fight
i did it was this guy up here that was the problem it was this guy the random guy standing up here
that was cool all right is that a boss or is it a how do i even know if it's a real boss
because we can go up there and nothing else right why does that just end up being a standard enemy
that would be so disheartening that's five community gifted subs from germa lied about
minecraft vr what a liar thank you uh nightjar monocular bamboo tube used to see distant objects
well shinobi already have good vision looking through this tube with one eye enables one to see
even further okay so this is the binoculars that no one ever uses i swear one day in one of these
from software games you know they oh wow i can't believe they're finding secrets in dark souls one
10 years later wow yeah that's interesting this is going to be something nobody puts the binoculars
on nobody uses them from software has probably something hidden in a skybox with the but you
can only see if you have the binoculars equipped the game like knows you have them on finally
another gourd seed i knew there was something going on in that last area like it was a secret
special little other area i had two flasks that place just felt way over my head and it was
anything else can't open that oh i see um uh this is like look uh i'm not doing this yet
i'm gonna like spend points and stuff hit 87 dollars i had like a thousand 20 minutes ago
uh do i have let me see three skill points maximum spirit emblems or three points i wonder if i
should hold off with this i wonder if i should wait one more point and get the better heal
or if i should do something else
i'm gonna have most of them eventually anyways but i think i'm gonna hold off for this one
i just don't know i just don't know maybe this uh uh this yeah i don't have any of these yet
counter thrust attacks by stomping down let me see do i need to put it on or is it just available now
i think it's just i just know it right passively right there's something about this game that makes
it distinctly more frustrating than other from soft games uh i think it's just not being used to
how the game is not supposed to play like dark souls it's the same engine it's the same inventory
slots the same ui technically right but you really are not supposed to play this like dark souls and
that is frustrating not because it's frustrating like oh i can't believe i want to play dark souls
4 but because you're just so used to playing all these games in such a fashion that
now you don't not anymore and your brain and your body kind of run into each other
but it's great i think it's great so far uh forget about these guys get me under
all right so oops that's the antagonist of the game uh cutscene no wait i'm not i have to fight
this guy this is the guy i fought in the first section is he just gonna all right um no it's
just it's just fight guy no this wait a minute people are shooting bows and arrows and shit
i'm not ready for this man he's got a lot of these things who's the other guy shooting
bow where is he where is he i didn't block that what how did you not block that
well now i know get everything i know there's no cutscenes that trigger why
all right you got a guy standing in a big open zone it's like okay like this is something's
gonna happen here nope aggro the whole time i gotta stop doing that because it's not a boss
i thought it was the guy from the beginning of the game
when you get in a situation like this you just die it's almost it's almost impossible to come
back from this with like five people chasing you might as well just die twice just do the title of
the game just bone out yeah like no reason especially considering that it's the game
pauses why wouldn't i just leave oh my god and we get to learn the hard way that
that takes almost twice as long as it does in dark souls okay good cool so we're gonna wrap around
wrap around and stealth kill a few people and then fight the guy in the middle just like this
where do they are what else do i got come here i just if you do that you're gonna
shatter every bone in your wrist you have to give me another arm um yeah can i
i just want to sneak around but that guy's is looking this uh nice stealth well this
and now here we go again hey play the fucking benny hill music here's 15
fucking people chasing you reset all right again so what's over here can i do something over this
way i feel like this guy's always taking a look to the left so i'm you just i can't even go that
way so let's try this way nope are they all connected to the same computer
yes they are actually yeah i mean i mean like but they communicate with this thing called son
well then you have to go to the left so the question is how do i get this guy to turn
fuck around because it's obvious it's obvious right that i have to go this way i can't go
over there everybody sees you and then the entire game aggro's to you so let's let's try this way
no guy walks guy walking this way right now he's ready to come over here um how do i pull this guy
without pulling the whole entire game it's got to be over here like this he doesn't walk all
the way up here does he what path is this he just comes to the very top of the stairs
don't tell me you just stand there you turn around eventually right thank you
that leaves this guy who i wonder okay let me just throw this out here does he not hear that
um i mean this i guess i just go get him everybody saw here we go but even the guy from down here
this guy with the frying pan maybe i should kill frying pan guy first
this is enough weeds to hide me probably not still get line of sight oh god what do i do
what um okay i'm gonna i'll take it i don't know where i am but i'll take it
that confetti again what was this turn back if you value your life you can't behead the headless
our swords and pikes did nothing so this is a new zone i'm not done with this one yet though
not yet as if i can go around there's an opportunity this is an opportunity to
catch this guy without anybody else maybe i think i can pull this guy and just be me and him i don't
see anybody else let's go here we go not far enough all right the question i had is
i got and he didn't see me first he's literally looking at me i don't oh my god oh that's a jump
that's a jump okay he does that slap he broke my guard easy no wow oh what oh why that was
like a quarter of a second move oh what was that oh i thought i was dead i just wow
oh holy shit now i gotta do all that dog shit again the whole courtyard with the guy the frying
pan i gotta kill that guy first he's frightening but he's gonna start playing the music the second
i step out here it's like gonna be like ready watch this i'm gonna stay i'm gonna go for frying
pan man first and then it's gonna go everyone's gonna be fighting me ready here we go it already
happened it's very much only go so far it only goes a short distance in front of you where is this
how did you even get there should i even ask
good game must be bullshit there he is let's go oh no no no no no no no no i want to fight
him alone not like with three people move and move is oh there's this like dickhead friend that
came running i have to get away from this it's not possible to fight two or three people at the same
time you gotta like a running hide or something i'm gonna go upgrade i have a seed no that's not
the right way it's this way let's create three heals undying samurai training oh uh i'm gonna
do that why are you guys talking shit about the vaude what's we why are you making fun of the vaude
you may use me to hone your staircase let's see how this works i should know we can perceive
incoming thrust attacks encounter them by stepping on the enemy blade
there's a powerful if risky move that deals more posture damage but how do you dodge in a direction
that's actually really good face me again it's a chat thing i wouldn't understand well that's good
to know so it's just a standard dog whatever you like if you have techniques thank you what about
in here anything unhip what do you mean unhip who's the lady oh no are they like dying here
together what are you doing hmm oh i didn't realize you were here the sculptor has been
coughing blood i took a sample of this blood for my dragon rod research a sample of his blood
yes blood that he's coughed up the color of the blood itself appears to be tainted
tainted blood but sculptor's blood alone isn't enough to reach any conclusion is there anything
i can do yes bring me samples of blood coughed up by others that suffer from the dragon rod
if i have more i'll be able to learn more about the disease if i come across anyone
afflicted by the dragon rod i'll ask them thank you three heels and i don't think i don't think
i have any more skills i can do right not at the moment no no well midair deflection or run and slide
i'll hold on to it quick give me some of your blood so i can use it so what about that door
can i just open the door hold on it's important uh where what was that where is that door i don't
even know what to do here i really don't it's gonna wait for this guy i want maybe i can stealth
kill that guy eventually i don't know i do appreciate the stealth kill but it i don't
like how loud it is if you i feel like everyone's hearing that the big like chime sound um okay those
two guys with shields or they just props i kind of i don't know what do you do when you have a
shield that big you just kind of sit on the ground and rest on it right well these guys be able to
see me this guy's freaking me out all right so there's that guy over there can i get on top
of the roof this is not that is a roof right there but what's the next step did everybody hear
that he's the guy with the pan he's gonna he's gonna start smacking the pan then everyone's
right here there's a big guy there he is he's a guy with a musket over here i had to let him do it
for a little while longer because that's the only thing he does he doesn't know how to do anything
else i mean i just wanted to make sure that he at least got some enjoyment of the last few seconds
okay i believe that's everybody where's big guy there he is now can i get the drop on him
with a stealth jump thing because he comes back to here right he's gonna come walk and he's gonna
turn around um i don't know if i can at least not from here i could try to just backstab him but
i feel like he's he'll probably hear me i'll try i'll give it a go i'll give it a go on this next
turn here just do that every time oh that sucked he's gonna get all of his posture back now
ah no don't do that shit oh my goodness gracious that's a new move i'm gonna die again
i had it going too i'm gonna kill him i think but it's gonna be real fucking messy well i have three
all it took was me uh making everybody sick again at least that guy's dead you know what this game
reminds me of metal gear rising it's like a more punishing version of metal gear rising in a way
that parry feels like metal gear rise it's like a slowed down version of trying to block with that
so all right so how do i cross this bridge doesn't look like i can grab it from here
uh well i think i found it what
no i'm gonna sneak attack you if i died by that lizard very embarrassing i need one more bead
i'm assuming memory is when you do those other areas oh that one hurt that one hurt okay
all right here you go you ready for the my impressions of the game first impressions
is hard as shit yeah i feel like the learning curve is way steeper than their previous games
but i feel like killing even basic enemies feels like you did something in the game i would say
it's definitely really really really good there is a sense of accomplishment for killing guy with
sword in his hand what is going on because yeah they can kill you just as easily what's that
earthquake is there gonna be an avalanche don't tell me there's an avalanche mid yeah i know how
to do that well not yet not yet wait wait wait wait wait wait there's probably something over here
there'll be something cool it just don't die don't die don't die don't die don't die good what it's
a turtle what is that it's a snake it's is it a turtle they's those turtles with the huge heads
remember those things oh god i know oh that's big that's a big snake do i have to fight this snake
uh okay it's like it's like mario no no no no no not like mario i i mean uh does the thing in
mario 64 we have to walk on it it's like it's a moving uh yes it's not gonna hurt me i have
to actually walk on this just like in mario here we go oh shit okay i'm alive did i miss something
i think i may have missed something maybe he's just here for fun i get to come back
his shadows died three times in my case uh but there's an item right there god damn it hold on
can i get back over here is he just in the cave i don't even know where i ended up where is he
oh i don't know where he is he's gonna make it down here i don't think he can this sucks
oh wait what okay so snake looks for you don't go near snake avoid snake died to pin snake
you guys are gonna be on that all night huh you guys gonna be on the pin snake thing
well now i can at least there's no items or anything so
i thought i could maybe just make the jump and not have to go here
all right that leaves this watch out snake just get across he can't go over that way
right now from in here i have to hide from the snake oh he's right here already though
where am i it's all misty and shit um is he's gonna do that again
fucking god damn it man god damn it no get why can i even go this way
oh um i don't i don't what the fuck what did i just do what's down here oh fuck i don't know
what to do i am just panicking i don't understand i mean i guess you hug that wall but then
make it out here just so dark and misty i can't see anything watch out ready whoa
okay i can hide there so then if i go like this and hide in the bush no dude no dude dude
dude wait wait wait you should be going this way you're not gonna come to the left are you
i can't i don't i can't see what the fuck i'm supposed to be doing here like i need to go over
here but there's like you just always just don't wait just wait okay easy enough can you smell me
or something oh man he's gonna touch me he doesn't even know he's gonna kill me he's gonna accidentally
kill me where's his head should i swing at him he's gonna constrict me that's a lot of teeth
uh hug this wall he's gonna go down i gotta wait till he goes down there again right
he's gonna slither over there maybe i can go this way bad move bad move bad move very bad move
whoa you still see me
that was in an instant not even an aggro second all right these are on his office one opportunity
when he turns to the left and then i'm gonna be hit by the icicles right i don't even know
what this is gonna look is it like mario rpg if i can i hide behind he's gonna see me he's gonna
see he sees he sees me he sees me um uh is the item up there i don't know there's no way
just can i hide in the dumpster look at him looking at me through the broken holy shit he
knows i'm in here this is horrible huh what do i do should i um i think i might be trapped i'm
at the softlock guys i can't even press start i can't press select i can't press y
i think i have to i have to pause the view uh so press block me i wonder if that'll work
all right i have to that was really loud um
maybe if i breathe wait hold on why can i do left and right but nothing else
where's this gonna put me i was under the impression that it was i was gonna hurt him
or something and then i would have to hide again i'm i'm i can't even how am i gonna justify
anything anymore let's see what happens i'm the only person that ever walked back in the dumpster
but i felt safe in there even the developers didn't go back in the dumpster please don't tell
me that that right that's not fair okay that's um we have a major problem here i couldn't just
resurrect r2 didn't work uh-huh r2 doesn't work anymore i and neither to start i can't pause the
game can i do it on keyboard no hold on all right that was weird why look at my i didn't i didn't
okay that let's go unplug the controller it seems like it's fixed now but just for the sake of doing
that i'm gonna do it just because you know okay i think everything is now fine let's go back and
this time only go in the bird house once i thought there was no fall damage in the game silly me
don't do anything silly okay then it's into the outhouse until he turns left and there we go into
the dumpster but the item i gotta okay i'm gonna stab him and then get the item i have like a couple
seconds to quickly get it snap see the use of breaking the illusion of the effective illusion
techniques okay now where wow safe i think i'm safer yep jesus my god maybe not he's gonna
worm his way in here i think he's stuffing his body in it wait which side is he going
oh my god he's coming over this way i think what's all over me snake peepee more sugar what was that
guy's name for the infomercials taught everybody different languages what was his name yes the guy
that taught other languages that was on the infomercials it was like late night tv in the
90s muzzy yeah i was never here we can ease trying i can't really pause the game right now
no no no no keep talking who are you even looking at me something up there can you see
i feel like that guy can see still i want to hear this conversation like this is gonna help
lord gilbo i love how you actually put your hand up to your ear like that let's get up uh what is
this touch remnant i don't get it i'm gonna get invaded yeah okay pretty nice uh remnant wait hold
on uh let's clear this it's probably items down yeah there is all right fight time ah i who is
i'm getting those indicators that's the rust okay see if i can do that well jesus man
oh my all right you're gonna be let's go yeah the game did say that that skill was tough you're
right you're right i shouldn't it what is that over there we have one of those things we do
sick so i have uh unseen aid 13 well it's good that i have this so is there anything else i can
do that is items over there oops wrong button stuck i really stuck a little hole all right who
else has a gun that guy does i feel like should i kill that then yeah i mean let's go
so well didn't know you were there don't i tried i tried just heal just want to see what the
item there's an item down there i just don't know it was stupid ceramic shards um do we have here
interesting uh hold on this person gonna get up gunpowder and soon you will be too
ash good healing pellets and the door does not open from this side of course it doesn't why
would it why would it open there's no reason why it would this is very large area i like it hurt
falling down here well this is very obviously a boss but we're gonna get the cutscene though
oh there he is whoa all right okay all right not fair not fair not fair not fair not fair i need
to get up or something i don't know i have no idea get up can i jump can i right oh he said
gunpowder can i throw like a bomb or something he said my horse gunpowder for my horse i'm gonna
die here and that's pretty cool but is it enough the horse has to go i don't have any healing
uh somebody else is dying so uh let me try it do i have anything i could do i think the gunpowder
in it i think so did eat the sugar too yeah well let me just do it again if i look how much money
do i have if i lose do you just just die i don't know whatever i just cut off cut you off sorry
it seems very unfair but it's still possible no maybe it's not i'll say that yet come on he's
looking at his come on come here get off the horse let's go no never mind let's try
oh i timed that wrong it's definitely possible but i'm definitely missing something i feel like
i could actually do it but for the purposes of where else can i go i gotta go back to drunk guy
i could try to kill him without secret item go kill truck go fight drunk guy wasn't there
someone else back here i feel like i missed something back here no i can kill him i'm gonna
i'm killing the horse guy i can do it i've i've faith let me let me use some of the items that
i'm not using at all you know what i mean i have all this stuff shave it shave it shave it might
just use it attack power vitality damage let's just let's like just eat one of these
can i have more than one at a time pellets on i'm gonna give it one more try i'm gonna
know two more tries without using any items i'm gonna give it a go go up right here
oh comes out of here all right let's do it what about for this shit i wonder if this is like worth
really you got some reach fuck i didn't see that fuck bad start really bad start
shit oh yeah he did moves around so fast i i still am trying to wrap my brain around
when to resurrect and when not to resurrect don't tell me i'm doing this very wrong
just don't res unless you legit think you can kill him yeah let me try it again can i step on
the spear i don't think so i don't i don't get a prompt for it what's your name again
i need more of this i can probably jump on that
oh wowie let's go all right i'm gonna take one of these right now phase two
whoa what was the what the fuck are you doing back up back up back up take another one
oh you're killing me don't go that far am i burning in the fire
no i don't think so goodbye fuck off yeah shinobi execution memory
the battle memory of an extraordinary foe lingering in the mind of the wolf
commune with the sculptor's idol and confront memories of battle to permanently increase
attack power keeper of ashina castle gate mechanical barrel a mechanical metal barrel
that can be given to the sculptor to enable prosthetic tool upgrades it's perfectly inside
the wrist okay so after almost six hours of playing i started to realize that you don't
have to just parry every attack that's why i beat him there not really it helped it does help but
you don't have to i was under the impression that that was you had to do that it makes you look cool
yeah it does you can just block and then parry parry block swing swing block and you can dodge
it i'm i was trying to go a little too fast with it in regards to perfect parry perfect
parry perfect parry swing swing swing swing you don't have to do that okay so i have
prosthetic tool upgrades yeah yeah yeah upgraded tools can be created now i should okay that's
another level up cool is there anything else here that i can do i think i'm good here unless
i can get up there which i don't think i can wait what's in there might as well the enhance
attack power option has been unlocked you can now consume battle memories to increase your attack
power causing you to deal more vitality and posture damage with your attacks but wait a minute
should can i put this in the buddha and should i not use this yet let me see what is it attack
power one let's just do it battle memory of an extraordinary foe although distant
recollection of such a memory provided sustenance for the wolf onewa once led a group of infamous
bandits but was defeated by ishin who was so captivated by his show of strength that he took
him in as an ashini warrior onewa would later go on to become gen nichi row ashina's most trusted
retainer attack power has been enhanced yeah why is that memory one out of one weirdly enough okay
let me go back to the temple give this upgraded thing so you can't hold on to more than one
it's a mechanism that can serve as the very core of the prosthetic
pendant here fit it to the arm what difference does the barrel make with a versatile base such
as this i can use various purifying agents to further all agents purifying agents of materials
gunpowder scrap metal things like gunpowder and scrap do have a lot of those things i don't have
any more tools do i no but i do have upgrade materials and sen can be spent to create upgraded
versions of tools you must own the base tool and also complete any prerequisite upgrades
okay so we've got unknown tool look at this spring loaded axe unknown shuriken it's like
monster hunter spring load flame vent i can't do any of these yet very cool okay that i already did
so now now i'm gonna try to go back and do fat guy i have no money unless there's some hold on
let me see the castle gate is there something else i missed here yeah it didn't open this door
why is sub only on uh people are kind of going crazy in the first like hour or two of the stream
so i figured maybe we should chill it out for a little while so we're just gonna keep going
progress oh right give me the days i wish sub only mode was on all the time things are
chilling i could read messages um i mean it has i think it has a time and like a place for it
something like this is not really uh brand new from software game i think you know warrants
maybe it being on for the sake of you know somebody's
vaccinating like crazy or saying spoilers or stuff like that you know it's kind of it's by
design right all right let's get let me see i guess we're gonna go this way spoilers anything
else up here i want to get over there uh can i nope that's just not gonna happen is it
i'm gonna have to go on the roof from here that's more like it more attack power candy can only hold
so much of it what really i mean i think i jumped into it i that's not fair i just got kaizo blocked
well i'm kind of being sloppy now yeah look at how look at how just sloppy i'm being i used
five thousand percent of my brain power on that last boss i'm dead i i'm just gonna die i don't
want to use the resurrect okay let's try this again so let's take a look at this before i just
sloppily just run out naked two guys down here something over here too uh let's go over this
way thanks for the info okay i thought these guys would just chumps and they're not at all
they're very okay they're very talented i thought they would just okay i'm gonna die again i have
to actually take their boy oh boy oh boy i can't i gotta i gotta take the actual health down
i can't even tell when they're attacking really just die again uh it's possible we're getting
close to gamer fatigue it's very possible yeah when you make mistakes like that like literally i
it's like a cinder block in my brain right now let me go back here for a second
okay that was a car on top of another car there's no way that wasn't just a triple decker car and
the car on top even though isn't moving is in neutral was holding the gas down why
can't go up there do i know this person oh whoa whoa whoa wait wait wait wait somebody in here
what is it a chest whoa it's like a person
to purchase an offering and maybe i sell items to be off so they might rest in peace
why is he taking his head through uh i can sell here okay why would you buy money that'll be 550
coins for 500 for money for a bag of money it's because money what is this using it will slightly
increase resurrected power restore the power of life to those who have been drained of it by
offering this drop to the sculptor's idol with the recovery charm in hand in turn all afflicted
with the dragon rod will be healed okay uh i kind of need this sell the coin purse
sell the coin purse buy it back sell it buy it back sell it buy it back and let me use
one of these pouches here how many do i have a lot what do you get for it 100 use another one
okay so i have roberts firecrackers oh oh and a gourd seed oh okay all right all right it
damn i didn't even see those okay so how much do i get this 500 a thousand is this going to
be 500 right i'll take it so now do i have anything else i can sell i need coins i got
another gourd which is good there was somebody else down here this guy moved is this guy a
magician oh no no no that's just their shirt they have on all right wait up what is he going to start
swaying
he is random guy gives me the name
that's the name of this game yeah
excellent you'll need this if you're with me second rat description a description of the rats
that have snuck into ashina speak to the tengu again once the rats are dealt with the rats are
assassins from senbu temple short stature wear bamboo hats a large a number of rats are lurking
about last seen around the castle gate oh there's the guys the people up front that were talking
shit it's the people out front
sure i'll give it a try lady uh let's go over here well there's very obviously more up this
way i gotta talk to that lady too uh more there's a way out there okay oh there's a chest in here
the mimics in this game yes finally a prayer beard i can level up my attributes now all right
let's go do that now if i just dropped out and r2ed this guy sliced his head off let's talk to the
lady then go kill the rats what was that lady down here this was the door that i couldn't open before
first
i have not wondered
no matter what
okay anything else
okay nice cupcake it's on fire stupid uh where uh where let me go down on you right slow motion
i'm gonna take in a bunch of vitamin c and i'm gonna get another good night's sleep
and another triple decker no i'm not sleeping i'm just like just coughing the thing about
coughing that sucks the most is like my like abs hurt my like stomach hurts my face hurts
it just drains you of all ability take medicine i took day cool like five hours ago you only take
that shit like once every 10 to 12 hours all right let's see so enhance physical attributes
enhance physical attributes do it strung together an offering to a sculptor's idol
maximum vitality and posture nice max vitality and posture both increased good i'm very happy
about this let's go deal with the rats you take a shit every 10 to 12 hours sometimes
sometimes that happens all right where were those little guys like up this way right where
where were those little mushroom dudes little like little guys over here no other way
did i beat the horseman i did i did he was he's pretty cool well i'm gonna have this is it up here
need a vroom emote at this point yeah but a vroom emote
all the time they're over here there we go okay let's fight the where are they
there's one here he's facing this direction there's one that's the point of emote
yes i know black gunpowder good get off me get off me get off me
is it weird that i want somebody to do that to me
it's like looney tunes he broke every bone in my back all right how many more
is there another one did it say how many there were last seen around the castle gate
oops i think that's it unless it's somewhat here which i don't see there's only three i think
let's see what he says is this guy just gonna give me kill quests imagine finding out your
neighbor is not only a streamer but is obsessed with you and has an emote dedicated to you because
you drive loud apart from my arm machinist style skills it's a whole nother treat
it's our school of fighting no hard and fast movie just win your battles that alone is the
most important rule of the ashen style i hope it can be of assistance with your rat hunt and most
of all your own battles you get to fight about the ways of the ashina yeah it's our school of
fighting you just win your just win that alone somebody mentioned this was chat earlier
they're uh they were completely correct they were absolutely right okay here's uh
ashina i guess i have to be sitting down it's not a big deal you just win well okay
i wonder if i'm good enough to attempt fat guy again i'm gonna try ashina delivers a heavy one
hit overhead strike high posture damage and also recovers one's own posture with a strong forward
step single-minded mastery is the heart of the ashina style strength so just one big huge heavy
swing i gotta pick something and stick with it uh well here's your replayability that people
were concerned about i don't know if you can get all these maybe you can only do one of these trees
and maybe some of the other ones i don't know but this to me looks like replayability but
i'm going to end of the stream no no i'm trying to decide on what i want to do with my points
should i try this should i just do this all the way okay there's a slash and then there's a power
up power up there's all power ups this is the parry do something and but i got i'm gonna take
my time i want to make sure it's what i want to do i'm not just gonna go as fast as i can or hurry
up so when you just deflect it increases damage done to their posture from all sources that's
great so this is this is deflect every move let's put this up and see what it looks like
that takes a while ha ha wow that's it's gonna be hard to do it's worth a shot let's go try to
fight the the drunk guy i'm gonna be slow i'm gonna clear it out this is where we want to be
after this i'm probably gonna take a break and we're gonna start tomorrow probably early again
tomorrow i've leveled up twice well at once technically right let's just see if i can do
this shit does this go oh right okay and then i'm not going let me let me let me uh work backwards
and i say that because i want to fight the wizard he's the real boss of the night for me
i can't really tell what that was but no matter the boss was the friends we made along the way
i mean yeah okay clear now where was the wizard asshole so there was a way to go down
i panicked around here and i just started sprinting in random directions there's a
cave that was the cave i just came down though where is that guy here okay it was down here
all right let's go me versus the wizard i'm ready fuck i was waiting okay so that was a sweep
is there more than one wizard yeah there is it's a bunch of them they're just a regular enemy what
didn't block it no i blocked it fuck you what you got you can't block thrusts
no so many mechanics that need to memorize fuck dodge parry jump rock paper scissor
i have to go down there i don't know where the fuck i am right now i killed the first spear guy
now i have to do all this shit you know what i don't care i'm just gonna run by these fucking
people i'm just gonna run by the first wizard i want i'm supposed to see what's down here
i don't want to fight 10 15 people what's even down here that really just happened get it get it
get it get it okay that's it i got it i did it no oh my god just the the back and forth with the
fucking the dash the fucking it's just you have to just fucking muscle memory memorize it and it
takes a long time no that's wrong but i'm still gonna kill him like i had a ton of money on him
thank god i did this just my brain has trouble when that little indicator pops up it's almost
like i meant it's it's like playing batman right you're waiting for that to happen
but also on top of waiting for that to happen you need to like play the game too because think
about when batman you can just wait for that to pop up and just press y and be fine and be done
you gotta like be aware of everything going on and wait for the batman signal and it's one of three
different batman potential counters this game really makes you feel like batman i'm dead here
i got a bone out of here just don't let this guy kill me in the bone up it's a slow guy he's gonna
end it he's gonna end it isn't he isn't he no he's not don't do i don't have any pellets
no we don't throw that just distracted him all right bone out oh shit he's gonna end the stream
okay i'm not done yet all the way to the bottom okay okay
that leaves me with there's two ways for me to go right now i want to try i want to try to do
the drunk guy just once and then i'm going to rage turn off the stream don't ask me why i
boned all the way out here i'm dying of dragon rod yeah i know very very appropriate thing to
be suffering from right now right all right let's do this let's just go through wait a minute wait
wait wait wait don't i have a seed didn't i buy a seed did i already use it i did i use that seed
that i bought i don't remember using it maybe i did you piece of crap you piece of crap seriously
i didn't use it did i wouldn't it be in my inventory no i gotta go use this and should i
heal everybody's rod or should i wait till they're just barely dead and then resurrect the houses on
fire well let's heal is this healing them no that's the wrong thing what do i i gotta give to the
his buddha wrong thing you do actually do it at the bonfire oh i thought it said like he had
used it at his like buddha thing did he just he just didn't use it hopefully this is not a mistake
offer okay restore the power of light to those who have been drained of it by offering this drop to
the sculptor's idol with the recovery charm in hand still don't understand it appears as though
your body come and see me i will so i need i need the recovery charm all right these are all things
to consider for tomorrow but i want to just try to fight this guy and give one solid attempt
then i've got to go i'm gonna cry i'm gonna get some food i wanted to go a little bit longer
because i still want to play but of course of course i get cursed with getting sick the day
before one of the biggest releases of the year and not only that one of the most anticipated
releases for me that i wanted to play i just slid on that just stop being sick i wish it were
that easy this part like my goodness because ever you have to get rid of these guys otherwise they'll
just keep coming come behind the wall here it's people shooting the arrows does these guys run
across the whole lake we've done it like three times it happens every time can you stealth not
here it's a big open field you can run past them well every time i run past them they just run
across the lake and i get hit by they like four or five people come from behind it's happened the
last three times we tried it yeah i on the roof you can run by them on the roof but there's always
a few that aggro i'm just gonna kill them all and i want no variables maybe through the building
here to the right maybe you can walk through the building like on top and then around okay
uh i have two heels there shouldn't be anybody left let's go try to do this i'm gonna really
seriously attempt it let's go talk to this guy maybe should i can i pull these guys first i wonder
because all these let's go archers first okay not bad i'll handle this you take care of him
all right let's go let's go let's go let's get him get him together can i heal him i don't know
what just hit me oh that's a jump it's a sweep oh two punches in a row oh do i have any more
healing anything nope i'm in trouble i'm dead i'm gonna try it let's come back didn't get it
it's definitely doable no heels i'm so concerned with taking that guy's money
come on i can do it how many times is he gonna what's that do whoa oh no god damn that it was
so close the double i tried to dodge the double tap oh no i have to do all this bullshit again
slapping ass cheeks and anger god i've never concentrated more in a game than like that
i had it too so close it's definitely doable but fuck man that was i was like two hits away
just that string is so strange it's like champion gundyr that's what it reminds me of
when champion gundyr does that little like pain in the ass all right come on and see what i mean
though that that motherfucker right there is not gonna stop that guy is he's gonna bow he's gonna
shoot me like see that indicator is gonna be on the screen the whole time thank god all right let's
go i'm ready i'm ready i'm ready let's go i'm ready let's go let's go let's do it let's go
make it quick all right easy i got four heels let's go you drunk fuck that's gonna fuck me
every time i'm on the ground dude i can i can you not parry his hand sloppy you can i just tried
this is really really really bad attempt you know it was it was sweet jesus christ
just kill me i'm gonna kill this guy before it's through the stream it's gonna happen i know it is
it doesn't mean it's not frustrating as hell trying to kill this guy i'm gonna do it it's
gonna happen eventually i know it okay if i go up there without him then i aggro everybody
especially even the drunk guy so i have to take him with me you got to this part in two hours
well so did i but i went and did two other bosses and came back here i think it's time i don't even
care i'm going for it i'm using these things so this is attack power i feel like i'm just gonna
use this like right now go hey you really i got this dumb aggro right now actually probably for
the best is he should i don't think he'll die to these guys really he might all right easy i don't
know why i did that but i decided to do it for some reason he's gonna die here i don't know
anymore even killed him thought he was done not enough go drink get it get it oh my god there's
so much breaking up my posture oh it hurts back up back up back up back up no not the palm
anything but the palm triple quadruple palm quadruple bypass palm wait a minute who is this
guy you're shitting me no he's just drinking for free no no no anything but that anything but that
anything but that it's over unrefined sake a bottle of cloudy unrefined sake sake's drink
meant for sharing this cloudy sake is one of ishan ashina's favorites and his reputation
for getting one too drunk too quick okay yes oh that was rough and that's just like the third
mini boss there's been one real boss and then two or three mini bosses and man they're pretty rough
so let me see can i i can go this this is like the first act i told you i was gonna do it i
just have to try you have to just relax uh what's in here pellet
he thinks it's over it is it's over there's nothing else in here there's only a couple of
like random dudes and then we'll come across you know what just fight them i've come this far
was the worst that you could do right now oil thank god i can oh my god there's a thing here
just open this i got three points i like that so i'm gonna get both of these so this is
more posture damage when you deflect and after a deflect you just do more posture damage um
yeah sure absolutely nice let's rest here okay hello son of a deep
image okay anything else items okay young master cut scene that's i've rested already right just
in case i didn't what do i have uh more than 80 dollars i'm resting here right any more items
no uh well he just kind of came out of nowhere didn't you too you are so i'm gonna kill that
guy with a swing i know it i'm gonna accidentally swipe that guy and hit him right in the head
will you just don't let me accidentally kill this dude all right here we go what's the deal
i have one of those i have those an illusion
and you listen tried my best to be his guardian the heraldala is finished okay shift tatami aside
who oh i thought tatami was a person i didn't know tatami was a thing i don't have the key to get in
here she baited that was fun you got a key sir listen well hey thanks for coming to stream i'll
see you guys tomorrow guys i apparently need to get a key for this that i don't have i have
absolutely no clue with hell that could be let me see what i got here i have don't have tools
do anything no uh it's i wonder if it's here all right um i have no idea where i'm going but
i'm gonna find it wherever it is or maybe i'll just die let's just reset them just reset them
okay so now what rooster okay i don't think i didn't go down this way this is new i can
tell because there's a wizard here that's a that's a much that's a strong wizard that's a two
hp wizard countering thrusts yeah yeah i already got it but that guy's gonna be a pain countered
it's one again let's do it again let's all fuck this up if i bring in another idiot over here and
it's a slow swing guy no good got it he's dead another prayer bead i only need two more
i felt good i felt really good okay bird's eye view we got item over here just pellet and
nothing else this is the item balloon where am i another sculptor's idol so much for gamer
fatigue apparently yeah i guess sometimes all this liquid has to get drained out of your body
before you can refill it with more liquid what i don't know he says true
ah true that did it to me i don't know why just did maybe i am getting tired but that's fun
uh where am i going
all right i gotta relax it's not that big of a deal let's go this really is jeremy has tv
oh god where did that just take me to the mist mist oh wow oh oh rick get away from me get away
i'm being hell is raining down on me right now by one guy anybody else feel like the health pool
is lower than in the other from games oh there is hell it's just it is it's actually four guys
motherfucker you're better with a sword than you are a bow there's a guy with intestines coming
out of his stomach okay this is a fight you came up a little short maybe you should try that again
it's a sweep that's a sweep he's a sweeper i think a side dodge is better than uh he baseball swung
up my lord that's heavy he caught me in the air i was actually pretty good on his part
yeah i don't think i should try to parry that just dodge forehead guys with the bows are really
really really bad in this game they okay here's what they did from software took the dog and
yeah the dog sucks in every from software game let's make the dogs not a big deal but bow and
arrow guys used to be a joke the the arrow used to shoot like slower than it does in minecraft
now these guys are not a joke to replace these this is the new dog they get these guys have
guns sometimes now like seriously it was a big deal if somebody shot you in any of the other
from software games of the bow because they may as well have blue plates specials you from tribes
it was an embarrassment if you got hit by a bow and arrow in those games um some i'm gonna
somebody gonna all right wait a minute no that's i'm not there's no dad fight that's just dead
that's huge wonder i turned on the gas in the kitchen i was gonna make a fucking
tuna melt i fell asleep on the couch was a long day of killing all right here's the key key to
the hidden temple in the errata estate given by the owl you inconsiderate fuck
uh hold on this one's been building for a while the very back of the estate i know where it is
too the lord is absolute defended with your life if he is taken bring him back at any cost
no one ever told me to not put utensils in the microwave i was trying to heat him up to make it
so when i ate my soup it was nice and warm i'm not laughing at that wait why did the fire get worse
uh somebody talked about do how they do that without the ice cream you use you put you warm
up your utensils so you can eat ice cream easier it's like that's genius but what the fuck
so you what you put warm water like under the sink i've never even thought about that sometimes
i let the ice cream just sit on the counter for like three hours because it's too cold to eat
and i never thought for a second just to take a spoon and like put hot water on it well you
just chisel out and eat little ice cream chips and then you get sick of it you throw it that hurts
where do i need to go sneak i'm just boning out of here get to my left and follow the cliff
who's left my left or your left there might be an item or two that i missed
from here might as well just do it yeah it's possible jump down there because we're gonna
miss like the weird jumping from like monopoly house to monopoly house right that's cool that's
cool yeah ah that's cool all right here we are uh i can bone out of here just want to see if there's
anything that i missed on the left when did i stop taking the stream seriously i'm i'm still taking
it seriously all right here we go it's gonna is there anything i can i have nine hundred and
sixty four dollars i think i'm gonna where's the guy that i can buy stuff from somewhere in here
right no where are they you're like up here i got money and if this is a major boss that i'm going
to lose to over and over again i might as well use this money okay so is it up this way i know
there was a couple of npcs if here no this is progressing further what about this way maybe
possibly because this goes up into the rat guy and then over here yeah hi i do want to purchase
something yes i do i'm gonna get the firecrackers it's just another thing to try uh maybe i should
just buy a bunch of this stuff why would you purchase a coin i guess maybe just um yeah you
know what let's do it let's do it because i understand why you do that it's to store the
money so you don't lose it that makes sense what else would you use a coin pouch for in case you
die yeah that's cool interesting way to do it okay i'm ready god i just love video games okay take
those seeds use the key what's behind door number one oh boy that's a cutscene
is the real magician yes it looks like an actual wizard battle yeah good luck good luck you look
like a shoe i was gonna untie you and you'll be done uh vitality and posture yeah the lower
one's vitality the slower their posture recovers that's right posture gauges color gets redder as
recovery rate slows fast posture recovery ideally you gotta bring i gotta bring your health down
okay why lady butterfly why ah i don't know what that move does i'm assuming it's when she does
that like big dun dun like that well was that a grab i can't even tell i'm dead game over uh i
i'm not gonna resurrect until i have a better idea what the hell's going on no reason not to
well it's on a timer right it's not i thought when you what what about the pie she's just waiting
for me listen so that once she goes in the air it's a grab so you just have to dodge it
what is that is that does that count as a thrust dear god i have no idea damn it's hard to really
get around okay not bad back it up yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah die get out of my way
wait a minute the snap peas snap see snap peas should i even do this should i another attempt
so wait ah she's oh no but i don't have i need more healing i don't want to use one of these
items i know snap peas now but where i only have six of them where am i what do i get more of them
you know i'm saying i'm not gonna use them until i have a good attempt
why i have no reason not to respond i feel like this ain't gonna help me here
you can revive once the second one is on the timer okay i see start again i'm not gonna use the
those pellets either let's try let's go i'm hold on i'm all tangled up here really that sucks
that's a waste of an attempt right here get out of the way i'm out of posture eat this
that's actually not a bad move to do that it's so hard to avoid that fucking move you gotta wait
till the last possible millisecond kind of like spend some money to make that guy never come back
thankfully this is right here all right let's see you think i'm gonna die 200 times
no i think that's the first time i've seen that move what the fuck man oh my god give me even like
a second oh even one second one fucking second i didn't even get a chance i'll give you point
five seconds i'm gonna get i i'm gonna give us a few attempts somebody else is like dying from
fucking cough rot speak of which there it is this boss is really easy just make sure you don't get
hit and hit her if i can jump down all right easy ease it ease that's a that's a sweep
it was a sweep it's hell it goes on my healing she's already like backed up started out all
right and then uh you know what i think i'm gonna do i think i'm just gonna instead of healing just
die and then use all the heels she just blocked it really well i mean not heal at all go as long
as i can and die and then use my heels she's just very unpredictable that didn't come on now don't
do this to me breaking my rule it's a sweep on the ground pretty much every time gotcha don't let you
recover okay phase two let's just use them i'm gonna see what it does oh just eliminates them
okay i know it doesn't i what does that do that's kind of okay is that a sweep i can't tell
of course this asshole it's always a sweep on the ground it seems dude these little magical
fucking orbs watch out for those magics no god damn it that move oh fuck that move
that move sucks such ass oh fuck off what a load of dog shit perfect fucking dodges with like
no iframes oh fuck off each shit that's bullshit okay what the fuck give me a fucking break
no i didn't throw my controller i put it on the table slightly angrily i'm stuck on the
all right bites controller in half that was definitely the attempt to probably do it and
is it three phases i wouldn't be surprised you know it's like funny about these games especially
this game especially about squirrel i you know i probably could it's probably easier to win the
lottery than it is to beat these bosses you know what i mean i bet you okay in the time it takes
for me to beat this boss i could probably buy like a scratch ticket every like 20 minutes
and like win 50 bucks all right this is a dead run let me start over
every death is an hour of minecraft no i really i you know what i really need to do i really do
need to get out of here because if anybody knows anything about muscle memory and playing games
like this you gotta have like 24 hours for your brain to even know what it's doing see i haven't
like saved my game in my brain yet everything i've learned so far is not here until i do until i go
to sleep in skyrim no it's a sweep you have to get more uh no i wasn't close enough
are you almost at the health pool or i can actually hurt you i thought it was another dash
i thought it was gonna be a spin oh i can't get out i'm stuck oh my fucking god guys i can't move
like if i fell in my well it's in my house i don't know i don't know somebody is a rope
because i fell all the way down i pee into this fucking thing just throw the rope down here i'm
trying to climb out it's only like it's only like 60 feet i have to i'm gonna take a break
it's time to take a break you know it's time yeah get walled stupid thanks for coming to
stream everybody i'll see you tomorrow there ain't no way i'm beating this shit tonight
this this is so difficult for me to do right now if you if you walked in here with like gasoline
right and you were like jeremy uh you better hurry up and beat this the whole house is gonna burn
you can just walk around and like i didn't know where i was going with that one
this is pure insanity what i was trying to say was in the time it took for somebody to like pour
gasoline all over my house give me 10 warnings and then start it in the corner i'd still be here
like in fucking an hour and a half not even that you could just make you could make like a small
little like wood tp downstairs and sit there and blow on it while i'm up here screaming
you can steal everything in the house uh this is actually the last time that i'm gonna get out of
this person come from i'm at it's i'm actually dying this game it gave it to me it's killing me
of course you block it you dick i tried to jump and every time it's incorrect every time
hello hello all right i'm gonna run around and uh
off of where to go where to go where is it don't you dare do that to me i swear to god i will be
very upset with you i'm losing my fucking mind fucked man the second phase fuck me no don't don't
don't i tried to jump it i tried it just happened so quickly that happened real fucking fast now
didn't it it's so fucking hard it is so hard it's so hard it's so hard it's the hardest thing i've
ever done so hard it's so hard bro bro let me tell you something bro it's so hard kill me kill me
just do it kill me it's that second phase trying to get the damage to be able to do the posture
damage it just sucks you gotta get behind them you're gonna dodge to the the only way you can
really do that is when they go in the air they throw the thing wait how long has this been on
for how long has that been on for did you not see that attempt how what is the last thing you saw
no fucking way okay just okay good i was gonna say that was a really good attempt
oh this game is so hard it's like next level now i see what people are talking about
i was like no it's not like what do you mean it's like the hardest game that they've ever made
everybody says that no this is fucking brutal it's it's fun though because it just fucking
it's something i i might have to restart again that was a good exchange you just fucking embarrassed
me on my stream the only person that embarrasses me on my stream is me come here come here come here
group up group up group up not this time not this time elsa oh and we can finally call it quits
fucking frozen shoe bitch do i it's too hard please don't burn my house down with gasoline
that was really fun okay droplet pale pink crystal residue known to form when an immortal
oath fails to step okay i'm gonna talk about this for a second those you've that you guys
that have seen the cinematic masterpiece and written down book masterpiece that is
the harry potter universe okay you know that scene when dumbledore the most the strongest
character in the entire universe right he drinks that he tells harry to do it he's gonna drink
that potion and he's like i can't i can't do it please no please i know no the strongest guy in
the whole world and he says let make sure that i do the whole thing right it's really hard and
he tells her like throughout the course and he's like i'm not doing it i'm not doing it i'm getting
it away from me but they do it and then spoiler alert i was gonna say that something else but
point is i was saying those things i was going no i can't do it i'm not gonna do it i'm done
i'm going home but all i just had to drink the rest of the potion and i'm now i'm fine
it's too much for me no it's too hard i gotta go i'm leaving how is that a bad analogy
dumbledore drinks the potion and he says he can and you took your hands off the
controller and this is what happens died to cutscene wheel okay
the potion actually like was the potion was killing dumbledore
no he was fine look i just missed him i just missed a major major storyline cutscene because
somebody questioned my dumbledore analogy i'm furious right now i am fucking furious what
just happened nothing here put this in firecracker blinds foes and inflicts posture damage on beast
type 70s i can't even it's time to go that is such a perfect opportunity for me to tell you that's
i'll see you tomorrow that wouldn't even words that was just phonetically pronouncing sounds
where i thought the spaces needed to be for the text that was on the screen all right so what do
you think about sakiro where would you put it in the oh we're gonna call it something different
now the the sakiro is born the the the the the the souls the souls kiro born games i don't know
it's really hard to say i i do think it is probably so first time playthrough i think is
the hardest i'm trying to remember dark souls 3 dark souls 1 bloodborne try remember the first
10 hours or so in the game i think it's the hardest first 10 hours of any of the games
now that who knows if that's going to keep being the case whether or not you know when i have my
save point when i wake up tomorrow my muscle memory and all that it it's fantastic though
it's everything and more that snake was just 10 out of 10 it's great to get your ass kicked by
a game that's really really hard but i'm gonna that's just exactly at eight hours here i will
see you i'm not even gonna move from this spot well i am but the character is not so tomorrow
uh i'm just gonna whenever i get up and get going we're gonna go again i'm not gonna play
without what are you talking about when have i ever done a from software game on stream
and didn't finish it no wait i'm gonna try to get through the whole thing dark souls 2 i didn't
know but dark souls 2 was i already beat dark souls 2 twice before that stream even started
demon souls i beat all the demon souls on stream all dark souls 1 all dark souls 3
we have no evidence of that i can show you steam achievements that would count long story short
i'm gonna give this a yes out of all right my final rating will have to come later
definitely two thumbs up if you are on the fence oh i'm not so sure they went a different direction
it's great if you like smashing your face against a wall over and over again and eventually putting
on both pants and tightening up your belt i'm achieving great victory in a hard video game
absolutely it's fantastic so uh let's actually put on the outro screen hopefully by tomorrow
this cough will be gone or at least diminished to a point where you won't even know what's happening
okay and we are going to go back to the bits i'm actually going to pee though first because it looks
like we got probably like about 30 30 40 minutes of bits shouldn't take us too long but i will be
right back i'm just gonna pee see you guys in a second oh i thought i muted me passing stones
oh i'm sorry about that i usually pretty good about muting hey let's
cough you were all biked up i enjoyed the ambient cars all right so thanks for coming
see you guys tomorrow we're going to keep going through it and why don't we move on to
bits don't miss the toilet miss the toilet i do just fine okay so let's go back uh eight
hours ago a long time ago there but there was a lot of money tonight a lot of it too much
one would say there was 225 250 dollars one twice 50 50 50 a shitload an absolute
shitload of money so let's go back sad vega thanks for the 250 i'm so mad right now my amazon
pre-order just came in the mail they mailed me my digital code i had to wait all day for it
why would they mail you a digital code why wouldn't they just have it so you can just copy and paste
or something that yeah that sucks well hope that by you you got it hopefully you uh enjoy it it's
it's a great game some guy thanks for 15 bucks 15 dollars from some guy wow holy crap an eu
friendly stream oh sub only is still on right uh how do i turn that off sub only the room is
already in sub only mode sub only off i don't even know how do i do the sub how do i turn
off my what's going on okay my my chat just crashed um i actually don't know how to do this
i feel like oh no no no i know hey there no that's not how you do it i don't know how to do this
everybody know what the command actually is because i don't i have no idea
this just goes to show you how often this gets pulled on i don't know how to take it off oh i
forgot even the mods don't even know nobody knows how to turn it off it's is it subscribers off but
this does that turn off all my subscribers oh there we go okay hey welcome back everybody hope
you enjoyed the stream sorry you were uh muzzled thank you but some guy 15 bucks eu friendly stream
sadly i won't be watching this stream because i want to play the game myself but anyway he's a
meme video only about five people in the chat will understand what this is let me see get a life
this is a meme video i just cut it off like before the breakdown uh it said there was a
warning on it it was like beef brain bath like warning i'm afraid to link this i don't know
if that means like it's gonna be loud or something i'm scared to link that but uh yeah if you're not
going to watch the sakiro streams and you want to enjoy it yourself i completely absolutely understand
these games are meant to be cherished and have your you know take your time through them
enjoy it it only happens once every few years enjoy it but thank you for the 15
dollars if you come across this thank you uh thank you venomous violets for the five bucks
your stream is going to get me through my last two hours of work even thinking about skipping the gym
to go home and watch the rest i've held out on watching all other sakiro streams to watch
yours such a big fan of my very first bit donation here's to many more thank you
i hope you enjoyed it i did i thought it was a blast in a uh continuously stab yourself with a
small needle kind of fun but it's it's really great to play these games i was going to pass
a kidney stone maybe i'm gonna go take a bath after this one but thank you venomous violets
if you come across this thank you these were a long time ago so i can understand if you're not
here anymore uh multi trip thanks for 250 can't believe you're doing a sequel to the neo meltdown
stream i'm very excited here's the difference uh i got out of the first area in sakiro i can't say
the same thing for neo the one and only time i played that i was drinking a bottle of whiskey
it was such a bad idea so let's do it again tomorrow uh i'm gonna maybe i'll have a few
drinks tomorrow yeah you know i deserve it i deserve it you know i haven't had like
i haven't i haven't any drinks i deserve like two glasses of wine tomorrow i've been a good boy
yeah i'm sick never mind that's true i do have a cough never mind damn it yeah
no no try to be a good boy again let's continue to be a good boy i do want to get over this it's
really really annoying you can tell when you have that a cough that you can just feel it's almost
like people probably think i'm laughing but half the time you've heard me go like
uh has been my chest has been trying to escape my body alcohol is not going to help probably
better deal but thank you for the 250 multi-trip this is we had this is this is where the string
started of 50 bucks from cats beanie 50 bucks from juno upsetto 225 from die 335 250 dollars from guy
dude 50 dollars from the reno 50 dollars from koopa troopa holy shit earlier in this stream it's
it was bunkers it's insane uh but thank you butt butt sniffer or butt sniffing uh thank you for
the 25 dollars from earlier i'm just gonna pretend that your dog dogs do that is a germa i've been
watching you since i was like 12 when you played borderlands on lepters channel oh man that's it
it's a long time ago 2011 it's 2019 i'm 20 years old now and i figured i'd show my appreciation for
all the content that's helped me through some tough times from 12 to 20 well i i am stunned
that you've been around for that long your whole teens into your early 20s i hope you listen to
me when i said to like be a good try to be a good person eat like vegetables eat um always
you know pay bills and i said a lot of things right vegetables ew what's 22 now 30 the grim
rapers biting my heels i did something today that i haven't done ever this is like you know
potentially embarrassing but who cares i ordered a back brace because i want to wear it on stream
because i want to keep my posture good and support my back has been killing me
so i'm trying ways to uh approach it you know like bottom kind of middle back right flanks on my back
it's been going on for six seven months i've had every i've checked my kidneys it's everything's
fine apparently i've i've had so many tests over the years to see like what the fuck could
be wrong no i think it's just i think i'm just getting old i have no idea i have a colonoscopy
coming up so maybe we'll see if something else is weird going on back there i'm gonna start
doing exercises but yeah i've got i got a back brace i'm gonna be falling apart i'm gonna lose
on my hair i'm gonna have a back brace on a good damn cane but regardless thank you thank you
esp especially root thank you root for the 26 bucks german say something funny germa venus
oh like i did say something funny and then that was like a pogchamp oh okay i see well thank you
for the 26 dollars that's a lot of money and thanks 26 bucks hopefully i'm hopefully what i said
was funny ferodian weapon thanks for the 250 ferodium no message just 250 thank you dork cube
thanks for the 250 here's a free video title for holy mac sakiro germa dies twice has crossed out
many times or i could be a really good youtuber and remember how i did that thing where i fell
down the well it'll be sakiro episode one i fell down a well in two or three exclamation points
and like three question marks and there'll be a my mouth wide open like that like that
hyper pogchamp right on the front and then like a picture of a well and the game like the video
game is so far in the background it's my face blowing out almost all of it a picture of a well
but this is one sentence or two sentences in an eight hour stream please somebody god click this
video is what that says and you have giant saucer photoshop eyes the internet they're gonna dig
this shit up in a thousand years and they're gonna be like what what's wrong with humans
uh thank you hey zeus for the 250 be a part of soil twice
it's true marvosh mcgalley thanks for the 250 hi german just want to let you know that one punch
man 2 is gonna be out soon make sure to save your yearly anime token for that no i'm gonna watch it
because in my opinion my yearly anime token currency that's okay that's a second season
it's not one season per year it's one anime per year so that means one punch man season two
is still part of the one anime a year because it's one it's just another season that's a loophole no
it's a loophole that's that's the same show hey peaceful hailey thanks for the 250
hi jeremy how are you doing i'm doing pretty good they say to be honest these past couple
days have been feeling pretty unhappy i don't want to share my sob story though i always feel
happier watching your streams i don't know hard times right now i'm just hoping it can get better
i hope it isn't weird thing to say well i wish i had a friend like you you seem like a very
understanding person and always have a good day hope you're enjoying sekiro i'm sorry that
you're not feeling good that doesn't that makes me sad that somebody people that hang out here
that have supported the channel are potentially not doing good not doing all right i really hope
whatever you're going through you get out of it you push through it i want everyone to be happy
you know i want you to i want you to be like enjoying yourself enjoying your life i really
truly hope that you start that what the did you hear that that person just tried to cut me off
did you that was somebody trying to talk over me and cut me up that was like a
cars do you have how many people are in your like rumor cult are they self-multiplying
are they it's a single cell rumor organism they're like bees they found a hive and they're
just going to and fro at least hope they're pollinating plants but anyways
uh i'm enjoying sekiro i will i would implore you to i know you're pretty active in this community
already but there are a lot of great people around here especially in that discord i know
you hang out there a lot of like-minded people hopefully that over the over the months and years
you can find somebody to hang out there somebody that can
chill with you we should make it called i don't think that's a good idea it's a very bad idea
but take care of yourself i wish you the best thank you so much for the 250
like-minded indeed we all eat an equal amount of glue now i eat way more i eat the most
smelly boy thanks for the 250 how would you feel if you found out uh that death consisted entirely
of an eternity where the only thing you can perceive is germa defoe in front of you you
cannot hear smell feel or taste anything just stare at germa defoe eternally with no perception
of anything else i don't think it matters what image it is any image would be terrible that could
be it could be a a puppy and after 200 millennia you'd be like get this fucking dog out of my face
it would start to morph you ever look in a mirror for long enough at yourself
if you just stare at yourself in a mirror for five minutes your eyes and your like teeth start to
morph imagine looking at yourself in a mirror 60 years straight thousand years straight don't
ever do that during a dream though are you high no just sick honey chain thanks with three bucks
hey germa just want to send you some love you away thank you thank you thank you thank you
we said super seal 250 i can see why you wouldn't want to but don't be afraid to turn on sub only
mode more often i like how chill it is more than the others yeah it i think it works sometimes
but i like having chat go crazy sometimes i like having chat react instantly and be able to look
over there and see something instantly from everybody right sub only mode all the time is
it's like paying to chat right and sometimes when there's i guess more than two three four five
thousand people who are chatting at the same time it can be necessary especially if stuff
starts to get out of hand or there's a big argument or a bunch of spam or something it's a good way to
kind of calm it down the low delay is amazing remember how it was before something would happen
and i would look over to the chat and it would take 10 to 15 seconds for me to see anything there
how did we manage before i don't even know but this is time and place for it like we said
talked about it already it might maybe it'll stay on for secure maybe maybe after another
six hours or so maybe i won't need it anymore we'll see it's not something i do all the time
hey sparrows thanks with five dollars sparrows uh hey jeremy just want to let you know that your
birthday shout out into a video for my friend i put your birthday shout out into a video for
my friend it went over super well uh you definitely went harder than 20 dollars deserve so i figured
i'd share some extra love treat yourself to an ice cream cone any flavor you want all right
feel better pinwheel was a punk ass take it easy glad that it went well glad that it made them happy
thank you for the five extra dollars on top of the 20 that you already gave
appreciate it spare uh nor thank you nor but thank you nor binary for the 10 dollars
and there's another hot take alert just give five community subs right now thank you thank you hot
take alert really appreciate it thank you thank you thank you but nor binary thanks for the 10
dollars jeremy gonna join in on the bits feels just want to say that after watching you from
near beginning of your youtube days you've grown a lot but kept being the same genuine guy you've
also reached your goal you've kept being funny evolving your content throughout the years
appreciate you dude for all you've done and shared throughout having mental instabilities and that's
just inspiring hope to be able to do such do such greatness as you've done with my shit now get that
sakira thank you there's already been a couple of
bits tonight talking about how long they've been around this community and that's that's a long
time as a member of my friends was seven years how long was like sign film now i'm not comparing
i'm just saying like in a television sense right like 10 years potentially of media
that's a very very long time to still be in the community and still be around and still be
sending me 10 dollars this far down the road from the beginning i am forever grateful and
i'm shocked sometimes too thank you for the 10 bucks and for the continued monumental support
tony said jerma talk on the subreddit is nintendo's killing your twitch channel suing
you into oblivion hope this is fake is one of my new favorite streamers hope the lawsuit goes well
maybe set up a patreon what where is this coming from i need to see where this is coming from this
is like the third time i've seen this where's this whole thing about me being sued oh it's
just that people are just making this up don't tell me talk on the subreddit as you're getting
sued i don't even know this information that's like why would i ever get sued by nintendo have
i even played a nintendo game on stream uh thank you cremator for the five dollars jerma my sister
found my twitch password and disabled my account is that why that's what the two is there for
cardboard infringement something similar to resist another 250 from cremator something better than
discord i don't know what that is a memo i'm not gonna have another anything else besides discord
it's it's already hard to manage that there's a lot of people on that discord and i'd rather
have that just be the place aminos and oh the mino is another chat community no no no no
no there's already it's all centrally located on that discord and it's already i don't i'm not
spreading myself out over like three four five social media platforms three two three four five
different community apps discord is the only one i barely tweet but uh thank you yoshi master for
the five bucks every time you die and don't resurrect i'm flipping three coins if all are
tails i die of dragon rod and close the stream for the night this is scary functional nightmare
no discord is just fine i pop in there a few times a week and just talk give announcements talk about
things i'm not gonna make another no i'm not downloading origin you know but thank you dude
door cube with the 250 jervis mad part benny hill that's definitely somebody said that i was
at my most like salty and savage tonight is that true i don't think so not even close
it'll never be as bad as hotline Miami 2 hotline Miami 2 uh yeah cremator says will you go on google
plus before it shuts down it's gonna shut down a couple weeks no why would i ever open google
plus good riddance to that platform google plus is the toy equivalent of a free race car in a
cereal box if it was there was it was why no there's a ton of already great race cars already
some of them even are free but thank you door cube uh we also had fluffy tuffy gave ten dollars
he's asking me if i'm gonna play the half-life 2 beta no no half-life never guaranteed
but thank you appreciate it anyways thank you thank you dork cube for the 250 pro chip when
you're so sick you can't reach the bathroom just shit all over the floor and dream germa will pick
it up with his bare hands there's so many layers to what you just said that i can't even explain
what you said that's like a 25 minute explanation to people that weren't here but thank you thank
you for putting in weapon for the five bucks explain it please no i had a dream where i
had to walk around and pick up shit with my bare hands because there were people coming over
that's pretty much it that's i that's essentially the entire story we also had garfield the monday
killer 250 here comes gar flock with a new garfo graph you're getting that pokemon sword and shield
game geronimo i know you don't give a hoot about pokemon but i always wanted to see a germa pokemon
team you don't care about competitive stuff so i'd it'd make for a fun team rather than the best
team lots of pokemon playthroughs have teams that look too similar but germ would do us right it
also gives a lot of new germa rubble characters it'd be more interesting than you are than you
think it'd be more interesting than you playing garfield's cart well i'll tell you i'll tell you
the team already it's uh the hypno what hip hip no what's it whatever his name is hypno top
um who's the what's the dirty rock the dirty rock guy geodude okay so hypno top geodude and
the weird like little mole bird that comes out of the ground this is like the little
yeah diglin yeah that's the team the mole bird is like a little mole a little gopher
but it's got a bird face there you go that's the dream team hey tingy thanks to the 250 for every
death in sicario you have to buy one lottery scratcher and dedicate an entire stream to
scratching them okay i'm serious okay that sounds fun sure was there a death counter tonight
and then and then and then whatever is one on the lottery tickets whatever's one on the scratch
tickets right whatever it is that goes back into community subs i'm into that that sounds fun
it's gonna be zero is gambling on stream terms of service i don't know i don't know
i don't think so if it's legal right don't people play like blackjack on twitch can i
like scratch like 45 scratch tickets gambling is a category right i i guys i live in las vegas
it's definitely legal here me streaming doing scratch shots and i look if you want to be
completely and totally like oh you don't like tell it like the gambling thing you don't want
to like make it look like fun no no i'm gonna write on the screen like do not fucking ever buy
these i'm gonna write like the word mistake 12 times it's gonna be around the screen while we do
it it was i think that'll be fine i'll double check to make sure that would be like okay with
twitch so yeah we'll see what should it be for every death should it be a dollar or like five
dollars because one dollar scratch offs don't win shit they have the worst probability five
dollars is a pretty good medium i think oh that's gonna be expensive though i have to be careful
if i die a hundred times like 125 to 150 times i died like 10 times just to the butterfly lady
we're at 15 it's got it's more i think it's more than 15 deaths today only at least 10 of them
only 10 were in the last 40 minutes you tell me i only died five times over the course of that
first seven hours in a way i probably died at least five to six to ten more times probably like 25
yeah yeah not resurrects we're going true deaths actual you get the ending not resurrect game over
we'll see how it turns out that's a fun idea though thank you tingy uh that was a great idea
it might have to be one dollar scratch tickets because if i died more than a hundred times
i don't know fuck it whatever you know what i mean that would be fun let me do a little bit of
research on that but thank you germa lied about minecraft vr he didn't but thanks to 250 i know
you have the black lung but yell into your mic as loud as you can and i'll gift 20 subs
no no i'm sorry i'm not doing that thanks for the 250 cough as loud as you can into the mic
thank you froidian weapon for the 250 appreciate it froidian peek a banana thanks to the five bucks
how come you're streaming when you're all coughing and sick take care of yourself hope you feel
better soon thanks for the fun stream thanks for being here and why am i streaming today because
it's sakira launch day i'm not gonna put put a thermometer in my mouth and put the covers up
no no no no i'm sorry i can't stream today it's only the launch of one of the most
anticipated video games in the last half decade
no i'm playing on launch day i want to play i wanted to play and i'm not going to play
off stream you know what i mean oh fuck i haven't been catching these with the mute i'm sorry
i know it's it's so grating i know people hate coughing i tried to do it as best as i could today
but i feel okay you know i don't i don't have like a headache i don't have a stomach ache
i'm a little sluggish but i'm not tired you know what i'm saying it's not i don't i feel
fine i just have a cough and a little irritation in my throat that's it
and hopefully it's been for the last few days i have to assume that it's going to be
coming across the you know going down the roller coaster here it makes you feel like spider-man
i had to leave the room this morning i was coughing yeah we we both have here's the
kim and i have just been on a seesaw cough seesaw we're sleeping in the same
bed one person will cough really loud and wake the other person up and then that person will
fall back asleep and then the person that woke up then 30 to 40 seconds later coughs really
loud and wakes the other person up and you go back and forth getting awful dog shit sleep while you
cough wake each other up over and over again and this morning i just kind of got up and i was like
i got and i wanted to take some medicine too is kim your mom did you just hear when i said that i
share a bed with kim is we think that statement for a second yeah i have a nightmare and i have
to go sleep with my mommy's bed she's your caretaker she's my girlfriend it's a girlfriend
okay but thank you frody and thank you pika banana for the five bucks uh thank you halo
for the 250 250 thank you for the stream it was fantastic to watch and enjoy hope you feel better
soon the ending was amazing thank you oh hi kiwo i didn't even notice you there hey kiwo and i are
now discord friends don't you guys know listen we're not we finally made discord friends
she was rp character got murdered today oh what no murdered she's dead now that's terrible
she's dead germa dead dead this is dead dead first person that knows what that is gets nothing
but i will clap once nobody this is dead got it seal boots nice work got it only person to get it
it was venom yeah it's from the movie venom now the though these if you haven't seen venom
you're gonna watch venom and you're gonna hear that and go oh shit that could have been me i'm
not going to watch it yes you are i know you're gonna watch it you're gonna be sitting there
you're gonna eat a tub of ice cream one day and it's gonna be hard for you to get up off the
couch you're gonna have your ps4 remote in your hands and you're gonna be on hulu or netflix or
something it's gonna be right there and you're gonna just ah no but you can't get up and you
need to press x over venom i'm gonna go but you guys don't do that what do you mean rude
how many people don't eat like three mcchickens or eat like a shitload of ice cream on the couch
and then they can't move and you just watch like tv for four hours nobody else does that
nobody in this chat has eaten three to four mcchickens in a row and watched tv for four
hours no that was literally me tonight see somebody gets it why mcchickens because that's
i don't know this is kind of what you do you've never had a mcchicken before
mcdonald's gets a lot of shit it's not it's i don't it's not very nice mcdonald's
that chicken come from it's this pink slime they've been murdering you what's wrong with
mcdonald's you're the one who was shitting on mcdonald's well we call that a hypocrite
is what that's called
i made air fried chicken for dinner it's good shit no but i get that oh that sounds actually
really great i want an air fryer are they worth it josh is an air fryer worth it do you have an
air fryer i'm getting one i'm ordering one tonight was an air fryer look it up but look
fast food gets a lot of bad rap but sometimes you just want to just drive down the street
and just pull up hit the brakes and get a bag of gross food and then you and you sit down you
eat it and you're like all right that was great just don't do it every day do it like once every
couple weeks or something and just enjoy it it's not gonna kill you you eating four cheesy gordita
crunches that's very bad for you but it's not if you do that like once a month or once every
couple months four is too much too i don't have that's no problem there just eat in and out
no in and out is i would say at least two or three rungs down the list behind shake shack
that's just i'm sorry i'm speaking with factual data in and out still good but i would if i could
get a shake shack burger is that i would get it over in and out every time shake shack's not as
good as five guys uh no i think it is i still think it is i still think it is i've eaten five
guys a lot i've had it a bunch of times you're on the west coast now oh yeah i'm in las vegas
this is in and out it's fucking everywhere out on the west coast here i've had it since being here
it's just like it's it's all right i don't know i i people this is worse than saying
i i'm gonna say this and people are gonna be really mad this is like saying witcher three is
not game of the year what am i about to say and that's in and out tastes the same to me
as a wendy's dave single i would kind of just rather go to wendy's because at least at wendy's
i can get their spicy chicken nugget get the fuck off my coast re i'm not on a coast actually
i'm landlocked i'm landlocked baby no coast here here i officially hate germa
but in and out is good look if we all liked the same things but i told you the squidward argument
already you want to eat canned bread and everybody loves the same place everybody eats the same food
everybody no i don't want to live in the squidward town what fast food mascot is the best
definitely definitely the king until they like killed him or something they got rid of him i
don't know why the scary king commercials were great where he was just like staring at people
and stuff it was like just so odd they still they still haven't i haven't seen him in a commercial
a long time yeah they killed him off in an episode one of the commercials and one of the
commercials he took like an arrow to the neck or something it was crazy he was wild you guys
remember don't remember that controversy
uh ronald mcdonald i feel like they just buried all these fast food cereal characters i haven't
when was the last ronald mcdonald commercial no they don't do that anymore guys every fast food
commercial is just two cool hip young people oh let me steal a fry oh delicious there's no
fucked up weird cartoon characters anymore the hamburger that doesn't get punched in the face
they tried here you go ready fast food commercials now are chilies and fridays commercials from 10
years ago look at all these people having like a great time they're sitting around dining in at
mcdonald's look at they're all smiling clinking glasses taking a big sip out of their drink nobody
gives a fuck no bring us our weird demented twisted cartoon characters they're all switch
commercials now and frankly i think it's bullshit what psycho goes to burger king to have a good
time i never noticed that they killed off a lot of the cartoon mascots till now yeah they did
uh you can say you can say what you want about kfc but at least kfc still has the
kernel in these commercials it's finger looking good my five dollar fill-up box is worth uh it's
waiting gold they still do that kfc sucks no it doesn't well then i'll level with you here
every other kfc sucks because sometimes you go to kfc and get a five star quality crispy delicious
uh perfect meal and then you go to the one down the street and it's like a lunch lady put pig
slop on your plate there is no in between kfc is either terrible terrible zero out of zero out of
five or perfect if they were more consistent i would eat there more often but they're just not
Popeyes is a lot better i've actually never had Popeyes i gotta change that
yeah i've never had it do they have Popeyes in vegas i don't know i think so order it right now
it's based off of the popular cartoon character of the same name
well wouldn't they serve spinach there Popeye didn't eat chicken he ate spinach it wasn't like
biting into like a big crispy chicken leg no he squeezed the
he squeezed the can as hard as he could and it shot out of the top
that marketing worked by the way i used to want to eat spinach so bad because
it looked so good when he ate it i was i didn't eat vegetables i hated them
it was very difficult for my parents to give me food that wasn't captain crunch
or like mac and cheese and a hot dog but holy shit that like propaganda campaign that they ran
for spinach worked on me bugs bunny eating carrots it worked i wanted carrots too am i
gonna go to pax east i am not i am currently not in the area i am on the west land walk
now am i gonna go to evo probably i think so evo seems really cool am i gonna go to anime expo i
no i don't think so but derma lied about minecraft vr thanks to the 250 you did lie you didn't even
drink any cider well i didn't lie about minecraft vr i just didn't do an action in minecraft vr that
you wanted me to do i didn't lie i did the thing by the way here tonight's subs and resubs thanks
everybody a lot of community subs now i want kfc really but am i am i really gonna go fucking flip
a coin right now because i'll tell you if i don't like it and i think it's gross and it's a zero
out of 10 experience like it could be 50 percent of the time i'm gonna be really upset let me look
and see if there's a pup eyes that sounds pretty good let me see if there's one they have pup eyes
in vegas oh damn okay the kfc fries suck um hold on kiwo have you ever gone ever again that might
be a 50 percentile case there did you go twice okay all right okay but you flip a coin it's
gonna be heads twice yeah the wedges aren't gross fuck what wedges i don't know i don't get that
who wants to eat potato wedges no i want fries they're just so mealy and the skin on the outside
it's just it's like stuck on your front teeth it's you know here i'm gonna ruin potato wedges
for every single person here are you ready for this no one's gonna eat one ever again
you know the reese's wrapper have you ever put the reese's wrapper the thing that's actually
around the cup in your mouth if the answer is yes that is the same texture the same consistency
and the same mouth feel as the skin on a potato wedge i ruined it for you disgusting right you'll
never eat it again it's just it's like reese's wrappers in your mouth it's like eating the reese
cup imagine if the reese cup was not chocolate and peanut butter it was potato and a little
crispy on the outside you're just eating you're eating you know what i was about to say
your taste buds suck well that's funny because i was i had a taste bud test you know some people
do like a dna test to find out like oh what's you know my where where where where am i from
you know like no i did a taste bud test i have 214 trillion that's the t for those of you
that's with a t taste buds and i have way more of a savory palette than i do with a sweet palette i
have like two point like 200 and something like 2.8 billion on sweet and like 200 billion for
savory weird taste but okay weird flex yeah flex i don't know whatever but hey thank you bingo
sunshine for the five dollars germa go on doughboy podcast um mitch is a boston boy i don't know what
that is i don't know who that is boston sounds cool boston's a great place he uses all the
taste buds to eat s i can't believe i read that how am i gonna read it wow i can't believe i've
read that jesus why you guys what's with you guys all those taste buds you couldn't tell cheese it's
from cheese nips i actually that joke got so ruined because i really couldn't tell which
was which with my eyes closed and i was so desperately trying and i fucked it all up
that's okay oh bw well he read it bw well all right guys that's it that's my time i'll see
tomorrow more secure i'm gonna go try to track down some chicken i thought you fucking up
fucking it up with script no precisely one hour of bit reading yeah i think it's more streamlined
since the change it's been somewhere between like 30 like 40 plus minutes rather than like
two to three hours sometimes you know well i that's an over exaggeration it never took like three
hours but it's definitely taken about an hour off the time at the end so the last few streams have
been about 30 minutes two hours has happened three hours maybe maybe it's only happened once
yeah it's only like 10 30 here in vegas i started really early i started at like one
o'clock two o'clock something but thank you for joining me sakiro is amazing it's incredibly
frustrating but that's the nature of beast i'm having a blast with it see you tomorrow for more
take care guys see you soon