Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. Sniper up there is gonna see better days. Get him! Oh! Was that like somebody else up there? Oh, there's a soldier up here too.
Playing as the Demoman on Gold Rush with the Default Grenade Launcher. Taking me a lot longer than usual to say these things. Just trying to get some compressing fire, compressing fire, suppressing fire.
A lot of people up there. A lot of people up there. But yeah, you are real. The strange Sticky Bomb Launcher, the Grenade Launcher, and the Hafts of Toichi. There we go.
People, a lot of people. Whoa! That guy flew in the air like 5,000 feet. Come on! Come on! Oh, good thing I didn't pull it out all the way.
Oh, I, in a lot of my videos when I use the Hafts of Toichi, people say, okay, hold on, how to smash a scout in the face. People are always asking, how can you pull the Hafts of Toichi out like this and not be able to go back?
Like for instance, I just switch back right to the Sticky Bomb Launcher. If you do not let it get to the end of its animation like that, you can still use your other weapons. But if you go all the way like that, now I cannot switch back.
But a lot of people have been asking that in the recent videos of Devilman at least. Now I pulled it out and I got to kill somebody. So who am I going to hit? Hello. I am not a spy. I promise you that much. Give me the health. Give me the health. Give me the health. Oh, it worked.
Oh, going to eat my Clementine. I love Clementine so much. They're so orangey and delicious. Going to eat this Clementine on camera because I'm hungry and this is becoming way more difficult than it needs to be.
Look at what I've done to this thing. In like the five seconds I've been trying to open it, like the ten seconds. Look at this. I can't eat that. Oh, bumping the mic. All right, hold on. They're like pushing the cop right now. I can't sit there and eat oranges. You are maybe a spy.
No, no, don't let him get it. It's all the oranges fault. It's all Clementine's fault. I'll kill this guy at least. Don't let him get it. Do everything you can. I blame the orange. I can't believe that just happened.
I'm sitting there eating fruits and vegetables. There's no vegetables here, but I can't open this. I cannot eat this. All right, let's just time travel and I'm going to eat that and go. All right, we've time traveled successfully to the beginning of the match and I got a sticky trap laid down here. Who is going to get their face absolutely exploded?
Hopefully it's you and it's going to be the sniper. Here we go. Bye. Let's do it again. Let's do it again. Any more unsuspecting people? Let's go on this side now. They're going to be weary of me being there. Weary, weary. Hey, hey. Oh, oh, this is going to be crazy.
How did that heavy not die? How is this heavy a superhuman? What the hell? Dude, that heavy took like 7,000 damage. Oh, I'm so scared. Gotta take those hits. Got him. Did I kill that pyro? Who the hell did I even just kill right there? Oh my goodness. Whoa. Whoa. Oh, that's a double cheeseburger right there. Getting lucky.
We got, we got Soldier. Soldier, you want to get on that cot? I don't think that's a good idea. Oh, this heavy is, this heavy is buttered toast right here. You ready for this? Hide in the window. In that window. I love just sitting in this window. It's just like such a bastard move. All right, I'm getting out of here. Anybody else? What just happened with that? Oh, give me health. Spy. Oh, this guy's going to kill me. Oh, good shot. I would say your name on camera, but
I'm not going to. Rumpelstiltskin. Wow, did those two guys, I love that heavy's mask. That heavy's mask was hilarious. He's just lying there like dead on the corner with the stupid seal mask on. God, I love Halloween so much. So much goofy s-h-i-double-h-i-h-i-t. It's so much fun. What's going on here, man? What's going on here? Hey, scout. Get face stabbed. I almost killed myself with my own bombs. Damn it. Oh, by the way, if
you're wondering, I didn't eat the clementine. Oh, boy. I have no space in my backpack. I need to buy, a lot of people are saying I need to buy one of those backpack expanders. I'm definitely going to do that. And you may or may not sometime soon here see a backpack giveaway.
Could happen. Just saying. It could happen in the next couple of weeks, probably. I would think so. Hey, look, it's a fish. Ah! No, don't snipe me, you son of a bitch. Get him with that. How did I not direct you?
You know, I'm going up there. I'm going up top, man. And you're getting smashed. Oh, so much stuff is about to be destroyed up here. Where's the teleporter? I know it's up here. Definitely right here. No. Where the hell is it? Oh, it's right there. Your teleporter is about to be down. And I apparently killed. Oh, my goodness. God gracious. Look what I just did. He was coming through the teleporter with his sentry gun. That engineer. Oh, now I feel pretty bad. Because if that was me, I'd be very upset about that. Come on. Come on. Lay in trap.
How did I get all the way back here? It is beyond me. I got to kill somebody with the sword. Get my health back. Or just be like a complete nuisance. That works, too. Come on. Come around the corner. Come around the corner. Oh, they're going to cap this and we're going to lose. I got to get up. I'm so scared of something from behind. Here we go. This is where I'm going to kill like three people right here with the sword. Come on. Come here. Come here, you. One is one. Let's get three. Let's get this sniper, too.
No, it's heavy. Oh, heavy had to ruin my fun. I think they're actually going to win, though. That's the bad part. Maybe. Maybe. Should I stay demo? Yeah, there's only one. I'm going to stay demo. I'm staying demo, man. Come on. We've got a sentry gun. We're good. I think we got this. Got two sentry guns. Oh, my goodness. That's his crit. That's going to hit somebody. Whoa, I'm going to die. Dispenser, dispenser, dispenser. There is no dispenser. Come on. They're going to come around the corner. I need health. I need to put more stickies than one.
This is what I need to do. Here we go. Get that dispenser built, baby. Get these stickies up all over the place, all over the place.
I'm not confident right now. All it's going to take is an Uber charge and they will push in big time. No, get that scout. That guy's standing completely still.
No. Oh, good shot. Good shot.
Orange pieces all over my desk. If they get an Uber, this is going to be a big problem.
I killed plenty of problems. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. No. Oh, well. But that's going to wrap it up, guys.
Thank you so much for watching this edition of Facecam Fortress 2. And I'm going to try to actually eat this.
I tried before. You know what? Screw it. That was disgusting because there's seeds in this.
I didn't know there were seeds. So that was just really, really an unexpected texture.
But that's going to wrap up the video, guys. I'll see you all soon. Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching again. And I'll see you all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.