What's happening? What's up? We're playing Phasmophobia with some people.
Got a coffee here. I'm ready to go. Vod real? That's right.
Do the Luddie. All right. I'll listen.
I'm going to be doing VR because of the Among Us VR is coming out.
When I do, I will do the Luddie during when I do full cam.
OK. And it's going to be sick.
Going to be one of the best you've probably ever seen.
I'm just going to make that very clear.
Yeah. So today we're playing. I didn't tweet. Oh, shit.
We are playing Phasmophobia.
Then at dead of night.
Then maybe stay out of the house.
Nice to finally join us, dude.
Why were you here late?
Why are you talking? Why are you saying it like that?
Why are you saying it like that?
I know my I know my I know I have the radio voice today.
I know that every single stream, it seems, over the last five years.
I start out with the radio voice.
And then it slowly goes from this to this over the course of about seven hours.
I'm getting old. And that's just the way it is.
All right. Are we ready?
Are we good? Dinner is cold.
You change your pinned tweet.
Yeah. All right.
OK. Can I can I can all the social media managers of the channel
just relax for a few minutes to change your pinned tweet?
All right. All right. All right. All right. OK.
Uh, I'm I'm going to tweet a regular tweet right now as
asmophobic. How do you spell asmophobia?
Can somebody spell it?
Is it phasmophobia or phasmophobia?
It's like phasmophobia.
So it's phasmo. OK.
Asmophobia, let's go.
Let's get it. I like let's get it.
It's better. How about phasmophobia and other scary things?
Let's get it. Yeah, that's perfect.
Hope you guys are having a good day.
And OK, I hope you guys are having a good day.
Let me just say words.
Well, I write the tweet. There it is.
All right. Here we go.
I wonder if everybody's ready.
I guess I don't even know how to play phasmophobia.
I'm a level one.
I played it like a year and a half ago.
OK, check in and see how we're doing.
Fuck, I forgot I was muted for them, but not for you guys.
How we how we doing?
How do you guys feel good?
My stream is running.
We're ready to rock and roll whenever I am.
Can you guys hear me? Yep.
All right. I'm back. Hello.
If I show the screen, there's nothing on the screen
that's not going to like leak the game code or anything, right?
No, it's hidden up top, right?
Well, cool. Yeah, game code.
They actually implemented that.
OK. So, yeah, once again, everybody, I have with me
Jerma Ross and Liam Triforce and also a basketball guest.
How do I walk a guest basketball jack-o-lanterns?
How do I leave this this board space?
I think. Oh, thank you.
All right. Yeah, there you go.
Who the hell is Jerma?
He's a famous streamer.
Now, now, now streamed to once or twice.
I watch now.
I mean, go watch my Anubis tutorial smite video.
That's what I'm known for.
That one.
All right. I got to make it so it's not pushed to talk
because I'm going to I'm going to scream something at you guys
and you're just not going to hear it.
OK. Just for the record, everyone watching, Liam and I are in VR.
Ross and Jerma are on desktop.
Yeah. Our experiences will be different.
If you want to watch Jerma's perspective,
you can go to his channel as well.
I can't tell which is which.
It's so funny hearing the different in each ear
because it's the positional audio that's funny.
Throw a football.
All right. Is this is this better?
Can you guys hear me?
Yeah, it's a good Halloween game.
Oh, well, you can keep the basketball on you if you need it.
Like I just have it on my belt now.
Save it for later. Throw it at the ghost.
How do I turn some people saying that everyone were all loud, apparently?
Loud.
Is it was at the menu screen?
Is there a way I can drop people's levels in here, a tab or something?
The menu screen here, you can turn it.
Oh, right. OK, right, right, right.
Oh, OK.
Chad, everyone's good on my end, right?
Like they sound like human, like human with good volume.
I think that's probably a little better.
How's my volume? I'm OK. Yeah, everyone's good.
I think everybody sounds all right now.
But yeah, they did a pretty good job with the lobby.
You can see the spooky bats up there.
There's jack-o'-lanterns. There's done.
I just left the fucking game.
Fuck. OK, hold on.
I I thought it was like a leave.
They're going to be pissed. Hold on.
Give. We're about to start to.
OK, join game.
I don't want to show this or walk over and like place it in.
OK, so leave is not leave is OK.
Hey, I'll be the judge of that.
I'll have to. I'll be on the corn hall committee.
I accidentally press leave game instead of leave the menu.
I would love to hear a committee.
All right. So this game is pretty dark.
I don't know where we're going. How do we get out of here?
Oh, my Jesus Christ. That was scary.
I didn't even see that.
If Chris Martin from Coldplay shocked you on some steps,
I'd be scared, too. Yes.
You know, I can barely see. Is there like a brightness?
I do. There are lights on in this room and I can't see anybody.
It's so dark.
Yeah, it's really dark.
Flashlight, I think that we can use it is
tea tea.
Let's try that. That's so much better.
I just went into brightness and just turned it up.
OK, I might do that.
I'll do. So, Chad, it's been like,
I guess over a year since I've played this, so it's been updated quite a bit.
There's like a there's like a mental asylum.
Like, Liam, you played this a lot.
Do you know how to, like, go to the asylum?
Yeah. When you select a mission, you'll be able to pick the asylum.
As long as it's available, I'm pretty sure it says it's locked.
Oh, damn. I guess we got to play the other missions then.
Would you be able to make a map like a server and like select it?
Or is it just because we're all underleveled?
Yeah, we're all pretty good, like zero.
I probably don't have it whenever I have levels.
I just piggyback off of my friends to get the new levels
because they'd always be like sitting here or something.
Um, well, we could go to the farmhouse.
I don't think we've seen this one.
I have no info. I don't know where anybody is.
Oh, wait. Yeah.
Oh, hang on. Let me see if I can find the asylum.
I think I can pick it.
Oh, really? What's it called?
Sunny Meadows?
Maybe we don't want to start at the asylum anyway, because we're all rotten at this.
Yeah. So we'll figure that out.
Let's try this Bleasdale farmhouse and we'll bust some ghosts.
Yeah. OK. I think, yeah, we can vote for the asylum whenever we're ready.
Oh, OK. So ready up. Ready up.
OK. And what about equipment?
Do we want to bring equipment?
Yeah, we don't have a crucifix candle,
motion sensor, salt, sanity pills.
We're going to need those. I'm going to bring a lighter.
OK. Why are you guys all like hunched over?
I don't know. I'm not hunched over.
No, this is just my normal posture.
Oh, well, everybody's everybody's leaning forward.
I'm an osteoporobro. Oh, my God.
We got some stuff like the way you guys were standing is the way that I guarantee
a side profile candid picture of me sitting on the couch with a remote control.
The TV is that's exactly what it looks like.
It's like that. Like, yeah.
Yeah, this that that is the exact pose, like the neck forward shoulders rolled.
All right, everyone, I think we're ready to bust some ghosts.
All right. You guys are going to have to hard carry.
I have no idea what the fuck's going on.
And we don't get Ghostbusters equipment like that last game we played.
Oh, no. We only play games together.
Jerma and I in particular, if it's ghost busting related.
I know it has to be ghost related.
It just started happening this way.
OK. Oh, yeah. We don't have any sanity pills.
We might need those. Oh, yeah.
Oh, am I not ready? Vdub left some at my house.
Hang on. Yeah.
Oh, there we go.
No, now you're unready school.
Yeah, you double click.
I got confused. All right.
We got some sanity pills now.
OK, we have at least one.
Oh, we're going. Oh, OK.
Guys, there's a skeleton in here already.
Hey, let me investigate.
Oh, yeah. There's a little bit of meat on the bone if anyone's hungry.
Gross. No, I'm not.
I'm not wearing a Halloween mask.
Stop fucking saying it.
I put it in the title.
People keep asking me this.
It's like just getting annoying.
Like, dude, why do you have a Halloween mask on?
No. Look, whatever.
Trying to. Why am I already at 99 percent sanity?
Ninety eight percent. What?
Oh, I just. Oh, I looked at the skeleton.
Oh, yeah, that must be it.
All right. So we tell the ghost with a smudge stick while it's chasing someone.
Well, I hope we have a smudge stick. Hold on.
Um, it changed a lot of stuff.
We've got a lightsaber, a camera.
How do you open the inventory?
Well, there's the book on your your belt.
You can open to see your items.
You got a big hand.
How do I pick up a flashlight?
Oh, there we go.
So, hey, Liam, do you remember how to do radio communication?
I think it should be your shoulder.
Oh, wait, there's a radio now for an update.
They added a little radio.
And if you hold it, you talk over the comms. Oh.
Try to take the camera.
Oh, how do you how do you do that?
On the utility belt, you take out the little walkie talkie
and just hold whatever button it's mapped to.
I don't know on keyboard.
V. Is it V?
Hello. Hello. How do I open the belt?
Utility belt to the belt is trying some buttons right now.
Oh, OK. If we're going to do this, we need smudge sticks.
And I don't think we have any.
So we're just going to have to try and identify the ghost
based on what we can see.
OK. And then head on out.
Yeah. All right. All right. All right.
OK. Well, it's not being a pressure.
OK. OK.
Like, if I just use the flashlight, wouldn't it?
Hold B. I'm holding B. It's not doing it.
OK. How do I access the belt?
Did we bring did we bring an EMF detector?
That's Spirit Box.
Oh, boy.
We did bring a camera. That's good.
So we can set that up somewhere and look for ghost orbs
where the thing may be.
But if we don't have an EMF, that might be tricky.
I got the camera right here.
You take pictures and the ghost shows up by the thing you scream, right?
Yeah. OK.
I'll burn her up.
It's really windy.
It's Vinnie.
It sounds like you're like in a call with me, like on my desk speaker.
Like, oh, man, we couldn't get Discord to work.
It's all right, Vinnie.
You can come through like on my on my my iPhone or the speaker.
Oh, piano. Let's play it. OK.
Jesus, what the fuck?
That was you did that, right?
Wait, was a ghost doing that? OK.
Well, you guys got to play something.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that's sad. I wish I could do that.
Wait, can I?
Wait, we just tap it when we're down.
Oh, oh, gosh, you have to deal with whatever song the game gives you.
Boy, I left the camera here.
All right. Who's going to work?
Who's coming upstairs with me?
Where we off to? Where we going?
We can hit the attic.
See if there's a check the attic.
Any spooky phenomenon?
We are doing this so wrong, man.
Like I should be all the way back.
I should be like key light.
You should be focused light. You know what I mean?
I don't like this.
Oh, I just love. OK, you are.
OK, I found a brush.
Does that matter?
I don't I don't think so.
We do have like a book we could put down.
Oh, I could take a picture.
Right. I do have a book.
We should put it right here. OK.
Yeah. Put it there and see if the demon like writes in it.
OK. Then we can point a camera at it.
Do we need to open it?
I don't know. I got a camera here. Oops.
Oh, I really have no idea.
We're just like, I'm just making this up as I go along.
All right. Hold on. Take it.
OK. Beautiful.
How many photos can you take?
Get my good side.
No, you didn't.
How do I press? Oh, OK.
There we go. OK. I put the put it down.
It's open on the on the table.
All right. Now we've got to wait for it to.
Maybe it'll write on it, I guess.
We can come check on it later and just go downstairs.
Yeah, that works.
Doesn't this game listen to your microphone, too?
Yeah. If you like, learn its name and say, suck my balls, suck my balls.
Oh, OK. Oh, hey, what's up, man?
Hey, did you know?
Wait, you have a camcorder?
Yeah. The lens cap is on.
All right. So I was that somebody was a shadow.
I don't know. OK.
Something just flew. Something just flew by.
Something just flew by me.
Well, I saw something like a book just flew from right to left.
I swear. Oh, well, you think it was the book you left upstairs?
I don't know.
Lame. Oh, I'm getting chills.
Wait, where is he? Is he is he is he at like 7-Eleven?
Hey, can you stop?
Can you grab me some flaming hot Cheetos, dude?
Like on your way back?
You gave me flaming hot.
I want the powdered doughnuts.
Get the new lime ones, though.
Those things are fucking sick.
They actually are actually sick.
The new lime flaming hot Cheetos are awesome.
All right. Let's check the book.
Where's the book over here?
Not that I can tell.
It would be pretty obvious.
It draws like pentagrams and shit.
Maybe not up here, then.
Huh? Going to bring it with you?
Oh, yeah. Maybe we'll put it somewhere else.
Maybe because it would have probably done it by now, right?
I imagine you maybe put it down.
Hey, what's up?
All right. I'm putting it over here.
Yeah, maybe.
What's the scariest place in this whole house?
I would have said the attic, but I guess, yeah, we could do downstairs.
Piano's pretty scary.
OK, yeah, my light just like somebody's singing.
OK, yeah, I don't like this at all.
OK, they're coming from that room in there on the left.
I heard that door.
I got a frag grenade going out.
I guess somebody's right here.
Yeah, there's a ghost.
What? Excuse me?
They're strangling Vinny.
What? What just happened?
I killed Vinny.
OK, we're probably going to die next.
What do you think?
Um, I'm going to put the book down on the ground
and then we're going to see almost like a landmine.
Yeah, it'll get distracted and draw pictures.
It'll draw a picture to be like, oh, I have to do this.
I'm a fucking ghost. I have to draw a pentagram.
Right. That's what's going to happen.
So what even was that?
Yeah, I don't actually know how to open doors and decks.
Desktop. Do you know how to do that?
This is the second time I've ever played this game.
So no, I don't either.
So we're trapped in here.
All right. So we need to figure out how to open a door,
which is probably E, which is probably click.
It's click. Oh, it's left click.
Oh, this toilet's nasty, dude.
Let me see. Oh, are we the only two people left?
I think so. Oh, wait.
We are. When did, um, who?
Yeah. When? When did that happen?
This ghost is aggressive.
Should we just leave and just go?
Yeah, I know. Close that door.
You scared you. Oh, God.
You scared me just then because you walked through me.
I saw your teeth.
It's already singing right now.
Oh, for fuck, dude.
I feel like we're playing Left 4 Dead.
And like this is the oh, the good idea.
Let's go in the bathroom and aim our shotguns out the door.
It never works. It always feels like it should, though.
I'm not scared, by the way, just so you know.
I'm going to hide it. OK, I'm going to crouch.
I'm going to also crouch.
I think it's out there.
Do we want to go try to get back to the trailer and see if we can guess?
I think well, we know it's the singing one.
What does that matter?
That's all the like the information I made.
Are we locked in here?
I do. We actually did that.
You're joking.
Can we actually knock it out of here?
I'll try the window.
The window doesn't work.
What did you do with that?
No, I just tried to open it.
Wait, you let the ghost in, didn't you?
I might have. I don't know.
It's possible.
I'm sweating. I'm sweating.
I mean, no, I'm not. I'm brave. Let's go.
Let's just leave. This place is bad.
Oh, wait, hold on. Actually, let's check the book.
Wait, the book actually might have something in it.
No, it's got nothing. Oh, come on. Really?
Yeah. Oh, well.
OK, let's try to guess.
This is a warm up around anyways.
It's the the the the singing
singing specter.
OK, yeah, they're down here.
They can't get up there.
Yeah, you're in.
Um, I think they're I don't know.
It got me. It got me.
It got you. It did.
Give me stuff.
Do you have any items?
Hey, this is why is this locked?
I'm getting the fuck out of this house.
I'm the one that got to stay alive.
And by the way, you're the singing specter with the car.
All right. It's the singing.
All right.
She's choking people.
All right. I think I got it.
How do I how do I guess?
It's open your journal. OK.
Um, ghosts, it's the.
Oh, my God, there's so many.
What's the one that sings?
They're probably just like, dude, just just just fucking just get out of the game.
Go to evidence.
OK, all right, right, right.
The ghost, I believe, is a we heard singing.
It was very cold.
There was a music.
I think it was a bay.
No, I'm going to say it's just a gym.
I'm going to say demon and that's it.
Right. A demon.
I don't know, guys, I don't know how any of this works.
I'm going to say demon and and just call it.
How do I how do I say yes?
Go to the truck door. OK.
We do it.
Oh, did we win?
It was a revenant.
It was what you what you guess.
I guess demon.
OK, German, can you hear me? Revenant.
Yeah. German, apparently you couldn't hear me in game because my
like you had me too low.
I did. I was talking, but people were saying I wasn't audible.
But they're OK.
You were coming through the walkie talkie for a little while.
I think it was a glitch.
I don't know. I can hear you now.
We're yeah, I think it's a glitch now.
Also, Liam got booted before we started.
So the one dude knew how to play the game was booted.
That's so funny.
We were trying to figure out my book.
Oh, by the way, I'm back now. Finally.
I. OK, I opened my book.
I was looking at the evidence and my game just kicked me to the main menu
for no reason.
I guess it was a connection, according to Vinnie's chat.
But I have been cool.
I'm surprised at least one of us made it out of there.
I don't know how.
I'm going to add all like as much equipment as I can get.
OK, so we have we're just going to all walk behind you saved up.
Yeah, I'm trying to navigate this new menu, though.
I'm not used to it.
I'm telling you, we should just there should be three people with flashlights
in a triangle pattern, all pointing in the direction that he is facing.
Yeah, we should.
We should just be your studio lighting for you to go around and find stuff.
OK, candle by that.
Let me just get set up real quick.
I do the same level.
Yeah, I'm going to add a lighter.
Just going to just keep adding lighters.
OK, we got two.
So we're good.
Motion sensor, hairball, microphone.
What's all this stuff?
I get some there's some jiggling happening.
That's the stuff we're buying right now.
Somebody said gamer neck.
Hmm. So Vinnie, how are you using the walkie talkie?
What is it?
Are you holding what you did?
You have to physically pick up the walkie talkie to talk into it.
Yeah. Oh, like this.
And then I have to do this because I would do.
Do we how do we have those as non VR?
Yeah, yeah, we do.
I think you hit Q or maybe we have to hit B or V because I was hitting B or V
and it was making like a noise, you know, noise maybe.
So it's just we have to.
Oh, I thought that holding B was voice chat.
But OK, I get it.
I get it. Green on one side, red on the other.
That's like you got to do RGB lighting if you if you're like an epic
Call of Duty gamer on YouTube.
OK, there we go.
OK, so now you're lit properly.
Speaking of light, do we need any more lighters?
I'm getting as much equipment as I possibly can.
We're if we're using smudge sticks, we're probably going to need
at least one per person.
OK. OK. Yeah.
I VDub left a couple smudge sticks here last night, so I'm I'm down for that.
Wait, candle.
How much money do I have?
Um, you can see it over here on this monitor.
You can see it in the top right.
How much money you have?
Oh, I got 25 bucks.
Do I get a lighter?
I'll get a
can of whipped cream.
Yeah, there's is that whipped cream?
Is that whip? It's I don't know.
I don't have it's ghost assault.
Hey, it's OK.
Guys, I brought two lighters motion sensor.
OK, there we go.
We are now all around to to to detect when ghosts like are near us.
You have one of those.
Yeah, math. Yeah, we've added one.
OK, that's good.
We add another.
I think with what we have, we'll be all right.
We've got everything.
I'm voting for 10 Ridgeview Court, so sure.
We're writing up.
Sure. Sick.
All right. Hopefully I don't disconnect this time.
We definitely need we definitely need you.
We need your expertise.
Amen has money.
We're all here.
Perfect.
Oh, I really, really hope I don't get disconnected this time.
And if I do, good luck.
Is this wacky device?
Well, I think that's all the whipped cream sound.
Yeah, I think it's a parabolic microphone.
Ah, hey, hey, guys.
Oh, I love whipped cream.
That joke was awful.
That was not even funny.
I don't have it today.
If I ever had it, I certainly don't have it today either.
I just I just we have to understand something.
I just did the look at I'm turning the thing upside down
and eating it at like three o'clock in the morning out of the fridge.
That was the humor there.
Oh, OK, that's cool.
OK, so we should probably spread our equipment
thin here based on what we have.
Like, no, we shouldn't have like four EMFs like divided between us.
We only need like three.
We need to get the ghost to blow out a candle,
prevent the ghost from hunting with a crucifix
and clear the area near the ghost using smudge sticks.
So I'll bring the crucifix of just a crease through.
I just played faith.
So I know how to do this.
You just hold it up, is that?
Yeah, basically, if it's hacking, you just like do this.
Yeah. The power of Christ compelled.
OK, exactly. I think so.
It is actually prayer.
I mean, like I've never it's it's 50 50.
OK, so we don't have to actually recite the Lord.
Like when I went to school, they taught me our father.
Should I say that if that makes you more comfortable?
I think you should do it. All right.
All right. I'll set up a camera and tripod.
Yeah. Yeah, we should.
We actually should just take a bring a candle.
Oh, I need a lighter. Yeah.
How much can we bring in this new utility belt?
Like the area looks like three items, right?
Yeah, I've got pretty sure three.
Yeah, I have my flashlight and some think flashlights
probably really important.
Oh, you're going to need that.
You can do three.
I think it's three items.
You could. Yeah, on keyboard.
You're you don't have the hands, so they have to accommodate.
Oh, your mouse wheel to go between them.
OK. Oh, my God.
Is this going to be OK?
Why am I taking a lighter when I could take a flashlight?
That seems like you can probably.
The lighter is probably going to just be for the concert.
I'm definitely taking a flashlight these days.
So who you have crucifix who brought is anybody have smudge stick?
I have a I have a smudge stick.
German, if you have the lighter, definitely bring a smudge stick.
Oh, yeah, 100 percent. You're good.
OK. All right. So I should drop the lighter then and get something else.
I'll bring maybe bring bring the book or the blacklight.
So that way we can see if there's any like nocturnal emissions in the bedroom.
You guys you guys have EMFs, right?
Do I need this?
Uh, some ghostly goo.
I have flashlight, lighter and smudge stick.
Yeah. Did any I don't think anybody else has an EMF.
So take that. OK.
I'll take a spirit box.
And OK, my hands are full, but I mean,
you're walking in with like you can just juggle as you go.
Yeah, I think that's what I'm going to do.
You are right now the infomercial where it's trying to show you a product
that includes everything that's on your belt and holding it.
And you're like dropping shit in black and white. Yeah.
Like, why would you carry all this stuff?
Is this you can set that up here?
No, no, no. I just need to turn my flashlight.
We need to once we find the room, it's in.
Then we set it up.
Where is it snowing from?
Is this ghost snow?
Because it's like clear night and snow.
Maybe it's like ash.
The earth's like Silent Hill. Yeah. Yeah.
Like it's just coal fires burning under the town for 50 years.
That's that's earth door right now.
Shit, my flashlight.
That's not the moon. That's fucking earth.
Wait, wait, wait, what?
That looks like earth, man.
That doesn't look like the moon.
This shit's blue.
How did you bend that way?
Like broke your spine.
Oh, my goodness.
Permanent. Permanent.
OK, not having a flashlight kind of sucks.
Permanent spine damage.
All right.
All right. I hear something already.
That's the spirit box germ.
It's OK. OK, good.
OK, I've got the the camera set up over here
and I got the cross in case any demons wish to attempt.
All right. Should I light the smudge stick damage?
No, no, not yet.
We need to know where it is first.
OK, it's not in this room.
I'm not getting anything.
Give us a sign. I'll be right back.
I'm going to go get some more equipment.
Why would we be why are we doing this?
What is your name? Give us a sign.
Uh, let me go over here.
Well, I should probably now.
I'm not going to break up.
I'm going to stick here.
Where's Vinnie going?
Uh, probably to get get an item.
Vinnie, where are you at?
OK. Vinnie, you good?
No, I'm fine. I'm just grabbing some Crystal Head vodka.
Oh, we thought you were dead.
Oh, oh, OK, cool, cool, cool.
30 seconds before a ghost appears.
That's what it says here on the time.
Oh, let's we should put something down then.
Yeah, I've got the book.
Do you want to put down the book?
Yeah. Where should we put the book?
In any any particular location you like?
Hello?
OK, I'm coming.
You're stuck at a wall.
Oh, the way you said that, you were like,
it sounded like you were trapped in the wall
and you didn't know how you got there.
Give me a sign.
We need to put the book down somewhere,
somewhere that's scary enough.
Yeah, I do.
It says it's blue, it's blue.
So there's nothing?
OK, there's nothing, there's nothing.
All right, let's my hands are full.
You're going to have to open the door.
What did I saw a thing here?
What? 5.9, 6.2, 6.2.
It's all good here.
What's the clock say?
I'm holding the thing that except sound that I'm getting decibels.
I don't know what's happening.
It's midnight.
I don't I don't know what that means, but I'll follow you.
Oh, that's actually really good.
This one, uh, give us a sign.
Give us a sign.
You're the piano man.
It's probably where you were, Vinny, if you're getting a reading there.
It's probably in that hallway.
We can do can you speak?
And let's let's make sure that it's not just you speaking.
OK. Hello.
I'm a ghost hunter.
Hello.
Creepy ghosts.
You got a five dB voice, apparently.
Oh, I'm quiet.
My friends tell me otherwise.
It's so funny because honest to God, all four of us don't need to be here doing this.
Like, like two of us could do this, right?
Right. We could split up into like scuba groups.
You know, like, yeah, yeah.
We're just blocking the hallway for each other.
That's so funny.
There's I don't think there's anything here.
Never mind. Like, let's let's be honest.
What am I doing?
What is my job right now?
You're holding the flashlight.
Yeah, you are Ross's lifeline right now.
Yeah. Without you, I can't see.
That says nothing in there.
Well, I think it's probably downstairs.
Oh, we didn't check this room yet.
It's got to be downstairs.
I can't open it because I have a ghost.
Fellas, don't worry.
I can get the door.
Thanks, Jerma.
Are we in the bathroom, ghost?
Are we in the bathroom?
No, it's still blue.
Still blue.
74 dB.
Yeah, the EMF is still reading absolutely nothing.
How?
I guess it's downstairs.
I guess it's downstairs. Yeah.
I mean, there is a isn't this house have a basement or?
It might actually.
Yeah. I might think of the first one.
What is that? What is that?
What happened?
You're good.
Something happened.
No, no, I.
I.
Nothing.
Spider land on you.
It was itchy. I thought it was a fucking centipede.
Spider.
Centipede.
I'm all right.
Once we know where it is, we can use the salt.
Imagine being in VR and having a centipede climb on your neck.
You just click when it's active, but don't use it just yet.
And I was like, you know, I was going like this behind the pillow.
And then I was like, what is that? This feels fuzzy.
And it was a house centipede on my hand.
Oh, my God.
It was the worst and it was huge.
It was the size of like three quarters.
Is it weird that I would rather have Jason fucking chase me through a house
than have that experience where you just had.
What would you rather?
I would rather be chased in a house with Jason behind me
than have a centipede around my neck in bed.
You see how disgusting how centipedes are.
They're like the worst.
There's a pentagram in here.
So I think we're close.
No, it's normal.
Is it normal?
Yeah, I don't. I don't think I recognize that from the last update.
No, on Zillow, they showed the pentagram.
It was fine. Oh, I see.
OK. Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, your ghost. Hello.
How old are you?
What is your name?
What is your name, ghost?
And I'm just waiting for the
Oh, did you close that door?
What the fuck was that?
Sound like a door opening.
Something.
Guys, shh, shh, smoke stick activated coming out.
Fifteen, twenty DB.
Smoke stick activated.
Fifty two DB.
Where's the cross?
In the name of the Lord, Savior, Christ.
I can fuck.
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
As it is in heaven.
Give us this hallowed.
Is a ghost laughing or somebody else laughing?
And I'm sorry, I'm just I'm laughing.
Oh, that was a ghost laugh.
That was me all along.
You were like just close enough to my left ear where it was like
you were inside of my left ear.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, OK.
Um, it's not down here.
It's upstairs. Yeah, it went back up.
Yeah, I don't like this one.
Here is our home.
Oh, what?
Do I sprint in there? No, no, no.
You will. You might die if you do that.
Oh, this one's like scurrying around.
I'm going back.
Oh, you're done.
Well, I guess the crucifix didn't work.
German, where are you?
Oh, shit. I have to go find you. Where are you?
Are you down in the basement?
Well, that's a great question.
I got you. I got you.
Is that you? Is that you? Is that you?
Guys. Holy shit, dude.
Um, it yanked my flashlight out of my hand.
What? Did it get Vinny?
It got Vinny. He's dead, I think.
Oh, look, there's his head.
I saw him on the floor.
I was like, we should probably go back to the house.
The spirit box is useless.
How do you open it? Oh, no, the door just closed.
Oh, thank God.
Did you get level five in the EMF or did you just freak out?
I did. I just panicked and ran.
I couldn't I couldn't see anything.
I do two flashlights.
We can we can regroup here.
Talk about it.
Try to pick that. No, that thing's useless, you said.
OK. Oh, what did he drop it?
So we should I should not pick this thing up.
Grab a flashlight.
I got it. OK.
All right. So what do we know so far?
Did your EMF reach level five at all?
No, it didn't.
At least if it did, I didn't see it.
OK, let me see if the crucifix even helped at all.
No, no, he died.
OK, well, we all have really terrible sanity.
Let's work on that real quick.
Do we take pills or?
Yeah. How many do we have?
Oh, my God, it's bad.
Bill's here. Bill's here.
So we just wait. Shit.
I dropped I dropped the shit.
There we go. And it's just I just.
Yeah. Right.
Click. Did I do it?
I heard the sound. It probably worked.
Yeah. Yeah, it worked.
My hands are sweaty, so I'm dropping shit.
I was so loud.
All right. So we should take more than we take two pills.
Let's hang on just in case.
Yeah. We should ration them out.
Yeah, Vinny didn't get to eat it.
OK, I dropped the pill bottle.
It's on the ground right here.
I'm going to pick it up. I wish I put it.
How do I put something down here?
Give it to me. Oh, you got it. OK.
So what should I take instead?
Because I got a flashlight. That's it.
Did you use the smudge stick yet?
Yeah, I kind of panicked.
And just when we were down in the basement,
I clicked it and it made like a smoke thing.
It didn't work.
So we can you can use another one just in case it attacks again.
OK, I need the candle.
I have no clue what it is.
You did not get level five, correct?
I'm sorry. I didn't see.
I know I didn't see level five.
I just saw the level blue.
OK, we can rule those out then.
Let's check the journal.
Let's try and place it where the ghost might be.
He died in the hallway, right?
Oh, yeah, the door to the basement.
So. OK.
Yeah, we get a video camera set up yet.
Yeah, this one right here in the in the that
we're currently recording the office.
We should probably move that to where Vinny died.
OK, and then I'll place the journal and I have a journal.
Do you want to just place the camera?
Yeah, OK. Plus, you got VR.
You probably better than us.
OK, hit cameras right here.
Cameras right here.
But it was one of you guys lagging.
Wait, no, they're right here.
There's a ghost right here.
There's a ghost. I thought there's a ghost right here.
They're holding a cup.
Yeah, could this be?
I need everyone.
No one's going to believe me if that if I don't see this,
I'm going to look like a fucking weirdo.
I swear to God, this cup was moving.
Oh, he's fucking on this.
Yeah, you can do that when you're a ghost.
It's great. I love it.
I thought one of you were lagging for a second.
Which Vinny's communicating with us.
Liam, is your camera on right now?
Do you want it? Oh, I see a flashlight.
Oh, OK, OK. Yeah, I got it right here.
It's me right here.
OK, you got it. Oh, you found it.
Ross, do you see this floating mug?
Oh, where do you want to move to?
Something's behind it.
Something's loaded behind me right now.
Go somewhere and hide and be quiet.
Hold on. What?
Help. Help me.
Oh, smoke sticks.
Smoke stick.
I didn't get it.
Did it work?
God.
Smoke sticks.
Hi.
We want to get back here.
How you doing? Hey.
Oh, whoa, a ball.
So that was you that was moving the stuff around.
That's funny.
I was moving the coffee mug.
Yeah, I was moving it.
Are you on... Am I muffled when you hear me speak?
Yeah, you are talking through...
You're a very thin wall.
Yeah, exactly. OK.
Yeah, when you're ghost, you just get muffled.
Oh, that's OK.
Well, I can still kind of hear you.
Apparently, we have to go outside to fix that, so...
Roommate voice.
Yeah, that's how I lean over to the wall here and go...
Hey, man, you want anything from McDonald's?
Hey, can you lower your music?
Holy shit.
You just opened up the room to my apartment and did that.
Oh.
You're not muffled anymore.
You just stormed over and opened the door.
Please, I need you to lower the music.
So, where are they now?
Uh, I don't know, actually.
Maybe the basement?
Dude, let's mess with them.
All right, I'm going to grab...
Can we grab knives?
Let me see.
I can grab a fork.
Oh, OK, I got a plate.
All right.
Then we just need to find them.
Can I throw this and hit them with a plate?
I don't know if it'll hit.
I don't know if it'll be like a...
I wonder if it'll break.
Let's see if they're down here.
They're not down here.
Do you see this?
Do you see the lighter just bouncing?
No.
OK, I'm not making this up.
Like, there's a lighter that is just infinitely bouncing on my screen right now.
Somebody else is fucking with us.
Somebody died in the ghost world and now they're able to mess with the ghosts.
I see.
Yeah.
Oh, I think they've lost.
OK.
I imagine you guys lost.
All right.
It was a thay.
Of course.
How could I get that wrong?
How did I think of that?
I got 80 bucks for that.
Oh, good.
Last thing I saw was a lighter covered in repulsion gel.
What?
It was weird.
Yeah, someone, I'm sure, clipped it, but it was very strange.
So this game is scary.
That was good.
Oh, can I buy anything?
No.
Yeah.
If you have money.
Hmm.
Seems that two times of zero is still zero.
If I use the...
So if I use the smoke stick...
Does the smoke stick work?
OK, so if it's like, oh, you're about to get attacked by a ghost.
If I do the smoke stick, then they won't get me.
Is that how it is?
Ah, you know what?
I think we have to know what room it's in.
And then just when we're in the room, we just smudge.
I think that's what we did wrong.
Oh, OK.
Also, the cross have to drop it on the ground.
I was holding it up like a...
You knew that?
The first time I tried to do it, I did that exact same thing.
And you know what?
It didn't work.
So it wasn't 50-50.
I'm just bad.
Got it.
I figured it would work like that.
I mean, you see it in movies all the time.
You hold up the cross.
I know.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Anyway.
Liam, can you vote on the asylum?
Yes.
None of us vote.
I'm assuming it's Sonny Meadows that I'm thinking of.
Chat will have to probably clarify what level it is.
Chat, is it Sonny Meadows?
It is, yeah, confirmed.
Perfect, OK.
I just saw one yes in my chat, and I took that as objective truth.
So, it's for me.
Do we have a thermometer?
We're probably going to need that.
We have a ther-pop-eter.
Don't laugh at that.
I could...
Playing this game alone would be hard, I think.
It'd be scary.
I tried it once.
I actually had to take the headset off one time,
because I was like...
I was too spoopy.
Yeah, it gets like too real in the headset, probably.
Yeah.
OK, well...
Let's...
Let's just go with what we have, I think.
Turn your lights off.
It's like two o'clock in the afternoon right now.
Like, there's no light. It's not going to do anything.
Crucifix does work in your hand.
It just has a small range, and it prevents the start of the hunt,
not if the ghost is already after you.
OK, I understand.
You West Coast lads, thank you for joining at the time,
because I wouldn't have been able to do this later.
This is perfect.
If it worked out, that's good.
Perfect for me.
My audience was like, this isn't my usual time,
so they're like, wait, why are you online?
Why are you here?
Please leave.
I just wish there was like a melee,
just like a single right-handed melee punch.
Punch the ghost?
I would be so much better at this game if that was in it.
Like, I would just be the guy that...
You just deck me out in like the melee gear,
and I just...
Even if I can only punch three times,
I would still be... I'd be so much better at this.
Jerem, I think, ready up, and we'll go into the...
Sorry, it's my problem.
Oops.
It's OK.
We get it. You like Dark Souls.
Great franchise.
All right.
Everyone load in?
OK.
Yep.
Get a ghost to blow out a candle.
I'm taking the cross.
Have a member of your team escape the ghost during a hunt.
Repel the ghost with a smudge stick.
OK.
Well, you know, when I was writing the Ghostbusters film,
I got a lot of inspiration.
The trap.
Let me tell you, the ghost didn't blow out a candle.
Who wants to bring the candle and lighter?
I'm walking around with this thing.
I got two spots.
I'll take the EMS.
What is the rice scanner?
What's this thing?
That... You just picked up a thermometer.
That helps.
If we're looking for freezing temperatures,
we need that.
Why is this flash, like, crusty?
Basically, we just need to make sure...
We need to rule out all of the possible evidence
for the ghost type by using, like, the spirit box EMS,
just spreading them between all four of us.
OK.
So I have a cross.
I'm taking the cross.
OK.
I got a spare slot.
Do you want to take anything?
Can you take the journal again?
Yep.
And once we know where it is, roughly, we can come back,
get a camera, and then go back in.
Beatboxing?
No, I'm just pretending this is a weapon.
I thought you were, like, spraying compressed air.
I was like...
From his mouth.
All right, let's do this.
I got a candle.
Don't make me pick up the whipped cream can
and turn it upside down and do that funny joke.
Oh, this is... You should.
Yeah.
It looks like I'm not a bum.
Did anybody take an EMF?
Yeah, OK.
This place is actually kind of terrifying.
I hate it.
All right, I'm leaving.
All right.
See you.
OK.
Already?
I've not played this map before.
OK.
We're all screwed.
Hey, Liam, when do I light the candle?
Once we know where it is.
It's all basically contingent on one...
Six bucks.
How much do you guys think this chair is worth?
Take a guess, like, all three.
At least one.
One dollar?
Don't look at the price.
Oh, if the price is right, I'm going to say $14.
$14?
$35.
I'm going to say $35 and one cent.
OK.
All right, let's see.
Sassy.
That was $12.
So who was closer?
I said $14.
Yeah, that was close.
You win it.
It's your chair now.
You win the chair.
Why is there a price gun in this game?
That's what I was trying to ask.
Something behind this door.
When you turn it on, look for temperatures.
It's 30.
OK.
Oh, it's Celsius.
I don't know what this means.
Celsius.
Oh, I'm the Canadian here.
I can discern.
All right, so what is bad?
What am I looking for here?
Well, you want, like, negative temperatures.
OK.
Apparently 10.
So once it goes below zero.
OK.
Good to know.
Pretty cold, pretty cold in here.
OK, I dropped my.
This is the loudest clicking.
That's what we're doing.
It is a joke.
OK, I'm doing that with my mouth.
That's how loud that is.
That's me going.
Ross, is your EMF on?
Yes.
OK, perfect.
And it is so blue.
I'm not sure is VR or real life.
Like, I don't know what's happening.
Books.
Star dies in crash.
Man eats self.
Oh, man enters space.
That's less gruesome.
Man eats self.
That's the headline for today.
Extra, extra.
Read all about it.
Man eats self.
Definitely on a slow news day.
Yo, Liam, come here.
I lost my flashlight.
Hold on.
Do you see this glass?
What movie is that from?
I'm just going to say Blade Runner.
Wait, what?
How would you know that?
The one they drink whiskey from in Blade Runner,
where Harrison Ford is like, just walking every scene.
Like, it's in other things.
Lightning.
Just let me have this.
OK.
Thunder.
Are these the only rooms?
No, there's got to be more rooms.
Hold on.
10 degrees so far.
What about this?
Is this a door we can open?
I can't, because my hands are full.
But can someone check out these doors?
Oh, it opens.
Well, now that makes a whole lot more sense.
I was going to say, this is a pretty small map.
Oh, there's a staircase downstairs.
Oh, god.
OK.
All right.
Don't push me.
I'm sorry.
I like this.
I found wet wipes.
Oh, wait, no, that's just never mind.
Are you here?
Give us a sign.
What was that?
Was that me?
Oh, it's locked.
OK, OK, OK.
All right, back up.
All right, so the basement.
Oh, my god.
We don't have to worry about the basement.
OK, in real life, lads, how scared would you be?
That, now that is spooky.
As we got a crucifix, we've got a man.
What?
There's a sacrifice written on the wall.
It's like that place in, was it Winterhold in Skyrim?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Except demonic.
What's this thing down here?
It's like a music box, and it's circled.
I'm sure nothing bad will happen if I.
Oh, you didn't just.
Why would you do that?
Do you like this music, Ghost?
Can you please answer me?
I'm sitting back here.
I know what's going to happen.
We're going to get the.
Oh, it's time to play.
Here it comes.
What was that?
It's still blue, guys.
There's no ghost.
No ghost, OK.
Not Elmo.
Elmo wants to play.
No, it's like.
Pretty good.
It was supposed to be like, oh, the scary little girl ghost,
right?
I think so.
Oh, UV light.
Got it, OK.
There's like knocked over responses.
I'm kind of surprised this place hasn't burned to the ground
by now.
Yeah.
I don't know the Lord's word.
There's a re-claw mark here.
There's a claw mark of swiping claw and blood.
Oh, I'm pretty sure that's for decoration.
I think it might be an animal.
OK, this is like the whole thing.
The ghost is actually a jaguar.
Wait, what you mean to say is that this asylum
has been turned into a spirit Halloween?
As is the fate of any abandoned building.
Boss, I think I told you.
I heard something outside, by the way, guys.
Fallout set I showed you, like where it was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, like where they filmed some of the Fallout show.
It's now a spirit Halloween.
Of course.
Of course it is.
It's getting colder, 6.6 degrees Celsius right now.
Dropping rapidly, 4.4.
I just like pianos in VR games.
4.4, do I light the candle now?
There's a...
Going back, 9.1.
Wait, wait, what just happened?
The temperature is going all over the place.
We're at 5.5.
Yes, that's a piece of evidence.
We need that for the ghost.
Rapidly changing temperature.
In your evidence, write down freezing temperatures.
Sorry, I'm clicking.
I only have one free hand.
Yeah, it's going from like 4.5 to like 9.0 to like 4.1.
It's jumping all over the place.
If it went down that cold, it has to go below zero.
Yeah, we're not at zero yet.
Okay, nevermind.
Well, I guess we might be close then.
Fluctuating temperatures, is that in the evidence anywhere?
No.
It has to go freezing, I think.
But we must be close.
Should we open the door?
Either that or just try to kill us and it couldn't find us.
Ghost, please answer.
Hello?
You're getting sick of your shit.
Yeah, ghosts.
Zombie ghosts, leave this place.
Yeah, big hallway.
I'll be on my deathbed and I'll remember that video.
Big hallway.
If you are here, give us a sign.
Give us a sign.
We found the room.
You had to set off the...
That was me.
Sorry.
That was you?
I was so excited for a second.
I pressed that.
Guys, I found a book of fairy tales.
By Hans Christian Andersen.
Yeah, I love how there's just a shower running
the entire time we're walking around here.
That white noise is good for me.
I like it.
Yeah, that's why I keep it on.
I know it's not a good idea, but I do it anyway.
Do you hear that?
Hit thunder?
Weird.
I was so excited.
I thought we found the room.
Wait, temperature check.
Oh, more Deckard drinks.
5.3, 10.2.
This is fluctuating.
Is it?
5.5, 10.0, 6.3.
Try moving to different parts of the room.
See if it gets really cold.
10.4, 4.8 in the corner here.
10.1 in the corner.
It's going from like 10 to three to four to 10 to...
That's a big change, isn't it?
He just walked off on his own.
Oh, that's great.
I'm good.
I'm just...
Okay.
Hey.
Oh, nevermind.
Nevermind.
This door is glitched.
Is it?
Do you see?
Why is this door like comically huge?
Is anyone else seeing how big this door is?
It is kind of big.
This is Andre the Giant's bedroom.
No, seriously.
Is it reaching the ceiling for you guys?
No, no.
No.
I think you got a silly door.
I got a silly door.
I swear I have a Monty Python-esque door.
It's really wacky.
A little ghost.
Sounded like I sounded two days ago.
Hold on.
Do I look like I'm in the washing machine?
You do.
You sure do.
5.1.
Oh, it's like that scene in Better Call Saul, Vinny.
So he's Gus.
Wait, wait, wait.
I haven't seen past the first episode.
How can this be possible?
Shit, I'm so sorry.
Well.
There's a guy named Saul.
I'm kidding.
I've seen past the second season.
Okay.
Past the second season, okay.
Past the first episode, it's like, all right,
so you just literally haven't even seen the show.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, no, I saw the first episode five years ago once.
I watched it when it premiered,
but only the first five minutes.
I lost everybody.
Where do I go?
Yeah, just down the hallway here.
Oh, thank God.
Can we just like turn the lights on maybe?
8.3, no, it's not, not cold.
Well, hold on.
Yeah.
4.5.
Every time I think I hear a noise,
it's just like some object that someone actually.
Yeah, something's moving.
Still nothing, huh?
No EMF or anything?
Yeah, and I got no, oh, my flashlight just.
Uh-oh.
Gipped in and out.
Temperature check.
EMF, storm blue.
We're fine.
10.
What's that?
That's thunder, that's thunder.
That's thunder.
I was gonna hold the cross out.
Remember to drop it if there's a spooky ghost.
Oh, actually, actually drop it on the ground?
You have to drop it on the ground.
Yeah, that's how I died before I didn't drop it.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's very good info.
This, this gotta be it.
This little room, come on.
Come on ghost.
That wood is mine.
What do you even store in here?
Ghosts.
Yeah, exactly. As soon as you're getting attacked,
whoever has the smudge sticks,
as soon as you're getting attacked,
just immediately pull out the smudge stick and smudge.
No matter what happens.
We're locked in.
Oh, we're locked in.
We're locked in. Are you sure?
I am. Are you sure it's locked in?
We're locked in. Pull it back.
Pull it back.
No. There you go.
Whoa, whoa, funny door.
Ah, yeah.
There's some funny doors in this game.
This door opens too.
I just don't need to be here.
The fourth person here,
and I just don't know how to open a door.
I'm like, we're locked in.
We're locked in.
It's like, no, you just didn't open it.
It's push, not pull.
Yo, there's gherkins in here.
Oh shit.
No ghosts, but gherkins.
Dropping the flashlight
when the thunder hits is like perfect.
Zoinks.
What the fuck is that noise?
What is this door?
It's too big.
Vinny's brushing his teeth right now.
He said he was gonna brush his teeth for a minute.
Weep, weep, weep, weep.
Is there even a ghost in this whole place?
Yeah.
Okay.
Is one of the options for nothing?
It feels like ours.
This is just, you know what it is?
Is there an option for no ghosts to go home?
Yeah, yeah.
It's the scariest of all the Phasmophobia maps
because this is just real life.
Yeah.
I think the ghost is a gas leak.
Do you smell bark, ghost?
It's just, that's the sound we're hearing.
Ghost, give us a sign.
Carbon monoxide alarms failed us.
Yeah, oh, I think I can smell the ghost, guys.
I think I can smell it like sulfur.
There's a small pencil on the couch.
No ghosts, but.
Where is this?
Is there like a ghost that doesn't come out
and they kind of hide and we have to do something?
Yeah, there is a ghost that's shy.
Oh, and you have to split up, right?
Yeah, that could be it.
All right.
But we need to, we don't have any readings,
so we have nothing to go off of.
Yeah, we don't, yeah.
I was gonna say, I'll volunteer as bait
for the ghost if you want.
Okay.
It did work well last time.
Well, have we been down here?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
How would it not be in this room?
I guess we went through a giant circle.
This room is like the I am a ghost.
We're heading back to the truck.
Uh-oh.
We're heading back to the truck if you wanna.
Oh, okay, I'm coming.
I'll guide you, where are you?
Okay, good.
I didn't want you to get lost again.
Do we have any cameras or anything?
We do, we just, there's no reason to set it up
if we have no idea where it is.
All right, let's, let's.
We had a board brush for the ghost.
Oh, what?
Yeah, we're at zero sanity.
What?
There's activity at 10.
What happened?
The half reader didn't do anything.
We just all went crazy in there.
We are all apparently insane,
but I mean, I don't feel any different.
Should we just take pills?
I guess we should.
Well, it was so probably haunted you guys.
I guess I'm taking a fucking pill then, all right.
So this activity you said at 10.
Yeah, it said the activity was at 10,
like so soon, right here.
Somebody said we should check downstairs.
So we were probably on the verge of potting.
Okay, we were right there.
I just spilled coffee all over me.
I could really use anything.
I don't care.
Is anybody there?
It's not that much.
Hello, is there anybody in there?
Spirit, show yourself.
We should just lure it out with mean words.
I mean, we've been down this hallway.
We need to go down.
Let me go back to the church
and I'll just like separate from you.
Wait, that's a terrible idea.
We got to go in twos.
We got to do twos.
Yeah, we'll pretend to not be in there.
Yeah.
So if you like shut the door, maybe.
You guys didn't try to pull on the basement door,
says a chat member.
We didn't pull on the basement door.
There's a basement door?
Where are those stairs?
That lightning was closer.
So where's this basement door that we're,
oh, oh, oh, basement door is open.
Okay.
I'm.
You all right, Vinny?
I'm fairly sure we went down here earlier.
Oh, fuck.
We did.
Did we already go down here?
Yeah, we did.
We did.
Yeah.
The mattress at the bottom.
Shit.
It's not the room?
I'm starting to think that this was an elaborate scheme
by somebody to tell us to all be here
and yeah, go find the ghost
while they rob all of our houses.
Like, we're just here.
I have no idea.
What funny door.
You don't see it, do you?
If you pull on it, Liam, pull on the door in VR.
Okay.
Tell me if you can make it a funny door.
You got it?
It extends.
No way.
Oh my God.
Wait, what?
What?
There's a funny door.
Holy shit, this is the biggest door of all time.
Can you guys pull on the door backwards?
Like pull from the edge back?
Oh my God.
I just turned it into a wall.
Every time someone uses the door, it gets bigger.
Yeah, it's huge.
It's at the ceiling for me almost.
I'm gonna load up your stream.
Oh my God, what the?
What?
Dude, what?
Is it funny?
This is better than the ghost.
It's like someone's gonna use
the free transform tool on the door.
Maybe the ghost is inhabiting this door.
Maybe this is what it is.
Is that in the evidence, giant door?
Can we, yeah, put the ghost as door?
Oops, can I pick that back up?
Okay.
The door is now.
It is 10 point, what did the game,
did we get locked somehow
and the ghost just didn't spawn in here?
This door is now broken for me.
I can't actually grab it.
Okay, here, let me try.
Yeah, neither can I.
I think we're in trouble here then.
Yeah, the door's, yeah, the door broke.
Oh, I got it.
There you go.
You got it.
Oh my God.
I have to maneuver around the door.
Do I spin like this?
Does the door look silly?
Oh, oh, it's gittering.
It's got collision too, all the way through.
Yeah, oh my.
The more collision it has.
Jerma?
Yeah.
Yep, I copy.
Where am I?
Where are you, Jerma?
Actually, help me.
I actually, help, help, help, help, help, help me.
Help, actually help.
Are you behind this door?
I'm behind that door.
Okay, I can't open it.
Why is the door locked now?
I don't know.
You could try the other door to get into, yeah.
It's right here.
Help me.
Open the door.
Open it, open it, open it.
Open it.
Where, where are you?
Where was this?
What the fuck?
I was, okay.
I did the, everyone that says
that I would never do the thing that happens
in movies, right?
Where, oh no, I'm trying the door.
I'm pulling, I'm yanking on the fucking door
and it's closed and I can't open it.
Everyone says I would never do that, right?
You've got three seconds to get away from that thing.
I did that thing.
I went for the handle and I tried to grip it
and I pulled as hard as I fucking could.
I should have just sprinted.
I should have sprinted the fuck away.
And yes, I understand.
I realize I'm in a family guy death pose.
I get it, I understand.
It's funny.
Well, at least I pulled the ghost into aggro.
I'm happy about this.
I recommend, we need to be careful what we say
because the ghost will know if we're going to be some kind.
All right, can I see the ghost now that I'm dead?
Same as family guy death.
It's been better than I thought.
Oh my god, how beautiful.
Oh my god.
Oh, holy shit.
Holy shit.
It's definitely falling easy.
All I can hear is just muffled Peter Griffin
and impressions.
Holy crap, Lois.
Your roommates are watching family guy.
Oh, that's, what the fuck?
I could have pulled the door off.
Wait, I could have pulled the door off
and just walked away.
You got to be shitting me.
I wonder who she's coming for.
Who's screaming?
She's right there, she's coming.
What?
Oh, it's you.
Give me, I need to fuck with them, right?
I need a, I need like a small plate.
I just stood behind Liam and let the,
Oh, hey, Jerma, what's up?
Hey, what's up?
I died a horrible death.
Yeah, that was, it's pretty rough.
Yeah, that's, they can do that when they die.
Oh no, they're telling us to check the book.
Okay.
So what did we have?
We had, did we have,
This is so funny.
Wait, pick up the book if they drew something.
Did they?
I don't think they did.
Okay, pick up the book if there were fingerprints.
I didn't see any, I had the thing, nevermind.
I just died and panicked, that's all that happened.
Yeah, you died in the Family Guy pose
and like your skull was caved in.
It was just terrible.
Really?
All around.
Yeah.
It was freezing.
There was no EMF level five.
Like we could see your teeth.
It was, it was gruesome.
They're waving a book at us, does that mean?
Do I have a book in my hand?
Obviously, this is probably just gonna be a guess.
Yeah, I didn't see any writing.
I don't even think it interacted with the candle.
I think, oh man.
Gym.
Gym?
Oh, it says gin, I thought it said gym.
Wait, I thought it said gym too.
Oh, ghost orbs, let me,
let me symbol the ghost orb thing, hold on.
I can't pick this shit up.
Chat, how about this, chat, why don't,
based on what you've seen, do you have any guesses, chat?
Do you wanna do gym?
Chat.
How do I, how do I signal that?
What do you chat think?
I don't know, how do we, how do we show?
A lot of people say gym.
Yeah, move it around.
I'm just checking your chat now.
This thing, this thing, this thing,
floating around.
On the book.
It's all a prank by some guy named gym.
Did you see it?
Book might mean book evidence.
Please.
Just start pulling wires up from the computer.
Yeah.
Okay, they're, wait, they're, they're,
they're throwing a, I can't, a ball, a ball, a ball.
Oh, they're telling us to look at,
they're telling us to look at the camera.
Look, look, look, look, look, they.
The bell.
Why did that happen so many times?
I'm gonna go get another fucking weird object
that means nothing, hold on.
Oh, they brought a, they brought a bottle of ketchup.
I wonder what that means.
I'm gonna just keep throwing shit in here.
Look, you can hit the bell while they're holding it.
The Solonka returns.
Can I bring this plant?
No.
Was that like a pen?
What was I gonna pick up?
A clipboard?
Okay, yeah, a clipboard.
I think I'm lost.
But I guess.
Are you a clipboard?
Yeah, a clipboard, a clipboard.
Where did you find that?
I don't know.
Stay out here.
If I don't come back, you guess, I'll be in touch.
Do you want my headlight thing?
Yeah.
I actually have no idea how to take it off.
How do I do like a follow me this way, this way?
Just like throw in front of their face
and then drag it this way.
So.
Or like just shake it around and then.
Yeah, I'm gonna make like a little trail with it.
Why don't I, you take the camera.
I'm like trying to gesture them to come after you.
Yeah.
Don't do it, Vinny.
Take a smudge stick.
You know what?
Nope, since Jerma and Liam died,
I'm just gonna vote Gin.
I don't care.
Oh no.
Yeah, fuck it, let's go for Gin.
Screw it.
Worth a shot.
Wait, we get to go.
Oh, I forgot to vote Gin.
There we go.
We got nothing.
Do we not get it?
Do we get it?
Miling.
No.
Not Gin.
I got $20 for that.
I know, how are we supposed to make any money?
Single level or single dollar.
Oh my God.
I made 25 bucks an hour ago
and I don't know how it happened, but it did.
That map was just too big.
Maybe it's the difficulty we're on?
No, no, intermediate's fine.
Liam, are there any other levels
that are like mid to small sized that you have access to?
Yeah, can you access Tanglewood and Edgefield?
This game is cool.
Is there a hoop?
Yeah, actually up here.
Is there?
Right here.
Oh, okay, that's blending in for me.
All right.
Maybe that's too small, but that's all right.
That's not very well-interesting.
I guess we wanna feel some success today.
Wait.
No.
Oh.
Yeah, I don't at least make Jerma fuck
more than five bucks.
Yeah.
That's my goal.
No, I'm good.
It's fine.
It's fun just to kind of walk around and be scared.
Look at the twins playing basketball over there.
That's so pleasant.
The Zuckerbergs.
Oh shit, I gotta add my equipment.
I gotta, I gotta, I got it in.
You got it in?
All this equipment is still here.
Yeah, I got it in.
That's a win for me.
Hold on, I have to do it now.
Oh, cause I died.
Let's just bounce back and hang me in the face.
See, yeah, they, the UI on how this works.
So I'm like a little confused, but it'll be.
I don't like that they changed it to this.
I don't get it.
It was weird at first.
What, they did like a big UI update?
$15.
Yeah.
I mean, it looks nicer, but.
Have you guys played the Village DLC?
Not yet.
No, not yet.
It's good.
Are you still playing Splatoon?
Yeah.
You want to play Splatoon one of these days?
You want to do the salmon thing?
Salmon run?
Yeah, I'm down.
I love salmon run and play that.
That's pretty much all I play on that game now.
Except for maybe some rank.
It's such a fun PvE mode.
I got really addicted to that for a while.
So yeah, I'm down.
I'll play.
I slept on Splatoon for, since the first came out.
First one.
I did not think it was as intricate and fun as it was.
It is, yeah, it's great.
I mean, it, but it evolved too.
The first one was good,
but now it's like the best it's ever been, so.
I think you know what the big,
the huge turnoff for me was?
That first game being on the Wii U,
and like I, it's just that big brick console in your hand,
and the gyroscope, I don't know, it wasn't for me.
Well, the gyro is definitely way more manageable
on an actual controller,
rather than the Fisher Price game pad they gave you.
Hey guys.
Yeah.
That door over there, can you go and press that door?
Press it?
Yeah.
What the?
Who are the other people in the lobby?
Did we invite some people?
People join off you?
Chad said go in the center.
What are you, Chad?
Use a black light.
Use a black light on the inner circle.
We have a black light.
My name is Jeremy, what's up, man?
What's your, what's your channel?
What's your Twitch channel?
I think your mic is messed up, man.
Who invited, are these friends?
Yeah.
Behind the counter.
Oh, oh, oh, hang on, hang on, guys.
There's a little thing that we have to do here, hang on.
All right, here, look.
Oh.
It's gonna get weird,
because we're all gonna be talking at the same time,
so I mean, can you guys mute your microphones
so our streams don't, I know we're like all.
There's too many people in this lobby, sorry.
Yeah, I mean, it's gonna be weird.
Oh.
Maybe we could split it off
into two different discords or something.
It's gonna be kind of weird.
What's that?
They're dead now.
If you stand here, did they do the thing for you?
What thing?
Wait, wait, what is happening?
What is happening?
Oh no, what?
What?
No.
They became come on the floor, what's happening?
That's what I was thinking.
I didn't want to say it out loud.
Nothing's happening.
Oh.
Hey, dude, one of you guys turn your TV down
as he's coming to the mic, one of you guys.
They left, they all disconnected.
Yeah, they DC'd.
It's all right, it's for the best.
We don't like them anyway.
It'd probably be hard to do that anyways.
We'll just do this map.
All right, let's ready up.
I'm confident this time.
We'll get it.
I mean, I'm down to play another like half hour.
Is that cool guys?
Yeah, then I'll have to hop off anyway.
Okay, so we'll definitely get the.
That's like the kind of like,
you got to back away from the TV.
Both hands up, face into the television.
That was, you were too close.
Okay, smudge stick,
and we have to have a ghost walk through salt.
Okay.
German's on smudge stick duty again.
That sounds good.
I can take EMF again.
We don't have enough flashlights.
I don't think.
Wait, really?
Oh boy.
That's all right.
That's just peachy.
Hey, there's, I'll tell you what,
I'll use the black light.
So who wants this extra flashlight?
It's right here.
It's.
I'll take it.
All right, hang on, I'll put it back up here.
Did we have an EMF?
Yep.
Yes, perfect.
I got lighter smudge stick flashlight.
I got salt, I got black light,
and I'll bring. Do you have a lighter, German?
Yep.
Okay, I think we're all set.
I'll bring a spirit box.
I'll bring the sound thing. Oh, you are?
Yeah.
If you're bringing spirit box.
I've got EMF and spirit box.
Oh, do we have a thermometer or did I?
No, I don't think we have one.
I don't think so.
Okay, that's fine.
That's just one equipment, that's fine.
All right, well, I'm gonna take a journal, man.
What's this key for?
What's this thing?
That's the key to the house, yeah.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
So remember, we have to have a ghost walk through salt
and we have to use the smudge stick
when the ghost is chasing one of us.
Okay, wait, isn't this the baby level?
This is the baby level?
We need a win.
We need a win, we need a win, we need a win.
Okay, yeah, I remember this.
This level I've played a million times, we'll be fine.
All right, cool.
I say confidently, knowing that I'll probably die first.
All right.
I'm gonna make a pickle sandwich if anyone knows one.
Ghost, are you in here?
Pickle and peanut butter.
Ghost, how old are you?
What is your name?
Getting ratings over here, guys.
There's four knobs here.
I don't know what this ghost detector is,
but somebody can read that, maybe?
Can you read it?
I'm over here.
There's a ghost detecting machine over here.
It's got four nodules on it.
I'm just trying to figure out what it is.
Can anybody read what that says?
It says gullible.
It does?
It doesn't say that.
Pencil crayons, neat.
This is a small house.
All right.
There's a chat member that said if we do this,
he'll subscribe to my channel.
Really?
All right, let's do it.
We gotta do this.
It's on the line now.
Spirit, I'm not the ghost,
but I have to say the spirit temple is more fun.
Spirit temple.
Honestly, that's kind of a tough one for me.
I don't even know what they're talking about.
Oh, you guys can hear me.
I thought I was far enough away.
Bartholomew.
Nancy.
Okay.
Ghost, are you Nancy?
Why is this computer so big?
It is huge, isn't it?
Like, that's a comically oversized computer.
Speaking of, let me see if I can make
these doors bigger.
No.
That's a big tower.
Well, you can fit a 4080 in there comfortably.
It might just explode,
but the connectors might burn up before it explodes,
so you might get lucky.
Yeah, you might get some gaming in before then.
Level two matches on Call of Duty.
Nope, Nancy.
There's a basement, by the way.
They might be down there.
Oh, there's a basement.
Oh, they're definitely in the basement.
Where we access that basement?
Over here, I think.
Yeah, it's here to the left.
I'm ready with a smudge stick,
if you want me to use it.
Don't touch that, you'll get electrocuted.
What is this?
Oh, that's for catching flies, I think.
Oh, I thought, honestly, this is insane to say,
but I thought this was the ghost,
like baiting somebody to come pick this up,
like they're, like, I'm gonna grab this.
Like, carry it on a stick.
It's like tomato soup or something,
like, oh, tomato soup, and I'd pick it up,
and they would be like,
oh, it would pull us up or something.
I thought this was, like, a thing the ghost was doing.
Well, I mean, no.
That's gross.
Yeah, it's kind of nasty.
How long has this been up here?
How did this many flies get in the basement?
Not even a window down here.
Bridge, anything in here?
No, no, nothing, no.
Oh, what's up?
You all right?
Minnie, Minnie?
What?
I don't know, nothing happened.
You just made, like, a Five Nights at Freddy's scream sound.
No, a little bit, maybe.
By the way, what a franchise.
Right?
Aren't they making a TV show starring Henry Cavill
since he's no longer on The Witcher?
He's no longer on The Witcher?
Uh, Liam Hemsworth.
Your namesake is replacing him.
Where's this ghost?
What was that?
Lighter?
I think Jerma has a lighter.
I have it.
What do you need?
Okay.
A little something fun will happen.
Oh, that'd be cool.
Let's see.
10 DB, 11 DB.
I don't, ow, my fucking thumb.
How do I light this?
Ow, ow.
Uh, maybe if it's, I'm in VR, it might be easier.
Here.
Oh yeah, you can light it.
I'm ready with the smoke stick.
All right, and.
Smoke stick, smoke stick. Holy shit.
I don't have to fucking light her.
Oh my god, oh my god.
Maddie.
Ah, run.
Oh my god, no, no.
I closed the door.
What?
Oh shit, he died.
Where's the lighter?
I can't light the smoke stick anymore.
I have the lighter, I'm sorry.
Smoke stick me.
Uh, here.
Oh shit, where'd it go?
I saw it.
It was big.
Yeah.
Where's the lighter?
It looked like a naked Slenderman.
What does that mean?
Um, it could mean nothing.
The lighter just disappeared.
That's bad.
We need to go back to the truck, right now.
Run.
I don't know if it.
What's wrong, you okay?
It's getting, I've got a three.
I've got a three.
Oh, you got locked in there.
You're in trouble, you're in trouble.
I'm gonna.
Yeah, okay, it got to a four.
It got to a four.
You good?
He's dead, he's dead.
Okay, well, that's your problem.
Let's just close that door.
Okay, well, now let's.
All right, so what evidence do we have, Jerma?
The evidence that we have,
it was a thing on the ground
that we lit the candles to summon it.
So it's a summitable monster.
That's one piece of evidence.
Second piece of evidence, I would say, strangulation.
There's been two strangulations.
Third piece of evidence, I would say, is the skin.
They've got skin, and they like,
I don't know, something about it.
They looked like they're, they looked like naked.
Yeah, they were naked.
So I saw EMF level, it only got to four.
It never got to five.
So that's not evidence.
Fingerprints, well, I saw it had fingers,
so we can assume it might have fingerprints.
Okay.
Ghost writing, didn't stop to find out
if it could, if it was, you know.
We didn't know.
We could go run in there and look.
You say EMF level five?
No, no, it only got to four.
Freezing temperatures, I didn't have a thing.
Spirit box.
I don't know.
I didn't, I had one, but I didn't use it.
Uh, ah, shit.
What does DOTS projector?
Is that like capturing like spirit orbs or something?
Or is that separate? Probably.
No, spirit, ghost orbs are separate.
How do we look for fingerprints?
What do we do?
I think we have to put down like a powder or something.
Oh, we need salt, right?
We need to have it walk through salt.
Should we try to do that?
We could try.
Okay, so how about this?
Yeah, I'm going to go stand out in the middle of the house
and just pretend like, oh, I don't know.
Well, where's my friends?
And then like when it, when it's going to show up,
just put the salt down.
No, I was going to just be,
I was just going to bait the ghost out.
It's right here.
It's here. It's here.
It's here.
I think it's going to kill you.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, I'm dead.
Without a doubt.
It's literally, but I'm right in front of the door.
Put the salt down right now.
Ow.
Dude, it's like he had a can of bug spray.
He looks, he had a can of bug spray, like a can of raid.
Where is it?
Shh.
That was loud.
Hey, what's up?
That's a cat.
Your ghost was on the camera for some reason.
That was funny.
Hey, will I be on the camera?
Yeah, I think you will.
Okay.
Woo.
There he is.
Oh wow.
It's Vinny's ghost.
Sounds like Dodd.
Here, hang on a sec.
Quick floss.
That's got the letters of dog in there.
Yeah.
I'm just going to.
I have no idea what that,
and I don't know how to shake the salt either.
I don't know how to make the salt.
I think you just put it on the floor and then.
That was so funny, dude.
That was literally, you literally were crawling in.
Like you had a can of bug spray in your hand.
It was so funny.
I was close though.
We got money.
I got $10.
We got 10 bucks.
That's all right.
That's the most money I've got all night.
Oh, 33.
I got it.
It's money.
You got five bucks.
Oh my goodness.
Well, I mean, somebody in your chat Vinny mentioned
what were they expecting when they lit it.
I was like, I don't know, something would happen.
Some action maybe.
I didn't think we were going to summon a demon
like immediately.
I thought maybe it would be subtle.
I didn't think we were going to summon
like the fucking skinwalker right in front of us.
That was, it was not prepared.
Wait, there's bowling?
Wait, what?
Wait, does the bowling work?
Oh, does this work?
It does.
We can, wait, this Jenga?
Oh shit.
Oh, you've lost.
Hold on, man.
Jenga.
Yeah, that was the move.
You don't want to play Jenga,
but you're going to just like humor us and.
Let's put it back together.
And you're going to be like, oh shit, I lost.
This will be the rest of the stream.
Putting back, putting back the tower here.
Oh, I see.
Let me add some color to the town.
Oh my God.
What?
Oh, it's making like source engine sounds.
Check this out.
Oh my God.
That does sound like Gary's mod.
Does this look weird?
Oh, I got it.
That you guys, you guys want to do another one
or you guys think it's not enough time?
Do one more.
We got to win.
You can do this.
It's still fun though.
Do you guys see what's happening to the basketball?
It's.
I see it like hovering, jittering.
Oh, a ball.
Does this work?
It's just a table.
Hey, you dropped this.
No.
I'm just enamored with the source engine sounds
over here on the table.
Okay.
Yeah, we can do one more.
Maybe we'll do like, oh geez.
Hey, is there anything easier than that?
Is there, is there another easy short one
that's like not a house?
Like what's the one on the right there?
This one, the, all the way on the top right.
Willow street?
Is that a house?
It could be small.
What is this a times 18 times two things?
Is this how many floors there are?
How many rooms?
Oh, it's how many, yeah.
How many rooms are in each house?
So we did just pick a small one, Willow street.
All right, let's do Willow street then.
All right, one more.
This would be definitely,
that'll get that chat member to sub.
Oh yeah.
Let me add more equipment here.
How much money do you have in this game, Liam?
$1,600.
What?
Okay, wow.
You like this game, don't you?
A little bit.
I have $42.
It's 17.
Okay, I understand how the UI works.
I'm gonna add all this crap.
We need a candle crucifix.
What's happening?
Hey!
Why are you in the ground?
Oh, there you go.
I'm just sitting.
Sorry, just finishing up adding all the equipment here.
I hope I don't die because I'll lose all this,
but what can you do?
Am I a puddle?
No, you're like a,
It's very impressive what you're doing.
Guy running onto his feet while shitting, like you're.
You know, it almost looks like you got
like a really baggy pair of pants
and push your arms and legs through both leg holes
and put it all the way up and are walking around
kind of with your arms and legs in each pant leg.
I just spent $600.
It's a very specific mental image.
Goblin mode, someone wrote.
Okay, wow, $600, you say?
Yeah, I added a bunch of equipment.
Well, we're definitely gonna win this one.
There's no way we're not.
Investing in success.
All right, let's do it.
Here we go, everybody.
All right.
Another campsite map.
Ooh.
Let's get that sub, guys.
What was the campsite?
We need to get at least that one sub.
Yo, can we go back and do the campsite instead?
Because people are saying that one's cool.
I remember it, kind of.
Oh, you wanna do that instead?
Yeah, is it possible to abandon this
and not lose the equipment?
Yeah, we just guess immediately and then leave, right?
Yeah.
We won't lose any equipment,
but I think we'll lose money.
No, only if we die, so yeah.
Yeah, that's fine, we'll just guess.
The campsite sounds great.
I think Jermal would like it, according to my chat.
Oh yeah, let's do it.
I'm gonna guess, um,
Let's go for it.
What's that called, chat?
Okay.
Moroi, okay.
Woodwind, it's called.
Woodwind.
Camp Woodwind, I see it, okay.
Perfect, okay, it's a small campsite map.
The other campsite I played years ago was too big,
so that's perfect, okay.
All right, sorry, everyone.
This should be fun.
I'm gonna add some more equipment.
Yeah, we're fine, we got everything.
Okay.
Do you think I could quickly squeeze a game of Jenga in, or?
We can play Jenga and then watch a terrible movie afterwards.
Really cool to see Shifter Xeris become a streamer,
I loved you, thanks.
Swarhas, Jerm, are you gonna write it yet?
Oh wait, you did, sorry.
I just did when you were saying it, so you were right.
Is this just a campsite, huh?
Glory, shell, and gold.
Do you remember Salute Your Shorts on Nickelodeon?
This'll be like that, like it'll be like camping
and Zeke the Plumber's gonna come after us.
Okay, I got an EMF.
What is this thing?
Okay, or I could throw it.
What's this like, this knee pad, what is this?
And just the crucifix, okay.
So we don't need to do anything specific
other than crucifix and EMF and not die, so.
This is for dots projector.
Oh, okay.
I can live, I can live.
Can I take it?
I'm gonna take this thing.
Somebody else take the spirit box this time?
I'll take the spirit box, where is it?
Right here, next to the book.
Is that the orange one, okay.
All right, cool.
And then I'll take a glow stick.
Temperature thing here.
Why is there a camera already pointed
at the back of the truck?
That's creepy.
Yeah, that's a little weird.
That's weird.
We don't need a salt or a stick or anything?
No, we don't.
All right.
Just the crucifix and EMF for sure,
and then the rest we can discern as we go.
Okay.
We should be okay this time, maybe.
I'm just gonna stop saying that.
Camp Woodwind.
Oh my God, I'm sorry.
I don't know, I just, like,
you guys walked right in front of me.
I just thought you, it was like immediately,
I was getting attacked.
All right, I'll be okay.
For some reason, I just forgot
that you were right there somehow.
I knew you were there, but I don't know.
What am I looking for on the EMF?
You are looking for level five or anything.
Level five as well.
Oh, the spirit box.
Oh, you're just listening for sound.
Like if it's the ghost talks.
Who's got the EMF then?
I have the dots thing.
Where should I put the dots thing?
Does it matter?
Dots thing?
The dots projector?
Oh, I don't know.
Does that mean?
What does this do?
Wasn't in the hole.
I have no idea.
There's a Ouija board.
We can use that to talk to the ghost.
Oh.
All right, let's do it.
Okay, that's what that does.
Can I turn it off?
Oh.
What is that noise?
Wait, was that?
It's level three.
I just got level three.
Level three?
By Jerma.
Ghosts, speak to us.
Yo, that thing is moving on its own.
That bottle is moving on its own.
Yeah, that bottle is moving.
Which one?
Ghosts.
It's just level three though, not level five.
So we can roll that out, perhaps.
Okay.
No temperature change.
It's still like 13.
Not really.
It's going between like...
Okay.
I'm gonna set up a video camera.
I'm gonna go back to the truck.
I'll be right back.
All right, good call.
Ghosts, what is your name?
Oh my God, they got hand-pined beans.
So what are we looking for with this?
Kiwi beans?
Did you die in the toilet?
Uh, was this like an Xbox Kinect?
What does it do?
I don't know.
It projects dots.
Okay.
Does that help us see ghosts or?
What's that?
I can't be good for your eyes.
Is somebody out?
Are we all together or is somebody walking around
back there?
Are we all together?
I think we all are.
Wait, did you guys turn the camera on?
Oh, are we all on the campfire?
Oh, the shower just turned on.
The shower just turned on on its own.
Did you guys see that?
What do you mean it turned on on its own?
There's a shower?
Ghost, are you taking a shower?
Ghost, what are you doing in there?
Talk to us.
Oh, there is a shower.
Wait, you get the dots thing.
No.
I'm not weird, but I'm gonna set up a camera in the shower.
Good thing you clarified that early.
Okay.
Ghost, why don't you speak to me now
and tell me why you turned on the shower?
Can you shower in the afterlife?
Oh, okay.
There we go.
Why is it not on when I put it down?
You wanna turn it so it's facing the hot ghost action?
Yeah.
Ghost, what was that?
What's that?
I hear crunching.
That could be us just walking, perhaps?
Maybe the ghost is eating Cheerios, I don't know.
What's that then?
Oh, okay.
You said maybe.
That's right, it's weird that your name is Liam, you know?
Yeah, that's weird.
Can we turn the, can we light the fire?
We start the campfire or no?
Because when we did our interview,
like we talked about Liam Gallagher
for like 10 minutes for no reason.
Well, no, because your name is Liam, like, you know?
Oh yeah, right, yeah, I remember that, yeah.
So I am Liam Gallagher.
But you're also gonna be in The Witcher, so.
Yeah, that's right, yeah, I am.
I just got the call from Netflix.
Netflix is telling you they wanna chill.
It's not a time to be messing around and making jokes.
There's a ghost here.
Ghosts.
Wait, it's minus seven, it's minus seven, right?
It's minus 11. Oh, perfect, okay.
I'm gonna write it down, freezing temperatures.
Freezing temperatures.
Freezing temperatures for sure.
Ghosts, freezing temperatures.
Speak to us.
Does anybody have a UV light or the journal?
I got one over here.
Journal?
A UV light.
I had a UV light, I put it down.
If you have a journal, put it in the shower.
That's the first time anyone has said that sentence.
What do you wanna do with the UV light?
Just look for fingerprints.
Oh. I don't see any though.
I just threw it into the.
Yeah, like, don't do that.
That's a glow stick, actually.
Will it show?
Yeah, on the walls, if you look around.
I'm pretty sure, I don't know
if the glow stick reveals fingerprints.
I'm pretty sure the UV light does that.
No.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, colds.
I had cold breath right over there.
Cold breath.
Right there?
Okay, that's where the ghost is.
It's not the shower.
Ghost is here somewhere.
What's that?
I dropped the temperature gun
because I figured we don't really need it.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good idea.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go get some more evidence.
Ghost, can you speak?
I'm trying to communicate with you.
Please, tell me.
I'm just trying to get the black light in the shower.
Ghost, who do you think I am?
We can rule out the shower.
I got a book.
Do you want me to throw it out of the book anywhere?
I got the dots.
Move the dots.
All right, I'm gonna put the dots over here.
There should be a camera on the truck pod.
Ghost, how do you feel about the Brighter Chief?
Sorry, I was in my own world for a second.
What was your question?
How do you open the book?
Oh, you have to press F on a surface.
First I can tell, no ghost.
So should I get rid of the DOS projector?
No, I think we can leave it there.
I don't think I'll scare the ghost off.
You can go back to the truck and see if we see anything.
Oh, hey, Dapper Chief.
So it's either a demon, a Moroi, or the Mimic.
You know what, Vinny, I do too.
It's just gross.
Wait, wait, so you said it could be four things?
What do we need?
So it's four things?
It's either the demon, the Moroi, or the Mimic.
Why don't we all just pick a different one
and then we'll at least get a partial win.
Listen, I need that sub.
That's true.
So what, okay, so what do those four ghosts do
that we should be looking for?
They make some kind of sound?
Do they make some kind of noise?
Do they leave fingerprints or?
Throw a football.
So what did you say it could be?
It's either a demon, Moroi, or the Mimic.
All right, so we're looking for ghost writing.
Did we get any spirit box readings at all?
Like did it say anything to you, Vinny?
No, it doesn't want to talk to me.
Okay, did we have a UV light?
Yeah, we need to find fingerprints.
We can rule out two of these if we rule out fingerprints.
Wait, did you turn on the generator?
The generator just turned on.
That was Vinny, I think.
Okay, Vinny, turn it off.
Yeah, that was not.
Who's did?
What?
How?
How did that happen?
Honestly, like which one of you two did that?
Because there was no ghost.
I was further away.
Oh my God.
Whoa, Gumby.
Holy shit.
Why did you kill our friend Ross and my framerates?
All right, well that was.
Okay, the DOS protector's down too, right?
Nothing?
It's right here.
What are we looking for in the DOS protector?
We need to find fingerprints.
I put a crucifix and I dropped it, I think.
Where's the UV light?
I got a crucifix.
Oh, I don't think we have a UV light.
We don't have a UV light.
I thought we did.
Ghosts speak to us.
What is your name?
Can the glow stick look for fingerprints too
or am I totally wrong?
That's what we were trying to figure out.
Yeah, I figured you could only, I don't know.
Well, I think we might have to leave the chance.
Hey, this process, this looks like it.
Oh, they just.
Yeah, they.
Oh, yeah, it's.
Oh.
Hello?
Ghosts die.
So it looks like we got it.
Yeah, I just dropped the crucifix
and it's gone.
We should go to the truck, truck.
Before anybody else dies.
Yeah.
They're weird noise.
They closed the gate.
Oh, the gate's closed.
Well.
Just jump it, man.
Can we not help him?
It's here, it's here.
There it is.
There it is, I think.
There it is, it's on the ground.
It's crawling on the ground.
It's got me.
Jesus, it's so loud and I turned it down.
Man.
What's up?
It crawls on the ground.
Yeah, it crawls on the ground like a little goblin
and then chokes.
I'm a member of your team escape.
No one has escaped.
We're at zero sanity.
All right.
People saying, hey, why didn't you do anything?
The ghost was attacking and you didn't do anything
and I'm sitting there just trying to,
I'm just trying to give info, right?
I know I'm dead.
So I'm sitting there going like crawling on the ground,
looks like it's a demon and I'm dead,
but they have that info.
My job is to make sure they get that info.
So we got freezing temperatures, right?
Is that a, we definitely got freezing temperature?
We got EMF level five or no?
No.
Basically, I ruled out ghost orbs and EMF level five
because I didn't see.
I think it's a demon.
Well, first of all, it wouldn't go beyond three
and the ghost orbs just aren't showing up on the monitor.
We just didn't do anything, for instance.
I don't know how to look for stuff
in the dots projector though.
Yeah, I didn't see anything.
Chat, did you see any?
You're winning, son.
You gave them the info.
Yeah.
If you click twice.
So no spirit box either.
Oh, it's the demon.
Does that look like?
I'd say demon too.
Yeah, I just ruled out,
after ruling out three of the types of evidence,
it just gave me the demon as one of the possible answers.
Let me see the demon.
Demons are aggressive.
Going to attack without reason.
This is very aggressive.
They enjoy the thrill of the hunts.
They initiate hunts more often.
Demons fear the crucifix
and will be less aggressive than you're one.
So that makes sense.
Yeah, it did blow it up.
It would have been fingerprints,
ghost writing, and freezing temperatures.
So I guess if we found.
Did we not bring a book
or did we place it somewhere else?
I don't know.
The only thing we could do now.
We had a book.
Oh, shit.
The light, I don't think.
We do.
It's the thing.
Do we have any pills?
No.
Oh, fuck.
I think it's on the ground somewhere.
Either of us going back out.
I'm going to guess.
I think it's demon.
Fuck it.
I'm going to guess demon.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to guess demon
based on what I've ruled out here.
All right.
We did get some objective.
That was actually kind of successful.
For what it was.
It's getting money.
Even though two people died.
I'm so sorry you're in the wrong.
It's all right.
We got this, I think.
I think we still win.
I can taste that sub.
That's a win.
Is it?
Fuck, it was a shade.
What?
Oh.
EMF.
I think it was a shade.
I think it was crawling on the ground.
It was none of the things that I, it was.
But I love it.
All right.
Well.
No sub.
Shit.
Damn.
All right.
Shade, okay.
Once you start getting the hang of this,
this game is pretty interesting.
It's pretty fun.
Yeah.
You've got the hang of it.
Cool.
Oh, let me make this more accurate to Gmod.
Hold on.
I hope that sounds good.
Cool.
I'm killing it.
Did you guys see the ghost out here?
Did you guys see the thing that's, you know,
staring at us through the window?
Oh, I do.
Mm-hmm.
It's like looking like the Mario Galaxy 2
Hell Valley Sky Tree thing.
Fuck's sake.
That was very specific.
Yeah.
He knows his Mario.
You're in the, oh, you're in the table.
You are.
I was more in the table, but yeah,
these, in VR, you can pull the basketballs
through the table and they glitch really nicely.
I love how it's really nicely.
Yeah.
Oh, it's such a nice one.
I made a career on very nice glitches.
That's true.
So.
It's like, oh.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yo, I spent hours stomping Koopas.
Someone said Koopas.
Someone said they gave me a participation sub.
Chat members, I didn't actually need the subs.
I'm fine.
But thank you.
That's very kind of you.
All right.
Well, here, I'll stand up for this one.
Who is this? Stand up.
Is this Jerma?
That's me. Oh, hey, Jerma.
Jerma, thank you for agreeing to this.
This was a lot of fun.
Good Halloween spooks.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's always a fun time.
I like playing games. It is.
You're very close to comfort there.
I don't, I have no idea what the hell I'm doing,
but it's fun to walk around and get scared of stuff.
But we can, maybe we can be squids one day.
I don't know.
We should definitely be squids.
I 100% agree.
Okay.
Cool.
Liam, it's always, you're Liam, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, if you guys want to,
if all of you want to play squids one day.
Yeah, I'd be down for squids.
Liam, do you play, you played squids together?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I just had a random match
during the Splatfest or whatever.
So, but yeah, also for the new video, as always.
Sorry?
What did you say?
Good video.
Oh, thank you.
Sorry, I thought you said it was mid.
I was like.
No, no, no, good.
No, no, I didn't say mid.
I said you were mid dunk because you had your arm up
and you were like in a mid dunk with the ball.
Oh yeah.
And Ross, where's Ross?
Yeah, the one with the basketball.
Now Ross is doing, yeah, I'll take that.
Ross is doing a series of things with Minecraft
with Bounce SMP.
Oh God.
Is that what's called SMP?
Yeah.
I might be in there at some point, chat.
I don't know, it'll be after Halloween,
but you can check out Rossy Streams on,
are you on Rubber Ross yet or is it Rubber Ninja?
I am Rubber Ross now, yeah.
Okay.
I changed a while ago.
Alrighty, thanks everyone, I appreciate you.
Yeah, it was fun.
Happy Halloween.
You guys are the best.
Bye.
It was a fun time, guys.
It was fun.
Goodbye, everybody.
Goodbye.
All right, chat, you got me for a couple more minutes.
Okay, so let me do this.
Okay, that was fun.
That was actually pretty scary.
Welcome back.
I am going to move from that.
We are going to open at Dead of Night,
which is a like FMV horror game.
I don't know, I've heard it's fucking horrible though.
I heard it's terrifying.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna pee, I'm gonna get a drink
and I'll be back in literally two, three minutes.
Be right back.