What's up?
I guess Kimmel didn't do much for him.
Will you guys stop saying the words Jimmy and Kimmel right next to each other?
What do you mean? Of course somebody said it. I just read it.
Oh, he uses Reddit. Alright, easy. Fuckin' loser.
Give me one sec. Sorry, I just had to tweet about it.
Guys, I get like... I get like 200 plus people instantly from Twitter.
I have to tweet it. Sometimes 400.
Why are you laughing?
I guess I'm laughing too. We're both laughing.
What are we doing today? A couple of things.
Continuing our just grab bag week.
Just pulling games out of a hat.
Because we've got a whole plan.
Next week and the week after that.
Jobby Bunny is tomorrow.
If you are wondering.
As well as Hive Mind.
Which is something I've been looking forward to playing for a pretty long time actually.
Hive Mind is a game that was made by somebody in the community.
It is a family feud game.
That we can play.
Where I have to essentially kind of guess what you think.
What I think your answers are going to be.
He's been working on it for a while. We're probably going to do it tomorrow.
And Jobby Bunny is tomorrow too.
Remember when you promised Jobby Bunny?
I just gave you a date. I just gave you a hard date. It's tomorrow.
Am I going to revisit Phasmophobia?
I don't know. Maybe.
I think the right amount of lightning needs to strike.
For four people to be ready in VR.
To play that game.
I was the guy that didn't have VR.
You said that you would eat an egg.
What egg?
We're doing face cam today? No. Face cam tomorrow.
Fix your VR.
Should we tell him?
Should we tell him that I streamed VR for like two weeks?
Don't tell that person that I already streamed VR for like two weeks.
Alright. Let me clear my throat off.
Why is there a slug emote?
I added Jerma Slug Pug and everyone was really mad at me.
But now I'm in that weird awful place.
Where half of the people that use that emote.
That think it's really funny.
They love that shit.
But then the other half of you that almost throw up in your mouth when you see it.
And that you want to delete it from the internet.
Now I've got half of you that say that too.
So now I've got to deal with both of the sides here.
That are like, we want slug pug. We don't want slug pug.
Then at that point it comes down to what I want, right?
And here's what I want.
Chaos.
So it's working perfectly.
Alright, let's play. We're gonna play a couple of games.
Oh my god, what's going on today?
Oh, what the fuck?
Okay. What's happening?
I can't get it out. I can't stop it.
Is it gone? Okay, it's gone.
I don't smoke.
I'm dry of water. I swear to god.
I'm just fucking over 30.
How come 35 is the new 60? This is bullshit.
Anyways, we're gonna start with streamer life simulator.
Before you freak out, before you throw a rock at me.
Just hold on.
Listen, I'm not gonna play this all day.
I'm gonna play Exanima.
Exanima? Right? Yeah.
Exanima is a physics based top down dungeon crawler.
I made a video on this fucking game like seven years ago.
And I was told, it was recommended to me again.
They said, hey dude, so much shit has been added to this game.
And it's way different and way better than when you played it before.
It was a little wonky before. It was like alpha or something.
Play it now, please. You'll love it.
So I'm like, alright man.
I guess the actual 1.0 came out and they updated it a bunch of times.
So I'm gonna give it a try. We'll try it again today.
But that is before.
That is after we're gonna play streamer life simulator.
This was also recommended too.
And if you don't think I pull from the recommended channel on the discord,
then where are these two games coming from?
The only reason why I want to play this, one reason,
there's only one single solitary reason,
is because you play a game in the game to a fake audience.
And like that, I don't know why that's funny to me.
Is this a cringe game? I don't know what that means.
What does that even mean?
I don't even know what that means.
Look, I already have my settings ready.
We make a character.
Alright, let's put clothes on this person first of all.
Porn game?
It's perfect.
It is not perfect.
Is this just the character? Do I even care?
I'm being honest.
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's facial morphing?
Low cheek posit? What is this doing?
Oh, hold on, this is face morphing.
What's with the camera?
The camera's freaking me out, man.
Okay, that's a little much, but whatever.
Is this Chad?
Hey, what do you mean?
This is me.
Ear position? Why does this even matter?
I'm just making golem.
Eyes. My eyes kind of go like this a little bit.
Do they? I don't know, I can't turn the camera on.
I don't have any clothes on.
I have big eyes. I have big scary eyes.
They're like this.
I've been told that before.
You know that your actual eyeballs are kind of fucking huge?
No, I don't have that.
Maybe a little bit, maybe like that.
Forehead size?
I have big eyebrow hinges, whatever these are called.
I don't have a big forehead though.
My forehead's actually pretty small.
I have a small head.
It's not tiny though, it's pretty narrow.
I can get a better image.
Jaw position?
Okay, this does not look like me.
You look like Pinhead.
It doesn't matter.
I kind of have a big nose.
It's not really big, it's just warped.
It's not, I don't have a big nose.
I have a warped nose. This is different.
People miss get through that all the time.
Oh, he's got a big nose.
No, no, no, no. It's just crooked at the top and broken and twisted.
It just looks bigger.
Okay, that's fine.
I can actually be glue man?
No, no.
No, no, no.
You make slime guy.
Why are all these things in the game?
What's the point of this?
Arm width.
Huge arms.
No, I have long arms.
I got that big ant stomach now.
This is 6'7".
6'6", 6'5", 6'4".
I don't even know.
What height is this?
0.5?
Neck thickness.
I like cartoon pythons
swallowed a plate or something.
My character right now is going like
And then the other secondary character comes over
and punches me in the stomach
and the whole plate comes out.
And the turkey dinner on it too and I eat it and it's normal.
Let's do normal.
Feet size.
Forearm length.
I get it.
I understand.
Leg separation.
You know what?
I do have pretty big leg separation, don't I?
I have short legs.
The long thing is
I would be so much shorter
if I had a shorter torso.
I actually have
an alien body.
I have a really long torso, but short legs.
If I had a short torso, I'd be 5'4".
So you're compact.
Kind of.
I'm like an accordion.
Upper muscle.
Upper weight. A little bit heavy.
This looks nothing like me.
This is just a weird guy.
No eyebrows.
Style 1. Style 2.
Style 3.
They're kind of like this.
Eyes. Cat eyes.
Alligator eyes.
Oh, there we go.
My eyes are like a slate gray.
I don't have blue eyes.
I have a slate gray.
Cool.
That looks good. What about hair?
I'm going to keep it bald for all of you to laugh.
I like this look.
No shoes.
Elf ears?
This is good.
This doesn't look anything like me.
You just said the F word, dude.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
I'm too.
Hold on a second here.
This is not even correct.
Now it's a little more correct.
There we go. I'm ready.
Streamer life, the first installation may take a little longer.
You can find some items to sell.
You buy gas?
You drive a car?
Does this get an automatic plus one?
Plus A? Plus a letter grade?
What do I do?
Press the up arrow on the keyboard to open the phone.
Welcome.
Okay, turn it off.
Talk to Mosi.
Is this a drug dealer simulator?
Hygiene? Toilet? Heat?
Messages. Settings.
Sound. Alarm. Car assistance.
Turn the overturned car
back to normal.
Spoiler. Thanks.
Zuber. Select the location you want to go.
Oh, it's like Uber.
Health. Current weight 83 pounds.
Calories consumed.
Recommended calories. Flashlight?
Okay.
What the fuck is this game?
The computer parts in the trunk of the car.
Can I pet the dog?
How do you pet dog?
Do I have to just go home?
Talk to Mosi. Put the computer parts in and go home.
What the fuck?
What is going on?
What is this drug dealer simulator?
But it's a different video game.
I thought it was a streamer.
I thought it was a streamer simulator.
What happened last night?
I can't explain right now. I'm about to faint.
What's going on? Money?
I said buy a computer to pay me your debt.
The computer is in front of the door.
Now fuck off.
Okay.
Press E to get it in your hand.
What? X47?
This is a real motherboard.
Isn't that a real motherboard?
Press E to get it in your hand.
Press and hold to put it in the bag.
Okay. Why do all motherboards have the exact same name then?
How do I put a legendary monitor?
Why does it have rarity?
Old case.
Oh my god. What is all this?
Do I have to build a computer?
The Samsung 03.
That's a great way to not get sued.
You've done a great job. I can't carry any more items.
What? Where the hell do we live?
This is a potato PC.
What are you talking about dude?
Alright.
No it's not.
We didn't even get a good look at it.
Alright. I have $814.
Pretty sick. Alright. Wait. What happened to my...
Put this in there too.
Durability. Socket.
You build PCs in this game?
Wait. I want all this stuff.
Zintel.
You put a Z in front of every single word.
Zorsair. Zintel.
Zinvidia.
Alright. Okay. Let's go.
Okay. I have to be fair to the game.
I do. This is plus one full letter grade.
It is.
This is not just a...
How do I drive?
W and S is forward and back.
It's not doing anything.
Handbrake? Oh the handbrake was on.
This car sucks.
But it does get...
It does get a full letter grade.
I have to be fair to video games.
This is Silent Hill.
This game is actually creeping me the
fuck out a little.
That sound is in 3D Movie Maker.
That's in 3D Movie Maker. It's one of the car hit sounds.
So where's my house?
Holy shit. There are people.
Alright. Get out.
I can't do this while the car is moving.
How do I get out of the car?
Exit the vehicle.
Okay. How do I stream?
This is my streamer room?
Press to get in your...
Oh no. I have to decorate my streamer room.
You live in the Postal 2 universe.
Apparently.
How do I...
Cool. Okay.
Set up and run your computer.
What? Alright.
This is the streamer room right here, right?
Is this a high chair?
Alright. I need a desk.
Fuck. That's not very good.
Plastic chair.
Okay. I need my...
This is a shelf. Let's just like clean this
place up a little.
Has it enough wallpaper on the walls or anything?
There's no drywall on here.
Credit shelf. That's pretty pog. Yep.
Okay. This is my bed.
I'm gonna just say this is my bedroom.
Oh. That's how you rotate. Rotate. Okay.
Cool. Oh. You can sleep.
I need to get... This is my streamer room.
Wait. No. It's not. This is like... People can just
crawl in here. People can just reach over
and just grab my fucking mouse.
Whatever. How do I leave?
Oh shit. I have so much stuff.
Okay. I need this.
I need this. I need this.
Alright. Let's go. What is he doing?
What do you mean?
Oh shit.
That wasn't me putting it in my hand?
No. That was. That was right.
You guys just got it in my head.
Okay. Put this on the table.
Now. How do I get my backpack?
How do I open up my actual backpack?
You should do... You should do your
toilet. What?
Z? Move the desk.
How do I get my backpack?
You can turn the character's features.
Okay.
That's not controls.
Okay. I. You can open up
the streamer skill panel. Okay. So I.
Here we go. Close that.
And put this right here.
That's the motherboard.
And then I got my
desktop PC. Rotate
this. Okay. Whoa!
Wait. The computer's already done?
Is this an iMac from
2001?
Do you remember those things? Those things were fucking awesome.
Um. Okay.
Press F to access computer.
Oh. Okay. Okay. It says I got a chair.
I need the tower. I need the keyboard.
I should do my toilet urgently.
What the fuck does that even mean?
I should do my toilet
urgently. How do I get up?
How do I get off the computer? Q.
Okay. Where's the bathroom? I don't even have a bathroom.
I don't have a bathroom. In the corner.
You should do. I don't know.
I don't know how to do that. Streamer.
Is it a skill? What the fuck?
What? What is
all this? Make stream and get
a stream crown. Open extra
slots. Where's the P
skill? F.
It's not F. I don't think. I don't
think I can go to the bathroom. Buy
a toilet. Well hold on. Wait. Wait.
Alright. Buy a toilet. Wait. Wait. Wait. Okay. Okay.
Hold on. I need my case.
And the keyboard and I'm good.
Close this shit up. Okay. Put this
down here. That's actually where my
PC is right now.
I'm actually going to make this my streamer room.
What's wrong with it? Why is there an exclamation point?
Okay. Keyboard. Go to the bathroom.
I don't know how.
That's kind of weird to say.
There we go. Alright. Computer's done.
It's not. Set up and run your computer. What the?
How do I? Okay. Where are the cables?
Are there any cords? Oh
my god. Okay.
Um. I need a motherboard.
So it's right there. Good thing I
have to go drive back to that dude's house.
Okay. Close this. Get out
of this. Get out of this. How do I close this? Out.
Out. Get out.
Get out. How do I get out?
Oh. It's escape.
Okay. I have to go get parts. Motherboard.
Put it in here. Motherboard.
There it is. Put it in.
Got it. Alright. Now we need a CPU.
We need a video card in a hard drive.
Alright. I'll be back. The keyboard was really
preventing me from leaving the house. Alright.
I gotta go back to that guy's house and get my stuff.
Anything in the dumpster? Nope.
Ice cream? How much money do I have?
I don't want to do this.
Why is there an ice cream vendor just right outside of my
house? Alright. I need to
go back to that guy's house. Do not
hit anybody. Don't hit anybody.
I already have it in the trunk?
Do I? I don't have a video card.
Oh. This is a video
card. Okay. Video card, hard
drive. Oh. I do have it all.
Holy shit. I took all the right stuff. I didn't
leave. Oh. Awesome.
Alright. Let's go back. Oh. I can't wait
to turn up my stream for the first time.
Hard drive. Is it an SSD?
Is it the graphics card?
Is it the CPU?
And here's the RAM. Let's go.
Let's go. My first stream.
I'm gonna open up a bunch of fucking
Fortnite boxes. No.
Here we go. Boot it up.
Turn it on. What's wrong with it?
Open up the phone. Uncheck
first house from map app.
Click to enlarge the map.
Oh my. This is a coin game. Okay.
House one. House two. House pizza. Taxi.
Waiter. Pet shop.
Okay.
Cat shop.
Oh. Okay.
That was fun. I unchecked it.
How do I turn the computer on?
Register on the Blender website?
What's wrong with the keyboard? Go to
the club. I'm not going to the club right now.
I'm busy. I'm trying to set up my first fucking
Fortnite stream. God if I only knew
that I was going to play this today. Fuck me.
Shit.
I would have recorded a fucking full video
of like me streaming Fortnite.
And like when I zoomed in to like start
the stream I would just play the video. God damn it.
What the fuck am I thinking?
Turn it on. Am I doing something wrong?
I need to eat food.
I tried to buy an ice cream. It didn't let me.
A case? What's wrong with it?
Oh.
This thing is slow.
Protecting flash. Generic.
Welcome. To
stomach growling noises.
What the hell is that opening sound?
This computer sucks.
You're not my type.
What is this?
Stream calendar?
Let's see by internet speed. It's pretty bad.
It's really bad. I'm going to have to do
soar enough.
Alright. Let's see how good my
upload and download is.
Yeah. It's pretty bad.
You can't stream with a connection that's
this bad. You can't stream.
You can't stream at like 400k
up. It doesn't work.
Even Hearthstone would look bad
at that setting. What's wrong with me?
Okay. Register on the blender.
Can I change the background? I want to make it like
carnage or venom or something. Not this.
Alright. Let's go back. You have to eat.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Can I order food? Oh no.
Scratch. Food shop.
See? Okay. I'm going to get delivery.
Zone hub or coward?
I'm not a coward. I mean, I'm going to
blank out the screen to make sure there's no like
naked people. Alright. Banana split.
Burritos. Croissant.
Alright. Let's get a burrito.
My cart. Burrito dish. Complete
payment. Alright. Where is it?
We will deliver your order to your home as soon as
possible. Our courier will ring your bell when it reaches
your address. Due to some problems, we can only accept online
payments. Alright. Well, we'll hurry up.
I have to buy a toilet?
Zoo tube.
Where do you buy taxes?
What the fuck?
Oh my god. I thought that was in real
life that scared the shit out of me.
I was like, who's here? Why are you here?
Alright. Hold on. I got to get off the computer.
Oh, too real, man. Too real.
Make it something goofy.
Okay. Yes, I'm here.
Oh, ugh.
Alright. Thank you. Didn't even put it
in a bag. Worst
fucking Uber Eats driver.
Okay. Eat. Okay. How am I doing?
I need to go to the bathroom.
You ate the plate, too. Yeah.
I should do my toilet urgent.
I don't have a toilet, man. You keep saying that.
What the fuck just happened?
Alright. Turn the computer on.
Do you have people walking by this window?
Hey, Klawski. Thanks for the
10 community subs. Appreciate it.
Move your desk, please.
Find a toilet. I'm going to have to
buy one. There's an outside
outhouse. Is there really?
Alright. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Ooh. What the fuck?
Outhouse. Where is it?
Do you know where the bathroom is?
Where's the bathroom? I need a bathroom.
Excuse me, sir.
Do you know where I can find a bathroom?
You scares me. Do you know where I can find a bathroom?
There is no outhouse.
Joe Biden?
Ooh. Bathroom. Bathroom.
You got a bathroom in here?
Shit. Wait. You can buy stuff?
This is like a computer place.
Isn't this the guy that sells ice cream?
Uh, I'll be back.
Why are there no toilets?
Thank you, Sakamoto, for the 10 community subs.
Where's my house?
I have to buy a toilet. That's the only way
this is going to work. Thanks for the subs though, really.
Okay. Wait, I didn't turn
it off. I didn't turn it off. I didn't turn it off. Why didn't I turn it off?
Oh, my stream deck's wrong.
My stream deck's wrong. There we go.
bucks. Wow,
dude. You don't
$180 a month?
Let's go, boys. No.
Let's not go. Job King.
I have to go to the Blender. Wait, wait.
No, no, no. Fuck this. We're going to Blender.
Whatever the hell that is. I think that's a
dig at Mixer.
I'm going to take a shit. I need to buy a better
internet. This internet's so bad.
This is triggering such a response
in me. How many times have you been sitting
there with like your phone or like a device
and it just does that and you just rage?
thousand people are watching streams right now.
Okay. Wait, am I on here?
I mean, is Zerma
on here? Is Zerma on here? Is Zerma
985 on here? Let's find out. Come on.
Come on. It's a
play on like all streamers.
I got to be on here. Come on, dude.
Let me see.
I'm not important enough.
Alright, so let's watch
what game is this? The thing, The Witcher?
Everybody's at the same
part of The Witcher 3.
You all started your
streams at the exact same time on launch
day. Okay, well,
register. Enter. Oh, okay.
Registration complete.
I have to scan my finger print.
Alright.
Here comes Zerma. Login.
Zerma.
Do I have to start my stream? Become a
partner. I have to stream for a while
first, don't I? Dashboard
followers. That's my stream key.
That would be so bad if that was how it
actually worked. Can you imagine if
it was only four digits?
You would be able to just guess half of the
people's accounts. Okay, advertising
revenue. Lenders share. Seventy percent.
Expected earnings. Subscription goal.
Average live viewer is zero.
Alright, let's...
I should do my toilet. That's not important.
Ad duration. No, no, no. No ads.
No ads in the very beginning. Stream name.
That's stream one. That's not going to bring any eyeballs.
Right? Like, aces only.
How do I stream?
Free subscription to one streamer.
Special in-game loot.
Get free games every month.
How do I stream? Become a
partner. Get invited to special streamer
events organized by Blender.
Okay. Blender shares drop by
fifteen percent. Faster Blender
support. Chance to join streamers
recommended by Blender. Oh, I need to have
four hundred live active viewers and
a hundred subs. Oh.
Well. Download the OPS
program from the app's website.
Why is this way more detailed than I thought it was going to be?
Apps? Go get the OBS.
Buy a microphone.
Send all money to your
credit card from the bank app.
Steam. An application that you can
download and play. Okay, we're going to do OBS.
Oh, my download sucks though.
This is going to take so long.
This sucks. Buy a microphone
from the Zamazor website.
Watch something. Alright, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay. Buy a microphone.
From Zamazor.
I'm very hungry. Hold on.
Where's Zamazor?
Buy a microphone from the Zamazor website.
Oh, there it is.
Why is it not Zamazon? Oh, right.
Because it actually says Amazon.
If you make it Zamazon.
And I'll buy a toilet too.
Okay. We need
furniture.
Toilet's furniture.
Yes, it is. Thank God.
And a
What else? We need a microphone.
Look at this thing.
Like a WWF mic.
I need the cheap one. I don't have any money.
This is a really bad rating.
Quality sound in this microphone.
97 bucks. Get it.
Alright. Toilet and a microphone.
Only the essentials from Amazon.
I can't afford it.
Shit. Okay.
We can't have a toilet.
A cheaper toilet.
Do they have cheaper toilets? 420.
Oh, 215. Here we go.
Alright. When do they show up?
Give me my microphone. Give me my toilet.
Oh, here it comes. Don't ring the bell, please.
Oh, no. That wasn't it.
Download Fortnite.
Hold on. I can't
download Fortnite yet.
Wait. Does this take like a couple of days?
I'm sure it does.
Alright. I can just send money to a credit card.
Oh, this is my shitty computer.
I gotta go to the bank app.
No Amazon Prime.
Pepe left.
Alright. Fuck this. I'm gonna
Where's my bank?
Way too many apps. Get rid of that shit.
I don't have enough money to do a ZornHub account.
What happened to the burrito?
Okay. Money transfer.
Complete the transfer. I now have $800
in my account.
I need to transfer to my credit card.
Transfer to card.
All your money.
So I've got $918 on this
credit card. That's enough to buy a ZornHub account.
Why did that not work?
Didn't that be a quest?
Don't fucking do it.
Oh, on the phone.
Why use the phone app when you have access to the desktop
application? They're always ten times better.
Alright. Transfer to my account.
Like $70.
Now I'm gonna transfer all this. We're gonna open up the bank.
Where's my bank account?
Send all money to your credit card.
Thank you.
Sleep and save the game. Sure thing.
Now deliveries will be there. Cough.
Murmur. Turn left.
Okay. I did it.
I need to order some food, too.
Delivery? Oh, what?
I gotta order food. I gotta order a lot of food.
I'm gonna get like five things.
It's in the dumpster. Okay.
I gotta go to food shop.
And I'm gonna order like three burritos.
I'm gonna order two Big Macs. Two McChicken sandwiches.
A large fry and a large Coke.
Get the German meal.
Lamb rack? Mushroom bucket.
Ugh. Who would order this?
Just only
mushrooms?
Octopus balls?
Parfait? A pierogi?
Of just a whole pig? It's $8.
Baked beans.
Alright, we're gonna just get a shitload of these.
Alright, we're gonna get a bunch of beans and candy.
And some dog food.
Don't we have a dog? No, that was the other guy's house.
Alright, wait, wait. Get some actual food.
Okay.
When you get a post-bates
or Uber Eats or like a Grubhub order like this
you're just like, come on, dude. Like, fuck you.
Am I really gonna go get you
12 cans of beans and like
a bag of dog food?
Come on, man. That's a lot of money.
I'm very hungry.
Three whole pigs.
I wanna see them put this over here.
I'm gonna be the-
Dude! The smile's on the box!
Oh shit, hold on.
Oops.
Don't throw the microphone.
Alright, hold on. What the fuck?
Hey!
Okay, I ordered-
I ordered enough food for the Super Bowl party
I'm gonna have.
Let me put this down.
What is this thing? This is like a bar of Rice Crispy Street.
Alright, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Wait, where's my other Amazon order?
Okay, no. Pick that up.
Alright, where's the bathroom? I don't have a bathroom.
I think this is supposed to be the bathroom
but this is my streamer room.
So, you know, whatever.
Press to make your toilet.
I have to go again.
Twice.
I've had- Hey, do not-
Everybody that's freaking out right now is saying, what the fuck?
No. How many times have you done that before?
You did a full 30 or 40 second piss
and then-
Okay, here comes another one. Here comes another full
30 second piss.
Okay, I gotta eat this whole pig.
No, my mic!
I have so much food.
Do I have a fridge?
Does this food go bad?
Okay, I got a lot of canned food though.
What does this build?
Uh oh. What? Okay.
Let's just gonna have to stay there.
Alright.
I'm not doing this all day.
This will work eventually.
This is canned food, it's fine.
I just ate the dog food.
Didn't throw this dog food.
Candy!
I can't even pick these up.
I was just seeing if I could break the glass.
What the- Hey, come on.
Wait, I can do- There we go.
Candy Andy.
That's me.
I feel so dirty.
Look, just let me get one stream in
and I'll make millions.
Doesn't matter.
Back up, back up.
First person sims.
Okay, I did it. Turn the computer on.
I'm ready for my first stream.
Your P gauge replenished all the way.
Okay, I've got OBS. Stream key.
Link your blender account and start streaming.
Set the highest quality broadcast based on your current upload speed.
Alright.
I don't need any more food. Come on, hurry the fuck up.
What's the stream key?
It was 1390, yeah.
Blender.
I have OBS.
1394.
1390.
Okay.
Oh, shit. Stream quality.
144p.
Show cam.
Oh, I don't have a cam.
30 fps, I can't handle anything else.
Recommended bitrate, 700.
Stream category.
Okay, just chatting. Stream settings.
Okay.
The lowest bitrate you can have is 100.
The lowest bitrate you can have is 100?
Oh.
400.
Oh, fuck. I wasn't ready.
Just like everybody's first stream, okay?
No one's watching the stream.
Wait silently.
Listen, every single person that
started a Twitch account, there's somebody here.
Yo! How long is the stream?
Just...
Just messing with some settings.
You are obese.
You are...
Yeah, sorry for that. Or you are
all stupid.
How many people here listen to music?
No, I don't like music.
Drop, drop, drop. You can't even
speak properly. I think throw your computer in the trash.
Fuck you, buddy.
Go watch another stream if you don't
like it. Oh, wait.
I banned that person?
Two viewers fight each other.
Warn them. Say, easy. Cut it out.
I feel so dirty.
If I wasn't sleepy. What's up?
Hey!
There's someone who says he can never be
a streamer. This does not concern
him at all. I think he's right.
Stream a game.
Oh, shit. Hold on. Okay.
Uh, game.
Wait, I'm lying. I'm faking
the category. There's someone who says he can
never be a streamer. That doesn't concern me.
I need a game. Hey!
You ever seen this before?
Speedrun
ban incoming. Donate
received. Have you ever...
Have you ever been stealing?
Never.
First stream. I'm gonna get banned.
Wait, I'm getting donations.
Hey!
Why are you hacking me?
L, R,
R, L,
O. What happened?
You have been hacked. You lost
$200. How?
Have you ever been stealing
one day?
What are these? Okay.
I am about to get
banned in real life
in the game while I'm
pretending to get banned in the game
on the fake stream.
Oh, the stream died.
What happened? I passed out?
I got banned?
Oh, well, whatever. We'll be back tomorrow.
I got six viewers though.
I'm fucking hungry.
I need to download some games tomorrow.
Alright, fucking move this goddamn thing.
There. Alright, now move this.
Much better. Get a camera?
Get a camera
and go to Zornov.
My fucking god.
I'm never gonna, my career is never gonna
take off. Hey, Princess Hotcakes,
thanks for the five community
subs.
Thanks for the five subs. I need to take a shower
too, but hold on.
Ooh, a pig. Alright, what does heat mean?
Any air conditioner? Alright, I need to
wait, download some games. How tired am I?
Okay, wait, I have energy.
I need to download steam and then I have to download a few games
so I can stream a game. 3080?
Okay, don't stream yet.
Nope.
Ooh, dude.
Somebody comes over your house.
Your mom comes over.
Your parents are over your house.
Computer turns on. That's the last thing that Mozilla saved.
And you fucking hit back wicked
quick, but they saw. They saw.
They know. Oh, I can do cryptocurrency?
I can buy houses.
Why is there so much in this game? Okay.
Apps.
Zorn, were you watching Zorn?
Zno. Zom.
Zai was not.
Okay, just download them all on Spotify.
Enhance your stream with music and sound effects.
Stream Lap.
You can see the donations and subscriptions that come in, okay.
Oh, virus scans.
Cryptocurrency Miner.
And a VPN.
Wait, what?
We're going to think we used access websites where accesses are restricted.
That's not for security purposes?
VPNs are snake oil.
Zokey. Zokey, dude.
Wait, let's watch YouTube.
What can we watch on YouTube?
I'm going to call the fucking cable company.
I have to upload a video.
I don't have any videos.
Aw, shit. Okay, I have to record videos.
Alright, where's my apps?
Come on, Steam, hurry up.
Zermacraft or Zagat.
Please take a shower.
Alright, Steam's almost ready.
I'm going to say fuck this joke.
I'm sorry. We're just having fun, man.
Alright, Steam.
TheMitcher3.
CarStryka.
Fallgang.
CyberPrank.
ThePastOfUs.
DarkSouls. Yep.
RocketSucker.
Fallgang. Alright, I can't afford anymore money.
We're going to be a DarkSouls.
Fall Guys.
And Rocket League streamer.
And we're going to preorder the
$120 CyberPunk277
Keanu Reeves Figurine Box
that has the ten
figures in it in the art book and it wastes 42 pounds! 42 pound art book that's
right. Ooh library do I have any games? No. Quite the selection on Steam. Okay
those are downloading. Okay Streamlabs. I got donations. Enter your stream key. You
don't give your stream key to Streamlabs. The streamers look very nerd.
Ban that fucking guy. Don't let him come back. Ooh scan for viruses. I got hacked
remember? Like just scan them all in. I did go to Zornhub a few times so I
wouldn't be- oh uh oh. The funniest part when you run this on somebody's computer that
doesn't know anything about computers is this looks like this and then it jumps
up to like four or five hundred in ten seconds. Doesn't look that bad until it
gets halfway through. These are also people that have probably never cleared
their cache, their temporary files, their browser history ever. You could literally
like on like your grandmother's computer you could probably see a website in her
history that she went to like in 2013. What about the other five viruses? What's
this bullshit? Scan it again. Do it again. If you're not fully clean then what's the
point? They're just gonna multiply and you're gonna get more viruses. You gotta pay
for those. You do? This computer is cleaner than you are. For now. For you. So
what happened? Did they just went away? Oh a five gigabyte hard drive. That's pretty
pathetic. What year is it? All right, spottery. Uh, is it just songs? Okay, well it's just on
there. Wallpaper! Oh yes! Like I'm on the moon. Cool. All right, I like that one.
Here's your mining stream key. All right, shut this off. I don't
want to listen to music. Tutorials. Stream, game stats, mining, internet speed. Oh wow
it's all here. Gambling? Bills? Oh, okay cool. All right, what was I doing? Oh yeah
games games games games games. Okay, we're steam. Okay, I'm still not done downloading.
How big are the downloads? What the fuck? They didn't even start. Download on C.
What do I get? 50 gigs. I want Fall Guys and Dark Souls first. Cyber Prank 2066 is
that's a huge game. I need a, I need another, I need a full hard drive to put
this on. All right, we're gonna start with Dark Souls and Fall Game. I got 200
bucks. Let those download while I use the bathroom and eat some beans. I need to go
sleep. All right, those downloads will be ready when I wake up. Nightmares? All right, we're
gonna do our first gaming stream today. Steam. Okay, still not done. Jesus. Okay,
what, how do I get faster? Internet, internet speed. If you're tired of late
loading of pages of poor quality streaming, buy a new internet package.
There's a website where you can buy an internet package. You can also buy in
daily turbo packs. I need to take a shower. I haven't taken a shower in three
days. Okay, where's that app? What's it called? Amazon. Can you buy a shower on
Amazon? You can't, right? You can't buy this big, like appliances like this. I can
buy a full shower on Amazon. I don't have enough money to do this. Bridge. I don't,
I don't have enough money for a bathtub. Where's a, what about a shower? Air
conditioner. Stands. Bed. Fireplace. Fridge. Shelf. Sofa. Bath. Toilet. Washing
machine. Go on, just zed it. How do I clean my body? VR headset? I'm gonna have
to be dirty for a little while. I can't clean myself. Go shower in the
neighbor's house. That's actually not a bad idea. I'll, I'll bring some, uh, I'll
bring an offering. Can I like spray myself with the washer fluid? I feel so
dirty. What do you think I'm trying to do? Okay, this is, this is like a rust.
That's not even, these are, this is rust. This is, this is, I'm playing on a rust
server. Hey, hey, hey. You have a bathroom? You smell disgusting. Get out of the
shower. I just ate a handful of beans with my hands in front of them. Is this
his car? I wanna, I'm not disgusting. You're disgusting. What are you talking
about? Bite with my canine into the top of the can and like cartoon around to get
the lid off and then reach in with my bare hand and eat it with the other one.
Can I play, I need some money. Almond Jerry, yeah. Okay, are these done? This is
what it felt like. Some of you guys don't know, but this is what it used to be
like. Back in like the mid 90s, most people had a 28.8k modem. Of course, if
you, if you were really, really, you were doing well, you had a 56k modem.
Some people had 128 and that was just holy shit. You mean that you can open up
your email and load all of your emails in five minutes? You could not download
anything. A 12 gigabyte download? No, no, you didn't download video games. They
came over a series of like 12 disks if they were big enough. Quick, make a World
of Warcraft joke. 2004, my graphics card couldn't handle, wow. So I had to
play on the lowest settings and it still ran at like 20 FPS. That's all, folks.
I couldn't even load the mountains in the background. I had to turn everything
down. That was a nice internet clown. Thanks, man. Hey, I'm here to please.
Internet Clown, E-Clown, German at 85. Nice to meet you. That's a good handshake
you got there. Now what do I do? All right, I need to remember you're the
Bugs Bunny of Twitch. I feel like I'm more of a Daffy. Bugs like was kind of
smart and he like outsmarted everybody. Daffy just got angry and broke things
and acted like a child and couldn't comprehend basic sentences. But he was
funny. Daffy Duck. I don't know what cartoon character. I'm sure there's some
stupid online quiz where I can determine what cartoon character I am. I'm not
Elmo. I don't have any money. I just, I'm just going to sleep. Just go back to
bed. I can't, I can sleep after an hour. Do the quiz. There are so many. Which
one? What cartoon character are you? Hold on. No, but this is so, this is not
even accurate. This is, this like, these questions are so, so just basic. I don't
even know who the, what the character pool is. Well, what's the character pool
here? It's accurate. Okay. I don't, I don't feel like capturing this right now.
I'm just going to read it. Okay. You have a free afternoon. What are you going to
do? Sing, tidy my room, go exploring, and relax, relax. You're hungry. What do you
fancy? A zebra steak, a grilled cheese sandwich, sushi, or ice cream? Hmm.
Probably grilled cheese. Zebra steak. Favorite type of weather? Snow, sun, monsoon, or
blistering heat. I love the heat. Pick a sport. Baseball. Baseball. What's your
favorite class? PE, woodwork, art, or math? I literally didn't like any of these. I
hated all these. Where's the free period? If I had to choose art. Totally random
question. How are you feeling today? Which one emoji would you choose? The sad
face? The surprised face? The heart face? Or the eating face? The eating face. Okay.
How old are you? This is asking me how old are you? And the first one is under
six. I'm the oldest 16. I'm older. If you were a sweet, what color would you be?
Yellow, red, green, or orange? I'd be green. Green apple. You've got two plane
tickets. Pick a destination. Japan, Norway, America, or Africa. I've always wanted to
go to Japan. Pick a best mate. A snowman, a spaceman, a lion, or a bunny?
Uh, a lion. Pick a hairstyle. Spiky on top, short back and sides, ponytail, or buzz
cut. What's a spiky on top? Hey, how about a song to get the party started? Thank you
next. Baby shark, wannabe, or wrecking ball? I'm gonna go with, I'm gonna go
with, uh, uh, how about, how about wrecking ball? Okay, here we go. You, hey, okay, ladies
and gentlemen, we got to see, uh, an ad. What cartoon character am I? Let's find out. This
is just a gamified ad for the, we stopped doing that, gamified ad for, uh, Detective
Pikachu. It's just a gamified ad. Oh, I'm Pikachu. And then on the bottom, I don't
know if you can see that. It says image by Detective Pikachu movie on Instagram. So,
I'm apparently Pikachu. But I get, I think all of, all of us are. Is it Pikachu? Hold
on a minute. Spiky hairstyle. Pikachu doesn't have that. Lions are your best friends. Who,
what lion is Pikachu's best friend? Is it because I picked Japan? It's like a,
originated in Japan? I picked, my favorite color was green. Yellow was an option. I didn't pick
it. I picked green. Pikachu's not green. My favorite class was art and my sport was baseball.
I loved the heat. Pikachu doesn't like the heat. It doesn't retake the quiz. No. You guys, I don't
know. Some of you new viewers might not remember this, but we did like 40, like quiz personality
tests, like three years ago. Is it time to do it again at some point? I'll set that up. All right.
All right. We're going to do that tomorrow. I'm dead serious. Tomorrow, I'm chubby. Tomorrow's
going to be a fucked up stream. We're going to do, we're doing chubby bunny. I've mined and I'll do
a bunch of fucking cartoon character personality quizzes. This is your stream tomorrow. I'll get
those set up. At least downloaded yet. Okay. Steam. What the fuck? Hurry up and download.
Tomorrow is chubby bunny. Yep. I paused it. No, I didn't. It's gone. What about my VPN?
You can change your current location by activating the VPN. What's MBTI? Those are the Myers-Briggs.
I've taken it twice. I forget what it was. The first time I took it was ENFP. The second time
I took it, it was a little different. The first time I took it, I was like 20. The second time I
took it, I, it was different. It was like, it was like E N like I J or something. ENFP is what I,
the last, the one I really remember was ENFP. Are you fucking moron? You have to leave the
download window open. All right. Let's see if this person gets banned. It gets banned for real.
8.5, 8.6. Oh man. They're right. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Might have been a, might have been a
glitch. VIP in for the day. God damn it. I'm not going to mod them. You get VIP for 15 minutes.
I don't even know their name. I just saw their text. Make him the new Jerma. Give him the stream
key. I can't believe I had to actually have the, I slept two days in a row for this shit.
It was me. I, it could be anybody. Cause I don't know. Can you get off the PC while leaving the
window open? Um, hold on. I'm about to get Dark Souls. It could be in this very room. It could even.
Oops. Dark Souls. Oh, dark walls. Dark wall. Downloaded. All right. Let's go. Dark souls.
Does the game play itself? Turn on the stream. Hold on. I want to make sure my settings work.
I'm not going to stream Dark Souls at 400 K up. You won't be able to see anything.
What are you, what is this? This is Dark Souls. No, no, no. This is, this is what you get when you
torrent Dark Souls. This is what happens when you get the wrong torrent and then you go,
what is this? Oh no. What did I download? It's supposed to be Dark Souls and oh, I'm in trouble
now. I got to clean my computer. I got to reinstall windows. Am I about to beat the game?
All right. Hold on. Wait. I got to stream this. I have to stream. I got to have real reactions.
All right. Let's do it. Let's stream. Let's go. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to beat Dark
Souls on stream. On stream. You understand? Okay. Game. 700 upload. Shitty quality, but it's okay.
How do I cap show? Save the stream. No, I can't. Okay. Here we go. Stream going. Donation. Oh,
where's my stream labs? Hey, somebody subscribed. Thanks. What's up? Yeah. I'm just checking out
Dark Souls. I will subscribe to you with a credit card that I stole. Uh, don't do that. Checking out
Dark Souls for the first time guys. Welcome. You got chips and cola. Nice dude. What the fuck was
that? I just hear a, I think the 18 plus category should be added here. I'm looking for my favorite
streamer. Well, yeah, just hold on. Just wait, dude. I can mod them? Press the F key to ban.
Oh, that guy was looking for a favorite streamer. I'm not a sub. I'm using ad block. I don't send
donate. I watch for free. You're obese. Sorry. Spam, spam, spam. Shut up. Hey, can I reach you?
Yes. What are you, what can you do? What can I do for you? There's 12 people watching. Holy shit.
I gotta play. I will. Hey, don't fucking do that. How? What? Why? Why would you do that to me?
Bad stream. No, ban these people. I need a mod. Do not ever ban me. It's not a bad stream. Just
wait. I'm going to be dark souls on stream. I want to be a streamer too, but the blender refused my
application. I gotta get 400 live viewers. Fuck. Okay. Can I do, why does this feel like a real
stream? Oh my God. I'm so bad at this. So don't fucking hack me again. I just ran a virus scan.
Thank you. Jay1299552 for the sub. I appreciate it. I'm currently getting hacked right now.
Uh, you've been hacked. You are king. Thanks for the subs. Wait, where's my other, one viewer says
he's imitating another streamer. Whatever. All right. Get it off the screen. I can't see.
Don't show the IP by mistake. It's a single player cereal box game. Suggest a good TV show. Uh,
the boys. I'm watching the boys right now. It's pretty good. The boys is a pretty good show.
Really? I've just, season two is pretty crazy. I think you can be, I think you can be a good game.
Shut up. I have to beat this. I mean that in a very nice way. I closed the stream. No! Right
when I beat the level, Esports are ready. Can I save it and I will pick up tomorrow and I'll
continue my Dark Souls playthrough? Okay. I'm going to save it here. How many, I made some money.
Holy shit. I made 17 bucks. Never sub, never donated, ad block on, stolen laptop. Okay. Thanks
for the 17 bucks. That doesn't make any sense. Never subbed, never donated, ad block on. Okay.
Thanks for the $17. Pog, I made my coffee and I, thank you. I, how much money? That's pretty good.
I have a different, wait, get paid. If the incoming donates are over the $10, we instantly
transfer you to bank. Today, total donation, total account is $35.08. Thank you. I want a different
sound than the doot to do. Minus the $200 from hacking. I have to pay attention when the hack
happens. All right. Now I leave my cam on and accidentally keep it on while I sleep.
And I'll make way more money for some weird reason. Oh, I forgot to put the music on.
All right. I'm going to continue my Dark Souls playthrough tomorrow. You need the VPN.
No, didn't never sub, never donated. Except for right now, I gave more money than anyone has the
whole time you've been streaming. I need air, I need air conditioning. This dude left his cam on
and ate two cans of beans off the floor. All right. Let's go. I don't got any time to waste.
We're going to continue our playthrough. I'm coming back. Hey, you got to be, I'm going to
be consistent. It's me. I got 25 followers. Let's go. Ooh, what happened? Thanks for the sub.
I'm paying for this internet. Entertain me. That's what I'm doing. Who just came in? Hey,
thank you. Oof. Even though there are publications that I don't like, it's generally good. Sure.
Whatever. I don't know. I have no idea what that means. Where do you live? I live in Las Vegas.
Continuing my playthrough of Dark Souls. Streaming is going well. Yeah, it's going pretty good.
Someone is advertising. Ban them. What do you want me to do? Watching stream while eating plus
one. Do not ever ban me. Hold on. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What the fuck? KeckW. All right,
who is it? Somebody's going crazy here. Support. They subbed. Hey, thanks for the sub. This is,
all right. Those of you that are wondering, this is a great example of why I do not read
subs and donations really on stream. This is why. If you want a perfect example,
someone's advertising. Talk about his mother? No. All right, whatever I did. You never read
anything. Yeah, but I'm just saying. Hey, thanks. Wow, what am I doing? Dark Souls. Oh, hey. I
didn't like you before, but now it's fine. Hey, thanks. Thanks for the dollar. Okay, bye.
Dark Souls. Nice, nice. Pretty hard. Pretty hard part. I didn't get the, oh, I got to get the coin
in the middle. Fuck. Wait. Fuck. Why am I trying to entertain these people? They're not real.
Got it. I'm trying to entertain a fake audience. I bought chips and cola. All right. Hey, whoever
that was. Thanks. How do I get down here? That's how. Oh shit. I feel so dirty. You got to go quick.
Fuck. Stop. Just leave me alone. Leap. The streamer is bored. Hey, hey, hey. This is very,
very nerd. I'm your sub. Thanks for the sub. Hey, mouse a lot action. Thanks for the subscription.
Spallolalia. Thanks for the sub. I4dimwit. Thanks for the sub. Tom Unicorn. Can you say my darling's
name and say I love her? Sure. Uh, talk about your mother. Hey, listen. Thanks for the subscription.
Appreciate that. Uh, hey, have a good, have a good afternoon. You and your loved one.
Steemolotology. Thanks for the $7.08. I'm sending you the last money on my card. What are you doing,
man? Are you crazy? Hey, thanks for the $3.08. I made my coffee and I came here. Hey, thanks a
lot, man. Appreciate it. This is getting meta. I just have to beat this fucking level. How many,
how many people are watching? Am I even streaming anymore? Oh, fuck. Turn the stream back on. This
is a hard level. All right. I'll get back at it tomorrow. No progress. Omega low. No progress.
What does this mean? Oh, I have, I can level up, right? I can, I have a skill tree. Streamer skills.
Okay. Learn this one. I have an extra slot in my backpack. Oh my goodness. What do we got now?
Increase the number of miners you can buy. That's a crypto thing. Garbage motivation
decreases more slowly. Uh, increases your zoo tube video upload limit. I don't have enough money for
this. I'm so tired. All right. Hold on. What's wrong with me? That didn't sound good. I'm like
dying. I'm like sick because I won't take a shower and I won't sleep. Why can't I sleep? How do I
take medicine? Get paid out from Streamlabs. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Right, right, right.
Where's my Streamlabs? 45 bucks. Let's go. All right. How much money do I have? Where's my bank?
Total money owed. All right. Send all money to credit card. All right. I got a hundred total
money owed. Okay. I got $163. Bill Corp. You have a new bill that you have to pay. Oh shit. All right.
Hold on. I gotta, I gotta make some money. I need to get a job. Waste job. This is a job thing,
right? Workers. Job King. Just gamble. That's blackjack. Easy money. Don't tell me that. I
have $85 in my account. You don't tell somebody with 80 bucks to their name that blackjack get
money. That's horrible. Why are you telling me that? Okay. Cashier, taxi driver, courier,
Uber driver, waiter. We're going to be waiter. We'll get tips. We'll send you a message three
hours before the job. Let's go to work. Waiter. I used to do this, you know? I was a waiter.
I need to take a shower before I go to work. I wouldn't want to be waited by this guy.
I have probably have stink lines following me around. I'm going to get thrown out.
I'm going to walk in. Oh, come on, dude. Leave me alone. Leave me alone. You've done this three
times to me now. What did I do? D, M, A, G. D, M, A, G. Okay. Is that hack blocked? Come on. Like,
what the heck? I'm just trying to stream and just hang out. Come on. Don't do that to me.
Play DMC2. Like, right now? What is horse? Yes. No. Horse racing. I got out. I made it out.
It's too easy to do this. I need a better internet package before I do that. Give me ace. Oh,
shit. Okay. I need to go to work. I need to... Okay. Wait. I need to sleep. I need to sleep.
I have to take a shower. Okay. Eat. Where are my cans? Where's my candy? Why did I lose health?
Fuck. What's wrong with me? Why is my health... Why am I dying from eating beans?
What? I'm going to die. I'm going to die. I'm going to die. I have two health. Why do I have
two health? Why do I have two health? What happened? I can't go to work today. I have to eat
something. I need some medicine or something. I need to pay a bill. Oh, shit. I used it on
Blackjacket. Oh, shit. My stomach. Only eating beans and candy is probably not very good for you.
That's true. I can't even buy food. I'm fucked. I'm fucked. I'm fucked. What? Hello? Welcome.
What is it? Your waiter job will start at 13. Please be at work. Oh. What time is it? I got
to go to work. I got to go to work right now. Turn off the computer. P. Take a shower before
you go. What? In what? Where? Where's work? Get water from the toilet tank. I got to go to work.
Where's my maps? Okay. Work. Waiter. Okay. Let's go. Eating beans and candy. Oh, shit. I have to be
a streamer, man. A fucking week of just eating canned beans and like trolley worms. What? Oh,
my goodness. All the cars are on the road. I got to get to work. Do I have gas? Oh, shit. All right.
Hold on. I'm good. It's the first day you look out the window, you see this. Is that the new
waiter that we just hired? I think it is. Oh, fuck. Okay. I got to go to work. Fuck. I didn't mean to
do that. Watch out for that school bus. Where's the entrance? Where's the restaurant?
Why am I going into work with no nourishment? I have like my vitamin C level is probably zero.
Okay. Get out of here. Okay. I'm ready to work. What happened? Wait. What time is it? What time
is it? 13? What? I'm like four hours late for work. Wait. Did I work? How much money do I have?
I did work. Where's my money? I don't have any money. Wait. I have $136. What? What the fuck?
You need, I need to buy pills. What? You're saying my car is in the way? You're driving
on the sidewalk. What the fuck are you talking about? Okay. Let's go. All right. Back home.
I can't believe I fucking read that. Jesus Christ. Leave me alone. I'm trying to,
I'm trying to just live, man. All right. We need to go home. Should I go get a pizza or something?
Wait, I need, uh, get away from me. Okay. I need, um, dealer. Who has medicine? The dealer, right?
Okay, dude. All right. Leave me the fuck alone. Oh, it's not, he's not even, he's not beeping at me.
All right. Let's go get some medicine. Dr. App on phone. Oh, this is Tinder. Oh shit. Okay.
Current weight, calories consumed. Uber, no. Where's the doctor app? You're eating how many?
Wait. Okay. I mean, I got to go to get drugs. It's 83 pounds. Actual shortcut. Wow.
You are literally playing Rust. I know it's bizarre. How are you doing? I need medicine.
I need medicine. I need medicine. I'm going and going and going and going and going and going
and going and getting it. I'm getting medicine. I need that medicine. You smell disgusting.
All right. We're going to play blackjack that we have nobody by bath. Wait, can I eat in here?
Can I just eat? Can I have, I need medicine. Is there actually a doctor? Use the neighbor's bath.
I don't think I could even go in neighbor's houses. I can't go into other people's houses guys.
Nothing in the trash. Trash motivation. What does that even mean? Can I dump that on me? Wait. Oh,
I can't just spray this all over me. All right. Shit. I just, I'm going home. Where's my house?
You can go to like the hacker's house. Where's the house? All right. Can you shut that music off?
I need to buy a bath. Don't eat any of this shit. It's going to make me puke and I'm going to die.
Okay. I, how much money do I have? I need medicine. Yeah. Okay. Can I buy medicine from Amazon
workers, taxes, bills? I have to pay bills. Let me just pay my bill. Get pet medicine,
buy scratch tickets, due date. Okay. Pay that. Not enough balance on the credit card. Oh, fuck you.
Here we go. All right. Pay my bills. I got a hundred bucks left. What can I, I need money.
Laugh my ass off. Get scratch tickets. No, I'm buying medicine. Guys, I haven't streamed in
three or four days. People have been waiting for me. Okay. Medicine. No. VR headset. Clothes.
This is not, I can't, I need medicine. This is what he did on break. Tax, pet shop, feedback,
car dealer, food. I wonder if it's food. Buy a dog. You think I could take care of a dog right now?
I have a hundred dollars in my bank account and I'm about to die. And you want me to buy a dog?
All right. Come on. Come on. Oh, that's 50 bucks. That's a thousand bucks. I just made like five
grand. Oh no, you have to match them. I like this game. This game's like fun. Oh, okay.
I gotta buy food. What's like a healthy food? I need, what do I buy? Where are you supposed to
buy medicine? I need to shower. How much is a bath? 400 bucks. Should I spend my remaining day on
Zornhub? Well, I got one HP. I just want to go to Zornhub and open up a hundred tabs.
How about clam soup? That's pretty good, right? Just Zornhub to death.
All right. Clam chowder. That's going to be good for me. What else?
No, I can't say that, but that's funny. Asnet blender freelancers.
Please buy a shower. It feels bad. What the hell? Hold on. Okay. All right. All right. We got that.
We just got that for free. I'm out. Oh yes. Okay. Clam soup. This is going to be filling and delicious.
Not really, but kind of. I need medicine. Okay. Guys. Hey, I'm live. Swearing prohibited? Nope.
You can say fuck. Hey, hold on. Hold on. Hey, someone's trying to teach you how to stream.
Pretend to listen. Hey guys. Amazon prime. Whoa. What the heck? Weird. What just happened?
Oh, thanks for the $5. Magnus, no effing way. Guys, I am primed to play Dark Souls.
I'm feeling primed and ready to play Dark Souls for you on stream here right now.
My favorite characters. Oh, what the heck is this? One of my favorite characters ever is
Optimus Prime from the Omega bots, whatever the fuck it is. I don't even know. Let's get some music
on. 37 viewers. It's pretty cool. You guys like the tunes? Yeah. You know, my favorite. I love
prime rib. Oh, what's this? Somebody's gave money. I always thought of prime rib. Thank you for the
prime. Canine. Thanks to the $1.04. Hey, and Russophobia. Thanks for the $5. If you never
make money, do you keep streaming? I don't do this for money. I pretend to not do this for money.
Yeah. I tell you that I don't do it for money, but of course I do. Oh, $20. Stop the presses.
20 bucks from you. Thank you. They say 20 bucks. Simp, simp, simp, simp, simp. Thank you.
Go ahead. Okay, guys. I'm going to end stream. Thanks for watching. I'll see you guys later.
Yeah. Stream's still on. Hey, it's been a fun stream, guys. Thanks a lot. I'll see you guys
some other, probably next in a couple of weeks. All right. Let's fucking go. How much money did I
make? Let's go. 23 bucks. What do I have for money? All right. I got how much money? I got
to open up my bank account. 203 bucks. Okay. At this point, it's not even like scary. I'm just
annoyed. You do it so often that it doesn't even bother me. Okay, cool. I'm going to block you.
XRCL. Okay. Thanks, dude. Change your password. Why would I? I got 200 bucks. Shit. I need to eat
food. Quickly. Don't eat those beans. I need to order Uber Eats. Something really, really expensive.
We get a bathtub. We get a bathtub. I can finally clean my body. Okay. Clean, clean, clean, clean,
clean, clean. I need to eat first though. No, eat first. You're running out of luck. Not yet. Okay.
Bathtub. Go on Amazon and get a bathtub. Repeat bet. No. Once we get to the bathtub threshold,
that's when we pull out. 400 bucks. Portable air conditioner. No, that's not what I want.
Although, sounds pretty nice. Bath. 400 bucks for this bathtub. Thank you. I will take it. Please
deliver it to my house. I have six dollars. But this is okay. I can go to work now. Wait.
Was I supposed to go to work? All right. I kind of. Sell your bath water. Guys, I'm not popular yet.
Oh, fuck. Oh my god. Food. Food. Food. I need six. Oh, shit. What do I do? I need to eat. I need to
eat right now and sleep. I need to eat or sleep. Which one? I don't know. I need something that's
cheap. Not the beans. The beans killed me last time. I lost 30 HP eating beans. All right. Food
shop. Food shop. Something good. Something healthy. That's less than five bucks. Something cheap.
Something healthy. Something that's less than five dollars. Not a donut. Land pudding. Fruits.
Melon bread. Miso soup. That's healthy as shit. Get two of them. I want two miso soups. This is
healthy. It's like fish broth. There's like chunks of meat in there and stuff. Yes. All right. Now
I gotta go sleep. Oh my god. I'm about to die. I'm actually about to die. Quick. Deliver it to me,
please. Deliver my bathtub, please. Sleep. I gotta ding. I think I just slept through work.
I'm sorry. All right. Miso soup. Okay. Wait. I gotta save this game. How do you save the game?
Okay. This is good for you. It's got like tofu. It's got broth. It's got like lentils. I don't
know what else. I've never had it before. I think I've taken one sip and I went, no. I don't know
it's good for you. I know it's pretty good. I got a text. I got bills. I don't. Okay. Those can wait.
Where's my bathtub? I need that bathtub right now. Check the dumpster. Oh shit. You're right.
Bath tub. Get it in the house. I need medicine. All right. I'll get you medicine in just a minute.
Just hold on. I have to take two baths in a row. Okay. Now we're doing just fine. I can buy the
medicine now. I don't have any money for medicine. I need to work first. What time is it? I gotta get
to work later. Hurry. Where's my car? It actually is an outhouse here. I thought that was bullshit
that you were lying to me. Where's my car? Where the fuck is the car? How much is medicine? Gotta
get to work. Gotta get to work. Gotta get to work. Gotta get to work. Gotta get to work. Quick, quick,
quick, quick, quick. Hurry, hurry, hurry, work. Hurry. You have to sign up for the job?
Didn't I already do that? Why are you cutting me off? I don't have the job? How? It's not a crash
joke every time. I'm trying to, it's, I have to get there by 13. Why does everybody use military
time? I want to use just, just 12 hour time. I thought I was going over the building. I'm here
and I'm clean and I'm energized. Sick. 136 bucks. Let's buy medicine. Quick. Excuse me. Soon gasoline
will run out. I have to buy gas. What? Oh fuck. That's not good. Okay. I gotta get gas. Where's
the gas? Gas station. Oh wait, there's a gas station right next to the house. Isn't there?
There is. Get off my screen. This is life simulator, but you are a streamer. Uh oh.
I need medicine. What a perfect time for that to pop up. You know, I think I need medicine.
My car is just a little dirty. All right. Gas. How much is gas? I've rented a gas
driveway. Okay. Perfect timing. I need medicine. Okay. I want, I don't have anything. I have to
put something up. Where's, I don't have any drugs. What? Buy pill. What? 200 bucks? God damn it.
Sell the toilet. Not a bad idea. I come with a toilet. What are you going to give me for this?
92 bucks? Let's bargain. Or did I get? No, I, I give me pills. Okay. Good. I got medicine.
Here we go. Okay. It just costs $10 to use this toilet. Be serious. That's why I take a shower.
For God's sakes. Yeah. It's 10 just to use it. All right. I got, I need, I'm hungry. Do I have
any money? Pee into the shower. That's what I say. I don't know why that's so weird. Job king,
you wait a job with star. Yeah. Your employer can rate your work. Car assistance. Okay. Let's
bring the car you have. Add 25% fuel to your car. No, I'll just push it over there. What do I got?
I have $14. That's enough to eat and then stream tomorrow. Ice cream. No. Um, what do I got?
Delicious meal. I need fruit. I have two bucks. I'm very hungry. I know I ordered it.
Boo dollar Andy. Just wait. Just wait till my career explodes. What am I doing on hygiene? Good.
Okay. I got to sleep. I'm hungry and I need to sleep. Bean. Eat beans. I'm going to lose health.
It's 200 bucks for health. That's, I'm not doing that right now. Wait. Hello? Yep. Thank you. I'm
going to sell them the poster. That was not filling at all. Sell the beans too. Yeah. You want this?
How much is this worth? 43 bucks. You can do better than that. You can do better than that.
I'm going to, I want 50. I'll take 35. I'll take 35. I'll take 35. Thank you. I'll be back. You want
beans too? I got beans. I'll be back. Like blackjack. No, I don't have enough money.
Eat the beans. Beans hurt. They actually hurt. It's just, it's expired. That's why.
Expiration date. It looks disgusting. Well, let's see if we can sell it to that fucking dickhead
over there. Just take a, take one of those metal mesh cloths. The things that you scrape the bottom
you sync with and just scrape off the expiration date on the bottom. I got beans and they last
forever. Everybody knows he looks very angry. He looks very angry. Why? What the fuck? What the
fuck is happening in here? Why a cat? Just release them. Oh no. I can't get that. Can you move out
of the way? Whatever. I don't care. I don't care. I need to go to sleep and I need to stream
tomorrow and I'm going to stream. I'm going to be, I'm going to stream fall guys tomorrow.
Stream eating beans. Fall guys in 2020. I need to eat again. I need to pee. It's okay. I'll make
some money. Do I have any payouts? No. All right. I need to stream. Okay. I'm ready to start my
stream. I'm going to stream fall guys. Going on guys. I'm back. It's been kind of a wacky week.
I'll tell you. I'm going to play fall gang tonight. Beautiful girls add me.
Get the fuck out of here. He's very late. Yeah. Is there a lottery on this channel?
I don't think you can mod people. This takes so long to load. This computer sucks.
Oh, I have to work in three hours. That's okay. We're going to do a short stream.
Holy shit. This looks awful. This sucks. Like 10 FPS. Come on. I don't need people paying me
money though. It's okay. I lost like half my viewers. I'll get them back. Someone wants you
to close the stream. Turn off the stream dude. This sucks. Oh yeah. I made it through. That's
money. Your next word. It must be loving. It's loving. Welcome. Thanks everybody for sticking
around. How do I, what do I do? Your next word. Uh, loving. 31 viewers. I have, I'm hungry. Okay.
Hold on. Well, I just made, I made a lot of money. Let me see. Holy shit. That's a lot.
Subscribed. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the simp. Thanks for the money.
Get paid. That's 24 bucks. I'll take it. Someone praised you. Thank you.
You're streaming your stream labs. Yeah. I'm just waiting for somebody to step. Hey,
thank you SETI for the $4.05. My brother is watching you all the time. Hey, thanks a lot.
Support you. Thank you. Stream's going pretty well. I hate all of you. This is not a stream. This is
garbage. Be arrogant about it. I'm paying for this internet. Entertain me. I love these streams.
Thanks. Is there a lottery on this channel? I, sometimes I do a lottery. Depends on, uh,
kind of how I'm feeling. Hey nugget, thanks for the sub. Uh, we did a giveaway, uh, giveaway a couple
of hats a few weeks ago. So I'll subscribe to you with a credit card that I stole. I promise.
Dude, don't do that. Don't do that. That's fucked up. Don't, don't be like that. Hey, uh,
histogenesis. Thanks for the $4 and 20 cents. Appreciate it. I got to go to work and I missed
work. Thanks for the praise. I got 50 viewers. What are your chat commands? Uh, slow press keys
will break keyboard. LUL. Close the stream. Okay. Can I go to work? How much money do I make?
I just read that out loud and then I'm live. Okay. I got eight bucks. That's enough to eat.
He's out of energy. Okay. I need to put money over here and I'm going to work tomorrow. Bills.
I got a, how much money? Okay. I got 105 bucks. I'm doing all right. I got to get gas. Wait,
can I like say this never showed up? Can I just like do fraud and say like, hey, these 16, uh,
pigs didn't show up. Okay. I want a refund. Uh, go back. I need some food. I have a hundred bucks
so I can do some high quality food. Being a hundred percent with you. I made that doot doot
sound and I uploaded it in 2015. I mean, what do you mean? Okay. Burrito, clam soup. I need
something way better than that. I need like a seven star meal. By the way, seven stars.
What kind of rating system is that? Seven out of seven. All right. We're just going to get the,
this thing up here. Burritos is probably the best. I'm going to get two burritos.
Dog. The dog food is six stars. Oh, I should set an alarm. Okay. We're going to set an alarm for,
um, 10. So we don't sleep through work. Okay. That's my food. Get it. Goo goo gaga. Oh shit.
I'm starving. Thanks to the burritos. All right. We're good. I need to use the toilet. I got to
pay this guy to pee. Shit. Just get rich as fuck. What do you think I'm doing? I'm trying.
Let's pee down the drain. All right. I'll sleep and I'll pee somewhere in the morning. What's up
with, hold on. Let me read this. What's up with Jerma today? He started streaming today. It was
marked as Dark Souls, but he was just playing impossible games. Chat was incredibly slow.
Most of the people called him obese and advertised their own channel for some reason. No mods.
But the worst fucking thing is that I donated and asked him to say hello to my loved one and
he just insulted my mother. Anyone knows what's going on with him lately? Um, quite a lot,
as you can see. Omega lol. Oh my God. Omega lol real. All right. Send money to the card. Wait,
any money on my wallet? I don't have any money in my wallet. I can't pee. I can shit at work.
I can just pee at work. I always go to the bathroom at work. It's fine. I need gas.
I have to pay for that service. How much is it? Oh, I'll take an Uber. Set the destination where
you want to go. I can't take an Uber to work. I can't walk to work. I know why I gotta go.
Stop. I know I have to work. Leave me alone. Job king. Your waiter job starts. You're ready.
I know, I know, I know, I know. Take the bus. Can you? Wait, can I take taxi? Walk, dude.
I gotta ditch work and stream. Hey, surprise stream today. This motherfucker's got it out for
me, huh? Uh-huh. F-O-M-D. Blocked. This is by Lucas. The same Lucas. Leave me alone.
Please. I'm opening the stream because I had to do this. I love to, I love stream make
sound in background. Oh, I got you. Hey, chill man. I got you. Someone says they know where you live.
I'm gonna sue you. All right. Where do you, are you sure? Okay, I'm gonna turn it on.
Someone on chat, do you ever get bored? I'm trying to turn the music on. Shut up.
Okay. Hey, what's going on guys? Just chilling today. I get bored while streaming.
Sometimes it can be, but I like to try to be as cool as I can.
Just chilling. Hey, somebody just gave some money. Thanks a lot, man. What movie you like?
Um, I love, I'm big, I'm really into pornography. It's my favorite movie genre. Hey, thanks a lot,
man. Thanks for 22 bucks. Got a couple of subs here too. Uh, guys, chill out, please. Don't,
don't mess around in the chat, please. Thank you for the subs though, guys. Appreciate it.
You hate zootubers? No, man, I used to be a zootuber. All right, they're not gonna stop.
Just ban them. Just get them out of here. I mean, just guys, you can't, you can't,
stop fucking around. We like this stream a lot. Thanks for the two, uh, three bucks, man.
Appreciate it. Lots of subs here. Ban these people that are fighting.
I'm not into that. Cut that shit out, guys. Cut that shit out. All right, we're going sub only.
We're going sub only. Does donating support you better or subscribe? Well, that's up to you.
Stop fighting each other. Stop, why is it just fighting? What language does it do you speak?
Well, I speak English. It's what I'm speaking right now. Does donating support you better?
It's up to you, man. Let's do whatever we feel. Fucking stop fighting. Hey, uh, tick girl,
thanks for the sub. Vin Petro, four dollars and five cents. Appreciate it. We're just, uh,
chilling out here, hanging out. Thinking about doing a, uh, always support good streamers. Thanks,
man. Appreciate that. Bilbo, uh, toilet. Thanks a lot. CacW. Yeah, I love that email, man. It's so
cool. All right, so I'm gonna fucking end the stream if you don't stop fighting. I'm, I,
there's 75 people there. I'm banning half of you for fighting. Stop fighting. Who's, what happened?
Thanks for the sub, though. Thanks for the three bucks. Thanks for the three bucks.
Thanks for the sub, too. A lot of, a lot of subs today. Good morning. Hey, good morning. Uh,
speak from your past. Let's talk about the future. Probably gonna see Jerma Rumble live
on Twitch eventually at some point in the next couple of years. What song we got going on here?
Let's change the music a little. Uh, how about, uh, I want to be a little chill. We'll talk about
my past. One time I shit my mother's bed. I think I play a lot more talent. I think I'm more talented
than you in Fortnite. That's all good, man. I don't play Fortnite that often, so pull that out a
little. All right, guys. That's an, uh, I'll see you guys later. That's, uh, that's it.
I got the same stream title for like two months. Dude. All right. I got 60 bucks. He said, well,
it does say aces only. I don't even have Counter-Strike installed. Okay. I don't have
Counter-Strike. Why? I'm not even playing that game. Oh, rocket soccer. Okay. Let's uninstall,
uh, Fall Guys. Fall Guys sucks. How do I uninstall Fall Guys? You must choose the disc.
I want it on C, but I know no free space. How do I get it off? Uninstall it. I can't uninstall
the game. I need another hard drive. Are you kidding me? Well, I made some money though.
That's pretty good. Let's see. I got 145 bucks. That's enough of me to fill the gas with, fill,
add gas to the car, go to work. I'm going to go to work today. Oh, I got two, uh, gamer points.
Let's see what they do. Shit. I have, can I upload videos? Did I record any videos?
Zootube. I could get like ad revenue. A new coffee pasta, new coffee pasta. All right. Upload.
I don't have any recorded videos. I'm so tired. All right. I gotta, I get to start recording.
I'm doing all right. Let's go to sleep. Okay. Now I, I'm, I'm okay with food. I need to go
to the bathroom. Then I'm, I'm going to pay this guy, which is stupid to pay 10 bucks to use the
bathroom, but I'm going to do it. I don't have money in my wallet. I go to my, what are you doing?
What are the ATM? All right. Well, whatever. I'll just, I'll pee. I can't wait to have like
thousands of dollars in my bank account. It's going to be sick. All right, let's go.
All right. So how much, I have 25% gas. I probably should fill it up more.
Where's the actual gas station around here? It's probably one in town, right?
Are you going to play this all night? I gotta be real honest with you.
Probably. I was going to play Exanima. Exanima was the backup, but
I don't think we even need a backup. I'm, I'm kind of like completely engaged right now.
No, don't go back to the house. It'd be dumb. Don't break the car. I just saw the
mini map thing, the tool tip pop up and I was like, Oh, I go that way. Exanima is actually
awesome. Apparently it's changed a lot since last time I played it. All right. We need a real gas
station here though. I hope there's one here so I don't break down again and have to pay 80 bucks
to fill the tank. Internet cafe simulator. Was that another game that this person made?
It has to be. No, I've seen that. I've seen that before. I've seen it on steam. Okay. I need a,
I need gas. Bad. Like right now. Turn the car off. I need to go get gas before work. Where's
there a gas station? Okay. Gas. This one right up here. All right. Straight ahead. I'm out of gas.
I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. Please. I'm out of gas. No,
I'm not out of gas. Oh, I just barely made it. Jesus, man. This is so expensive. How much money
do I even have? All right. You don't have enough money in your wallet. Wallet? Just go to work.
I've got work in 20 minutes. Let's go. That's the kiss door. I'm not going in there.
Just live downtown. Can you add forehead at that end of that sentence, please?
I think I have the superpowers, I think. 136 bucks. Let's fill that tank. That should be in
my wallet, right? I just got paid. Yeah. All right. Fill this tank up. I don't want to get
gas ever again for this damn car. Let's go with half tank. Okay. That's going to get us a pretty
long ways. Open. Okay. Hold on. Go to the club. No, not this shit again. That guy just ran into
a school bus. So did you? No, the school bus ran into me. Is this illegal? Is it nudity in this
game? Hide screen quick. All right. Let me see if there's nudity. Is there nudity here?
Maybe you're a fire. This is lap dance area. I got to leave. That's fine. It's fine. It's
kind of resident sleeper in here, I'll be honest. React. React. Oh, sure. Okay.
Okay. Whoa, what's in there? Oh, I think there might be naked girls in there. No way, dude.
What's your naked girls? That was my mom? No, it wasn't. Go to work. Oh, shit. I forgot about
work. What time is it? No, I have to sleep, dude. No. You were at work. Yeah, I just was at work.
And then I went into that fucking snooze club. I mean, no one was even dressed up as tracer in
there. I don't like it. Don't hit this guy. Okay, I gotta go to sleep. And I'm very hungry. I need
a fridge and it's hot in here. How many complaints a minute can I do? You haven't shit in two weeks.
As it happens when you eat candy every single day for every meal, it kind of bunches you up a
little. What should you get from McDonald's? Hey, my order. Get the German 985. Don't say I'll take
the German 985 because they have no idea what the fuck you're talking about. That's two McChickens
with a little bit of mayo. Oh, sorry. Can't order that. Those don't exist anymore. Don't get the
spicy ones. They're not that good. It's a Big Mac. Sure. Get that. I'm too pissed off that they got
rid of McChickens to continue doing that little bit I was doing there. Maybe I should get a bucket
of mushrooms. Nachos. Octopus balls. Sounds good to me. No, they didn't. Yes, they did. There's no
regular McChicken anymore. It's only spicy McChicken. They don't have them. Yes, there is.
How come I can't get them? Spicy is better though. You're stupid. Wrong. I ate one today. They must
have been at a stock for like a month. I'm telling you. I tried. I don't hate the spicy McChicken.
Yes, I will. Spicy. Everything has to have spicy. Spicy McChicken. Spicy Big Mac. Spicy
soda. You put spicy in front of something. Apparently, it sells. I don't know why.
You know what? What's the difference between spicy McChicken and regular McChicken?
The spicy McChicken makes your nose run. That's it. I can open cases. Shut up, wanker.
Dude, let's open a case. CSGO case. Oh my god. Am I going to get the knife? Come on. Do it.
I just made some money. Dude, a green Mac 10. That sucks. It's not even purple.
I got mail. I got email. Do that on stream. I would rather you pull out every hair on my body
individually with a pair of tweezers over the course of a few hours than me to do an open CSGO
box stream. I would rather do that. Blender payment. I don't want to do that. I've done
that before a couple of times with TF2. Open them in crates. I don't like it. I don't want to do that.
Oh my god. Leave me alone. Open the crates for YouTube. Holy shit. That's genius, actually.
V-T-O. It's Lucas again. Yes, like clockwork, Lucas tries to hack my computer every three days.
I feel like it's automated at this point. He's just checking to see if he's using that password
anywhere else. I gotta go to work. All right. New rule. I'm not going to do any gambling until
I have at least 500 bucks and then I'm probably going to go all in on one hand. Wait, do I have
any parts I can sell? Oh, sell the beans to that guy. Wait, can I just go rob my friend's house?
He had a bunch of computer parts. Yeah. What happened to the beans? I put them in the trunk?
I didn't put them in my backpack? I swear to god. He in the grass? I don't think that's going to
work, man. Three bucks. All right. I'm not going to bargain for this. Of course I am.
Inspired beans. Of course I'll take $10 for that one. An extra 50 cents. Whatever. Give me that
money. Enough for food. I'm kind of obsessed with this game. I don't know why. Something about it.
There's like scratch tickets. There's blackjack. There's streaming. All right. What time is it?
I have to pay bills. What happens if you don't pay the bills? All right. I got 100 bucks.
Let's go to work. I've missed work, but it's okay. Lifetime weight change. I lost one pound.
Calories over the course of your whole life. I've only consumed 6,666 calories over the course of
a month. This is not in the game yet. All right. Let's go. I don't know. Let's go explore for a
little bit. No, no, no. Stream. I got streaming. What am I doing? This is streamer simulator.
I got plenty of energy. Let's go. We're doing a big 24 hour stream right now.
I'm beating Dark Souls on stream today. Let's go. What's up, guys? Today's the day. Dark Souls is
going to get completed on stream. Finally going to beat it. Favorite emote? Lul. I didn't like
that apparently. Fuck all of you. Oop. Somebody gave some money. There should be an 18 plus
category. All right. Sure. Fine. Oh, no. I went the wrong way. You're a king. There's some more
money. All right. I got to turn Spotify on. There. That's going to bring in the viewers.
How can I reach you? I have to ask you something. I don't want you to reach me.
I don't know who this guy is. Leave me alone. 38 viewers. I've got to get to 100 followers.
How am I supposed to get through this though? It seems impossible. It's not possible to do this.
Someone says they know where you live. Okay. Whatever. There's a definite bot user. I opened
a broadcast and it was not watched. This is weird. Fuck this stream. Can I just leave through
anywhere? I don't even know. Somebody's got collateral. Someone in chat insults those who
subscribe. Ban his whole family. Okay. We've banned his entire family. That's loud. I'm getting a lot
of donations this stream. I'm doing pretty good, I think. Honestly, I don't think I can beat this
level. How do I do this part? You can't beat this part. Green spots. Yeah. I got to go to that one,
but I can't even go past here. Go in the corner. Oh, fuck. Okay. What about... All right. I'll use
the... Thanks for the tip. How much money do we make? Cry. Cry. Cry. You guys have said that before.
You guys have done that. 66 bucks. Let's go. What if I turn the stream on and just leave the desk
and go to bed? Do it. Cry. Oh, I got to move this shit over. Cry. Cry. Cry. I got to get a webcam,
you're right. No more gambling. No gambling. I'm serious. No more $50 scratch tickets. I got to
get to over a thousand bucks. And hold on. I got to pay bills. Wait a second. This is bad.
Don't do it. Please go take a shit. I'm fine. Okay. We need to go to the bank. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I need to go to the bills app. I'm going to... Speaking of going to the bathroom,
I have to go to the bathroom right now. I have to do taxes too? Oh, man. I've got to do taxes.
Today, zero dollars. Pay it. Okay. Electricity bill. What? Electricity bill due date of this
penalty. Electricity bill. Fuck. It's taken all my money. I had to have the 200 bucks.
What about taxes? Didn't I just pay taxes? I'm hungry. I'll order something. Hold on.
2020. Taxes. Just like in real life. Due taxes. Total unrecorded money. Tax rate. We will send
your current tax to you as an invoice every four days. I have to pay taxes every four days?
Tax rate. What's this? Value added tax. What is that? I have 9% tax rate, but I have to...
What's this value added tax? 4%. Don't companies pay that? Isn't that like a company thing?
Why is it an individual thing? It's an EU thing. But I thought like companies paid this.
Why do I have to pay that? Companies don't pay shit. What's up? Excuse me. By the way,
what's going on with that, by the way? Go to work. I'm going to work. By the way, 120 hertz. Thank
you. 1080 monitor. Is that some kind of currency thing? No. No work stream. I'm beating Dark Souls
today, guys. He's still at 144p quality. Yeah, and I still pull in the fucking big numbers.
My stream toxicity is at 120%. Why? What are these? Oh, I have 26 subs. Cool. That's way over the
limit. All right, guys. I have to be nice now. That's not accurate. You guys are calm. The mood
of the stream. Let's just chill. Chill. Chill. Everybody chill. Let's get that number down.
Nice with the money. Everybody relax. We're just chilling today. Why is that toxic? I hate all of
you stupid nerds. I reported your stream. Why? Why are we so toxic? Everybody fucking relax.
It's boring. This stream is boring. I have two dollars. I cannot be a sub if I find money.
Why is everybody like this right now? The toxicity is too high. How do I calm everybody down? I need
more viewers. I only have 30. What happened? Good morning. Legend is back. I'm losing viewers.
25? That's it? I'm gonna do something crazy. Oh, no. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
Play music. Wait. Hold on. I'm trying to beat the game. Okay. Hold on. I'll get... Let's get...
I know. Wait. Wait. I know I'm supposed to beat this, but hold on. Oh, shit. My tax rate.
I don't want you guys to see that. Hey, I know how much you guys love this shit.
We're gonna open some cases on stream. Oh, people like that one, don't they? I got a really slow
connection. 27 bucks. I cannot watch this stream, but I leave my support. Thank you very much. Thank
you, too. Thank all of you. I'm an idiot because I sent money. No, you're not. Cry. Cry. 10 out of
6. I don't know what that means. Thanks for the 10. Oh, thanks for the money. Just read them all
quickly. Read. Read. Read. Read. Read. Read. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. All right. Here we go. Case opening.
Do not ban me. All right. Just minimize this. I got 78 people here, man. Come on. No,
minimize this. Okay. We're gonna open a super case today, guys. This is 50 bucks. We're looking for
blue. Come on. Give me that knife. Oh, too bad. Too bad. Too bad. Too bad. Dang. Oh, whoa. Thanks
to the subs, guys. I opened one case. Oh, offline subs. Pug. I've opened one case and end this
stream. I made it. How much money did I make? Seven. How is it 17 bucks? It's because Twitch
took 70. Twitch is taking 70. It's not Twitch. You spent it on cases. No, but that was... They
take... Didn't it say they take 70%? I didn't see what it was. Somebody tell me. Quick. Quick. Quick.
I didn't see. I didn't see. Somebody please. It's like a 10 second... Now he's just fucking with me.
Oh, my goodness. I don't have food. All right. I'm gonna go on a food shopping. I need a fridge.
I'm obsessed with this game. I can't stop. I'm gonna buy... I need a fridge. It's stressful.
If the donation's over 10, it goes to your bank automatically. Oh, okay. Yeah, but didn't it say
that they take 70, 80% of the money? It said that on the thing we were looking at, didn't it?
In the very beginning? That's for subs. Oh. Let's get three burritos. Why don't I go... I just eat
burritos and donuts and canned mealworms. Why can't I go to the grocery store? Waiting for the food.
I gotta pee so bad. All right. Let me pee. I'll be right back. Gonna eat this and pee. And I'll sleep.
Okay. How long does this last? What was it? Last storage on this thing. I just put burritos in my
backpack. They're fresh. Okay. It's probably fresh for a couple days. I would assume, right?
High genes. All right. Let's shower. Get some rest. All right. And I'll be right back. I have to
actually pee in real life. Be right back. Okay. It's hot in this room. It's hot in here.
Fuck Vegas. I'm moving. I'm out of here. It's too hot. I actually love it like this. I'm a
weirdo. I'm one of those insane people that really actually truly enjoys hot, hot, 100 plus degree
weather. Let's go back. What are we doing? What the fuck are these mods doing? The whole chat?
Is something wrong with it? Next game, please. No. Sorry. What's the toxicity of this chat? Yeah,
I wonder. 40? Maybe 30? 40%? I need a better microphone too. I need more money. I need
everything. Chubby bunny waiting room. It's happening tomorrow. You want your real fuckface
stream? It's going to be tomorrow afternoon. I sweated. This place is hot. It is. I like it
though. A billboard? Wait, can I advertise my stream on a billboard? What time are you going
to stream EU tomorrow? Probably around like 2 PM Pacific. That's, I don't know. That's, I don't
know. It'll be plus 10 hours plus 12 hours something EU midnight. You got to add 8 hours.
I live on the other side of the planet. I'm sorry. Add your ad to the various websites and video. I
can do advertising. Add duration one day. Do an ad for my stream for one day on the internet.
A billboard. One billboard for one day. Jerma. New concepts and fun streams are here. Hold on.
No, no, no, no. We need money. We need money. I need money. How we get money is we keep that stream
going. I need like two monitors for chat and stuff. What is this? All right. What was it?
Opening cases. People love that shit. All right. People love it. What can I do on stream that
people would like think is cool? We got to take a look first. Speed test bank. I could do scratch
tickets. Buy a house. All right. We'll play blackjack on stream, but not crazy amounts of money.
All right. Here we go. We're just going to be ASMR. I'll do that later. What's up, all you toxic
fucks? Today we're going to be playing the fart blackjack on stream. What is this? What amount to
be? What is this? I don't play blackjack. Oh, this is higher or lower toxic. We're reaching
levels of toxicity. You never thought possible. I'm going to give you guys some basic strategy.
Or how to. We're going to do a base. We're doing one dollar bets in blackjack here. Wish I did a
fucking thousand. Wish I did a thousand guys. I wish it was a thousand. I just got blackjack.
First dollar bet. Right. I can't even tell. I want to teach you guys how to play. Keck W.
Stream I enjoy. Thanks for the sub. I got 33 subs. Thanks guys. Okay. So we're going to,
we'll see what we get for a hand here. We'll get 11 versus a four. Now if I was able to,
I would double down here. I would double down, but I'm not able to do that on this particular
game, but we're going to hit this. That's 21. These are dollar bets guys. It's just kind
of hanging out, having fun with you. Oh, thank you. A la qual for the subscription. Appreciate that.
Someone realizes that you are sleepless. I stayed up all night watching porn. Thanks for 10 bucks.
How could you tell that by the way, this streamer is very, he's a nerd. Yes. All right. Let's do,
let's get a little bit crazy here. Let's go for a seven, a $6 and 90 cent bet. Cause we're a comedy
guy here. We make lots of funny jokes. That's a 20. I'm looking to stand on 20 guys. Always stand
with the 20 versus anything like that. And we won again. Cool. Fuck. I banned the wrong guy.
All right. Everyone relax. We're doing $20 bet. I got a two. Ooh, 21. I am the king of blender.
You have to pay me taxes. We're getting 91 viewers right now. I got more subs. I didn't like you
before, but now I do. Toxicity is going up. Should I just run with that? Do something to entertain
the audience. It's just a good movie. Fucking do something. Fuck 16. Oh crap. Crap. I thought the
cops were just here. It's like, what the fuck happened? Okay guys, this is for you. This is
for the stream. This is the big one for the stream. We just passed a hundred concurrent viewers,
$50 bet for the stream. Oh, and it's a good one. Oh, it's not a good one. We have to stand here.
Too bad. Oh no. I lost some money. Ooh. Okay guys, I'm going to, uh, I got, uh, I got to go.
Oh wait, how long has the stream been off? How long was the stream off for?
Was I even streaming? I'm watching some sick fuck like this at 144 P at 700 bit rate talking like
that and losing some money and then just ending stream every day like that. This is bizarre.
At least I got some more subs. You never turned it on. Yes, I did. I was getting, I saw the
view account. What's wrong with your voice? Are you imitating somebody or are you actually asking
me that question? Turn the stream right now to 144 P 700 bit rate. I don't think I could do that.
I would have to read. I have to turn the stream off and back on again. All right. I will,
I promise I will do that before this stream is over. I have no money. Get a loan. Holy shit.
Daily installment payments of 800 bucks. That's not going to work. I'll do it. I promise I'll do
it. It will break everything. Yeah, guys, we're like hanging out, having a fun time. I'm not just
going to turn the stream off because if I, here's the thing, this is what you guys, this is some
streamer insight for you guys. If I turn the stream off, even though, even though this boy,
there's 10,000 people here, you all know that I'm coming back, but like 4,000 of you are gone
permanently. You're just going to leave. That's just how it works. I actually think it would be
that kind of a fun experiment to like turn a stream off and back on like 30 times and see
if you get down to zero. Will one person stick around after you go through? What's the diminishing
returns? I have to go to work. Have I eaten? All right. I'm okay. I would stay. Thanks. Okay. I mean
it. No more gambling. I would rather eat food on stream. I'm going to eat food on stream with
a webcam. That's the new meta. What do you mean gas is going to run out soon? I just got it.
Excuse me. Can I just buy gas? Yeah. I'm going to put it on ASMR, webcam, with food. I know, I know.
Someone siphoned gas from the car. I feel like they did. We want you to butt chug. Time that
person out for real. For at least two minutes. And I'm serious on that one. That's a serious,
that's a serious time that person out. We make that joke all the time. Oh, man, that guy. Oh,
modem. Really time that guy out for two minutes. I want him to sit here and think. He's looking at
his screen saying, we want you to butt chug. I said that. I want this kind of butt chug. Yeah,
I did say that. All right. I'm back. I'm back. I'm okay. I'm sorry for saying that. Start time.
What? I missed it? No, I got early. I'm really early. I'm so ready to work. Oh, God. I'm here
two or three hours early. Is the restaurant even open yet? No, I'll be here. Hey, need somebody to
help clean the dishes and everything? I'm here. Oh, I know. I'll just tell people to come in the
restaurant. I'll point at the restaurant and be like a dancing guy in a costume outside.
Go to the strip club. No, I'm not going to spend any money. This is eerie. Just standing out here.
Okay, hold on. Look out the back window. You know, kids typically when they look out the back window,
they go like, if you ever pull up behind a school bus at a red light, there's always like four or
five kids that are always like pointing at you out the window. And then you go like, oh, hey,
hey kids. You like cover your eyes and your ears and you go, and they go,
wave like out the window. Hey kids. I forgot to have to work. Right. And then when the light
turns green and three or four seconds go by and the school bus driver hasn't gone yet,
they didn't leave it to me. It's green light. Let's fucking go. Hey, easy. Oh, you're only,
you're only like nice and sweet into like, I think he's going to get away with that.
Does he? I need to guess. Yeah. Everybody's nice and sweet until. Can I please just say this line
that I want to say? I just want to say a line. Everybody's nice and sweet until somebody sits
at a green light for four seconds. Okay. It goes from this cop has been riding on the sidewalk
the same every time. Fucking go. I'm hitting the button. I'm out of gas. I'm out of gas. Fucking
go already. That's why I have no gas. Can I work again? Can I work a good double? I have to take
an Uber home. It's 50 bucks. I love you. I thought he pulled up and was making that sound with his
mouth. It's an assassin. Oh shit. Thank God. Yes. Oh my God. I get burritos. I'm so hungry.
Trunk burrito. Still good. No, it wasn't. Come on. Please. I just want to go. Somebody push me.
Can I push the car? I can't push the car. I need to, I'm going to have to pay for the gas thing.
I'm going to get like five jobs. We're taking a streaming break. I need medicine. Fuck. Wait,
hold on. I'm going to take the rest of the computer parts out of that guy's house.
Does he live? Where does that dude live? What was that guy's name? Wait, this is the hacker's house.
Is this the guy that's been hacking me the whole time? Why do I know where he is?
This is the guy that's been trying to break into my bank account for the last three months.
Where is he? I thought it was that guy. Wait, where is he? What? What's up? I just
wanted to ask you a couple of just questions about what you're doing and why you're doing this to me.
Okay. Uh, price to buy a, oh, this is a cryptocurrency miner. Are you the guy? You're
not the guy. You're not the guy. The BTC miner. How have you not been found out that you're back
here? I would, I'll get, I'll come back and get that in a little bit later. Yeah. He's dizzy. I
know I need medicine and I'm going to run out of gas again. I need gas. Where's the gas station?
How am I? Oh, this car sucks. What's the miles per gallon on this fucking thing? This thing's
terrible. Okay. I got gas. We got to turn, go back up and then go down that road. So back up
and take it. Okay. Let's go. Wait. I'm gonna go stream. What's going on? What? Does this car
have a leak? I don't, I just bought a quarter tank of gas. I didn't, I went down the street.
Level up in the skill tree. Oh shit. All right. Yeah.
Rash meter. I don't have enough money. No gas. Yeah, that's fucked up.
You will die after your bladder finally says fuck you and explodes.
You've been on a hundred toilet. All right. I have a plan. Here's my plan. I'm not going to
fucking work again. I'm not going to work. I'm going to go home. I'm going to stream every day.
I'm not going to open cases. I'm just going to play fucking fall guys and people are going to
eat it up. I'm going to make a thousand dollars over the course of a week. Then I'm going to fill
my car up with gas. I'm going to use the bathroom to buy a bathroom. I'm going to order some pizzas
and shit and I'm going to be fine for now. I, I have, I have to get home 50 fucking bucks. What
a joke. That's a plan. Yes it is. So I need food. I need to go to the bathroom. What do I have in
my wallet? I need to transfer some money to my wallet so I can go to the bathroom in this outhouse
and then I need medicine too, but I'm okay. I've got 14 health. Okay. Hold on.
Read these out loud. Just, okay. There we go. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Okay. 47 bucks from my stream lab. Now I need to go to the bank. I gotta pay bills too. Shit.
I think I saw Zerma at the grocery store and he went like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Buy a toilet.
I will get necessities. I promise. Electrical interference. Yeah. Oh, okay. Okay. I'm going
to put some money in my wallet if I can. I know you need medicine. Just hold out a little longer.
He's going to stream one more day. How can I get money from his bank account? Like why can't the
hack backfire and I take a hundred bucks from his account? Okay. Transfer to wallet. Let's transfer
just 10 bucks to the wallet. It's enough to go to the bath. No, 20 bucks. I have to go to the
bathroom twice. Just buy a toilet. The toilet is $400. I can't afford it. Oh, good. All right.
I need to buy a new house too, but slow. Baby steps. I need to order some food. I got plenty
of food. All right. We're locking myself up here. Two burritos. I know. We're going to get two
burritos and some canned food. Not getting to the second game. No, no. I'm locked in here. I like,
love this. I'm having a blast. What am I doing? Oh, food. Right, right, right. Get three burritos
and some beans and just keep them in the desk. Please move on. This isn't fun. I'm playing it.
Are we both playing this game at the same time? Are you playing it too? I know. I thought this
isn't fun. Ban that guy permanently. No, we don't ban. We did no permanent bans here. Oh,
yes, there is. It's a lie. All right. Two clam soups and a couple of burritos and a couple of...
What lasts? Beef jerky lasts like forever. Get two of these. Get fat. Somebody called me fat,
right? Somebody was like, oh, you've become obese. I was like, how the fuck do you know that?
We're streaming enough to get medicine and then we're going to stream permanently.
It was, you are obese on the computer. Yeah. Thank you. All right. Clam soup. Eat it. Burrito.
Eat it. Let's... Okay. Eat this clam soup because that will probably not keep very well.
Hundred. Store the rest in my backpack. Does it matter if it hits the ground? I hope not.
Somebody said European taxes and American healthcare. Okay. Let's stream. I need
medicine. I know. I'm working on it. Let's go. What's going on, sinners? It's me, German985,
coming at you with another live stream. Just, whoa, hold on a minute. Okay, everybody. I want you to
relax while we... Shh. Everybody breathe in and breathe out.
Fuck this stream. What? Is it loud? Oh, it's actually going. I don't have both earphones in,
guys. I only have my right one in. I didn't know that... Hold on. I'm getting a ton of donations.
I have to keep doing it. I feel dizzy. Where's the toilet one? Which one is toilet? Okay. Thank you
for your subscriptions. We've got 44. It's 19. Is there a lottery? How we had so much toxicity.
Relax and enjoy the tingles. Thank you. Click. Estabator for the subscription.
Bonesie Prime, thanks for the sub. Thank you for the three dollars and one cents. I say I love you.
Oh, I'm not going to say you too, so you can go fuck yourself. Valti, thanks for the sub. I made
my coffee. This is a shit stream. Okay. Good stream. Thanks to Pog. Appreciate it. I love you
very much. I'm preparing a surprise for my darling. Read my name. Do you say your lover...
Is this live? Yes, it is. Wake up. Stream is over. How much money do we make today from our ASMR
stream? Oh, 50 bucks. All right. Same thing tomorrow. I got backpack full of burritos.
That was a madhouse laugh. I will pay you any amount of money to never do that again. Okay.
The amount is $500 million. Okay. Back at it again. Eat the food in my inventory and then
let's go. This is a little dirty. That's okay, right? I'm kind of afraid to eat this with 11
health. I'm going to sell it to the fucking guy. Yeah, let's sell it. I'm terrified. I have 11
health. Even if I lose like five, that's really bad. Five bucks. I'll take it. I'll take it. Let's
go. Do I need to use the bathroom? I do. I don't have any money. Why? How are we doing? Okay. I've
eaten. I'm going to have some beef jerky. How is this dirty? It's beef jerky. If I lose health,
I'm going to be mad. Oh shit. There's even more in here. I don't know. That's pretty awesome,
actually. All right. Store that. Only buy beef jerky. It's like the best food ever, apparently.
All right. I'm back. We're not doing ASMR. We're doing a creative stream today. Okay. Let's do
some paintings. I'm not going to be reading any sub or chat messages today, guys. I'm concentrating
on my art. Thank you, whoever that was. Just drop the pen. Uh, that's an eraser. Okay. Hold on. I
need to... Why do we keep climbing with toxicity? This is so annoying. Good morning. I'm just trying
to draw a face. Next pen. I need medicine. I'll get it after this. Looking for a favorite streamer?
That's going to be me. I guarantee it. All right. Can I sell this to one of the viewers?
Or can I sell this? Xeric opened a stream. Let this disgusting stream. How do I lower this?
Am I just that unbearable? People are giving me money, though. I'm getting a ton of money.
Look at all these subscriptions and... Look at all this. This is crazy. This is a sub train.
This is a huge amount of subs. Okay. That was cool. Now let's erase this and let's make a new one.
The legend is back. That's right. Here I am. This is going to take too long to erase. So I'm just
going to go like this and let's... Here. You want to see my bank account? Still at 144p. I'll show you
guys my bank account on stream. Here's my actual thumbprint. I have 56 bucks. I'm going to transfer
money to my card. I have like 80 bucks or so. I want to watch me get a loan on stream. 500 bucks.
I have three days to pay it off. I'm never going to be able to do that. That's way too much.
More subs. I know everybody in Blender. I see you first stream. How long has the stream started?
How long do you have been doing this for a job? Sorry. Mic off for now. He's a waiter. Look who it
is. Nod. Nod P. Getting hacked on stream but blocked him. Still streaming this. Okay. Stream's
over. I want to play one of the other games. Why did I install fall guys? I need medicine though.
Okay. I've got 92 dollars. That's not enough. I think I have to just get lucky at blackjack.
Eat some beef jerky. Go to bed. Loot again. I can't uninstall fall gang. I want to play counter
strike or fifa. Can I? Wait. Computer. Oh. Hold on a second. Can I go in there and take it out?
No. No. I don't. Wait. I don't have a microphone. No I do. Okay. I was like wait a minute.
All right. Let's eat food and go to bed. Where's my beef jerky? Did I have two? I thought I had
two of these. No. Take out a massive loan and then do a hand in blackjack for all of it.
I don't know. I think that's a really really bad idea. Go look in trash and see if you can
find anything. Nothing in this trash. All right. I'm gonna go look around all the dumpsters.
Nothing in here. I want to buy like a cat and have a dog and stuff. I need to make some money.
Any more trashes to look through? You have to press space? Take trash. Space. There's nothing
here. Move. Whoa. Does this hurt? I think that might hurt. No. All right. We're good. This is
free shit. It is. Oh a gas bottle. Oh a plastic crate. I don't have any more motivation to be in
the trash anymore. What do these things do? This is a. I can sell it to a dealer. I can sell it to
a dealer. I can sell these to a dealer. Gonna make some money. Zero hygiene. He's gonna be mad. Take
a shower. Maybe I can trade him for some medicine. What's up? I got some things for you to look at.
I've got a water bottle for you to look at. Nine bucks. I've got a gas canister. That's a lot of
money and a plastic crate. I think we can have make a little bit better of a deal there I think.
Fuck you. More trash? Nice. Oh how do I get more trash motivation? I think it's a skill point.
Garbage motivation decreases more slowly. How much is it? I don't have money to do that.
Back on the stream. Oh you know what? I think I'm gonna take like five jobs. Yeah. I'm gonna try to
make like 500 bucks in two days. Freelancers. What's this? Gamble a loan you idiot. Imagine
telling somebody saying the words gamble a loan and then a space bar and then writing you idiot.
Oh coding? Do I know how to code? You should get a key by finding capital letters and numbers from
within the scattered code block. You must enter the keys by typing code at the beginning. Get a key
by finding capital letters and numbers within the scattered code. So I need capital letters
and numbers in here. Okay. So then I type in code and then wherever you have to look. Let's go.
Here we go. We've got eight. Eight V. Eight V V. Eight V V five. Eight V V five. Wait eight.
There's another one. Eight V V five. Eight V V. Wait eight. Code eight V V J eight. Eight V V J
F five. That's it. It does say code. Got it. Three. Three. Uh zero. Um O. Okay. N. And uh
W. And um done. Okay. Code. A. And uh S. Uh B. D. Come on. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go. Go.
A. A. A. A. P. P. T. I don't know. A. P. P. What? T. What? What is that? A. P. P. T.
F. What do you see? F. I don't see an F. Blind. Hold on. A. P. E. P. There's nothing here. That's it.
Oh I thought it had to be five. R. F. This is actually really easy to make a bunch of money.
We just do it. Put R. F. E. B. Um done. That's uh 95 dollars. Let's do it again. This one is 115 bucks.
Are you kidding me? Let's go. This is where you make the money. That's it. Oh fuck. What was that?
That was fucked up. Okay. Uh E. E. Uh A. E. A. What's the next one? E. No. D. E. What? What's
the next one? D. Oh shit. You can get them wrong. J. M. J. J. S. J. S. M. Look for numbers too.
Is that it? J. S. V. M. Okay. Y. W. K. Uh Y. W. K. A. Oh come on. That was wrong? Eight. O. Y. Five.
X. Six. Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten. Knock out. 74 dollars. Let's go. This is so easy. We can finally
buy a toilet if we want. PG-6 and no. PG-6. PG-6 code. We're playing a middle-aged office
worker simulator. No. We're losing viewers. I'm making money man. Why don't you stream this?
Holy shit. You're right. This is double money. This is making double money. I can't believe I
didn't think about that. We'll do that tomorrow. I think that's good. That's it. You can't hack me
in the middle of doing my own hacking. Hi Luke. Good to see you again. How are the kids? How are
you? Same time next week? Cool. See you then. U. B. Nine. Z. No. X. A. E. Okay. X. There's a three
there. X. R. Three. There it is. Fuck. I'm so bad at this. Five. R. B. A. U. Thank you. 42 bucks.
All right. We'll do this tomorrow on stream. What's my bank account look like? That's probably
most money I've ever had. Yeah. Look at that. 280 bucks. Good. We'll do it on stream tomorrow.
I'm going to order some food and we'll go. Legit working. Yeah. But it's all good man.
Don't even look at this stuff. Beef jerky only. Do we even pay bills anymore?
I want to. I want to. I want to. Thanks to you this stream. I looked up what Yankee Doodle was
and I learned about macaroni. Okay. We're going to get a pig and then beef jerky. I got a lot
of unready meals. Okay. I need to pay bills. That person's right. They probably overdo.
Get better internet. There's a lot of things I want to get.
Bills. Why is beef jerky more expensive than a whole... I can't even talk. I'm sorry.
Words that just have trouble coming out sometimes. I'll get it in a second.
Let's leave it at the door. No bills. Can I see some pogs in the chap and no bills?
You know I've started to really like that word pog. I'm older than a lot of you guys,
but you know it's fun to say sometimes. Okay. Let's put the store these on the shelf.
That better not be dirty. Where did that go? Are you fucking kidding me? Just keep it in my backpack.
I don't care. Where'd it go? Can I take a bath? I got to use the bathroom too. Don't touch my beef
jerky. It's out here. It's mine. Don't touch this. All right. We're going to wake up tomorrow. We're
going to dig through the trash. We're going to eat some medicine. Sounds good. I have plenty of
energy. What am I doing? Turn the stream on. Let's go. Let's turn the stream on. Today we're
doing just chatting and I'm going to do coding on stream. Welcome everybody. How are you? Bear with
the hearing. We're going to do some coding. I left for an hour and he's still in this dump.
This game is, it's a slow burn, but I like it. Okay. Freelancer. I can't, I don't understand this.
I am a boomer. Okay. Coding. Check it out guys. We're going to be coding on stream. Z, F,
five. This is a very boring stream, isn't it? So you have a five J.
Fuck it. I fucked it up. I screwed it up. Hey, VOD watchers, skip 20 minutes. All right. That's
what they should be saying. Okay. Uh, three. H three J, H three R, six R, J. Someone realizes
that you are sleepless. I'm sorry, but I'm coding right now. Leave me be. Did I do that job right?
I did. Okay. Code four. I'm making triple money. This is the way to do it. G. I'm getting a lot of
money. Two. Oh my fucking God. It's all right. The donations are still coming in. Is it? Hey,
what do you think about that? I know everybody in the blender. See the first, I think the 18 plus
chatting. People wonder what you think about the shape of the world. The world is flat. The world
is flat. We're going to do, we're going to, okay, sure. The world is flat stream over F, A, S, E,
20 bucks. That's not even worth doing this. 10 bucks worse than FTK. Get out of here.
I'm scrolling over my chat. I'm going to ban you. All right, let's go medicine. All right. I can
buy the medicine. 200 bucks. That's such a bum. That's such a money sink. I need money. Ah,
let's say he's a, this guy's a positive streamer. I'm not as toxic as this guy.
All right. So I said, you guys are about 30, 40% toxic on that meter. Where am I? Over 50,
under 50, 50%. There's nothing in there. How can you have nothing in there? Just crap. Take it.
Fuck, whatever. I'll just sell it to him. Why is there even a wallet in the game? Why can I just
swipe my credit card into the lock? All right, let's go sell this stuff to this guy. And then
I actually am going to go and see if I can go take some computer parts out of that guy's house.
I'll take pills. Get a better house. You see how much of a struggle it has been for me to keep
$50 without blowing it on beef jerky and CSGO cases? You think I'm going to get like
hundreds of thousands of dollars? Short stream today of me transferring money into my wallet.
Just a quick one. Short stream of me just transferring money. What's the cap?
Okay. Let's transfer to my wallet. Let's just put like 50 bucks in here and then let's transfer.
Okay. We're good. No, I need 200 total money in wallet, total money on the card. Transfer
this money back to my account. Give me transfer to wallet. Okay. Let's go get that medicine.
The stream is still on. Okay. What am I stupid? Why wouldn't I just turn the stream on
and fucking leave and go to work? What if the computer gets hacked?
You'll get hacked. Has it happened yet? Hey guys, I'm back. Childhood memory. Say you were a very
clever baby. Tell the memory you pissed underneath. Okay. How much money do I got? I'm going to keep
like I'm keeping money on my wallet because seriously I need it. I put gas and all that.
Thanks guys. 84 viewers. I need to buy a webcam. That's really important. I have enough money to
buy a webcam. Oh man. Somebody gave a lot of money. Who gave a lot of money? Just read them
all on stream and they'll keep coming. Okay. I closed the stream. That's fine. I'll take the
160 bucks please. Awesome. Now we're making moves. This is where it really gets, this is where it's
going to be good. How much is a fridge? How much is a shitty fridge? 200 bucks. I can afford that.
I can afford it. Fridge and a webcam. 112. God, Luke just picked somebody else to do this to.
Anybody else but me. Luke, I'm just going to move. I'm going to get a new house anyways. All right.
Ball? Webcam? This one here is 112 bucks streaming for webcams. I need 312 bucks. All right. Let's
put that on the credit card. Level up. That's a fridge and a webcam. You need a toilet. Streaming
comes first. Do I have any food? I do. Is this dirty? It's a little dirty. It's okay. It should
be fine. Yeah, that's good. I got any money on the wallet? No. But I'm just like, my underwear is
sagging behind me. Like Santa's knapsack. Like Santa has all your presents in there. Go to sleep.
Well, that's the grossest thing you've heard all day. Come on. It's been four hours. I'm a little
gross, but not that gross I don't think. There's a wheel in here. That fridge is huge. Can I fit
this fridge in my house? It's as big as a doorway. Oh, dude, we're going to have a streamer fridge.
What an ugly fridge. That's the worst streamer fridge ever. Oh, and I can sell that. A Red Bull
fridge. No, this is the, this is the fridge that, so if you have a, if you buy a new fridge,
this is the fridge that becomes the second fridge that ends up in your garage.
All right. Let me go. I need, I can buy a bunch of food now. That's the best part about this.
I can actually buy food. I don't know why, but for a second, I thought this was a second fridge
lying down. I can buy and store food. Oh, thank goodness. A webcam. Get this shit on here. And
I'm doing a webcam stream to test it out. Let's have the donations roll to fucking. All right.
Settings. Full screen cam. Show cam. Recommended bit rate. Stream settings. Full screen camera.
Wait. Hey guys. Welcome to stream. I'm taking you guys on a, oh, you can't do that. It's all
right. If I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I got a cam now. What do you guys think? Thank you.
I can't change this. What is this even a picture of? This isn't the wrong spot. This isn't a
terrible spot. Wait, can I move the camera? Nice fucking slideshow. Wait, I have an idea.
Be serious. My computer's disconnected. I turned off the computer with a shitty stream.
Oh, that's so stupid. Can I get a chair that's not a baby high chair?
Turn it on. What's wrong with the computer? Stream in the bathroom. Oh, you give me ideas. I wait
till I have my own house. Sorry guys. That's my fault. I screwed up a little bit. I'm back.
Can you see me? Please fix this. What's wrong with it? Misuse other streamers to attract viewers.
I mean, just how many people are coming in? 40% of stream. This game is so fucking. Talk about
artistic things to improve the quality of the stream. Talk about beautiful pictures.
Art is boring. All right. Let's talk about beautiful pictures. I need to point the webcam
at my face. Stream trend. Focus on your own chat. Tell a story. Let's tell a story. Where are the
donations? Oh, here we go. It's time to do a joke. Cheap joke. Clever joke. Great stream. Thank you.
Oh, I can pretend there's a sub train so people will just start to subscribe because they think
it's a sub train that's going on. Whoa, dude. Oh, that's not even. I thought that was real.
People say that they are bored. This is too real, man. This is too real for me.
If you never make money on streaming, will you keep doing it? That would do it for fun.
Huge viewer count. All right. I got something crazy. What do I do? This is the most viewers I've
ever had. What is what movie you like? I don't know. Action. Viewers are skyrocketing. I want
to be a streamer, but the blender refused. Oh fuck. That was pretty good though. That was
almost 200 concurrent viewers. That's a big deal. Put your face cam on the game's monitor.
Yeah, I can't put it anywhere. I want to put it right here. Put it on the shelf.
Look, I can't do it. Look. See? And by the way, what images is this even taking? Why is it not
showing me? Do a feet cam? I don't think I can even do that. Come on. All right. Let's go. Stream
outside your house. I need better internet. I need money too. This game is actually pretty hard.
It really is. Try to get a better stream quality. Yeah, but I drop. People go drop, drop, drop
frames. This stream sucks. Loser. All right. Let me dig. Let me do some trash digging.
Damn it. Yeah. I need better internet first. Come on. All right. Do you want this weird wheel? How
much is this worth? Well, bucks. I have to take it. All right. Now is the time where I'm going to
take a bunch. I'm going to take like a bunch of jobs that at least two jobs that I can go to
back to back. Let's take a look at our bank account. 118 bucks. I feel like I'm always
at 118 bucks. It's always at one to 200. Okay. Stream. Hmm. What can I do here?
Buy a toilet. I need 400 bucks. I want to just gamble. What is fast net? Well, here's the thing.
How much more is the better internet package? It might not be that much more. Hold on. This
is the package that I have. Two down, one up. This is four down, one up. That sucks. $20
for four every four days. Or I can do turbo. You can buy a maximum of one turbo package every day.
So hold on. This is I, if I stream with that's 300, that's $33,000. All right. Let me get ready
for that. I need to eat. I'm going to get sleep and I'm going to turbo boost and do an insane
IRL stream. I'm going to order some food. Turbo boost into the bathroom. What are your opinions
on this emote? Let's see. Is that a bag on somebody's head? What is that? All right. Let's
get food, cheap food that I can put in the refrigerator. Let's get some sodas, three sodas,
two waters, an energy bar, some apple juice. Somebody once told me the world was
going to roll me. I'm sorry. It's the first thing I thought of. I'm sorry. I know everyone's going
to do that. Everyone's going to say, yeah, it was terrible, but come on. I had to do that.
I had to do that. Stop treating me this way or I'll start banning everybody.
Don't make fun of me. I'm in control here. All right. That's enough for now.
No, you dick. Okay. I don't understand the internet. Okay. You put Shrek on the screen
and have that song playing in the background and everybody pogs their pants and plus two,
holy shit, the best thing I've ever seen in my life. You just sing the song and you're an
asshole and let's put his head in the guillotine. It's like they both have to be combined for that
to work, I guess. Bunch of clam soups. All right. Complete payment. We're going to fridge this shit
up. Pog needs to be banned. Why? Why do you want to ban Pog? We haven't even clicked on the deep web
app. By the way, if you see an app that says the deep web app, don't click it. It's not really the
deep web. This website is built on a blockchain that cannot be followed. It cannot be followed,
but every move you make leaves a new trace. Please pay attention to your steps. You cannot
sell online for security reasons. You can get a minor device. Okay. Backdoor hack. After the
hacking attack, if you have backdoor hacking, you can hack the person who hacked you. What?
Wait, we can finally get our revenge on Luke, the hacker. Okay. I need to get some BTC.
It's too much to do in this game. I have to focus on one thing at a time. This is like the ADHD
nightmare game. All right. Perfect. This is a soda. Drink it up. Crackers. Delicious. All right.
Put the burritos in the fridge. Put us all in the fridge, actually. And then what was I going to do?
Something very specific. BTC. No, no, no. Something else. Oh, the web boost. Right. The web boost
can do a one-time only super stream. All right. Store this out. Into the fridge it goes. Well,
why did I just zip my pants? Use the toilet urgently. Don't worry. I'm going to make sure
that the stream that I do, I'm going to be fully washed and fully bathroomed. Don't worry. I promise.
All right. We've eaten. I actually should probably have a little bit of apple juice.
I love apple juice. 100. Cool. All right. I got pretty good health. Let's put 10, let's put 20
bucks in my bank account in my wallet so I can go pay the guy to use the bathroom. And we'll go from
there. And we're going to get the super boost internet and I'm going to turn the stream on
and we're going to get a huge amount of people. Okay. 9K Andy. You're on this shit again. All
right. Where's the bathroom? All right. I'm going to finally use the bathroom. It's been a week.
Thank you. Appreciate it. Take a shower. Close the fucking door. I want to be left alone right now.
Internet boost and I'm going to play Dark Souls. No ASMR gave us way more money. No way. Yeah.
ASMR gave way more money. We do ASMR for like four hours. Just turn that turn the volume. Guys,
it's the biggest money maker. Just turn your volume down a little bit. Fast net. Let's go.
Turn off the VPN. Oh shit. All right. So this is $20 every four days. This is two megabits up.
This is double what we have now. We just do the soup, the big one. This is three. All right. It's
going to be worth it. I'm going to make a bunch of money. This is a big one. Oh, I have a ton of
internet now. Okay. OBS. Just start the stream. I don't even care what it is. At least you wait
until I'm done with a sentence. He never interrupts me. He always just waits for a sentence break.
Turn the stream on. Okay. OBS. Stream settings. Normal camera. Go cam. Normal cam.
We're going to save this stream. 2200 bit rate. We can do that. Quality. We're going to go to 360p.
We're going to go 360p. Don't save the stream. 60 FPS. 30 FPS at 2700. This is big deal.
Let's go. What's up? How's everybody doing? How do you like the quality? Pretty good, huh?
There are people in chat who write without using their brain. Welcome to life. All right. How do
you like it? How's the quality? What do you think of the shape of the world? The world is geo it.
I don't know what that means. No drop frames either. No donations. This is a, this is a boost.
I need money. Stream control. Chat only. Video rendition stream. What? Video rendition. I have
to do something. Where's my camera? Oh, there it is. Full cam. People love the full cam.
Let's go to ASMR. Turn your headphones down. Turn your headphones down. Here comes the donations.
Read them all. Rate stream. Subscribe. Subscribe. Subscribed. Fan the wrong guy. Whatever.
We're about to break 200 viewers. 200 viewers. Here comes the 200. Come on. Do it. And I could
get partner at 400. Big money coming in. This guy's only got one trigger. Okay. Is this a big
Great Dane shaking his head around? Read the fucking donations. Hold on. I love you. Hey,
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. Thanks for the 20 bucks.
I love you. Thanks for the sub. Appreciate it. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah. And when,
when you guys come back, remember, it's me, the fat fuck IRL. Come back next week and I'll
shake my stomach around for you more after drinking three Gatorades. You know you love it.
Thanks for the sub. About to break a hundred. Wait, we're going to break a hundred. We can,
we can apply for partner at a hundred subs. Right? Come on. Somebody sub. Somebody sub.
Somebody sub. Toilet break. Please. Just somebody sub and I'll do it. What's your favorite color?
Green. Thank you. What does it say? Hello. Hello. How are you? Thanks for the sub. Ooh,
thanks for the sub. I told you ASMR kills it. 102 subs. We're going to apply for partner.
12 bucks. This is a big deal. Okay. Is it really good to just grab a bunch of shit on my desk and
just knocking it around and just go like, I bet, you know, I'd probably be a really good ASMR
streamer. Think about that. I could probably just sit there and be like, I'd make a million
dollars in a day. Oh, Hey, we've got some money. Can you say my darling's name? Hey kitty. Thanks
for the sub. This is fucking torture. Whisper, please. Someone stole my credit card and subscribe
to you. How would you even know that? Read my message. We're at 300. Come on. We're at 300
years. We can get higher than this. We can get high in this. No, that was right. That was up.
I was right in the middle of the big deal. Right. Killed it. Okay. Here we go. Let's see if I can
apply for partner. Become a partner. Join in the I'm ready. I'm in the approval process. I just
applied average viewers, total subs, total followers. Hey, I got the average. I got the subs,
total followers, 400, 107 subs, expected earnings, 283. What? All right. Tomorrow I'm getting up early
and we're going to do an ad. I'm going to do an ASMR ad stream. What the hell was I doing? Okay.
I got a lot of money. 154 bucks. Not bad. Tomorrow. We're back tomorrow. Donation said to stream while
you sleep. Yeah. I'm going to get hacked. I need to hire mods. Oh, okay. Please change the stream
title from aces only. Don't even own counterstrike. Okay. We're going to do a 90 second ad every 90
seconds and see what happens. No, that's too, that's, that's, that's okay. Whatever. Who cares?
Come on, ban me. Will I get to see my name pop up here eventually? I'm supposed to be right here.
I'm supposed to be right here. I'm right here. What the fuck? Did I get it? No, I got, I got
declined. It's cold. What do you mean cold? Is it, has it been, has it winter time? What year is it?
All right. I'm going to have some burritos and a water. Refreshing. Not bad. All right. Nice and
hydrated. Let's go use the bathroom. Punch the water. All right. Now I have my boost, right?
Okay. I'm ready. Same deal. What I said, I said I was going to do, uh, I'm going to run a bunch
of ads, do ASMR because it kills new title, show cam, start that stream, stream settings.
God damn it, Luke. Luke, one of these days, I'm going to hit you back hard.
Okay. We're back. Okay. Let's run ads. Wait, don't run ads yet. Wait till there's like a bunch of
people here. What's my stream look like? Okay. I got my full camera pointing at nobody apparently.
Let's get those triggers going. This is very cold. Here comes the subs. 23 bucks. I love pizza.
Thanks for the $7. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Put the music on too.
Music on an ASMR stream. That seems kind of odd, but I, okay. Okay. Shaking to the beat.
I'm so bored. I just go into a stream and have the fat guy naked, shaking his stomach to the beat of the song.
And you say that you're bored. It's boring. Boring. I need to run ads. Just run them again.
This guy would fuke. This guy would fucking fuke.
I can't do it very much longer, everybody. I can only have five E-rates before I throw up.
400 concurrent viewers. Viewers, sweat up. Oh, too much. Too much. Too much. Slow down.
He's tapping on his stomach. Oh shit. How much money did I make? $24.
So much toxicity. Funny. Funny. Cry. Cry. Cry. Subscribed. That's it?
Like shaking my stomach around to the music? Come on, man. Really? It shouldn't be like that.
We're doing it again tomorrow. We're doing it again tomorrow. We're doing it again tomorrow.
We're doing it again tomorrow. We're doing it again. We're going to do that again tomorrow,
but we're going to go even higher quality. I need to go to sleep first.
Get the turbo? You have the better internet route. Just get the turbo today.
Fucked up stream. Okay. Eat. And then I'm putting some cash on my wallet so I can
go out there and use the toilet. Pay taxes. I can buy a toilet? No. Why would I buy a toilet
if things are going so well? I just need some money on my wallet. Just buy a toilet. Fine.
All right. I'll buy a damn toilet. I have 500 bucks. All right. We need to have another song.
Another like shake juggle ASMR tap the stomach stuff. People loved that stream. That's their
favorite stream. We're going up to HD quality. 720p coming up. Full screen camera. And we're
saving this one. And it's going to be 60 FPS. 120 FPS. You're going to be able to see the
jiggling stomach, slow motion, the wrinkles and shit. How much do I need? I need 8,700. What
do I have? Three? I can't do it. We're going to have to stay with 60 maybe. What's the boost?
It's three. With the turbo boost it'll be five. What's six? All right. Maybe we're not ready for
60 FPS yet. All right. I've got 99% energy. I'm ready. Wait. Don't do it yet. I need to go to the
bathroom. Buy the toilet. There. This is just what he does. And people love it. We can run ads too.
Minimize this. All right. That looks okay. We'll go come back here. I just want to go. I need to
buy toilet. Hasn't paid bills or taxes in years. Just juggles his stomach to the beat naked on
Twitch. Stop saying Twitch because it's not. Blender. Let's just put $500 bet right now on
Blackjack and then end the stream. All right. Mods. Let's see if we can get this. Hire a moderator
for stream. Own number of moderators to be hired. One is $5. Let's get two. Five dollars to mod.
That's the salary. Change the ban rate. Where's my $5? Ban rates. Mod ignores. Mod ban machine.
Balanced. Oh. Well, they're going to be pretty soft. Okay. I'm going to buy the fast net booster.
After I buy a toilet. God. I can't even pay attention to anything. I'm going to pee again.
We're going to pee one more time. Toilet. The cheapest shittiest one I can get. You're just
pissing it. Who cares? Finally have a toilet. We still have $288. Are we going to do a green screen?
Are we going to put a small ram in here? Green screen. Softbox? No. I can't afford this.
How are we doing on everything else? All right. I need to eat something.
I'm going to eat this last meal and I'm ready. I'm going to do it again. This time super boosted.
I need a gamer chair. I kind of do, don't I? Take a shower. Okay. Time to buy it. Buy the
boost. 5k up stream. Toilet. I don't think the toilet's here. Doesn't take a day to deliver.
That's not here yet. Webcam. Here we go. Turbo. Upload plus three. So this is, that's 6k.
I got the boost. I'm at 6k up right now. So we can do 60 FPS. Damn it. We can't. 30 FPS.
We'll do 6,000 up. Save this stream. Dreamsetty's full screen camera. ASMR. Let's get the music
ready. What's the song? Hello everybody. Welcome back to Juggles the Great's 140th stream of his
career. I just wanted to be the first to welcome you and say I love all of you and I love the subs
and I love the bits and I love all the money that you give me. I love you too.
Watching while eating. Oh, I ate a lot earlier. I ate a lot earlier if you could already tell.
So if I do, please do announce the next song we're going to be doing this afternoon.
I'm up. I'm ready. I'm stretched. Are you ready? Are you ready?
Mods, take care of some of these little assholes. Coming up next on the track we have.
Palm Avenue. This is going to be a good one. Hope you're all ready. Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm going to get a little sweaty. So what the hell's happening? Somebody's hacking
me. Hold on everybody. Just everybody calm down for just a minute. We'll take care of this piece
of shit. CWC. Oh, I blocked his ass. We're okay. We're good. Where was I?
All right. Sometimes I forget what I do here. Hey, do you like zootubers? Of course I love
zootubers. I love them. You know, I used to be a zootuber myself. Don't forget me in the future. I
won't gastroscope. I will not forget you. Of course I would. Hey, y'all want to see somebody
eat something? No, I don't have any food in the fridge. Somebody gave some money. Let's check out
who that was. Hey, what do you say we really get this poppin', huh? I needed another song.
Ah, we need some bigger, bigger than that. It's tough to hurt after a while, but I do it for you.
Ah, I love everybody here. We're just going to get partner suit. Oh, good night. I'm going to bed.
I didn't run ads. Shit. This dude gets banned. This dude gets banned every day. He just makes
a new account and he titles his stream the same thing so everyone knows where to find him. If he
look, think about that. If he titles every single one of his streams, juggles the great stream number
142 tomorrow, right? If he just makes a new account, he's just going to make people know what to look
for. Upload that VOD. Oh, right, right, right. Yeah, yeah. It'd be copycats. You'd find the real
thing. All right, publish that video. How's it doing? I wish we could watch this video.
Okay, the video's three hours and 36 minutes. That is a very, very long time to be doing that.
All right, I'm going to piss. I'll be right back. Actually, like not in the video game.
Give me one sec. Uh, did you guys say there was a raid? Did I miss a raid earlier? It was.
It was a juggles raid. Oh, I see. Okay. Let's get back to this here. So that's our video. I'm tired.
Speaking of getting paid, let's see how much money that stream made. I didn't,
I couldn't even see the stream labs. Holy shit. Look at this. I can't even scroll up far enough.
26, eight, 10 bucks. People love juggles the great. This is awesome. How much money might
get paid? 68. Let's see though. Dude. Holy shit. Oh, actually it was all right. I thought that was,
I thought I was. Sorry. Sorry. I gained a lot of traction. I gained a lot of traction. I bought a
toilet. That's right. I didn't run the ads stake. You got to play some games. Juggles is a wholesome
streamer. He doesn't play ads. Yeah. Let's take a look at the skill tree. I have money.
My goodness. There's a toilet finally. I don't have to pay anybody anymore.
All right. And yeah, let's get some light in here. X garbage motivation decreases more slowly.
That's a hundred. That's, I don't know. I don't know about that. I feel like I don't even want
that. I'm going to get it though. Open extra slots in your inventory. That's a lot of money.
Number of miners you can buy and decrease your YouTube video upload limit.
How did they, did they expect me to have this much money?
What is this? Item transfer and use of inventory items are much faster. That's kind of pointless.
Get a BTC miner. I just, I don't know. I need money again. I think I got this thing going with
the juggles. Oh, that'd be fucked. I need food. Let's buy some. You know what? I also need another
hard drive. The video made 10 bucks. No, what? Re-upload it. No, re-upload it. Oh, come on. I
didn't get paid. What a misclick. That was one of his best streams. All right. I need to get,
what am I buying here? I need food. I also need something else to do. What do I need?
He keeps talking about how hard it is. Hard drive. Right. Okay. HDD and SSD. Something cheap.
175 bucks right here. Okay. I need to buy this. Somebody said completing a game lets you delete
it from your hard drive. I got to pay bills too. Oh, very overdue. Very overdue. This one's due
today. We got a stream today. We got a stream right now. We got a stream right now. Impromptu
stream. Let's go. Hey, everybody. It's me. Juggles are great. You know what we do here.
What's the problem? What's the problem here? What's going on? What are you talking about?
Drop, drop. Please fix. Fix what? Oh, what the fuck? Oh, what the fuck? What's going on with
the internet? I don't know. How do I fix this? Oh, let me sit down. Let me sit down for this.
I ate two cakes today for this impromptu stream. Fix, fix, drop. Do you hate YouTubers?
Fucking ban that guy. He's annoying. All he does. How do I fix it though? Drop, drop, drop. Hello,
swearing prohibited. Shut the fuck up, man. Hey, thanks for the money. I said my internet
is in my computer. Maybe I need a better computer. All right. Well, sorry. I'm really
sorry everybody that this is happening. But the computer I don't know. I don't know what's
happening here. Fucking get out of here. I do what I can how we normally do. But I can only do so
much with the computer. Sorry about that. I just I'm gonna run a few ads. Maybe we'll shake around
a little you know, like you guys. We don't need that much stream power for that. I don't think
I'm gonna write a couple ads. Take a take a minute and see if the internet kind of gets better. Oh
shit. These are due today. Hold on just a minute. I'm gonna run a few ads and you'll just support
the stream support. You know me shaking around. I know how everybody has ended that I'll see you
soon. Hey, how the fuck am I gonna fix this bullshit? Hold on. I'm turning this off. No,
no, I don't want to show that. I don't want to show that. Fuck is that any personal information
on there? I hope not. Hold on to me. I don't know what I did. I screwed something up. But we got
when we get I'll be back tomorrow though. I promise you. We'll do well ended out on a good one here.
I'll see you guys. I don't know what's happening. This is fucking God damn it, man. I am starving.
Fuck dumb, stupid ass fucking stream. Drop frame stream close. Fuck. You know how much I
fucking ate today to do this and how much I had to get this ready. Everyone's expecting me to be
here. Looking over the chat. Yeah, great. What the fuck? What the fuck? Professional streamer
professional streamer, huh? If only they fucking knew. I'm upset too. They don't think I'm mad
about this too. Well, I did it. I prepared for it. So I'm gonna fucking do it. You like that one?
God fix my fucking internet tomorrow or I'll be pissed. We've been in a virus game like four
hours. I was using this stream to test the slime guy bit. What? I thought that was me doing that
again. It's going up. There's so many viruses. I have to pay my bills, dude. 20 bucks. I didn't
get any money from that stream. Course I did. Okay. 123 bucks. They look at thank you. They
supported him. They know he's got to pay his bills and I know he shakes around for their
entertainment. 500 fucking viruses. Look at him. Look at him. Look at him. Found him. Who is this
guy eating cheeseburgers? Why does he have bold cheeseburgers with the buns on the grill with
the buns? I feel like that's not good. I feel like that's not gonna be very good. That's Randy from
the trailer park boys. Okay. That was the wrong link. What is going on here? What the hell is
you? What is this? Did you make this? What is that image? Hey I got all the viruses are gone.
Now I gotta pay bills. What happens if you just don't pay them? Expected earnings. 386 bucks.
Payments are coming out tomorrow morning. Apply for partner. Come on. I had it. Look I got 137 subs.
44 bucks from ads. 165 live viewers concurrently. Come on. You need a thousand followers? What's up
with that? There were 500 people here on stream. I bring in the numbers. They can't get enough of
that. They want 400 concurrent. Fine. Buy some food. 800 follower Andy. Buy a bunch of burritos. They're
the most filling. Upload that stream. That's a good idea. Back to zootube. Go on fucking Zornhub or
riot. You're gonna have to riot. I'm afraid of seeing like a naked lady on it or something.
$50 burritos. Well $50 is in. I'm right there. Burrito delivery. Thank you. Zero energy. Twitch
mod said do it. They did? Hold on. They did. Wait. Wait. What do you mean a Twitch mod? You mean one
of my mods or do you mean a Twitch like staff member? Staff said it. Wait a minute. I want to
confirm this. Twitch staff just told me to do this. I didn't see it. Yep. Zornhub time. I just
okay. I just got confirmation from Twitch staff to go to Zornhub. Okay. I'm telling you. I just saw
it. I hope you didn't get hacked. What is this? This is my character? This is just like drawings
of people. How is this Zornhub? This is just like the cast. This is like a Wikipedia page for
any anime you could probably come up with. Okay. Click one. I just did. Keep going. Keep going.
I'm so tired. I need to rest. We did get confirmation from Twitch staff that like I
could do this. I'm not playing the fire anymore. I'm not holding a lighter up to my hand and going
ow ow. I'm not doing that shit. I'm not holding my hand up to a lighter. Just to see if it hurts.
That was 50 bucks. Great. Now I can't eat tomorrow. Boxbox said it was okay. Did he? He hates
anime. No. I just. I don't know. How many of these are there? What is this? And why do you
have the worst fucking website in 2020? It's just an infinite scroll with no text. No nothing. It's
just an infinite scroll of anime characters. It hurts my finger to do this. I'm scrolling as fast
as I can. All right. We've made it to the end. Cool, I guess. This is just like a League of
Legends character skins. Who is this? This is not worth $50. But I mean, I'm going to stream it real
quick. I'm going to stream this tomorrow. Dude, there was a raid. There was a raid. There's like
12,000 fucking people here right now. We had like 9,200 people like 40 minutes. Did Boxbox raid?
All right. Okay. Twitch staff, you got to look into this. No, this has nothing to do with you
guys. This is streamlabs. How come it doesn't say that Boxbox raided? The same shit happened.
Welcome, everybody. Thanks for the raid, Boxbox. Sorry that when you raided last. It almost happened
again, by the way. Almost happened again. Almost just somehow complete. Because it's like, hey,
Boxbox said it was okay. Oh, okay. Boxbox, I like him. I like Boxbox. Wait, Boxbox raid. Oh,
I idiot. 2k viewers left. That's what happens during a raid. You come to the stream, you go,
oh, cool. Then you leave. All right. Let's sleep. I'm going to get up tomorrow and we're going to
stream. I'm going to do a gameplay stream tomorrow. You forgot about the bills. I can't pay them. I
don't have enough money to pay the bills, man. Let's see. Oh, shit. Yeah, I do. I got my payout.
Pay bills and then stream Zornhub without a mic. Just me scrolling. We'll see how many subs we
can get. I was about to do it. I can't do it. All right. Mods. We're going to change the mods.
Ban rate balanced. We'll have four mods. Get the stream ready. Make sure I got, have I eaten?
I should do my toilet urgently. Yeah, I'm going to eat. Let's have some burritos
and let's go to the bathroom. Now, seriously, thanks. Welcome, guys. If any of you guys still
here. Probably not going to go that much longer, but welcome. Live tomorrow too. Boxbox is awesome.
If you do not follow Boxbox, go do it now or I'm going to be, I'm going to be incredibly fucking
irritated with you. Do you want that to happen? Okay. All right. Pay the bills. Here goes all my
money. Like that, huh? All right. Let's wait. We got to do a stream. I lost my internet boost.
I got to boost it again and we're going to run a bunch of ads. Do scratch tickets on stream. All
right. Yeah, that's not a bad idea. Let's scratch. We'll do scratch tickets. We'll do skin cases on
stream. Just a few of them. Find the boost. We're at six up. Okay. We're good. Let's put that to six
up. Six thousand up. Get off the ASMR category. We're going to do just chatting and we've got the
cam on. We're going to save these streams so we can upload them later and we're going to start
with Zornhub. We're going to just open it with Zornhub. Okay. 60 FPS Zornhub stream. Here we go.
Hey guys. Oh, we got some subs already. One of you guys know that today is going to be
an interesting stream today. Today I'm going to go mic-less so I'm not going to be talking.
What's the lie to my viewers? I'm just going to lie to them. Whatever. I just want to say everybody
that today we're going to do something a little different. Usually we play a game or I do something
IRL but today we're going to go to Zornhub. I'm going to turn the mic off and we're just going
to enjoy it together. Yeah, that'd be a beautiful streamer. Thank you. I reported this stream
because this makes me happy. That's kind of weird. But yeah, if you're not 18, I would say
please leave the stream now. I'm going to turn the mic off. I'm going to put some music on.
What terms of service? Switch to ASMR. Okay. You guys ready? I'm going to be quiet. I'll be
typing in here with you. We'll put some cool tunes on. I'm going to set it a little lighter.
Yeah, it's going to be a chat only stream. Yeah, I'll be in chat with you guys. Let's go over
some of these. Let's take a look. Here we go. Clever baby. Leave me the fuck alone. I said chat
only. Keckw. All right. Sub only mode. Chat only. There's another streamer on the agenda. Make a
boring statement. Tell constantly. What do you mean on the agenda? Change the outfit to extreme
energetic movements. Wait. Hold on. Okay. You didn't think I was going to be here today,
did you? Probably not a good thing to have right now. Probably not a very good thing to have right
now. Probably a very bad thing to do right now on the Zornhub stream. Okay. Probably not a great
thing to do. Let's run a couple of ads. Quick before the stream turns off, run five minutes of ads.
Don't. No. Like a band. Zand for zerking off. You didn't think you were going to save me.
47% is the blood to share. All right. Did I make any money? Not really. Oh, I get, actually that's
up in three days. I get 418 bucks. Well, it looks like I'm tired. That was a fun stream.
Uh, it's still fresh. I can eat it. People only want belly shaking. Yeah, I know. Can I do
anything? Can I do something different? Can I do some variety? Not allowed to do any variety.
You want me to just shake my stomach into the camera when I can't play Fortnite for an afternoon?
Oh damn. All right. Bingo. Oh yeah. I can afford another hard drive, which means you can download
Counter-Strike. I can finally do a Counter-Strike stream. Finally. I wanted to do a Counter-Strike
stream five hours ago. Hard drive. I'm tired. Just wait. Scratch tickets, scratch tickets,
I will. Just give me a sec. Not enough balance. What? There he is again. Oh no, it's Zookas.
All right. Here comes the hard drive. Let's sleep and let's put our new computer together
and be able to play Counter-Strike. Oh, I love when you get that box. There it is. Awesome.
And I'm going to do the super internet boost so I can download it faster. Two hard drives.
I'm going to do two graphics cards too. All right. Boot it up. Download Counter-Strike.
I didn't get the donos. Yeah, I collected them. Okay. Counter-Strike. Get it. Finally. Downloads.
Where is it? Oh, I can actually do it. Can we do both? Okay. We're going to get Counter-Strike
on D. Get that super boost internet shit. When do I get paid from Twitch? Stop saying Twitch.
Guys, I haven't left my house in a couple of months. I'm realizing. When was the last time
we drove the car? Making bank though. Yeah. Doing pretty good. I don't even know where the car is.
It's in the city somewhere. Isn't it parked in the city somewhere? Out of gas. It's still in
the other town. Yeah. I took an Uber back here. It's still in the city. It's too bad the Tinder
thing doesn't work. That would be really funny. Oof. I haven't gone to work in probably three
months. I've been up and fired. I just want to play it. I just want to see what it's like.
Yeah, you can drive in this game. It's a fully functioning car. Almost done. So I'm still
interested in this game. I'm still having fun. Tomorrow we have kind of a fuckface stream.
I'm probably going to play this again. I feel like there's at least another little bit of
content left to do. Tomorrow we're doing cartoon personality quizzes. I've mined, which is a
community-made game, which seems pretty fun. And I'm doing Chubby Bunny tomorrow. Tomorrow's
going to be weird. All right. I'm going to just, let's see. Let's open it. Counter-strike by
Vanv. Not Zalv. You're not going to make it Zalv. You're going to make it Vanv. Enter IP. I don't
know why this is scaring me. It's scaring the shit out of me. I don't know why. I don't have,
I don't have an IP. Matchmaking? Do 192.168.0.0. Oh, router. You don't actually play. It's going to
be the impossible game or something. It's going to be like a cube. You move around.
That's very loud. Dead game. Okay. Anti-terror or terror? Okay. Oh my fucking God. I can't believe
this. I have nine FPS. I need a better graphics card. He's at door. He's at door, door, door, door.
Got him. No, he got me. I got him too. I need a better, okay. How do I get a graphics card?
I'm rage-quitting. Graphics card. Where do I get one? How much money do I have? I get 500 bucks in
two days. I'm getting another graphics card. That's a good trade. All right. Let's turn the
stream on and just shake our stomach a little bit and you get money. This doesn't matter. Shit.
It doesn't matter. It just has to be live. Hello. Hey guys. Yeah, I'm going to have some food.
You guys want to watch a guy eat? Audience quality. You guys are, you guys are awesome.
Oh, let's turn the cam on. What are we thinking here? Cat wonders what movie you like.
Slow 10. What are you guys doing? Minus two. What's going on? Whatever. Bad joke. What joke?
Run ads. Cat talking about a popular person you don't like. I don't like. All right. Read,
read, read, read. I got to read. Run ads and read messages. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Can you introduce a product that you don't like for money? I do everything for money.
There you go. Read that. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the bits. Thanks for the money. Thanks
for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the money.
Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub.
Thanks for the money. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the
sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for
the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for
the sub. Thanks for the sub. Thanks for the sub.
I'm gonna do it for you guys. I'm gonna get... I got hacked and I'm gonna get an ace.
Mid hack. There was a plane? What? Wait, buy menu. Oh shit. Okay, hold on. Guys, I'm gonna get a
graphics card in a minute. I just shot his own friend. I didn't even kill that guy. All right.
All right. Cut the music. How much money did I make? Did I get paid from Twitch yet? How much is
a graphics card? Upload all these VODs. You're right. Holy shit. I'm wasting time there. A thousand
bucks coming in. All right. Upload. I think I have a video already here though, right? Where's juggles?
He got banned 140 times and finally they IP banned him. You think that guy has any idea how to do
that? I do anything how to get around that. 14 bucks. I'll take it. All right. Let's take a look
at graphics cards before I do my last stream where I open cases. We'll do scratch tickets.
We'll play blackjack and do one hand and then end the stream. I mean mine, not the one in the game.
Graphics cards. These are cheap. Zadion HD 770. What do I have right now? What's in there? Okay.
It's the MTX 950. That thing's junk. All right. I'm going to upgrade the fuck out of this.
That's junk. Do scratch tickets. They're expensive though. They're like 50 bucks.
All right. This is a 990. Oh, that's the one I have. ZRX 400. I'm going to go to sleep and
have money in my bank. Yeah. Let's go to bed. Leave the computer on. I need to eat too. Get
hacked while sleeping. Take out a huge loan and just do scratch. I don't want to just blow up the
rest of the game. Did I get paid? No, I didn't get paid yet. When are they going to pay me?
Gamble a loan. Do it. Guys, I can't save scum. Payment will be there tomorrow morning. It's
going to be 500 bucks and I'm going to do my Counter-Strike stream and then I'm going to
turn my stream off. I'm going to apply for partner too. 5,000 followers. That's going to
take ages. Oh yeah. I'll do 144p stream. A little dirty. It'll do. How does it smell dirty? It's
soda. You're fine. All right. Let's go to the bathroom. Do voice ASMR. Can I do that?
Might as well stream. What else am I going to do right now? ASMR. How do I do that?
See you later, suckers. Be lucky if I'm alive again. How much did I get? I didn't even claim it.
Oh, I got it. I didn't even burp for them either. No ad Andy. So many people left. So like,
what, four or 500 concurrent? There's only 200 there. People were actually leaving the stream.
That's so funny. I'm not going to do, what do you mean I'm going to do that one day?
What was the joke? Fuck you. Stop. I wasn't going to talk until I got a hundred dollars.
I didn't see any of them. I didn't. I just lost probably. I kept everything. This person
doesn't even care. All right. We're buying a graphics card tomorrow and I'm doing a CSGO
stream. Then I'm going to turn my stream off in real life. We're going to have a lot of money.
Time for bed. Wait, let's get a late night smack. Do 144p. I will. I didn't forget that.
I'm not even sure I can stream in 144p. I'm not, I don't think you can even do it. I'll try. Okay.
Let's buy that graphics card tomorrow morning. Go to bed. No, order food. All right. Good night.
Go to bed. No money. I'm getting like 500 bucks tomorrow morning. Uh, this stuff is trash. I got
to get rid of this. Am I going to pay for the card? Whoa. That was a lot. Okay. I got it. Don't
worry. I can sell this. There's a, there's a payment coming in of like 480 bucks tomorrow.
I store these and put them in the fridge. What about the emails? What about my emails?
It's like you're hearing about your damn emails. I just ate one. Why did I eat that burritos only?
Okay. Stop eating them before you put them in the fridge. You fucking dummy.
What the hell are you doing? All right. Sleep. Graphics card. Toilet. Graphics card. Oh, my money.
All right. Let's buy that card. Install it. 718 bucks. Hell yeah. I mean, if I'm going to be
live, I'm going to be here. It might as well be live. Ordering cards. All right. Do I want the,
do I go with the MTX go? How about, yeah, the MTX go. That's the one. Horrible reviews.
Just chatting. Here we're hanging out. Yeah. I'll play music for you guys.
When's the delivery get here? Hey, when are you going to play Xanima? Right. Yeah. I did say that,
didn't I? I got kind of absorbed into this game. I'm sorry. I couldn't help it. I'm getting
donations right now. Music's loud. There are people who say your conversation is boring.
Ban them. We're doing our money. Actually, kind of a lot came in. Popular person. Say I don't like
them. I hate all of you. Stupid herd. You will never be a good streamer. I saw the IP address.
You didn't see, I don't, what IP address? Change the subject. Talk about cats. Talk about shit.
I do that pretty frequently. So there's a lot of bands going out. Is this kind of,
does this happen in channels? I, I'm just, there's like 10 people banned a second.
Does this happen a lot? Waiting for that graphics card, man. I want it. Does that mean I'm a liar?
Is that the Pinocchio face? Can I get any, can I download any games? You can get Zephyr. Oh,
cyber prank. Childhood memory. I don't know. Cyber prank. Start download. Oh, I don't have
big enough hard drive. I can't do it. Goodbye. Time for bed. And I can't wait for my counter
strike stream to end all streams. I can't sleep yet. What can I do? Check emails. All right, fine.
Blender payment. Blender has issued payment. Yep. Blender, no reply. Thank you for applying
the partnership program. Our support team is reviewing your account. I'll give you the
necessary feedback within at least two business days. We did Valve Corp. We detected that you
left the rank match before Counter-Strike game ended. We have reduced your rank score.
Please be more respectful. I did that both. Oh, thank you for replying. Okay. Thank you for
replying. I'll meet the requirements recreated for partnerships. Whatever. Message is deleted.
What about some of these other apps that I never downloaded? I got them all. Yes. No, no 10. No 10,
no 10, no 10. No, I didn't mean to do that. No, there's no 10 under there. You don't have
Blackjack. Duh. I hate cards. All right, I got my graphics card coming in the mail tomorrow. I'm
happy even though I lost $250. Where's the ASMR? There. Happy? Eat something before bed?
This before bed? I need health. Zerk off and then go to bed. Zerk off. You know, I can say it because
it's not even a real word. Isn't that how, uh, wasn't there a TV show on TV that got away with
that for a while? They had swears in the universe. So instead of fuck, it was something, it was like,
it was like frack. What show is that? Firefly. Or like, grack. Battlestar Galactica. Yeah,
they had a whole list of like, just swears that they made up so they could say them on TV even
though they weren't real. And people in the show, if it was like, oh, come on, like, grack you,
it was like, excuse me. So it felt real. It felt like, holy shit, that was a big, that was a bad
word. Here it is. Look at this monster. Let's get a good look at this guy. Prepare. It's too big.
Prepare to dominate. The Zadeon HD 6450. I'm ready to dominate. This thing was, what, 500 bucks?
Throw this thing in the trash where it belongs. Wait, I'll sell that to that idiot. Let's do it.
Here we go. Are they both, two graphics cards? Oh, booted up. We're doing SLI. Imagine doing SLI
with a 1080 and like a GTX 240M mobile card. I don't think that would work very well. Let's test
it out on a strike. Hey, guys. Guys, we got, hey, hey, new gear. Let's check this out. New gear.
I'm ready to play. Let's see if I can get that ace. Welcome to the stream, everybody. Last time
you saw this, I was playing at nine FPS. Not anymore. Look at that loading time. It's like cut
in half. Fight. What the fuck? 15 FPS? Where's the bottleneck? This is like a $600 graphics card.
Where's the bottleneck? It's the CPU. I need a better CPU now. Do you see like the four donations
I just got? That's people spamming me saying, omega lol idiot doesn't understand computers and
bottlenecks. I clicked outside the window. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Behind. Behind. Behind. Behind. Behind. Stunning. Stunning. All right. They're down. They're down.
They're down. They're down. They're down. All right. I'm going banana. Maybe a quad box. I'm going
banana. Nobody here. People wonder. I don't care. Get the fuck out of here. Well, that was just the
monitor. The computer is still on. Flush this fucking thing. Rage quit. Yeah, whatever. Rage
quit. That was my first stream. I get hacked every day. I get hacked every day. I get hacked
every single day. When is that guy going to get bored? All right. That's the end of my stream.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for cartoon character personality quizzes. Weird to say that out loud,
but I am. Hive Mind and Chubby Bunny. Let's try to turn the stream down to 144p. See what happens.
I got to remember to... Okay. Please remind me in the offline chat tomorrow to revert this.
Actually, let me do the... Let me just end the stream and show the credits and everything,
because this is going to be a joke. It's going to have to turn off immediately.
Please remind me. I don't want to have to turn this on and have to turn the stream off tomorrow,
because I fucked it up. Thanks for watching, guys. We'll see you tomorrow. Starting probably
around 2 p.m. Pacific. This game was surprisingly very fun. I thought this was going to be a thing
that we did for maybe 40 minutes, but it was pretty good. It was pretty fun. Thanks for watching,
guys. I'll probably play it a little more. At least enough to get partner. Not tomorrow,
though. We'll do that probably later this week. Play it tomorrow? We've got a plan tomorrow,
though, man. Are you ever going to play Mafia 1? Those of you that might be a little new to the
stream, the limit that is on if I stream a game again is usually about six days. If I play a game
and I don't play it within six to seven days, you're never going to see it again. I've come
to terms with that. What about Saw? Well, hold on. The only reason why I played Saw again is because
I have Saw 2, and we needed to conclude the first game before we played the second one.
That's the only reason why I played it again and beat it on stream. Yeah, I'll do House Flipper VR.
We'll do that next week, though. I'm not going to do it at lunch. I thought I was going to.
Grass Head Tooie? It's been seven days. Don't think so. Thanks for the subs, guys. There actually
were a lot of community subs, and no joking around in the fake game, in the real life here,
so thank you for those. Let me see. I want to make sure I didn't miss anything huge before I
do this. Let me just see, and then I'm going to do the 144p thing. Okay, hold on. What is 144p?
What bitrate is that? 144p is what resolution? 700 bitrate, and it's 700 144p.
It's 256 by 144. Oh, Jesus Christ, that's going to look terrible. 256 by 144.
Okay, you do realize I'm only going to be live doing this for like 30 seconds before I leave,
and thanks Boxbox for the raid, too. Make sure I didn't miss that one. I'll be right back.
Hang tight. I'm going to come back at 256 by 144 at 700 bitrate. This is going to be stupid.
I might not even be able to go live. 256 by 144.