Okay, that's better. I've been talking this whole time, by the way. I've been muted the whole time.
My GoXLR was not activated for some reason. Let me, let me restart that. Let me do the whole thing.
Let me do that entire, like, four- I was wondering what he was reacting to what I was saying.
What I was saying was, hi, how are you? I need a better title. Like, I was freaking out about the
title because the title was awful. It was like a placeholder for when I got here. But anyways,
people saying 420, 420. Listen, I don't, I don't let the calendar dictate when I'm gonna fucking
smoke, okay? I, I don't, I don't pick when I'm gonna get high based on what calendar day it is.
But frankly, I don't even know how to type on the keyboard right now. I have absolutely no idea
where I am. I'm, I'm sober as a fucking stone right now, okay? Relax. I'm not high. I'm completely
fine. I haven't, guys, I know that's a meme on the channel at this point. No, I'm not.
I don't know. This music doesn't help, by the way. Not the one you're hearing now,
this one. Bro, I promise, it's 420, but I haven't done anything. And yes, this is admissible in
whatever court you want to hold this up. Yeah. This is the background music from Monbizo.
Monbozo. How do you say this? Monbonzo? Bonzow? Let me pronounce, give it to me so I don't fuck
it up the rest of the screen. How do I say it? Monbozu. Monbozo. Monbozu. Monbozu. Monbozu.
Okay. I got it. Uh, but yeah. No, I'm not high on 420. I'm sorry. Sorry about that. I do think I
may have come up with a really cool, no, no, I need a title. Stop making, I don't want to go off
on a tangent or what, a title. Monbozu? What's a good title? What's, what's going to grab people?
What's going to grab them? How do I feel today? I feel okay. We'll see as we go on. I honestly
think it might've been like a seasonal thing. Over the last couple of weeks here in Vegas,
it's been ridiculously windy. Three or four, five days a week over the last like two and a half
weeks. It's been like 30, 40 plus mile per hour winds every, like every other day. I'm imagining
with the seasonal change and all the crazy wind, maybe it's kicked up a bunch of bullshit.
I don't know. Okay. How about, uh, let's drive. Does anybody really care about my titles at this
point? You know, like almost, almost like almost 12 years later. Imagine needing to come up with
like a title for your book 4,000 times. You know what I mean? I have, I have a thousand videos I've
uploaded on YouTube of like five plus years ago, right? Like 10, 12, 11, 12 years ago or whatever.
I've streamed like fucking a thousand, 2000 times. I'm talking about two to 3000 book titles.
They can't all be good. In fact, half of them weren't. So whatever. How about let's drive.
That's fine. Doesn't matter. My titles are awful anyways. Let's make it car. No, let's drive is
fine. Let me tweet too. Oh, also I think I've, I got something interesting. So I didn't want to be
late today and I had to go to the bathroom. So I think I came up with a really cool thing.
You can call me a weirdo if you want, but that's fine. So I, I like to have a coffee before I
stream. Just like a little, like an espresso or like one, just, just a coffee to get me kind of
going. Um, and I had to go to the bathroom really bad. So I drank an espresso while I took a shit
today. It was kind of cool. I kind of liked it. I don't know why. Is that like weird? I mean,
that's kind of weird, but like what there was, there wasn't anything wrong with it. Like one
of my mods just, I think freaked out. You cannot tell chat certain details of your life. It's okay.
You know, over the years, like I've got these great mods, right? That help out a ton.
There's lots of people in this community that help out that and a ton of their time, you know,
hitting me up about stuff and helping me do things and all this, right? They're awesome.
I have a, I have a manager, right? I've got a production manager. I'm starting to realize
that like a lot of people try like, Hey, hey, dude, dude, dude, hey, tone it down because like
what you just said is fucking weird. I never had this kind of feedback. I just kind of was weird
to you guys and everyone was, I just thought like it was normal. Community Jake will kind of give
me some like, Hey, did you happen to say this the other day? Yeah, don't say that. Okay. It doesn't
happen that often, but it happens like enough for me to realize that like, Hey, should I have told
everybody that I drink an espresso while I take a shit? But I'm okay. I fuck around a lot on stream.
I do. I tell fucking stories. We make up jokes. We make a bunch of shit up. We just have fun.
That's the whole point of this stream. But in between the nonsense, like I'm telling you some
some truths and this is true. This is not like, Oh, he's making that up for like a funny bit on
stream, right? A lot of times it is that you'll hear me. We go over all kinds of weird shit, right?
I brewed an espresso today and I shit while I drank the espresso. And I felt like I couldn't,
I had to tell somebody that I had couldn't lie about that. I couldn't like pretend that didn't
happen. I could not pretend it didn't happen. You know, I like have to confess to somebody.
And you guys are some of the first people that I've seen or talked to today.
Holly doesn't even know this. I didn't have like time to explain it. I didn't have time to tell
Holly this stuff. But you know, all right, so we're going to do mon bison, mon bazoo.
And the whole time I was doing it, I'm just waiting, just relax. I'm here all day.
The entire time I was doing it, I kept saying to myself, I don't know, it was almost like I was,
I was doing it. I was like, Oh, this is weird. But I'm doing, but I kind of, I think it's that cool.
I was holding the espresso cup. Cool. Cool. I had it like tilted in my left hand. I'm just
sitting there like acting cool. There's nobody who cares. I don't know why I was doing it.
Okay. Mon, I was gonna say car game, car driving game. How do you spell it? B, A, zoom. What about
a cigarette? B, how do you spell it? B, B what? Cigarettes on the toilet. No, I wouldn't. Okay.
Even if I did smoke, I would never smoke in my house or in my apartment or anything. That
shit. No, that builds up. And then, no, that's gross. I was smoking in a house. No, thank you.
Okay. Mon, nobody has told me how to spell this yet. I guess I could just look over here,
couldn't I? There it is. People asking, enough like fucking around. People are asking how I'm
doing. I'm okay. I just figured I could stream. I didn't want to, if I got up today and spent the
day kind of figuring out how I felt and I feel fine, then I'm not just going to be like, Oh guys,
I can't stream today. It would be, it would be bullshit. So, cause I told you I wanted to stream
today. Okay. Let's do it. All right. Real voice. Yeah. Good to go. I think we're good to go. I
opened the game just to see if it worked. And by the way, you get a face cam if you've done your
homework, which I can't, I don't, I can't confirm that you have. All right. This is Mon Bazoo.
So, those of you wondering what this game is, is a game where you have to fix and build a car
and then race the car. It's kind of like, I don't know. We'll see. What kind of shirt should I have?
I don't know. What color? Okay. I'm kind of a gray Andy. 80% of my wardrobe is gray and dark blue.
Is that okay? Let's see. How do I, is there a punch? I can go to sleep, but I don't think
I should probably, I shouldn't do that right now. No, I mean, unless we can confirm,
unless we can confirm that chat has done their homework for tomorrow,
I'm not turning the face cam on. I don't have any electricity. What? No water. There's no water
and no electricity in the house. Mods, can you do a quick poll that says, did you finish your
homework? And if it's more than, I'm not going to tell you the percentage that I have in my head,
but just run it. Cannabis packager? Calm yourself. You need to sit down to use the pack. Wait,
weed grinder? Oh, it's this Easter. I forgot it's a happy Easter. Isn't, was it yesterday, the day
before? There's E to use. There's a total of zero pack of joint close by. There's no harvest basket.
You want to try to roll air? Okay. Should I do the Easter stuff first? How do I stand up?
Should I get the Easter stuff first? Okay, so mouse scroll is to move it around.
Can I open the fridge? Oh shit. What's in here? I thought this was ground beef. Yeah, don't lie.
Seriously. Poutine and maple syrup. Maple syrup, poutine, energy, anxiety. All right. Well, let's,
I'm not doing that yet. Is this a Canadian game? I guess it is. Judging by that. Okay. Let's go out
here. This item can't be recycled. So I have a truck. Can I go in the car? What am I supposed to
do? Okay. Is it in drive? Where's drive? I don't, I don't know. Manual transmission guys.
Where's drive? This is four wheel and two wheel. Is this in drive? What is drive?
It's a manual. I don't know how to drive a manual. Is it the park? Oh, the parking brake was on.
The parking brake was on. Okay. Wait, what am I supposed to do? Okay. Um, do I have a map? You're
a 15 year old. I did not, I guys, I drive, I drive a car every day. All right. You, I'm turning the
cam on for this. If you give a video game to your parents and you say, Hey mom, dad, I want you to
drive around in this car game. Okay. Your parents, even though they drive fucking like 80 hours a
week, whatever it is, I drive like a hundred fucking hours a week, a hundred, probably like,
no, way less than that. How many, okay. Like if you put like a couple of thousand miles a month
on a car, which is like probably like a hundred hours a month, I don't know, whatever it is,
you, your parents are going to sit there and go like, I don't, I don't, this just doesn't make
any sense to me. Uh, uh, junior, junior, how do I do this? And your fucking mother drives you
wherever you want, right? She, she has for years. You're my, my parents did for years.
They're not going to know what the fuck they're doing. They're going to have absolutely no idea
what to do. My dad used to, we would, when GTA three or GTA four, whatever it was, GTA three,
I would watch him play it and he would be sitting there going like this with the controller in his
hand. Like tap, tap, tap, tap. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What did I, I just hit that person and he would
just drive into walls and shit. And this guy, this guy like commuted every day. So come on.
You can't give me that much shit about this. What does a four wheel drive and get out of here?
Okay. For the love of God, I don't, I don't even need this truck anyways. I don't care.
Need to reverse. I've, what does this take place in fucking Europe or something? Like,
hold on, let me see what this car is. Okay. All right. There we go. All right. Here we go.
A car reverse neutral drive. What the hell's going on in that truck? How do I not have electricity?
Hey, what does this mean? I don't know. I've never driven one of these before. So let me,
can I even, God damn it. I think I have to restart the game. Why would this, why is there a ditch
right here? I can't. Okay. What is reverse in a truck like this? Four wheel drive. This, this one,
three, two, three, four. What's, what's reverse? Three, two, one. Where is the shift?
He's a city boy. I'm honest to God. Where's reverse? Is that pedal right there? Reverse?
Oh my fucking God. Okay. I don't, what are you? It's not clearly labeled. All right. I'm just
going to go. What am I looking for? All right. Where am I right now? I have a hundred bucks.
Where am I? He's driving with his knees, crash incoming. I just don't know where I am. Do I
have an indicator on the map of where I am? Where's my house? Okay. I see the wind turbines.
How much gas do I have? Half tank. This is not even possible. What? Put it in four wheel drive.
Quick. My anxiety went up. Come on, go. All right. I'm fine. Um, sigh, another fall joke.
Okay. So that's the river. Hold on. I need to get like a better view. Should I have it in four wheel
drive and four? Well, I'm off roading right now. That's fine. This is an old German. I got,
I don't fucking know what to do. I don't know where I am in the game and I don't have any
instructions. Okay. Here's the wind and this is a road, right? All right. So this road has to be.
All right. Just stop the fucking car. Turn the fucking car off. It didn't break. Dude,
why do I have to play like fucking ping pong to put the car in park? Does this car even have a
park? Okay. I see the wind turbines. So I need, do I have like a compass? I don't know what
direction I'm facing. I'm on this road that's on that kind of right side there where the wind
turbines are. I guess I could follow the road down to go to this parfait. I'll try that. I'm
just going to follow the road. He's an automatic Andy. Okay. How many people here? There are 13,000
people here. I guarantee you. I guarantee you only like eight of you know how to drive a manual.
I'm serious. What is wrong with the car? Yeah. How many of you guys know how to drive a manual?
Fucking none of you. The parking brake is on. Oh, I didn't, did they do their homework? I didn't
even look. Did they do their homework? Okay. Here's the split. I need to go to the right or
left. I think to the left. Okay. You need to shift up, please. I got it. It's Monday at 1230.
You're going to stall out the engine. I don't drive trucks. Shift to second. Shift. I don't
want to go that fast on this road. Don't you understand? Oh shit. What's this? The brake,
please. What's going on here? Is this on the map? I need to call them. Where's my phone?
Do I have an inventory? Do I have a phone? Do I have a telephone?
What? I just spit? What the hell was that? All right. Let me look at the controls for a second
because I, there's no, I don't know what anything does. Smoke. Say sorry. Say a French slur. Spit.
I don't think I have a telephone. Can I get around this? I don't think I have a phone here.
All right. One, two. Oh, there we go. Dash is reverse. And then I have all the gears. There
we go. I don't have to look down off the road. All right. So I have, I can't go here for a while.
So let's put it in reverse. Let's get out of here. What the fuck is happening?
God damn it. I, who uses that? I guys, I haven't, I'm sorry. I'm not in a Ford commercial.
I haven't used my parking brake to park on a hill in the entire time I've ever owned an
operated vehicle. Can we get face cam back? Okay. You can. All right. So I can't go that way.
I wish there was a little blip where I was. I'm going to go back and go left.
I'm going to run out of gas too. This is going to be a disaster. Oh, what's this?
Jim's You Pull. How do I get in here? Can I get in? Is this on the map? Jim's You Pull.
It's not on the map. You're not friend enough with Jacques to get here. Oh,
well don't Jacques. Am I up there? Top right. Hit Y. I think I'm up in the top right. So if I go
this way, I should hit Parfait. I don't even know how to go home. So this is all right. So if I go,
if I just keep going this way, I'll end up at Parfait, right? I think that's what's going to
happen. Let's find out. We're in the webcam one. Okay. Do I have like an objective list?
Fucking God. I am never going to get over that. I'm going to have the parking brake on every time.
So let's keep going this way. What does the maple syrup indicator mean?
How do you look like that? Because I turn 40. Probably before you are like 25. Okay. I'm hungry.
Oh shit. Okay. There's no damage. It doesn't matter. All right. We're at a split here.
So what does this look like on the road? All right. So if I go right, I'm going to go over to
Jeve. If I go left, I'm going to go down till I hit another split and then I want to go right.
Where do I want to go? I don't even know how to get back to the house. Go to the city. Okay. So
to go to the city, I want to go left and then drive until I hit another kind of fork. And I want to
go right at the fork, right? I want to go left here, right? Please help me. You should go home
and eat. Yeah. You left here and then keep making rights. Yeah. That's what I figured. Hopefully I
have enough gas to get there. Go left and drive past two rights, then right. All right. Here it is.
Here it is. Here it is. So go keep going on. It's not on the map. Left is right. Left. And then
I can't read this map. Turn right. I think you lost, bro. I am. I just, I don't know how I even
got over here. Is that, okay. Ariette. Oh shit. It's the town right there. All right. I got it.
I got to, I got to the road. I got to the road. Right. Oh, okay. Don't be fucking idiot. It's not
a driving game. I mean it is, but you know what I mean? All right. So I made it to the town. What's
what is here? Is this where I came from? What's here? We work on the farm. Serve yourself. I got
a potato. I have a to-do. What did I get? What do you mean to-do list? How did I get a to-do list?
Curds cheese pack. Okay. Remember to pay. I think I am. I spent 20 bucks. I need gas too for my
truck. This is going to fall out. What is that thing? I think I'm good. I need a gas station.
They're still in there. All right. Gas station. What does that sign say? The cam is blocking.
Oh, where should I put it? I don't see a gas station in this town. And let me see it on the
map. I am like in that upper left quadrant, right? Oh, what's this? Can somebody like fuck the car?
Oh, post box. Do I have a mailbox? I don't think I have a mailbox. How do I get to my like to-do
list? I don't even know what that was. I quest friendships. Okay. Brother gas owner and mom. How
do I pull up-is why? How do I pull up the quest menu? Every time you clear your throat,
I'm going to play one game of Hearthstone. Snack delivery. Oh, I need to figure out how to get
back to the fucking house. You know, I'm just going to walk around because what's the point
of wasting gas? Okay. Snack delivery. Five dollars for poutine. Oh, I just ate it. All right. Cool.
So I just ate. I wish I could like fucking mark on the map where this is. I think it's the one
that's circled 10 out of 10, right? So if I'm right there, I wish I had just knew where I was,
what direction I was facing. Okay. Let's get in here. So I now need to eat or drink maple syrup.
Is that how that works? You have an, had an egg snack. Other car located. Is this a gas station?
Ooh. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I found something. How much is gas?
Weather we have today. Yes. Well, anyways, thanks for stopping by. Have a nice one.
This is also expensive. What am I supposed to do with this? Um, coffee cup, eyelashes.
Hold on. I can put a car eyelashes on. All right. Wait, I want this. Okay. What do you, what?
Normand, leave me alone with the racetrack. There's nothing. What else do I need here? Okay.
So this is where you get the equipment. Window tint or green windows. What do you think?
I probably shouldn't spend any more money to be honest.
Next one. This is unique. How do I store this stuff? I don't know what this is. I'm taking this,
whatever it is though. I don't know what any of this stuff does, but I'm just going to take
as much, as much free stuff as I can fit in the trunk. Cause I don't know what this stuff does.
And I need to put gas in the car too. What about over here? What's this mixing paint?
$30 per can. What the fuck? This is stealing. I'm, I mean, this should be fine. Can I take anything
else? All right. I got to remember where this is. I need to start to put this into long-term
memory. Cause I'm going to drive around in a gosh darn circle or almost 45 minutes in without a funny
joke. You missed when I flipped the truck 400 times and went in the ocean. Sorry. Sorry. You
came late to the stream. All right. So now let me close this and put some gas in the car. I
probably shouldn't be on four wheel drive either. Right. I get $36. What side is the gas tank on?
Left side. What? What do you mean the store is closed? What are you talking about? Can I sleep
in the trunk? Do I even have enough gas to get back? How do I get, how do I get home? Okay.
Where's my house? I, from here. Can you guys please direct me? You actually, I actually don't know,
Wald. So if I'm on that top left kind of quadrant over here and my house is across the kind of lake
down, right? Just go right. Just take rights. Okay. I don't, I don't have enough gas to fucking
get out of here. I'm just going to sit here. Just sit at the window. Can you get hit by a car?
How long does it take to get to the morning? Go to the church. I don't have enough gas to go.
This is going to be a fucking disaster because you understand I am, I look at my gas tank.
How do I zoom in? I'm not going to get anywhere. Walk to the church. Oh God. I'm going to forget
where the fuck this is. All right. I'm going to church. That's gross. I can't, I don't even
think there's a run. This is making me think of the hot dog guy. I'm just saying I can do,
I can do it quick. It's in the air and it comes back down. Fastest hot dog shooter.
Hey, I don't know. I've never seen anybody do it like this in the Northwest. I don't know.
This is closed. I'm actually just going to be walking around until it's dawn. I've seen,
oh, I thought you said you've never seen that video. You know what's really wild thinking
about that? There's not, I think a person on earth that has not seen the fastest hot dog
shooter video. Imagine knowing that every single person on earth has seen that video and you're
that guy. Every single person on earth has seen that video. That's kind of crazy. All right. I
need to get out of here. Even I, should I just restart the game? Go back to your truck. You're
going to get robbed. You can wait, you can get robbed. Are you serious? Yes. Oh my goodness.
Don't even tell me. Do I have a weapon? I have a flashlight. How do I run? Slender man. All right.
I went this way. Can I do AMPM? I don't, I don't, I don't like the 19. I, I like to see AMPM. I have
to burn into memory how to get back here. Where the fuck am I going? Where's my truck? It was the
other way. It was, wasn't it right down this way from the church or was it that way? Gas station.
It was this way. I'm so useless without a fucking map indicator. I swear to God.
Where's the gas station from here? There's something behind you. There's nothing behind me. I'm
fine. It was, it was this way, wasn't it? Watch out. We literally saw it. There's no sprint either.
I just missed it. How could I, I don't see it. Where is it? This is the snack place. Okay. So
it's over here. Remember I go, I got a snack. Ah ha ha. And then I kept going. There it is.
What do you mean? Did you not hear that? I don't hear anything. Holy fuck. What? What? What? What?
I'm in the car. I'm safe. Drive, drive, drive. All right. All right. All right.
All right. How do I get out of here? I don't, I can't, I don't know. I can't read that.
Take the bus. It's almost midnight. Get out of here. I don't, you guys are fucking with me.
I'm hearing like sound. Okay. Should I just go this way? How do I turn my headlights on?
How do I turn the headlights on? Okay. It's a flashlight. I don't know. How do you turn on
headlights? Can you fucking imagine holding a flashlight to drive? What's that say? Guys,
there's no car light. Oh, there we go. I got it. Okay. If I follow this road, am I going to end up?
Okay. This is residential. Do the German nine eight five here a bit. I can't do that right now.
Don't stop at the barn. Run. Am I on the right track? I can't, this lights are terrible.
I can't take a left because this stupid ditch. I have to find the road where there's no ditch
right here. I'd be honest. Am I actually going on the right? All my shit just fell out. I'm
restarting the game. I'm re I'm going to restart the whole game. I'm restarting the whole game.
Now I get it. Now I understand what's going on. I'm restarting the game. I'm just going to restart.
Just redo the game. Let's restart. I'm restarting. Yes. I quit. New game. Okay. Now I get it.
Okay. Where's my. All right. Am I on the map? So this is my truck. This is the car. I have to
like do work to this car, right? I need a tire. How do I get to the task menu? Does it even exist?
There's a map. I don't think there is. Go to the shed bro. Build the sugar shack. Buy a roll of
tubing. Connect 10 maple trees to the shack. Okay. Build a sugar shack. Very. All right. Here we go.
All right. Okay. All right. What the fuck was I driving around for no reason? Look. Okay. To do.
Use the tool adjustable spanner to screw bolt. Okay. Screw bolt. I do that on the car like down
here, right? Yep. Okay. Very nice. Happy 420. Hey, happy 420 man. Yeah. One of those days. Can I
store stuff? Make this easier. These are so rusty. I put this here. Is this done? Yeah. I was going
to place all the screws first and then maybe I can actually drive this fucking thing and actually
drive an automatic car. My God. Those things are the same color as the ground. The screws.
Whatever. I'm not going to. Why would I restart? I'm fine. I need one more. There we go. Okay. So
now that I have the tire on, does this thing have an engine? Very cool. All right. So this is to do
right now. Install the intake back on the engine. Intake. How do I open the hood? I need the wrench
to do that. Inside the car. Oh, there it is. Open the fucking hood. What happened to my wrench?
How do I open the hood? You need to use the hoist. Hoist puller. Place it on the ground.
Patch it to vehicle. It was just a button. You fucking whackers. Whatever. Okay. Do I have to screw
it in? Oh, it's a generator. All right. So what happened to the wrench that I had? Install the
intake. Torque the wheels. Dude, I had a wrench and it's just fucking gone. Where is my wrench?
Is it right there? Where? Dude. Okay. I don't know where the wrench is. I have absolutely no idea.
Do I not have an inventory? Look down. Guys, it's not here. It's by the car?
Ha! Bruh, I can't. It's not on the screen right now. I'm being dead serious. It's not on the
screen. It's not on the screen. I dropped it somehow. Is it like in my hand? Is it like a wrench
button that I took? I stored it? Look down. Dude, we are at a bird's eye view. The wrench is not
on the ground. I'm, I think it's fucking bugged. I don't think it's in the, I don't think it's here.
I'm going to sit right here and I want everybody just to fucking tell me exactly where to go from
right here. I'm going to wait 10 seconds every time I ask. Behind the shed. You motherfucker.
You got to be kidding me. It's, uh, yeah. I, I never stepped, I never went over there.
I was never behind the shed. I, it bugged through the wall or something. Whatever. Who cares? Let's
go. All right. I need screws. I gotta screw this in, right? Short-term memory loss. I didn't even
go back there, dude. All right. How do I, um, is it 12? Is it, or is it just, okay, there we go.
Right there. That's in. I think I need like two or three. Bingo. What? One more. There. Okay.
Need more? When are you going to play Strawberry Magic 2? Okay. The people that are disrespecting
the streamer on telling me to play Strawberry Magic 2, I want them timed out. Um, is it, is it in?
I think it's in. Should I just close the hood? Are we good? Um, how do I, how do I say like,
uh, what else should I do? I screwed it in and do I have to do anything else?
Uggy part. Screws. Um, I don't know how to, like, solidify this. I need more screws. Really?
Oh, I don't know. It's right below you. Yeah. It looks like there's no more screws I can put in.
I don't think there's any more room for screws. How can I fit in here?
It screwed in. Are you mad at me? Look towards the black box? Oh, there we go. Okay. There it is.
There's my, there's my mon-bizow. Okay. Engine's in. Torque the wheels. I don't know what that
means. I think that's what it wants me to do, right? City boy. None of you guys here know any
of this shit either. Please. Some of you probably, some of you that do are sitting there going, I do.
You fucking bozo, right? But most of us have no idea what's going on here. Buy a tire pump at,
okay. Buy a tire pump at Cali Gas in town. Build the sugar shack. Let's go ahead and
just do this part first. I need a tire pump at Cali, Cali Gas in town. Does this car drive now?
Or do I have to take the truck? This has got no gas, so never mind. Don't take the chain,
so I'll put it in the shed. Why is he so mean today? I'm not being mean. I am handling a toxic
community. Take the gas can. Good call. I'm kidding. You guys are fine. Relax. Somebody said,
damn right. Get out of here. Relax. Okay. So, so where I am right now, I need to go to the gas
station. So to go into the gas station, don't go that way. It's just go to the main road,
which is that way over there. I have plenty of gas. I got my gas tank. I've got plenty of money.
I'm going to eat and drink something. That was a hard day's work on the car. I'm going to drink
this coffee. I'm going to spit into the toilet and miss and hit the ground and not clean it up.
We're going to go with our gray shirt today. Let me make sure I'm fully okay. I'm good. All right.
Good to go. We move. Remember this road. Burn it into your memory right now. This is loud,
isn't it? Day nine of German not reading my messages. I just read it. Sorry. You're going
to reset it. Okay. So this is now the main road. So this is a left. By the way, that's not a very
long counter. That's not that long. Do you understand? I said I was going to play paper
Mario like three years ago and somebody's been waiting for paper Mario every day. Do you
understand? It's just that like there are people that were waiting like two years for me to play
Cheeto, which understandable. I said I was going to play Cheeto like a year and a half ago and I
never did. What the fuck? I'm waiting for paper Mario. I don't think it's ever going to happen.
I just don't think so. We're fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. Just don't freak out. Just let it go to
four wheel. The fuck is the road? You literally own the switch online. Just play it. Okay. I lost
my gas can. Was there anything else in the back of the car? Dude, where is the gas can? My God.
Is it the other way? No, I took this. I took the chance out. We're good. Other way. Oh my fucking
God. Disrespect me again and see why I'm on that today. Where is it? It's not. Hey, there it is.
I got it. And right now that person right now is going like I like go over I go and you can see
them through the windshield like and then they turn to the person in the passenger side and they're
like fucking idiot. Piece of fucking shit. What a dumb fuck that guy is. Fuck that guy. And then
as they as they're pulling away, it's like, yeah, good job, man. And then like, oh, and then and
then I go on like a 25 minute rant about like society and like humanity. The person writer.
Wrong way. This is the right way. This is the right way.
Um, am I I'm going the right way, right? I don't know. Oh, shit. Sorry. Hey, I go down. I grab my
phone. Oh, my phone. Hey, I think no, this is the right way. Isn't the church over there? I actually
think I might have turned around. I don't know. No, it's not. Can I drive by this? How do I hit?
No, please. No, please. I was going the wrong way. Gas. It's in the trunk. It's right there.
Stop distracting me. Oh, my God. I can't fucking play this. Did you lose the gas can?
I can't fucking play this game. If the game does not have a map indicator, I can't play it.
I have to be honest with you. If I can't see a blip on the map right now, I can't play the game.
It's not possible. There it is. I got it in the cab. Yeah, there's no map indicator. I can't play
the game because I'll get distracted and look over here and like, look at you while I'm still
holding W turn like this and then look back this way. And I think I'm on the same road that I was
when I looked over at you. So it's not happening. You should just do paper Mario. You wouldn't
survive 23 hours in the wilderness. Yes, I would because I would just eat fucking bugs and dirt
and I'd be fine. You don't need a map to eat bugs on the ground. Excuse me. I would be just
fine. Did you never survive like in the wilderness 24 hours? I would eat bugs on the ground and I
would live. Okay. Next question, please. I don't need a map to figure out how to eat fucking like
stuff on the grubs on the ground. Sorry about that. I wish there was a horn. Yep. Still funny,
I guess. This is not even remotely where the town is, though, by the way. Like, do I even have a
compass? I don't even know. How do I get to the fucking town? The gas station is going to close.
Hurry up. This person thinks I'm fucking chasing them. I'm driving in a giant circle. I don't
think this is how you get to the fucking town. I've been. Oh my fucking God. I've been driving
around in a circle, the bottom left. Okay. So where the fuck even am I? There's three of those
silo places. Am I driving straight now? Just keep going straight. You actually need waypoints.
I'm sorry. There's one road to get to the town and there's no compass and there's no. The map is
just like a map that I. It's like Elden Ring. It's like the Elden Ring map. And to get to Lunaria,
I have to. Whatever. North, south, east, west. They've had that since the fucking stone age.
Where is it? There we go. Take a right? What the fuck? I just wish I had a compass.
Cavemen were looking at the sun like burning their eyes and going like, oh, that way. You need to use
the sun. Okay. Oh, there we go. Hey, I don't. I found it. All right. All right. All right. All
right. I need, I need to go to the store. The store was over here. I remember the school. Hey.
Okay. What did I need to do? I needed to buy something from here. What did I need to buy?
It was something from here. Don't you don't close yet. It was some kind of a torque thing, right?
Pire pump. Thank you. Why not? I don't want to buy super. How do I fill the tank? Take the cap off?
How made the wrench? Uh, it's, they're going to close in fucking one second. You just get gas in
the car. Okay. Take this off. I got the tire pump at least. Okay. Um, how do you fill the gap? Do I
have to actually go in here and say, can I fill this? They're not closed yet. Do I have to like,
how do I, I wanted to fill this open the cap. I, there's some special fucking like sit around
and do a seance to get the cap to open, steal the gas. I can't. And guys, where did it take the
nozzle off the can? How do you, but how do you do that? The other one? God damn it. What is this?
What the hell is that? What, what is this? What is the item? I'll be back tomorrow motherfucker.
And I'm going to fill this. I'm out of gas. Yeah, I know. Take the, but I thought I could just go
over there and like press E. It says like E to U. I don't, I don't, I'm trying. I, I don't know.
I had to like unscrew the cap. I, I come over to this fucking thing and I'm pressing it. First of
all, it says, sorry, you don't use that, that like pleb gas. I got the tire pump. Who cares?
Where's the, okay. Okay. So what's the fastest way to get back to the house? That way, the,
this way, right? There's the church, but bro, I don't even know what direction I'm fucking facing.
Absolutely not. You have a map. I don't know what road I'm on. I don't know what road I'm even on.
I'm like in the town up here somewhere. Okay. Is the church on the map? I can't look closer.
I'm going to growl in a second. Snack bar. Okay. The snack bar is circled at like, as like 10 out
of 10. So I'm on, I can't even point at it. I can't even show you. I think I'm on the road.
That's like to the bottom right of 10 out of 10, right? So I need to go straight left, right,
straight left, right. Let's see if that works. Straight left, right. That not right. This is
the school bus straight, right, left. I think I'm going the right way is now. Wait, is it that road
right there? Cause this is now, bro, I have no idea. You pass the bus to get in, but then I'm
going to be on this. This is really far away, isn't it? This is the wrong bridge. Yeah. Now I'm all
the fucking way left. Okay. So I passed this, but I drove around in a huge circle. I'm not going to
have enough gas to get home, let alone come back here and fill the tank. Left was a shortcut.
I'm not going to be able to drive the car back here. Why do you have Fulbright on your webcam?
I have auto exposure on. I don't know. Am I in four wheel drive? You need to take, I'm literally
driving the worst possible way to get back here. Oh God. I'm just, okay. First of all, where am I
on this map right now? Where, where is, where is my fucking house? Where is my house on this map?
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? What is it called? It's called roulette. Okay. Roulette
means my house. Okay. That's all I need to know. So if I go left on this road and then go right
and then go left, I'll be in town. It means trailer. So I go left, just bang right. Don't
go down this stupid ass highway. Left, stay right and then left and then get into town. I got it.
Okay. Get me the fuck out of here before I freak out the fucking goddamn door. Put the stupid gas
tank in here. I'm ready. I'll fix the car up in a minute. I'll fix the car up in just a moment.
I'm not going to get angry. I'm just going to relax. We're just going to go and it's, it's,
it's literally left on this road. Hang a right and then hang my first left. I can take, I'll be in
town. Left, hang a right. Let's go. Let's go. Everybody relax. Everything's fine. This is,
this is it right now. We're going to go. Nobody yell. Nobody freak out. We're going to, everything's
going to be just fine. Okay. Everything. We're good. Hey, see, see, I'm happy. Fucking
I'm 36. We don't fucking freak out. It's a video game. I turn, I'm 36 years old.
We don't have fucking temper tantrums over like not being able to know where the parking break
is. We relax and we're an adult now. We're an adult and we've been an adult for a long time.
Don't run into the school bus. Okay. So no, no, no, no, no. Go this way.
I am now on this road. We're going to go left. Remember this. This is like the little, like the
Moses split the fucking ocean. We're going to go here. Here we are. Okay. We are now at this
intersection where we're going to go left. Stay, don't go that way. Stay left. Stay straight over
here. Left, right. Stay this way and go. Okay. Left and go. Very easy. Simple. We're good.
We're good. Don't freak it out. No, like dry out of a clips. We're good. We're good. We're good.
Everything's fine. Now we're fine. It was easy. It was just simple. I just didn't know where my
house was. I didn't know that roulette meant house in fucking French. I got my compass. Now
that's all I needed. Remember this. I do. All right, everybody. We're good. We're good. We're
good. We're good. We're good. We're good. No, fuck. Just don't fuck.
Okay. Can I put this in the glove box? So now I need to pay attention because take a look at this.
Ready? I am right now. I wish I could point with my mouse. I, I am right now right at the little
tip of the bottom of the top Island. Right? So if I drive straight on this road and then
I got to remember, let me burn this into my memory right now. That mountain right there,
this one right here, drive towards that mountain and have that mountain be on your left here on the
right spot. The church needs to be on my right. Going out mountain right there. There it is.
Got it. Abstinence Andy. Mountain peak, mountain peak, mountain peak left. Mountain peak, mountain
peak, mountain peak left. Mountain peak, mountain peak, mountain peak left. Mountain peak, mountain
peak, mountain peak left. I will never forget it now. I made it a stupid fucking song and let me
like make it so I'm not like a fucking red Andy here. That's better. All right. All right. We can
now play the game now. I apologize to everybody that came here and said I'm fucking leaving this
stream. This guy sucks. If you came back to check, you probably didn't, but I'm, I'm now playing the
game now. Question is from the church. Who's that? It's not going anywhere. What's up? Some cars make
so much noise. Ew. Can you find something for me, please? I take a walk this afternoon. I can look
for your object. I didn't lose anything. Did I? You only have $80. That's interesting. All right.
I gotta hurry up before the sun goes down because I'm restarting a third time. That would be an
embarrassment. I'm not going to run somebody over for fun. Okay. The gas station is now down here.
So it's just straight to the gas station. Don't look at the snack bullshit. Don't go over there.
Right here. It's just straight. No, it's not. Okay. It's a left at the snack shack. We go straight
and then it's a left at the end of the snack shack road. He's so mad. Um, I am. I am. I'm trying to
calm down. I really am. I'm trying to relax, but I'm so fucking heated. Okay. Where's the gas station?
School bus was there and then it says snack shack, but this, the gas station is all on here.
What do you mean? Ludwig's coming. What do you mean? All Ludwig for directions. What do you mean?
What's Ludwig coming? I got it. Give me fucking gas. Stop. Stop the car. Stop the car. So what
do I do now? Okay. Please screw this back on. It took him two hours to do this. Dude, give me a
little bit of a slack here. Okay. This is confusing. Okay. I have gas. I want more gas in this car.
Give me this. Open that up. I want more gas. Get out of the fucking car. Is this actually working?
Turn the car off. How much is the bike pump? How much is the bike pump? All right. Okay. I only have
$6 left. Is that bad? Broke ass. I made it before they closed. Hey, it drove into a house. All right.
Do I have everything I need? Okay. What was that fun song that we sang? Mountain peak left. Just
find the mountain peak. Save the game. Uh, how? It's not that one. It's over here. There it is.
Got it. Okay. Mountain peak. It's be on our left. So now we just drive on this road. We go through
the, the Moses pass, which is right here. Well, no, no, no, not quite. So now we are at this
intersection. We stay to the right. Wait. No, we don't. We go. Yes, we stay right. Yes, we do.
Stay to the stop lying to me because I'm at that. We stay right. And then I drive on this road
forever. Wait. Yep. And then here we go. Done. Done. Done. We're good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. We're good. We're good. I'm not going to let you guys gaslight the fuck out of me right
now. Not when I'm this upset. Here we go. Here's the Moses split. Get it. Finally got it. Everything's
fine. Right? Yeah. This is worse than the unlocked stream. Oh, it's not. You're out of your mind.
You've, you've gone, you've gone hollow. If you think that. Thank God. Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Where's the gas tank? Oh my God. Finally. There's a gas tank. Let's do it. Oh my God. I
finally can drive the car. This is working. I'm not fucking doing that till I'm certain that's
happening. Okay. I know it's on. Yeah. I'm not doing that till I'm 100% certain. Where'd the
cat, where'd the gas go? I'm not certain that that's actually working. So I'm just going to
sit this down. Okay. I don't know if that's working or not. So I'm afraid to do that until
I'm certain. So let's, let's do, let's fix the goddamn car. Good. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Very good. Very good. Very good. The wrench, the wrench out here. Let's go. This is big progress.
It kind of, it is. It really is. I wish I could pick up more than one thing at a time though.
Every screw is going over here. This is worse than the unlocked stream. No, it's not. And you know
why it's not? Because you couldn't even read the text in the unlocked stream. It was not even
visible. You couldn't read it. And that was the whole stream was you being able to read the text
on the cards. There's no way this is worse. Not a chance. Not a chance in fucking hell.
All right. Let's go. All right. Bingo. This dude's hair makes him look like he got back from a parent
teacher conference. Oh, what is it? Parent teacher conference hair. I don't, I wish I knew. I, I'm
too old to understand what that means. What's that supposed to mean? You're, oh, parent teacher
conference Andy. Why do I like just picture like a bunch of kids laughing at me right now?
Doing the loud kid point laugh thing where they go ha ha ha ha like loud.
Really? Parent teacher conference. And I'm just sitting there with like suspenders on.
Look at this guy's hair. I don't even, what do you even mean? What are you, who, who,
what are you on about? Wrong screws. I'm going to fix this car and I'm going to play this game.
And I'm telling you right now, it's going to be epic. Um, you just, I need to put the car up so
I can get underneath, jack the shit up right now. Where does it go? I don't, I fucking don't
understand what's going on with this goddamn thing. Give me the, is that bad? That in? Okay.
That's in. I think there's one more that I have not tightened. Here we go. Okay. The engines in
there. What the hell do you want me to do now? Pork the wheels with this thing, right? I got it.
I got it. I got it. We're good. Do power generator and save the game. I don't think this has any gas.
Does this have gas? I can't tell. I don't know. Uh, is that halfway? So I have to start it. I think
it's on. All right. Power the computer. Chill the computers. I want to save. Hurry up. Okay.
Save the game. Thank God. It took two hours to save the game and be at a place where I'm good.
Oh my God. Thank God. We're playing age of empires. Okay. So now there's a good bed. Okay.
It's Monday. Still raining. I have potatoes and shit in the car. Right. Deep fryer. Okay. All
right. All right. Right. Let me do this too. Put it in the fridge too. It's 12 AM. What I'm bringing
my groceries in. Oh, I put 50 curry. Oh, I didn't want to do that. Okay. We're good. Should I have
not put those in? Should go back to bed. Hold on. Listen to shed. All right. I think everything's
out of the truck. There's only one more. That's it. Yeah. Okay. Everything's out of the truck.
Do a trampoline stream. Okay. Close this up. Should I put the cheese in here? 100 curds cheese in
there. 0% French fries. All right. Here's the French fry cutter. You're missing a frying basket
in the deep fryer. Do I have a frying basket? I probably should put these in here because the
won't they go bad? Um, all right. So do I have to don't lose that potato? I only have one potato
for the love of God. Is it in the sink? It's not in the sink. Do I need to buy a fry basket?
But do I have one here somewhere? I don't think I have one. Well, I'll just put it in the fridge.
Figure that out later. Is it in the sink? I mean, if that's it, I can't. No, that's like a sink
thing. Frying basket. I don't think I have one. Turn the light on. No, I don't have one. If I do,
it's in a place. I don't know where it is. Okay. All right. Uh, that car is almost ready to go.
I don't know where it could be anywhere. It's the square basket in the. No, I don't have one.
I'm just gonna go back to bed. Okay. It's almost time to get up. Can I turn the computer off? Yeah,
turn that off. Lift on Martin. Ask Martin for a lift. Martin is sleeping. Try later. Wait,
you'd mean to tell me that I could have just gotten in somebody else's car the whole time?
It's 3 a.m. Hold on. Can I change this to? I don't think I can. Oh, dude. 144. Ow, my ears.
We're almost there. All right. Let me just. I can work on the car a little bit more now.
All right. So that was the wheels. What's now? I have to pump the tires up, right?
Talk to your brother, Francis. Um, plant a tree, find some seeds, harvest a plant, make a cannabis.
Wait, I got seeds. Where's my brother? Is he on the map? Okay. Do I know where Francis is?
Potato is gone. No, it's not. Right there. Brother's name is Francis. I don't see Francis on here.
Parfait. Does this mean like one of these mean brother? Brother is top right. Top right. Okay.
So I need to go right on this road and then bang a right and then bang a right and stay on the road.
I got it. I don't think it's actually top. But don't lie to me. Where is it? That was a lie. Oh.
Brother is French is, uh, ask your brother. What does the fridge note say? Oh,
that's a let's find out. Mammon mother. Can I call my mom and ask what my brother's phone number is?
Or is there like a note with my brother's phone number on it? Martin. I'm just gonna call mom.
Maybe mom will know. Snack delivery. Need driver. Okay. 2109 room cleaning will be done.
I'm just coming to clean my room. Okay. Uh, plant the potato. Where can I plant the potato?
All right. What's this? Stick it in the ground. Coupler. I probably put, I gotta put gas in there,
but not yet. So how am I supposed to know where my brother is? A potato seeds. So where should
I put these? Can I put them anywhere? I'm back here, right? All right. I'm going to put my potatoes
like over here. I need the shovel right here. Holy shit. Let's go. Got water too. We've rains coming
in. All right. Hell yeah. So that's infinite food now. Okay. So now I need to find the brother.
I'm gonna drink something first. Pass bow. Is that brother? Where? This one's low left.
All right. So does he just take, go left here? That's where he is. I should have enough gas.
So he's right here on this road. That's not brother. All right. Hold on. Let me take a look.
So right now I'm about to pass pass bow. Uh, let's keep driving. It's there. They're lying to you.
Okay. All right. Looking in town. Well, this is a house right here. Let's see. Let's see if he's
here. That's probably him right there. All right. Who the fuck are you? How's your day going? Can't
wait for summer. Each weekend I will go out camping for sure. Okay. You can sell firewood here. All
right. All right. So now can I drive that other car? If I put gas in that car, can I drive it now?
Place firewood here to sell. How do I get firewood? Uh, do I have to buy like an axe,
chainsaw? Can I cut down any tree or do I have to cut down specific ones?
Just hit a tree with your truck. I'm going to go get the chainsaw because I need money. I don't
need. I have $0 man. Am I on gas on this car? I'm okay. So I'm going to load this truck up with a
shitload of firewood. That sounds good. The parking brake is not on. All right. I got to stop looking
at the chat room when I'm driving a vehicle. That would be fucking swell. Oh my God. Don't even
fucking tell me we're good. Okay. Chainsaw please. Now does this thing have gas too? Like does this
thing have gas or is it just going to work? I can't cut this. Uh, okay. Well, what about over here?
Gas too. It's only the dead trees. This is a birch tree. All right. So that counts. Okay. So now
I'll load this up. I'm good. This is going to be sick. Let's go. I'm just going to pull it over
here. No, I'm not. Just walk it. I have to cut it again. Cut it until it's okay. All right. All
right. Let's go. How much do you get per, uh, per thing of wood? I need to use the log splitter.
Well, I got to, I'm going to load the truck up and then I'll take it from here.
Right. I'm assuming the green circle is how you turn it into firewood, right? Nobody here knows.
It's behind the house. I don't think so. Let me just check something real quick.
No, okay. I can't cut it anymore. It's the red thing. Guys, this is like a trailer. This is a
trailer. What are you talking about? Am I high? Are you high? This is not a log splitter. This is
a coupler. You attach it to the back of a truck. It's not, I think, what are you? Oh my goodness.
It's not a wood cutter. This is the thing you attached a trailer to a truck. That's not a wood
cutter. What do you mean look at it? I'm not looking at it. Bro, fellas, ladies and gentlemen,
that is not a wood cutter. This is not a wood cutter. It is. Yeah, it isn't. Look, I'm not,
I'm not, I don't need to prove this anymore. You guys are losing your minds. You guys are
losing your fucking minds. It's not a log splitter. What the, what is happening in this chat room?
This is a trailer. What is happening here? Oh, you guys are fucked up. I'm leaving.
Look up a Google image of a log splitter. I'm fucking freaking out right now. Log splitter.
This is a trailer. This is, I don't know, I don't, huh? You gotta be kidding me, man.
No, it's not. This is not. I tried to use it. What? You can't be serious, man.
No, I thought it was people just fucking with me and just making up random shit.
This is a log splitter. I thought this is something you attach to the back of a truck.
Dude, no way. No way. I thought every, wow. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. How do you turn
it on then? It does both? I've never seen one of these in my entire life. Is there enough fuel in
it? City boy. I'm sorry, but I don't know how many of us here have never seen a wood splitting
machine in their entire life. I haven't. Come on, dude. Apologize. No.
Is he high? I'm sitting there freaking out about this. How do I turn this on?
Do you see how soft my hands are? Look at how soft they are. I've never seen this before in
my whole life. I always just, it's always the guy that's, okay. It's always, anytime I think of
wood cutting or log cutting, it's this jacked guy with like huge pecs and a fucking like just abs.
And he's wicked sweating and he's like smashing through wicked hard with an axe. I've never seen
somebody do it with a machine ever. It's always a jacked guy with no shirt on. I've never seen a
machine. That's so funny. That's actually really funny. I can't believe it. Okay, turn this off.
Don't waste gas. How much can I put in the truck? Probably a lot, right? Apology. Okay. I'm sorry
that I told you guys that you were stupid because I thought that the trailer that you attached to
the back of the truck was apparently like a piston operated electronic gas operated log cutting
machine. I'm sorry that, but come on, you guys have been messing with me all day though. How am
I supposed to know when you guys are not? All right. Give me, I need to make a ton of money.
He's a city slicker. The only, guys, people are doing like, I'm the kind of person that, oh hey,
oh yeah, we're going to go up back and we're going to, we're going to build a fucking shed.
I'm like, okay, does anybody need their taxes done? Like I can, I'll help you do that.
I can, you know, I can help with something else. I'm not, I'm not the kind of person that knows
what this is. Like, oh, do you want, I can actually like, you want me to run, what do you need?
You need oil and you need, you need like this like kind of like special kind of like grease or
something that I can go get or you need like, I'll run, I'll run Home Depot. Yeah, I'll be right back.
I'll be back in like 10 minutes. Anybody need coffee or anything? Like I'm, that's me. I'm that
kind of person. That's, I'm that guy. I gotta pull the truck down. Yeah, I'm that guy. You don't want
me to cut the wood. You really don't. I'm telling you right now. I promise you. I, I don't even know
how it would happen. I would go to cut the wood and like the axe would come out of my hand and
like go flying. Like the handle would break off somehow. Like a fucking, like a comic, like cartoon
style. I don't know how it would happen, but it would. The wood and the meat grinder. You were a
gym bro. Like 10 years ago, I, and I wouldn't, I wouldn't have cut wood back then either. I still
would have been the guy that goes and gets the coffee. Just because I was in the gym does not
mean I would be comfortable swinging an axe or touching heavy machinery. That doesn't change.
I would go like to pour your coffee, you know, and it'd be like this. It'd be kind of hard.
I don't know what I mean, but I'd still do it. Please don't even give me a break. Did you ever
skip leg day? I never did legs once. That's a lie. I'm kidding. Don't fucking be an idiot.
Goddamn parking brake is going to make me lose my mind. Okay. I am doing this. I know this is
people are going to like, oh, snooze fastism, snoozing. I can't, I wake me up when he's doing
so I'm, I'm one try to like, I need money. I'm going to fill this car with this shit.
It's going to be to the brim and I'm going to make like $150 at least.
Three trees is enough. We'll see. Maybe one, one more tree. I promise. That's it.
I can't, I, that was visible, audible and mental shock that this was actually a real thing.
Please be okay. Everybody here. Be honest with me though. Be honest with me.
Did you actually know what this was? Like how many of you knew what this, this, this was actually
that, what that is? I've been to Home Depot. I've been to Home Depot a shitload of times too. And
I've never gone to the wood cutting machines and gone and wow, that's interesting. How does that
work? No, I go to Home Depot and I walk around in a circle looking for a light bulb and I don't know
where the fuck they are until I find the one person that points me to the other end of the entire like
three mile long store. That's like, oh, the light bulbs are at aisle 400 and then I go to aisle 400
and then I leave. All right. Well, last one, one more and that's it. I promise. This is it. Okay.
We're good. This is not efficient, but it's okay. What about Ikea? Well, the great thing about Ikea
is Ikea makes it so you cannot screw it up. You have to walk through the whole store and the store
is like, Hey, by the way, just letting you know, you're walking through this part of like Disney
world. You have to walk through everything in Ikea. And there are like Dark Souls shortcuts in Ikea
if you feel like skipping to something else, but you don't have to do that. Like I know that I'm
just going to eventually walk into the kitchen appliance section in Ikea. I'm just eventually
going to, it's going to happen eventually. I love that place by the way. Oh dude, all the meatballs,
right? All right. That's enough. They're actually really good. And I know everyone's like batch
testing right now, but they're actually really good. Well, pretty much all the food from there
is really good. They have like salmons. They have sauces. They have all kinds of meatballs.
It's cool. It's really cool. It's a nice place. It's fine. What's what? It's good stuff. I love
Ikea meatballs, Bat Chest. And then when you go to Ikea and you eat them and then you fucking
literally delete all of your like the chat logs. I don't want to even know I said that. They're not
bad. They're not bad. All right. There's a lot. Okay. I understand now when people say, okay,
I'll tell you right now, if I drive on the road and I flipped this car over and it's ruined and
this was like the last like half an hour was a waste of time. I'm going to do everything in my
power to make that not possible. Cause this is probably like a few hundred bucks worth of wood.
Put a tarp over it. Can you do that? And this off wasted gas. Stop wasting gas. Bat Chest.
Almost there. Everybody hold on. You can wake up in a minute. You know what's really ridiculous?
I'm so glad that I was not in a call with somebody. I would have bet money that this
was not a woodcutter. If I was in a call with somebody and they were like, dude, that's a
woodcutter. Like pep and they were saying like Pepe laugh. And you guys were saying Pepe laugh
and shit. I would have, I would have been like, fine, put a thousand bucks up and I would have
lost. I need to eat something. Save the game. Good call. That's a very good call. Is the rest
of the stream going to be about, can you recognize a woodcutter? No, we'll move on probably pretty
shortly here. Probably like now I'll give you $10,000 to flip the truck. No, no, I'm serious.
There are 15,500 people here and that would like annoy and like irritate 15,000 people.
So essentially what that would be would be, I would be getting a dollar like per person
to like irritate the fuck out of everybody. And I don't, I don't, I kind of don't want to do that.
All right. Well, this is fine. I got to sleep. I need to eat something. I don't think I have any
food. Oh, I have this. Yeah. We're good. All right. Let's go see. Should I turn the power off and go
to bed? Maybe you should. I'll give you a thousand dollars. No one's giving me a thousand. No one's.
Okay. Don't even joke. What time is it? Is it really 1 AM? What is the sleep schedule I'm on?
Fuck. Well, I'm cutting another. Okay. I'm cutting another tree down then. Yeah. Okay. I'm going to
cut another tree down because it won't fit. Actually it really might not. You're right.
Let me spread this out because this will be a disaster. I'm going to go very slow.
I'm going to bring the chainsaw too. There might be stuff at his property I can cut down.
It's not going to be a disaster. It'll be fine. All right. Oh, let's bring the chainsaw
that in the car. I'm not trying to cut this. Go back to bed. I've watched this video on
fail army a hundred times. What does that mean? All right. This is empty. So I have to fill that
back up if I have any. All right. Here's the plan. I'm going to go make a bunch of money.
How am I on gas? I could use some. Fail army? I saw the stream five days ago. That's weird.
Can I see how much is in there? Empty. Okay. All right. I got a full tank of gas. Okay. We're good.
Full tank of gas. Bring the gas can because after I do this, I'm going to town to get more gas.
Car is almost ready. I can just need to fill it with gas and I can drive it. Do not flip the car
under any circumstance. Do not flip the car under any circumstance. Don't do it. It's not funny.
It's not a joke. It would be annoying because you just wasted like 35 straight minutes cutting
wood. Jeremy, I know you think you're quite the comedian, but this is not the time to do that.
And a lot of people are going to think that that was on purpose, but it was not. And I,
you gotta be fucking kidding me, man. I'm going to quit the game. Honest to God,
you don't even tell me that like this is, that's unfucking believable. And it looks so stupid.
It's so stupid because it looks like I have fucking meant to do that. I'm fine. It's fine.
I can just reverse. That looks so shit and so planned. That looked so fucking fake and
it's annoying that it did. I can't fucking believe it, man. I can't believe it. I can't,
I cannot believe it. Scripted fucking bullshit. I can't believe how fucking fake that looked.
In fact, I can't, I really thought that this did not drop off like this. I thought it
was just here and that I could just go left. Because remember, I was up in the truck like this
and I'm driving this way and it's like, take the left. I didn't think there was a divot right there
and it doesn't matter what I say. I'm like a try hard funny Andy that like thought that was funny
and there's nothing I can do about that. I used a lever. Dude, come on. I, my life is a, I can't.
So scripted and so just fake. He's doing the thing. Look at, he's like talking about like,
don't mess it up, Jeremy. I fell down guys. I'm so mad right now. You have no idea. Load the save.
Quiet. Not you, me. Just put it like under here. Would that work? I don't think that's doing
anything. I'm just going to reload the save. Far away. What if I just used it? I can't use it again.
Guys, I'm fucked I think. Put it in neutral. How do I do neutral? All right, all right, all right.
I swear to God, this wasn't on purpose. I promise. I pull it like from here. There it goes. It's
fucked. The back side. There it goes. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I can't believe it. Can I get out now? I might be able to get out now. I have to reload the save.
Pull the front right. Front right side. No, it's wedged in here. This shit ain't going anywhere,
guys. It's like just stuck here forever. Yeah, this is copium. It really is. Ram it with the ATV.
Now, this is absolute copium and I, this is copium. It's copium. I need to reload the save,
which is, it's this one here, right? Turn off, turn this off. Turn everything off. Go to bed.
I'm not going to get stuck again. I, I will, this is the worst stream ever. That sucks so bad that
like I really did not mean to do that. It's like one o'clock in the morning. Just sleep until
six a.m. This was my first stream. Fuck it. I'm done. I'm out. Get in the fucking car.
Turn the fucking car on. Put it in one. And this is what I saw before. That looks like a level
fucking plane. What about the gas can? Check that rear view. No, no chainsaw. No, no, no, no, no.
No, I don't have time for that right now. It's the worst stream. Fuck. No, it can't be. No,
I'll fix it. I'll fix it. It can't be. It can't be. I'll fix it. Don't go down that way. I'll fix
it. I'll fix it. Let's go. I get five bucks for every log. This is going to be a fucking
millionaire at the end of this. Pull it closer. Closer, closer, closer, closer, closer. Oh my
God. Thank goodness. Just drive over it. That work. I'm not, no, no, no, no, I'm not. I'm not
fucking around. Does work. All right. I thought you were lying. I have 265 bucks. All right. We're
in business now. Let's fucking go. All right. Plan. Here comes a plan. We're going to get the
plan going. Plan. Load up the car with gas. You're going to come out of the birth canal.
I'm not coming out of the birth canal. Full tank of gas. Let's go. I got 300 bucks. I'm ready to
do it. Let's go. Stream just started. You just got here. Okay. This shit's empty. I need to fill
that back up. I've got a full tank of gas of almost 300 bucks. I can go into town, which led me.
Let's take a look here. If I keep going just to the left straight, go through the Moses tunnel
and we'll go back into town. It's the worst stream ever. It's not the worst. No, it's not.
I refuse to believe it. Nope. Sorry. Nope. Okay. Here we go. Stay left. Bang a left here.
We're going to go buy some equipment for that car. It can't possibly be the worst stream. He made a
silly cats being mean. It's okay. We don't have to listen to them. You and me, we get it. I can.
Is that another potato? No, I do have to. I'm going to buy some snacks. I think because I'm
going to run out of food zero as soon here. Snack shack was down here, right? Isn't the snack shack
over here? I don't know, dude. Every fucking house is identical and every road is identical.
One of these houses is the snack shack. Okay. Turn this off. Let's go. Let me just got a damn thing.
Fill this up. I got cash. I'm good. I can buy another gas tank. Okay. So it's 17 bucks to fill
this can full can. Very nice. All right, let's go. Now we're working. Now we're working. Let's go.
All right. What do I want from here? Oh shit. No, I don't have that kind of money.
Um, summer tire. A muffler. I could buy, I could afford one of these mufflers.
Should I get a new muffler? I have a torch. Dent repair kit. Rust repair. Something useful. Yeah.
Wouldn't a muffler be useful? What about a shock? Sport shock. Like that would be pretty,
pretty sick, right? Rust repair. Rust repair kit. Okay. Oh yeah. The car is rusted. You're right.
Good idea. What else should I get? I'm thinking maybe suspension. Dent repair. Yeah. I don't want
to buy too much shit though. Another gas can. I don't think I have, do they sell it? It's in paint.
Gray paint. All right. What kind of, what color do I want the car to be? Uh, Robin's egg blue.
Now how long does that last? Or do I have to buy like a shitload of them? Does it last forever?
Ooh, a steering wheel. Cool. What's that? I'm, I probably should get like some shock or something,
right? I shouldn't I? No, get food. Oh, you're right. Okay. I can't get that. All right. I'm
going to buy a bunch of poutine because I need to buy it. I don't, I can't afford it. I can't
afford it. All right. Okay. Okay. I have enough to, that engine is going to be pretty cool. One of
it. Oh, no eyelashes. Yep. Buy a lottery ticket. All right. I got a full tank of gas, a full gas
can, a under glow kit. No shifter. Oh, this is kind of classic. This is kind of classic. No, no,
not this one. The other one is all right. All right. All right. All right. I have 50 bucks.
I don't want to waste it because I need gas. I want to be able to afford gas. Okay.
So Snack Shack is right here, right? That's Snack Shack. Yep. Okay. They're right next to each
other. Drive carefully, please. We're good. Vroom, vroom, crappy car mods. Reddit. What the fuck did
you say? I'm sorry. I got like really angry. Calm down. Woof, woof, woof, woof. What do I mean
locked? Are they closed? Come on. Are they open in 20 minutes? Worse than Skate 3. Everybody that's
saying that this is the worst stream I've ever done. You are going to be timed out for five
minutes for each offense on your. Okay. For your first offense, it's five minutes. Your second
offense, it's 20 minutes. Your third offense is permanent. Deal with that one. Deal with that one.
Imagine waiting 50 minutes in front of a restaurant to go in. I've done it before,
not 50 minutes, but like it probably 20. So maybe some of you guys can relate to this. We'll find
out. Being on a reverse sleep schedule and having, and like, let's say you, let's say you're getting
up a long time. I haven't been like this in a long time, but for a while, especially when I was in
Massachusetts and I lived in Massachusetts, I was sleeping at, I mean, I would start my stream at
seven or eight o'clock at night Eastern. And I, my stream would stop around like 12, one, two
o'clock in the morning a lot of times. Right. Every, almost every stream was like that. So I
would be ending my stream at like two, three AM sometimes. And like, I would maybe take a shower
after streaming and relax. Very good. What am I going to do for food? And there were breakfast
places that opened at like five AM. So, I mean, I was, I was essentially on a complete reverse
schedule. I was going to bed at, I want to say I was sleeping a lot of times at like eight, nine,
10 o'clock in the morning and waking up at like four or five o'clock in the afternoon.
So I would, sometimes you, I'm really hungry and it's like, fuck, I can't go, I haven't gone to the
grocery store in a few days. I don't have anything in the fridge. So like four 30 would roll around
and I'd be like, fuck, I'm, fuck, man, I'm ready to go. And I would go and kind of, I wanted to like
eat and I want to beat all the old people to the restaurant because they all showed up at like five
36 AM. So I would get in the car at like four 30, get there at like four 45 and just be like,
I'm ready. And they would open and be like, like, oh, hey, how are you doing? Oh yeah. Good morning.
Good morning. It's sunny out there. I don't know. I don't know what the people maybe thought I did,
but like I was always not always. And I didn't do this that often, by the way, this happened
to make maybe like a total of five to 10 times my whole life. I would be there like at the crack of
the door opening and I didn't want coffee, right? Because I was going to be going to sleep. So it'd
be like, no, no, no, no coffee, no coffee. Uh, but I would love the extra large, uh, corned beef hash
and three eggs breakfast place and a big orange juice. I would love it. Oh, it's open. These are
expensive corned beef hash and eggs is my favorite breakfast in the world and nothing compares. So
there you go. I got here right when they opened, I cleaned them out and now I'm leaving. Do they
have anything else? Is there a drive through fry basket? I don't think they have a fry basket in
here, man. Okay. I got everything I need. Let's go. Let's go work on the car. Corned beef is
terrible for you. It's so good though. But I mean, everything is terrible for you. As long as you're
not eating corned beef for every meal, every day of your life. We have the same conversation. We
talked about like fast food, right? That you eat McDonald's. Fucking piece of shit. You're disgusting.
If you eat McDonald's like a few times a month, you're fine. It's you're going to be fine.
All right. I got to find the exit. This is not the exit. That's copium. That's not copium.
Did I drive on somebody's fucking front deck? What the hell is going on? I didn't lose anything,
right? That's not copium. It really isn't or McChickens. Just do if you feel like having
like a brisket sandwich, eat it, but don't eat a brisket sandwich every single day.
If you like chicken nuggets from McDonald's or Wendy's or Burger King, whatever, that's great.
They're awesome. Don't eat it every day. There. That's it. Done. Done. That's it. And like taking
some more good stuff too. To, you know, to even out the bad stuff. I don't want to. I want. Well,
I mean, here. You could like incorporate. You just incorporate some more greens and shit.
You maybe cook with some like better oil, right? Just keep an eye on your cholesterol. Like whenever
you get like a blood test from the doctor, just go right. Make sure you like your, you know,
all your levels are okay and be going, be healthy and be happy. You'll be fine. Or don't eat like
shit. Nobody cares. Yeah, but you will though. Let me tell you, as somebody that's old man,
you're going to want to treat your body at least all right in your teens and twenties. Trust me.
You really are. Dad, shut up. I'm serious. Let me be the one to tell you that I said the same stuff
when I was like 20, 25, whatever. I don't give a shit when I'm older. Who fucking cares? I'm going
to be old. I'm not that old. 20. Yeah, whatever. You're a wise elder now. Oh, somebody what happened?
Sorry. What happened to my house? Honestly though, did I leave the door open the whole time?
You're like 50. Oh, we're going to turn this. We're going to make this a beauty.
All right. Rust repair kit. How do I use it? I only get to use it once. I use it one time. Nice.
Very nice. Okay. Dent repair kit. All right. Is there any major dents to take care of?
Probably. Should I just use it on this car? Like right here? Is this working?
Am I making dents in the car? Oh, whatever. Oh, I'm just going to burp. What do we have on
the to-do list? All right. That's all done. Oh, my potatoes. 36%. Do I have to water them?
What the fuck? That's my car. Should I not do this yet? And is this infinite? It runs out.
It's infinite. It's no, it's not. Test it out. I think it might be infinite. I think so. I think
yeah, it's infinite. It is. All right. Well, let's, I know we could do the rust and everything first,
but whatever. This is looking all right. Leave some parts while it's cool. No, I want it to be
blue. So I have to buy a shitload of those rust repair kits. We have to do way more wood. Yeah,
just eat all right. Don't, you know, if you can, sometimes it can be hard. Trust me. I get it.
It's empty. You actually can run out. Did it go in? That looks way better than it did before.
And whatever, who cares? Okay. So now, oh, I got this blue. I'll save that. Can I drive this thing?
Does this thing actually drive? Can I actually drive the car? I can. Oh, hell yeah. All right.
Let's get gas in this thing. Very nice. Pop the trunk. Let's put this in here. Okay. Nice.
Everything will be secure in here. That's so much better than the trunk. How do I get it off this
thing here? I just pull this out. I have to jack it up. Um, how do I, I don't, how do you do that?
I really kind of don't understand. That's not a jack. Oh, do I have a jack? Oh, can I just
drive off of it? It's in the trunk. Um, it is not in the trunk. The jack on the front,
it's a log splitter. That's a tire pump. It's a watering can. Wait, there's no water in it.
That's a tire pump. It's in the truck bed. That's another hoist puller. It's not a jack.
I mean, can I just pull it off though? I don't see it. I think that's just going to have to,
I think I have to buy it. Oh, put the food in the fridge. Yep. That's true. I got to piss.
Did you take a fat dump in bed today? Kind of a weird question. A very strange question.
Use the hoist on the front to lift the front. Yeah, that's what I was thinking. I'm going to
run out of this stuff soon too. What's in the freezer? Okay. We're good. We're good. Wait,
if there's no electricity, how's the fridge work? Right. I got to pee. We'll be right back.
I'm not even close to being done. I'll be right back. Give me like two, three minutes.
All my songs got moved. Going to the folder and they're not synced up here. Sorry about that.
I'll fix it. Here, pee. I'm back. I didn't, I wanted to speak really softly so I didn't
scare the shit out of people. The hot boxed his house. Ready? That was a long piss. I refilled
my water and tea. Water and tea together. It's a water. It's a tea. I can hear your hot box.
Okay. So I need to sleep. What time is it? What time is that in? That's six o'clock at night,
five o'clock at night. What is it? So I'm not going to bed yet. What can I do? Let me see if
I can get this off the thing here because I don't really want it on there. How do I get this off?
They like bolt it in. Inflate the tires. Oh, that's a smart idea. Keep pumping them.
I don't want it past like 32, 30. What do you mean? 30? You out of your mind? You don't want
a hundred PSI in your fucking tire? What are you talking about? No, like 32, 30. Not, you out of
your mind? 35, 32. Herman has only ridden a bike. All right. I might've gotten the log cutting thing
wrong, but like 30 and 35 PSI on your tires is like safe. It's not, you're not supposed to have,
fucking, are you crazy? I know, I know this. If I know one thing is, is this 70 PSI. I would not
do that. Yeah. Come on. Okay. So now that's good. I need to go. I know what I'm doing before I go to
bed. All right. This game's fun. I am going to cut down some trees and I'm going to make a shitload
more money. How's that sound? Punk. That's right. Yeah. I'm talking to you. No, no, no, no, no, no.
On the second seat in the couch. You with the brown hair. Talking to you. Yeah. Put the spaghetti
down and let's talk. Somebody was just like, what the fuck? Somebody's eating spaghetti with
brown hair on the second seat of a couch. This 15 plus thousand people here. The person that was
just eating spaghetti on the second seat in their couch with brown hair. Me? Wait, what?
Do you guys, I don't know. Do you remember when I think of one, didn't one day I like look right
in the camera and go like, like, Hey, Hey, Michael Anderson, what's going on, man? I used to do that
a lot, didn't I? And also it's just like, what the fuck? Oh, like how did he, what is he talking
about? Like, Hey, Dave Smith. Oh, I can cut a pine tree. Okay. These are chunky. I thought I
couldn't cut these. Okay. I'm just going to load the truck. All right. That should be good. Let's
load the truck up and then I'm going to sleep and then we're going to turn this in all chat
individually. Yeah. Oh, well I can deliver pizza, right? Or something. Okay. Let's park it right
here. Oh, I'm going to get dark. I got to hurry up. Hopefully I have enough gas to cut this.
This is less efficient, but then just wait. I just got to get it over here. So what is the next thing
that I actually really do need? Like no messing around. Like, what do I need actually? I need
something, right? Sugar shack. How do I build a sugar shack? These are massive. These logs are
so much bigger than I thought they were. Shit. It's going to be difficult. Um, okay. I'll go get
these. I wish I could sprint. Do pizza stuff. Hold on. Did you cut down a rubber tree? I don't
think so. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Everything's fine. All right. Let's see if these,
if I cut this up, if it, if it fits, hopefully this gas, please tell me this gas. Come on.
How come this is so spooky? Um, I think it's just a flashlight outside in a game. I think it's just
at night is scary. So a sugar shack will do it. I'm almost time for me to sleep.
Spider-man is going to get you. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, what, what, what, what, what? Hey, hey, who's doing this? Who has my car? What the fuck? What
the fuck? Who's driving my car? I put the brake on, didn't I? Oh shit. Brake is on, isn't it?
I could have sworn the parking brake was on. I, it's on. What? Hey, I actually thought you guys
weren't kidding around. Out of gas. How do I turn the lights off? I don't want the battery to run
out. Turn the lights off. How the fuck is this thing out of gas? I might be in trouble here.
I was here two hours ago doing, doing the same exact thing, but somebody just asked for it.
So they were asking, how's my TikTok voice? And I'll tell you, it's really doing pretty well.
Although I'm trying hard not to make it sound like that. So it's still there,
but it's not as bad. I think it's a seasonal thing.
Now I started talking like that and now it's there. This is empty, huh?
Fuck. Um, this is bad. This thing has a full tank, but I can't drive it. Can I, can I just drive off
this thing? It's got a ton of gas. See if I can get to town. Call Martin. Oh my God, you're right.
High five five. It's what? 8 a.m.? Martin's on a reverse schedule. He's at the local diner right
now. The first person there. No, he wouldn't be actually. 7 a.m.? Old people central. He's
still sleeping. How are the potatoes? 44%. Hell yeah. This is kind of cool too. I haven't even
used this. Ooh, really? How much should I do this? This'll work, right? No energy first thing in the
morning. I have that. No, the meters are backwards. I don't want to use that. I have two eggs. Let's
save the game here. Oh my God. No electricity. All right, Martin, will you get up? Wake up, please.
What time? It's 8 30. I'm stranded here. I don't have any gas in my car and I need to ride to town.
How long? When does Martin get up? I have to save. It's 4 p.m. Right before he streams. That's so bad.
Okay, I will tell you that moving to the west coast was really, really good for me because instead
of starting streams at like 7 p.m., 7 to 8 p.m. my local time, I couldn't really do that anymore.
That was just not going to be really efficient at all because being three hours behind eastern time,
I couldn't start my streams at 7 p.m. local time. There's no way. I just wouldn't be able to do that.
That would be so late for everybody. And even starting at like four, like three, four-ish,
is still really late for people. That's still 7 p.m. eastern, but it's 4 p.m. local.
So it actually, I've been on like a better schedule since I've moved.
So moving across the whole country made me get up better. It's crazy. All right, turn the generator
off. I'm calling this guy again. It was just enough to save the game, thank God. All right,
it's like noon. Hang up. Yeah, dude, I'm on my way to pick you up. All right,
I need the gas can. Where is it? Is he actually coming or is he, is it not real?
Taking like an hour or something? Will he drive me back? I don't have to walk back, right?
He crashed. That's like not, right? Click the jack stands. What? How did I not know that?
What's up, man? Hey, what's up, man? Cars running just fine. Turns out I don't actually need you.
Thanks, dude. Appreciate it. You got a cool tire in there. Hey, hey, hey, hey. That's mine.
That's mine. What the fuck? No, where's the, why do I, who puts a parking brake on right here?
Close the parking brake? Why is the parking, where's the parking brake on this car?
Damn it. How do I get a gas can back? What do I, do I have to, I have to call him back?
Don't even tell me that, seriously. Martin's already on the road. I have to go fucking hunt
him down. You gotta be shitting me. How do I get out of, he went this way. I don't know where,
I don't know where he went. He's in town. Go to the town. Oh, the lost items guy. That's right.
Okay. Where's the lost items guy? What a pain in the ass. I gotta go the other way then.
This is the wrong way. Is there a faster way to shift? Cause it's not one, two, three, four,
five anymore. How do I shift? I don't, I don't want to like look down here. Oh my God. This is
such a pain in the ass. What the hell? Um, I'm just going to go to town. How am I going to get gas?
I'm talking about to go to reverse, not like gear shift. I don't know how I'm going to,
I gotta go talk to the guy. Whatever. Let's go to town. I could restart the save.
I think I'm just going to restart the save. Yeah. Fuck this. That was like, yeah, that was like
five minutes ago. Okay. Same thing applies here. This time I'm actually going to get in the car,
which is so, I don't know what happened. He just, I maybe got annoyed that I wasn't there.
Okay. He's on his way. I hear something's running. All right. Okay. All right. Gas can pick it up.
In the meantime, I actually can do this because it's going to take a minute to get here stuff.
That's cut up. Just put it in the trunk because I know I'm going to use it. I might as well just
get this out of the way. Is this cut? No, I don't think so. It does not look cut. Are you
torturing yourself with this game? No, I'm, if I wasn't enjoying it, at least it's fun to play
just to fuck around. I would not be playing it if I didn't enjoy it at least enough to play it.
So don't worry. I'm having fun. Rewater the plants. That's a good call. Yep. I don't know
where the fuck it went. I got to go. What's up? Let's go. You are adorable today, Jason.
Let's go. Oh, wait. He actually, what? What the fuck? I'm not drinking or smelling the gas.
I'm just holding it over here. Oh my God. Damn it. I'm not driving with Martin anymore.
I'm not, I'm not getting in the car with Martin. So how do I get back?
How am I supposed to get back to my house? Bro, where are you going? Martin? Martin? Hey,
are you going to wait here? Thanks, Martin. Wait, did we just lock ourselves out of here?
Please remember where this is because I don't. Right near the big Christmas tree. Where's the,
what do I do? Go in his house. That's Martin's house? Okay. That's Martin's house right there.
I got to try to burn that into memory somehow. It's like to the right of the church. Okay. So
from the church's front entrance, it's like to the right and straight. All right, guys. So
how am I doing? Can I actually get back to the house from here? This is Snack Shack.
I think the gas station is over here. I look like such a fucking weirdo. I'm just walking
around the streets holding a gas canister. What am I doing with this over there? Person? Okay.
I only have $26. I got to be careful. All right, let's do it. I just need to gas. I can fill this
whole tank here and then I can bring the, I can fill the truck. Okay. So I got to go find Martin.
Okay. So this, I got what I needed. The church is over here and it's over this way. Okay. All right.
Let's go. How do you get your maple syrup bar to go down? You have to drink maple syrup. So Martin's
house is over here. Okay. As long as I can have landmarks burnt in, I'll be able to know where I
am. Okay. Cool. That's what I wanted for free. So is he in the house? It was a look behind the
house. Wood spoiler. Why would you want, I don't, a wood spoiler? This is a shelf. All right, dude,
let's go. I don't know what you mean by this, but I somehow get it somehow. Somebody said this is
like when I bring my TV to my friend's house. What do you, you mean like you're holding a fucking big
ass TV? What do you mean? Like you sit there with it on your lap, bringing a big TV to my friend's
house. Well, so you guys can play like smash brothers at like zero milliseconds. All right.
Thanks a lot, man. Give me out, give me out this fucking car right now. Give me the fuck out of
this car. Get me out of this car and give me my shelf. All right, let's go. We're good. That looks
great. I promise that one day I will drive this car. I can spray paint it. I can spray paint it.
All right. Yeah. All right. We're going all night. I'm fucking, I'm ready. I'm into this now.
No, dude, we got to play in my CRT TV. Otherwise I can't do my chic 50 hit combo. I'm going to
chop up so much more wood. You have no idea. Yeah. You guys don't even have any idea how much more
wood is going to get chopped in this thing. Get ready to snooze. I'll be ready to go to sleep.
This is not going to be an exciting one. We'll get to the truck. Oh yeah. What happened here?
Oh, when it backed up. Right, right, right. Okay. That's a lot. Um, this is going to make me some
money. I'm going to bring, this is probably stupid what I'm doing. I'm going to bring the truck and
the chainsaw and the cutting machine to that guy's house. And then we're going to just cut a shit
little wood. I'm going to make like a thousand dollars. I'm going to put a $1,000 engine in that
car and beautiful. Let's just take what I have now. I fill it with gas. You can't cut the trees
around his place. Oh shit. Well, nevermind. Don't use the whole thing. Don't dump it either. All
right. What's the, how much is in here? I need enough for this. How much is in the actual tank
here now? All right. That's good. That's good. There's plenty of gas now in this car. It was
moving. The car was moving. The car was moving. Did you see the car move? I did. The parking
brake is on. Why is it moving like this? Why is it moving? I have the parking brake on. What?
It's too up. It's what? Dude, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Can I suck it out of here? Can I suck it out? Wait, excuse me. I thought there was no nothing
left in there. What? I thought there was nothing left. What is going on here? I want to tell me
how much is left in the tank. What happened? Why is the HUD turned off? Okay. Very good. I'm very
happy about this. Let's close that up. Let's cut some more wood. I'm ready. I have a bunch of logs
here. I don't think I can fit very much more than this. So he's happy. I'm very happy. I'm doing
great. Hopefully you're doing great too. I hope so. Smoke on stream. I'm not going to smoke. It's
not even 420 anymore in England. So whatever. What's wrong? Oh, I need to drink maple syrup.
I'm going to die. Go. I might only be able to do one more little batch of this. Can we,
Jerma, can we do a race before the five hour mark? What do you mean? I don't know what that means.
I've raced in the game, right? There's races. Yeah. My car's a piece of shit. How am I supposed
to do that? That car is, where's my car? Okay. Look, do you think I'm going to race with that?
Okay. Let's put this, I think that's all I can do. Maybe, maybe one more, but that's going to be it.
I think I don't think I can do much more than that. Maybe one more. What was it? Like 300 bucks?
Do the racing. I guys, the game, the map is in French and I don't even know where to go.
What do you want me to say? Well, I'll go do a race. Oh, I'm not mad. I'm fine.
I think I can get one more tree in here as long as I'm very safe about it. Dr. Thunder is good.
I have not had Dr. Thunder in a very long time. I think one more tree can fit in here and I'll
just drive over the thing. Nah, fuck it. I want money now. Let's go. I'll cut this last one.
That's enough. Can I turn this in at night or not? Any of you lore masters in here? All right. Good
night. Save the game. He's faking it. He knows how to speak French. Check out episode four of his
TF2 series with Sir He Literally Fluently Speaks French. Okay. I showed my sister one of your old
VODs and she said, she said he's good with it. What does that mean? I don't know. I have absolutely
no idea what that means. Okay. Now turn off the generator. How do I turn the lights off in the
car? I can't. Lights. Like I can't turn it off. It's right mouse bumper. All right. Tomorrow is
when I make the money and then I can finally drive that dumb ass car off the lot. I can finally get
that dumb ass car out of here. It's 5 30 in the morning. Plenty of time to eat something,
drink some syrup. My reserves are kind of going low though. Every night at the abandoned grocery
store. Car meat. Okay. We'll do that tomorrow night. I got to get this thing nice and souped up.
I need to rust repair kit, some more blue paint. So I need how many? I have one, two,
three, one, two, three, or five. I need like five or six rust repair kits and I need blue,
that light, I need like two cans of that light blue paint. So the spoiler be, I'm going to make
the spoiler clean. Okay. Sounds good. I need money though. So let's go. I swear to God,
I'm going to do that every fucking time. All right. So let me think here. All right. I,
one more tree. I want like three or $400. One more. I promise. Just whatever's right here.
You can't drive for shit. I'm using W. See me in with real car. Okay. Don't drive a real car with
WASD. I know that like they did it in a James Bond movie, but that's not how it works. He sat
down with his fucking Nintendo DS and drove the car around. True. Sure. All right. That's enough.
Fill it up. Cause it looks like there's a lot of room at the back of the yeah, right here.
There's tons of room. Can you parallel park? No, but you don't need to parallel park to be like
a good driver. I could, I could probably do it pretty well. I just don't really need to
parallel park these. I'm not going to say the rest of it, but a good one. That's copious.
What's with the copium comments today? That's not copium. I can't remember the last time that I
needed to parallel park. I just can't think of the last time I really had to do it where it was like,
Oh shit, I have to parallel park. All right. That's good. No more. I'm going to take this
came with me because I'm going to keep going to town and I'll fill it up. Wait, I can't do either
driving is stressful. It really is. If you driving can be pretty stressful. So no, I don't,
I wouldn't worry about that. Especially driving a big city or something. No,
no, don't let anybody tell you. It's not the one thing I will say that. I mean like Las Vegas is
seriously goaded Las Vegas. It's highway system is just a square. Is it? It's just a
it is so easy to drive in Las Vegas. It's unbelievable.
Driving around Boston was something I, I hated doing because it was, it was just,
it was terrifying. All the roads are like four inches wide in Vegas. Like there's so many
turning lanes. It's tons of like rotaries and it's just so much better. So much better.
I think Vegas is one of the best cities to drive in. It's one of the easiest to drive in,
in the country. I think now the drivers in Vegas, that's a little different story.
The roads are great. The drivers on the other hand would be way fucking better. It's actually
insane. How bad the drivers in Vegas actually are, which is crazy because I'm sitting there
going like, man, we have this huge, amazing, like it's everything's so easy to navigate.
Why are people driving around like fucking psychos? They're like you. No, I, no way, man.
I'm the person that in the car, when some crazy driver like blows by,
I'm the one that's going like, I'm going like 65 and I'm just like, my goodness, my goodness,
but be you be careful. That's me. That's what I do. I just shake my head. I'm just like,
unbelievable. I'm, you're going to fucking hurt someone. That's what I do.
Come on. 400 bucks. You've seen this. Hey, $400. You've seen this. All right. Let's keep going to
town and I'm going to keep going. All right. I got to go back, right? Because hold on. No,
no, no, just keep going this way. Don't lose the chainsaw. I won't. Yeah. I'm the person that
gasps when somebody drives by going like crazy. And look, I get like, oh,
60. You're just going to go 60, 65, 60, 60, 60 Andy. Don't be a fucking idiot in a car. Seriously.
Don't drive that fast. There's no reason to go like five to 10 miles per hour over the speed
limit. Like there really just kind of isn't like, just fucking be careful. Seriously guys,
don't be stupid. Like if you're on a road that's like 60, 65 and you're like, I'm going to go 90,
man, come on, just fucking chill. My car won't do 90. 90 is not five to, I'm just saying what is
this? Whoa. What's this? What's going on here? I already have a spoiler, but that's kind of cool.
Wheel spacer shifter. Hey, what's up Roger? What do you got in here? Ooh, metallic. I want that.
He's a hoods. Okay. Do I, can I afford any of these nitrous bottle blue bolts? These are way
too expensive. I can't afford any of these better trunk. I can't afford any of this. I need to just
do the basic shit first. Well, thanks for the metallic spray paint. I'm kidding. Relax. All
right. So now I just got to go to the gas station and get some more gas, get some more spray paint
and some more repair kits. It doesn't have to look good. It can look bad and go fast. Yeah.
That's true. But all right. Where's this guy? I always like, yeah, it's right there next to the
truck. Let me fill all this shit. I have plenty of money. So are these, are these both these the same?
Say Aaron, please. Aaron. He's the same thing, right? Yeah. That for the car that's on my lot.
We'll have a full tank. I wish I could, I buy another gas can somewhere. I feel like I need to.
All right. Hello. I'm here. I'm here to get a rust repair kit.
Oh, I need like four of these. This car is so beat up. 240 bucks. I could, should I get shocks?
Two of them? Can I afford to get these and put them in? Don't do it yet. Okay. I can't afford
these. Ooh, tires. Window tint. Oh yeah. Let's do, um, I don't know. What should I do? Green?
I need another repair kit, right? It doesn't have any left. Window film remover? Pruning?
Pruning loppers? What's a pruning lopper? What should I do? Get the under glow kit. All right.
I'm done. I bought all their, uh, repair kits. Let me see what I got. I have two repair kits,
green tint, the paint, gas. Let me fill the tank here. I don't have to worry about this. Do I need
to buy the loppers? Go to the maple syrup center. I will once I can actually drive this car
because it's so much better than the truck. Should I actually buy these loppers? I'm going
to buy them because if I'm, I don't know, I'm probably going to need them for some random
stupid thing. Do it now. Where's the maple syrup center? Is it one that says hmm? All right. So
where am I right now? I don't know how to get that from here. So how do I get that from here?
Right? Or it's right on the edge of town. Drop it off at your shit house. Jesus. This is it right
here then. Yeah. Federation syrup de-edible. Barrel. Place barrel of syrup here to sell.
Sap. Ooh. Hand sealer? Wait. Okay. Do I need to buy a bunch of this stuff? Okay. Sap spouts.
Okay. I'm going to get some of these. Should I buy more than one? Tubing roll? I'm just going
to get everything. I have 50 bucks. I probably should be careful. Tubing post? I need cans too.
Can crate? I'm going to run out of money. And then cans. How many cans should I get? A few? I don't
have enough for a post. I don't have enough money. Okay. I don't want to run out of money. So I'll
just take those. I'll just get this started. Kind of. I got to fix the car up still. So let's go.
I'm okay. I'm not going this way. This is going to take me forever to get home. Turn around. I need
lids for the cans. You don't have a canner or a barrel. Well, I'll get this later. All right. So
now I'm just going to drive straight and then take a right. Let's go. Grow weed. I've got potatoes
growing. Okay. What is that? Is that free? My God. It's a thousand. Okay. That's way too much.
Decorations. You're going to think for five dollars. I guess not. A wheelbarrow. All right.
Whatever. Let's go. Out of my way. All right. So now it's straight, right? No. Where am I going?
This way? Oh, rear end that guy. I got the map now. I got it. I have no idea what he's doing,
but I can't look away. I have all my shit here still, right? Yeah. Okay. We're good.
And then at night tonight, I'm going to go take my car. Fucking be an idiot. Turn the radio on.
There's nothing on radio. It's DMCA. This is one log in the road. All right. Let's go. Repair kit.
Repair kit again. This is starting to look like a nice car now. All right. What should I do it to?
One of the tires? Yeah. I'm going to do to one of the tires. Hell yeah. Where's my nice. Very cool.
All right. Hell yeah. Now I want the spoiler. Look at that. It's looking good. Looking much better.
Are you serious? Can I not paint the spoiler? How do I use this under glow kit? How do I use it?
How do I put that on? Put it under the hood. This is a remover, right? Crouching and lift up the car.
I don't have, how do I, I don't have a jack. I don't like have a jack, right? I mean, I can't
really. Where's my, where is it? If I have it, where is it? Is it for the interior? Oh, yep. It is.
Okay. It's for the interior. Whoa. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. It's, it's a fucking stick of Ram. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. All right. We're ready. I'm ready to, I think I'm ready to race
this thing tonight, right? Good friendship with Francis. Complete the garage. Gain access to the
scrap yard. Install a manual transmission. I'm not doing that. Okay. So let's go race. How do I,
I get it. I can take this off. Oh my God. I'm so sorry. What happened? That ear was itchy. I'm so
sorry. This thing's ready to rock and roll. What time is it? It's okay. Let me, um, I have energy.
Let me check it out. Why does the spoiler keep falling off? Do I have to screw it on? Oh, green
tint. That's right. Holy shit. You're right. How could I forget? Wait, am I gonna, am I gonna be
supposed to put it on? The tires are deflated. No, they're not night vision. Oh yeah. The tires
are not deflated. They're fine. What the fuck happened? This tire, something wrong with this
tire. Dude, what the fuck? How do I keep it on there to tape it? This is my wrench. I don't,
I have no idea what the wrench is. So whatever. All right. It's time. It is almost six o'clock.
Almost make sure I have gas to do this shit. I want a full tank of gas. I can finally drive
this thing. I don't want to use the whole thing because I need this over here. Someone here,
someone here. All right. Save your game. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Save it and then it'll be really late at night and I can go do the race. How old are you?
I turned 19 a week ago. I was graduation. Are you 19 in dog years?
You look younger than ever. Moisturize. If anybody asked me for any actual advice,
the advice is actually moisturize your face. That's the only, that's the advice I'm going
to give you for anything. Wait, I can boost the seat up? How do I turn the fucking lights on?
Oh, look at this car. I need the radio. This car doesn't have a radio. What do you mean?
Doesn't have no way. There's no radio. All right. Into town and I'm going to do,
I don't know where I'm going, but I'm going somewhere in town. What? The spoiler came off.
It is. It's so dark. It's so dark. I can't see anything. Did I go the wrong way? I feel like
I went the wrong way. No, I didn't. It's right here. Can you play this game in third person
does it have to be a first person? Oh shit. Okay. I got it. Hey yo, what's up? What's up?
What's up, fellas? All right. All right. What do you think? What's up, dude? What's up, bro?
Yo man, even though it's kind of cold tonight, it's nothing compared to how I stoned I am.
You have some for that. You have some for that. You have some for sell. Don't bring him in that.
I would probably wait. I would like to race. Good to see you. So boring racing here in almost straight
line. I like tore up the road. You look good today. My twin cam engine is so fast. Imagine
when I turned it more. How's everything? You look good today. Thank you. Pretty cool. Are we ready
to go race to the sawmill? I don't know where any of this stuff is. I don't, I don't have $50.
I'll see you in two days, man. By the way, call the fucking Kellogg's box. You got that
fucking piece of shit out of good one. Easy run. It's just going to chase me. Oh shit. I need to
eat something. Where am I? What's the point of that if I'm just wasting gas? There's no point.
I just literally used a half a tank of gas for no reason. I need $50. So you know what we're doing.
Wood cutting stream. How is it? I need to go to sleep. Burn this off. I don't want to waste the
gas. This dude's going to end up at level 99 wood cutting. You got to sell weed. Go climb the
wind turbines and you'll get weed seeds. I might buy potatoes over here too. I need to check on
them. How are they doing? Getting there. 88%. Probably tomorrow. All right. Here we go. I'm
taking my truck down here and I'm going to fill it. I'm going to try to get like five or six hundred
bucks. Chainsaw's in there. Let's get this stuff out. Everything's empty. Good. Chainsaw in there.
Okay. Time to cut some wood. Everybody's favorite part of the stream. Weed is a crop that's been
grown and harvested. You don't need to copy and paste the entire paragraph to get me to
do the weed thing. Let's move. Okay. Fill the car. Wood right here should be fine.
Parking brake. I'm going to keep the lights on because I think it illuminates the area a little
bit if I had it the right fucking way. Great. Good job. Good work. We want weed. I'll do it.
I'll do it tomorrow. Let me at least get some cash so I can keep playing. You can find weed at the
top of one of the windmills. That seems like so out of the way. Why would they? That seems like
really far away. Let's do two more trees. Chainsaw. Okay. Dude, what am I thinking? Am I like stupid?
Look at this. I can just put this shit in the car like this. It should stay in there, right?
I'm looking for at least a thousand bucks. This is enough. This will get me to at least 500.
That's fine. It's all right. I'm not going far. Quickly and efficiently. I'll grow weed. I promise
I'll grow weed. His cheeks are the same color as his shirt. It's because my white balance is fucked
up. That means I have a lot of like blood in my face which is like, you know, healthy. They call
it a glow, guys. Come on. That's all I got for now. Is there a... It's probably a better way to load
the truck, right? Whatever. A healthy 70% total blood level in your cheeks. I don't know what's
supposed to be healthy or whatever, but I feel okay. I feel fine. What time is it? It's not too
late. I can keep going. I actually probably can put another couple of trees in here. We'll see.
Maybe not. I'm getting hung. I'm getting... What did you just say? Do you sleep like a bat? Is that
why? I don't know how they do that. How do bats do that shit? It isn't hanging upside down. How
do they sleep upside down? Wouldn't that be just bad? How does a bat sleep upside down and have it
be like, okay? They evolved to do that. But what, like, mechanically, how is that functioning?
I can definitely put more than another tree in here. Probably two more. Oh my god, fine.
Okay, I'm good. I'll go get the weed. I will. Wait. These are done. 88%. These have been
done tomorrow. Probably have a different... I feel like if I read that, that's me saying something
weird. Different system in the brain? I feel like that's like a ligma, like ligma nuts or something,
right? What are you saying? Everybody wants to say that so I don't look like an idiot.
The limbic system. Yeah, but I don't know. I just was reading it for a second. I'm just like, wait,
is that like a ligma, like ligma balls? I don't know. You said it though. If I was just saying,
is it one of those? Because, I don't know, I can't trust any of you. I can't trust you guys.
Sometimes it's, you guys go... I don't know. Vinny just hosted. What's going on guys? Thanks Vinny.
Welcome, welcome, welcome. We are in the process of cutting wood and we are creating
an environment where I can make some money in this game. Hope you had a good stream. Thanks a lot.
Stick around, we're gonna be here for a little while. You caught us at a great time because
we're about to make about five to six hundred dollars here and then I'm gonna go do a street
race. So we are, it's gonna be Pog. I'm afraid that there's not enough gas to cut all this but
let's find out. Welcome to the cutting wood for five hours stream. I've done other stuff
like get lost and complain about the map for a long time. I mean that was a while.
Are we doing one more? One more batch? All right, that's it. Enough, enough, enough, enough. No more.
Take this, sell it. Go to the windmill, get the weed. From there we'll go from at the weed.
Potatoes will be done by then. I feel like I'm making a Thanksgiving dinner. What was Vinny doing
today? Anything interesting? Something cool? Waiting, one more. What's, ah come on, what's one more?
Kirby? Is that new Kirby game any good? Is it the new Kirby game? Should I play the new Kirby game?
I wish this was strawberry magic. Yeah, it's good. Interesting. Lego Star Wars 2? Yeah, there's a lot
of things I could play. What should I do next time? You want to do like a full-on viewer's choice
right now? There's like 20,000 people here. Are you ready to have, you want to go for it?
What do you guys want to do? I'm open to suggestions. All right, that's it. No more. Do M&M's Beach Party?
Ah, I played that game. It was all right. Elden Ring Part 35. Did you do Breath of the Wild?
Not now, not yet. I need to be really in the mood for that. Ace Attorney? I can't play Ace Attorney.
We, all right, let me go over this real quick for a lot of the new viewers that don't know.
I would, I want to play Ace Attorney. I want to play it. But Ace Attorney does this thing
where every minute to like two minutes, the screen goes and it's a white flash in your face.
It actually happens like every 15 to 30 seconds. It goes. I wish I could turn it off.
The next time you play Ace Attorney, just watch. It flashes the screen every 15 seconds. This is
a lot of wood. We're good. All right, let's go turn this in. If I could mod it out as an option to turn
the flash off in the newest Ace Attorney game. Yeah, the newest one, but not the old ones. Then
everyone wants to see the old ones played on this stream, right? I get requests all the time to play
Ace Attorney. Oh! I'm fine. We're good. Didn't lose one brick. Do the remade one? Switch version.
You can turn it off. Huh. Wear shades. Just wear sunglasses while I play. That would be so stupid,
but it would work. All right. Who's going to be the closest? How much am I going to get for this?
Or like 50 or 25. All right. I'm ready to fucking race. Can I do it? It says become friends with
Francis. Can I say anything to him or do anything with him? Can we hang out? I don't. We just
completed the second floor in the garage. So much room for activities. Okay, cool. I don't think I
can go in there, but sure. Okay. $125. I have gas. I'm going to go bet and I'm going to go race and
I'm going to go sleep and I'm going to come back. I'm going to race. Sounds fun. Let's do it.
This is wasting gas. Is it? It takes more gas to back up. Oh, my spoiler's back. That's actually
cool. Didn't I lose it? Oh, I've reloaded the game. That's right. So that means I have to do the
tires again then. This one especially. No. Maybe I did. Did I save it after doing that? Yeah, I did.
Okay. All right. I'm ready to do it. Let's go. Rest up. I'll save the game when I get up.
Bolt the spoiler down. How do I bolt the spoiler down? Do I have a thing to do that?
It doesn't look like there's a slot for it. Is there a slot for this? I don't see one. I need
the wrench. Okay. What do I do with the wrench? Where's the wrench? Dude, where's the wrench?
Thank you. Is it on there now? Do I need two? I'm ready. Turning this on. Save the game and
let's go race. Very cool. Almost time. Night night night, right? Night time. Stanley Parable Ultra
Deluxe. It'll be night time when I'm done with this. Don't yawn. We didn't decide what game.
I don't know. I'm down for whatever. What's something that I haven't done that you guys
would like to see? Do Ape Escape? How about Paper Mario? No. I've heard of that game,
Iron Lung. Should we do Iron Lung? That game's only like an hour and a half long though, right?
We'd have to do something else. All right. Well, next stream, we're going to do Iron Lung.
And no, I'm not stopping the stream right now. I have to win. I have to do at least race one time.
I've got plenty of gas, right? I can't find the lights every time. They're in such a weird
spot. Where are they? Right here. All right. Both? Okay. Yeah. Yes. Let's do it. B for third
person. Holy shit. I cannot fucking believe it's taking me five hours to press B. Oh, I don't know.
How am I supposed to know? This is so much better. You should do a drift. Medium left. Just play
Baldi's Basics. No. I'll do Iron Lung and something else. We need like two or three games next time.
I have a list of stuff that I haven't played yet. That might be fun. I could jump out of the car.
All right. I'm back. Race to the sawmill. I don't know what the sawmill is and I don't know where
it is. So let's go. Go beside. All right. Let's go. Here we go. I'm ready. What? That's it? That's it?
How am I ever going to beat anybody? How am I supposed to do this? I need to cheat. All right.
Does somebody else have a car that I can beat? I feel like the truck is faster. The truck is
probably faster. I feel like it actually is faster. I don't know why I'm using this thing.
Let's go again. Okay. Race to the... Okay. Race to the Federation. This is just $200. All right.
This car didn't look as fast. How do you reverse? I don't know. Oh, come on. Jesus Christ. Actually,
like actually stuck. Where is everybody? Did that motherfucker take $200 from me and leave?
Because it's morning or something? What the fuck is going on? What? I drove off? I didn't drive off.
I was trying to turn around and then everybody leaves? Like the geek in the fucking wooden
spoiler car? You take my money and leave? All right. I'm going to the windmills. We're doing
the weed. Fine. Reload the save. Yeah. Sure. I'll give you $200 and I'll race you. Okay. Good.
Thanks, man. Okay. Let me just like turn around real quick. Oh, I don't know. I don't know. This
is a new car. I don't know how to reverse it. Don't leave. Why is everybody leaving? Don't leave.
This motherfucker tinted his windshield. We got to go. We got to get the fuck out of here.
Cartoon geek. Oh, you can use your blinkers. How do I turn my blinker off? I don't know.
Where is it? How do I turn the blinker off? All right. One, I want to let me do the $200 one.
That's it. I feel like that's going to be longer and there's more opportunity for them to make
mistake. Well, I take the more expensive track because I feel like the more expensive one is
longer. So I probably have a chance to take a turn or something. It's probably harder,
but if there are turns involved, then I might actually be able to get an advantage.
Whatever happens here, no matter what, I'm going to get over to the windmill
and climb the wind. Let's just do it now. No, I will go to the windmill and see if I can get up
there and get the weed. Oh shit. It's the fucking green geek again. It's the fucking green geek.
Don't do that. God damn it. Come on. God. Okay. We're good. It doesn't count. It doesn't count
because you have to touch it. Oh my God. He's blazing. I'm in the fucking dust. This is late
game shit. How am I ever going to do this? Look at this. Look at how much loser my grandma does
her shopping faster than that. No, it's in the ocean. This geek didn't, he didn't belong.
Oh shit. The car's smoking. I got to get out. What the fuck? All right. I obviously can't do that. So
my car is way too shitty. So I'm just going to go get the marijuana.
I don't even fucking care if the hood's up. Let's go. We're going to get the marijuana.
Some fucking geek comes over to the street race in like a fucking, in like a 2000 fucking,
like 13 camera or something puts lights on it, has a wooden spoiler, goes 70 miles per hour
and misses the first turn and goes into the ocean. All right. So you're telling me I climb up one of
these things and there's marijuana on top of one of the windmills. This feels like horse shit,
by the way. This feels like absolute horse shit. Like you made this up.
How am I going to climb the windmill? You made it up. You made it up. It's on the game's Wiki.
Oh shit. You didn't make it up. You've accused Chad of lying like five times now.
I would have bet, I would have bet $10,000 that that wasn't a log cutter. Cannabis seeds. Oh yeah.
Did they fall damage? I got weed seeds now. Who cares if I don't know how to drive?
I can just sell weed. All right. Get me out of here. Back to the road, which is over here,
right? The road over here. Okay. How do I go? How do I get out of here? I gotta get back into the
main road. Where's the main road? Am I on the road right now? I think I have to turn around.
It's so dark. I don't know where I am. Okay. This is it right here. Right. Am I going the right way?
I can't fucking read this map. It's too dark. I think it's this way, right? Right. That's right.
Right. I think this is, this is, this is, this is, this is, I don't know where I am. Windmills are
down here. Um, I actually don't know. I think this is correct. Am I just going in a circle?
I might just actually be going in a circle. Nope. Okay. I have, this is the garage,
which was, uh, I think I'm up. Okay. I just keep on this road.
This should take me all the way around, right? I can't read the scrap. Uh, yark. I don't know.
I can't get in. Yeah. Okay. I remember this. This is the next road to go this way. You can go down
here, which should take me, wrap me around past the windmills again, which will put me down at
the bottom part of that map. Think, right? Your car's on fire. It's not, it's just a little smoky.
Okay. Now I'm going the right way. Is the windmills are right next to me?
Like I go down and then I take a right. I think. No idea. Actually, I think it's,
I think it's the next time I can take a right, I can take a right.
Remember, it's your father. We need to change your oil. I think that's correct.
Think. Uh, you gotta change your oil every 3000 miles. This is, I just went in a circle.
I just wish I knew what direction I was even facing. The three windmills are over there on
the right. So I need to turn around and go that way and then take a right on that road.
I think we lost. Block the enemy race car with your truck or something.
Hold on. I need to get back to my house first. This is way more important.
I just went in a circle again. Go this way back this way. And then I take a right
this dirt road. All right. Thank God it's becoming daytime.
I can actually see what I'm doing. Here we go. All right. Let's go get out.
Okay. Please don't do that. Please don't do that. I feel like I'm in a world of Warcraft
zone and I'm like, I hacked the game and I modded it and I'm in a car. I've done,
I feel like I'm not supposed to be driving a car here. I don't know where I'm going.
Oh my fucking God. I'm back at this. Please God help me. What do I keep doing wrong?
What do I keep doing? Just go back. Is the thing on the right,
that French word in the top right, is the thing on the top right,
is am I at a Wille Donk Jacks right now? Is that where I am? Is that where I am?
So if I turn around and just stay on this fucking road, then why does this thing say like
Jim's Automotive? What happened? A rock just hit me. All right. Slow down. I'm going to fucking
relax. So now if I just stay on this road and just stay left and then stay left again and just go
around, I don't fucking know, man, whatever. So just stay left, stay left both times that way.
Can I just get on the Griffin and fucking get out of here? 15 K people are watching you lost
in Westfall. I'm telling you, man, it's confusing. Not here. Okay. Take a left. Okay. Left. Stay left
and then stay left again. If I turn around another circle, I'm going to eat the monitor. I'm going to
just eat it one by one. I'm going to break the monitor over my knee and eat it. I'm so, my
character is so tired. Okay. Stay left again. And that should be, and then just go, I think, right?
Yeah. I got it. And then my house should be on my right. Please. Please. We're so close to Disneyland.
I tell you, I don't know where it is, honey. We already went down that road. That says Epcot.
Maybe if this place wasn't as big as fucking like four cities in Texas, we'd be able to figure out
where we were going. I don't know what the fuck happened. I swear to fucking God, man, I'm about
to just walk home and just use the truck and fuck this thing. Chop this thing up and throw it in the
trash. Who cares? I'm not a truck. Okay. I'm going the right way now, right? And just stay through
here. This is correct. No. Give me a goddamn blip on the map. Like honest to God. Just give me a
blip. Like there's so many weird twisty turns. Give me a blip on the map. Even if it, okay.
Even if it was like, this was your last known location 30 seconds ago, it would be better.
I would at least be able to know where the fuck I was going. Where am I now? The weed seeds are
fine. They're right there. All right. Now, now we're okay. Now I'm just straight here. Straight.
Straight again. Right? Yes. I'm about to drive into the fucking ocean. Buy a GPS.
The seeds are fine. They haven't moved. I promise. Go back. This is the wrong way.
Oh, it's the wrong way. Is it? Get me the fuck out of here. Oh, dad. Um, isn't it like already four
o'clock? It is. Yes, it is. Doesn't do. I think we missed the Donald Duck breakfast. It's all right.
It's okay. We're fine. We can't, son, son. Oh, son. Dad. Dad. Son, I'm coming.
Son. Get me out of the car now before I freak out. Give me these. It's all I care about. I don't care
if that thing fucking explodes. I don't care if this car explodes. I don't fucking care. Explode
for all I care. All I, I don't, the truck is way better. Why would you not have a truck? Let's go
over what trucks have. Versatility, four-wheel drive, space, speed. Don't overdrive a little
shit sedan like that. Why would you overdrive a sedan like that? The truck is 5,000 times better.
I wish I could put a better engine in this fucking bad boy. You know what I'm saying?
Where's the weed? I need to dig. We missed the Donald Duck breakfast. I have two seeds, right?
You need a harvest basket? Fuck off. I don't need a harvest basket. It's called use your hands like
a man and just rip them up. Dad, why are you planting seeds in the ground in our hotel?
Son, it's everything to be fine. Dad, the only thing we rode was it's a small world and that ride
sucks. That's right. I like that ride actually. I rode that three times in a row because nobody
fast passes that piece of shit. We can ride that as many times as you want, son. But I wanted to
ride Space Mountain. Space Mountain sucks. It's, you can't even see it. It's just dark. Who cares?
You don't even know you're on a roller coaster, son. Trust me, it's a small world. It's just
paying for your buck. Dad, don't you understand that it's going to take like four weeks for the
marijuana to grow? Son, I got fertilizer. It'll happen much faster. Are we planning on being
at Disney World for four weeks? I have to go to school. You don't have to go to school.
I'm not huffing that. He was spray painting the wall. Put it away. Put it away and get on with it.
Turn the car off. Water the plants and I'm going to sleep for a week and I'm just going to eat
food and sleep for a week and then I'm going to go back to that meet and greet at where all the
cars are and I'm going to sell weed to everybody and then it doesn't matter if I drive my car into
the ocean. It doesn't matter because I'm the guy that sells the weed. Precisely what we talked
about in the first like three hours of the stream. I'm not the guy that cuts the wood. I'm the guy
that I don't I'm not the guy that sells the weed. I don't do that. I'm just saying that like I don't
need to that was came out weird that came out very wrong. My point is it's like I don't have to drive
the car. I can do another activity and it's fine. Where did it go? Breaking bad. Marijuana is not
oh yeah I got marijuana in my possession.
He's got weed in his glove box.
Please it's just illegal in fucking all every county in America almost.
Dad why are you doing that? Why? Put it back. Breaking bad. I've got like a gram of marijuana
in my possession. Oh breaking bad. All right how does it look? How many days to take? How do I
harvest this? A harvesting basket. So let me go get a harvest. I'm gonna sleep 10 days in a row.
Harvesting basket. Would you get it from the store? Which just I'm gonna go to sleep again.
Who cares? Chill. You just slept. No. Go to bed now. Dad why do you keep humming that song?
Why are you doing air guitar? It's just marijuana. I can't sleep. So what am I supposed to do?
I guess I got wood. Car is still running. Why is this fucking seat? Dude okay
relax. Why is it so far up? Car is off. The lights are just on. Okay all right I'm going to use the
ATV. Should I? Is there gas in here? I haven't drove this yet. This sounds like fun. How do you
where's the ignition on an ATV? Does it even have one? Where is it in the middle? How do I think it
turns on? I mean I thought this thing here. How do I drive it? Parking brake. It obviously has gas.
Put it in gear? How do you put it in? I've never driven one of these before. R and F? That was fun.
All right go back to sleep. All right is R and F on the car too? I'm just so awake. Do I have
enough to turn it on and save? Oh shit. I'm out of gas too. Fuck me. Really? I'm just going into town
and waiting till it opens. Excuse me? Wait I already have a harvesting basket? Are you kidding
me? I actually do. No I don't. That's the Easter basket. That's the Easter basket. That's not it.
Yeah I have to buy it. Let's go. This bullshit. I don't know. I don't have a heart. I feel like
I've seen it but I know what you mean. That's a maple syrup can thing. All right I need to go to
town. Get gas. Buy a harvesting basket. Be ready to rock and roll here. Gas can it's in the trunk.
Why does your car have eyelashes? Why not? I just wish that they could blink. I wish I could like
blink my eyes without having it like mess with the lights. Have it be like transparent or something.
This is not Elden Ring? It is. What do you think you're watching? It's just a shit load of mods on
it. I'm trying to do the Any% uh super glitch speed run where I beat the game in 18 seconds.
Where I mod the game to have a car just drive to Elden Beast and drive through the map and then
Elden Beast dies and I hit the split button. All right here we are. What am I doing here? What am I
why am I here? Oh basket right okay. Harvesting basket and I need gas. When do you open? Just
open let me in now. I will pay 10% more than all the products have listed if you let me in right
now. Just let me in. It says 8. It says 8. It was 8.01. It says 8. Your sign says 8. You'd actually
need these. One of those customers? Um I mean I don't know about that. I'm just messing around.
I'll fill the car too. Who's my favorite Family Guy character? Uh probably Joe. Can I just use
this right now? I can. Okay cool. Looking much better. Actually not looking bad anymore. It
looked terrible before. All right now should I get the windshield wiper thing? Now what? Um
oh I can get a muffler. How do I put this on? I'll figure it out. Okay I got the gas. I've got
and now I need a basket. They don't sell baskets here. Who sells the basket? They do. Oh it is okay
it's right here. All right thank god. Let's go. What else can I buy here that I need that I could
what else should I get anything else I need stock up on poutine that's actually a good idea
the snack shack yeah speaking of snack shacks speaking of snack shacks what do you guys think
what should I do is it a uh is it a mcdonald's kind of night tonight don't think so a big salad
hmm what is going on okay where'd my basket go what's going on the hell is that why would
you be locked right now you open in like an hour come on hurry up there's gotta be something else
I can do in like an hour I died where's the car hey it's 12 30 I feel like resurrection sickness
or another minute I can spray paint the truck wait this is don't do this yet I want metallic
where's the metallic one I know I have it it's rare there it is why is it not working oh no I'm
making the fucking Thanos thing like the grimace mobile the what's going on man no but I can't drive
this here because the both the cars are gonna be there reload the save but I did so much since then
I can't I need to I'll take the atv whatever fucking who cares about the atv right I'll take
the atv to town and just dump it in the ocean continue right who cares I'm gonna ghost ride
this into the ocean it has my harvesting basket too god damn it what I'm gonna have to take
Thanos car and then I'm gonna have him drive me back and drop me off and I'll get it hello
what's going on why did I just lost control of the car why did I lose control of the car
that was weird I couldn't turn I act I could that's gonna make me puke I couldn't turn I
swear to god I feel like I'm playing Mario Kart the SNES I gave my car back I'm gonna drive my car
back gas up the tank save the game harvest the potatoes all right where's my car do not hit that
guy all right here we go now did I buy oh the poutine right okay cool my shit still in here
yes okay thank goodness snack shack is open what the fuck are you what is happening why does this
keep happening this car is fucking possessed this car is possessed what put it in reverse
get the fuck goddamn car just buy the whole entire store worth I just want to sell weed that's all I
want to do I want to make one weed sale and then drive my car into the ocean and then the stream
the mountain on the left that where is that mountain it's like right here right
let's go back I'll come back and get the truck later poutine is gravy cheese and french fries
right I think I've had it once it's actually pretty good it's pretty good I liked it you kind
of really can't go wrong I don't see what what the problem is with that if you don't like that
that's kind of I mean it's cheese gravy and crispy potatoes like that doesn't seem like something you
could be mad at oh it is good yeah it's good right okay sounds good yeah ask this up so I can
save the game again fill the whole thing out fill the atv right yeah the muffler is gone the muffler
is gone but that was like 150 bucks is it actually gone it might be in the car over here it could be
like stuck somewhere it actually gone it's not like under the seat really oh that sucks actually
whatever okay uh harvesting basket let's get the potatoes whoa 78 full doesn't dump right
I get more seeds that's actually kind of cool all right cannabis is at 14 what do I do with the
potatoes what do I do with this you make poutine french fry cutter you missing the frying basket
okay have we figured out where the frying basket is because I have no idea I have to buy from the
let me save it why is it so bright favorite sci-fi character george it's definitely george
grammar is cool too but it's george how much time until I can actually sell the weed
I need to plant this other potato too 20 another puppy five to ten days in game I want to see what
that does um and then the stream is ending that's the last thing I'm gonna do everything is so
bright 25 probably car running no it's fine we said do george saying a little bit of spi
no that's too that's dumb a little bit of spi jerry a bit of spi you know it's kind of sad that
Seinfeld I kind of wish that they was like Seinfeld existed now imagine like the george is
a streamer episode he would accidentally walk in like naked or something right they get banned it
would be about how how george got like a like a 30-day twitch ban you didn't turn off the stream
you didn't hit this end stream button I thought I did I stuff and the kramer comes in yeah I stream
too another website it's called like chatterbait or something right he's like doing porn and and
kramer thinks that george is also doing like chatterbait that's too specific oh but go back
to bed I want those things just to grow by chatterbait I don't know it'd be like if I
kramer has like been doing that I guess for a long time and okay and george is talking about
streaming on twitch but kramer's talking about streaming on like chatterbait so but they don't
you know what I mean like they don't understand that they're different places until the very end
where kramer is like oh I'm gonna go live on george's computer and he's like taking his clothes
off and he's on twitch and that's when it's like the ding ding ding ding that's where it stops
and to get the ending 34 we're almost there this is just outside what am I doing you look very
handsome today thanks newman is a vtuber and and the whole time like jerry doesn't get it jerry
doesn't understand like he he doesn't get what how it works or why it works he sees like newman
walking down the street with like a wad of hundreds hello jerry newman oh you're probably
wondering where I got all the money not really and then jerry incorporates that into a stand-up
it'd be oh it'd be great episode what's the deal with vtubers what are they at I'm telling
you I'm just like sleeping and eating until this is done 36 god damn it I still have so much more
keep the episode going I don't know just it's a thought which is a fun thought and then george's
dad like wants to get into it too who's that George I'm gonna do this vtuber thing I'm gonna
where are we going how's life what no I don't want to go to school where am I going
I heard new I heard newman did it for a million bucks he's a millionaire jerry he's a millionaire
george a million bucks I don't I have no idea where I'm going no no don't actually don't stop
I'm gonna all right Ernie Sanders oh to get the truck holy shit that's awesome everyone's doing
this thing with a weird thing where they find everything you say funny and is omega lulling
everything you say they're so nice oh we're going up omega lol true they are kind of nice
it is pretty fun we want him to feel good about himself so we do that I would love a Seinfeld in
current times I guess that's kind of Larry David that's Kirby enthusiasm right now right he hasn't
been actually funny since the sorcery streams you're seeing the first streams that I really
kind of really went in hard on on twitch seven years ago were the only things I ever did that
you liked interesting where's the truck can you go a little bit further a little bit further up
here it's my stop you're all nasty stop it all right get up get up get up how do I get up thank
you I've been watching you for 10 years that's that's ridiculous I can't believe I've been doing
this for that long you know sometimes like you just think in my brain like three or four years ago
it was like it was it was like 10 years ago it's weird it's ridiculous I did not expect it to be
going this fast because it's carbon on the whole time no god I do it every time it three years ago
feels like 10 years ago the other way around right yes I meant to say the other way around
all right let's go back home that should be enough time for the weed to grow I need to go
that way it makes me think now I know we've kind of been messing around this whole time just
fucking around but real talk if 10 years went by that fast another 10 years is that's kind of
ridiculous that's insane to think about that like 10 years from now I hope it doesn't go that fast
are you gonna stream in your 40s I'm not even 40 yet relax he's gonna do something even cooler
you know here's the wild thing oh eventually eventually you're gonna stop doing this right
eventually what when I think of the things that I want to do and there's a lot of things that
I'd like to do like going forward right uh but it's gonna be hard to match like how I feel about
this forget about like money forget about anything I'm just talking like to be able to match how I
feel about this doing this I have other things that I'm equally passionate about right but
I don't know it's gonna be weird it's gonna be hard but we're not talking about that right now
because that's not happening right now we're not talking about that right now because that's not
happening right now everyone relax what we're doing is we're eating poutine and we're making
we're growing weed in our backyard retirement randy not yet 38 all right let's go some more
water on there I did not say eating poop see we're eating poop and growing weed in our
backyards son save the game go to sleep I'm gonna turn this on no no go to sleep then save the game
that makes more sense to me become a cod streamer no no I don't think so I don't think so you're
gonna become a family man because maybe I'll become Peter Griffin Peter Griffin in real life
you're gonna go back to making tf2 tutorials become a game show host that's kind of a good
gig isn't it right if I if I just like was I hosted real fortune I don't know one's gonna
give me that job I would watch it if it was you I'd watch the hell out of that what is that for
almost halfway there we're there come on how can I make time pass very quickly I could cut some more
wood sleep I can't my energy is full build the sugar shack I don't even know how to do that
build the sugar shack but I don't buggy pack installed oh buggy part this thing I need more
buggy parts that's annoying that the muffler is gone that would have been fun oh I know why it's
so bright because I'm shining the headlights into the house high beams actual high beams into the
house we were trying to figure that out for so long what time is it were you a teacher or was
that a bit I was never a teacher I did substitute but any you don't need a teaching degree to
substitute teach let's go take a stroll with this thing why not why is this dead there's plenty of
gas in here why is this dead no you don't you don't need a teaching degree you do not need a
teaching degree to be a substitute unless that has changed in the last 10 to 15 years which maybe
it has I don't think so oh you still don't know it's probably per state that does not seem right
to be honest um I mean the issue is if you had to require like a masters in education to sub
it might be really hard to find a substitute because if you had masters in education
you'd be a teacher you'd be you'd do like teachers aid and then you become a teacher you wouldn't do
subbing really maybe you would for a little while different states probably have different criteria
I'm sure there's plenty of teachers that start doing substitute teaching for a while
and then you move on to like teachers aid stuff and then again do teaching it would be nice if
hold on hold on hold on it'd be nice if teachers made way more money
hold on you know we you know that we pay teachers like such a shit amount of money and the incentive
to be a teacher is like not that fucking great really and these are the people that are like
developing our children's brains I don't I don't understand how that makes any sense
arguably one of the most important jobs in the world and they make fucking nothing why that's
so strange that's such an that's such an important job it's so important it really is I forgot let's
go I didn't just sleep most of them can't so what was it they get the summer off yeah but that's
I mean trust me when I say that having to teach students is like you need that time you need that
time and teachers aren't just kind of lounging around in a fucking lounge chair for the summer
a lot of them are planning their lesson plans they you they might not be in the classroom for
three or four months but they have to get ready they have to get prepared when you go to your
class right you're not necessarily oh I'm just here and the teachers just got a whole lesson
plan ready to go now there are a lot of shit teachers I had teachers that I thought were
fucking terrible but maybe if we incentivized being a fucking teacher and they didn't make
like fucking like like nine dollars an hour or whatever the fuck it is like on the average
like 12 dollars an hour or something maybe people will be way more incentivized to be a teacher and
take it fucking seriously earn his mic up all right honestly I don't I don't care how you
feel about the world forget about political leanings anything doesn't matter I think we
can all agree that just like spitted by bed well we could all agree on that we could all agree on
that uh I think that we really need to make teaching way more incentivized and the lesson
plan's got to get updated too yeah we I can talk for an hour about this we need to talk about like
credit and fucking taxes and how to take care of yourself and shit and because I didn't fucking
learn that stuff till I was like in my mid-20s it's fuck it sucks my parents helped a lot right
my parents like told me some of these things but man I don't give a fuck about like geometry too
help me help fucking help these goddamn people help these goddamn kids learn some shit that
actually helped their life help out their future and shit I didn't give a fuck about geometry too
geometry is important I fucking hated geometry there's too many fucking lines I didn't like it
insurance yeah there's like so much shit to know and dude you know what a lot of people don't
really know what they're doing or what they want to do or what they want to be when they're 16 17
18 19 and we tell everybody oh hey uh by the way when you're like 17 18 you better know what the
fuck you want to do with your life go to college immediately go um go to trade school go um I don't
kind of know what the fuck I want to do I have this opinion that after high school there should
be a period where like of a year or two maybe even a year it's just a program for you to figure out
kind of without the anxiety of like oh my god I gotta fucking figure out how I'm gonna pay for
college I gotta figure out what I want to do with my life a gap year a gap a two-year gap year to
your two years in a gap for you to be able to figure out what you want to do even if you don't
get it completely right even if you're not completely exactly correct you'll be closer
than you were two years ago we we just push kids out of high school directly into another
thing that they're forced that they feel like they're forced to do and I was one of those
people I was one of those kids when I was like 17 18 19 I was I didn't know what the fuck I
wanted to do I thought I did but there is a lot of pressure to be like all right I guess I'm gonna
go to college or I kind of have to do something right because I gotta do something with my I
gotta do something with my life like I gotta hurry up I think we should kind of reevaluate that
people will be way better prepared if programs like that existed 52 we're almost ready to smoke weed
and this is not like some kind of wow what what a genius topic you're bringing up you're so
tons of people have thought about this and talked about this right I think it's it would be so
important because I think of me when I was younger and if I had some time and I could kind of do like
a pre-college or like a post high school kind of year where it wasn't a bunch of pressure it was
just all right let's figure it out almost ready and not a big financial burden a bunch bunch of
money you got to spend because I'm getting heated here when you start to spend a shitload of money
in the years where you're not sure exactly what you want to do a lot of people kind of get trapped
and you end up a couple of years in college or even doing like trade school and going into like
one of like the trade unions or something and if you don't have it right you have thrown a
shitload of money into the fucking trash I don't think I don't think that's okay I think that sucks
changing your major tons of people did that tons of people were doing that when I was in college
and it's like man imagine if you were able to figure that out and then you didn't have to
have the insane loans for the two or three years or a year or two and you're ready to go tell them
sis you're explaining how wow we we we we that's not what happened compare it with the rest of the
world I just think that we we could be doing things a lot better you should do a podcast about this
no no I'm not smart enough to trust me I am not fucking smart enough I am not the person you want
to be listening to with this kind of shit I'm just telling you how I feel you do trust me I don't
have the resources I don't have the brain to handle this kind of stuff I can speak on a couple of
small things I can that's it come on hurry up and weed hurry up you should be prime minister no I
should not why is the truck in the ground I probably rolled it's fine and also hmm I think
that people are inefficient the more that they're doing something excuse me I think that a four-day
work week increases efficiency excuse me I'm just I'm telling you I think the more that you like
have to stay and do something in a row you get exhausted and you don't want to do it I'm not
even a four-day work and look people a lot of people like to kind of really hunker down I know
people that like no dude I kind of like doing like two fucking 13 12 to 13 hour days in a row
and then just give me fucking four straight five days off right everyone's kind of different like
that no man I actually kind of like work I like fucking just bang give me like a big like 24 ounce
coffee and just I'm going for 14 hours let's fucking go I want to go somebody somebody just
bad chest me it was one bad chest and I was like it was lasered into my brain it was laser beamed
into my head I just saw it and I was like that's a bad chest that motherfucker got me and I just got
like bad no I thought I did not excuse me I hold on let me be really clear to some there are people
that saying oh so you're a socialist that is absolutely not what just happened that is not
what just happened let's be very clear I want to be incredibly clear that's not what that just was
okay how is a how is a four-day work week and like a two-day work week where you do like two
14-hour days in a row that's what are you talking about so you hate socialism I'm gonna sit here
till you fucking relax you admitted I lost 500 viewers dude I lost 500 viewers because like four
in the morning it's like three o'clock in the morning what's I and I every day I get closer
and closer to having a voice that's different than what it was five years ago no I no I'm not
getting up till you stop listen all I'm saying is we do things we could change it and we'll be
better we could do we could make some good changes we could make some good changes get me a podium
put me in front of it let's go I'm telling you right now he's a million I think that we could
have so many better things with education and treating people a little better okay that's it
that's it I didn't say anything else I didn't say anything else okay it's like 4 a.m. it's not even
midnight well I'm talking 12 1 2 it's 2 a.m. Eastern and it's like 7 a.m. European the next
person that calls me millionaire Andy is getting banned from my chat I don't even have running
water in here what you talk about you want education to be a little better you talk about
how you want like people to have like better smoother work weeks and be happier that's all
I'm asking for that's all I'm saying I know I get the million millionaire Andy I just I just don't
I want people to have better like lives it's nothing that's nothing to do with anything else
that's a billionaire take he's a based socialist
oh I'm calling mom
what I I screamed at that person that person get the person out of here I want that person banned
for at least 30 minutes I want that ban for at least 30 minutes you're out for 30 minutes and
I'm telling you you're gone for 30 minutes I'm telling you to right now mods ban that person
30 minutes I gotta go I'm out of here I should never talked about how I want like education to
be better I should have just smoked weed on stream I should have just smoked weed
and I never should have said anything and then I never should have looked over a chat and read
the guy that said I said the blowjob comment I don't I'm not doing it ever again I'm not doing
it again I wanted to say one of the education system to be better it's the worst part is they
said blowjob Andy like god damn it man you I'm looking over at mod chat and they said auto mod
caught that and he read it he's reading blocked messages now oh I'm so sorry mods that's my fault
if only this grew faster I would we had to we had to sit here and have like the
let's talk about the world I'm going back to bed uh no I know we're just fucking around you know
what I mean yo yo you get it you guys you got you guys are a lot of you guys are smart maybe
a lot of them some of you aren't some of you aren't I'd say like 90 I'd say like 90 percent
of you guys are very smart and the rest I'm sorry sorry sorry okay now I'm just like kind of now
I'm just poking all right like I don't know why I'm doing this right now I'm just like
I'm just I don't know why I'm like teasing and poking why are you guys just saying you're in the
10% I didn't say this chat did I I was about ready to doze off because I was feeling the
sleepies happening and then he screamed blowjob and I woke up that was one of the mods by the way
did you think did you think that like there was a blowjob in the game and I was freaking out
because I showed it on stream oh my goodness I'm so sorry and like I was panicking about it
why would I scream that I scream it in point I would not say anything I would turn the game
capture off where's my watering can moral the story is there and there is done but who cares
I was clipped and shipped you're a moralist I don't know what that means anyway so cutting
logs yeah anyway so I'm cutting some logs here if jerma reads this he has to do a push up on stream
wait how many how many you guys think I can do huh how many push-ups you think I can do
let's let's like make a bunch of people think I'm doing a ton of push-ups if I could get the
fucking thing to work oh it's the other way and then it's gonna be horizontal here because I need
to be going that way how many think I can do one five six seven three oh fuck oh fuck
Jesus man I'm clearly sitting down you can see my like stomach coming up from this bottom
I'm clearly sitting down did that even look right was that fucked up oh let me see let me see I'm
sorry for any viewer that joined wait what does it look like it kind of looks real it kind of looks
all right it actually kind of looks all right it doesn't look that bad it actually really doesn't
look that bad it looks fine it looks like it makes sense it was you were I think it was fine I think
it was funny it was funny because I was doing push-ups how do I get this back to normal there
you go you dude I it was it looked like I was doing I was trying to do like 100 push-ups
yeah I'm looking I'm doing push-ups look god that looks like shit all right the audio yeah it's a
person doing a shitload of push-ups and it's very stressful hey I'm telling you right now I'm looking
at my phone community Jake has not said anything so I think I'm fine my mother watches these
streams she wouldn't she didn't say anything I think I'm gonna be fine I blame the fact that
the weed didn't grow play it back I'll play it back later your mother saw no I'm doing push-ups
it's like I'm doing push-ups on stream I'm doing like 50 push-ups on camera that's that's what it
was play it back now six seven I'm counting push-ups this shit ain't ever gonna grow I'm
just telling you it's only been five days since your last worst joke I wasn't trying to make a
joke I was trying to fool you that's best one guy moment the guy that said the blowjob thing
fucked up the whole stream that fucked up the whole stream let me just be very honest with you
the whole stream got fucked up how did why we were talking about like education in America what the
fuck happened what happened education in America to somebody said blowjob Andy to I'm doing push-ups
on stream like fake push-ups what happened what actually somebody bad-chested me and I fucking
freaked out all right let's go your fly was open it no that can't happen okay you can't have two
accounts that say omega lull best stream and then omega lull worst stream at the same time just
screen cap it so you go the duality of germ is chat that's not how it works what earphones do
you use these are Bose earphones oh my god I was looking at mod chat I have to show this this is
so fucking stupid what have I done I sometimes I don't know what I'm doing sometimes I'm just
fucking around oh god damn it man this is so funny oh the I know the edits that are gonna come out
of that are gonna be fucked up I'm sorry everybody what have I done but the thing is that picture
already exists of me like with my shirt off sleeping in a bed why do you the context already
is there there's already god damn it that's fucking funny double award-winning Andy duplicate
I think I have to leave I think I have to leave I think I have to leave right now I think I have
to leave I have to leave I gotta think I have to get out of here I think I have to get out of here
where why is the car so far away from the house where am I no seriously where what's happening
why is the car so far away from the house what happened oh my god my fucking head hurts from
laughing this is so fucking stupid oh you guys are too fucking funny seriously I don't know what
I don't know what happened the last 45 minutes of the stream but it's been it has been a shitshow
I hope it's been fun I hope it's not you thought it was funny unstuck I can't get out of here I
have to pull it with the no no I'm I think I'm gonna go I think I'm gonna get out of here I think
I have to get out of here right like I have to like go take a bath and just like think about what
I've done how seriously how do I get out how does it fit this perfectly in the stitch put it in neutral
I'll pull it out I'm not leaving till I sell the weed oh my god what a disaster they're making it
the banner for the discord I think my favorite part is double award-winning Andy but it's like
midnight we're just chilling we're just fucking around it's not what is this I don't know what
this is what is this this is these edits are fucked up oh yeah what is this what is this one
what is this what is that I don't know what this is is this a dj guys I don't know I don't know
tell you I don't I don't know why I had to do more than 50 I'm thinking about this now you know you
know what it is let me explain the reason why I did like 70 of those is because I was trying to
burn time the marijuana plants and I'm like all right I guess I'm just gonna keep doing it
because like the marijuana plants aren't gonna be ready the game was paused was it actually
what oh whatever who cares do push-ups with I got I got modded here i connor's chat what do you mean
what are you ready no no no no no god I gotta keep this thing attached I'm actually might be
able to get out now but did Connor raid honor raid what's up Connor you came at a great time
because a few moments ago we were discussing some topics about like education talking about
education here um nothing weird happened after that at all we went over a lot of topics that
you know it's really crazy I was like I gotta like I gotta internalize this so the stream
went from everyone being like based wow this is actually a really like level-headed talk we're
having to you're gonna get banned TOS dude you need to stop doing what you're doing it was within
10 minutes 20 minutes oh my god just hold it the switch up was instantaneous okay that's but
easy stay up here and put it put the parking brake up all right I made it up the plants ready yet
oh that was so funny these edits are killing me they really are doctor who I don't even know
what these are in context but I know that they exist that was best one guy for sure I don't know
I don't know what that was I think I got derailed like three times and then I did like the push-up
thing but it was just fucking weird and here we are now I like how you did that sideways but all
the edits have you at a normal rotation oh I fucking love this community so much it's so funny
oh it's so fucking funny you don't see I'm saying what I'm saying like I what else can I
fucking even do you know what I mean like oh you know like eventually I'm gonna get like probably
old I can't scream I can't like do fake push-ups wherever I'm doing next I'm not gonna go on my
game show host and pretend to be sideways for five minutes and embarrass myself in front of
fucking like a stadium full of people I don't know it's this is fun god what a fucking shit
show okay all right I'm gonna go to bed and I'm gonna wake up and the marijuana will be ready
but no Connor seriously thanks for the raid if you're here it's kind of an interesting time
for you to come over here are you the funny onion ring guy no that's somebody else he didn't raid
why'd you guys say that then oh it's so close 70 percent we're so close
no I'm the put I'm the the cringe push-up guy looks like you have tiny hands in real life
they're actually huge they're actually like really big I have huge fucking hands is this an edit
is this an edit I can't I can't why am I sitting sideways why am I sitting sideways in this picture
why is everybody sitting next to me this dr pepper shirt like what the fucking weird
oh there's another one what is this one what is this one is why is this person putting the hand
into this I'm gonna lose my mind today why would I be allowed back here I would not be
allowed back here what am I just some friend's dickhead that got back here was that is that
that's unedited right is this edited I think it's edited if it's not then wow I'm weird looking
oh my god you guys are gonna fucking kill me yeah what's the point of the left side of my face
why don't why do you have to have that you can't just have the what is this one I don't know what
this one is is this star wars you guys are quick with this shit this is quick this is fast is it
coming out too fast these are coming out way too fast and again I'm in a dr pepper shirt extreme
branding on the star wars movie one of the actors had to be in a dr pepper shirt the whole time
god you guys are fast okay all right all right honestly god I'm glad that happened
because at least they can be people can take the piss out of me oh what the fuck I this is not
just real I just know this is fucked up this is weird it's fucked up I think this one actually
might be fake it has to be I think it is what the fuck is what happened to me on the stream
this is fake right it has to be fake I think it is guys I don't know what's going on this feels
like I was I dreamed this dream I didn't do this I dreamed of this one I'm gonna wake up in like
15 minutes and it's gonna be like I have to play this game today no that's fake it's been edited of
course it is all right all right I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm done I'm done let's let everyone
take a step back and relax for a second we're gonna take a quick step back just rewind about
an hour you look like a cat we are at 76 for the cannabis plant pull it back but when I did the
car it's fun so I need to drink some maple syrup this game is fun by the way this game is kind of
like a long drive my summer car it's fun it's cute it's fun you look like the Michael Myers
cat in the hat it can't be real right this is the last thing I'm going to show before I just do the
marijuana shit I'm gonna lose my mind was it actually real oh what's going on oh I think
that's what's gonna happen why don't turn the webcam on I'm done I think I'm done this is a
Breaking Bad spoiler this is a Breaking Bad spoiler coming up I just want to make sure
everyone's aware this is a spoiler for Breaking Bad and you know what it already is everybody
already knows what it is if I don't need to show this because I mean everybody knows what this is
you know what it is it's a it's a major Breaking Bad spoiler and it's shown on the screen right
now in three two one I don't even know what the context of this one is I've made a grave mistake
tonight spoiler yeah how is it a spoiler is just him lying on the ground that's not a spoiler
it's just him lying on the ground he's not dead it's not even a all right no more no more no more
no more no more no more this last one no more this is it I'm gonna I'm done after this one
I promise go to the discord the this I think the sub discord is posting a shitload of these
you want to see more no I can't even open it I can't this this shitload of them there's like
a hundred okay I need to eat I'm sorry mom if you're watching it's been a wild one
sub stream is going crazy right now what a fucking idiot like I just haven't uh okay
on let's go I need my watering can wherever that is I have like a stuffy nose now how did that
happen where's the watering can anybody know where it is I'm almost I just want to sell weed at that
thing and I'm gone where's the watering can it's on the couch thank you god all right I just want
you to see this one um I need to chop some wood because I need do I have to do anything else with
the weed once I get it or is it good I just have to grind it up on the table right no I'm not
going to smoke it I'm going to sell it at the car thing if I save the game time will pass let's do
that can you blow up the gas can I don't think I really want to I think he lost all his brain
cells in the last 30 minutes you guys are fucking ridiculous god I have too much fun on this stream
I really do yeah I just do it's like just bad but it's no it's not it's awesome why is that bad
I have too much fun hurry up and go back to being a communist all right 80 something percent 82
we're almost there just save it again time will go by again we're just gonna we're gonna do this
like three times one more time and that should be it I didn't figure out what I was gonna do I
think there's food in the fridge they cook something all right let's go to sleep okay and
the plants should be ready to harvest I hope so oh I have this this potatoes in this what do I do
about this I don't want weed in the potatoes 93 percent what do I do throw them in the water I
don't how do what do I do about it I don't think I can get rid of this in the sink I can't cut the
french fries I need the fry basket cook them oh I can't no it's not in the sink I can't get it
shit I need a fry basket to do anything so can I not harvest the marijuana what happened to the
basket hey where's the basket it was just in my hand oh it went through the wall can I dump these
I feel like I just want to dump this shit I don't want this I need another basket can I throw it
out I don't I kind of don't want to but did I I went up a thousand followers that's weird
you're gonna throw out potatoes no I don't want to all right I have an idea if I harvest the
potatoes and get 200 percent can I dump it can I dump it after that all right I'll get another
basket it's I can't let's go use the computer for an hour where's my uh gas can I do I'm so screwed
up from the last like hour I don't know I don't know where my stuff is hurry up and boot so I can
do it 900 000 followers yeah that's kind of crazy that's almost everybody on earth the road to a
million I think it's gonna take a while I don't think we're gonna do that that soon that's gonna
take a little while you probably have a million I don't know I might not even get to a million
okay it's time for harvest they're ready so I can't put them in here I need to get another basket
all right I'm getting another basket and I'm done I'm taking the ATV it has gas what's wrong
with this thing like what's actually wrong with this thing gas it's full look at this it's got a
full tank is it in neutral oh I don't understand what those lights mean all right I need the gas
tank is that gonna fit in my little fry box whatever the hell that is I have to take the car
what has more gas I think I left this on all day I got gas all right let's go
let's just get this shit out of me for some reason I'm not making that mistake more than
once got your ass this car is disgusting why good night mr Albertson good night thanks for
watching uh thanks for hanging out I know it's late I'm almost done I'll be done in the next
probably 10 15 thanks for staying up as usual oh the next uh the plan for the next stream right
I wanted to do iron lung and something else something that's like another hour or two okay
while I'm in town is there anything I need for weed or do I just have to grind it on the table
and is there any item I need from the store or something do I need anything from town
or my good to go besides a fry basket I need a lighter when's the next stream gonna be what's
today today is Thursday technically midnight it was a shitload of subs wasn't there I missed a
shitload of subs the other day too uh they were like tons of 50 I mean I know I don't like shout
like out subs or bits anymore but they were a lot the other day I always feel bad of not
saying anything about it but yeah Freddie showed up the other day too yeah there was a bunch of
people that I don't know I try to I don't like I don't want to incentivize it really I appreciate
anybody that subs this channel I appreciate that you would you would at all but I don't I took a
policy of just not saying anything if you do you do and it is appreciated if you don't then you
don't have to then don't you don't ever have to uh but yeah some people give an insane amount of
money to this channel still um which is like I don't know I just it means a lot I hope I can
continue to make streams that you think are worth paying for I hope so all right I need gas first
and if you don't think so and don't give me any money right bye Jerma bye wait what are you
leaving what do you mean you're leaving forever what are you talking about you're smart that's
reverse psychology I can't believe that was a real face that I made is it not come on what
about smite Thursdays if you're good oh it's on the other side I can oh my god really why did I
just do that I love the streams thank god you're not real what are you talking about this counting
is it a full tank it's full okay all right I need another basket and I need a fry basket I don't
know I don't think I can afford a fry basket so it's too late let's go goodbye you're my favorite
vtuber thanks dude I really appreciate it thank you for the subs thanks for the 10 subs appreciate
it oh no way I can't believe you showed up my computer lagged a little bit no you can't 50
push-ups oh my god lol plus two bussing joke thank you maybe wait yeah maybe you're the fake ones
maybe it's you guys that I don't like that no no I don't like that that means that this isn't real
I don't like that oh okay it's time there's no car damage it's fine I'm not getting out of this
one I don't think I don't know how I do this every time I don't like how does it get perfectly
wedged in I how no you can't even try to do that if you try to do what I just did it doesn't work
why does it keep happening turn the car off I'm taking the truck anyways
all right I got some marijuana still extra seeds all right what do I do with this marijuana
I take it to the table right weed grinder how do I use this 10 packs to one weed grinder packet
oh I have to sit first there's a total of zero pack of joint close by 10 joint packs how do I
use it there's no harvest back at basket close by oh they already do it 10 minimum not enough
for one pack no I got it this is it right here right so I got it I already have one all right
I'm gonna sell this it's time it's time put it in the trunk now pack it what call me yourself
you need 10 pre-roll packs I can't I can I sell this your vehicles are in ditches man
can I sell this I think I yeah I can I'm gonna go sell it what time do I need to wake up I need
a gas can that's in here give me a fucking break 420 is over oh you're right I can never smoke weed
ever again let's uh speed it to nighttime I'm gonna take the truck let me get the truck let me
get this out of the ditch come on come on I think it's out I should be able to pull it out now
how did it go in got the car turn off hey let's go all right give me the weed now out of the
ditch that's good just be careful I gotta be very careful getting out of here snow runner
let's do it this is it this is the culmination of the whole stream eight hours of this you're
transporting one pack of joints in a pickup so I put it on the tray too yeah all right I'm
gonna put it on the tray I'm gonna we're gonna have to light it up or something where is it what
do I do with it where's the pack there it is where's it I have 10 joints how do I sell it
I didn't smoke it what are you talking about it says 10 in the corner I used it I opened it go
back to the packer okay I think I can I think I can save it this is zero packs of joints nearby
dude I I couldn't leave the house I had to I couldn't open the fucking door with it in my hand
god how far away does it remember when I saved it last how far away was it 17 minutes how far is
that I couldn't open the door it's not that far I was walking around in circles dude get up I
didn't even harvest it yet oh my god dude I can't you can't open the door if you have something in
your hands so I have to put the thing down open the door pick the thing up off the ground and
walk out the fucking house I'm just gonna smoke the fucking thing I don't even have a basket
I didn't I didn't think if I like I pressed like E I thought I'm like up there trying to just put
them like I don't know I was gonna like stick it in my personal inventory I need to do I have
enough gas to even save the game oh this is a disaster I okay can I just dump this shit out
can I just dump this what do I even do with this it's I can't even do anything with it
is there like a dump thing how do I get rid of this so I just have a basket that's full of
something I can't use and I can't get rid of it well the stream goes on for another 10 minutes
press Y to dump it out okay I can't even make time pass because I don't have enough gas to turn
the fucking computer on can I just like sleep on the ground for can I just like good I like
what do I how am I supposed to pass time get out of my fucking way I love a god I gotta go buy
another fucking basket because I can't dump the other because I put potatoes in it accidentally
oh the misery I'm almost there I just want a soft little head like his my head is hard as a rock
you see how big my brow bone is dude please I'll be really honest with you I've been playing this
game for eight hours I still don't know where the gas station is I just drive around till I find it
okay all right guys let's go oh push up edits those are the days
I just want to try I don't want to reverse I just want to turn
fill up the can can we go to Disney after this maybe if you're good he's pouring it I'm not
pouring it on the ground okay sorry so gas in this car I'm so close to being done I just want to
sell one weed to one person and then fucking be done we're good it's past midnight yeah it's very
late it's very very late you could have walked to Disney by now okay I'm just gonna go get the weed
right now go go go go go go go go go I need one basket go go go go go go go bye bye thank you
appreciate it goodbye basket done close go get out weed mission to sell one weed is commencing oh
let's go let's go hurry up come on this is the one this is actually the one this is truly the one
no more bullshit this is it I'm going back harvest sleep till fucking 10 o'clock at night
sell the marijuana get out this car seriously drives as if it has no fucking wheels there are
no wheels on this car it's made at the wheels are made out of wood it just rides on a straight line
why is he mad I'm not I'm just fucking around dude he's he has to see what he's mad I'm I
promise you I'm not bad Kappa I'm Kappa not I'm not mad Kappa I'm not Kappa I pro Kappa I'm not
we're almost there here we are oh they miss me every every every single person is my enemy
what no what happened okay so close we are so close we're so close 13 all right we just need
to sleep drink maple syrup and get out oh my fucking god what are you talking about 99 percent
are you drunk this will take me into the end of this I gotta pee all right here we go it's
sundown here it is let's go bingo sell the weed stream ends in t minus five minutes oh the countdown
just started got it dude why am I glued to this I've got it I'm like holding it in the air here
we go it's turning into nightfall it's time to sell this and then I will be done game can end
and I'll see you in a few days over this weekend what's today Wednesday Thursday Saturday Sunday
Saturday yeah I'll see you Saturday turn the fucking lights off turn the fucking lights off
what lights like in my room I just remember like whatever xqc plays a scary game everyone just
spams lights off with a mad face and then he goes and turns them off it's I love it where is everybody
what time is it here we go lights off lights off and then he comes back and sits down all right it's
nightfall where is everybody I'm not gonna die right do you have any maple syrup over here where
is everybody I'm just trying to sell one pack of weed 30 seconds until the stream ends I need to
drink something maybe they'll spawn if I turn around and come back it's it's too early it's
sundown right it's only 7 p.m. what time do they come out all right there we go now it's nightfall
are they actually not here yet I need to eat or drink something right now or I'm gonna die
snack shack still open please be please still be open thank god you don't have you don't have
maple syrup here oh no no no no no you do over here at the gas station the gas station closed
please be open oh my god I'm gonna die please before I die just sell this one weed it's okay
it's literally nighttime it is nighttime crickets are chirping I can hear crickets
where are they it's crickets are chirping literally I'm gonna die okay I'm done I'm done
I'm done thanks for watching did you sell a single weed no I died died I'm apparently they
don't start street racing I don't know when they start it just said nighttime I don't know
nighttime is that seven eight nine ten o'clock it was seven eight nine good night guys I'll see you
later this was a wild one it was a lot of fun though I will see you guys on Saturday we're
gonna do iron lung thanks for putting up with my bullshit as always I'll see you guys soon
take care of yourselves have a great night make sure you get some good sleep eat some good food
call your mother you know have a wonderful rest of your evening and thanks for the subs too
obviously I got class in four hours oh I hope you get some sleep yeah Saturday four o'clock
pacific I gotta go figure out what I'm gonna do for food I made curry earlier while watching
I'm very jealous that sounds incredible yeah good night guys see you later