What's happening? Hey, I'm back on my part two of three of times where I'm going to disappear for like two and a half weeks, or one week or whatever. Ten days.
That was the second time in the last two months. There's gonna be one more.
Not right now though, don't worry. Got a couple weeks here of just chillin'.
Saints Row, yeah. Saints Row. You gotta pre-stream chat, guys. Pre-stream chat. I would start participating.
They hold a lot of power. Let me break it down.
Every time there's a stream, let's say a stream is scheduled for two o'clock.
Or four o'clock, whatever. Somewhere around like one to three p.m. I will come in here.
And I'll say, hey, what's up, guys? How are you? What's going on, everybody?
And we'll go, Jerma! Oh, Jerma, what's up, man? Oh my god, he's here! Oh my god, I'm such a huge fan.
Nobody says anything else negative or anything like that.
They're always very supportive. They never tell me to leave every time.
I don't see, in all capitals, leave anytime I write a message, which I don't get that, by the way.
Every time I've talked in the pre-stream chat, everybody just says leave at the same time.
Hey, this is my chat here, okay? If I want to poke in... Look, this is my house.
We literally did that today. Yeah, you do it every day.
Regardless of the mean nature of some of the pre-stream chat, we talk.
I kind of chill in the pre-stream for like 10 to 20 minutes, usually.
Well, I say that I write like three messages, but I'm there watching.
I put a poll up. Here's three or four games that I want to play.
Which one do you guys want to see?
So let me tell you what the non pre-stream chat viewers have missed out on.
They voted today for Saints Row 3.
There was Chivalry 2 was on that list. It got three votes.
I'm not making that up.
Out of, I think, one, maybe I think like two or three hundred people in pre-stream.
I think three people clicked Chivalry 2. I was very surprised.
I mean, I'm probably going to play at some point.
What's this emote? Germa cheesed. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know what it is. I can't even see it.
What is it? I just see the text. I don't know why I can't see it.
What does it look like?
You uploaded it. I did not.
I have given my mods complete and total creative control for every single emote on BTTV.
I don't even know what they are.
You personally uploaded it.
But I've been away for a while working on stuff, doing some personal life things.
I'm sure some of you guys have seen the picture of me, what it looks like officiating a wedding.
I don't know where that photo is from. I'm going to. I didn't do that.
Very strange. Somebody. I mean, I got Photoshopped into that somehow.
People called me. People calling me priest Andy.
No, Community Jake got married. And that's kind of where it was.
I officiated Community Jake's wedding, which is crazy, right?
I've never done that before, but it was a beautiful ceremony.
Two really great people. So I was more than happy to.
No, I'm not. I'm not ordained.
Hey, I just want to ask, dude, what's wrong with you? Love the streams, by the way.
That's a loaded question. How do I answer that in five seconds?
Actually, I can. No, I could. I could answer that.
What's wrong? I ate Captain Crunch every day for like breakfast, lunch and dinner for about four straight years when I was a kid.
There you go. This is your answer.
I'm in. I'm a bell. I'm embellishing.
I did not have it. I'm kidding.
And only for I would say probably like a year or two years.
I ate Captain Crunch every single day. It's got vitamins in it.
That's not the only thing I ate.
People take the things I say here when I'm fucking around and they act like, Holy shit.
Of course, he's a weird guy. He ate Captain Crunch for breakfast, lunch and dinner. Nobody would do that.
Nobody. I'm kidding. Who would do that?
This dude has a lack of neurons now. I do not have a lack of neurons.
Yeah. OK. OK. Lack of. Oh, he's got a lack of neurons.
He's killing. Oh, he killed all his brain cells by eating Captain Crunch.
How many times a week do you smoke weed? Yeah. Yeah. OK.
Don't don't come at me on the high road here. None. I don't do that.
Some of you do. This is PR. He's projecting, projecting on Megalo.
You're a bad influence. I really hope not.
Look, what the fuck is this emote?
I'm looking at the mod chat right now. This is what that is.
Who allowed that? Who allowed that? That shouldn't be allowed.
That's a horrible looking. Eat human, eat human food.
Guys, I eat plenty of greens, plenty of vegetables.
I have a pretty balanced diet.
I try to I try to eat not too much meat, but enough meat because I like I like meat.
Try to balance it out a little bit. Yeah, it's good to see you again.
I'll be back the next couple of weeks. I'll be here pretty normally.
Two, three times a week like you're used to.
Then, oh, we've got the German Baseball Association, which is I'm very excited about that.
And then we've got we've got the green screen stream, ladies and gentlemen, the green screen stream.
Thank you for all of your submissions.
There were thousands of submissions.
There's no way I'm going to be able to do them all.
They've been narrowed down to a a doable amount.
Had to narrow down thousands of these submissions.
So on June 30th, mark that on your calendar.
I will be in front of the green screen doing all of your favorite all of your favorite actions.
Also, something else really cool on the 27th.
So in two days from now, Miss Kip is running a smite tournament, a one hundred thousand dollar tournament.
I am a team captain. I am a team captain for this tournament.
Who's on the team? The team is.
OK, here we go. Me, Poke Lulz, Russell.
Sure for. And then the final contestant is NoCo with our coach being weakened.
This is going to be a good fucking team.
These are going to be cringe, Andy. I didn't even do anything.
Just watch just watch us just roll over the competition. OK.
Have you guys practiced? Not once.
I, as team captain, have called for a practice.
I wrote a I literally wrote a paragraph and nobody responded.
I think we're going to hopefully get together at least.
Look, can we type practice? Right.
I wonder if that would work. Is typing practice?
What? OK, in in a in a discord group, right?
Just kind of be like, all right, so you go down that way.
You got out. Well, do we have to actually do it?
I think most people in the competition, I don't think I don't know if there's very many people that are really amazing at the game.
I don't I don't know. I know what some of the teams by now.
There's a lot of people involved. I mean, I think we've got a pretty good shot.
Have you guys seen? Have you guys seen my Anubis?
You guys have watched me not miss a single mummify.
I'm telling you right. This picks and bans.
They let me get Anubis. It's fucking over.
It's over. I don't know what their plan is to broadcast.
I think I'm sure there'll be people probably commenting it.
I don't know. Should be really fun. Sounds like a fun team.
Who else was I good at? I remember those.
You don't know that Anubis got nerfed. That doesn't matter.
I could be the worst God in the game and I'd still do all right with it.
You're Anubis. Guys, it's this is all psychological.
OK, if everybody thinks that I'm really fucking good with this character, then they're going to freak out.
Just shut up. I have a plan.
You don't understand the psychology here.
The more I talk about Anubis, they're going to fucking ban Anubis.
And who gives a shit? That character sucks.
Do you get it? Are you understanding this now?
Can you please just relax and let me do what I'm doing as a team captain?
For God's sakes, would you let me do what I'm doing as a team captain?
Quiet enough. I don't want you to screw this up for me.
And then good. Look, all you guys are going to go to the other teams.
He's actually the Anubis thing is a joke.
And then they won't ban Anubis.
And then I get like 20 kills in one game with Anubis.
It's all psychology. I'm glad you guys get it.
He wants the money.
I just want to I think I thought it was a fun idea.
All right, you guys ready? Let's get going.
It's good to see everybody. Hope you're all doing well.
Did I tweet? I did. He wants the money.
So this is Saints Row 3.
I have never played Saints Row 3, just like when it was Saints Row 2.
I think maybe I was in the menu.
Maybe I went to the first area. I don't know.
I don't have any memory of playing it.
But there's your plan for the week.
We got bang Saints Row 3 tonight.
27th Smite hundred thousand dollar tournament, which we are guaranteed to win.
And then the 30th green screen.
Let's go. Stacked fucking week. Stacked week.
OK, let's go. Saints Row.
Can you hear it? We can now.
Can you see me?
You know, I guess notice I've been doing face cam every single day now.
That's complete. That's unheard of.
Can you guys remember a time when I ever did this?
And I don't even know why I'm doing it. You know what I mean?
I don't even know why I started doing this.
It just I just sort of started doing this.
Right. I was a no face cam guy forever for almost 10 straight years.
And then I played Elden Ring and kept the face cam on.
And now it's just on permanently.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't even want this on.
I don't want this on. And I'm going to turn it off immediately if I get if I feel like it.
The second that I don't care anymore, it's going off like I'm a weirdo.
Whatever. All right, let's go. New campaign.
Normal. We're not playing hardcore.
How is it? Is it loud? How loud is it?
That looks fine. 60.
All right. Quiet. Here comes the opening cutscene.
Quiet. This game has DMCA songs.
I don't I don't even care.
I'm sorry. I just don't anymore.
Conquest. That's what we're playing, by the way, in the Smite one hundred thousand dollar tournament.
It's Conquest 5v5.
We're not doing an arena. I haven't played Conquest in five years at least.
We're going to lose.
If I play mage and I do mid, I'm going to miss every rotation.
I'm probably going to go 0 and 15 or something.
No, I don't think so. I think I'll be all right.
Dude, you suck at Smite.
No, I don't.
I don't suck at Smite.
Okay.
Loading into a game that you haven't loaded for two or three straight years
and you jump into Conquest when the meta has changed completely is you can't.
It's not just like getting back in there and just, oh, yeah, I'm going to go 10 and 0.
No matter what, that's not going to happen. You're going to lose.
I stream the game one fucking time and get my ass kicked by a bunch of other people that we're playing every day.
I'll be just fine.
What about the lore? Energy drink?
Can I do that? What?
Oh, it's an ad. Okay.
Japanese commercials. Easiest money you'll ever make.
Grand Lawson is right up there. You ready for this?
Is this 30 FPS?
I do my own stunts.
Hey, you're just a ride along, man.
What the hell?
I am a method actor.
If I'm going to play a saint with any degree of emotional truth, I got to make it real.
Is this 30 FPS?
It'll be real.
You're robbing a bank dressed like yourselves.
Hell yeah. Who doesn't want to be Johnny yet?
Ultra postmodernism.
Who cares if it's 30 FPS?
But do we really got to drag this asshole actor around?
Cut Josh some slack. He's just researching his part.
I hope he signed a waiver.
Alright, people.
But he died.
Sorry, jumps his line. Can we go again?
You all know the drill.
This game came out in the 60s. No, it didn't.
What are you talking about?
Can I get a picture with the boss?
Say sleaze.
Get in line, bitch.
Hey, don't be a dick.
Do you call yourself gang bangers?
You're a bunch of pussies.
We should be all up in there shit like fuck.
I don't know. That's different.
This game is older than you. It is not.
We're just shooting all these words to me.
Wait, it's time to play?
Is it time to play?
Okay, now it's 60 FPS.
What's happening?
I thought that was a fucking person.
The one thing that I shoot at.
I have it on ultra graphics, by the way.
Let's find that bomb.
Can I switch between people?
Alright, where do I go?
Is there a melee? What's melee?
We can't go in? Alright, let's go.
What's melee?
Okay.
Is there screen shake?
It's not really.
It's barely screen shake.
The audio sounds weird to me.
I gotta change the audio.
The audio sounds weird, right?
You know what I was trying to do.
Audio shake.
How do you sprint?
Alright, go upstairs.
Shift? I got a controller. How do I do it?
Left bumper?
No. It's already way too big.
Why are you not playing the remaster?
I didn't even know the remaster existed.
There's a remaster for Saints Row 3?
Is there really?
I didn't know.
Why the fuck would I know this?
Alright, let's go.
What just happened?
Where's my weapon wheel? Give me the weapon wheel.
Alright, let's go.
Let's move, move, move.
Am I signing an autograph?
Why the hell am I signing an autograph?
Make the head part of your face cam bigger.
No! We're gonna take these masks off in like 10 seconds.
Zoom your face in.
Alright, chopper.
Now what an idiot. He pressed the alarm button.
Now what?
Alright, BLS.
Oh, okay, yeah.
What is this? Alright, let's defend.
How do I crouch? Left stick, I think, right?
Why would you do that?
This is a huge open area. Why would you do that?
That was completely and absolutely unnecessary.
No reason to do that.
But wait, come here.
Come on. I forgot how ugly this game is.
Does this game really actually have a remake?
What was it called?
Yes, it does.
Saints Row the Third Remaster.
It's trash.
Oh my god.
Do I even fit in health?
The remaster is actually bad.
Is it really?
Pick up the shield. I'm out.
I'm out of bullets.
I don't think I can die in this.
I literally can't die. I'm being lit up by a Gatling gun on a helicopter.
Minus two, what?
I can't die.
It's just minor graphic improvements.
Germania? What are you talking about?
I haven't announced any wrestling stuff.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Is the game volume too high or too low?
Too low.
Crank it.
You would not want to be firing.
What's happening?
Better? Alright.
Fucking crank it.
What?
What the fuck is happening?
This feels like a mobile game ad.
Crank it.
Not bad.
Which by the way, I gotta do the mobile game stream.
I was talking about that for a long time and I never did it.
We gotta do it.
We have to do it.
Is it weird that I want to buy a completely new iPad?
Because I feel like it's not going to ever work ever again.
Where we just play all the games that you get ads for.
All the mobile games you get ads for.
Play them all.
And spend at least an hour in each one.
Or at least 20 minutes at least in each one.
I need to get a burner iPad for that.
Get a burner iPad.
Just emulate it?
What?
You can actually emulate it?
Alright, there we go.
You can get an Android OS emulator.
Really?
I didn't know that. That's cool.
Alright, let's customize the character now.
Here we go.
We're making the McRiddler.
If I can.
That doesn't look old.
That just looks kind of dehydrated.
This is before the glass of water.
And this is after the glass of water.
Sex appeal?
Okay, that's a dick.
You can just give the guy a huge dick.
I thought it was going to make me like handsome.
I didn't know that's what that was.
Okay.
That's fine.
Build.
I'm going to try to make the McRiddler if I can.
Can I not?
Is there an advanced mode?
Oh yeah, that's right. I used hacks last time.
Oh no, I actually used hacks.
Fuck.
I did use hacks last time.
Damn it.
Oh, I can't do it. I don't have the hacks.
It's alright.
How hard is it to get the hacks?
Do they exist?
Scroll down on the skins.
You can make your guy made out of emerald?
I kind of want to do that.
Okay, that's whatever.
I'm going to get so sick of this though.
He's a Minecraft diamond.
That's fucking hilarious.
Minecraft diamond.
Without the sliders,
I didn't think they were going to exist for this game.
Make him Mr. Emerald.
No, he's Minecraft diamond.
Mr. Green?
No, he's not Mr. Green.
I know what Mr. Green looks like.
I wonder how he's doing.
I wonder if we'll ever see him again.
In person.
I wonder if we'll ever see him
in person doing something.
I don't know. Maybe not.
It depends on what Mr. Green is up to.
Alright, let's do the ears.
This is just the Silver Surfer.
What did the Silver Surfer do?
What was his thing?
He came in and marked the planets.
For the big guy to eat.
Isn't that what it was?
Not wrong? That's what it was, right?
Whoa, what the fuck? I thought I hit accept.
My friend Joe is playing
Saints Row 3 right now. Can you say hi to him?
What's up, Joe?
This is going to get so irritating. You know what it is.
I don't know. Why do I feel like this is
popping up and asking me
a wish and I said, I want to be the most strong
super powered man in history.
You go like this and I would turn into that.
Like this would be what I turned into.
This dude's made out of resin.
Yeah, this guy's just going to lie down
on a wooden table.
Oh nice. Nice, dude.
Whoa, you can put their whole face up
or down? Resin.
Don't act like you have not fallen
asleep to resin poor videos.
Come on, dude. Really?
Don't act like you're better than the rest of us.
I want to have a really big mouth.
Okay, I like that better.
What's going on with his mouth?
Alright, I'm happy with it.
Let's suck the chin up though. Let's get like a
really fucking big turkey neck.
Alright, I'm happy with it. I'm not happy with the eyes
though. Getting there.
Getting there. Definitely getting there now.
I just don't care.
Oh my goodness. Okay.
Whoa.
Alright, maybe. Maybe.
Yeah, it's Dr. Manhattan's fucking
stepbrother.
Resin poor. No, not resin
porn. Resin poor.
I don't know if the hair is not doing it for me.
That's too easy though.
Should I just be bald?
I kind of like this.
Should I have like contrasting
hair? Or should I just be
No, not the German colors.
I don't know. What do you think? Make it
your hair color. I guess that
is kind of weird. Yeah, it is
weird. These kind of characters
never have facial hair.
They never have beards, right? Ever.
Can I make? You can't even see it.
I want a big beard.
Imagine Dr. Manhattan
with a goatee. It just doesn't
fucking work. It does not work.
Porn stash. You can't even see
it. Alright, what about if I do this?
I can't even see it. Hold on. This one's the most
full, but I need to do it. Okay, can we see it if we
change the color?
Doesn't it kind of look like he
painted his home with marker? It just
looks slightly more oiled.
It's just spray paint. Yeah, it's just spray paint.
Wait. Oh, that one
shows up. That looks like shit,
though. That looks awful. I
don't like this at all. I really don't like it.
I can't even see it. It doesn't matter.
You can't see this either.
Hold on. I don't hate it.
He looks like a fucking pro wrestler.
Turn the reflection off on the skin.
Dude, do you guys really care that much? I'm going to play this
for like five hours and never
install it ever again. Does it really matter?
Yeah, without, without.
I kind of like the glistening kind of
like car oil.
Yeah. Personality.
There's a McGriddler. No.
No. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope.
No. No. No. Fuck that.
No. It's so easy.
This is the funny thing that everybody does.
This is the funny one.
No.
I don't
God damn it.
do it. Can I change it later?
Can I go back and change this if I want to?
I can. Fine.
I hate it already. I do this shit
all the time.
I will just be walking around my house and I'll just start
doing this. I swear to ask Holly.
I swear to God. Like I
do that. No. Not that.
No. Nope.
No. No.
I do that too.
We're just gonna do that.
I hate this character.
What's this character's name? I forget.
Resin? Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. I'm excited. Okay. Yeah. This is it, right?
Resin table.
Resin four. That's his name.
I'm gonna turn it off now.
It's stupid. It's not even funny.
This was funny like 10 years ago.
to us. Burke's right. We traded our dicks in for pussies. Seriously, movie deals, commercials.
This is going to be the every single cutscene.
No, it's oh my god. It's always about the money, Mr. Gat, which is precisely why our employer
wishes to speak with you. If you'll indulge us. Sounds like you know it actually doesn't.
That's a tuber joke. Of course, a remarkable likeness. These visions are viola and kiki
and I am Philippe Laurent, chairman of a multinational organization called the
Taz impression.
I wonder why my foot's not up your ass at this point. Like it or not, Mr. Gat, our organization is expanding into still water. I am offering you the chance to leverage your assets against your lives. Ladies.
Worst dream 2022 because you don't like the zombie voice. Come on, relax.
No, it sucks.
What? No, you're going to get us all sucked out of the plane.
I can take them. What about the plane? I'll fly it back to still water.
I definitely can't even change it. What a mistake. Details. Details. Just cover the boss. Go. I got this.
Yes, that's right. Resin pour. Dr. Manhattan's step brother with the power of costing fifteen thousand dollars.
That's it. Attention passengers. This is your new captain speaking. Our updated flight plan has us
landed in still water. I'd like to remind all passengers to remain screen shake. Ah, fuck this fucking screen shake.
Here's some relaxing music for your enjoyment. Wait. Oh, let's go do it. There's all this fucking screen shake.
Find a parachute. All right, let's go. There's so many people. What are these people doing?
This fucking sensitivity is so low. God damn. What the fuck is going on? I don't have any guns.
What? Nice Minecraft aim. Dude, I'm. I'm holding. Look, I am holding down right now.
Holding up. It's like pitching an airplane. Let's go. Resin hands.
I love how he goes off camera for cutscenes like any of us care. Yeah. Well, I don't know. I'm just
used to doing it. What the fuck? This is so stupid. Flip. Flip. Flip. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload.
How can I go faster? Oh shit. That hurt. Can I get hurt? All right. That hurts. What is going on?
Got you. I can't change it. It's over. Oh, man. Why the fuck did I listen to the
10 people telling me to do that? What's going on? Do I have to do something?
Am I supposed to press a button? Dude, what the fuck? What? That guy's just going to die.
Oh, no, they're not. What is this guy doing? Skip the cutscenes. This whole thing is a cutscene.
It's the tutorial at the beginning of the game, man. This is the original, I think. I actually
have no idea. I just bought Saints Row the third. That's it. I didn't know anything else.
I wasn't looking for a remaster. I didn't think they were going to remaster this game.
We're falling for a really long time. Don't you only really fall when you skydive 30 seconds or
something? Don't you only fall for 20 seconds? No. Three minutes? Why do I feel like
you just get sucked to the ground wicked fast? Are you on drugs? How high do you jump out of a plane?
And the Saints are not welcome. When you skydive. I don't know. How high do you go?
14,000 feet? And leave them nothing. Not as high as you are right now. I am sober.
Sober. Oh, there's a phone. Okay. Stop leaving. We don't care about the cutscenes. Try to skip
the cutscenes. But I'm not going to know what's going on. All right, let's go.
Steal a car. How do I put the gun away? Don't skip cutscenes.
Steal part. It's kind of like Bangkok's abusive father. Access cell phone map.
Oh my fucking god. Get rid of it now. Okay. So this wants me to go see the GPS. Set the GPS to the
what over here. Okay. Set GPS. Sounds good. Let's go.
I feel like that should not have. Look, where the fuck are we going?
What the fuck? That wasn't even a road.
It has GPS, right? Check your map. I think you can get Luigi. Okay, you can actually get Luigi.
Jump or dive. Yeah, we raid the guard armory. What the fuck was that?
You can't be serious. Oh my god. Shut it off. How do I get rid of it?
Oh, a shitty idea. I thought this lady farted.
Like I scared the shit out of her.
I was like, what? I thought she farted. I really, I honestly thought she farted.
I was like, okay, it's like a comedy thing. When you publicize their car, they like shit their
pants. I don't know. I've never played this one. Can you get in trouble in this game?
I don't think I can get in trouble. All right, I made it. Go to the plastic surgeon.
All right, we have to get through this tutorial first. Purchase weapon upgrade.
Car crash is funny. That, I guess I'll have to buy the upgrade, right? Okay. Level one. Purchase a
weapon upgrade. Is there a way to do that? Buy upgrade weapons. This one. Level two.
I have a hundred dollars. What? Oh, okay. All right, go to the guard armory.
Where's the car? Holy shit. What's sprint? There's money all over the ground. R3 for melee.
Like some hellish children's book, the sky has fallen in Steelport.
10 people are dead after several cars are running out of the sky, crushing an apartment building in
a fiery blaze. Dozens of bodies, along with a number of crates of vehicles, filled the streets nearby.
Family guy. Car stereos and sex dolls seems to be... Wait, is that it? I don't have any money.
What's on fire? What? That's our car? Is she dead? No, you're fine. I can't lose on the tutorial.
We're good. All right, follow me. I didn't want to. I didn't want to do that. I thought I was.
Whatever. I'm trying to. How do you sprint? Oh my fucking God. Now what? Left bumper? All right.
Do I have enough to change the voice? All right. Change voice. Oh, come on, dude. Really? All right.
I know what it looks like now, though. Get off. All right. Get on. Let's move.
How come I can't hear any acceleration sounds? That's what's weird to me.
There's no... We're just floating. It's an electric motor. You're so slow. What?
I'm not looking over here anymore because I just drive into shit. Stop. Let me do what I'm going to
do. Okay. Let's go. Don't worry. Pierce has that covered. Kill the guards. Go.
Get better aim. Can I fight? I need to... All right. Just get off. I got it. Red barrel. Got it.
I shot up a hundred times. Oh my God. This gun sucks. This gun sucks. Excuse me? All right.
Weapons. This gun is awful. This one's not. I'm sorry. I'm keyboard turning right now. I'm sorry.
Holy shit. That was cool. The McShitter.
UAV drone controls over here. It's making me... Is it anybody else getting angry?
It's kind of angering, isn't it? Oh my God. There's so many people. What? Do I have a grenade
or anything? This is too many people here. Oh my God. There's way too many people.
What the fuck? Help. Help. Help. I need to get up. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help.
I'm down. Use the what? Dude, I can't even... No. Half the sound effects are missing.
All right. Where's this thing you're talking about? Did you pirate the game?
No. I didn't pirate the goddamn game. Do I just have to hold position?
Something's missing. It's weird. Something is missing from the fucking game.
I'm getting pissed. Oh my fucking God. Why are there a million people in here?
There's no music and I feel like half the sound effects don't work.
Buy the remaster. Somebody say the remaster sucks. See, yeah, this wasn't here before.
Pull it up. Oh, fuck. It's all right. It's all right. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Oh my fucking God. Holy shit, man. What the fuck is this game?
How many people are here? There's too many people here. I just have seen that.
Way too many people here witnessed that. I'm trying to kill the helicopters. Nice. Got him.
Not dead. He'll be in a minute. This dude's doing CBD injections anymore. All right. Let's go. Let's
go. Go, go, go, go, go, go. This dude's fucking scrunked. There's way too many helicopters flying
too close. I just moaned. I could feel it. I actually, I know I just moaned. I know I did.
I did. How many helicopters do we have to shoot at? There's been more helicopters than people.
All right, let's go. Just go play iPad games instead. Dude, you're having the nightmare
stream where you expose yourself. We're like, stand up and this is naked. This is shit. This
is how it started. Let us take care of business. I'm doing this for Johnny.
You're worried about real estate? We have guns. Let's use them.
All right. I got money. Who is he talking to? I'm streaming. I need to quit the game and then
disable and enable v-sync in the Nvidia control panel. Stand up. No, I can't. I can't. I can't. I
can't do it. I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't do it because everyone knows me from here up
and I look professional. I look like I'm well done. I look well made. All right.
When I stand up, that illusion goes away because I'm wearing, because I'm wearing the fucking
goddamn, I'm wearing the fucking Super Mario pajama pants again. All right.
Is that what you wanted to see? Oh no, it happened. Oh no, it happened.
I have a new chair though. This thing's fucking really good.
This is a Herman Miller chair. They actually, they sent it to me.
Oh my God. My whole fucking life is changing. How many unlockables did I get?
What? This TF2 stuff in this game? Yeah. There's like 10 different adjustable knobs on this thing.
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. Okay.
Hey. Okay. Enough slices. Don't yell. I'm sorry. All right. Let's go.
All right. Weird science. He's got a pirated copy. That's all DLC. Oh, did I buy the DLC pack?
All right. Let's go. Game is now open. Really? Is there a casino in this game?
All right. Where do I want to go? Where was that? That there it is. It's so far away.
Do these exist in all the little sections of the city? There's probably another one over here,
right? Unknown. Which one is it? Those that are played this game a lot because these are all
unknown. Bottom one, like right here. I'll check this one. That one. Go to the strip club.
Why would you do that? All right. That's a gun place. Is it this one? Check this one too.
The top center. I thought you guys said it was the bottom one.
Nope. Car place. Whatever. I'm sure I'll get up there eventually.
Go to the strip club and turn on face cam.
With your steel board breaking news. What? That's basically why would it mean to turn on the face
cam? Stronger. You said you needed me. All right. So what's this one? Do the ipads for the ipads
room is going to take a while to set up. I got to get like 50 games. This is DLC. Oh, only do face cam.
I see they failed you Johnny. Never will. Number one fan for months. I've been cut sunglasses.
I thought I had had enough things that he touched.
He's trying to make a clone. You cloned Gat? Yeah. That just took me by surprise. I forgot
that was a person in the game. I was like, who the fuck is that guy?
Okay. Robot chicken. Do I have enough firepower to do this? Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, slow down. Yeah, but you knew we had to take on the center.
A clone of Gat ain't gonna know that. Is it like a giant version of? Okay.
Change the voice? I mean, I'm so far away from it.
Okay. The next time I come across one, I will change it. I promise.
Do you look crusty today? I'd rather be fucking crusty than soggy and like wilted.
All right. So where is he? Oh, he's narrating this whole thing.
Interrogate. Oh, get in. All right. Come here. How do I interrogate?
What the hell do you want? Is your favorite food chicken? Oh, that's one of them.
Better find Gat before these guys do. I was like, why did my voice change?
I thought that was me talking. Okay.
Why am I still holding this person? Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump.
All right, let's go. I feel like I'm watching someone else watch someone play this game.
Why? This is like a weird feeling I'm having. I feel like I'm not playing. I'm like watching
someone else play. Does that make any sense? I don't know what it is with this game.
Why Saints Row 3? I didn't feel that way in Saints Row 2. I think I'm watching someone play the game.
Oh, no. I'm just saying it's like, I feel like I haven't played the game yet. Does that make
any sense? It's probably the camera. It's not the camera shake. I can't lose. All right. Where is he?
Screaming his name and something about stripper poles and then started
trashing the place. People panicked and he ran off. Okay. Why don't, what are you, what?
We were not supposed to kill him. All right. What is going on here? Get the fuck away from me.
Get this guy. I thought we were supposed to kill this guy. I didn't do that. Okay.
Okay. Grenade. Grenade out. Oh, be careful. I love the crow hop. This is DLC.
Okay. Somebody said, dude, I wish somebody in chat would let me know if this was DLC or not.
Okay. Where's Jimmy? All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's get out. Out, out, out. Turn around,
turn around. Get behind me. Shoot, shoot. All right. Let's go.
What the fuck are you doing? Hey, dude. Come on, man. When the fucking Uber pulls up,
you don't, come on. Don't, don't, now don't text me and say, hey, where are you, man? I'm looking
for you. You drove right by me. I have the GPS thing right there. I'm not, I don't want to walk
a half mile to go find you now. Oh, this is a rocket launcher. All right. What is this person
doing? I don't have to even shoot at them. They're just going to, what is it? Is it a monster?
What the fuck was that? I thought he was going to be way bigger. Is it weird that I'm not intimidated
at all? I thought he was going to be five times bigger. Protect the car. All right.
Discovering shortcuts, update your GPS. Okay. Oh, stop, stop. What, what, what? There's too many
rockets. This game feels like a fever dream. I'll tell you, I feel like I haven't played the game.
Am I out of ammo? No. I feel like somebody is describing Saints Row 3 to me right now.
And I'm like imagining what you're describing. Like I'm sitting there listening to you be like,
yeah, man, so we're in the car. Uh, one of the missions you drive around and shoot the rocket
launcher and stuff. It's fucking Saints Row. And I'm just sitting there going, okay, I'm picturing
that what that is. Don't play the deal. Well, this was in the beginning of the game too. I feel like
I've been hanging out of a window for an hour, an hour and 20 minutes. Oh, this car is going to
explode. There's so many things. What the fuck is happening, man? No, no, this is the real long play
that the world is doing to me right now. See, I'm going to wake up. I'm going to wake up and I'm
going to be in the chair and I'm going to have the controller in my hand. I'm going to be playing
Saints Row 3. Be like, oh shit. Oh my God. Okay. No, I was, I was sleeping. I was asleep. I was
weird. What a weird dream. I'm going to look down and then my dick is going to be out. I'm going to
be like, what the fuck? No, no, no, no, no, this can't be real. And I'm going to look over a chat
and everyone's going to be screaming that I did it. This was the long dream. This was the long con
that my dream was pulling. Do you imagine me just sitting here sleeping? I'm just sitting here like,
but that means I would have had to have turned the stream on, right? Wait, did I not? What about the,
I got a lot of money. Okay. I got money. Let's get health regen. Let's do abilities,
do welding, notoriety. I like that. We'll do sprint. These all cost money. Okay. Hold on.
I got two grand. Okay. So missions. So this, so this is DLC, right? So which one of these is just
story mission? Go to your weapons and outfits. This is like a garage. Okay. So it's all DLC.
All right. So, so I just want to do like the next mission. Okay. Wardrobe. Oh my God.
It'll be Darth Vader. Oh my God. I, this one's great. I'll put the heavy mask on only for a
little bit though. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. Do I get cars? What the hell? What? I just
get this at the beginning. Oh my God. Really? All right. Well, I want this thing. Chainstay. All
right. So now let's go. I look like one of the worms from like Worms Armageddon. Gang operations.
Oh shit. Do I have a grenade? This is the fucking dickhead that just sits over here that you find
in the online game and he's dressed like this. He has like $500 worth of in-game currency
and you can't even hurt this guy. Oh shit. Somebody got to him. GTA hacker.
You know, like a UFO is just going to spawn up there. What? I just got on it.
What the hell is going on? Um, okay. Why is this fucking Fortnite? What's going on here?
Fuck is going on? What? Why does this person have this ultra move? You got to keep up grandpa.
Now this is, this is where this guy goes. Fucking goddamn online store. 500 gems. 29.99. Checkout.
Checkout. Password. Accepted. Thank you. Your purchase is complete. Ammo. Guns. Rocket launcher.
Full ammo. All right. I want to, let's, let's do something. That's John from Delocated. That's
John from Delocated. It really is. That's what that was. That was, that was a blast from the past.
Holy shit. All right. So where do I go? What should I do? Should I pick up one of these missions?
How about, uh, all of these DLC? The top is the mission. Okay. Let's do this one. Your character
is looking thick. Why is the helmet coming off? Why was that so brutal for that one guy?
That was unnecessary.
I know about the, I know I got to change the voice. Okay. Look, it's taking me over here.
Is there one on the way? Is this one? Is this it right here? Or is there one closer? I don't think
there's one closer. Let's go to this one. I feel like it's probably this one. Let's move. I was
not gonna, I was just not gonna stop. I don't, I didn't care. I was not stopping. Holding the brake
was going to be too hard. Too much shit. It was, I was too lazy to. All right. So what is, what's up?
This is not, this is not one either. Really? Come on. This one, just go west. I mean, this is the
only one I haven't seen. I'll try this one. This one's close. I need a new car though. This thing's
annoying. Watch out. What's the horn? Sprint and steal to get in faster. Oh, that's true.
You're right. Does this say anything? All right. I'm getting, everyone's, I'm just getting lied to
over and over again. I just, I'm just going to go to the mission. Everyone said that one, that one,
that one, that one, that one, that one, that one, that one, that one. That's probably like two in
the whole map. What a smooth ride. I found one. I didn't want to shoot the gun. I wanted to punch
him. Okay. Voice. Here we go. Yes. We're doing one. Okay. Now everybody will be happy. Why not
three? Cause three is the McGriddler. That's not, I'm not the McGriddler right now. I'm with resin
pour. Somebody give me a car. Okay. Thank you. That'd be so fucked up. Do you imagine seeing
that? If you watch that happen, it's like, Hey, why? Whoa. That is gone already. All right. Let's
do it. Mission time. Oh, right. The title says McGriddler. It's not even accurate. Let's go to
tune it. Let's find a real asshole. All right. We're going to get this tuned up. Shani's taking
this thing. We can't stop. Don't cut me off. We all are, but you're always pissed off. The girl's
not as crazy as you. Don't worry. Keep an eye on it. Long time. He was there when I first joined
the saints. He click baited us. He mellowed with age. Somebody called it too. You really did.
Somebody in prestream said he's going to get to the character creator. Something's going to make
him laugh and he's going to change everything. And I said, no way that happens. You were right.
You were completely right. Yeah. Yeah. You actually got it. Correct. Minecraft David.
That was a good idea, but that was too funny. Come on. Like the guy lies on a lying on the
table on a wooden table. Resin guy joke. I had to do it. I had to. I had to. I don't want to
level up this car. This guy sucks. That's all I'm doing. Got some more style. Now it's our turn.
Hey, the planet saints. I don't know, man. That's like wearing the band's t-shirt to the concert.
Nothing wrong with wanting to look. I always look good.
Okay. Go to planet. Planet saints. Turn cruise control off to hear the engine. To the streets.
Got me up the cigarette. Is that zip? She's on my feet. To find a reason.
Reason things went wrong. Got to find a reason why my money's all gone. Oh,
no. I could still get high and I can play the guitar like a motherfucking riot.
Yeah. I like this game. You didn't shut up. I do it because I'm the one that can sing in this group.
Life is what you got. Well, you might get run over or you might get shot.
Everyone stop doing this. I'm the singer of the group. That's what I got.
Oh shit. You hit a lady. You hit a lady. You hit a lady. Holy fuck. Oppress that person.
Get that person. He needs to be under arrest. All right. Let's go. What's happening? What am I
doing right now? No. Wait. Give me the engineer head. What's the other? What's the color? What's
the colors for the engineer? It's that. It's brown, right? Yeah. That was correct. Okay. Good. Yep.
And then we need the engineer head. A light. All right. What about gloves? He's got gloves,
right? They're the big bright yellow, right? Yeah. They're huge. Here we go. I don't even need to
change color. They are. No, they're not quite yellow. They're there. That's a pretty, that's
pretty close. This is bad. This is good enough. Who the fuck is this? Is that thing something
pissed off? Okay. I'm an engineer, but that means I solve problems. I solve practical problems
like this. I'm doing my routine. Stop. If that don't work, use a gun. If that don't work,
use more guns. Did I win? I got it. I want to queue up. Why am I shooting at these people?
I want to queue up the TF2 theme song, but alt tabbing this game will break it.
Are these people? This is wrong. I don't know what's happening. Hey, look, bud.
I'm going to do it because why the fuck not? I'm having fun today.
We're just having fun today, you know?
Oh shit. Get him. I'm an engineer. Was that me? Where's the safe house?
No, no, no. Put it down. Put it down. Put it down. Put it down. Put it down. Put it down. Put it
down. Put it down. This is a 2013 video you made. True. True. Where's the fucking safe house?
What? Abandoning who? Where is he?
Save your game. Oh my God. You're right. What am I? Clothes change. Oh, nope. That's my friend.
Throwing grenades. Get in the safe house. I don't need to kill everybody. Get in the safe house,
please. All right. We're safe. Get in here. I'm in the safe house, right? Oh, there we go.
What about autoplay? It's not a six grand. I'll take it. Hey, look, bud. Okay. Well, if we're
going to do this joke, we need to do it with other characters too, because that's what I want to do
today. So that's what we're doing. That's just what's happening. So close, right? How do I change
the color? He has underwear with a big dick. All right. I gotta go back to the store.
New missions available. Cool. Party time. I need to put that backpack on too. Save the game. Yep.
Yep. Mission checkpoints are not saved. That doesn't matter. Okay. We're good. Okay. Let's go to
tattoo parlor. Yeah. I need to buy that backpack. All right. There's probably a closed store
where I'm going, right? There is. There's one on the way. We'll go to this one here.
And the real estate agent will be there, right? Real funny. Oh, that's a nice car.
It's not the one I wanted, but whatever. What's the plan? I want, I want the car in front of me.
The nice one, the one, whatever. Now I'm not going to get it. Right. Pen houses. Psychos. Yeah. I'll
take this one. What's wrong with this car? What's wrong with this car? The tires look fine. There's
no body damage. What's the problem? I'm not breaking there. We're good. Stop using both feet.
Like I'm pressing down both feet onto the, yeah, it's turbo power. That's how you go faster. You
can double the gas. I need to, this is going to kill me. Okay. We're good. Sorry. Okay. I need to
change the colors on this to red and white outfits. Okay. Here we go. What color was this? It was
not this color, but red. If I'm on red team, it was always gray. That's right. It was gray.
That's fine. Okay. Upper body. Where's the thing I'm currently wearing outfits. It's coming up here.
Right. Where is it? No, it's the thing I have on right now. What's it called? Now there it is. I
don't want the witch hat though. How do I change the colors? How do I change colors? I don't want
the hat. Okay. So it's what? Whoa. Yeah. It's white and red. We'll have this just blend in
and then red gloves. Okay. Yeah. Big red gloves. They're huge. What's the biggest ones they got?
These are pretty big. Okay. And then his pants, uh, they're kind of maroon. It's kind of like this.
They're like slacks. Yeah. They're like, kind of like this. It's like a dark, like a brown.
It's like just kind of brownish. That's close enough. Okay. What about the shoes? Boots?
They're just black boots. But everything's fine. They're, they're not, they're kind of,
I'll just make them. It's all right. It's making black. All right. Here we go. I made the medic.
I'm good to go. Hey, there we are. Medic. I thought the game just crashed. Holy shit. Why is
that person on the ground? Emerald skin. All right. Let's do the mission and I will put on.
Yes. Well, this is what's keeping us active today. So I put on voice lines to just put on the
sound effects. Okay. I'm going to put on, I'm going to drop all the sound effects in the game,
every sound effect in this game. And I'm going to put on like gameplay, no commentary, an hour on
dust bowl, put that on in the background, put the music in the background, and then put a bunch of
medic, uh, voice lines. I've just been to play. I think that's what I want to do. Do you remember
why? How come you're not eating pirate's booty on stream? Why would I be doing that? The mods
are just on top of it. This is great. All right. I, I'm going to tell you, this is my first,
this is my first day sitting in this new chair. This is way better than the thing I had before.
All right. So this, so this chair, you can turn a knob and it like, it pushes the kind of spine
support thing into your back. It just like kind of wedges you in. Yeah. It's Herman Miller. I'm not
sponsoring anything. They, I just was in the market for a new chair. And I mean, I guess you
could say this is, I mean, if you want to call it a sponsorship, it wasn't paid to say anything
about it, but I think I got a chair. So that's fucking cool. So yeah, this was, this chair was
provided to me by Herman Miller. If you want me to say that, right. That's kind of what I should be
saying, but it's fucking awesome. They are expensive, but I mean,
you should review cigarettes. They are very, very expensive. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. We're not doing that song. I don't know. We're doing the TF tooth joke. Will that work
here? This is going to fall so flat, I think, but whatever. How flat do you think this is going to
be? Let's find out. Okay. Red medic dust ball gameplay. No commentary. Medic voice lines.
That's just everything here. Let's get it ready. How's that? This is fucking stupid.
Please.
He keeps talking. What? It's a spy.
Everyone's a spy.
Okay, I can't fucking do it anymore. It's too much.
Oh, okay.
That's enough. I think my chest hurts. When he's talking about his head,
push, help me push the point. Oh my God. That's so fucking funny.
Okay. Well, let's get back to this. Yeah. I know can't for that one that the,
I think the bit needs to play out my head, my head. Okay. This is okay. Now this is like,
this is like strange to me now. This is, isn't this a weird now? I feel like I did. I did. I
put on another song. Whatever. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Go, go, go, go, go. Quick.
What am I doing? What the fuck did I do that for? I don't know why I did that. I started
coughing and just did it. My head, my head. Okay. We're good. Back to it.
We need to start Dustbowl again. What a fucking amazing game. It's so good. It's so good.
Right? You know what I mean? They'll never be another team fortress ever. It's impossible.
You know what I think? Here, I can give you a take here. Everybody that thinks that the,
oh my God, half-life, half-life, half-life, half-life, half-life. It's going to be so hard
to make another half-life. No, no, absolutely. Team Fortress 2, they'll like, they'll be,
never be another TF2. It'll be impossible to make TF3. I feel strongly about that versus
Half-Life 3. I think they could do a Half-Life 3 and be fine. I don't think they could do a TF3.
That game was perfect. It was perfect. It was a perfect video game. So now I'm more afraid about
them trying to do TF3 if they ever decide to, right? I mean, what is going on right now?
There's a bass high take. There's the characters, the voice work. It was like this whole world that
they created and they didn't have to do anything. You know what the craziest part about TF2 really
was? There was this overarching kind of storyline, right? But it really lived in the background
and the characters made everything. The characterization of the classes made the,
you kind of got to, hold on, sorry. I'm like, I hear like music. It's like the characters were
the whole thing. You didn't even need a story. And there was just enough overarching stuff in
the background that made it perfect. If I could, okay, okay. I got three wishes. If a Genie came
in front of me and was like, hello, Charma. Good to see you. I'm the Genie and you have three wishes.
I would, okay, here's what I'd wish for. I'd wish for like literally world peace and world hunger.
And make Team Fortress 3 as good as TF2. There you go. Those are my three wishes.
And by the way, release it in like six months.
What the fuck? Where are they? I didn't, look, I'm sorry.
You should wish for more stuff. You can't wish for more wishes. Let's go. Follow what? Did I fail?
No, okay, we're good. I failed? What happened? What the fuck just happened?
What? Oh my God. I can't do a cool action jump. It hurts so bad. All right, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go. Am I calling somebody? Crash your helicopter into him. I thought about it,
but I don't think I can reach him. Oh shit. I'm fine. Everything's fine. I don't care.
I don't care. I don't care. Whatever. Everyone's yelling at me. God, yell at me. I don't care.
I don't care. It's fine. I don't care. No, I don't care. I don't care. People are like,
oh my God, he must care. I don't care at all. I don't care. Go. All right. Don't be an idiot.
I'm just a full throttle. Okay. Now I feel like I'm playing the game, right? Like the last 45
minutes. What are you talking about? I didn't care. Whoa. Shooting shit at me. Okay. So let's go.
He crashed. What? Do I have to land? I'm okay. Come here. Red wire. Whoa. Somebody's phone's
ringing. Let's fire the gun. Did I lose? Oh, not again. The saints aren't going to back down.
Maddie, there's nothing to worry about. My thoughts exactly, Mr. Kilbane. The saints
are no more than a white noise of empty sights. With respect, sir, I'd say empty is no longer
applicable. I forgot that it's in the cut scenes. I completely glazed over that.
Max a fucking psycho. Sound of progress, my friend. Oh, I own this place now. Okay.
A stun gun. Can we, wait a minute. What the saints wear, what vehicles they drive and their taunts.
Are you telling me that I can make a full Team Fortress 2 gang? Do you not even talk? Please
don't tell me that because that's all I care about for the rest of the whole day.
Well, how do I do that? Where do I do that? It's only pre-made costumes? Oh, okay. All right.
Access the crib. Let's find out. Wardrobe. Okay. Gang. Style. Okay. Oh, no, you can't.
No, it's all right. You can't. Oh, well. Oh, well. Oh, well. Okay. It's all right.
I mean, everyone's going to get the dumper though. That's very important. What about their car?
Yep. Yep. Yeah. Maybe I should upgrade some guns. All right. Damage. Bullet damage. I mean,
why not? 5% reduction in damage taken from bullets. 10% reduction in damage when hit by a vehicle.
I got 14 grand. Oh, explosive ammo. Carried 25% more grenades. Yeah. More pistol ammo. More
shotgun. More SMG. Mailing enemies throws them slightly further. Yeah. Yes. Okay. Don't spend
all my money. Bonuses. Hourly city income. 500 bucks. Yeah, I'll take it. Pay cash for 4,000
respect. Okay. Gang abilities. Vehicle delivery. Yep. I like that. You should do mods. Maybe I'll
do like an insane mod day. You know, yeah, let's write that down. I'm going to do just a wacky mod
day where I pick up a few games that have just never ending mods and just ruin them and play
like three or four games. Because, okay, here's the problem. Once you start turning on mods that
are crazy, you're not the games over. You're not playing the game anymore. There's no going back
to like, oh, I'm going to use the pistol and go to do the mission. It's not going to happen anymore.
So you got to give yourself like an hour or two to play in the mod playground and then move on.
So that we'll do it. We'll do a we'll do a cookie mod night. We'll do it soon. Can I parachute off
this? All right. That's pretty cool. Answer cell phone. You're attacking our grip. All right. You
got it. I'm on my way. I didn't even see that. Wait, they're up here. Recreational drugs and
numerous hookers. Now gunfights can be added to that list. Shots were fired in a downtown penthouse
apartment resulting in several deaths. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Oh my God. Give me the car.
Did you actually get in the car? What's up? Put her down. Put her down. Put her down. Put her down.
Put her down. Get out. Get out. What are you doing? What are you doing? Why?
Why? Oh shit. Go. All right. I did the mission, right? We're good. All right. Cool. New mission.
What am I going to do? What am I going to do next? Guardian angel. Let's do this one.
Let's go to the HQ. Hey, I think I'm ready to make a move on the syndicate. What you got in mind?
Get to the crib. You see, this better be worth my time. I said this is boring. I want to watch
you gamble. Oh, I mean, I know a guy that does a lot of gambling. I've got to know him a little
bit over the last few years. Yeah. OK, let's do it. Check it out, boss. What's up? Since this
used to be a syndicate crib, but I poke around and see what they left behind. No one's getting
any more hints. Now shut up. The syndicate will know we have the keys. They'll be waiting for us
to make a move. I guess then you better watch my back. All right, let's go.
Oh, hanging out of the fucking chopper, shooting grenades at people, hanging out of the side of a
fucking window. Why do I have control for that? Just keeping you on your toes. Stop driving into
my missiles. I can't even aim that far. I can't aim that far. Air shot. I got it. I actually got
it. How do I heal your car? Well, drive by them. Your car is fucked up, man. They're blocking the
road up here. Help me out. Where? Well, I stopped flying the helicopter so far. You idiot. I'm going,
Mouse, for this. Your sensitivity is so high. You haven't been touched once. Relax. Come on, move.
Help me out. Stop hiding behind the car. It's just over the bridge. I'll find a place to set up.
Oh, right in the middle. What? Why would you pull up that close? Oh shit, they got
this. I think his mate saw me. Yes. Yes, he did. Oh, we're in a Team Fortress 2 movie today, huh?
Only two grand for that? What the hell? That's kind of bullshit if you ask me. $82 per hour.
Oh, this is... I don't want to do this again. Jeremy, you're good at sniping? Just wait till you see my raw
snipes and the fucking misgive $100,000 smite tournament on the 27th. What happened over here?
What are these people doing? What's wrong with you? Oops. All right, mission. Let's go. This one.
So you're saying it has to be me. Oh, I'll do the selling. You just get my back and I have the
perfect places to hit. I thought you weren't going to play smite anymore. I didn't say that.
I didn't say that. When did I say that? You literally did. What are you talking? So how
do we know where to sell? Let's cut right to the heart of this shit and hit the Morningstar
territory. How do you know where that is? The documents we got with those keys gave up a whole
lot. Smite Thursdays. I like it. What sort of things we have to sell off? I'm driving? No,
he's driving. So we have a bunch of shit drove into a tree as fast as they could. Why?
All right, let's get the deal done. Protect the dealer and the buyer. You got it.
This saint's biography is signed by the whole crew. Give me some pickles and I'll wear anything.
Protected. Let's go. Shoot this fucking guy, please. All right, let's go. New deal. Yeah.
Hold the gun to their head. I don't think that'll work. I'm not driving the car. This car has beat
the fuck up bad. Will you just stop already? Finally. That's another deal. Something wrong
with your eyes. You get out of the car. Haha. Stupid. Don't fuck with the saints. It just
in these universes, I would never want to walk anywhere. It's just driving into people like I'm
not going to. I'm literally not going anywhere. I got to go over there. Oh, he left without paying.
Did we get him? These people are fucking pissing me off. Did I just make them so angry? Wait,
you fucking idiot. You're going to drown them? All right, let's go. All right, take their car.
Haha. Drive. Get us out of here. What are you doing? Where is he going? You're going to get
into melee range. Where is he going? Oh my goodness. I snapped his neck. This is fucking brutal.
Can we can we leave? Can we leave? Just get in the car and let's leave. Okay. I pissed these people
off so bad. They're never going to leave me alone. They're never going to leave me alone.
Is there a reason why you're going 20? You good? I'm just like, I don't even want to be here.
Two grand. Let's go. Six respect. Pretty good. Ban the spammers. Ban the spammers. Ban the spammers.
Ban the spammers. What's next? All right, now let's take over the city. You want to rob some
store? That'll cause more problems than because they'll jump at the chance to sell to us. Nope,
because we already have come again. We take the deed from the lock box. They can't argue.
Call the banners. All right, if I called the banners, would you guys come to my aid? Like,
if I made a World of Warcraft account, I was like, call the banners. I want gold from everybody.
Would it work? No. Yeah, it would. Why wouldn't it? I mean, I'm never going to play World of
Warcraft. Don't worry. Oh my god. This is a nice car. You still did Shadowlands. I literally
installed it. Played it for like a week and didn't do anything. If it was an FPS game,
maybe I would. A whole week? What the hell? Why did they have to do that cutscene?
So, friendly fire? Yep. Best thing is, owning it gives us a discount. It's 100 bucks.
$500 per hour? That's a huge deal. This city's full of businesses and buildings we can snatch
up. The more we take from the syndicate, the better. Right. I thought we were going to need
steel port on our side too. Drop around and see if we got any fancy. All right, I want some new
stuff. Grenades level two. No, it's too much. That's way too much money. What about, is there
any melee weapons I can buy? 27 grand. No way. Mollusk launcher? What do I get that?
I like the shotgun. What is this thing? The shark-o-matic? What are these weird cartoon
guns? These are TF2 guns. I need them. Oh, give me this thing. Yeah. I'll take that.
Buy grenades. Let's go. What do we got in here? You already own the shark one. Do? What the
fuck? What are these? All DLC weapons or something? I already own them. Well,
I'm going to equip them. Why not? Buy ammo. There's only one shot. Okay. Well, I'm kind of concerned.
Let's go. Find the sex doll. Who's talking? Oh, somebody died. Somebody died. Did I just kill
that person? No, that's not fair. That's not fair. They were already dead in the road and I just,
I didn't kill that person. They already were dead in the road. That shouldn't be attributed to me.
I don't, I hate that thing. I don't want that. All right. Find the sex doll.
What the hell is this? Oh, that? A little hobby of mine. Okay. I'm out of here. I don't mean like
that. Collectibles. They're collectible. You're supposed to try and find them all. People collect
some weird shit. Let's get out of here. How do they need to shoot something now? Don't you dare.
I didn't do anything. All right. Estates. I'm so sorry. Rick and Morty. Rick and Morty.
I have a question for all of you guys. For all of you, all you negative Andes.
Negative Andes. I have a question. Did you say go fuck yourself? Okay. Listen. Do you be honest?
I want you to be completely honest with me. Don't lie to me. Don't act like a dick. Just be honest.
Please. Do you, did you think that, I don't know, like, oh, all your friends are watching. So you
have to like make sure you type carefully because all they're going to hear. Did you think that
season one and two in Rick and Morty of Rick and Morty was good? Come on. I want you to be
honest with me. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. Okay. All right. So then so then we can agree, right?
Okay. Right. Up until the up until the Pickle Rick episode is when I liked it. Sounds perfect.
We wipe them off a corner. They'll think twice about coming back. You know what? I really think
it was when that copy pasta was first created. Everybody didn't want to watch the show anymore.
I think that's what it was. I think everybody collectively all went fuck. I think that's what
it was. That one guy ruined everything. Yeah. No, you know what? I think actually, you know what
it was for me? What I think what it was for me was the sauce thing, right? It was like, where's my
sauce? Right. I think that's what it was for me. I remember seeing the sauce thing and I was like,
fuck, fuck. Okay. Can I like this show anymore? I feel like I can't anymore. What the fuck?
What the hell does the weapon do? Good times.
Up to the north. I just what the fuck just happened, man? What happened? I'm so confused.
I don't even know how to play the game anymore. That was never supposed to happen in my life.
That was never a thing that was ever going to happen on screen. I was about to say this
weapon sucks. Okay. The Venture Brothers are good. All the old adult swimming shows were awesome.
I actually I don't really like new adult swim. I know I'm older, right? Am I just older and I
don't care? Or is this with my boomer Andy here? All right. Shark. How do I get the shark to come
up? Where's the shark? Where's the shark? Oh my goodness. What about these little things?
What does it do? What is happening? Ethical. I'm so confused. It makes them your friend.
Oh, I get it. All right. Who's my friend now? Shit. Stop. Can I? All right. I'm going to ethical
that. Come on. How do I revive? Let's do it again. I was so shocked by those those new
abilities that I couldn't play. Okay, so let's go. I was right. So don't swim all over the
city doing deals and shit. I remember Aqua teen. They'll think twice about coming back.
I wasn't a big fan of robot chicken. Not really. Robot chicken to me was just only family guy
cutaways. There was nothing else. It was just the family guy cutaways. And I liked family guy. I
thought I liked family guys like actual stuff they did in the first like six or seven seasons.
But it was that whole show was just a just cutaway jokes. I mean, I just was I was like,
yeah, it's okay. Yeah, the first five to 10 seasons of family guy were they had hit character.
I think they were fun and funny. You see smiling friends. It was fucking hilarious. Oh, yeah.
That's adult swim. But I feel like that's one of the only shows I've seen. I actually like
Come on. It's bugged out. This needed another fucking two years in development.
Yeah, but this should have been in development for two more years. Unbelievable. You know, I mean,
like other cops in the gang cars. Where did they come from? All right, let's go.
You don't look like having fun. Yeah, I'm having fun. What are you talking about?
This game's hilarious. I just I did the first hour of this game. I did not like I will be honest.
I felt like I wasn't even playing a game. Now I'm having this is a great game. I have fun.
I mean, I could I would appreciate it like another year in development, though.
He came up. I killed that guy so bad. He came off the driver's side.
Yeah, the first hour I was like, yeah, but I gave it time. And now I'm having a good time.
I think the game is really fun. Oh, God, is he dead? Oh, shit. This is going to kill him.
Whatever. I'll revive him. Come on. Don't kill me with this shit. Dude, don't even do that.
Get in the car. Get in the car. Get in the car. Get in the car. Get in the car.
Don't kill me, please. I don't want to restart. What is he shooting at? Oh, my God. I would love
to lower my notoriety if my passenger wasn't firing out the window. And there's a jump right
here. And it would be cool. Oh, my. Just get out. Just kill these fucking people following us.
They won't leave us alone. So just get rid of them. OK, let's go. Let's go. Bike. They spawned in.
They actually spawned in. What are you doing? Let's go. Get on the bike. Don't get in your
own car. What are you out of your mind? You idiot. Stop. Get on my whatever. I'm leaving you.
I need to hide. You fucking asshole. Oh, so I was back in Massachusetts, right? Because I'm saying
to be at the wedding stuff and I could tell I was back in Massachusetts. It's been it had been a
while. I was driving and I just hear I'm just sitting there. I pull through red light and I
just hear out the window. You fucking douchebag. Somebody was just screaming at somebody like out
the window. I was like, oh, yep. Oh, I I'm in I'm in Boston again. You passed it. Oh, shit.
Where is he going? It's called not paying any attention to being on complete and total autopilot
while I talk. What do you stop? What do you stop it? What is he doing? What are you doing?
Um, why are you doing that? There's nobody here to shoot at. He's just shooting at random.
All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna dump this guy. Are we hiding? Does this count as hiding?
Not two more. I guess should be two more years in development. Buy grenades.
What can I buy a melee weapon? Doesn't look like it. We're gonna get a melee weapon. You can.
Oh, it's the taser slot. Okay, it's not the actual punching slot.
Cool. Oh, sure. Okay. What would level? Okay.
Can I how do you switch? How do I switch weapons? How does it work? Okay. Okay. It's fun.
All right. So what now? Tank mayhem. You feel like blowing shit up? Go on. I'm all ears. Down the
route. The morning start user to the same. We drop a few pipe bombs under him. Fuck that. I'm saying
we use a tank. This may be the best idea you've ever had. Holy shit. Are you okay?
You need to go get the scout outfit now? Yeah, I do. I knew we needed a break from the team fortress
to joke, right? We can bring it back. Can you like kick? No. TF2 is not a joke. I said the TF2
joke. Not that the game is a joke. Were you listening? Come on, dude. $125,000 in property
damage. Sure. High value targets. Oh, this was in Saints Row 2. Yep. This is loud, by the way. I
realize how loud this just was. Wasn't the trick from Saints Row 2 to shoot fences? The fences
were worth an insane amount, right? No, 31. Okay, 40 combo. All right, I got it. The fences are
still the meta. Okay, good to know. Good to know. Okay, cool. I didn't want to do that.
Professor Genki. You ready to be a star? I thought we already were. Oh, no. What's the
running melee? You've been personally selected for a spot on a game show. You're not trying to
auction me off on some dating thing, are you? Trust me, you'll love this shit. Meet me and I'll
show you. You better be right. Oh, nice car. Nice car. He has no emotion when he's killing people.
I'm... Nice car immediately crashes it. This is Saints Row. Okay, this is Saints Row.
Hello, Steelport, and welcome to Professor Genki's super ethical reality climax. Time to see how the
game is playing. Fight your way through Professor Genki's super sparkle app for fun and profit.
Now with every man, woman, and tiger shot, your prize money goes up. Look out. No one likes it
when you shoot a panda. Don't shoot panda. Once you've collected enough money,
the door to the lab opens up, and you're free to go. But if you think it's that easy,
you've never seen Genki before. Oh, and one more thing. On this show, no one gets to take a break.
If you want to stay in the fight, be sure to shoot the worst aid target. Good luck. It's murder time.
Fun time. Earn money by destroying targets, killing enemies, and exiting the arena before time runs
out. If you destroy things in quick succession, you'll earn a bonus. Let's go. Welcome to Professor
Genki's super epic reality climax. Time is fun time, right Bobby? You got it, Zack. If our contestants
can survive the deadly traps, armed mascots, and those freakishly huge hunters, they can win a
hefty pile of cash. This game looks deadly because it is, but it's still probably safer than driving
in Steelport. Our competitor isn't from Steelport this time, Zack. Genki is watching the leader of
the Saints, the world famous Stillwater Street Gang. As many times as this former gang banger
has been shot at, blown up, run over, and generally put through hell, this competition probably seems
pretty routine. Um, routine maybe, but lucrative. You are going to make Professor Genki sized
dollars driving hoes around, that's for sure. Chuching. Destruction. Our contestant is clapping
her back in Steelport. Have you ever been to Stillwater, Bobby? I did, and it wasn't a good
trip. My car got covered in sewage by a passing septic truck. Really? What did you do to piss off
the driver? Destruction. I didn't do a damn thing. I just wish I had rented a convertible.
Wait, you were in the car? Is that? It is. We have a present. A present is in the maze.
This is really amazing shooting. Cash in pocket. Carnage. Quite a performance so far.
Like sticking a fork in a socket. How can anyone recover from that?
I hope the money is worth this. So Bobby, how do you clean sewage out of a convertible?
With a tumor brush. Really? No, I let the rental company take care of it. Are you kidding me?
What's that kind of shitty of you? Not as shitty as what this contestant is doing to those mascots.
Mayhem. How do you shake that one off? I'm trying to jump over it. I can't jump over this?
Valuable seconds. That's some great action.
Every shot seems to hit something today. He's not dead. I didn't get points for that. I didn't get
points yet. I'm still getting a hit marker. What's going on? Chaos. Carnage. I'm making a lot of
money now. Cool. We've only just begun. I'm surprised the syndicate is still standing. How
many times did you get electrocuted? I don't know. I'm not saying we should. All right,
then see you at the broken chile. Is that a cement mixer? What the fuck? Oh my god. What is this?
Down's wasted. He has the face. He's wearing the head. He's driving a car with it. What?
Damn, I'm good. Holy shit. Okay. Fucking douchebag. What is this?
Oh my goodness. Okay. Give me a fucking goddamn controller. That's the fucking mouse. Whatever.
Controller aim is just like, okay, I'm putting my head under water and then playing.
You really don't want to ride with me. Let's go. I'm surprised the syndicate is still standing
after all this shit we've thrown at him. I don't see a reason to stop. Not saying we should.
Your cousin from Boston. It's a fucking lager. You don't know what a lager is, dude.
I'm your cousin. I wasn't looking. It's always so funny that Boston people in commercials,
TV shows and whatever, they're always a cartoon character. Like, don't you just imagine that
all the people that are like all the Boston people that are in all these commercials and
TV shows are going to bring out a big cartoon mallet. I'm a cartoon character? No, you're not.
Wait, I can do that?
I don't know that. I don't know how I could go all the way back like this.
How far can I go? We'll see. Holy shit. Can I just be like this for the rest of the day?
My old chair didn't do that. That old chair sucked, by the way. Can I be honest? Nice. Okay.
That chair sucked. That chair made you. Is it better? Yeah. I don't want to
say too too much about like, oh, yeah, wow, everything's amazing. But I definitely feel
it doesn't look more comfortable. I told you there's a crank on the back of the chair that
I can like crank, crank, crank, crank, crank and get it. Oh my God. What the get on the bike.
Shani, give me good news. We're going to burn powder to the ground. That's
okay. Let's go stream. See you there, Shani. Wait. Oh boy. Yeah. So something I didn't know
when you get, yeah, it's the, it's the gaming chair with the, um, it's such an E
as whatever the Herman Miller gaming one is. Check what it's E. No, no, not the easy gamer.
The embody. Yeah. It's the one that was, it's the blue one, the blue and the black one.
Cause I, although the gaming chair is, I don't, I don't like the fucking, I hate those things.
Putting your tampons and let's do this. The chair that I had before. Yeah. This is way,
way more expensive. I had the chair that I had before, I think was 500 or 600.
And it was like, Oh, back support, lumbar and cushion. And this to me feels more like a,
like a chair, like a chair, like a real chair. I think the problem that I had a lot of times
sitting in a chair for like an office chair, whatever is it was so cushiony that I felt
like I wasn't sitting in a chair. This to me is, this to me is a chair, a real chair.
Did I just drive in a circle? Oh, I'm sorry. No, I'm serious. This is my kind of plan.
What are we going? I forget what happened. All right, we're good. Let's get inside.
But I mean, I think I'm trying to think of how much these retail for a lot in charge here,
probably knows where to find the office and see if they're hiding under their desk.
But let me put it this way. My back feels like it's
propped up. Because before I kind of could just sink in and slouch a little. But this is like,
I'm in the chair. I'm sitting in a chair. Seriously. You both assume with sniper rifles
from like 15 feet away, you fucking assholes. I couldn't even reload. You know, also I like
about this thing. Maybe I'll show you. You can pull the seat forward. Alright, so here's like,
here's your ass, right? Well, this is like your ass sitting in the chair. I'll just show you.
No, I mean, I like pajamas on. I'll show you like tomorrow, the next day.
The bottom of the chair. If you've got a big fat ass, you could this the ass part of the chair
can be extended, which is a huge deal to me. An absolutely massive fucking deal.
So this has a setting that you can adjust for a huge ass.
It's in charge here probably knows where to find Loren. Let's head to the office and see if they're
hiding under the seat is like collapsible. It comes in and out. You like can pull the bottom out so
it's why like longer and wider almost. And I feel like my big fat ass is sitting in this comfortably.
Okay, I gotta go upstairs. Find a way upstairs. Let's go. I can't get up there. There we go.
You're never going to get a job after you stream. Because I have a huge ass.
Oh, Mr. Albukson, we're really happy. We really think you're very qualified for this job here at
Stevenson and Stevenson Associates. But I'm sorry, your ass is too big. We're not going to be able
to fit you any chairs. No chairs in this office will be able to do it. I'm sorry, but your ass
is too big. What are you talking about? Why are you standing in front of a Gatling gun? I got this.
Why why why why why why why am I gonna put a grenade in his mouth? That's gonna hurt us.
Oh boy. Yep. Come on, let's go go go go go. The arm rest can can move
like wider or. I like it. Let's see after like a week though, because that's a real test here.
I know a lot of guys know I have pretty bad like back and spine like chest pain shit.
it I'll give you my real assessment in like a week cuz I feel like it's gonna
take a while for me to figure that out and I'm not gonna bullshit you I'm not
gonna give you horse shit trust me you know you know yeah I come on you think
I'm gonna feed you horse shit no I'm gonna take what I think give it a week
or two what's wrong with your nose um I don't know it's crooked deal with it
it's the it's the it's the gaming hermit militia the M body I'm playing
randomizer in TF2 that game is so fun I miss that game god damn it you know I
mean damn guys yeah I was gonna say is it playable or if you open TF2 would do
like like 50 bots I snipe you in the head like in the menu okay we're going
way too slow put this down all right let's go put it down I don't need this
anymore I made it smash computers oh shit I need the minigun can I get the
minigun back big head I actually have a small head my head's not big it's
pretty small check this out look at my hands my hands are like way bigger than
my head I don't think my head's not small it's just peculiar Pierce we've
waited long enough now we go for Loren it won't be easy since what have we done
things the easy way so what's the plan kill everyone we see and find Loren
make sense meet me at the penthouse I'll call Shandi Shandi it's time just tell
me where to be we're meeting at the penthouse I am gonna kill that son of a
bitch oh you won't get away this time you bet your ass he won't in the game
well I whatever but it's still in real life too that person had the windshield I
want that car that is a nice car do you guys remember all the GTA 4 videos
where I one of the funny things I thought was the funniest thing in those
videos what I really tried to capture all right bye I always wanted to drive
really fast and I would like whether it was like stir or like boo and mostly
stealth it was like oh yeah you drive the opposite ways fast you can I drive
the other way as fast as I can and we're gonna line it up perfectly so when I
dive out of the car it's the perfect angle and the perfect amount of force
where I'm gonna fly out and I'm going to hit my fucking head directly into the
front of your car oh my goodness but uh but yeah but that was me though that was
I did that apparently that was me it fucking DDT what did I do yeah I would
always try to jump out so I got my so I could hit my fucking head directly into
their car and we I finally got it once it's actually really hard to get it you
be surprised at how difficult that actually is to do there's a lot of new
viewers here what's up how are you let's give that motherfucker what's coming to
the MVM trailer
Lauren has to pay for what he did and I want to be there when he gets what he
deserves don't worry girl we're not stopping with Lauren we're taking out
his whole fucking syndicate we didn't steal that one guy oh one guy do you
think fine and felipe will be come on he's a criminal mastermind he's got to be on the top
floor it's like top floor sin tower doesn't matter we're killing everyone in there
you should the crew has the right i just looked over here as if i was looking at the passenger
side so i was gonna be what the fuck doctors clear they'll drive it in how many times you're
gonna check that gun how long is it gonna take us to get there i was just asking save it for lorenz
goons get the fuck out of here that was like i did that on purpose get the fuck out of here
that guy was my target so fucking stupid they ain't fucking around here a fucking douche man
covering good good job nice work except not really
god really doesn't want us to get inside big guy oh shit it's a heavy oh look out look out look out
here comes the heavy what about what if i put him on my team no what about a shark get him shark
grab him shark get him nice dark souls dodge i played those games i've been driving train for
this moment what am i doing get over here i need the needle gun the needle gun was always so
satisfying because i was terrible with the needle gun truly awful but sometimes every once in a while
you would go like this you'd be running down a hallway stop what is going on who's shooting
that stop firing your gun shut up shut the fuck up shut up so every so often you would fire the
you'd be going down a hallway somebody would be coming this way and you would get it completely
perfectly where you'd go you'd go like and you'd watch it take two or three seconds to
and you kill that dad you'd kill him what a fucking fun game why didn't we wait to do that
until after we kill lorenz that's a really good question like 15 minutes dude all right we gotta
go i'm not i'm not angry every time i have a facial hair people think i'm mad every day
it's just i remember rage quitting a server because there was one spy in the other team
that was unkillable and killed every single fucking person and no one could play the game
remember that and you'd see the top frag list and it would be this person is spy 80 points
and then the next person under there was an engineer with like six all right up up up up
dude just hop on tf2 i'm already waiting what the fuck is this room are those people maybe one day
clones make sense to me what okay maybe make sense was too strong what's with these guys
who cares they're blowing up at the rest of this place how about breaks oh my god he's running
over here let this guy run over here what is letting this guy run down here you ain't getting
out his work sorry i knew this wouldn't be easy jesus pyro shoot that tank that is like the medic
oh my god fucking help me you idiot oh my god how long is it to reload fire fire fire
all right he's fucking dead where's my where's revive fuck come here come here come here come
hi everyone i am on fire oh my god let's play let's go let's play it at some point
in the next like six months it's the same all right let's go
okay torchem what the hell is all this the critscreek fuck the critscreek is fucking cool
philip likes his things custom made and for his brutes i am the master pattern you see
why are you still strung up that they already cloned your ass the copies are flawed all things
go back to you but not my brain i can help you the last time a big naked dude said he could help me
it did not end well what could he do anyway those wires and shit are probably keeping him alive
you swear words come on i'm still strong enough to kill philip i thought we just lit him up
you want some clothes man no time i gotta pee man like i said last time a big naked dude
this elevator will take us to the offices all right elevator jermey you didn't laugh at the penis
follow me to philip's office seriously man you know if you want i can find you like a curtain
we left him in the elevator is nothing to be ashamed of unless you have insecurities
we leave did he leave us how do we get a name my name is holy kerloff so what did you do before
you were a glorified pin cushion i think it's best for our friendship i never elaborate
just know that the enemy of your enemy is your friend as long as you can't fit down the stairs
you have nothing to fear from me works for me welcome to the saints we're supposed to be
following this guy all right where where do we go we're following you man i love this
hey what the fuck dude fuck off all right let's go so follow only all right come on dude
go hurry up you got spy check
that's an express elevator to the basement there's no way to catch it fuck that
look i'm gonna crush that son of a bitch leave it to me hurry it up he's getting away
it's the blood pumping to my loins oh let's get the shit out of me i don't know why loins
wait why am i why am i fighting him oh it's clawing right this guy's been
smoking the same cigarette four hours did i get him blow up the building
oh no is he dead i hate this place more than anyone but it would be folly to destroy
philip's research without seeing what we can harvest from it we came here to send this arm
bomb or destroy the bomb keep the building for yourself how do i just disarm the bomb
i want to keep this i get to keep it right we're gonna have to do something about the pink
you'd prefer a more manly shade like purple this makes me just get up and fucking dance
when i left still water for the senate i vowed never to forget my hometown roots my husband
gave his life defending still water from gang violence it is my greatest privilege to honor
him with this bridge i thought there was a chainsaw what the they're just people we're
gonna have to lean out of the car window and shoot uh fucking grenades at them about maybe
50 to 60 cars are gonna show up we're gonna be leaning out the window firing at it you new
to the saints time for the high spot boys you know why don't we all just split the money
the amount of money that we all have to spend as different gangs on new cars and new ammo and new
personnel they flow pretty damn good we would have been in profit if we just split all the money
equally exactly here's the syndicate sir tech dog what he did to johnny's funeral that's over
the fucking limit he doesn't i want to see the balance sheet of engagement they're like i can
work with six to seven million dollars in cars that you have to spend because people keep blowing
them up watch us versus what it would take if we just split all the assets together like would
we be we'd probably be in the green by a lot let's just go to the fucking movies let's just go to the
movies and hang out can you believe this what's going on here no no no i will not come down i am
heading back to the hill book an emergency session god damn it this is war let's just go to the movies
all right who's first picking up a girl named kenzie kensington i wonder what would happen if
i would just walk up to one of the you know the leaders or something to be like hey dude
fuck you say don't stress you want a little movies so we're getting a shitty fed don't start hating
because you know why not you want to go are you serious i'm not saying and pick something
fucking stupid you know what i mean pick like space jam oh my god flirt later who's gonna say
no to space jam right like just pick something like space jam but he made it sound like kenzie
was about to out the syndicate so the decker set her up for a fall i hope she's worth the
all of you would leave that movie and you wouldn't you wouldn't even care anymore you'd be laughing
about space jam be like yeah that movie was that movie was fucking terrible space jam too
fucking awful movie yeah movies what a bad movie right and i think wait well we can agree i don't
even know if space james a good movie i didn't see it yeah let's just all go see morpheus and
guess what that the other leader the other gang is gonna be sitting there going like like looking
at you you're like that's fucking look at me they're gonna go back to look at the screen and
eventually they're gonna that that's they're gonna crack because the morphing time scene is gonna
happen and you're gonna look over it and he's gonna be like okay all right it's funny all right it's
funny and then if we can just be like all right see and let's just go to fucking mcdonald's on
the way back all of us just get like six or seven of the of all the leaders in the car let's just go
to mcdonald's man let's get like let's split 100 nuggets no i don't know let's just all split
100 nuggets and everything whatever i guarantee i'd get a text a day later oh my god i wasn't
watching all right we made it seriously neo cyberpunk fashion was soaked three years ago
what yeah focus on finding the fed kinsley kinsington yeah you don't seem that excited
about being rescued i'm waiting to see if you were sent to kill me girls pregnant i like her
i untie so what do you want with me you don't look like feds we heard that you know some people
who hate syndicates as much as we do you like nuggets do you like nuggets well the de winters
are keeping zemos at safe word what the de winters are the twin sisters that run prostitution in
steel port and by the way competition so the sisters locked him up if one of the 10 gang
leaders whatever the various the name comes you don't want to go to mcdonald's
oh no mcdonald's sucks oh they're nuggets are the worst can we go to burger king kick that
motherfucker in the ocean and the zemo guy makes two usually i get three people to help me i think
i know someone who'd help but i gotta find him first the war restarts you ever been to one of
these clubs i look like i go to one of those clubs i just say you know powerful guy stressful job
uh that's what i thought i'm very sorry i don't like uh mcdonald's nuggets it tastes like wheat
that man pull out of his ass and then put in fryer i feel like fucking i'd tear the fucking
contract in half that wasn't much of a challenge that's how i like them what are you putting in
your ass i said it just tastes like weed that was it's i don't know it's somebody's ass i don't
know shake people down have i told you about the urban military where they're keeping our boy
it's very company what's oh is this actually to us i'll find out i really do like that i can
kind of there's a wedge that's it i've cranked into my back it's very nice
oh you gotta be kidding me
oh
grab but i'm what don't mess with the saints grab the paint get out of the fucking way you annoying
door grab the pay he says i can't grab him jeez where's the respect i didn't i'm trying to grab
this guy grab the he's on the oh it's upstairs oops a daisy i i'm trying to grab the guy i
grabbed the patrons i thought it was upstairs that's my bad that's my bad i was trying to grab
her you get it i didn't grab the guy oh maybe i did you the manager i don't know anything i'm
just here for a bachelor party yeah this didn't happen to the last guy how do i let go of people
without killing them all right he's alive find the owner jerma look at the bed hey hey what
i'm i don't want i didn't kill her no no no no no stop firing stop firing stop firing seriously
dude don't drop it get out of the fucking way get out of the we cool are we cool all right we're
cool come here where's zemos if i say anything the de winter sisters will cut me off if you don't
say anything something else is getting cut off he's in the pony bar who wins all right
we need to see who i gotta see how this plays out come on man excuse me i was watching something
oh hello sorry i didn't see you all there t.o.s where where's t.o.s where i think we're okay
i think we're okay on the screen in that room well what i'm not i'm not looking at it
why would you let me really never see this place again it'll be too soon remind how are we gonna
find zemos look for the cat in here who isn't excited to be eating a ball gag have you ever
been banned look for the guy with the rhinestone z on his back i've not got it here man oh well
shit that's convenient they went this way oh shit we don't got time zemos mosh what the hell was that
how you doing why do they explode they why are they exploding sorry about making you
you know pull us around this is a rescue right this ain't some elaborate setup for a gangbang
why you gotta put that image in my head bro oh i'll go and rescue them
i want to shake your hands with them floors or a little sticky if you know what i'm saying
and i'm good what in the name of god am i playing this is saints road third
what's up okay okay 20 grand until angel went crazy or kill bane went crazy
he's all bad you do should be willing to help what do we do what are they all doing
oh shit why didn't you start with that you have too many questions find angel i can't read
i appreciate you busting me out 8 000 feet like ever come on z we gotta rescue the mount
i take it saddle up is out too if you didn't you should auto-tune everybody
what can i buy with 20 grand the bugs in my hair he looks funny today why
is the camera in a weird position because i'm forward today i'm like kind of pushed forward
do i look like i'm pushed forward maybe a little you look normal okay because i know i'm
pushed up a little from the new chair i might want to crank the thing up a little higher
because it's supposed to sit in the kind of curve of your back you can hear the crickets instead of
the car it's an electric vehicle it kind of sounds like that i can't believe i heard john
from delocated earlier that was so weird this is john delocated it's called the rage cage
you know what's funny okay delocated did this bit where john had this thing called the rage cage
and it was a joke that you could come in and just smash a bunch of shit and it was really funny like
oh yeah there's like business where you go in and smash a bunch of shit you pay and break a bunch
of computers and stuff and that turned into a bunch of real popular businesses 15 plus years
later 10 plus years later all right let's get it what if i crash into somebody that's big like that
delocated yeah delocated was really funny to go oh this is john he doesn't
no hey hey john he doesn't no come on like if you if you know what i'm talking about
uh that that i would call that that's based you know what i mean that's what i would say
all right give me something bigger than this like the fucking shark gun
bite him bite him why are you going after the cop oh that's why this is so loud
you know let's fucking just here we go watch this shit i'm spinning what are you doing what
i'm so confused why was i doing that
exactly comfortable
this guy was walking away normally like nothing was wrong i'm not too late to the party am i
wait we have a new friend there's plenty of people left to kill let's head inside and find angel
okay shoot can we all get in the car or
downtown are we just gonna uh can he get in the car i don't think he can get in the car
he's a little too big there you are kenzie why are you calling me why are you wasting time
you know he's how do you know i'm outside i'm following the gps on your what what just go
inside i will just stop doing that can you just pick me up throw me into the window
you know that would be in the movie how we supposed to get in there it's the top floor
well i think i know a way to get you in building huh what do you mean and then it cuts to inside
the top floor and glass break of me getting it throw throw into the building flying through
and then it cuts outside and he goes like he's going like this i'm a writer that would be pretty
funny yeah i know don't just give me a give me a pen and a paper just give me a pen and a paper i
got you i can do that by the way you're not one of lorenz brutes if you don't believe me watch
germa rumble live action uh pac-man i was pac-man and i did that to somebody so fuck off if you think
i'm a liar now but they are this imposter to me well go get them then just an abomination
here let me help let me help i help nice pile driver good
all right we got him take care of peace
uh okay hide
stop shooting one bullet and reloading the gun man oh my fucking god i'm so dead
oh my god i'm dead nice toupee i didn't i said that i banned that shit like maybe we'll talk
about the toupee all right it's a it's a ban term uh you read the fucking rules leave this imposter
to me read the rules for you chat in the stream just an abomination do you say happy birthday to
my brother ben happy birthday ben it's me germa 985 if you get what you're looking for for your
birthday surrounded by friends and family with the strength of achilles
wow you're fucking bad at shooting that gun
dork skills improvement there's a guy i need to kill this guy where is he up top
where is this guy oops sorry where is this other guy i don't where is he oh please
of course where is he who you're fucking with all right let's kill this guy please together
one and a two and a three a little busy here i'm getting to it be careful they have flamethrowers
fuck i thought someone was gonna be up here somebody is up here
oh hold on see somebody's up upstairs who is it he's gonna explode that's what i'm talking about
you're bad i'm fine i'm fine well ladies and gentlemen philippe is dead and we are at a
crossroads and the question is who will lead the syndicate to a new era viola and kiki were mr
right hands what the hell i had someone else in mind excuse me the syndicate has to answer
for what they did and this time we're taking the fight to them since we don't know steel
board i brought in some people who do this is kenzie zimos an angel the barbarians are at the
gate we need a general not an ambassador come down eddie what did you call me
sorry venom what would you like us to do kilbane something anything before i wonder why i keep you
bookends around talk to one of these guys they'll have things for you to do
it's our time now let's get this shit started i knew you were gonna say venom it was so bad i
know that's why i did it i purposely did that so you would hate me level 10 we do hate you
what would i get new here new car
let me try this thing and i'll try this thing and i'll put the sniper rifle on too
oh no what's this yeah upgrades let me check it out oh this is nice all right i need to go to a
gun place bling shotgun you knew i had to do it i had to do it once purchase the hospital yeah
let's go mine now that was fast travel man i did that on purpose all right what else you got missions
snatch zimos i was you want me to swing by instead yeah see you see my god i'm not even touching
people i need a gun place there we go huh i just shot that guy in the shoulder and he didn't even
care what are you excuse me excuse me he doesn't are these bullets what am i shooting at he's dead
okay i got him okay what the hell is happening all right what is shooting at me it's harrow brine
harrow brine you know i've never seen harrow brine before and that's crazy scary right try by the
casino how much is it 10 grand let's go mine now harrow brine's not real isn't like okay wait i'm
going to tell you what i think harrow brine is i don't have a lot of experience with a lot of the
minecraft stuff so harrow brine if i'm wrong here tell me it's just minecraft steve and he just
drops explosive tnts in every direction and blows up everything that's it right and he's
got like a 0.0002 chance to spawn no what are you guys what's your problem don't talk about
him why are you coming down you're in a okay i thought that that's so beat up i didn't think
it was a squad car are they smart damn i'm good all right we're safe dude you didn't load the gun
you had me you had me i was right there you had me okay we're good on ammo grenades okay i'm gonna
upgrade something i like this gun let's get it upgraded i have no money left okay well that's
not good okay i'm good i'm gonna be making a lot of money an hour though oh here's the thing this
is the thing everybody wanted me to like do there you go i hope everybody laughed hysterically all
right so what is this this is a major shotgun okay what about this grenade launcher yeah cool
all right i'm into it and i just upgraded this okay cool very cool
i got a long way to go i need a car across the highway all right i need a car
junk junk the thing that takes the junk the thing that takes the junk junk good
no no there's another one right behind it call use your phone how do you use the phone where's
phone i don't want to take a shit in the middle of the street how do i open the phone come get
a taste that's not how you open the phone d pad up tab oh this is the phone dude okay i thought i
i thought there's just like a menu what am i looking for saint's book phone oh okay vehicle
delivery bring me a sexy kitten but don't kill that person okay thank you thanks for delivery
appreciate it that guy got run over two times you're gonna punch me in the face why are you
aiming you're gonna you're gonna punch me in the face what is what's going on is that a grenade
what is that what the hell just happened all right thanks for the car engage in nitrous
yo how do you turn the nitrous off i can't turn the nitrous off well let's repair the car i guess
i have one of these okay why would i not you just use this
because it's slow but it's a tank we will always get to our destination safely no matter what
oh i gotta go five to eight thousand feet you're right never mind that's a long way to go
this thing breaks like shit did it but it did not hit me in the head though okay where's the garage
stay on task i'm going i'm going i got it phone cash phone cash i slowed down so much too you have
no idea whoa all right how about um yeah let's do the sexy kid and then somebody else said cash
ah yeah i'll take eleven thousand six hundred dollars please okay shut up shut up oh no i thought
i was supposed to get off you should have bought the remaster i didn't know the remaster existed
i just typed into steam saints row three the third and i just bought this one i did this like oh
there it is saints row the third all right so now what the remaster is worse that's what people
kept saying i don't i don't know who to believe hey zemos
this is uh don't waste time terms of service well if you were chewing on a ball gag with a horse
tail up your ass for a few years i think you'd want on mine too fair enough i'm guessing you
ain't coming here for the pussy yeah if the saints are gonna stay in steel port we need the morning
star out of here i already work downtown these motherfuckers are everywhere oh i'm here to help
i know every track the mornings start working we can build up our stable
and that close up sisters at the same time sounds good you got some place i can stash them
can i upgrade i want to upgrade the car do i have time to upgrade the car
can i make it go faster i got i'll buy all right all right you can't oh come fine whatever this
thing has a gun okay this thing is insane wait that person must take a picture with me
always gotta stop for a fan what's up all right let's take a photo always ever anything for a fan
i this is why i don't like face cam i can't be on camera laughing i can't be on camera laughing
at that see when the face cam was off you would just hear like a couple of breaths and that was
it what oh wait there's a mission going on right we're good for a change thank you for rescuing me
wait that guy's alive hey you're gonna take the car
oh we just got super kicked all right get in oh shit there's only two seats what do i do
i need a different car god damn it i need i need to just get out get out get out get out get out
we're gonna just people just swarming me no get off what the hell where'd my head go okay
that i feel like far cry five okay we're good i didn't have enough room in the car
i needed more room in the car and now i can fit people in this car
we're good everything's fine
oh god damn it they were standing there
i thought i don't know why i thought they were i thought they were off to the side for some reason
the bitches you got some place i can stash them sure do you're just out of the burp taste you're
disgusting ban that person for five minutes stop pulling me out of the car it's so annoying
what's happening fucking dd2 that's what i want to see
all right we're good get in the car stop having the far cry five
truck with 10 people in it show up all right get in come on we can go go go go oh my god
stop far cry fiving me get in get in okay okay
i have what do you want me to even say that this is what do you want me to say
i don't have anything to say there's nothing i can say right now that would
that you are not already observing as well i have nothing else to say we're watching the same thing
describe the burp what you want me to it tastes like grapefruit juice
relax and stop asking about it this one more i need to get
shit okay wait wait wait wait wait wait all right all right all right come on
get in get into that smoke grenade and somebody what happened do not kill her
is she alive all right get in get in get in get in get in
who's this lady get in the fucking car oh my god get an a car get in a car
okay no more jokes i don't want time no get out get out are they okay are they okay they're okay
they're okay they're okay they're okay they're just both on fire it's okay it's gonna be fine
get a different car get in a different car get a different car this is not even the same person
that was with me before all right we lost one it's okay it's all right it's all right it's all
right everything is fine everything is gonna be fine all right i can't what's happening thank
goodness we lost one i didn't i really did not i was trying hey this happened to my buddy eric
i really don't i really hate to be the person to tell you this but your buddy eric is a liar
i don't know if i would believe everything that he says i feel like he embellishes a
lot of stories he would never i'm not standing on a corner flicking cars if that's what you're
thinking what am i doing don't act like you don't know eric his break yeah after this i will
i will everybody knows eric i thought i was gonna have way more forward motion there
come on germy need to eat potato soup that sounds actually really good so how does this work
for a profit catalog you run this shit like a department store or something
what are you doing
point taken these uh regular employees what the fuck is going on baby what was that
so far cry five get this far cry five shit out of my game
so pissed as hell then
i'm just waiting for an eagle to attack me or a huge bear just runs over and grabs me
you have pissed me off because you're being weird what what happened what happened man what did you
do what did you do okay i didn't get one person not one single person they were probably 40
people standing right there and i didn't get one not one single person that's annoying
i don't know i don't know i thought that guy was asleep i was i was like oh why is that guy in the
passage actually sleeping
turn the motion blur off i don't know how oh my fucking god dude what the hell
what did i do to make these people in every mission they're at every single mission
a hundred of them nice juke what he left without paying kill him well go go get him go get him
go drive to him go drive to him oh my god you dumb ass always win you're lazy you murdered their
leader i did you hear that that was like you have enough those things to go around
shit's running low gonna have to get my bitches a primal after this next drop
that's okay he's just sleeping stop driving around like a fucking maniac do the deal but don't go back
look at this fucking car dude what the fuck dude what what have you been doing what have you been
doing your car looks like a tiger what where have you been where have you been your car looks like
aluminum foil what the fuck happened where have you been what have you been doing
you can't even do your car can't even get that fucked up if you try
didn't i throw a grenade there's way too many of these people that come in here dude
i'm sorry i'm gonna be honest i get a criticism of the game there are 50 of these cars like
there's too many there are way too many of these cars are showing up at every mission
do you understand they're everywhere there's they're fucking everywhere did you take up
smoking weed yeah it's it actually tells a lot catch me after i get some more of these ready
for instance oh that's just a cop i've been pursued by the other gang more than the police
for every one police car there's been 10 of those other cars with the gang in it
i mean i guess i could fire back even smoking weed no i know i've been eating weed there's a
difference this game just yeah this game got way more fun the last like four hours have been so
much more fun that first i don't you know i think it was the audio being screwed up
and i didn't really have an opportunity to do anything so yeah that first hour was like
that kind of snooze what about okay there's a lot of stuff how about faster more intense
and i had the zombie voice so happy we can finally talk yeah yeah my name is andy jan i'm sure you've
heard of me the studio signed me on to direct gangsters in space and i want you to be the star
i mean sure you're already a star but think of immortalizing yourself on the silver screen
andy beautiful thought right and swing by the studio and you can see the script i'm sure you'll
love it okay let's go read the script yeah i'll go pee in a minute after this this is dlc that's
okay that's fine oh cool wait i'm not going on people just can't fight well what the hell what
do you i'm trying to get well it looks like i'm just going over it now i'm not gonna wait for
anything i don't even want that fucking car i'm doing that i decided i gave up halfway through
to make the cops think that i died down there so they'll leave me alone they'll think i'm dead
and then i call the kitty car and i'm gonna go off it that was all calculated
you don't think i did that on purpose holy shit that's funny okay vehicle delivery
sexy kitten bring it to me where is it where's my car oh my god what are you doing
what happened did you crash oh my god your neck is your body your neck is your whole body you're
just a neck and legs there's nothing wrong about that at all hold on any picture that's too weird
to not document i don't care help me bro i'm stuck i'm i don't think where does this gps want me to
go does it snow in this game it does oh punch it sick sick sick why does he look like that i don't
know kill that i just do i'm gonna kill that son of a bitch i'm gonna kill that son of a
bitch um every kind of soup uh cheddar broccoli easy to let you know that i'm so super excited
right now a nice thick and creamy tomato soup none of this runny bullshit it's gonna be really
like good like thick tomato soup with a grilled cheese or don't fucking give it to me you
understand me i'm i'm asking him nicely all the time wrapping my head around the script is the
script a problem just say the word baby we'll toss it oh oh it's cool i'm just i'm gonna need
cue cards like a motherfucker brilliant that's so fucking cinema verite you're killing so thick
and creepy it's nice to meet you mr gen who is this extra why she talked to me oh mr gen i'm
playing quilana really i thought we were getting a name for quilana uh nope just me
uh that's just fucking great look missy mcnobody over here isn't gonna bring you down i promise
i won't let her okay you just be yourself you're gonna kill it right let's shoot this fucker all
right what do we do it's like widow maker in this scene you're rescuing the alien princess
from the military okay jenny who oh double decaf soy latte okay wow just play this fast and make
that oat milk and maybe we can talk trust me whatever you say hey make that oat milk and we'll
have a conversation why did you just look into the camera because i don't know there's something
wrong with me i just it's there and i know i know that's you right like you're that you're up there
that's you you are this little webcam up there and when i'm addressing you that's you up there
and i'm talking to you that's i'm i'm talking to you right now that's you up there escape with
the alien not if i didn't say about it they're not supposed to kill can i go back and do it again
i saw a person i saw a person that is random over um the movie's still going we're good
do i have to do it in the same car this is ruin the movie this movie sucks yeah i'm not i'm just
shooting like over his shoulder and stuff more explosions that's what the kids like these days
is like big you know explosions and superpowers and oh i went the wrong way did i
this movie what a bad movie all right i made it i made it now what yeah charge up the hill
guns plate i'm coming princess hang on wait wait wait wait oh shit you you you saved me
no time for small talk we caught you know what for me what what what we got a star making performance
here in a cardboard co-star okay we gotta ramp everything up take it back to entering the base
we're sexing this fucker up no you uh you doing all right yeah just you know trying to make mr
gen happy okay so we're doing it again this time more it's a perfect spot take two and all right
land on the target i'm stuck in parachutes i tried to make the movie better i tried to make the movie
better take two and i wanted to make the movie better that's that was my fault i'm stuck in
parachutes i'm kidding flashbang i just flash banged the guy with the camera fuck where
fuck this fuck this movie oh my god he's uploading a whole clip on me
oh i'm in trouble now i'm in trouble now let's go i won't let them take you away princess
thank you ever so much for saving me i'll be sure to keep you safe let's go let's go keep it steady
i'll hold these guys off i've never flown anything like this this thing before it's called a helicopter
and i have faith in you princess watch out my name is is quilano quilano then
i have a better gun than this you can kid me you got a better gun than this please what
are you okay you crash like a pro and cut beautiful play the role with the punches
no i wanted to like do like to do a dump on the guy like not on him i want no let me rephrase
that this audio in my ear let me rephrase this after there's no shit blowing in my ears
jenny don't listen to him you're doing great i wanted to do the taunt where i pull my pants
down and like do like the i'm gonna shit on the ground in front of the camera
the taunt that i have that why is my taunt different this this one there we go okay
let's take that car all right let's go you know it'd be really funny if we got to actually see a
cut from this all this would be amazing this game gets a full letter grade higher if we get
to watch the movie and it's actually these scenes we can only hope right
sorry i forgot the line
thanks what is when the water helicopter
jesus how many guys are they throwing at us uh you mean your military leaders no driving
what is this driving bullshit drive you're ruining the shot we're good
oh no oh no the set got crashed by actually actual aliens wait what's going on i'm lost
that's part of the movie oh i thought that that we were getting oh no here comes another gang
and they're aliens this time or something i don't know well okay give me the benefit of the doubt
here there was an enemy in the very beginning of the game that had this purple kind of laser
shit and was teleporting around so i don't know i figured it was a different gang i thought it
was a different gang the game from the first like 10 minutes of the movie the purple neon they
teleport around with it it was blue whatever same technology it's pretty much same technology
that's saint throw four oh whatever you don't could go for right now just a big ass chicken
sandwich a big chicken set big ass chicken sandwich i'm talking the chicken the chicken
patty whatever is too big and is coming out the edges of the other one it's a big circle
and the bun is a little circle oh that's really messy yeah whatever there's and i i want i want
to grab it and i want there to be mayo coming out the bucket size like right around the edges
you can tell they put way too much on way too much but i want it and a bunch of shredded lettuce
shredded ass lettuce swiss cheese or even i i would take i would take a
prolonged and i want it wrapped in paper i want it wrapped up in paper
shredded lettuce
oh my god i think you mean jenny was talking more driving move on it's not worth it no i want it
wrapped in paper i'm just going with the flow okay prepare for jump they're not even filming
the right way did you see how far it was listen i'm really sorry please please don't let this
ruin our relationship this is 100 the casting director's fault i swear are you crazy he's the
director i don't care who he is you shouldn't take shit like that from anyone all right let's
reset and do that again no thanks i don't think i want to do that again okay we're actually doing
it again wait somebody wants to take a photo with me no no no no no someone's take a photo
with me somebody i want to take a picture with a fan trust me this works better just keep filming
you guys think i could beat smash tv in one setting you gotta learn to stand up for yourself
you think i could beat smash tv in one sitting even with how he's treating me stick with me
sweetheart i'll show you how it's done i have my doubts dude and i want to when i bite into
that chicken sandwich i want to hear it from across the room i want people to think i broke
a tooth because it was a crunch like a crunch i want to be like and i want like juice to go down
here and i have to go shoot be safe now one word you burnt it that's a wrap for today
because i've already forgotten your names because you are worthless now get off my set
oh my god where are all my oh my god fans what did the channel grow too much that you got
how many you guys weren't here for that what are you talking about that was a fun mission
you're jumping from joke to joke like you snorted 10 pixie sticks am i i feel like i was pretty
quiet for the last like 30 minutes what is that uh just wait that way what is that what are you
doing i feel like i'm pretty just muted today i feel like i'm pretty collected today what are
you talking about i talked about how i want a chicken sandwich and people think i'm like
making a joke about it i'm telling you how i want my chicken sandwich i'm describing my ideal chicken
sandwich right now this is not a comedy routine that's very suspicious that you be yeah i'm being
serious that was cool mission let's do this one what's your ideal breakfast i got a pretty
ideal breakfast you'd be surprised god damn it i want this now so bad more than the chicken
way more than the chicken sandwich i want what i'm about to describe to you more than a chicken
sandwich by a hundred a hundred leagues okay corn beef hash two over medium eggs crispy bacon
on the side maybe a couple of sausages and some toast oh my god corn beef hash and eggs oh my
goodness that sounds good it is good yeah and a carrot juice smoothie because i want to make
sure i get you know not just eating a bunch of greasy shit yeah like a carrot and apple
a little bit of ginger in it just sip on it for like oh my god we could talk about anything
i if i had a if i had a carrot orange and ginger smoothie or juice i could sit there and just
pretend to be interested in anything you were saying for at least an hour or two do leaning
back like yeah yeah yeah wait what am i doing keep the paparazzi away from the car
i'm i'm so confused what's going on just get comfortable while i undress you damn you smell
good somebody ought to flatten that fuck what get to don't get close to the news van
evade the significant other
so why don't i just bait them and have them go over the edge the client wants me to do damage
is that good enough for you at a time both whatever just don't stop they're not too rough
do a power slide uh don't you think it's a little unsafe okay there you go this would make a hell
of a sex tape oh i love it when they're pinched get two vehicle near misses in a row whatever
just don't stop we are not okay you'll be ready for more soon your tongue is crazy good
do you have to talk this whole thing like i don't want to even know what's why don't hear this i
don't know what do you i don't what are you doing back here i don't do this what's happening
why are you saying this i don't want to hear this what's going on back here and for you next time
i'll be ready for your magic i don't hear people have sex in my car it was just a magic show
it was just a private magic show
that's funny now that you're back in business we can focus on the morning star
no time wrong car
watch out there's a fight gonna break out look out this is the best mission coming up okay who
crashed i didn't move out of the way i'm doing something i knocked the phone over but not him
he's fortnight dancing he deserves to die why did he start to why did he do that what was that
sound the fight or flight response what are people doing fight or flight response when you see a
fortnight dance that was so bizarre i didn't know what to do he was trying to defuse the situation
fortnight dances are so cool it is so cute i love an ugly fucking painting you fucking
felistine what you know about art that's a winter sister's original bought that back in the day
when me and the twins were all live and let live well seeing as how we just let them know we're
taking over their business i doubt that deal's gonna hold shit remember the pony show i've been
off that christmas list a long time anyway i didn't call you over to talk about me you killed
philip loren and showed the morning star that you are here to stay time to relax and cut loose baby
why was he i'm so confused we'll party once the work's done i'll call you when i make another
move against the morning star i just woke up is he still a medic yep should i change the
way i have a boat oh that's um i thought that was a boat i thought that was a big
yacht it's a hat disappointing in a way okay i need a scout costume what do we got
it's just like a red t-shirt right i wonder if they just have a red t-shirt they're probably
i prefer to buy it yeah i have to buy it i'll go buy it how do i get the hell out of here
oh
i'm trying to leave i'm sorry i'm not trying to hurt anybody i'm trying i'm not trying i'm
just trying to leave the house it's hard to see out of this fucking mask okay are we good we're good
how do i get out of here
so
how come i can't fortnight dance down down down down down down down down down down down down down
i just want your eyes what's going on hostage i have a hostage are we all right
plenty had ice cream the whole fucking time are you kidding me how do you steal the ice
cream in your hand the airbag didn't even deploy no way no way you want to join a gang
i can't move i'm stuck on her i don't like that i'm out person's lost that
i killed that person someone's watching you on their fridge i'm not responsible i am not
responsible for you overheating the screen on your fridge by the way i'm telling you i'm not
responsible if you overheat the screen on your fridge how much money do i have oh i have a lot
i got a lot of money i have actually a lot of money i don't want one of the mods to get pinged
about like oh hey um so i did this thing but like i can't get germa's stream off my fridge i hacked
my fridge screen and can you help no no help no help i wanted that car all right i need to go to
a closed place check it out now i can't even see it this is probably the closest or no this
one is over here we're gonna get a scout outfit oh do that suck i i wish i could i find an umbrella
i'd give it to you i would literally if i had an umbrella i would give it to you and i would just
get rained on i would give it to you and you could keep it i wouldn't even care i i really would
right that that sucks obviously you got somewhere to go you got somewhere to go the paper is gonna
get soggy you're gonna get like the ink is gonna get all of your hands and shit
what's wrong why is he running screaming i fell you didn't need to you call me an asshole
he's scared all right i'm taking i'm i'm i'm taking that i'm taking that that's mine now
fuck this guy's driving so erratically i'll take good care of it okay wait i have another hostage
do i all right what do i do all right 45 seconds and i'm good can i get paid or something
why is our sniper shooting at me what the fuck are you doing what could you possibly be doing
what could you possibly be doing why is is your mac truck perpendicular on the road
there's no reason why anyone would do that that was that was insane the person blue screened the
the person blue screened the screen on their uh fridge by the way nice job i'm not responsible
for it good oh no maybe not oh it's burnt in right you know what i want your car can i have
that please these things are dangerous you know oh i can be get this off of me let's yeah i want
classical music too i fucking hate these people stop doing that okay leave me alone
i fucking swear to god they're deliberately driving into me they're deliberately trying to
kill me there's normal and then when i get close enough they just rip their car over
yeah i'll fucking buy it i don't care let's fucking change you know what i want i want the scout
outfit that was easy i need to get off the bike i guys you don't understand the reason why i did
that i can't get off the bike can you see me pressing the button i can't get off the bike
okay there we go i own this place what do you mean
i can't get off the bike in the store should i do a christmas sweater version
i also did not expect to slingshot at the guy here we go very nice but this i forgot about the
resin skin that's the closest backpack i can get what does the scout have i think these just gray
pants right like gray baseball pants and then what kind of shoes oh they're shorts yeah they're
shorts for shorts yeah no they're not shorts the hand bandages yeah yeah they're long socks capris
and long socks yeah that's what it is kind of like these but not as baggy oh close enough all
right what about socks that they even have i don't think they have it sneakers i don't think i can
get um actually they are kind of baggy aren't they they are baggy they're like this kind of brown
dr house this is a doctor house theme song okay and then shoes they don't look like that but i
don't whatever i don't care make these white wait what why is a big mickey mouse hand close enough
he's ubercharged that's true all right where do i go from here this one hey shawndy i was are you
fucking kidding me whoa what did i do a party we're throwing a fucking party now party i didn't come
on pull it up yours oh i'm gonna kill him hold on shawty you're not killing pierce you're taking his
side i'm not doing anything not until i talk to him all right fine what happened here guys you
don't have to drive okay buddy this is not what is he shooting
fucking abrupt chaos what happened what was the point that was just abrupt chaos
somebody just fucking saw the opportunity of a lifetime for them it was like holy shit man
shit's going crazy this is my opportunity to do the do the monster truck fucking relax man
are you crazy this is the only opportunity i'm ever gonna have to do something like this
get away from me just give me okay i gotta go to the party see what i mean what the fuck are
people doing what are you doing oh my holy shit i can hit that 10 times but there's no
way i know how to do math anymore i don't know how to do math
that was crazy okay can i get it's time to go it's time to go i'm gonna go i'm gonna go
i'm gonna go i there's no reason for you to watch this anymore it's time to go
i'm gonna go to the party that i was supposed i was been invited to i got invited to a party
none of these people did i got invited to a cool party okay somebody is unloading from where
is it you that person i thought that person was shooting at me who's shooting at me from what
direction this person in the truck has been a menace they've been just driving around this
motherfucker this this motherfucker has caused the whole thing that person caused the whole thing
yeah watch this look yeah oh yeah yeah oh oh sure you're safe you're a safe driver safe driver
you cause the whole thing man can i go to the options do i have a mod on like a cheat where
people are just fucking crazy i feel like i have a mod on that's like oh pedestrians and cars are
fucking insane right this is i think it shouldn't be happening i don't i don't there's no cheats on
or anything i feel like there are they're all scared of you should i take the pizza delivery
car i'll take the domino's car get out of the road i mean if i see a situation that looks a
little dire it looks a little scary i'm i'm not going to step on the pedal as hard as i can
and drive as fast as i can into all the other cars or directly into a wall so i fly out the
fucking windshield why
that's not a way to get away from danger you don't push the gas all the way to the ground
and just scream while you drive into everybody you turn around that was fucking hilarious
oh my god johnny's dead and you're throwing a fucking party i forgot i was a skeleton
like that sure sound bad i was saddled up in a human pony show but you see me crying
about a little girl i swear to god i will shove that thing down your throat hole
whoa shondy we can't mourn gatt forever eventually you gotta nice self-insert
no offense brother he's right whatever damn girl that actually i do look like that right now
you know i'm saying i put on a t-shirt
and i think i'd look all right but then you look in a mirror and you look turn to the side and it's
like jesus i have like a stomach and that big ass and hips and shit i actually kind of look like
that watch it watch it watch it
shit these holes ain't home
want the bat i want the bat this is not this is not on brand
that's not on brand i need the bat i need the bat that's not on brand
there's a scatter gun all right cool i don't know if that was a good i don't know if there's a good
i don't know who's good and who's bad i don't know are you good i guess not revive where
where are you where are they upstairs oh shit they're upstairs you picked the worst fucking
place to die
whoa what happened it's your party you tell me machine guns no they're not i thought i thought
there's machine guns on the wall they must have cut it this just gets better and better
looks like there's a light show outside snipers better grab a rifle and get up top on it
sniper are you good no sniper oh
do i get it get up to the roof i got you i see you
do the rest
there are so many snipers everywhere oh my god they're every direction man
and where is this person shooting from from where oh from down there snipers are down
let's get some power up in here i'm tired of tripping over bodies that shit's downstairs
after you yeah what are you on my team you can handle anyone all right take the other gun out
let's do power somebody's watching on a 2003 dell axon pocket pc i noticed so it's over
how isn't that impossible gigachad it's a screenshot from my phone cropped to 320 by
240 and uploaded to an sd card on the pocket pc while you guys all say nothing is impossible
that's so funny that's i love that all right we gotta go up where are my friends friends
where are they go take an edible break what if on the smite tournament i just i just got
fucking really high do you think i would do better just don't tell anybody can i not where's this
weapon can i not use the elevator you should do it i don't know i feel like it's really embarrassing
on a national stage i mean i mean there's gonna be a ton this there's like a hundred streamers
or something doing this i think miss kip's gonna probably i don't know about maybe
i think he's probably gonna cast it or something i don't know i that would be
embarrassment on a national stage that was a friend because i got i might forget like what
my moves are and then i've been talking all this shit about how i know what i'm doing and
and see you later goodbye
stop moving around so much bingo bingo
big money big prizes i love it i failed hooker assassins they came highly recommended
ladies it was a pretty shit plan go pee tell me something i think i think i'm all right i
think we'll just go to six hours and then i'll um i'll call it there's a reason philip left the
thinking to us we're done here you only need one of them my old your son is setting but it's not
too late there's still time to grab apollo's chariot and drive that fucker back across the
sky you feel me yes kilby apology accepted so again let's go over schedule i'll come you a vip
faster murder bra it's my tournament yeah 27th so in exactly two days from right now
then after the smite tournament green screen night it's gonna be wild i wouldn't miss the
green screen be crazy is it hot in vegas yes it is but i like it out here like that though
the hundred degree day to get that i get hold on let me take these out let's take in two three
deep breaths okay what i was trying to say is uh i like hot i like the hundred plus days
something about it it's just so searing but you don't sweat then that's people getting
trouble out here because they come out here and it's a dry heat so they're not sweating
they go wow this is great i feel awesome and they drink like fucking 10 beers it's like dude no
you've got to drink water even if you're you're not sweating you're still getting dehydrated so
make sure you drink a lot of water out here only a maniac likes hot weather why really i don't know
how to turn this off i don't know i can't control this i'm alive how do i control this
switch mode i don't get it i don't know how to just evaporate get me back up there i want to
there was like a bunch of stuff where was that where was that safe house where was that it's
right here where was that i want to do the other stuff where was that why is it always raining
it's always raining is this snow in this game yes oh is it this one here boat dog no where is it
is it the sains hq that's so far away fuck okay let's go i didn't know this game had a map
what is going on i do not feed i think my body has just utilized every piece of hydration that i
gave it i drank like a 24 ounce uh special green tea drink and then i had like a 16 ounces of water
right like before that before the stream i'm just i think i've utilized every penny let me try this
all right up to the roof where's the roof how do i get to the roof teleport there we go i need
to go to the roof all right look at this thing what is this what is that it's like a star wars
vehicle i'm gonna try this oh god how do you fly how do you fly okay a is up x is down there's a
laser this is how do i fly faster can i how do you fly okay that's hover mode okay
how high can i go where's the skybox let's take out the fucking sun
oh my goodness i'm high up can i go far even further i didn't go anywhere
just taking too long to fly
oh my god
fuck i thought i was gonna be able to do it i was so close i was lined up perfectly i just went a
little too fast oh that would have been amazing if i parachuted then i landed on top of it and just
got back in it oh my god it would have been unbelievable fuck that sucks oh that would have
been amazing oh man you're looking really white that's because the i didn't mean to press that
button but whatever that was almost a best gamer moment it could have been it could have been but
so close but so far although getting that lined up perfectly i landed right on the cockpit window
and i was slowing down i was really controlling the speed to the very end and it just was a little
too fast god that's it stinks it's okay that would have been a 10 million viewed youtube short i know
damn it okay why do you look so ugly huh i need to see it's because the the the exposure is
blown out let me i'll fix it there that now i'm not all blown out now there better say it was
ball was all blown out people don't look like that time that person out for one day what was that
all right that's it i'll see you guys later i will see you guys on the 27th so not tomorrow but the
day after for a smite tournament this is for one hundred thousand dollars so there's a lot on the
line here there are major stakes in this tournament that was really fun the first 45 minutes that was
and i was kind of i don't know it wasn't having a good time i felt i didn't like the tutorial but
that's why you stick with it because six hours later that was really fun i'm glad i played it
that was a great time i'm gonna save it just in case there's any reason why i'm back in it again
yeah hundred thousand dollar tournament i think we have a pretty good team i know there are other
teams that are very good so i'm gonna brush up on the smite maybe a little bit and then on the 30th
i'll see you for the green screen stream is it 1v1 no it is conquest 5v5 so that's gonna be very
interesting isn't it it's gonna be very interesting yeah green screens the 30th
smite big smite tournament in a couple of days that's kind of the plan for the week
oh well well week as in i mean the next three streams right and then we'll see what happens
next weekend but i'll see you guys in a couple days wish us luck it's gonna be a pretty intense
competition so hopefully we do well all in all i don't really care i think it's just gonna be a
fun time so that's all i care about cuphead dlc comes out next week as well well i can tell you
what we're doing i am without a even tiny bit of a doubt going to play that at launch guaranteed
what about dread x there's opportunity to do that tons of opportunity to do
there's a lot of games to play he won't play to launch yes i will i'm gonna play to launch
or try to but thanks for all the subs everybody i know i was gone for a while trying to stream
and do a bunch of personal stuff life stuff project stuff but i'm very excited i think we
have a at least two or three really really fun things coming up i'm really looking forward to
the actual green screen night after all the footage is out there for a couple of weeks
july is gonna have some cool stuff in it green screen hype yeah that will probably be the last
time i go in front of the green screen i think it's a good trilogy but yeah thanks guys thanks
for watching good to see you again see you in a couple days have a great rest of your night as
always take care of yourselves call your mother and have a great night goodbye for now