Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some more Hitman Absolution.
This is gonna be mission three called Terminus, where I have to gain access to a hotel room.
And well, basically the hotel. And hopefully I don't get hit by like a car.
Any cars driving down this road? No, there's a train.
But I gotta gain access to this hotel. I gotta find an arms dealer by the name of Blake.
Not sure what the deal is here, but I'm just gonna go in the front door.
Hey buddy!
Hmm, closed.
How you doing?
So I cannot go up there. Cannot go upstairs or else those guys are gonna shoot me.
So I'm gonna go this way. What is like Henry Winkle doing over here?
Well, I can't go in there. Staff only, okay? Staff only, I get you.
Is this guy part of the staff? Can I like break this guy's neck and take his outfit?
Probably not. Let's see.
Hmm, to get upstairs, I'm probably gonna need to do some interesting things here.
This is the restroom. This guy's coming in here actually.
Yeah, this guy's coming in the bathroom right now.
Oh my god, plunger, plunger. Can I like plunge this guy?
Oh god. Oh, I can like choke him out with the plunger.
Sick. No one's coming in here, right?
Get in the toilet!
Just shut the hell up!
You didn't see anything.
Oh my god, like this guy's gonna take like a dump.
Oh no, oh no.
Alright, don't worry. Don't worry, I'm not gonna do anything.
Knock him out.
Well, so things have gone very, very smoothly in the first like five seconds.
I have to dump all these bodies in the toilet.
Can I even hide these guys in here?
This is gonna be three random dudes in the bathroom. Oh no.
Can I block the bathroom off? Oh great, okay, that's like a dumpster.
Alright, I need to put on that guy's bowling shirt.
Whatever the hell he's wearing.
Hopefully nobody else comes in the bathroom.
Dude, I clubbed that guy in his face with a dirty plunger.
Maybe I can put that guy in the other room.
Wow, this is, I almost already have minus 5,000 freaking points.
It's alright. No more bodies can fit in here.
Maybe I can stuff this guy.
Can I open this door?
I'm gonna have to very, very cautiously drag this guy back towards the toilet.
Oh, I'm like breaking his leg. That was so horrible.
Look at this, like I'm wrenching him.
I honestly can't do anything with this guy.
Hold on a second.
I'm gonna look out here.
Is there like a dumpster right here I can dump this guy in?
Is anyone gonna see it?
If anyone goes in that bathroom, damn it.
Oh, whatever.
Well, people are getting curious.
I can't even go in the staff room.
What was the point of all that?
I can't even like walk over here.
Oh, staff only.
Whoa, hey, hello fellas.
Are they gonna see me?
They're gonna see me if I go over here.
We're good.
We're good so far.
Except for the fact that I minus 5,000 points.
If I open this, who's behind here?
There's a guy standing right here.
Hold on.
Can I like break a bottle or something?
Do I have a bottle?
I got a plunger.
Can I like throw the plunger at the door and like freak him out?
All right, good, good, good.
Perfect.
All right, now maybe somebody will come out here and I can distract them.
Oh, this guy's got like a worker's hat on.
Wait, no, he doesn't.
Is that one of like the crew?
Is anybody out there?
No, it's just not me.
He's in the damn doorway.
I can't do anything about this.
All right, he's walking the other way.
Good.
Oh, whoa.
Oh my God, I'm stuck.
I go up these stairs.
That's a real question.
I don't want to get spotted.
There's a guy with a ponytail.
What's this disguise?
Disguise is a hope goon.
But I already am disguised as one of those goons, aren't I?
Oh, except I got like a cowboy hat on now.
Hey, what's going on, partner?
Howdy, partner.
So now I should be able to go upstairs now, shouldn't I?
Because I'm one of these dudes.
Let's see.
Let's just find out if I can.
I hate spiders, dude.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, well, that's just lovely.
That guy's spotting me.
All right, where the hell am I going now?
I got to go like upstairs, don't I?
I got to go over this way.
Oh, let's wrap around here.
And just for fun, let's like punch this guy in his face.
Hold on.
Can I go in here?
The elevator is likely to have an additional basement entry point.
All right, fine.
Let's go down here.
Let's go down the basement.
Let's be a basement dweller.
Is it an apatage?
No.
Why is this?
Why am I?
Oh, that's to dump bodies.
Oh, boy.
Hey, fellas.
Hey, fellas, how are you?
Is that a worker?
Yeah, this is a hotel worker.
I should probably take his disguise.
I don't want a disguise staring at me.
Come here.
Come here, you son of a...
I'm not going to hurt.
I'm just going to give you...
I'm putting you to sleep.
Hold.
Don't worry.
You'll wake up tomorrow morning and you won't remember that damn thing.
Now, give me that.
Now, let me dump your ass.
What are these guys looking for?
Isn't it pretty bright down here?
Why would they need a flashlight?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Hey, how you doing?
Oh, damn it.
Oh, why did I?
I should have just walked up the damn stairs.
They don't know I'm here, though.
They just know that somebody is karate chopping their workers in the face.
Damn it.
Now, he's going to walk up the stairs.
Get me out of here.
Oh, hello there, sir.
See you.
All right.
I'm going back to the front door.
I'm going out this way.
I got the stupid terminus gear on.
I'm going to go this way, around the corner.
Oh, I just picked up more ammo for that snub nose.
I haven't met him before.
There's only two kinds of people in this world.
This lady's nuts.
See you later, lady.
Okay.
Let's go up the stairs.
Oh, that was close.
Hello.
Trespassing.
What?
I'm a worker.
I'm a wor- I work here.
Hey, I work at this restaurant, hotel, bar casino.
You can't tell me where to go.
I can still hear this lady.
This lady's annoying.
Oh, my God.
I couldn't take her talking anymore.
She was just talking.
She had an ironer in her face.
Oh, am I about to dump this poor lady off the window?
All right.
Well, see you later, grandma.
Ah.
All right.
Let me just tell you guys right now.
If I took an iron in my mouth, I would probably instantly, instantly kill me.
Hey, don't worry.
I'm just doing my work here as a worker.
Can I do that?
Look at it.
It says I can hide here.
Yeah, I can do it.
See?
Hey, just working my, working my job here.
Don't worry about a thing.
Just everybody stay calm.
Stay collected.
All right.
Now, let me up the goddamn stairs.
Ugh.
Maybe I got to be one of those workers.
All right.
Note to self.
Go smash a worker's face in with an iron and then take his clothes.
Let's try this again.
I'm going this way.
Right through here.
You guys don't see nothing.
Looking for one of those guys with a hard hat.
God, I'm so stupid.
I can't, like, do this mission.
All right.
Is this one working?
But this guy doesn't have a hard hat, so apparently I won't be allowed upstairs.
That guy is a worker, though.
He's got the worker like clothes on.
He's working on the elevator.
All right.
You know what?
Just get out of my face.
Oh, right in front of him, too.
Don't.
That guy's got this.
Oh, he's.
Oh, great job.
No, no, no.
You won't get away.
You won't.
Just calm down.
Everybody calm down.
Everybody just calm down for a second.
Great.
Fantastic.
Can I jump down here?
Jump down like frigging Batman.
Come on, man.
Oh, my God.
They're unloading.
Get me out of here.
Get me the hell out of here.
No.
All right, guys.
It's time.
I tried the.
I tried the the nice way.
It's time to start unloading on people.
Get me out of here.
I didn't want to happen to have it come to this.
Wow.
That was a cool move.
All right.
I made it.
What?
I can't proceed without with enemies on high alert.
Oh, boy.
I'm dead.
Oh, crap.
No.
I'm gonna die right here.
Give me the screwdriver.
Backup has arrived.
Oh, I'm in so much trouble.
I'm in so much trouble.
I'm bleeding.
I'm dying.
The question is, can I hide somewhere?
Can I hide somewhere?
Where are these guys?
One guy over there.
One guy coming around the corner right now.
All right.
What's another one?
Got to run.
Get up and run.
You stupid idiot.
Anybody in here?
Come on.
I need to like I need like a I need like a basket or something to hide in.
It's got to be like a stupid.
Like I'm so.
Oh, I'm so nervous right now.
No.
Come on.
I've got to hide in.
It's all right.
I'm good right here.
I'm okay.
They're still looking for me.
Oh, what?
I can't believe.
How did I gain points?
Why?
I'm at negative 4,700.
I don't know how I got points for doing what I just did.
All right.
Sooner or later, they're gonna have to give up their search.
I can go back to running up the stairs.
What a way to do the mission.
It only took to mission three for Jerma to completely be an absolute freak show and just
unload on everybody he sees.
This guy's coming this way.
Man, I need to.
Can I make my way back up to the stairs now?
I mean, I got one prick right here.
He's got a shotgun too.
Fabulous.
Listen, bro, you are gonna I'm gonna Batman the hell out of you.
Cautious.
All right.
We got down to cautious.
Got down to cautious.
They're looking for me.
They're looking for a guy that looks like this.
So I need to get behind this guy.
I got to take this guy's disguise.
Which way is he facing?
He's facing that way.
Come here.
Come on.
No, don't go outside.
He's the only one, right?
No, no.
I didn't want to shoot him in the back.
I didn't want to shoot the guy in the goddamn back.
Why did that happen?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, let me be sneaky.
I shot that.
No, no.
Go back in.
No.
Oh, no.
Oh, this is going so badly.
This is going so badly.
This is going so badly, guys.
It's all because I shot the guy in the back and I was trying to choke him.
Oh, man.
What a complete catastrophe.
All right.
Come here.
Goddamn disguise.
And let me just walk up the freaking stairs.
All right.
Nobody's around.
I killed like the whole hotel staff, apparently.
Dump this guy's body and go up the stairs.
I'm making this way more difficult and way more complicated than I have to be.
Get in there.
Sorry for shooting you in the back.
I didn't want to do that.
I wanted to choke you.
Well, oh, good thing I got 135 points for hiding the body.
Don't mind me.
Call the elevator.
Hey, look at that.
Sweet.
That guy completed the mission.
Can I get in?
Oh, yeah.
I think this is it.
Hey, let's go.
So that is going to wrap it up here for this first part of the hotel mission.
So I'll see you guys all soon.
And stay tuned for the next part of the hotel, upper floors.
And take care, everybody.