Hello! Hi, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Germa 985 Holiday Christmas Special.
And the award show. I'm Germa, how are you? How's everybody doing?
Ooh, sorry, it's a little chilly. Oh, it's snowing out there.
I have a few things to talk about before we get started.
Thank you for joining me on this beautiful holiday afternoon.
Over here is a schedule. Everything you need to see today is right here.
Awards are happening, by the way. Medius categories ever. 27 categories this year.
There's a lot. I hope you're ready.
Oh, not only that, we've got also the elf puzzle room. What is the elf puzzle room? Who knows?
You'll find out very soon.
Do I see holiday cheer in the chat yet, please?
There is a schedule, of course there is.
Can I see some people Christmas, please?
I need to see it. I'm not going to go any further.
Okay, so also, Bugleberry is in the building. Can we get some applause for Bugleberry?
Yes. Thank you, thank you.
Going to be making a nice, delicious holiday turkey.
From what I've been told, I don't know. We'll see what he comes up with.
But also, what's under the tree here?
I'm going to be opening a lot of these presents. Remember we did that a few years ago?
They're under here now.
It's going to be so nice. It's going to be...
Wait, what's in this one? Hold on.
I didn't peek, I promise.
Oh, I think that might be an Xbox.
It could be an Xbox. I don't know. We'll see, we'll see.
But anyways, before we get started, how do you do a holiday show?
Without, of course, an intro. Without a musical intro, perhaps.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome, round of applause, Top Shelf Vocal.
Yeah, absolutely. Thank you so much for coming.
Really appreciate everybody here.
And from hearing you practice earlier, sounds like you're going to do a little bit of jingle bells, from what I understand.
Yes, sir.
And I'll also be joining you as well, as a choir together.
Are you guys ready?
Okay.
Is that okay?
Of course it is.
Hey, before we start, Merry Christmas, Happy New Year. Let's get started.
Dashing through the snow, in a one-horse open sleigh.
All the wheels we go, laughing all the way.
Ha!
Bells on bobtail.
Just refresh the screen, then. I don't understand.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I mean, just refresh. Is the internet problem? We lost the internet. Is that what happened?
So just get it back.
Can you connect to another Twitch server?
There's a guy on the channel right now.
What do you mean there's a guy on the channel right now? What guy?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Production in my ear right now. Tell me what's happening. Because I don't understand.
The stream got hacked?
My stream got hacked?
What?
Should we do a different channel or what? What the fuck is going on?
Shut the fuck up!
Don't talk to me. Don't make eye contact with me.
You know what? Hold on. Show me what's going on.
What's happening in here?
Remember, there's a data breach right here.
Well, someone accessed our stream key.
How expensive were you two, right?
I see his name here. This is my channel right here.
That's right.
And what happened?
It looks like there was a breach in the firewall.
Oh, it looks like there was a breach in the firewall.
What's your hourly rate, by the way?
Yeah, don't want to say that, by the way.
So you both have masters in technology. You can't fucking figure this out?
Rewrite the source code. Go for it.
Prescribe that source code over here. What he said.
Do you understand how much money this cost? Do you understand how much time I spent doing this?
Yes, sir.
Where's Offbrand?
Where the fuck is Ludwig? Where's Atrioc? Where the fuck are they?
A copy for Mr. Albertson.
Thank you so much. I really appreciate it.
Hey, buddy. How are you? Fucking snake, motherfucker.
Who leaked my stream key?
I don't know. What's going on? What's going on?
Somebody is live on my channel right now.
And I'm sorry, but it's making me very upset. And you need to figure out how it happened.
We'll figure it out. Germo, we'll figure it out.
If this is a problem, by the way, we are done.
You and I are never talking ever again. By the way, this was made wrong.
Germo, dude.
Don, I don't want to talk to you. Go clean that up.
Shut up.
Hey, okay. So what the fuck the heck is going on here?
Hey, so are we live? Are we live on a different channel?
Okay. All right.
So what's happening here is this is the Elf Puzzle Room, by the way.
Elf Puzzle Room.
I don't know if we're even live yet. I don't know if we've even started yet.
But if we can get the energy in the room, we can get higher.
Yay. So we have a puzzle here that people are going to be doing in this room.
And it's going to be...
Stand up.
Get out. Get out.
I'm sorry. I don't want to be a dick about this.
But you were told in the contract when you signed it to shut the fuck up when I came in the room.
And that's fine.
So we've got this 10,000-piece puzzle.
We are actually live. Good.
So we've got this 10,000-piece puzzle, and it's going to be done over the course of the evening.
This is awesome. Hooray.
So you can get started here with this, and you can go for it.
And hey, don't you think we should have a little bit of snow?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right. So let's get it started here.
Hey, snow! Snow! Snow! Snow! Snow! Snow! Snow!
Ow.
What the fuck did I have, Dad?
So we confirmed that the other channel, my channel is not working.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
I'm sorry, everybody, that this is happening.
I just want to say that it's, you know, you've got to do what you've got to do.
And we're doing this now.
And it's time for us to just...
Can somebody please get rid of the ASCII art in the chat that I see over here?
All I see is ASCII art. I just saw Forsen like a thousand times.
What do you mean, like, come on, Forsen.
But there's a lot. We need to clean that up a little, I think.
While we're here, we're live, we're good, hi, how are you?
Can we potentially get some people to, say, clap maybe in the back?
Maybe just pretend like we're doing something good?
Stop spamming the ASCII art!
I've got an award show to do.
Regardless of where we are, regardless of whose channel we're on,
there, we have awards to do, and we have a lot of them.
So we have to get started.
I don't know what's going on over on the other channel.
I don't know what happened, but we're working on it.
We've got engineers that are incredibly skilled.
But we're going to have to do the awards over here.
So, we'll start. I've got to compose myself a little.
I've got cocoa over here.
And it was so freshly brewed and everything just got ruined.
It's okay. Is it all right?
Well, what is he even doing on the other channel while we just do this?
What's he doing on the other channel?
What is he playing? Is he playing a game?
Dude, you got no mods.
Do you think I thought of that?
Do you think that I thought of that?
Before the channel got compromised and we're on a different channel.
Do you think I thought of that? Are you stupid?
Don't get mad at people in chat. There's no reason to.
I'm going to do my awards show the way that I'm supposed to.
27 categories.
And we're going to get started here.
So, let's just relax. Can we reset?
Let's reset.
The first category is best bro.
And what is best bro?
Best bro is when I said, I don't know why this is even a category,
but it's when I said bro a handful of times.
So it should be fun to see what those nominees are.
Here are your nominees for best bro of the year.
There's one place I didn't go.
I need to go to the magic school.
Where's the magic school?
Bro, where's the magic school?
No more of this.
Bro, this is the thing you attached a trailer to a truck.
That's not a woodcutter.
What do you mean look at it?
I'm not looking at it.
Bro, fellas, ladies and gentlemen, that is not a woodcutter.
I'm pressing the buttons.
What the fuck?
I'm pressing down.
It just fucking hits a wall and freezes, bro.
Bro, relax.
Bro, where am I supposed to put this?
Why is this even a category by the way?
Bro.
This is at the last second.
What a stupid category.
Give me a break, man.
Are you kidding me?
Melaton is a rhythm game that requires precise timing.
For a dreamy experience, make sure your sound is on
and avoid using Bluetooth audio.
Bro.
Bro?
Honestly, man, when somebody asks you,
when somebody says, hey, dude, do you know there's a dodge in the game?
Bro.
Yes.
Oh.
You, bro.
What the fuck?
Oh.
Okay, bro.
What are you fucking doing?
What the fuck are you talking about, bro?
I was hitting X on the right spot.
This is making me really mad.
Bro, House Flipper is my number one most played game on stream.
You don't think I know what I'm supposed...
I'm just trying to do the missions quickly
to be able to buy the house.
Bro.
Bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, slow down.
I just need to hit you with this.
I got it.
Somebody in the chat said,
I just saw it, somebody in the chat said,
hey, bro, can you play Call of Duty, bro?
Right now, are you going to say that?
Right now?
Anyways, your winner for best bro of the year is...
Let me get into it.
I don't even know which one this is.
Bro, are you kidding me with 26% of the vote?
And did you know there's a dodge in this game for 24%?
And then bro, it's not a woodcutter with 13.
So bro, are you kidding me?
I don't even know which one that is.
But there you go, best bro.
We're going to do another one.
This is worst beater,
which also was actually supposed to be taken off the list.
But I left it on accidentally
and realized that it was still part of the categories
before we removed it.
So we're going to keep it in.
So let's go ahead and see the nominees for worst beater.
Over here, here, here.
He's doing a joke.
Beater, beater.
Beater.
I love it.
It was the chap.
It was the chap took beater.
We need a wow factor here.
Okay.
I'm going to bring it.
I wanted myself to be a dancer.
A dancer?
A dancer, something of a dancer myself.
That's a beater?
That is a beater.
Rats, rats.
We're the rats.
Peter.
It's your birthday today.
Cake and ice cream is on its way.
Peter.
You've been such a good boy this year.
Stop saying Peter
and help me with this fucking video game.
Stop.
It's half of the chat.
All I see is butt cracking beater.
Help me.
What did he say?
Wait, what did you say, Peter?
Peter?
I'm sorry, that's all I heard.
Hey, Peter.
There, old paly.
It's time for an old fashioned handshake.
The last supper.
Yeah, remember when Jesus
gave a hot tamale to Peter
and he didn't like it.
He almost puked.
Hello again, Peter.
It's me.
So.
I knew we were friends for a reason, Cricket.
Yeah.
We do joe.
We do gourmet.
We can do just about everything.
Where the hell is the medicate?
Are you reading?
Any amount of voices you can do?
Worst category of the entire,
the worst of the entire night.
I don't know.
People had to really search for that one.
There's no way you even knew.
Maybe some of you saved those clips from earlier.
But ladies and gentlemen,
your winner
for worst beer of the year
is, I actually don't know this,
so this is going to be news to me too.
You've been such a good boy, Peter.
And then ghost Peter.
And then infomercial Peter.
By the way, you've been such a good boy, Peter,
with 24.7% of the vote.
So that's cool.
Very interesting stuff.
Moving right along.
Look at this one.
We're getting through the real shit
categories first.
Let me be really clear with you.
So we're going through the shit categories first.
As the engineers are still working on the channel.
Best ooo
and I'll give one to you right now.
So here it is.
I apparently do that quite often.
I don't know how often because
why am I opening it now? We haven't even seen the nominees.
Why would I do that without you seeing
the nominees first?
Anyways, here are your nominees for
worst, no, it's best ooo
of the year.
That was a good one too.
Oh,
oh,
hmm.
Is that a mask?
Or does he actually have two heads?
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, we got it.
All right. Hello.
I'm here. I'm here
to get a rust repair kit.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh,
oh,
can I stand actually for a spell
because if it is, I want to know what it is.
Mud, oh,
oh,
I like this game. This is a fun game.
Oh,
oh,
oh, I didn't even need to, whatever.
Oh,
oh, get ready to nominate
that one. So all bad.
You know, before I
open this, I want to say I didn't
think that there was even enough to
vote for this year. I think I said
that a few weeks ago.
I was like, there's no way that I did this
this many times, but apparently I did
it a thousand times.
We'll see who wins. Ladies and gentlemen, your winner
for worst ooh ooh ooh
of the year is
with
35.8 percent of the vote.
We got it from
Sorcery. And then
get ready to nominate this one for 23 percent
and then Sorcery spell excitement.
I mean, I said it
like five times in a row. It was like,
ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
If you don't, by the way, there's probably people that have no idea what the hell that is.
So that is a
sound effect file from the
Simpsons arcade game. The first
boss of the game does that every time you hit him three or four
times. So if you, understanding
what that actually is from, it's
from that game.
And by the way,
speaking of shit categories,
by the way, I did talk to production
earlier about, man, this category
takes way too long. This is going to take
far too long. I don't even want to, I was
going to remove it last second.
I was going to say, let's not do it
because it's worst cat puke.
There's like 40, there's like 20 or 30
nominees. It's like an eight
minute video. So are you ready to watch eight
minutes or so? Is everybody cat puking?
Alright, I guess so.
There are no mods.
There are mods.
We modded random fucking people.
So people say this
is the best category. We'll find out.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are your
nominees for worst cat
puke of the year.
And then I move away
that they don't like.
And I start to
fucking pass out and shit. Like, I don't know, they
freak me out. That would be so scary.
If you're just in like a pitch
black area
and all you hear is this.
Oh, what?
Let me try that brew.
You can just
hear the crunch of
the bread.
Do you need a handsaw to cut through a piece of
fucking bread?
We're going to narrow this down to three.
To be clear, you can't decide 15
wins.
The penultimate round is here. Let's see
god damn things.
Oh,
nice. Holy shit, I was on camera. You got
to see what it looked like. I mean, you don't
you know, I'm not talking about like you like
no, you
pick it up and you like
fold it up and
you eat it.
I don't know. That was fucked up. I was having problems.
My internet's fine.
It must be maintenance.
Natural peanut butter with the oil
that settles and you have to
mix it up a little bit or I'm
telling you, man, sometimes I just scoop in there and I get
a bunch of the top layer oil and a little bit
of the top layer of peanut butter.
I eat it. It's delicious.
You're drinking the oil. I'm not
I don't
tip it up and like
no, I'm talking to you. It's like a little
test. It's a little tasting like
that's it, man.
I need the inspiration.
What's the point of this?
Oh, thank god.
There's too many of these.
Way too many of these.
I can eyeball that. I'm really good
with that.
Sorry.
Pumpkins just broke me.
Cappies.
There are way too many of those.
I lost count. How many were
there actually? How many nominees were there?
Twenty?
Why would I?
Alright, that's never coming back.
Here you go. Here's the last time you'll ever hear
that sound. It's very cold.
It's supposed to be hot cocoa
in my hot cocoa poetry power.
Okay, so the winner, who cares?
Does anybody give a shit about this?
Who actually cares? Pre-recorded
Andy.
What do you say?
There are 27 categories.
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner
for worst cat puke
is...
What do you think? Actual cat puke
at 14.4%.
I probably saw that one coming.
Pitch black
cat puke at 14.
It was very close.
And then eating eggs
with 9.8%. By the way,
I think two or three years running now,
this is the most skipped category.
Almost 20% of you
that took this poll just skipped it.
What's going on?
What's that? The hacker is ahead
of you. I don't understand what that
means. What's going on back
here? Why is that happening?
Can you put it back to the snow? I want people to think
I'm in an actual place with snow.
Hold on. Hey, hey, hey!
You too.
What's going on with my backdrop?
Your backdrop
is supposed to be snow, and there's like
meme shit on it.
Are you going to try something?
This usually works. Well, whatever it is,
it didn't work. You know what?
Why don't we mess with him back?
Why don't we send something that's really going to mess this stuff up?
Hello!
Stop talking!
Who the fuck are you? Who am I? Who are you?
What are you doing on my stream?
What do you mean, your stream?
This is my Christmas special. What are you doing here?
Is this the guy? Is this the fucking guy
right here?
Hey, bro! What's up?
Hey, bro!
Did you just hack it?
Oh, he's a hacker! Wow!
He's so skilled. He's so
talented. It's the extinguisher.
Wait, what?
You will call me by my name.
The extinguisher.
Your name is the extinguisher?
That's right.
Did you get that name from like the fifth grade?
What a terrible name.
It was sixth grade.
The extinguisher. Okay, extinguisher.
How are you? How are things?
Why? What are you doing?
What is your goal here?
Oh, my goal?
My goal is to get you to apologize for all the things
you haven't accomplished.
I've accomplished tons of stuff. We've got Dollhouse.
What about the hundred gifted subs?
Hundred gifted subs.
What do you mean?
What about you not playing Yakuza?
I thought you were going to play that one.
Yeah, I'm going to.
I didn't play Yakuza. That's why you hacked the stream.
At two billion dollars of debt,
what are you? The government?
That's, all right. Well, first of all,
there's a couple things. Let me rebuttal.
After I rebuttal, maybe you'll give the channel back.
Maybe when you play Glover,
I'll give the channel back.
I played Glover! That game sucked!
What do you mean, play Glover? Is that what you're really on about here?
And the chat loves it.
All right. Well, I kind of don't give a shit
about anything that you're saying right now,
because number one, I did try
to give the community subs a hundred.
My credit card got declined like five times.
I did try. My credit card got declined like five times.
That's literally what you sound like.
Did you get his fucking area yet?
You're never going to find me, Jerma.
So what the hell?
You just come in to taunt us? Is that what you're doing?
Is that the fun you're going to have here?
What are you doing? Yeah, that's why I'm here.
Thank you. And I'm here to
give the people what they want.
Yeah. And what is that again?
You're just hacking the channel? That's funny.
That's funny. Everyone's laughing about it.
I'm sure it's fun. Look at them.
Look at them in the chat. Okay, well, thank you.
I appreciate hearing from you. Now, can you please leave me alone?
Should I have to do? Leave me the fuck alone.
Wow. No?
Yeah, great respond.
No. That's the answer?
No. Okay.
Well, you know what?
What do you got? What do you got?
Why don't we send him something fucked up?
How does that sound? Do you guys have a connection?
Do you have a connection? What if I do this?
Wait, wait, wait. What do you mean? What?
What if I do this? Huh? Stop doing that.
Ah. That's funny.
That's so fun, is it? That is great.
I saw the IP address. Was that an IP?
Yeah, try that on for size.
Get that shit off.
Look at your face. It's so angry.
You're such an asshole.
You have a connection, right? Send something back.
Go ahead. Send something back, guys.
Eat shit, you hacker!
It's the extinguisher.
You will learn my name by the end of the stream.
Follow me, old chum.
I'm not a gnome.
I'm not a gnoblin.
Did you do that? Yeah.
I'm a gnome. What year is it?
Can you be gnome?
I want to tell me what year it is.
You're gonna gnome the guy?
That's so fucking stupid.
You're gonna gnome me on a live stream
with over 20,000 people?
That's so 2017.
I don't...
Why would you gnome somebody?
That's all you can do back...
Get his
location and send
something else. Get us back
access for the love of God.
Give me a fucking break, dude.
You send a gnome
over there. You know how bad that
makes me look? We got
CatboyGerma. We got the Suski.
He even turned off...
We can't even turn this back to normal.
What a disaster.
Anyways,
I may have made a few of these,
but...
You know, let's just get right into it.
Everybody's waiting for this category,
and it's a good one, so let's take our time with it.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are the nominees
for worst face
of the year.
Fucking gnome the guy.
Unbelievable.
Now listen here, Batman.
I think that's what's gonna happen.
Turn the webcam on.
I can see the music!
That was such an ugly face. I hate that one.
You look very handsome today.
Thanks.
This is bullshit again.
He didn't do that before!
Don't go
4-2 back,
because you're flipping spawns.
Yeah.
Just contain mid control, and just hold them out and spawn.
We should be fine.
Wow!
That wasn't even a real fight.
You can see every inch of my face, too.
I don't like this.
I hate this.
Oh!
Holy shit, people are so ugly with light, aren't they?
See? This is me.
This is my face.
Do you honestly think I don't know the horse has a dodge
65 hours into the game?
I thought she was doing another move.
I thought that was the big sweeping one.
Oh my god.
Fuck this fight.
Fuck this game. Return it.
I don't have 100 hours in it, but I'm returning it.
I'm going up to the counter with these eyes like this.
The fucking GameStop that I got this piece of shit from.
They're gonna be like,
Hey, I would like to make a return, please.
More games for your wax face.
Find me a path I can go.
Find me one path.
That was weird.
Abbott's a holy man.
Okay.
I wonder where I go from here, though.
If I had to keep it all in,
After like an hour, I'd be like this.
It would be insane.
I would explode.
Okay.
Put that in here.
I'm just going up the stairs.
I don't give a shit if he hears me.
I thought he was downstairs.
In a circle.
That was the chicken.
That was the fucking rooster.
That was a rooster.
That was actually a rooster.
Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
Fuck you.
Come on.
Is there an O-Rick?
Was that an O-Rick
at the end? What was that?
O-Rick.
Yeah, I have a tendency to make faces.
But, you know,
whatever. It is what it is.
This is going to be news
to me because we don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen, the winner
of the worst face of the
year. It was pretty close.
You look very handsome
today. At 16.8%
of the vote.
Germa cheesed is a little bit further after that
at 11.4%.
And then smushed sleeping face.
Which, if you had asked me, I thought
would have been number one.
So you look very handsome today.
This one.
That one there. I do that apparently frequently.
But, yeah.
You look very handsome today.
It's this one.
That's fine.
You can't nominate this stream
because it's literally
the day we're doing this.
We're going to do best accident now.
Rick!
Best accident is when something goes
wrong during a stream
and we need to figure out how
to fix it. So that's where we
are now. This is
the sixth category. Still plenty.
Still plenty to do today.
So, ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees
for best accident of the year.
Blue Bunny
makes the best grocery store ice cream.
Without a doubt. It's by a mile.
Here. Blue Bunny.
Chocolate. Chocolate ice cream. It's fluffy.
It's pillowy.
Don't do it down there.
Don't do it down there. Don't do it down here.
Don't do that down here.
You do not want this
down here.
It's time to fight some crime.
Made some adjustments to my suit.
I feel like it's a little more appropriate.
Let's go.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What are you?
Those!
No, I'm doing the thing. I'm doing the thing that
fucking meme.
I'm not grunting.
What sex noises are you talking about?
I've been silent the whole time.
What are you talking about?
What?
What the fuck?
Security camera.
Why is it going so high?
Here's your glove.
It fits perfectly.
As you see.
I promise. I promise I didn't
sit on it.
I'm going to do this.
And get really mad.
And get very upset that I sat on it.
Rebna?
Kalidna.
We need to know and I'm going to reload it.
Okay, that's enough of that.
That's enough of that one. That's it.
We're not doing that one again.
We're not doing that one ever again.
It's good, yeah.
And I was talking about a little recipe that I had.
If you don't know what hamburger, this is what it looks like.
It doesn't look like that.
It doesn't look like that. It looks like this.
Whip cream?
I have to wait an all week to do this one.
Alright, get in there.
I don't think I made it.
I'm assuming it missed.
I can't tell.
Do not flip the cart.
Under any circumstance. Don't do it.
It's not funny. It's not a joke.
It would be annoying
because you just wasted like 35
minutes cutting wood.
Jeremy, I know you think you're
quite the Canadian,
but this is not the time to do that.
Let's go. And a lot of people are going to think
that that was on purpose, but it was not.
And I...
You gotta be fucking kidding me, man.
I'm going to quit the game.
I make a lot of mistakes.
I see the spam in the chat.
We're working on it.
Just relax.
That's up a lot. It seems to be a theme
on the channel, doesn't it?
Let's see. Ladies and gentlemen, the winner
of Best Accident is...
Let's find out.
I mean, you
could have guessed this was going to be the one.
The mask falls off Spider-Man
at 15.6% of the vote.
Nice job, Spider-Man.
You get to see the outline of my
dick if you zoomed in.
I mean, don't do
that, but if you can see the outline of my
dick, whatever, that's fine.
My favorite ice cream, let's take a look at
11.8%,
which that's sad, because I really
do think that that is the... I think that is the
best ice cream. That's so
fucking stupid. I was so disappointed.
And then Booty Smash at 11%,
it took up...
This is pretty even.
It looks like
everything after Booty Smash
was within 1%.
So everything below that
was just within
1% of each other, so...
Make sure I'm not going to see my
dick on this stream. Okay.
Don't want to do that.
Alright, after this, we're going to take a quick
break after this, because I'm going to try to get back
on the goddamn channel.
We're going to go dark for a second,
but this is best overdone Boston
moment, if you don't know what that is.
So best overdone Boston moment, I'll give you an
example. This fucking cookie
sucks, dude. Where'd you get these fucking cookies?
In the fucking toilet?
Where'd you find this? In a fucking dumpster?
New category this year, by the way.
This is a new category.
So here are your nominees
for best overdone Boston
moment. Don't show
my dick on camera.
I know I got what he was coming to him, man. Don't worry.
I got plenty left for you, you fucking idiot.
Okay, good.
Ultimate destruction!
Yes!
It's a stupid fucking dumb fucking stupid fucking game. Fucking game's fucking stupid.
Yeah, that's fucking stupid.
Yeah!
I hate this fucking category.
Your Boston's showing.
Three, two, one.
Happy fucking New Year!
And a
dear
and a
dear old Lang Syne.
And
all the Red
Sox players
should fucking
get paid more than the
Yankees do.
And all
the patriots
who cares about Tom Brady.
He's a fucking loser.
I don't even fucking
care.
And all
the revolution
soccer team and the Bruins.
And fuck you
for fucking talking shit to me about my
mother behind my back that one time that year.
And I fucking never forgot.
Do you still consider
yourself a Bostonian?
Of course I do, kid. Did you just take Boston?
No.
That's fucking bullshit, dude.
Alright, kid, listen, that's fucking stupid.
Alright, fucking listen, kid.
I'll see you outside any
donkeys anytime. Oh, shut the fuck up.
You bring a pack of cigarettes and I'll fucking see you there.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. What are those
brown slacks called?
Oh, they're called cockies.
How do you drive your car?
Oh, with fucking cockies.
Jeremy, you're spending so much fucking time with these ants.
I mean, there's other shit to do with them.
You're spending a lot of time with these fucking ants.
I can't believe I did this this much.
You've been outside a lot.
You're just like digging around looking for fucking ants.
I don't know what is
getting a little concerned about you.
I love how I've turned
you guys like the Boston accent
guy into things that
like I'm allowed to kind of come out of
my like I can just say whatever I want
as that voice, that character.
And it's universally despised
anything I say. I don't know why it has to be like
the Boston guy with the cigarette
outside of a CVS.
I don't know why it has to be that guy.
I wish they were
fucking two drive-throughs, three drive-through windows
instead of one at like every restaurant.
Alright, dude, like
Okay. This fucking game
is fucking stupid.
Where does it want me to go?
Chad, do you fucking, what was it?
This game is for fucking kids. I don't give a fuck.
I'm playing a fucking kids game.
And you guys are fucking shit in the fucking chat.
Yeah, okay.
Pickle nose, pickle nose.
Fucking say that?
Pickle nose?
Fuck up.
What's up, dude?
That armor is pretty fucking cool. That's pretty sick armor.
I can't take this anymore.
I mean, I got magic defense
on it, though, pretty fucking low.
With just two more minutes.
My tail light does stuff like that, too, but magic is pretty low on it, right?
Alright, fuck. Alright, kid.
Alright, I'll fucking see you later.
Hey, mom, I said hi.
I don't know, not in like a weird, you know what I mean?
That was like supposed to be respectful.
That was not supposed to be mean.
I weren't ready for the fucking rain of stars.
Hey.
What about, you know, fucking starlight, kid?
Oh, fucking starlight.
I fucking hate this.
I'm annoying.
How do we cut this category off quick?
I'm farming for souls, so I don't want to die at the boss.
The boss is probably going to be hard.
Oh, you're causing
from Boston.
It's a fucking lager. You don't know what a lager is, dude?
I'm your causing.
I wasn't looking.
Oh, so I was back in Massachusetts, right?
Because I'm saying it's going to be the wedding stuff.
And I could tell I was back in
Massachusetts. It's been a while.
I was driving.
And I just hear
I'm just sitting there and I pull up through a red light.
And I just hear out the window.
You fucking
douchebag.
Somebody was just screaming at somebody.
They do just kind of stand here. They're all fucking
terrible. Hey, what's
in the telescope? What are you looking at, Maz?
Look at that.
Oh, look at this artwork.
Look at this artwork.
Why is it snowing?
That fucking foxy comes out of there.
I heard this.
My fucking son played this one.
Fucking foxy comes out of there and sprints down the fucking hallway.
It was fucked up.
They walk down halls and stuff. They fucking walk down the hall.
I played it before.
Wait.
Oh, shit. There it is.
Okay.
I'll fucking drop this guy if he fucking comes in my...
If he comes over to the door, I'm going to fucking drop him.
Apparently, I have a catchphrase
between me and my girlfriend that I don't even realize I have it.
And apparently, I say
like, oh, fucking like, gollick.
Gollick, kid. Oh, yeah, give me some fucking
gollick, dude. For no reason,
apparently. And I'm like, no, there has to be a reason
of why I'm saying like, oh, fucking gollick.
I just do like a Boston accent
joke. And I say gollick.
Okay. So,
the winner for...
Is it best or worst? That's the question I have.
It's best
overdone Boston moment.
Not worst overdone Boston moment.
People saying Maz. Maz
is the one. I don't know. I actually...
Let's find out. Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner of the
worst overdone Boston
moment.
Really?
It's the gollick catchphrase
story at 22.2%
of the vote.
Gollick catchphrase.
Me explaining that I have a catchphrase.
And then the Tom Brady
New Year's Eve song
at 11...
Okay. 11.8%
for the New Year's Eve song.
And then the Boston guy plays
Five Nights at Freddy's
at 10%.
Also, keep this in mind, that was the second
most skipped category.
Under cat puke.
Nobody gave a shit
about that one. I don't
blame them. I really don't.
It's funny just how many things people did skip.
People probably went to this list
and saw... I ain't taking all 27
of these.
No, I'm skipping this, we're skipping this, we're skipping this.
This is the second most skipped category,
which makes sense.
Why don't we check in with the elves?
How are the elves doing on the puzzle?
Can we go take a look? How are they?
Elves, how are you?
They haven't done
anything.
It just looks like you've poured a box
of fruity pebbles on the ground.
There's nothing even there.
Let's stay
with them for a few minutes.
I gotta go pee. Hey, who cares
if they get your channel hacked on Christmas time?
Right? Who cares?
Welcome back, everybody. Welcome to
the awards show.
Christmas special. Yes!
Come on!
Where is it if there's somebody playing Call of Duty
on my channel right now?
Fuck them, right?
We're gonna have fun over here.
What about the elves? What's wrong with
the elves?
It doesn't look like they just poured, like I said, a box of
cereal on the ground. They haven't made any progress
at all. Absolutely
zero progress.
Okay, so
how does it look today?
How does it look? We're doing that one now.
This is the
eighth category of the night.
Hey, how's that for you?
How's that look? This is worst
hair, not today, but, you know,
I've had some bad hair.
Most of these are from VR,
which is kind of unfair, if I'm honest.
I just heard the production
go, don't open that!
Alright, so ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees
for worst hair of the year.
Can we please
get a zoinks? Fine.
Zoinks, Scoob!
I fucking banned that person. I actually banned that person
for like an hour, because they just made me do that
and I fucking hated it.
Want a hair check? Sure. Hold on
one sec. How are we?
I think it's because
I like went to
my hair has a weird growing pattern.
Is it that bad? Alright, it is bad.
But listen, my
hair is a lot thinner here.
Look at how much thicker my hair is here.
Do you see?
It's really, I have really thick hair
here, and really thin hair
here. I didn't shave this.
You know what, I don't even care, just fuck the whole thing up.
What is going on?
I do look like a big
kid. What's happening right now?
I look like a big kid.
What's going on?
He's balding? I mean
yeah. Not really though.
I'm 36. Not really.
You dream you look like this
when you're 36. He's right.
You dream, keep dreaming you'll look as good as I do
right now. He's right. Listen to him.
Can they hear me? Keep dreaming.
Wait, let me say that again when it looks better.
You're not going to get away
with that.
They probably heard that.
It's really great.
I don't know why. This thing was expensive too.
What if I go like up this way?
We're trying a new hairstyle.
This is just Donald Trump's hair.
On my head.
My hair looks like
it came out of the oven and it's
done. This looks like
cooked hair. My hair
looks different. It's done now. It's ready.
I wanted to stream today.
Why do your sideburns look like
pubes?
I haven't seen this video.
Dude I
don't know. I haven't had a haircut
yet. Oh man.
He looks off.
Maybe you think it's because of this?
Do you think it has anything to do with
whatever this is right now?
Do you think it has anything to do with how off I look
today? I wonder if you think it
has anything to do with this?
Pube hair. Okay.
Look. Before I open this.
I'm 37.
You get older. Your hair gets a little
scraggly. It gets a little weird. But
it's still there. I still have
it all. I know people that
are way younger than me.
And some that are way older than me.
That do not have this.
Oh look at your hairline. Look at that.
Oh wow. Oh yeah. You'll see.
When you're almost 40 you come talk to me. How does that
sound? When you're almost 40 you come talk to me.
The winner.
Of worst hair.
Of the year is.
It was close.
22.1%
of the vote. What do you think it was?
Chad, what do you think?
Let me see. Off Andy?
Off? He looks off? No.
Not even close. The winner is
pubesideburns at 22%
of that. Okay.
Greasy cooked hair at
19%. And then
shaggy hair gets a
chat member banned
at 11.7% of the vote.
So pubesideburns.
Pubesideburns wins.
Alright. The next one.
How does this sound?
Let's get to best dancing.
Which there were some
I did a lot of good dancing this year.
I'm going to open it but I'm not going to look at it yet.
I'm not going to look at it yet.
I just want to get it ready. So you don't
hear the sound effects.
At best dancing, I know I've hit the
Luddy a few good times this year.
I know I did the orangutan, which
didn't even get nominated. So what the heck's going on
there, guys? Thanks a lot.
That's my dance. The orangutan.
Doesn't even get nominated.
The hacker wants to
1v1 you.
I don't know what that means.
We'll figure that out when we get back.
But here are your nominees for best dancing of the
year. Here are your nominees.
Right now.
Somebody said hit the Luddy. All right. How do you do it?
How's that?
I'm an actor. I act
for a living.
Can you fucking trick that?
Go for it.
It's all right.
Feed him to the lions.
Yeah, feed him.
Feed him to the lions. Don't you think?
I don't know how to twerk.
You can't resident sleep for this, can you?
Fucking jokers.
Tay, can you twerk? Yeah.
You think you can beat me? I know I can beat you.
I don't know what I'm going to beat you at. Oh, you know you can beat me.
Go ahead and cue the music.
Good luck.
Weird monopoly man.
Swedish monopoly man.
What is planned?
You guys synchronized this?
How are you doing it so well saved?
Nobody beats me at my own game. This is incredible.
These moves.
New German.
Here we go.
He had moves the whole time.
One handed.
New German.
Did you do the goofy
goober dance?
If it's not Char, then it's me.
Then vote for me next time.
Exactly.
Don't vote for me.
I didn't do anything.
But you did.
So your winner
for best dancing
is
So you think you can beat
me at 21%
of the vote? Very close.
Hit the Luddie
was 20.2%.
It was literally 1% difference.
And then twerking king
was 17%. But hit the Luddie
and think you can beat me.
Very close.
I was on stage. I had a whole suit on.
Come on.
This next category, we're going to get right through this.
I have 1v1.
I don't know what the fuck he's talking about.
I wish
I knew. I have no idea what he wants.
He's got ownership of that channel
right now.
Don't think about it too much.
Easy.
During the break I calm down a little bit.
But it's kind of hard to.
So this is
best auto moment.
And best auto moment is a great
category considering that I think every
single nominee on this list
were the only times auto was shown on screen.
I think it's five times
or six times over the year. So there's six
nominees. And here they are.
For best auto moment.
Auto.
You seem like we've had turkey now.
He was very sleepy.
Are you tired? Maybe it's a good idea
to just turn the VPN on. And have it just kind of
go somewhere else and have the traffic
come in a circle.
He knows there's a treat. He's right here.
God, he needs to lose some weight.
Say hello, Akio.
He's so chunky.
He needs to lose at least
a pound or two.
He's very chunky.
He's snoring.
He's doing that like
He's like dreaming and snoring at the same time.
Yes, he has two beds.
He's like Snoopy. He doesn't like that one.
How do I really feel?
He's a C.
He went from F to C.
There's a little too buttery at the end.
Oh, it's over Cantaloupe for sure.
It's over Pepsi for sure.
The same stream.
It's just in the corner.
I mean, they all win.
It's every single one wins.
There's no winner for best auto
moment. It's just anytime he's on
camera, it's fun.
It's best. Do we need to even
declare a winner? Can they all win?
They all win, I think.
But wow.
Whoa, actually, this is crazy.
Best auto moment of the year is
at 48%
of the vote.
Sleepy auto in
Jerma's arms. And then at
19% snoring in the cheaper
bed. And then 11%
is auto is a little chunky.
It always gets chunky.
What? Who is talking in my ear?
Who's what?
Hello, Jerma.
What's up, dude? I've got
a proposal for you.
I've already heard about it. People have been coming
over here. How's your stream
going, by the way? My stream?
Yeah. How's your stream going? It's going
great. It's going great.
How's the Call of Duty
campaign? How's that going?
You get through the first part yet? People love it.
I'm on the second level.
It's, it's, I'm quite good.
People are asking for hot tips
and I've been giving them out.
Okay. So, and what
can I do for you? I've heard this, oh, there's a 1v1
scenario that we're going to do. Yes, well, do you want
your stream back or not? I'm feeling Christmasy.
Yep.
I'm feeling, I'm feeling in the
mood. And you're feeling
in the mood for what, exactly? You want a 1v1
me and Call of Duty and I destroy you and I get
the channel back. Is that what it is? That's right.
That's your proposal? That's the proposal.
Yes.
So, let me, let me, let me just like make sure I break this down
completely. If I
beat you in a 1v1 in Call of Duty.
That's right. You will give me
the channel back. That's right.
No bullshit. I've set up the
lobby and everything. First to five,
best of three. First to five, best of three.
And you're not messing around or anything. This is for real.
Oh, no, no. I wouldn't lie to you,
Jerma. Is he lying? I don't lie.
You lie.
Do you, do you have me over, do, do, do,
do you get the information from him?
You should have it. Do you have it?
Yeah. Well, I, so, so if I win, I get the
channel back. If you win,
you get the channel back. Let's fucking go. Let's go
then. Let's go. I, I need
some, I need some support back here, please.
What do you need?
I need, excuse me,
I need a little bit of support here.
I don't know anything about Call of Duty. Time to focus up.
Thanks, thanks. Time to focus up. Look alive. Open your mouth.
Open your mouth. What is this, a team?
What are we,
boxing? Focus up. You're supposed to do it
very gently. We've done bro versus bro.
We know you're not the best gamer. You're going to have to focus.
Stop, stop, stop. Boxer dropped out. We need this.
Listen, listen to me. We need this. Quiet.
Quiet.
What's the loadout, what's the best loadout
in Call of Duty Modern Warfare? Can you get him off the fucking screen
before I puke? What is that?
Oh, thank you. I appreciate that. I think your play
style's a run and gun. Did you just put make-up
on me? What, submachine gun? What did you just do?
War paint. Did you just put war paint on?
War paint. This is going to be off for the rest of the
day now. What the hell?
You're ready. Just believe in yourself.
What's worse, having paint on your face
for the rest of the day or having him on your channel for the rest of the day?
Think about that. Come on.
Do or die. Hey, are you a fan
of Lugwig? Variety
streamer. Do you know Lugwig at all?
Hello? Do you know Atreyok at all?
Oh, you're talking to me. I'm sorry,
I'm setting up the game for you because you don't know how to play.
Alright, alright, alright. It's time.
Am I ready?
1 v 1, I get the channel back.
Alright, so first to five.
I'll put a ten minute limit on it. Can I get everybody
in here, please? I need
support, I need to be taught how to do this shit.
Tighten up, tighten up.
What's your class? What's your class?
I don't know what class means, Lugwig. Submachine gun.
Long, light machine gun.
Machine gun. I don't know what
any of this means.
Am I in the lobby?
Just focus, don't worry about it yet.
Why is Lugwig going to buy stuff in the stores?
He's buying things. How do I get this off?
This is going to be on all day. Look, it comes off easy.
It'll come off, it'll come off.
Did I get an invite?
Why are you buying the skin?
I was buying the bundle.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm the engineer. Oh, you were sitting here, sorry.
Extinguisher, that's gotta be...
Come on, come on, come on.
Can somebody get me a snack, please?
Alright.
Snacks!
Snacks! Snacks!
Snacks! Snacks! Snacks!
I don't want that.
I don't want that either.
You want me to chew it up?
I can chew it up for you.
Do you need water?
Okay, Jeremy, you get yourself a little juice box.
You get yourself some face paint.
Alright, go, go, go!
Everyone, I want to start a chant.
Are you ready?
Let's get this motherfucker!
Are you sure you're ready, Jeremy?
Go.
Your whole existence is on the line right now.
This engineer was on Facebook
for like the last probably hour.
Who have you been writing to on here?
Still one of the most popular websites in Europe
for like social media.
Alright, you ready? Let's go.
Let's go, extinguisher.
You're the extinguisher?
What is this? Nutri-grain bar?
What is this thing?
Fuel.
No.
Where are you running to, my friend?
Okay.
It's just waiting for host. Are you the host?
Yes, I'm the host.
You have to make the call.
Oh, I gotta send you another invite
because you don't know how to play.
I'm in the lobby right now, extinguisher!
Will you booty me?
You know what?
You start the back out of the lobby, invite him.
What the fuck? Invite him, fight on your turf.
And fight on my turf?
I'll play on your turf.
It doesn't matter the turf.
Not a lot of friends going on here.
Right there, that's him.
Where do I go from here? Join game?
Yeah, sure, join his game, fuck it.
Hey, what do you think about that? Are we ready?
I just backed out of the game.
Who are these people?
Get out of that lobby!
Invite him, invite him.
I see, I see, I'm joining your lobby.
Yeah, but I think he's in a lobby with a bunch of people.
Let's go!
Here we go.
Come on, Jarrah.
There's people in here.
Who are these people?
I think he's just in a regular lobby, he's in a free-for-all.
He's in a private lobby.
Who's in a private lobby?
How are the random people?
How do these people get in the lobby?
Moist bagel.
A friend-wisher doesn't even know how these people get in.
A friend request?
No, we're not doing that.
I need somebody from production to help me.
Oh god, it's going.
Let's see.
What happened?
You gotta set up a private body, maybe a customized one.
Invite him to your party.
It says you're in the main menu.
You're supposed to be a hacker.
And a free-for-all.
He's good at hacking, not Call of Duty.
Invite him to the party here.
It was one of you two.
I sent you in a DM.
I don't know who we did.
You are the one who's supposed to give it to production.
Let me tell you right now, don't ever ask me for a stream key in a DM.
That's actually stupid.
And I don't know why I listen to you.
Well, that's true.
It goes two ways.
We love it.
We love you.
Good news, he's in our lobby.
Good news.
Good news, everyone.
Let's win this, Turma.
I am still just thinking about how much I want to strangle you.
Right.
Well, okay.
You don't mean that.
We're trying to get a private match.
Multiplayer, create private match.
Can they answer this one question?
Classic.
He wants to ask you guys a question.
Is his face as red as his hair right now?
What's a good one? Knockout?
We want to go free-for-all.
Free-for-all.
Finally.
I mean, the hacker, seriously, I thought you could set this whole thing up.
Locked.
You've got a whole team of people.
Yeah, where's yours, by the way?
Where are all your team of friends?
Our friendship, our Christmas.
Right here.
Are we going?
Focus up, focus up, focus up.
More water, more water.
You keep spilling.
You keep aiming wrong.
Is this a good loadout?
Yeah, it's a submachine gun.
It's a run-and-gun, run-and-gun.
Keep on your toes.
Headshots or what?
You're not wearing a headset.
Hit him in the body.
Yeah, let's go.
What are you doing?
It's fine, it's fine.
Come on, Jermall, let's go.
We need the channel back.
Tighten up, tighten up.
We got PepsiCo on the phone.
We got everybody screaming at us.
There we go, that's one, Jermma.
Yeah, I can count.
Aiming a little low.
Where are you?
Keep the energy on him.
Are you camping?
He can hear you.
Because I need my fucking channel.
It's just Lane.
Are you Lane?
Now he can hear us and you fuck it up.
I see you, Jermma.
I see you.
This is really cool.
I'm not on his side.
Come on, come on.
He's made things interesting.
Focus, focus.
Iron, but get steel, baby.
I've always said that.
Your butt looks nice in those pants.
I don't know that thing.
Is this a bad idea?
You're lying down in the middle of the same spot.
There's a lot of openings.
Reduce the amount of entries he could see.
This might fuck him up.
Thank you so much, Ludwig.
Are you going to lay down the whole time?
I'm not going to lay down the whole time.
Let's go ahead and pound it right there.
You're not going to lay down again?
No, not anymore.
Running gun. Head shot.
Walk around a corner.
Go around a corner?
Look at you.
I don't know where the hell he is.
You have to go around corners safely.
Ludwig, I don't think you understand
that this guy's on my channel right now.
You don't understand if you fucking lose this game
you don't get your channel back.
I'm thinking of calling the channel The Extinguisher.
Twitch is not going to let you change my name to The Extinguisher.
I'm going to change it to The Extinguisher 986.
He's actually pulling a lot of numbers.
I've actually seen his viewership.
It went up since you were off.
How many viewers does he have on that channel?
He's got like 50,000.
400 million.
How many people are actually on that channel?
He's like a 30, 40K.
He's big. I actually asked if he was through an operating room.
That's it.
It's the first of five.
You're hitting me a little hard.
It is a flaw you have.
He does it a lot.
Wow.
First of five kills.
Two rounds. Three rounds.
Tighten up. Two more kills.
Maybe reload.
What?
I thought I automatically did that.
You're still not reloaded.
What are you talking about?
I pressed R.
What are you doing?
I'm stuck.
Okay.
Hey Hacker.
Hey Extinguisher.
Are you playing with a controller?
Uh.
He's playing with a controller.
Don't do this when you're talking shit.
It's first of five.
Three to three.
Drop arm.
You know where he is.
What are you doing?
This thing sucks.
What are you doing on top of that car?
Tighten up.
Everybody quiet in the room.
Shit. I don't want to press the button.
Get away from the bus, Jerma.
What? Don't go near the bus?
Stay away from the bus.
I'm walking around the bus.
I should hide under the bus to be able to find
when he walks by, right?
You're doing it though.
You're doing it no matter what we say.
It doesn't matter.
Man, if he came from behind
the bus right now.
He would kill you.
Extinguisher.
Let's bring it home.
That went down my entire body.
I need one more kill.
That's it.
One more for the channel.
One more. Come on, baby.
Are you nervous, Extinguisher?
The extinguisher is coming for me.
Is that what you're saying?
The extinguisher is...
Oh.
You fucking idiot.
Look at that.
That's your channel.
Best of three. It's not over yet.
It's actually my channel now, isn't it?
Oh.
Yeah, best of three.
You want two more chances?
Best of three? You said best of three.
I did say best of three. I'll give you best of three.
You said best out of three.
I did.
Are you nervous?
Look at your friends. Your friends are all
hands on faces.
They don't look like the Beach Boys anymore.
They look like the Beach Bums.
Look at them.
Go, go, go, go.
I'm ready. I'm ready.
I don't know what to do.
Go, go.
Wait, wait, wait. Back in.
You can do this.
I cannot hear anything you guys are saying, by the way.
These are noise-canceling headphones.
Look at him bring behind you.
They're worried.
I know.
Is this a good loadout?
Yeah. Good.
You think this is good? Okay.
Keep it up.
We could hit him up.
I think we could
sign him.
He's got charisma.
He's charming.
I'm walking this way.
What I like about him is he seems
like he'll stand by what he promises.
And I think that's
what a sponsor wants.
You got it, baby.
Keep it up.
What was that?
I thought you gave him the finger.
Hey, Extinguisher.
Deal with this one, bud.
Extinguisher.
Well, I like that you're calling me
Well, I don't know your name. It's the only thing you said.
You know my name.
You drained my bank account, too?
That would be nice.
Although I've heard you're $2 billion in debt.
That's fucking bullshit.
He's got host advantage, probably.
By the way,
I can hear every single thing
you guys say.
Let's go, Jerma!
Let's go, Big J!
Jerma!
You know, he lost someone.
You fell down.
I gotta tell you, I love shooting you
in your cute little butt.
First to five, you got it, baby.
Yeah, you are a fucking cod player, aren't you?
Press Q.
Q?
What's that?
What the hell is...
Ludwig, what the hell is that?
E?
Is this a grenade?
I think so.
You think so?
I don't know.
I just saw the bottom right.
But the icon doesn't look like a grenade.
It could be like a molotov.
Shh, I hear him!
Come into the room in the back,
near the car.
Hey, Extinguisher, if you come into the room with a guy
pointing a gun at the camera...
Son of a goddamn...
I need to get one kill!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, baby!
Are your palms sweaty?
No, they're actually very dry.
Thanks for asking, though.
Is it because you smudged the war paint,
do you think?
Could I reapply?
Get this, put it over there,
and don't do it again.
I'm getting fucking forward.
Come back.
Come back, season!
Holiday spirit.
That's what we need right now.
Stop touching me,
so I can focus.
I am fun!
This is so fun!
Oh, German.
How does it kill from here, right?
German.
Oh.
Reasonable.
Welcome to my channel!
The Extinguisher 986.
Go to break, just go to the elves.
Go to the elves.
What a disaster.
Do a fun holiday show,
and at least we still have
some other stuff to do, but
it's just so frustrating
knowing that I'm sitting up there trying to
just keep it together and do the awards,
and this extinguisher,
I kind of don't know what to do.
I could have been doing more awards if I needed to,
but it's just so fucking annoying.
I'm sorry, everybody, that you're supposed to be like,
Merry Christmas, happy holidays.
What is that?
No, no, he can't do it.
No, no, no, stop that, stop that.
Can you get me into it? Pump me in, pump me in.
Does he know?
I don't think he knows.
Oh, God.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
to Bugleberry's cooking segment.
Bugleberry, you can't, can you hear me?
What?
You can't do the segment right now.
We've got a situation here.
What are you talking about?
The channel got fucking compromised.
No, no, no, I'm going to do my cooking segment,
but what are you talking about?
I'm so sorry, dude, but
everything's, we're going crazy here.
That's not fair, that's not fair.
You told me, very specifically.
I know.
You said, oh, Bugleberry,
you can have one segment this year.
Oh, okay, you can do whatever you want.
This is my one segment, and you're going to take this from me?
I don't...
Why, exactly?
I don't want to, but the channel was hacked,
and we need your help right now.
Maybe if you could make some stuff happen,
you could cast a spell on his computer or something like that.
Maybe... What did you do?
I didn't do anything. What did you do?
I didn't do anything. What website were you on?
Let's look at your history.
Oh, what are you going to do?
Oh, a pornographic website, perhaps?
No. Is that what you did?
No.
I've been here for like four days, Bugleberry, please.
What do you want me to do?
Just help.
I don't have anything here.
I don't have any tools.
I don't have any of my spellbooks.
I came to make a holiday dinner.
Yes, I know.
You told me to leave all of my things at home.
You said, don't bring the spellbook.
You don't need it.
So it's not here. So what do you want me to do?
You're improvised.
Maybe you do... Can you do anything?
Maybe cast a spell?
I don't know what you can bring...
Bugleberry, can you please come on the show and make a turkey?
I'm sorry, dude.
I'm so sorry.
I don't have anything but time to try again.
I told you, yeah, we can make a turkey, but...
What is this for? Is this what you call a hacker?
Yes.
The channel has been compromised.
A hacker hacked the channel.
If you could do anything you can to help...
Engineers are useless, by the way.
I'm sorry, but you are.
What are you doing?
I'm going to do what I can, gentlemen.
Just hold on, hold tight.
Dude, you have no idea what this means.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.
What are you doing?
That's ketchup, Bugleberry.
What is he doing?
Cool, cool, cool.
I don't know what that is, but...
Everybody, I need you to stand back.
And that is production.
Stand back. Everybody watching, please be careful.
I don't know what could happen here.
I'm not entirely sure.
What are you going to do?
Don't do anything too weird, though.
Oh, my God.
Don't do anything too weird.
You all right?
What the fuck are you doing?
That's connected to the toilet.
That's not connected to anything.
Oh, God.
Can you feel it? Can anybody feel it?
I can. Tell them.
What?
You need to hold on to something.
All right, I'm holding on.
Oh, yes.
What is that? What is going on?
There we go.
What the fuck?
Hello.
Jesus.
No.
Put that down.
This is a sacrificial circle, Gerber.
Precisely what you wanted.
No.
What are you willing to give up?
I'm willing to hear it.
I'm nothing. I don't want to do anything.
Good shot.
Bugleberry, you could do something else, maybe.
Do something else.
What are you talking about?
Do something else. I don't want to do that.
Don't put the spell back in.
The spell is here now.
We need to sacrifice something that you care about very much.
Dude.
How about the presents under the tree?
No.
We will sacrifice something else.
Does a crew member have something that we can put in?
We're not going to sacrifice.
That's not happening.
It has to be something that you care about, Gerber.
Not something that anybody else does.
Let's go get those presents.
No.
Don't touch those presents.
It's the only way, Gerber.
Don't touch those presents. Those are my presents.
Do not touch them.
Get out of here.
No.
Please leave a couple.
This is my present.
Bugleberry, come on.
There's got to be something else you can do besides this.
Don't listen.
Don't listen to him.
Wait. Is he still there?
Bugleberry, wait. Stop.
Stop.
Can you hear me?
What the fuck, dude?
Those are mine.
I don't even know what's in those.
Pump me into him. Is he still there?
Bugleberry, can you hear me?
Don't touch.
Please leave a couple, please.
Oh, my God.
These are heavy.
I don't want to do this.
Anything else, please.
Anything else.
Gerber, there's no going back like I already said.
Oh, this is a new iPhone.
They get bigger every year.
Is it an iPhone?
Jesus.
Can you hear the screams?
I can. What's this one?
Oh, sounds like an Xbox.
Xbox.
Does it look like an Xbox?
That's my Xbox.
Maybe it's not.
Bugleberry, don't put that one in, maybe it's an Xbox.
Jesus.
That was juicy.
Oh, my God.
This one. Oh, a new sweater.
Is this possibly a sweater?
Oh, what size are you, Gerber?
Maybe I could wear it.
I'm a medium.
I'm going in. I'm going in there.
I'm going in.
Let me in.
Come on. Get off of me.
He must stick with it.
This is a double.
This is a DVD.
Two-part DVD.
Oh, no, this might be Final Fantasy VII
for the PlayStation 1, his favorite game.
That game sucks. I don't care.
Put that one in.
Put that one in. I don't care.
That's probably the only one I don't care about.
What's this? What's this one?
This one's making noise, Gerber.
What's in it?
You don't want me to put it in?
Don't put it in. Don't put that one in.
Leave me one present, Bugleberry, please.
One present.
Thank you. Thank God I get one.
Jesus.
How are you doing over there, Gerber?
I have no idea. I just feel sick.
I don't know.
What should I be feeling?
What are you doing?
That's two points, Gerber. Two points.
Two points, yeah. Bugleberry, I feel fucking sick.
Let's see. I don't even know what it was.
What was it?
Bugleberry, something's wrong.
How do you feel?
What the fuck was that?
Bugleberry, stop.
Stop. Stop it right. Please stop.
Oh, boy.
Hey.
I don't even know what's happening.
My chest hurts.
Is it even doing anything?
I don't think it's doing anything.
I don't think it's working.
Can you feel it, Gerber?
Can you feel it?
I don't know. I don't think so. Maybe.
What?
Nothing's happening.
What do you mean it's not enough?
I don't think it's happening.
I didn't get the channel half.
Now did I?
No.
You know what? Fine. You want power.
You want magical listeners.
I'll give it to you.
Stop.
Hello. Hello.
What's this?
A new box of chocolates.
Whatever it is, it doesn't matter.
Oh.
Don't ask me for anything ever again.
And by the way, if you invite somebody to a party
and you tell them to do something,
make sure it's what you actually say
and not this whole crap.
I don't want to swear, but I just...
Dude, easy on the language, please.
No, no.
I don't want to go home.
Oh, boy.
What the fuck just happened?
What happened?
What's going on?
Hey.
It's you.
It's you, motherfucker. I see you now.
I see you.
What do I do about this?
What do I do?
Oh, now you're scared?
That's why I had a magician.
I know a guy. You know hacking.
I got dark magic, motherfucker,
and I come for you now.
What did you do?
What is that?
I know we don't really know each other
and this is really strange.
It's really weird, everything going on,
but is your room cold right now?
It's very cold.
My nips are...
Do you have a heater here?
Yes.
I have something down here.
I don't know what this is. It's a swirling thing.
Do you have one of those in your room, dude?
Yeah, yes.
Okay.
I'll be honest.
This is kind of freaking me out.
Hopefully Bugleberry's okay.
Do we call someone?
I don't know. Hold on.
I put my hand in here.
What the...
Was that you?
I don't know.
Did it feel like someone slapped your hand?
It felt like somebody slapped my hand.
Did you touch me?
That was me.
You motherfucker!
How does that feel, huh?
Does that feel weird?
God damn it!
You don't choke me!
All right, man. You want to fuck around?
How does this sound?
Don't you...
I'm going to kick you in the goddamn face.
How does that sound?
Let go!
Put it back!
What is wrong with you?
Those were nice kids, by the way.
Yeah, they are nice shoes.
I'm glad you like them. You know what?
Look at you.
My camera's all twisted.
How do you feel about this, you piece of shit?
It's a piece of wood.
Yeah, it's a piece of wood. It'll knock your fucking teeth out.
What are you going to do with a piece of wood?
I'm coming in there and I'm going to...
I'm going to knock your head off!
Hold it right there, boys.
Santa!
This has got to stop.
This is not
the Christmas spirit.
What?
Santa!
Young man, get over here.
What do you mean?
There's a Santa here?
I mean, that's kind of funny.
There was nobody here before.
Put that stick down.
What?
I remember the last time you used that stick.
It's real.
It's him. It's really him.
That's a real Santa. That's a real Santa.
Dude, bro. This is a real Santa, I think.
We cannot have any more of this.
You're ruining Christmas with your dark magic
and your foul mouth.
I'm...
I don't know what to say, but...
I mean, the magic was...
was not with me. I hired somebody to come
and hang out. I don't know what to say.
Well, my magic-ometer
sensed it all the way from the North Pole
that something was not right in this place.
And I've come to set the
Christmas spirit right again.
Okay. Okay.
But that's going to require change
for both of your parts.
Okay.
What do you mean? What do you want us to do?
I want you to reconcile
as brothers.
I want an apology from both of you.
And we're going to start with
Extinguisher.
With me, Santa?
Yes. You get the chance to go first
to be nice
and to apologize to this little boy.
I'm out of my ground, man.
Well, when you put it like that...
I'm sorry, Jerma,
for hacking your stream
and playing the best game of Call of Duty
that I've ever put on board.
Yeah.
My bad.
Anything else?
You're not. I really do like
your butt cheeks.
There's no place for that here,
Extinguisher. Thank you.
This is a compliment, Santa, but
you're right. Well, I...
I mean, Santa...
He hacked my... He hacked my channel
and he tried to...
He wiped out my bank account
and he hacked the channel and I ruined
my Christmas show and it was really kind of annoying.
Selfishness
doesn't sound like an apology.
No, it's not.
Extinguisher, I am sorry
that I
called you a dork. I said that your
hacking abilities weren't very good. I mean,
you seem like kind of a nice guy.
And then you seem like pretty cool.
So, I'm sorry.
Really? Yeah.
Is that sincere, young man?
Yeah.
And that's... I also maybe want to say sorry
to the crew. I think I was a little
mean earlier. I've just been under
a lot of stress. And...
Stress? Stress.
And who else do you need to apologize to?
Maybe my mother, because she
thought I was going to be a doctor and I ended up being a clown
on the internet. But, I mean, still doing pretty well.
And sorry, mom.
I think that covers it.
Anyone else?
Jerma.
Oh, right. The two by four.
I'm sorry, Santa.
For... I didn't...
I didn't know. How am I supposed to know when I...
Excuses. But how am I supposed to know
that it was you? I didn't
mean to get you with that. I'm sorry.
Spit it out. I'm very sorry to
everybody. Okay. Well, that's
what I like to hear.
And Santa likes when you
make nice. Thank you.
This is very big. You're welcome.
I have a big candy cane.
And now, now that we have
reconciliation here,
I can finally grant
you your Christmas wishes.
You've been so
nice, extinguisher.
What would you like for Christmas?
Dude!
You got a Christmas wish, dude! What are you going to do?
Oh...
Oh, I got it.
Can you please,
please make me silver in League
of Legends?
It's about
time you got out of bronze. Yeah.
Did you get it? There you go.
I'm silver!
Thanks, Santa!
You're welcome, little boy.
It worked? Do you actually silver?
Yeah. Dude, that's sick.
So sick. Wow.
And now for you,
Jeremo. Money.
Oh, that's a good one. Greed. Ten million
at least.
Try again.
I wish
for the things to
kind of go back to normal. The way
they were before extinguisher
came on and hacked. I'd like
to do the rest of my awards
and just chill and have a good time.
The way things should have been, had you been nice.
That's true.
Ho, ho, ho! You're right. Santa can
do that.
Whoa!
Did it work? How do you feel?
I feel great!
Do you? It's all jiggly inside.
Hey, how about this?
I'll take you to lunch.
What? I've got at least ten
minutes on Friday if you want to hang out.
I've got fifteen minutes on Friday.
Wow.
I've got an hour on Friday.
Minimum.
That calls for a real sit down restaurant.
Do you like Ruby Tuesdays?
Yeah! Let's do it!
Alright! You and me are going to go!
It's good to see you
playing nice together again.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you! Bye bye!
Santa, thank you so much!
That was unbelievable!
Bye everyone! The power
of Christmas.
And the right magic. Not that dark stuff.
You can never go back to that again.
Well, I think Bugleberry might be dead.
Or he's gone. I have no idea
where he is, but
we might not see him for a long time.
And remember, the mouth speaks
out of that which fills the heart.
That's true.
So keep changing that.
And to all the community out there,
I want to remind you
that this is the season for giving
and forgiving.
And a Merry Christmas
to all!
Thank you, Santa!
Seriously!
And Extinguisher, I'm serious.
We should go hang out. I'm sorry.
It is the spirit for giving.
It is the spirit for reconciliation
and hanging out and having a good time.
Holy fucking shit!
What a disaster.
What was that?
I meant to say, Merry Christmas to all
and to all have a very
good evening and to all
good night and Merry Christmas to you.
And to all a good night!
Wow. Are we on the channel?
Are we on my channel now?
Are we good?
I'm so sorry, ladies and gentlemen,
but sometimes it takes the spirit of Christmas.
Sometimes it takes Santa Claus
to come out and right the wrongs.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are not
done. We are now
on the channel. We have control.
We're in fact just getting started.
So let's go into our
next category. This is
category number 11, by the way.
There are a lot more to do.
So, this is
Best Rant, and there's some
spillage here, and I'm gonna need
production
to maybe help me
eventually after this category.
Right? I'm not gonna say
any bad words. I'm not gonna yell
at anybody. Production,
I spilled some cocoa earlier
and
I may need a little bit of help
to clean it up. How's that sound?
There we are.
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, let's do this category.
This is Best Rant of the Year.
Here are your nominees. Thank you, Santa,
for fixing everything.
I get exhausted.
My brain goes like, alright, man,
that's enough. No humans are supposed to be doing this.
You know what fucking humans are supposed
to be doing? Humans are supposed to be
fucking picking up like a wheelbarrow
full of like logs
and just like slowly walking with it
and delivering those logs to the
community. And then like those logs
are used to build houses. And then there's also
like a baker and like a butcher
and humans aren't supposed to be
doing what we're doing right now. Humans aren't
supposed to be doing this. Guys, when
Ben Franklin was writing up the goddamn
fucking Declaration of Independence,
there was no guggity guggity in there.
There was no, oh yeah, we also need to make
sure to leave some room for guggity
guggity guggity guggity guggity.
There's no room for that, Ben.
Goat cheese is so gross.
Goat cheese is fucking vile.
Honest to God, I feel like everybody that eats
people pretend to like goat cheese.
You pretend to like it.
I'm so serious. I will die on this hill.
Goat cheese does not,
it tastes like dirt. Goat cheese is this
immediate, immediate
like
flavor.
It's like right when it touches your lip.
It's just like, oh, what's on this?
Goat cheese!
It's immediately, oh, goat cheese,
bro, I love it.
Oh, dude,
I'll eat a ton of it on a cracker. Of course
I will.
Yeah, right. What if
aliens don't have anything? Aliens
could just be like, oh, wow, you have
this thing over here that
keeps your food from spoiling?
Oh, on our planet,
fructose,
we have,
we got stuff.
What's that over there?
Wait, oh, it's a calendar.
What's that? You keep track of days?
Who knows, guys? The fact that you
can have sounds come out of your mouth
might be the most absurd thing that they've
ever heard. Hi, Mr. Alien.
How are you?
And their heads are going to
explode.
Exactly what I told you was going to happen. What?
What is this?
Why does this exist? This is magic
powers.
The game's fucking easy.
It's not even a hard game. Instant kill moves are stupid.
Delete them. Patch them out of the game. Instant kill
moves are fucking stupid. Delete them from the game. Instant kill moves, you should
never have to put those in the game. They're fucking stupid.
Nobody likes them. Nobody, not one person likes them.
Your health is just too low. He doesn't have any instant kill moves.
Okay.
If I, if I chop
you up in a meat grinder, and the
only thing that comes out that's left of you is your eyeball,
you're
you're probably dead.
You're probably going to
not you, I'm just saying, like
I'm not going to put you into a meat grinder.
I'm not going to put you
into a meat grinder.
Okay, we're going to take humans out of this.
If Alien Glob
GlobGlobGlobGlob1
fucking shoots a
disintegrating ray at Alien
GlobGlobGlobGlob2
if there's only fucking teeth
left, it's, it's fucking
you're dead. You're dead.
I've run my dishwasher
because otherwise it'll get
gross. I've
washed by hand.
I don't like that idea of taking, oh yeah
there's like a bunch of fucking like saucer
and like mess on my plate
just stick it in here and turn the water on.
No. I don't like the dishwasher. I don't like it.
And you know why I also don't like the dishwasher?
All the people question marking me right now.
So you enjoy
putting like your dishes in this thing
and then like for like
at least one to two fucking
hours, you hear
it's fucking obnoxious.
It's obnoxious. And it lasts for
an hour. An hour. Two
fucking hours of this.
Twenty-three.
Isn't that a scary number? I like that number. Twenty-three?
Hold on.
Scary thriller Jim Carrey
movie, the number twenty-three
is not based on
any actual real like folklore.
I am not fucking around.
I'm telling you the absolute honest to god truth.
I've been afraid of that number since I've heard that movie
and stuff. I don't know how old was I?
When did that movie come out?
Like twenty fucking years ago?
How old was I? I was probably like
I don't know. I don't know how old I
was. I probably was very influenced.
You were twenty-three.
What? Two divided by
three is six six six. That's what
I'm saying. What do you mean question marks?
Yeah. It's
actually biblically accurate scary
number. I don't want
the afterlife to be like this. Every
time people think of the afterlife. Oh heaven.
Oh my god. I'm moving on. They're
floating as a specter.
Oh wow. Look
at it. So Elizabeth's mist everywhere. Everything's
misty and you're floating. No
I don't want it to be like this. I don't want to meet
the caveman ancestor.
They're all going to be there.
I think we all think of like oh
grandpa and grandpa
and like Uga
and Uga
Uga is going to be there.
I don't want to go to hell either because guess what?
You know there's going to be somebody there
that's going to be like yeah yeah
it's fine. Everything
man. I'm glad to be down here. It's like
I don't want to be with the one
distant great great great uncle
that went to hell and hang out with him every
day. Oh that's going to be fun.
Guys
why is there why is there not
an option?
Should I even do this? I feel like everyone's waiting
for me to do this. Okay I'll do it
in one sentence instead of like
25 sentences.
So we're going to do that in one sentence
instead of doing a 25 sentence explanation of what I
mean by this. There is no add
to cart option when you're trying to buy
shit on Origin
for the Sims. There's like a hundred things
to buy individually.
I got texted by my bank
hey we've declined purchases. There's like all these
fraudulent purchases going through the EA
store. Like no that's me.
That's me and it's dumb.
You have to go through the checkout process on each
individual. Oh
one sentence. Shit.
I'm sorry.
I tend to go off the
reels and that's not
I don't know. I just I get on a
topic and I just don't stop.
And people clip it and then they send it
away. So ladies and
gentlemen your winner
for the best rant
of 2022
is
it wasn't even close.
At 54.7 percent
55 percent
is the meat grinder.
The meat grinder and then
humans are not supposed to be doing this at 17.6
alien panic
at 9.1.
It wasn't even close.
Look at the meat. Okay.
Let me defend myself.
The meat grinder category
the meat grinder rant was
one person
said something and I was pretending
like they were
it's a made up person. Right?
This person doesn't exist. When I
say you I'm talking about
you in general. Not you
watching right now. You in general.
You in general.
It's not. Oh I'm going to put
you in a meat. No I'm not
people going to clip that too. So I'm just going to stop
talking.
When I say you I mean just you in general
just you. Oh you know
if I put you into a meat grinder I'm
not saying you individual. You get it. You
understand. Moving right along
now here come the juicy
ones. These are the juicy
ones. There's so many categories left
we just get started. I tend
to do impressions and
some of them are very good
some of them are very bad. I think some of my impressions are
good. Although people would tell
me to do your impressions your impressions are terrible.
So we'll start with
the best we'll go to the worst after. This
is the best impressions.
I think I did a pretty
good job this year. This category
I mean people are doing that emote and I can see it.
The like blah blah blah blah blah my head is bobbing
around. Whatever.
You guys know what I mean when I say that shit though
All right, you have to.
I told Santa I wouldn't swear.
So I'm gonna say, what the shoot.
So here are your nominees for best impression of the year.
These are the good ones.
At least I hope they are.
Now, make haste to the tower and defeat the evil wizards.
Mermaid man.
Evil wizards.
No, we need to get into the boat and go get them, SpongeBob.
What are you doing, you old moron?
I am trying to do what it is a superhero must be doing.
Getting to the bank.
And who could forget getting it off there?
The all-knowing, there he is.
You drink?
The orange-blue chieftain of the Badlands.
The ever-knowing gold man.
The disgusting dung eater.
And of course, there's Sir Gideon up there.
The all-knowing, what's happening, my friend?
I would have voted for that one.
Meat, potatoes, and lettuce and fucking gravy.
Spinach and radishes.
And I'm alive and I'm human.
I like to eat, too.
And I like to have children.
I'm here and I'm coming.
It's like, oh, Perry the Paratapus,
I'm going to take over the entire world, Perry.
No, it's me, Dolphins.
But that was actually really, really good
and I would say that was probably the best one
you've heard anybody do.
Not showing anything under arrest.
I'm underwater?
Gentlemen, this is tobacco receive manifest.
Ever.
Look at that headlock there, see?
That chap over there joined.
Or by pay us this, is the local got me on the penis.
Before.
That's one voice.
Who's a pretty bird?
Who wants a kiss?
Tom Scott.
This water is electrified.
It will kill you if you stand within five feet of it.
Meow, meow, oh, Bowser.
Ah, annoying.
Oh, boys and girls, it's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something.
If somebody want to tell you to take drugs, always say no.
You see, Luigi tried to drink and do drugs one time
and I said, no.
And he said, Mario.
And I said, no.
Fucking God damn it.
And that's the bottom line, because Stone Cold said so.
Pretty good.
They're eating her.
And then they're going to eat me.
Oh my God.
Please, can you do a quick Seinfeld routine
about the word vast?
What even is vast?
What's that supposed to mean?
Vast.
Just say big.
Just say large.
Say big.
Why do we need names for so,
why do we have so many names to describe
what is effectively big?
I mean, if you want my vote, I'm voting for Alex Jones.
I don't think anybody does it.
Alex Jones, like, I can't.
I just, I gotta be really honest.
Find me somebody that can do that as good as I can.
People usually, you know, they go like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Find me somebody that can do that better than me.
I don't think you can.
That's my vote, that's what I voted for.
But your winner of the best impression of the year is,
of course, it's Alpenny the Platypus, Doof and Schmertz.
With 30% of the vote, that's a high one,
then Alex Jones right behind it.
16.8, not right behind it, pretty far.
Doof and Schmertz, Alex Jones, Doof and Schmertz.
It's a hard word to say.
And then democracy manifests subtitles at 12.3%.
Doof and Schmertz takes it.
I think I can do a pretty good job.
And now, obviously, I do a lot of these every year.
And we're not just gonna talk about the good ones.
We're gonna talk about the bad ones.
This is the worst impression of the year.
I don't agree with some of these.
Let's be real.
Some of these are a little, I don't like that character,
so I'm just gonna nominate it.
That's not how this works.
But just like the bad ones, they're also good ones,
and what you just saw.
Here are your nominees
for the worst impression of the entire year.
Did you do Jack Sparrow?
I don't know what that sounds like.
Fuck, I'm done.
But my career is over.
I'm ending my career.
It's over today.
Okay, so I got a letter.
Jerry, when you read this letter,
I will already be on the other side of the world.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry that I'm not the father you wanted me to be.
The rest is up to you.
Do your best and live a wonderful life.
You always will.
That's the worst George I've ever heard.
It's really not.
That's what I mean.
It's Gilbert Coffrey.
Hey, when I'm told I've been looking forward
to this for quite a long time.
Alpha's more popular than ever in the Mushroom Kingdom.
Wasn't that tourney yesterday incredible?
But if we want to keep the sport interesting,
we need some green players, you see.
Man, just show me folks who can hit the green.
Oh, whoa, wait.
That's not even that bad.
It really isn't. That's crazy.
That's all I had to do was like just clear my throat.
We need some fresh faces on the leaderboard.
Okay.
That was bad. That was a really bad.
I don't know if that was Toad or,
I don't know what game that was from,
but it was a bad impression.
Ooh, Skywalker, I must say, are you, are you?
Is that bad?
It really was one word elongated.
Wow.
You sound like the sweetest chef.
You have a Bobby Hill impression?
I'll try.
Yeah.
Hey, Dad, I'm sorry.
I can't, but I tried.
What does Cookie Monster sound like?
It's like, what does it sound like?
It's kind of like.
Cookies.
I love cookies, right?
Something like that.
Let me try it.
Let me go all in with it and see what happens.
This cookie is delicious.
I love cookies.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
There's the heavy from TF2.
Oh, yes, cookies.
That's not, that's not really, really not that good.
But I mean, it's, how do you even do it?
Let me try to do a dog.
Oh, Morty, we gotta be careful.
Put that back in there and we're gonna go back,
back in time to shave.
Actually, it is different.
Morty, Morty, we gotta be careful.
Guys, I've never seen all these movies.
I've never seen them.
I just know, I know Christopher Lloyd,
Christopher Lloyd, right?
His name's Morty, not Marty.
Marty, not, what?
Oh, I just dropped everything.
Do a Taz impression.
No, no, no, sponsor stream.
Ah, whatever, why not?
I was just about, okay, that Taz,
Taz Mania was just about to do that.
Somebody like hitman style,
like put a fucking piano wire on his neck.
Patrick?
Hey, SpongeBob, it's me, Patrick.
Oh yeah, SpongeBob, let's go have an adventure.
What was wrong with this one?
Does that sound like him, kind of?
Yeah, it does.
Why was it on here?
Enjoy yourself.
No.
It's this wide, strange world.
This realm has a way of getting right in the end.
What?
Okay, this one sucks.
This one sucks.
I like it.
This is bad.
I will be expecting many great things from you.
It will get hotter in ways you might not be able to imagine.
Geez, this one's the worst.
Does this win?
Voice is bad, voice is bad.
Shitty voice, worst voice.
Does that win?
You want my vote, it's that one.
Look, okay, you have to, I am live.
I don't know how many hours a year,
but if I'm gonna do an impression,
sometimes you get shitty ones, sometimes you get duds.
I don't think the George was bad.
Why that George Costanza was so bad, Jerry.
How?
Why would that be nominated that many times?
I think that one was fine.
Why was that so bad?
Question marks, that sucked.
Was it that bad?
I don't think it was.
I think you're mistaken here.
They were all bad.
The frog one definitely won.
If it didn't, then there's something wrong
with this community.
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner of Worst Impression
of the entire year is, what the fuck?
It's not even in the top three.
Toad was 23.2% of the vote.
And then Jack Sparrow at 18.9,
and then Patrick Starr at 10.9%, one, two, and three.
What?
That frog was so bad.
How was that not at like 80% of the vote?
All right, time for the meaty categories.
These are the ones that are full of flavor.
I'm gonna take my time with these because I,
this is my ego stroke here.
It's time for an ego stroke until this one, but you know.
This next category is one that hits very deep to me,
and probably to those of you watching.
This is for the best joke
taking more than five minutes to set up.
And what that means is that anything that took
at least a few minutes to get rolling, okay?
At least a few minutes to get rolling.
So there were a lot of nominees,
a lot of good ones that I think, and you're swearing.
Santa is already across the globe right now.
He's a very busy person, so it'll be a very busy man.
Ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees
for the best joke of the year
taking more than five minutes to set up.
Toad wasn't even bad, stop.
I think that would add some atmosphere
if like after every major kind of area,
and every puzzle was like music played,
and you just heard.
Scorn.
Have a kind of cool leg.
Jesus.
Oh, what the fuck?
Scorn.
Blood.
Lots of fucking blood.
Lots of blood.
That's a lot of blood.
Scorn.
I have to be better at fucking acting.
True.
Scorn.
I'm sorry, I can't do it.
I look like a different person.
Leave it on so the Twitch thumbnail gets it.
All right, fine.
Make this the thumbnail.
No, dude, I...
It's so fucked up.
This is fucking insane.
I think we're going a little too far.
I think we're going too far.
Okay, are you ready for the culmination
of what is the thumbnail right now?
Here you go.
Welcome to hell.
Now listen, buster.
Once we get down here,
I'm gonna make sure that we take care of this
as soon as possible.
Now, I don't get that move at all.
That move is absolutely unbelievable.
It's one of those moves that you can't do anything about.
And I'm telling you, yeah.
But you know what else ridiculous is that?
Playing soon.
They're gonna be like, I can fly eventually too.
How many fucking moves do you get before you...
I'm sorry about that, folks,
but what I meant to say was,
how many moves do you get to do in a row
before gosh darn it, you...
How many moves do you get to do gosh darn it
before fucking wrong thing?
Wrong thing.
All right, here we go.
I made the medic.
I'm good to go.
Do I need to be killing these people?
I'm not eating bugs.
I wouldn't eat bugs if my mother asked me to.
What about a doctor?
I don't know, what does the doctor look like?
Is he six feet tall, 200, lean cut?
What does he look like?
And he's so fit, he just got done cycling
and he's got cycling shorts on and a lab coat.
Stop sharing your fantasy.
Just got done with a quick bike ride.
Kickstand, comes in, just like sweat,
just glistening off his forehead.
So, what brings you in today?
And I'm like, oh wow, look at that,
crazy, that's why you got that, what a head of hair.
Yeah, haven't had a headache, by the way, in a long time.
Different music.
You wanna eat some bugs?
We're watching you in a bar, German,
you wanna do something wacky?
I like this one.
Hey, this one goes out to all y'all in the bar.
Hey, three, two, one, let's go.
Mm, green tea.
They can't even hear me.
Should I try to communicate?
Hey, you, wait, look.
Hey, everybody, hey.
I was on screen at a bar, for those back there
that don't know what's going on.
I was typing and shit.
Yeah!
What about a Twitch moment badge for longest stream?
Wait, can I do that?
You were here for the longest stream
I've ever done on this channel.
13 hours, 19 minutes, and 41 seconds.
Ain't ever gonna happen again.
Should I do another moment?
It's not, ever.
Like the 200 people that just left?
You fucked up.
13 hours, 27 minutes, and six seconds.
I think that deserves a quick bite of pizza.
Hey, man, I can't believe you made it.
Was I on drugs?
Like, what was I doing here?
13 hours, 36 minutes, and 52 seconds.
God, man, I can't believe.
You were here.
Don't ever call the sus guy at 3 a.m.
Hey, dude, can you speak up?
I'm in a construction site.
I would vote for this one.
I love this one.
Okay, hold on.
Why would you even go live?
Just wait till tomorrow.
Like, who cares?
Fucking keep your stream off.
Okay.
What the fuck?
What am I supposed to do?
Guys, what does that mean?
Whoa, a guy.
Hold on, watch out.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I gotta get this kill.
Gotta get this kill, gotta get this kill.
Oh, I died.
Shoot.
What if I just like,
ready to fall asleep on stream?
All right, I'm gonna pretend to fall asleep on stream.
I think this is in both categories, by the way.
Dude, wicked fucking tired.
Like, had a long day.
I hope it wins both.
And then you're woken up by the jump scare.
It might be a good idea to make sure
everyone's in a proper place.
Interestingly enough, you guys made it really awesome.
Fuck.
Yeah, yeah.
So, speaking of which.
Such a bad payoff.
I am a new man.
I'm here to do something that I said
I would never do, and that's to play Destiny 2.
I love this part where he says the doctor.
I know, I said I'd never do it.
But here we are.
Shpee.
That's the Shpee Ship.
We're taking the Shpee Ship to war.
You're, you're, you took everything from me,
even though it's really actually not that bad of a character.
And I'm gonna, I'm gonna haunt you for the rest of your life.
You better run, and you better never,
you better never look back.
Is this Scooby-Doo Van?
Is this the mystery machine?
It's too dark.
Well, that was quite a year.
Those are your top jokes voted by you, nominated by you.
Let's find out.
Sorry, I just punched you.
Can I get some of this off my face too?
This is gonna be permanent.
I just did it again.
What the hell am I doing?
Ladies and gentlemen, the best joke of the year.
Taking more than five minutes to set up is,
oh, it's an upset.
It's an upset.
This is an upset.
With 25% of the vote, 25%, the ultimate thumbnail.
The huge thumbnail wins.
And then scorn, far away at 12.6% of the vote, far away.
And then sleeping to five nights at Freddy's
with 10% of the vote.
That's kind of an upset.
I thought that scorn, all the scorners in the chat here,
probably gonna be pretty upset about that.
Well, we did the good one.
So why don't we do the bad one?
If you think that I nail it every time, you're wrong.
I have a tendency to, there's a couple of duds every year.
A couple of duds, not every joke is funny.
I don't expect them to be.
But how do you know if something's gonna be funny
if you don't do it?
Ladies and gentlemen, here are your nominees
for the worst joke of the year.
Taking five minutes to set up.
What if I just like,
pretended to fall asleep on stream?
That's right, there it is.
All right, I'm gonna pretend to fall asleep on stream.
I'm gonna put a text on the bottom that says like,
dude, wicked fucking tired.
Like, had a long day.
And then you're woken up by the jump scare.
It might be a good one,
but it's probably great to get interestingly enough.
Fuck.
Yeah.
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
Did you click spectate?
It's on the bottom left.
No, I clicked a goddamn arrow.
Where is it?
I don't know how I got in this Discord call,
but I need somebody to help.
I got the wrong server ID, I think.
What the fuck is that?
I'm gonna have to go, I think.
Guys, I think I got in the wrong Discord call.
I don't know how I got in here.
I got the wrong server ID.
I don't know what's happening.
If somebody can troubleshoot with me,
I think I have to go up here.
Who is that guy?
What a weird guy.
This guy's weird.
A lunatic.
Was that somebody in the call?
Who was that?
Oh shit, I didn't know it was still on.
It's been on for hours now.
I forgot your old voice.
Can we ban Iron Giant?
No.
All right.
Well, all right, we just need to figure out
a solution to our problem.
I don't fucking care if we lost, I'm doing the joke.
Yeah.
What's up, Jack?
That was pretty good.
That was phenomenal, Jerma.
Oh, just one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit, one hit.
He's dead.
Okay, we're good, good, good, good, good.
Goddamn.
Woo.
Hey, what up?
How's it going?
What's up, Doc?
I just bit my tongue in half.
We're in costume.
I'm Mercy from the Overwatch 2.
And who's that?
And hey, how are you?
It's me, Deadpool.
It's nice to see everybody.
Oh my God, it's so good to have you here.
Yeah, special guest here.
So where do we start?
I don't know, man.
I just showed up.
I just got the call.
Yeah.
They were like, hey man,
on Charlie's show.
I'm like, I love that guy.
Of course I'm going to be on that show.
I knocked out that motherfucker in the parking lot,
by the way.
He looked at me weird.
No, that sounds exactly what he deserved.
I'm like, I got to him.
Show him your high kick.
Yeah.
I went like this.
Hey kids.
Soda.
This sucked so bad.
Nobody move.
It's starting to lag.
It's starting to lag out.
I actually can't, I'm starting to get sick, I think.
I'm going to get sick.
I'm at like 20 frames a second.
Oh God, it's getting sick.
Here we go.
Soda said embarrassing.
Oh shit.
Oh shit, this is bad.
Actually be careful.
This might actually be flashing lights and stuff.
I'm not kidding.
Half these awards are embarrassing.
Okay, here you go.
You ready?
It's time for the latest episode of Breaking Bad.
This is fucking stupid.
That was so bad.
This is fucking dumb, man.
This is dumb.
If Jerma reads this, he has to do a pushup on stream.
Oh fuck.
I would have voted for Five Nights at Freddy's.
That's what I would have voted for.
But some of those I don't think deserve to be there.
I really don't.
Breaking Bad was just, I don't know.
I was just reaching at that point
because we were on the high of Scooby-Doo.
What's new, Scooby-Doo?
Coming after you, gonna find that.
And it's like, wow, this is so much fun.
I'm having so much fun.
Oh, what are the TV shows?
What are the television shows can we do, right?
Eh, I was reaching on the high.
Ladies and gentlemen, your winner
for worst joke of the entire year.
The worst joke of the year is
with 32% of the vote, someone got in the Discord.
Someone got in the Discord and it wasn't me.
Oh, someone's in the Discord.
Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's was 22%,
but hold on a minute.
So number two is Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's.
Number three on best of the year
was Sleeping to Five Nights at Freddy's.
So it was top three on here and top three on here.
You guys need to make up your mind.
And then doing pushups was 16.8%.
I would have voted for that one, probably.
The Breaking Bad one was pretty awful,
but you know, I'm not looking forward
to these next couple of categories.
These videos are probably 10 minutes long.
Something about the worst and best noise categories
this year, I mean, the mods went through it.
Me and Holly went through it.
We had to narrow this down.
Best and worst noise of the year,
there were 60 nominees until we really had
to get rid of some.
I think we brought it down to like 25 in each category.
So strap in, turn your volume down
because here are your nominees
for best noise of the year.
Or turn your volume up if that's what you care about.
Jesus.
Oh, what the fuck?
Score.
No!
One thing I can hold, I can hold the Wilma for.
Wilma!
Fucking long, dude.
I tried to walk over to my water in VR.
Hold on, no, that's not how that works.
Oh, I got a drink too.
That's pretty sus.
There was a cricket outside last night.
I swear to God.
I always wanted to record it,
like just get audio recorded
because this thing was so loud
and it was going super speed.
It wasn't, brr, brr, brr, brr.
This guy was looking for somebody.
It was like, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr.
Just like, what is it?
It was a hurt.
It was like static.
I couldn't stand it.
You know what sound that makes too.
It's like.
You just like that
because it sounds like the teacher noise.
Whee!
I can put it over my head.
Moving an amount of water from one room to another.
And go like this.
Should I do this?
Okay, I'll do it.
No, I just heard that in my head.
That hurt.
I heard somebody laugh off camera.
This is the Tasmanian devil in the electric chair.
Okay.
This doesn't sound right at all.
And let's do a scream test.
Wee!
Fixed it.
How can we look plastic today?
I mean, I don't feel plastic.
Two, two, one up.
That was pretty good.
Fuck.
Oh no.
It's one of those.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
You're wearing red because you're the imposter.
Yes.
When I'm lying in my death bed
and I'm connected to like, you know what?
I'm like 90 or something.
Like a hundred.
And everyone's like gathered around the bed
and everyone's like, oh, let's just say goodbye
to grandpa, right?
You bet your ass that I'm gonna be like.
You bet your fucking ass
that's the last thing I'm leaving you with.
Give me, give me, give me, give me.
This is sucking me up.
How many people are here right now on the channel?
Do I have a number?
65.
There's 65,000 people here.
And you just got subjected to that.
So, should I apologize, or should we wait?
Should we wait for this one?
I'm gonna hold my apologies till this one.
Ladies and gentlemen, the, oh, I may have ripped it.
The winner for best noise of the entire year.
Was it ever gonna be close?
Let's spam it in the chat.
You know what it is, spam it.
I'll do it if you spam it.
Mm-hmm, scorn.
With 39% of the vote, scorn absolutely killed it.
Gimme, gimme, gimme was only 15.
Scorn absolutely dominated this category.
And then, are you the imposter was three.
So, scorn, a scorn sweep right there.
40% of the vote almost.
39.7% actually, which is, that's a lot.
So, to the almost 60, 70,000 people that are here right now,
I apologize for this next category.
I apologize in advance.
I said a lot of sorrys already,
but it's time for another one.
I'm sorry about this category.
Most nominees, I think, total.
That had to get dwindled down,
but we have a best noise, we have a worst noise.
They could just be the same category.
I should just do a thing where it's just noise of the year,
because why even have two categories?
Here are your nominees for worst noise of the year.
It's just, you know what I mean?
It's just the, it doesn't even lather up either.
I'm so, that was bad.
You've seen me do it, like a hundred times.
You can't dodge them all.
He's like, he's turning.
Oh shit, he's turning.
He just growled at him.
Wrong game, wrong game from software, wrong game.
Like some people eat a lobster,
like it's literally the last thing
they're ever gonna eat in their entire life.
And they like,
what's in here?
And it's just like, God damn it, what are you doing?
Oh, there's some still in there.
And I just, I don't like it, I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
It's revolting.
It's absolutely fucking revolting.
How about you fucking relax?
Young Madduck, apprentice to Hunwit, the dream chanter,
removes his instrument from its case.
His features, composed, take on a startling dignity.
Let's hear it.
Oh!
What, this is on here twice?
How many times was this nominated?
Can I just say this is the worst moment of the whole year?
I can say that, right?
It's my channel.
Wait, it's from the ghost.
That's it?
It goes like, I just threw one of those nerf,
you know those nerfs, whistlers?
The thing that like,
Brett Favre was in the commercial and he threw it like,
I can throw this a hundred yards.
And it goes.
I just threw one of those.
I know what this is for.
We're all the way over here.
So.
What's wrong with you?
My baby, my baby, I only chose.
Hold on.
No.
Oh.
I'm sorry, I'm really in production.
Probably fucking just cringed.
Did you guys hear that?
What the fuck was that?
There is recency bias, I think, on this one.
We have some recency bias, I think.
I don't think,
I can literally see it through the paper, by the way.
I peeked.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the worst noise of the entire year,
recency bias, come on.
The multi versus squeal at 20% of the vote,
not that bad.
Growls at chat with 18.8.
And I don't even, I don't know what this one is.
Suck, snort, wheeze, cackle.
Do we even know, what is that one?
I was trying to watch, but I couldn't even,
I don't know what that one is.
Very good to know.
A third most skipped category.
13% of you that took the test did not take this one.
You're like, fuck it, I don't wanna hear that.
I don't care.
Which makes sense considering there's so many categories.
And okay, but multi versus squeal.
Hey, multi versus is a great game.
You should try it.
You know what?
Can we check in with the puzzle room?
Let's take a look at the puzzle room.
How's the puzzle, the puzzler's doing?
No one's doing anything.
Have they not done any of the puzzle?
Zero, hold on.
There's only one person doing it.
I'm going in there.
There's only one, they're all just like eating sandwiches.
I need to see the progress.
Oh, God.
I'm not gonna be angry.
Hi everybody.
It seems as if there is,
it looks like you've blocked out some areas.
Can you get this?
Where's the camera?
Can you see this over here?
They have one edge of one of the corners.
What have you been doing in here?
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
What is this?
You playing cards?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
What?
Santa said to be nicer.
So if you could please finish one section.
This was a lot of money.
This cost a lot of money.
You heard Ludwig and you heard H. Rucker.
By the way, where the fuck are they?
Sorry if it's worth.
You know what?
They're drinking and they're drinking too.
Deal me.
You want to go?
Blackjack, you and me.
Who wants to go?
You and me?
Blackjack.
I'll be the dealer.
Where are the cards?
Let's go Blackjack.
What are these comically huge cards?
Hey, by the way, is this the Ace of Clubs?
Nope.
That would have been fucking insane if it was.
You want to go Blackjack?
Ready?
You want to play Blackjack?
Why did you write this?
You wanted to see that movie?
In here.
You just wanted to see Avatar 2 The Way of Water.
We don't pay us enough to go watch it ourselves.
What does this one say?
Send hot cups of, that's a funny joke.
My name is Danny Elfman.
Please hurry.
I actually don't get it.
Do it for Puzzle Girl.
Who's Puzzle Girl?
You.
What are we doing exactly?
Do it.
Okay.
You ready?
Everybody here is being, by the way,
everybody here is being paid.
Just want to make sure everyone understands that.
How much you bet?
Yeah, I don't want the bank to take care of you.
It's like 600 bucks.
Right there is eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13.
That's 14.
What are you going to do?
Versus a, by the way, can you see this?
I got a 10 showing here.
What are you going to do?
You're going to hit.
That is eight, five, 10.
That's 18.
You're going to stay?
Staying.
Okay.
Don't look.
17.
Stop!
Give me that.
Give me that toy.
Don't give it to him.
Give me, Santa, if you're watching,
I'm just being funny.
Give me that toy.
I've made sure to not.
Five, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30.
35, 40, 45, 50, 55, 60.
You just made $60.
Woo!
Gonna do another category.
Excuse me.
Merry Christmas!
What do you mean you can't do?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can't do math?
What happened?
I can't do math.
Did I get it?
Wait.
Count those cards.
Wait, hold on a second.
This is 17.
That's 10.
18.
What are you talking about?
She won.
What do you mean you can't count?
That's literally 18 versus seven.
What are you talking about?
I'm a man of my word, so guess what?
All the elves in this area, you're going to split $60.
Woo!
Elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves, elves.
13 elves.
Ladies and gentlemen, 13 elves divided,
60 divided by 13 is?
$100.
Yeah!
Each.
It's like two bucks each.
Hey, how about this?
We'll double your pay.
How much they were getting paid in the end is good.
Whatever.
I mean, they were paid to do a puzzle
and they didn't do it.
Let me make sure.
Let me be very clear.
They were paid.
They were all, those people were paid to be here.
They were all paid to be here to do a puzzle.
How much income is that worth?
I'll double their pay.
Fine.
Yeah.
How about this?
Hey elves, can you hear me?
Elves, you can hear me, right?
How about this?
You get one section done.
And I mean, even a border.
And I'll quadruple your pay.
I wonder if they'll do it.
I will five times your pay.
Get a border done.
100 each?
Look, now they're all standing.
Now they're all ready to go.
They're like, holy shit, let's go.
They were all sitting before.
Now, hey, can we give it up for the elves?
In the chat, give it up for the elves.
You know, hey, hey, hey, you know what?
Hey, hey, let's five times their pay for fucking no reason.
How does that sound?
I'll do it.
Easy.
Do the puzzle.
That's what you're here for.
And I may have almost hit somebody in the face
with that turkey that I threw.
All right, we're at the next category.
This is best one guy moment.
One guy, there's a lot of people here.
I imagine some of you don't know what the hell this means.
A one guy is when somebody kind of derails the stream.
I will see it, I will comment on it,
and it changes the outcome of the rest of the day.
It's not just, oh, yeah, yeah, I read a comment.
No, no, no, no.
A one guy moment is you've changed
the course of history completely.
Here are your nominees for best one guy moment of the year.
I'm not gonna encourage this behavior,
but I'm gonna tell you something right now.
Don't fucking, this is not to be encouraged,
but it was just like, what the fuck, man?
Somebody asked what the baseball stream is.
And I said, whatever.
And then like, it's been like five minutes.
It's been like at least five minutes.
Somebody like added that person, I think,
and said he's gonna shove an entire baseball
up his ass on the stream.
This person's name too, yeah, what the fuck?
Their name was Ball Fondler, okay?
Okay.
Remember, you're on the website.
For collecting all of them.
What?
I don't want to stifle the intrinsic-
You're on the QR code?
What?
It's taking this friend of thumbnails.
Is it there?
All right.
What?
All right, now put the tarantula in my mouth.
Put the tarantula in my mouth.
I'm gonna be like shocked that it's in there.
You know what I mean?
Like.
I keep pulling.
The dev, the dev is even sick of this joke.
The dev is like, all right, it's kind of funny,
but like fucking hurry up.
I mean, we have to summon the person
that's called Barf Drinker, okay?
And then that's it.
Oh my God, I'm gonna get BM'd, aren't I?
It's so stupid.
He's throwing rocks at me.
All right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I'm not gonna let this happen.
Oh my God, I'm dead.
I can't believe this.
We're watching you in a bar, Jerma.
Do something wacky.
Hey.
Hey, this one goes out to all y'all in the bar.
Hey, three, two, one, let's go.
Mm, green tea.
They can't even hear me.
Should I try to communicate?
Hey, you, wait, look.
Hey, everybody, hey.
One, two, three.
Yeah.
Oh, I wanna show this too.
Hold on.
Somebody actually made this.
These are really romantic candles.
No, it probably stinks up here.
I, gosh, I filled the room with red candles
like you wanted.
Gary, you fucking idiot.
Did you have to get the red cinnamon apple candle
from Yankee Candle and put it in every room?
Somebody said just eat a handful.
That'd be so fucked up.
You'd probably have like,
you'd probably have like a fucking like mental breakdown.
It's not designed for that.
Eat a handful.
It'd be fucking disgusting.
I'm kind of curious.
I'm curious, let's go.
It tastes like hamburger meat.
Do you want Mario drug PSA?
Hoo, b-ah-hoo, b-ah-hoo.
Whoa.
Hi, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Super Mario.
We've made a lot of jokes here today.
We've had a lot of fun.
And I'm an actor.
But let me just be the first to tell you that,
you know, it's not fun.
What is not totally b-ah-hoo, drugs and alcohol.
This is by somebody in the community.
Are they comfortable with me sharing their name?
I don't want to share their name if they're not comfortable.
Ah, but anyways, they discovered a new way
of isolating viruses that kill
antibiotic resistant bacteria.
Somebody in this community.
And the first one I discovered using this method,
I named after germa.
This is apparently it fucking working.
Against bacteria, antibiotic bacteria resistant shit.
That's me in there.
That's me taking care of that.
I'm in there and I'm getting all of those
fucking molecules and I'm destroying them.
Make a sandwich with wood.
Make a wood sandwich.
I can't, I can't.
Submit this.
Play for now.
Okay.
Fucking quit the goddamn game.
I exited the fucking game.
What the fuck is happening?
If Jerma reads this, he has to do a pushup on stream.
One, two, three, seven.
Oh, fuck.
The ring light around your neck.
If I put the ring light around my neck,
it could actually fit.
That would be fucking stupid.
Wait a minute.
Nice swag, thanks.
I was told that if I spin a hundred times at $10,
starting with a thousand dollars on this slot machine,
that I will be able to get to 10,000 plus dollars.
There's a person in chat here who is putting
their stream chat life here.
They're going to be banned from the channel
if it doesn't work or they're gonna get VIP'd if it does.
Three, four, five.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
Hello.
Yeah, and guess what?
You can hear me, huh?
You can hear me pretty well.
Not like it was before.
What the fuck, dude?
I'm not gonna drink a, hold on.
All right, hold on.
Let's tweet that.
How long is this fucking?
Yeah, so hopefully it sounds all right.
These things are pretty cool.
These things, let me try a scream test.
Can I try, can I try, hold on.
Can I scream?
Can I scream in your ears?
I'm gonna scream in your ears.
They should fucking remove geometry from school.
Teach people how to do their taxes.
I got some soft locked?
How?
No, I'm not.
Someone tell Jerma I can tell them how to fix their save.
How do I do it?
That's so funny.
How do I fix my save?
Try X560Y330.
New tweet.
No, wait.
Z330.
Oh, Dev, looks like you're having a little bit of trouble
with geometry, aren't you?
Looks like the Dev is having a little bit of trouble
with geometry.
Dev, when was the last time you were in fucking high school?
When was I?
I am gonna get so validated right now.
I suck at math.
I am in my 30s.
I haven't had to do this for years.
Go look at the tweet right now.
I'm gonna fucking, I'm framing this.
I'm literally going to frame that tweet from Dusk Dev.
No, I don't want, all right.
Can I just delete all the weapons besides the shotgun
and the, I don't wanna like, oh, right, right, right.
Yes.
Oh, sorry, that was loud.
Unequip all of your weapons.
That is definitely the way.
Yes, unequip all of your weapons.
As the voice actor for this fight, making fun of me.
Bro, that looked like Battle Chess.
You can turn me back on.
Battle Chess.
Oh, that's, oh my God.
You just ruined Dark Souls 2 for me forever.
You just ruined Dark, I can't even play this again.
Andy funny voices.
You said that wrong.
No, no, no, no, no, excuse me, I gotta correct you.
That's funny voice Andy.
Andy funny voices.
Andy funny voice, I love that.
That's my favorite comment of the week.
That's so, I love that wording.
Time that person up for five seconds.
If you lose, you have to get one of the gyros from Arby's.
I love this, this was so fun.
This was so fun.
Grossest fast food item.
You know what's crazy?
I don't want to eat fucking Arby's.
I don't want that at all.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
I'm going to be silent now.
Oh shit.
Oh no, I don't want to go to Arby's.
I did it.
Sorry, Arby's fans.
Not tonight.
Causing havoc on the highway.
We're on break core for this.
Restart, restart the mission.
Restart the mission.
This is fucking with my head.
Imagine if the police were listening to this.
It's too fucked up.
So there are a lot of funny people in this community.
I've known this for a long time.
This is not a secret.
The stuff that some of you guys come up with is insane.
I'm just sitting here watching and laughing along with you.
I couldn't ask for a more fun community.
Seriously, I love it.
Your winner of best one guy.
Remember one guy, you know who that is?
We all know, come on.
Your winner with 48.8, 49% of the vote.
It's Ball Fondler.
Of course it is.
Ball Fondler, congratulations.
You won best one guy moment of the year.
And then after that, 10%,
day one Elden Ring played at the bar.
And then 9%,
Stanley Parable Dev adds a spider into your mouth.
Barf Drinker, you would have had my vote Barf Drinker.
You were 1.7% behind that in fourth place.
This was one of the most least skipped categories.
Congratulations Ball Fondler
for making an unbelievable moment of the stream.
Ball Fondler has been banned like three times.
Ball Fondler's comments since then.
Do you know what they are?
Play Skyrim.
Okay, dude, are you gonna play Skyrim?
Hey, play World of Warcraft Dragon Flight.
I'm not gonna do probably, well, Skyrim maybe.
All right, moving right along.
We are getting to the top seven or eight categories
and they're getting juicy.
This next one, this one's got a lot of nominees.
What is it?
Yeah, congrats Ball Fondler, you made a fun moment.
Best scare moment of the year.
Horror games, jump scares,
scariness, anything that's freaked me out
could be nominated.
Here are your nominees for best scare of the year.
No, I just was doing that to freak out, you know,
like, you know, viddy, you know what I mean?
Ah!
Hi, I'm just playing, I was doing my task.
I started to like look this way and this eye,
I went like, I went reverse cross,
I went frog eye for a second.
Did he leave the room?
Holy God, this guy sucks.
Ah!
Back, but this, ah!
God, I'm so sorry, holy shit,
that was like the worst thing that ever happened to me.
What the flying fuck are you doing, lady?
I'm just going up the stairs,
I don't give a shit if he hears me.
Oh!
I thought he was downstairs.
Oh my God, that was the worst thing ever.
That was probably the worst thing ever.
Ah!
In a circle.
That was the chicken, that was the fucking rooster.
That was a rooster, that was actually a rooster.
I don't know what that means, but whatever.
Jesus Christ, dude.
Where is he?
Whoa!
Oh, the fucking thing, the drape.
I thought like a tentacle came down and grabbed me.
What the fuck, dude, why?
Now I'm like, I'm all cracked out now.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Ah!
It's like a monster.
It's just sound effects, it's not even, nothing here.
There's nothing here.
Oh my God, it's a bat.
Hey!
I got a frying pan.
Oh shit.
I have what's it called, flash.
I could throw it at everyone.
I've got six minis.
Oh!
Run, I'm sorry, I don't know how to skip this run.
I don't know, I went in the dumpster.
It's okay.
I thought you were getting killed.
No, I thought I was dead, dude.
I was like, what the fuck?
Somebody like sniped me.
It was terrifying.
Oh!
That would be a fucked up start to Mickey Mouse's clubhouse.
Where do I go from here?
Okay, turn it off.
Turn that off, close it up.
What?
I'm wearing the same sweater too.
I have the same clothes on.
Relax, holy shit, dude.
Are you kidding me?
This is not even scary.
Did I just fake that?
No, I really didn't, I swear to God,
but like that was way over,
I haven't played a scary game in a long time.
Oh my God, how am I alive?
I am absolutely, I was like, what are you pointing at?
It's a cliff.
What?
Jesus.
I just shot down my computer.
I think I shot my computer.
I think I shot my computer down.
Wow, a lot of scares this year.
A lot of scares.
I wanna know what you guys picked.
No fanfare, let's go.
Yeah.
It technically happened last year.
Wearing the same clothes.
The volume warning puppet combo scare with 20% of the vote.
It's the one where it looked like I saw a mouse
go through the bottom of the screen there.
Yeah, it looks like, yeah, I mean, come on.
A Charborg corner jump scare with Among Us
is at 13.7, number two, 13.7.
And then Iron Lung at 7.3% number three.
The cutoff of the awards was right
at that puppet combo stream last year.
So, honestly, I think a couple of years came off my life
after that.
I felt awful after that stream.
I think I remember talking about it later,
being like, I feel bad, I feel awful.
I have a headache, my chest hurts.
It actually felt terrible after that.
Anyways, we are getting to the final seven awards.
This is getting juicy.
I've said that four or five times, but it is.
Time to get to the big ones.
Now, every year, I like to sing some songs.
I sing, I get involved, I enunciate.
And we are going to show you now some of those nominees
for what that means when it's good.
Not bad when it's good.
Here are your nominees for the best singing of the year.
Hopefully, it's good, because I haven't seen this.
Bo peep, bo peep, bo peep, bo.
You got a friend in me.
This is on the other one, too.
This is on four singing back.
You got a friend in me.
When the road looks rubberhead
And you're miles and miles from your nice, warm bed.
You just remember what your old pal said.
But you got a friend in me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Are you playing Dark Souls?
Hey son, what a game you're playing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, I wonder.
The only thing I remember from Arcane was
Oh, the misery.
Every single person is my enemy.
That's all. That's the only thing I know.
I don't know anything else.
You gotta find that mystery.
And this is Scooby Doo.
Coming after you.
Fuck the Scooby Doo.
This is the fucking new Zoomer shit.
This is not what I want.
To the streets.
You got me up the cigarette.
Is that sceptre on my feet?
You need to find a reason.
Reason things went wrong.
Got to find a reason why my money's all gone.
Oh!
I could still get high.
And I can play the guitar like a motherfucking riot.
Not this one.
Hope not.
Scared.
That's what you want.
I'm going to march out here and just start singing fucking
John Jingleheimer Schmidt.
What are you doing now?
You're supposed to be scared.
John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
His name is my name too.
That's bad.
Whenever we go out, we always shout.
Here comes John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
Why is this?
Get in the bathroom quick.
This is terrible.
Chat a la la bye.
Little baby, I don't see a burn.
I'm going to buy you a mugging burn.
If that mugging bird don't sing,
I'm going to buy you an iron ring.
If that diamond ring don't shine,
I'm going to buy you a glass of wine.
When you get old enough, over 21.
We're getting apples and bananas remix.
Are you talking about like the...
I want to eat, eat, eat apples and bananas.
That's what you mean.
I like to eat, eat, eat, eight percent banana.
And feel like I belong.
Oh, this one's good.
This one's good.
Way, I can go the distance.
I'll be there someday.
If I can be strong,
I know every mile
will be worth my while.
He would go most anywhere
to feel like I belong.
Well, I liked that last one.
That was pretty good.
Well, we'll see what you think.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner of best singing of the year is...
I don't know if production has it ready,
but you know, I'll just wait till you do.
Can we just put, can we just play?
Can we just play it?
Do you know what won?
Can we just play it through?
DMCA, I know.
The channel will get shut down, but who gives a shit?
They don't have it.
Okay, it's with 31.1%, 31% of the vote is,
oh, the misery.
Okay.
At number two with 25%,
all the Hatsune Miku fans, po-pi-po.
And then Hercules, go the distance,
which was actually the good one.
That was the good one.
At 9.85%, good job, by the way, good job.
There you go.
But now, I do wanna do something very special.
We saw them earlier,
didn't really get a chance to show off
what they could actually do.
Feel like it's a good place to do it though.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome back into the studio,
Top Shelf Vocal, couple of actual good songs here.
And I'm gonna get outta here because I shouldn't be here.
Santa did tell me to be better.
Top Shelf Vocal, ladies and gentlemen,
with a couple of songs.
Joy to the world, the Lord is come.
Let earth receive her King.
Let every heart prepare Him room.
And heaven and nature sing.
Joy to the earth, the Savior reigns.
Let men their songs employ.
Rock fields and floods, rocks, hills and plains.
Repeat the sounding joy.
Repeat, repeat the sounding joy.
He rules the world with truth and grace.
And makes the nations prove
the glories of His righteousness.
And wonders of His love.
And wonders, wonders of His love.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for bringing some joy to the world.
We're gonna slow it down just a little bit
because tonight we want to bring in a holy night.
Oh, the stars are brightly shining.
It is the night of our dear Savior's birth.
Long lay the world in sin and error pining.
Till He appeared and the soul felt its worth.
A thrill of hope, the weary world rejoices.
For yonder breaks a new and glorious morn.
Fall on your knees.
Oh, hear the angel voices.
Oh, night divine.
Oh, when Christ was born.
Oh, night.
Oh, holy night.
Oh, night divine.
Thank you all so much.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Happy holidays to all.
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you for having us.
Thank you for having us.
Appreciate it.
That was absolutely unbelievable.
Thank you.
You all out here to actually do a song.
So with that, now don't listen.
I want you guys to don't listen to this.
We're going to go to the next category, which is maybe
the worst singing of the year.
Maybe I sing.
You've heard me.
I've sung before a few times.
Yeah, a couple of times.
Yeah.
Here are your nominees for the worst singing of the year,
right after that great performance.
You guys killed it.
That was fucking amazing.
Somebody said, Bjork?
What do you mean, Bjork?
I don't sound like Bjork.
What do you mean?
All I think is sing.
We're shouting in the wind.
And then somebody says, Bjork.
And I'm like, ugh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
Take a punch to the face.
We're all good friends, and we all get together sometimes.
When you're feeling down and you're feeling out of luck
and out of change, we will work together and we will help.
I'm sorry.
That's what I expected.
I expected that.
She's such a misfit.
Always ready to fight.
She's got a super beam, and she's raising high
if you believe you're strong.
Do you know the whole song?
I don't know.
I heard like a minute of it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Sing a good night song for Boba.
Boba, the kitty, have a good rest.
See you in the morning.
Boba, such a good kitty.
Good morning, good morning, good morning to you all.
Good morning, good morning.
I'm going to take a fall.
It's such a wonderful world we live in, in this nice street.
We're almost there.
Here we are.
Oh, they're missing me.
Every, every, my, every single person is my enemy.
Here it goes, here it goes.
We go from Nashville to Norway,
to Zimbabwe, Chicago, Czechoslovakia, and back.
But she'll be like...
Fucking god damn it.
The weather outside is bright.
What's wrong with this?
I got fire, solar light.
Since we know place.
Hold on.
I'll get it.
Shut up.
Since we know place to go.
Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow.
Use that part.
What was wrong with that?
That was fine.
You've got a friend in me.
Got a friend in me.
Two people.
Having one of a life and I have...
That's it, right?
All right, I'm going to count you guys in, OK?
Three, two, one, go.
She sang over the hills.
It instantly voice jammered me.
Take your headphones out.
Wait, wait, wait.
Sorry, sorry.
Take out your headphones.
OK.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
She sang over the hills.
Peaks are shy, but sure dawn.
And sure as the sun rise, I'll someday be gone.
But recall me, my love, and our joy may live on.
And you do, and you do, and you do.
That's a howl at the end.
There has to be a howl at the end.
Some of those weren't that bad.
I mean, cringe.
Is it like a most cringe category?
Maybe, no?
I have to top the shelf vocal, I know.
These were close.
It was pretty much every single nominee.
15.5, 14.4, 13.9, 13, 12.
It's all of them.
You couldn't choose.
But if you had to, with 15.5% of the vote, it's Bjrk.
Bjrk wins.
And then right underneath that 14.4% was Beatbox O,
The Misery.
And then 13.9% was the Splatoon 3 laughing song.
I mean, the Bjrk.
That stream, I would have nominated
for worst stream of the year.
Is it in there?
It might be.
All right, let's count the categories.
We've got one, two, three, four, five.
We've got, what, five or six categories remaining?
These are the huge ones.
These are the major, massive categories.
Are you ready?
How you guys feel?
You guys in the Christmas spirit?
Holiday spirit?
Yeah?
Can you please do a Bjrk?
Yeah.
I should shine more than fire.
Pretty good.
I tried.
Bjrk is a very talented singer, by the way.
More talented than I will ever be.
Times 100.
Just make that clear.
I have nothing on Bjrk.
Zero.
What's that say?
That is best gamer moment of the year.
Did I do good in a game?
Did I play Call of Duty versus a hacker?
Who may have been cheating, we don't know.
See him for lunch or dinner on Friday.
Extinguisher, if you still hear me.
I like extra lettuce on my hamburgers.
I like crunch.
Best gamer moment of the year incoming.
These are the moments that I actually did very well.
Not this one.
Don't look at that one yet.
It's not time for that one.
We're gonna put that down
and we're gonna show you the nominees
for best gaming moment of the year.
This is when I did well.
Here are your nominees.
Somebody's probably actually insane.
Banned that person for an hour.
And then like, you bet like a little bit there.
And then maybe I'd be like, you know,
what's 50 more?
You know what I mean?
It's a nominal amount.
Somebody said Elmo.
What does that mean?
Oh, Jerma, you absolute idiot.
Am I stupid?
Cause I just won the game.
That's a three of a kind.
You just got shocked.
Were you here?
Were you in the room?
Were you in the fucking room?
I got a bet for you.
And I complete my own mini golf course
in less than 20 strokes.
Six and seven.
Here comes seven.
Motherfuckers, you didn't think
I was gonna skip the whole goddamn course?
Yes.
You all lose.
Never bet against me again.
What's happening?
Am I winning?
Am I beating them?
I don't know.
Did I win?
Why won't he fight me?
Hurry up, run.
God damn it.
I knew it was a problem.
I have to be off to this guy
before he rings the alarm.
Come on.
Why is he so much faster than me?
I got him.
I beat him.
It's a pretty good moments.
That game is so hard.
They made it too hard.
Ultra kill devs if you're watching.
Your game is too hard.
Hardest game at Walmart.
It's not even at Walmart.
No, that's an old callback.
The game's hard, just to let you know.
Anyways, ladies and gentlemen,
the winner of best gamer moment of the year is,
this was huge.
44.6%.
Almost 45% of the vote.
The ultimate poker bluff versus Ludwig.
Wins.
Come on.
Took all his money.
He's here somewhere.
He's back there somewhere.
Sorry, Ludwig.
Beat you in poker.
It's my game.
And then after the first try,
Cuphead DLC boss at what, 14.8%?
That's not even close.
And then beating Ulcerated Tree Spirit early.
But that was, what's so impressive?
You beat the Tree Spirit, who cares?
That was like 30 levels too early.
I accidentally walked into that boss.
So that's pretty impressive, I think.
So there you go.
Weirdly enough, the mini golf course
was fourth or fifth place.
People thought the Ludwig bluff was way better.
And just like the good, there's also the bad.
I don't remember these nominees,
but they were way more than best.
I think they were, we had to narrow it down
because I think they were like,
oh wow, cool, Jeremy,
he got like seven nominees for best gamer moment
and 70 for worst gamer moment.
So we really had to narrow this down.
Honestly, I don't even know what's on this list.
I haven't seen it.
I just knew we did a few passes on it because we had to.
So here are your nominees for just like best gamer moment.
Here is the worst gamer moment of the entire year.
Worst gamer moment.
This is a nine minute category, by the way,
so strap in.
Hand fire tornado.
Jesus.
Give fire to the tornado.
Bro, there ain't no tornado on the screen.
Hand the fire to the tornado, but do it quietly.
Orc Minecraft fire.
Me, me build dirt house and burn it.
Is, you ten, if, none of these work.
F tens of, F tens of,
ecten, el tens, el, el ten.
What is this word, man?
What is this word?
Contestant number two.
Extensible, extensive background.
Shit, there's a flag right there.
What is it?
Oh my God, it's Switzerland.
What?
Excuse me.
Why is this thing coming alive?
Stone talus?
I'm fucking dead.
It's going to be a lot of damage.
Yeah, it's going to be a lot.
I mean, we can try.
It might as well, right?
Yeah, you can back out whenever it's looking rough.
We get fire down at this point.
Oh, fuck.
Ow.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Don't let it reset.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh shit, it killed me.
No.
It killed me too.
What the fuck?
What the hell?
It's low, it's low, it's low, it's low, it's low, it's low.
Oh my God.
I'm trying to kill him.
No.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Was I not supposed to do that?
On my screen, you're holding onto nothing.
You're just floating.
How long am I supposed to hold this for?
A while.
I'm going to run out of, I'm going to run out of grip.
I'm going to run out of grip.
Hold on, hold on.
What?
Oh shit.
Oh.
Oh fuck.
How do I get out of here quick?
Wait, did I save it?
That's how it's gonna end.
All right.
Seven minutes including chest.
I'm going to put my headphones in
and just shut the fuck up and do it as best as I can.
30 seconds.
just ran back to the entrance time oh that's what ruined everything 656 19 that would have been it
time that was it yeah nine seconds right here go look in here there's a fucking clock in here
oh my god you can lower the dude i'm getting luigi all right i'm getting luigi i'm gonna need
these later i'm taking them with me i'm taking all these with me
what the can i have one can i please have one why did it let go
there's one other at least one other player for sure guys how do i land oh wait what
did you kick in butt right now dude
game's fucking easy shit do not flip the car under any circumstance don't do it it's not funny it's
not a joke it would be annoying because you just wasted like 35 straight minutes cutting wood
jeremy i know you think you're quite the comedian but this is not the time to do that let's go
and a lot of people are gonna think that that was on purpose but it was not
now like a utility we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good
we're good we're good we're good big points on the board right now big points
yours
oh guys we need we need to get to the fucking we need to get in the car and get the fuck out
i need rest i need rest i don't like that he's he's not a
i don't know
run
go
jesus whoa really whoa dude that's bad i i have to leave now that was awful
i can't i uh i didn't get anything we're in trouble how do i solve half of these
into the forest i'm so sorry shit oh this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad
this is bad this is bad um i think we're in trouble i think we're in trouble
i think we're in trouble see here keep your eyes on the lady where is she gonna go where is she
gonna go i got it it was easy oh bodo don't be feeling too bad ain't nobody can what wait what
happened that wasn't even looking hey let's do the rest of this with my fucking eyes closed don't
make a joke stop oh my god what am i doing why did i do that why did i do that i was gonna make
like a joke where i was gonna close my eyes and cast this hurt so bad what the fuck are you doing
this was so painful what am i doing internally i was so internally mad at myself what do you have
an index kill him kill him kill him i can't do it kill i don't know how to do it kill him
i don't know how to do it kill him how do you do it do it kill him
30 seconds before you can kill
a lot of good ones but there can only be one winner i'm trying to peek let's see i can't see
through the envelope your winner for worst gamer moment of the whole year actually surprising
24.4 percent of the vote kill him kill him i don't know how to do it from among us vr and then at 11
percent we're going way down 11.7 percent margaret is one hit away let's do the rest of this with my
eyes closed and then trying to land in fortnight at nine percent apparently that first one was so
bad i don't play among us i don't play it how was i supposed to know that is that that's not
that's not a worst gamer moment that is a i didn't do the tutorial moment because i wanted to get in
and hang out with my friends and play video games what is it a fucking crime oh boy this is a big
one coming up next this is number 24 on the night this is the worst overall stream of the whole year
or worst stream segment what do you think the worst stream this year was
i have few guesses i don't know let me before you show the nominees
oh it's toasty every stream i try to have it be fun i try to have a good time an idea that maybe
oh this is a new idea maybe this is an old idea every stream i want to be fun right that's the
whole goal as a streamer you want the streams to be good but sometimes you miss the mark
and we're about to find out how badly that mark was missed ladies and gentlemen for 2022
here are your nominees for worst stream or stream segment of the entire year
this is pretty bad all right whatever i don't play fortnight i don't play this game
i just want to hang out with some cool friends streamer friends right like what the fuck
is that so bad guys how do i land i have what's it called splash i could throw it at everyone
i've got six minis i don't know i went in the dumpster okay for all you worst stream ever andy's
all right and so i'm not i'm not i'm gonna redress it anymore i'm not going to address it
anymore i'm just telling you you need to respect me for a minute this sucks that's how you know
excuse me what do you mean excuse me this was picked in pre-stream chat this was a prank no
this is not a prank i like people i in the pre-stream people like yo dude clover pog
how much i'm looking at the chat the hacker wanted me to play this by the way which i don't know about
that this is this this is kind of this is pog champ game dude you fell off you can't fall off
in 20 minutes you can't fall off in 20 minutes okay you can't fall off i didn't fall off it's
been 15 minutes you don't fall off in 15 minutes okay 20 90 percent is buster already made
what am i doing wrong it's 20 and 80 percent or 10 and 90 percent right
settle down it's fine dude this is genuinely worse than the clock
what how is this worse than the clock i'm doing what it says i'm supposed to be doing
if you can get it to work it's uh it's definitely a lot better first i'm standing still and i couldn't
even kill him i'm so bad next point up let's go that's you that's you oh i thought that was a bad
guy we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good bye bye everyone see you guys
be blessed
but in the meantime uh if we if there's any more you laugh you lose compilations
i'd love to watch them maybe just we can get them vetted quickly or something but um i ain't
watching i'm done after this this is fucking what a shit idea this is one of the worst ideas
i've ever had figure out the disney lyrics oh up on that beach up on that shore up on that many
people galore makes you kind of think i can go the distance this was good i'll be there someday
hey if i can be strong i know every mile will be worth my while it's i figured it out any of the
bosses that have like the Ludwig has it Godric has it Ibritas has it they all have it bro that
looked like battled chess this stream was so bad somebody just said it was it was oh that's oh my
god he just ruined Dark Souls 2 for me forever no no no no no no no no yes yes yes funny story
about the Dark Souls from software tier lists and i'm gonna be honest i got halfway through
that list and internally wanted to stop but you can't it was like another three hours it was like
a four and a half hour stream i remember getting halfway through scrolling down and just going
there's like a hundred bosses i still haven't rated yet internally i wanted to turn the stream
off but i didn't i powered through and it was a mistake could have just played uh could have
crossed and people would have been happy ladies and gentlemen the winner of the worst stream of
the whole year it was close it was close with 27.6 percent of the vote number one and then 26.2
all these votes count by the way oh i'm not gonna vote because i don't think it counts
27.6 and one 26.2 and two number one it's the fortnight tournament i think i was alive for
four minutes and the stream was like three hours long and then baby sensory videos right behind it
at 26.2 that was a bad i thought that was so funny when we first talked about it uh dude what a fun
idea i'll do baby sensory videos i i don't know they're scary if you've seen one they're
terrifying it wasn't even funny it was just it was odd it's just odd you know okay those of you
streamers out there if you're watching you know when you get that moment when you're doing
something and you just go fuck this is bad and i don't know what to do i don't know how to get out
of this how do i get out of this how do i get out of this there has to be a way i can get out of
this and there isn't and you have to sleep in the bed that you made that was the baby sensory
because i hyped that up for a week or two oh we're gonna do baby sensory videos it's gonna be crazy
wow we're gonna talk about them and after one or two i wanted to turn the stream off so bad and
i was like i just want to go i'll take a bath i just want to get out of here but you can't
and number three by the way was at 15% myth busters the game yeah it wasn't very good
these are your worst streams of the year i don't play i don't play video games i'm not a video
gamer i am though because elden ring i beat elden ring it'd be dark souls 3 beat dark souls remastered
how can you not say that i just i don't play certain types of games i don't play fortnite i
don't play call of duty who cares right whatever you know what let's go check in with the elves
follow me i'm coming to say hello there's some noise in here
hello what are you doing investing we're investing the money brainstorming the money
that you promised us what do you got here how do you feel investing in nlt's nlt's they're
gonna take off nlt's now what you're thinking but they're actually elf t-shirts yeah
robots to build puzzles yes you need that considering you haven't done a goddamn thing
you've got really there's some some stuff happening there very you've done a border
of one of them puzzle girl puzzle girl puzzle girl puzzle girl puzzle girl you ought to just
stop i was doing it still that's good oops i got a better idea how about this
why do i hear smash brothers activities we were also playing games you're playing games all right
i tried to hide it you play games i'll give that a sick oh nice
hey these are a thousand dollar chips
hey elves what yeah do you think it should be snowing in here yeah yeah we're doing
a puzzle hey chat should we should it start snowing in here yet do you think i want i want to
make sure i see it first should it start snowing for real this time do it for puzzle girl
they were bored okay what is this oh a present
you know all my presents got deleted you know that right who is this from
from all the elves luck doing the puzzle but it's literally impossible
okay from from the else what is it maybe it's going to be an xbox what is this
that's the baby give it up for the elves can we please give it up
how did i do that it's like being at the lunch table we're like hey dude eat the
meatball covered in like gravy and all the fuck that i was i did that stuff when i was younger
give it up to the elves they did absolutely nothing the whole day that's good actually
that was an experiment to see if they could actually do anything it's like oh let's get 15
elves to be in a room and do something and make a puzzle they didn't even come close they were
just drinking the whole night but that's fine that's fine but i mean the snow was fun they
were fun they were a good group now they gotta clean all that up i can't believe we put that
in my mouth more puzzle pog pog more puzzle the mic is fucked up did i fuck the bike up
did i ruin the mic mic oh no
all right we are down to the last three categories of the night it's been a wild night
maybe you've had a few alcoholic beverages maybe you haven't maybe you've had some tea
but we're getting down to the last three and these are special this next one is favorite
collab appearance i did a lot of uh other streams this year going on other people's channels and
traveling and there was a lot of shows that i was on that were not mine um so this was fun
it was actually really cool to go hang out with other streamers and this is your favorite collab
of the year whatever that one happened to be so here you go here you nominees we only got three
more favorite collab appearance outside of the channel that of you i can't even talk of the year
the favorite of the of you of the of the next contestant is definitely not photoshopped
and is very caked up ladies and gentlemen let's hear it for germa
actually i wasn't going to bring this up his podium is bigger than mine
i want to replace look it's at least it's at least a quarter of an inch higher than mine podium
envy did you not read my rider let me tell you something you bastard let me tell you something
okay my podium might be one or two inches bigger than yours but that doesn't matter
you need to relax and go back to what you were doing yeah get back to what you're wrecked please
have a seat in that journal have a seat in that you bring that down for him will oh wow yeah
oh look at that okay okay 37 this year oh we are not insured for this the winner of name your price
between germa and mia is
this is where it gets very heated because i know you have a two right here somewhere
and ladies and gentlemen we did it there's no fucking way and then like you bet like a little
bit there and then maybe i'd i'd be like i'd be like you know what what's what's 50 what's 50 more
you know what i mean just small it's a nominal amount it's a nominal amount
what does that mean oh jerma you absolute idiot am i stupid because i just won the game
that's a three of a kind you just got shocked i my music's been buffering all day so i was
gonna count until it buffered but then the music didn't buffer this time so i've just been counting
rock you just got to get the right leverage
oh my lord hercules we're in costume i'm mercy from the overwatch 2 and who's that
hey how are you it's me deadpool nice to see everybody oh my god it's so good to have you
yeah special guest here you just missed jerma did i yeah he was a great guy oh he's a fun dude he's
fun kind of a weird guy kind of a weird guy but i just missed him just missed him wow so hey me
at the murk with the mouth let me tell you what i'm gonna do today i'm gonna take we're gonna make
pumpkin pie that's what's gonna happen here i've been waiting all week to do this one all right get
in there i don't think i made it i'm assuming it missed i can't tell oh you know what my lips
are jarring now oh are they what what the fuck is what did they get it just cut the jerma doing
exercise wait wait you guys just can't miss that yeah it was just jerma doing this
did they miss that shot i was stretching yeah and how about you tell us what you have in your
pocket earlier yeah he's got like a lip balm on a on a cute dip you're actually calling me up for
this yeah pull it out man i mean so it's i saw music that is a dab that you smoke weed out of
no this is not drugs it's in a drug baggie but it doesn't mean it's drugs
got it under control though i'm gonna land this gonna be an s-tier pilot by the way when you all
do your reviews i want you to say thanks for the s-tier landing and have a great rest of your
evening landing strong okay oh my god okay okay okay don't worry oh my god jerma yeah if we don't
make it out of this one yep i just want to let you know you're a great pilot okay thank you so
much this may require both of us all right and by the way i've got a bag under my back that is 50
random i'm sure somebody knows push back oh boy okay push back okay hold on to the side there you go
all right we're okay we're all right we're all right all right oh my god
we made it we're on the ground we made it oh oh my god
i may have switched my balls oh okay hey wait a minute we got a guest here we got the amazing
jerma everybody clap oh it's a wonderful time to see you yes sit here yeah you may sit there
now i hear you put on the biggest production of guys and dolls twitch has ever seen well
you're a bit close who's this tweet about all right a reply to jerma nine eight five all right
or is it a reply to super galactic porn star me malcova that fat juicy ass fat spelled with a ph
ph which is the good yeah i'm gonna say 2020 i'm gonna say this is about me wow all right and what
do you think donna am i missing something i'm gonna say me a malcova i would like to say
jerma is a a little full of himself it is me and malcova yeah no but i mean that's all i have to
be i i got one of my one of that tweet of me showing my ass in the mirror what anyway let's
take a look at some of our competitors jerma what question did you ask me earlier i was asked you
what the accelerate button was who's your teammate you okay let's go see how other people are doing
are you sipping it right now oh i just opened it well i did it's harder to chug a cold beer you
know that but it tastes better you don't chug for taste i i everything is taste everything you can't
just chug what do you mean taste this is a typical gold knights fan they almost won the goddamn
stanley cup the first year by the way they did almost how long it goes that that's not great you
don't love that for them i used to do that when it turned out i i used to i but by the way i don't
really like mario kart let me be very what why did you accept doing this because i i think you're
cool really yeah oh thank you statistically those ones do actually no exactly thinking
about fucking toad in this next last round you want to fuck toad is that what you just
i will say something before i open this that thanks to all the other streamers that let me
kind of participate in their shows because it's fun and i hope that you liked it i hope you thought
it was fun if maybe it participated in everything i did a lot of stuff this year so there's a lot
of people doing really really cool shit on these platforms so it's an honor to be able to participate
and have fun so thank you all these nominees everybody that's in here it's been a lot of fun
it has um thank you i actually do mean that thank you so much for letting me be part of your cool
shit but what was everybody's favorite they're all good what do we got here who is the favorite
collab of the year ladies and gentlemen it is oh close 28 percent of the vote and then two
was 25.6 number one was tummy time with critical which was so much fun that whole group is so
awesome that was an unbelievable experience name your price with austin show at number two and then
bro versus bro bro versus bro with ludwig bro versus bro ludwig is here so ludwig you came in
third place on best collab stream i don't know if he's even here anymore but yeah that that means
a lot it means a lot to be able to be a part of other people's shows um i hope i made them
more fun and if i didn't then maybe i won't get a call back all right all right don't get sentimental
don't start crying every there's a lot of people watching you you've probably heard that weird burp
we're getting to the last two categories there's only two left there's best overall streamer series
and best overall event um we can start with this one here it's been kind of a wild year
and there's a lot to go over so i guess i don't need to introduce this too much
this is the nominees for the best stream or stream series of the year and here they are
you guys are losing your fucking minds it's not a log splitter what the what is happening in this
chat room look up a google image of a log splitter i'm fucking freaking out right now log splitter
he's a based socialist
ow job what what the fuck what am i supposed to do guys blue flash means an attack is unperiable
guys when when ben franklin was writing up the goddamn fucking declaration of independence
there was no guggerna guggerna in there there was oh yeah we also need to make sure that uh
leave some room for guggerna guggerna guggerna guggerna guggerna guggerna there's no room for that
ben the jokes where are the jokes they bemoan they screamed they gnashed their teeth and said
entertain us right is there all right
he's the dev the dev is even sick of this joke the dev is like all right it's kind of funny but like
fucking hurry up well watch out i my thumb hold on
it's too dark need a handful kind of curious i'm curious let's go
it's a hamburger meat it tastes like hamburger meat i can't even eat it now oh why'd you do that
this was s this was s you i was gonna put it in s and now i'm like there's a pregnancy test in my
mouth what the fuck i don't know why i just felt like i was being held hostage this is fucking weird
i would this is weirdly
this game's for fucking kids i don't give a fuck i'm playing a fucking kid's game and you guys are
fucking shit in the fucking chat yeah okay pickle nose pickle nose fucking say that
shit oh this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad this is bad
um i think we're in trouble i think we're in trouble
oh shit it's gonna break stop doing the mario i'm sorry i'm sorry everybody
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry just doing the mario thing to make pasta on the stove you boil stir
and toil and watch out it's sure to make a mess then you strain that first is trashed this first
what i've got it's kind of a giant cookie pizza don't touch that remote during the next few
minutes we'll tell you about a 40 million dollar giveaway
promotion you can get a fabulous rocket ship for a friend
what the fuck is no way no but try to flip and food flops try to grip shit face i'm telling you
shit face are you about to win oh it's seattle god damn it what houston the space needle was
just on there shit there's a flag right there what is it oh my god
the troll too yell what
whoa i think i saw somebody's dick what was that what was that that was weird what's going on
oh
that fucking face squad god damn it excuse me whoa what's happening somebody's stabbing me what
what happened dude this is illegal that's illegal
oh my god hurry up hurry hurry i just shit my pants what my popularity is dwindling please get
what how am i supposed to do anything when everybody just attacks me what the fucking
woman where'd he go i miss this was so fun just a psycho i'm sorry no i don't mean
i don't all right uh you can arrest me i don't know i this is weird everybody looking at me
stop don't look at me what the fuck that's like a monster i'm trying to snap his neck
i'm trying to strangle him hey give me that gun motherfucker back for this god i'm so sorry holy
shit that was that was like the worst thing that ever happened to me you just stole austin powers
mojo jesus give me a fucking brick that was fucked up that was actually pretty
i'm sorry i can't do it what is what is we have one minute and 15 seconds to go this way
we're gonna go up where did you go we're going up
oh coffee oh
cheeto roadie bet
i'm loving it get off the fucking barrel get off the barrel that was awful get off the barrel
i don't like this i hate this oh holy shit people are so ugly with light aren't they
holy shit people are so ugly look at all right oh german you look real handsome today you sure
about that oh no he killed that guy what oh my god i'm so confused right now
i told you it was real hey let's do the rest of this with my fucking eyes closed don't make a
joke stop oh my god what am i doing if i chop you up in a meat grinder and the only thing that
comes out that's left of you is your eyeball you're you're probably dead now i don't get that move
at all that move is absolutely unbelievable it's one of those moves that you can't do anything
about and i'm telling you yeah but you know what else is as ridiculous as that yeah like we're
gonna get playing soon they're gonna be like i can fly eventually too so those are your nominees
for best stream or stream series of the year i feel like there are a lot of good ones i feel
like there was a lot of fun this year i say that every year but i do mean it and let's see i just
start crying on camera right i'm gonna start i'm gonna cry it's gonna happen just wait all right
ladies and gentlemen the what you have decided was the best stream or stream series of the year
oh the misery no uh elden ring at 27.2 percent and let me tell you it makes sense considering i
streamed that game for almost two straight months there was a high chance it was going
to be elden ring because it was a third of every stream i did this year and also game of the year
by the way uh elden ring at 27.2 underneath that is infomercial react andy gonna have to do more
of those react andy streams because uh okay and then breath i didn't even beat breath of the wild
yet but uh breath of wild number three by the way this is second most least skipped category
so people wanted to vote for this but elden ring obviously elden ring swept everything swept the
game awards swept my awards right so obviously it's gonna win and it was so fun those some of
the i honestly those some of the funnest streams i had i think ever on the channel that game just
had so many fun moments once in a generation you get it all right ladies and gentlemen it is time
we are approaching the final category which it's a small category but it's fun to do
the last category of the evening is best overall stream event there was only about four or five
this year um i love doing events i think they're fun get people together have a good time this is
an event can't vote for this though but hey maybe you can next year hey maybe jot it down for your
best event of the year the uh germa 95 uh holiday christmas stream but yeah this is gonna be it this
is the last category of the evening is what you thought the best stream of the year was that was
a event stream we did non-event here is event here are your nominees most least so what i've
decided to do is over the last few months we've scoured the country trying to find who i think
could potentially be able to replace me and a little bit of great and another one here
all right then we got a little might be a little too much pull back on the speed pull back
all right everybody had three jokes
we pray at night we stalk
you think you can beat me i know i can beat you i don't know what i'm gonna do
oh you know you can beat me go ahead and cue the music good good luck weird monopoly man
like a swedish monopoly man what is planned you guys synchronize this stir i've been for 10
years we've i tf2 and look at me look at me that's me i just want you to know you can google all
that he knows nothing i could tell who it was the whole time what oh you shot good job you shot him
hey everybody what's going on to be the sus guy i've been muted this whole time
oh
we can watch the door we'll watch the door you take care of your tasks no one's coming through
this you're safe it's these two it's definitely these two it's these two no it's these two
it's these two help okay so press what do you have an index
do it kill him i can't do it i don't know how to do it kill him i don't know how to do it kill
him how do you do it do tell him 30 seconds before you can kill what
what i think i agree yeah get this guy out of here is this one of your get this guy out of here
get this guy out of here the best way to uh how do we get how do we get how do we get this guy out
of here i turned around crank and jump scared me no one's listening okay i should probably
be on this camera okay all right okay okay it's my birthday everyone quiet
so by the way can i just say why camera for this
there's only 40 seconds welcome to car shield field where we have germa baseball association
action for you tonight a big time matchup between the california circus and the maryland
magicians you like that that call from elbertson behind home plate sometimes you're not sure where
the pitch missed elbertson always lets you know make magic slowly oh what a play oh we got
albertson pie in the face elbertson the circus one of that play called dad because
oh and he is tossed is this we we've got a streaker we've got a streaker ladies and
gentlemen before the jva the math may be a little bit off look at this he's pulled it down the line
it's fair albertson speeding past first he's thinking two throw comes in the second oh he
takes a quick turnaround and a good decision by crew chief albertson he rules himself safe at
first and that one's in for the call strike oh two and oh my goodness everyone clearing the bench
for the magicians oh my goodness this is bad feed him to the lions yeah feed him feed him to the
lions don't you think but you know it's not bjel who and what's not cool drugs and alcohol an organ
steve let's go you can see my dick you can see my dick if you want to see it freeze it
oh man you guys are unbelievably funny all right let's get it the winner of best event of the year
there's only about four or five of them so let's see it's gonna be close it's not close
it's not close at all 42.7 percent of the vote is the germa baseball association
and then the sus guy finally plays among us above who will replace me which the sus guy was 24.5
and who will replace me at 19.4 this was also the least skipped category of the year
people wanted to vote for this and that's it so i am going to say good night thanks everybody
for watching uh it's been an unbelievable experience before we go before we go i gotta
thank a lot of people but let's go ahead you know we we got them here and they're incredibly
talented let's bring out top shelf vocal again because you guys are so good we're not going to
just not do this a lot of time and a lot of work and a lot of energy went into this i know people
didn't expect oh well you didn't do your award show whatever okay cool like you do every year
a lot of people were involved and i do want to say thank you to a very specific few people
let's bring off brand out uh ludwig atriarch nick stans uh stans is not here right now
because obviously you know his shoulder got a little screwed up but seriously guys it was
a fucking blast always a pleasure to work with you guys you guys are amazing off brand everybody
there they are you know who all these people are and then bts bring up beyond the summit
working back and forth beyond the summit was you guys have been some of the easiest production
company to work with ever uh tons of i know i'm a fucking weirdo and i know that we had a lot of
phone calls about what the hell was going to happen here so i huge appreciate you guys are
amazing come on out if we get some of you guys to come out dakota especially i want dakota i want
and hey i want the elves out here too
we're gonna fill this set
you probably can't see them anymore but uh top shelf vocal is good yeah you guys come up to the
front what an incredible 2022 uh oh bugleberry bugleberry you're okay
are you serious did you make it out of we went out of the portal bugleberry made us cookies
oh my bugleberry bugleberry please give me a hug
i'm so glad you made it out safely uh thank you everybody for watching this was a wild day um
huge thanks all i can say is let's let's move forward to 2023 yeah yeah merry christmas happy
new year if we don't see you next week we'll see you very soon anybody want a cookie
one two three one we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry christmas we wish you a merry
christmas and a happy new year the tidings we bring to you and your kid that tidings for christmas
and a happy new year now bringing us some figgy pudding now bringing us some figgy pudding
now bring us some figgy pudding i can't hear ludwig i can't hear ludwig ring to you and your kid
glad tidings for christmas and a happy new year we won't go until we get some we won't go until
we get some we won't go until we get some so give me it right now glad tidings we bring
to you and your kin glad tidings for christmas and a happy new