Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with kind of a different commentary today. This is gonna be over
I'm not really sure what gameplay is gonna be in the background. I'm actually talking into a black screen right now
So I'm not really sure what's gonna be there, but there will be a gameplay there whatever loadout
I'm using whatever game it happens to be that's what I'm doing
But this video is gonna talk about something that I've been thinking about lately and it's a discussion video
So please chime in in the comment section if you have anything to add to this
And it's about the gaming industry
Plateauing and how graphics engines and gaming in general is kind of at that area
Where there's not a whole lot else left to do
There's not a whole lot else left to innovate on and we're gonna talk about some points some counterpoints as well to argue this fact
I'm gonna play devil's advocate to myself in a small regard
But first of all, let's let's bring up the fact that gaming let's talk about graphics engines first
So the graphics engines of yesteryear going back to like the Super Nintendo and regular Nintendo or even if you keep going back to
Atari we'll say I guess we'll start at Atari Atari. So you had Atari very very basic graphics engine
I don't know if you can even call it that either
There's like two blips on a screen for most of the Atari games and then you went from Atari to regular Nintendo
Regular Nintendo had 8-bit graphics and the change from the Atari to the NES was huge
It was astronomical people have never seen anything like that before ever in their entire lives
And the same can be said from the NES to the Super Nintendo
the Super Nintendo was miles ahead in technology same thing for the Sega Genesis and
It seems that we can keep going from generation to generation here
You move on to the Nintendo 64 you move on to like Sega CD and you got the Dreamcast
PlayStation 1 PlayStation 2 and then ps3 everything every generational jump has been an
astronomical change until
you got to the ps3 and the
360 when these two systems were being talked about when the 360 of 360 came out first when the 360 showed its first
Screenshots and showed its first gameplay demos and stuff. I I was kind of let down
Maybe that's because I'm a child of the 80s and I saw this whole revolution of video games
But the Xbox to the Xbox 360 there was a it was a jump, but it was such a tiny jump
It was like a little dude jumping over like a friggin candlestick. What's the guy's name? Come on?
Come on
What's the guy's name? Jack be meant Jack be nimble Jack be quick Jack jumped over the Xbox to the Xbox 360
That's how I felt textures looked kind of the same modeling looked kind of the same
It was in the same realm of graphics quality as the regular Xbox now that they're talking about the
Xbox 720 and the ps4
Are we gonna see a huge jump because guys you got to remember it's been like 10 years
Since we've seen anything really really innovatively huge like graphics engine wise in the last 10 years
That's a long time especially considering the fact that from the Atari to the Nintendo 64
Was like holy crap
You're like blowing up a nuclear bomb in changes to graphics quality and moving on to the next point here about not just the graphics
Quality games in general are starting to plateau. We're starting to see the same storylines rehash themselves
We're starting to see way too huge sequel numbers
What are we on Final Fantasy 75 now?
Like how far things gonna go before we see a really big innovation change in this industry, and I think it's happening
I really think it's happening guys at a much smaller level
I think it's happening at the indie level at the independent level because all these huge studios
They don't need to innovate anymore. They have all their franchises
They have all their ideas and they have all their things locked down
But it's the little developers the little independent developers that have to strive to create amazing content
Otherwise, they're gonna die. They're gonna die off
I mean how is Joe Schmoe gonna be able to make a
Indie platformer or an indie shooting game in his living room and be able to compete with Call of Duty or Battlefield
It's just impossible unless what you're making is a crazy cool new idea
And that's one of the reasons why I love Edmund McMillan so much is because he's an independent developer that just does such wacky stuff
He's always creating these new crazy things
We got the binding of Isaac from him Super Meat Boy Gish and he's working on a new title right now called
Mugenics which I cannot friggin wait for that game to come out guys because it's gonna be so cool
It's gonna be insane. I can't wait to play it but enough of smoking this guy's ass smoke what smoking this guy's ass
What am I gonna roll up his ass and smoke it? What am I talking about?
Tooting his horn is what I meant to say
Anyways
Without stuff like that without people like
Independent developers like Edmund McMillan the industry really might plateau it really might start to stagnant
But that's where you guys come in I'd love to hear what you have to say about this topic put it in the comment
Section below get a discussion going let's talk about the industry plateauing and if indie games can save us all I guess
That's that's the real meat potatoes point of this entire video. So thank you everybody so much for watching
That's gonna wrap it up here whatever game. I happen to be playing. I hope I won
I don't know who I the gameplay is not recorded yet
But I wanted to get this down and wanted to get this commentary done because I wanted to talk about it really badly
So well, thank you again everyone for watching. I'll see you all soon. And of course, take care everybody