There's only so fast you can move with a full hot coffee in your hand.
I have a hot coffee. I was downstairs, and my staircase, by the way, is like eight stories.
I have to go around the fucking pool. God, that's annoying. Over by the playground,
the slide that goes down from the top floor all the way to the bottom. I don't know why I made it
like this. Can't use the elevator because it's out of service. That's fucking annoying. Like a Willy
Wonka house. Yeah, but there's only so fast. I've like, I'm half-winded because I had to
move so quickly up the stairs. My eight story house. Let me tweet this out. Hold on. I'm not
late. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here. It was 12.01. All right, give me one sec. Okay, so today we're
gonna play The Sims 1. It's been a very long time since I've played this game. The Sims 1 what? The
Sims 1 won. Actually, it's the complete edition. What is half of the stuff in this game?
It's like a magician town. What is the magic? What's magic town? I have everything. How tall
are you, 5'8"? This chair seems like it's way too high. That's better. Okay. Did you guys hear that?
All right, so yeah, I'm welcome. This is once a week Andy here.
We might go two times here, depending on how much fun The Sims 1 is today and tomorrow.
You're gonna do face cam? Nah. No, not today. Would you play Zack? Wait, what was that? I play Zack
in Wiki. I don't know why I would play the game Zack and I'm not sure why I would need to Wikipedia
everything, but it must be a hard game. All right, let's go. Yeah, don't leave. I'm leaving. Don't,
don't leave. Don't, what was that? Why am I doing that? Don't, don't leave. Don't leave.
Putting on like a Boston thing. All right, it's been a very long time. I can't, I'm very excited
to play The Sims 1 with all of you. How are you feeling? I am very tight, very sore. Did some
stuff this week. Did some medical stuff this week and we tried something new and I kind of, I kind
of got like the shit kicked out of me, if I'm honest with you. Essentially, I let, I did the
equivalent of lying down on the ground and somebody just slowly running me over with their car.
That's kind of how it feels. Just very slowly, just the wheel going up over my back and then all
the way across and then over and the shock absorption of the car goes like boom, boom.
It sounds nice. Well, I didn't do that. That's what it felt, that's what it feels like right now.
He's doing suede science for his pain.
No, I would have to make a YouTube video where I explain that. See, you don't need, but guys,
the tire tracks, they have the groove that fits right into where your spine is
and what happens is it unlocks an area right in your T6, T7. The guy lies down
on his face down, just love his head down. He's talking into the ground and his microphone's
going like because he's moving around too much. The car's going to drive over me enough.
You get like all these horrible crunches. Well, it's like the dude's mom.
He's hanging out the window. Hey, are you sure you want to do this? I don't think this is safe.
He died. No, he didn't. He said suede wrong. I know I say, look, I like it. It sounds fun to me.
I like the way it sounds better. Suede science. Pseudo science sounds, I don't know, like real.
Suede science sounds, I like the way it sounds better. Who's Peter Griffin? Look, look, I know,
I know. I'm from New England and I have a New England accent and I'm like, I've turned into
like a fat guy. I wear glasses and I eat like fucking Cheetos and I have a dog. Okay. I must,
I may as well be Peter Griffin. I do a lot of referential humor too. It must be Peter Griffin.
I am. All right, let's play the sim. You heard? You guys ready? You guys ready? Oh shit, hold on.
This is kind of loud for me. And ta-da. Here we are in Sims 1.
Oh, this was a pain in the ass to get to work. To get this to be on your screen was,
I don't know why it was the hardest thing I've ever done. So I have to make a family and I know
you can go into like the bitmap editor and stuff, but I, I don't want to do, I want to play with
just the default sim. It's 180p. Yeah. Well the game broadcasted itself to your screen in like 360p.
This isn't the one for the NES. They made, really didn't. Is the goth family,
for those who don't remember. All right, let's, let's make a family. It doesn't, making a family
in the Sims 1 does not take very long at all. Oh shit, this is important. Oh, what last name?
What do you think? Sweets. Sweets family. I don't know why I think that's cool. The Sweets. I like
it actually. Not the Elbritans, no. The Griffins. I'm not making the Griffin family. You can't make
any, you can't even make that. Greens. The Andes. No. You want me to make Andy? No, it's got to be
new. New characters. New characters. How about the Gaslighters? Uh, Sway, the Swaydos? Swaydos.
Swaydoos? The Swaydoos. That's way too like, that's too comedic. I don't know. I don't know
what's jumping out to me is Arthur Sweets. Arthur Sweets. I don't know why. That's doing it for me
today. Arthur Sweets. Arthur and Jane Sweets. I got it. How do I do this? Okay, this is Arthur Sweets.
I forgot that the Sims 1 was, this is, this is it. You just make, you, you give them like a head and
then you change their t-shirt. I forgot how little it was in this game. You can go in and paint stuff,
right? Like a Minecraft character, but I'm not going to do that. There's so many. All right,
so let's go with Arthur Sweets here. This is scripted. What are you talking about? Make him
the Joker. That's, that's the Joker's name? No, it's not. What's the Joker's name in the Joker?
Arthur what? Arthur Fleck. Arthur Sweets. Just because somebody's name is Arthur doesn't mean
they're the Joker. All right, let's do, uh, let's get it like this. Let's do outgoing. We want a lot
of friends. Not active at all and very neat because I don't like it when they throw this
shit on the ground. Well, how can you be outgoing and not nice? Outgoing and not nice or playful?
Is there like mean outgoing? I thought outgoing meant you actively wanted people to be your friend
and stuff. Is it outgoing evil? Like you just, is that the guy that like talks shit to you and
cuts you off and stuff? Is it the guy that like cuts you in the ice cream line and like gives you
the finger? That's like a different kind of outgoing. You're outgoingly mean. All right,
well, no, I don't want that. That's fine. I don't want to be that neat. I don't want to be that
nice either. All right, that looks good. Arthur Sweets, uh, bio for Arthur Sweets. Okay, that's
Arthur Sweets. The family member here. Do we have a kid? Wait, I didn't even pick Arthur Sweets.
I didn't even pick his body. What, who is he? I didn't even click him. What was he?
Okay, wait, I can edit it, right? It's the Joker. It is the Joker. Whatever.
Keep it. I don't care. Damn it. All right. Look, there's only, how many options are there? Total
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19.
There's like only 30 heads in the whole game. This is Jane Sweets. This is going to be Harley
Quinn, isn't it? No, it's not. I'm going to make sure that doesn't happen. What is Harley Quinn's
name? Oh, wait, it's Harley Quinn. I mean, like, does she have like a, whatever.
Arlene Quinn. What is this? Oh, okay. It's like, what is that? Make the Elbertsons. Look,
there can be like 40 families in here. Let me just get in and do the, remember how to play the game.
I don't know why I like this. You know what I mean? There's something about it. I feel like
this lady is going to start singing. I'm going to break in a song halfway through the stream.
It's Princess Fiona. What is, what's the song that Fiona sings? All right. Well,
Jane's going to be way more active than Arthur. The active one. Um, like this, right?
Why does everybody have so many hashtags in their fucking thing now? Everybody's doing this now.
I'm like a scientist. Wait till people start doing this. Okay. That's, that looks good to me.
All right. It looks good to me. Let's go. They have a child. This is going to be, uh, Sean Sweets.
Ben Sweets. Boris Sweets. I like, I kind of like Boris Sweets, but the S's together. Andy Sweets.
Johnny Sweets. Peter Sweets. I like that. Nathan Sweets. That's not bad. All right,
hold on. What if, oh my God. I, it's perfect. It's, it's, it's absolutely perfect. Whatever
it's going to be. It's perfect. Not Meg. No. Car, uh, Caramel Sweets. And I'm not changing anything.
It's perfect. Caramel Sweets. Not Martha Sweets. Caramel Sweets. Not Meg. Stop saying Meg. You guys
hate Family Guy. Nobody here likes Family Guy. I know why we ironically hate it all together,
right? But like I'm not, I'm not going to make every character like Peter and like Lois and like
Chris Griffin. That's what Virgo is? Wait, hold on. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
I gotta see if this is accurate. That's not accurate at all. Yeah, that's more accurate.
All right. I'm way, that's me. Yeah, that's me. That's me. People are giving so many subs. What
the fuck is going on? Freddie Dredge just gave 50 community subs. 50. On top of like the 8,000 he's
given in the last two, three years. Holy shit, dude. Absolute disrespect of what? What? I, I,
I didn't, I didn't say Virgo's stupid. I said Virgo's not me. I said that's inaccurate. I didn't
say that's dumb. Uh, thank you, Freddie. Seriously. And there was a shitload more. Unionize Your
Workplace, Georgie Porgy, Knights of Old, Straight Pube, and Hole of One Zombie. Thanks, guys.
A lot of subs. It's not pre-recorded. No, it's not. Why would, why would, it's not pre-recorded. I'm
here. I'm literally in front of you right now. What time were you born? I don't want to answer
that fucking weird question. You're going to, because you're going to go back in time. And
here's the thing. You know, oh, what if you go back in time and like snatch me when I'm a baby
or something? I don't want you, I don't want you to know what, where that, what time that was.
Yeah. If you go back in time to the day that I was born and you go like to the hospitals where
you think I was born, you do, you need, you still need to know the time. I ain't telling you that.
Good luck. What was the temperature when you were born? You know what? That's funny. That probably
actually matters somehow. That's going to be like, what if, what if my, my ice sign is, right?
I could be like fire or ice. I wouldn't be surprised. Okay. What is, what's this bar for?
I don't care. All right. We have Arthur Jane and caramel sweets. I don't think we need anybody else.
When you have more than three Sims in a Sims game, that's how you start to lose interest
because everybody has to be taken care of and you can't pay attention to anybody.
So half the people end up like dying and shit because you can only even focus on one person.
So where are they going to go? Are you sure? I am sure you're a Sims expert.
There are the sweets. They have $20,000 and they're going to move that family.
All right. Should I buy a lot or should I just kick out somebody? This is starter home.
Sims one is notoriously hard and bad with the file meters. Get a good house. Um, this is pet paradise.
I have a 10 sim lane. This is a good one to own. Build my own. All right. 14,500 to spend on
household. All right. Let's go here. Let's buy this house. I'll build it. School bus will arrive in
an hour. Why? I don't want a school bus to arrive in an hour. Is she reading the newspaper?
This girl can't even read. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, that's a classic caramel sweets. She's the smart one of the family. All right. Let's build.
That was absolutely the intro. That was absolutely the season one, episode one pilot
of introducing these characters. Oh, well, that was a perfect start. And then halfway through season
two, we stopped as directors and writers and animators. We stopped. We stopped making her
smart because that's like too much work and like annoying to do now. Okay. Um, what do I want to do?
What kind of house do I want? I'm just going to go with this. Just a regular house. I'm so bad at
this part. This is why I always have pre-built stuff because I'm too stupid to do it on my own.
When I close my eyes, I can see a beautiful thing. I can exactly see how the architecture looks. I
can see where the roof is. I can see like a family opening the door and a dog jumping up and
everything. I can see this in my head right now. But when I try to make that, I just make a cube.
Yeah. I like this view better. I don't like the other side. This would be the living room.
I'm down a little more because I want a garden too. How much money do I have? 12,000. And by the way,
no cheating. All right. So that's the front door. I'm not done. This is just the first part. Why is
that so funny? This isn't even funny. This is the foundation of the house. Why is this funny? This
is not even funny. Okay. Then over here, it will go like this. It's going to be like the bathroom.
This is not even funny. Okay. That's like going to be a bathroom. And then over here, I like a
kitchen. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. Shh. Here's the little patio. Walk away. Door. Go in the door.
There's your kitchen. No. There's your kitchen. Kitchen's right here. And living room here.
I want an open concept. This will be a bathroom. And then the bedroom will be over here. Yes. This
house is fucked up. Why is this house fucked up? Is this the bedroom? Because there's nothing over
here yet. Holy shit. What? You forgot the foundation. Well, I have to do, hold on. Floor.
Well, this is going to be a combo. I think a Zerkoff room. I don't know why I was just about
to answer this with what I was about to say. And I'm not going to, no, I'm not even going to say
that. Say something. What con, nevermind. I was going to say what constitutes a Zerkoff room?
What are you talking about? That you don't go on like a tour, like a house or an apartment or
something. You're walking around. Okay. So this is the bathroom. This is a, it's a full bath.
And over here we, it's really nice that they have a walk-in shower. Really cool.
Here's the living room. Yeah. It's about, it's about like 600 square feet in here.
Oh, this, this, this is the Zerkoff room. Yep. This one here. Oh, nice. Very, very, very nice.
Honey, what do you think of the Zerkoff room? Oh yeah. This is great. It's got extra privacy.
Yeah. This is good. There's two doors. As you see, there's one door that locks and there's another
door in front. Just in case somebody gets in the first one. Oh, that's so useful. Yeah. Because
I'll be able to hear somebody open the first one. So then I could freak out and just like
freak out and just stop like, and then stand there like a toy soldier, like nothing was happening.
By the time they get to the second one, I'm just standing there. But if you go in the Zerkoff room,
you're not, what else would you be doing in there? Why would you need privacy in the,
people know what you're doing in there. It's not like it's, people wouldn't know.
Airlock. Whoa. What is this? Oh, this is wood. No, wood floors are fucking overrated.
I'm sorry. They get scuffed up. They get destroyed. They get broken. They're fucking
incredibly expensive. Respectful. Expensive. Wood floors are so expensive and they just,
they get beat up and stuff. I don't know. I mean, they look really nice. If you love wood, then
sure. It's a, they have tons to take. You have to upkeep the hell out of them. I don't want
a carpet in here. Oh, who wants to? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. Tile gang.
Ooh, this is swanky. Basic wood, Andy. Well, I like that. This is my house. I get to do whatever
I want. Okay. You can have, you can, hey, you can go and get this. You can do the Sims one.
You can go and do the painful, horrible installation process and desperately trying
to get it to turn on on Windows 10 and trying to figure out how to get it to fucking run
and have to pull it through a like DirectX pass through program to get it to like actually show
up on the screen. And then you can make your own house. You can run it in compatibility mode.
Ooh, what's this? I don't like that. Oh, yep. No, ugly. Ooh, what's this? Moss? This is kind of
like Minecraft. That's a Minecraft house. No, I don't want that. How do I sell castle floor?
Is this a rug? This is the Sims one. It may as well be Minecraft floors and walls and stuff.
It's not that complicated. All right. I'm going to go with this. This is my kitchen area. It's
like, give me a headache looking at it. Yeah. It gives me a headache. I don't like it. How do
I delete things? How do I get my money back? A contractor finishes the last tile and you walk
in. How do I get my money? How do I delete this and get my money back? How do I remove that?
Control area. Okay. Wait. Oh my God. What? You don't get the full price back? No, you don't.
Okay. I have to be really careful then. I need, I wish I could see what this looks like. This is
all right. No, it's the same color as the balls. Ooh, here we go. That's going to look cool. All
right. I'm done. It looks dirty. It needs to be washed. It doesn't matter. I'm too, it's too
late. What about here? This is the living room floors. Should I just do wood to just be fucking
wood? No, I don't hate this. Red, red, red. Oh, blue. Yeah. I like that. I like this too. I like
this one better. Do I like this or do I not like this? Okay. The part of my brain, it's at the
crossroads where it doesn't know if I hate this or if I love it. It's right at the crossroads and
it hasn't picked a door yet. You guys ever get like that? This is why I need everything pre-built
and done for me. I'm so indecisive. I'm so erratic. You have to just build this house
and sit me down in front of the Sims and be like, how's that look? And I'll go, well, it looks great.
Even if you, if you deliberately made a dog shit house and sat me down and told me, hey,
here's your house. What do you think? I'd be like, oh, cool. Oh, nice. I love it. I love the carpet.
Okay. That's that. What about, this is the bathroom. Weird, but okay. This is the bedroom. Wait,
where's the kid's sleep? I need to make a kid room. This is like a magic eye house. I can't wait to
like be sit on the ceiling looking down and just cross my eyes and like an elephant comes into view.
Carpet in the bathroom? This is not carpet, isn't it? I thought that's tile. I need a wallpaper.
Those walls up. This is just the first house. Relax. It's, I got like, I got all day. All right.
That was the worst part when you can't find that one piece of the house. Oh, come on. Where is it?
There it is. Why is Sims music goes so hard? Sims 1 really might be one of the best
gaming soundtracks ever. I really believe that. Okay. Wait, I didn't want to do this. Oh,
shit. I screwed it up. I want, what do I want for the kitchen? How about this?
Ooh, that's like a nice like sand in the kitchen. I like it. They're gonna be paintings and stuff.
Nobody said it's a pickle house. What are you talking about? Windows. Yeah, I'm just, hold on.
How is this a pickle? All right. Bathroom. I want the bathroom to really, really just pop
and be really cool. Let's do something, something wild, something wild. You know what I mean?
Like this. Oh yeah. That's wild. Love it. That's not the bathroom. Shit. What am I doing? Okay.
Well, I can fix that later. I'm just wasting so much money. Money is so valuable in The Sims 1 and
2. Where's this last piece? There we are. That's it, right? All right. Now this bedroom, let's do,
ooh, I kind of like this. This is a Russian grandma house. I can't laugh at this.
Okay. I know people are going to make me laugh today and I'm trying to not like, because somebody
said you're making the Among Us map. I don't even play it, but that's funny. I like know what that
is. Should I just make this Among Us? Oh, this is admin. I don't even know what admin does. I don't
know what admin is and it's not always that somebody's there getting in trouble. Okay. That's
a good start. This looks unfinished because it looks so stupid. Okay. I have 8,600 bucks. I need,
oh shit, I need doors. Men's room door. Should I have like a funny little, oh, there's like a,
look, it's like a public bathroom, but it's not. Do you need two public bathroom doors?
I hate it. What about the kid's room? I'll figure that out in a second. The kid sleeps in a crib.
No, nevermind. That's a baby. Ooh, is this a slider? No, it's not. I'm just, whatever,
just go with a standard basic door. No, that's a, that's the bathroom door. What's with all the
fucked up doors? Beach in door? Why do all these look like cartoon doors or hotel rooms? I just
want like a regular door. Celebrity security door? Wait, this is what we were just talking about.
It's a video game. All right, we're just going to go with the standard boring one. Now I just want
like an interior door. Office door. I forgot how ugly the Sims 1 stuff really could be.
Fancy door? Folk mountain door? I mean, Alpine snow door? These are all so weird.
All right, everyone, whatever. This is so boring, but I just need to get people into the house first.
Okay. All right, all right, all right, all right. Now we need windows. Zerk off room. Just we,
I don't have enough money to make the Zerk off room. All right. All right. So finally,
I gotta get appliances in here because I have to work in reverse. Appliances. So which
are we talking about refrigerators? Should I just pony up for the extremely expensive one?
Even this is a door. This is just a door. This is just a bureau. What the fuck? Never cold
food hold. Food hold? Why did I say it like that? Food hold? It's because of the rhyme. All right,
this is the standard one. This is fine. All right, how do I want this to play? You walk in here,
fridge always goes in the corner. That looks all right. What about stoves? Large appliances.
Here we go. Stove. No, this is a trash compactor. What do these things do? This kind of scares me.
So any of you trash compactor Andes, I have a question. Does this like crush the trash?
Do you put a bunch of trash in here and then you close the door and you press the button and it
like squishes it and crushes it? Isn't that like kind of scary? Like I feel like that would be
like scary. And then what? So you condense. So then what do you do with it after that?
Is it just crushed on the bottom? How do you get it out of there? What do you do with it?
They're dangerous. Yeah, but so what do you do? Just like, is there a bag in there?
So is there like a bag you put the trash into the bag and then it crushes the bag?
Like, how do you get it out of here? He doesn't know. What is this American shit? I don't know.
I'm asking. I don't have one of these. I've never seen one of these before. Are you pretending? No,
no. Like, look, I understand what it does. I'm asking like, is like, is there a bag or something
inside of this machine? Like, what do you do with it after it's crushed? What? How do you get it out?
In the bag? You don't. It's a video game. What? Hold on. Somebody said it. It crushes it with
the bag inside of there and it crushes the bag. When the bag break? Let's find out. I kind of
want to know. 375? Just put it outside. Whatever. Fuck it. I wouldn't be scared of it out there.
12 people have died from a trash compactor. What? Where's the stove? Should I get like a stand-up
stove? This is like a sink. Just put a barbecue in here.
Perfect. Why do I feel like a shitload of American dudes would rather this than having an actual
stove? Okay, I'm doing it. Fuck it. Let's go. I don't even want a stove. Okay, what about this?
All he would eat was just, Dad, I don't want to eat hamburgers, hot dogs, and Italian sausages
anymore. Hold on. The game is on. It's always a game on. You have every channel you watch
Japanese baseball. Yeah, there has to always be a game on. Always. Okay, that's fine. I mean,
it's probably not going to be fine eventually, but whatever. Oh, wait, wait, wait. What do you need?
You need a stove, you need a fridge, you need a... I need like a microwave. Oh, here we go. This is
good. I like that look. This over here. I need a table. This is so bad. Okay, tables. Just a little
one. Shit. This house is not big enough. There we go. I wanted to spin it. Spin it. Okay. It's like
the kitchen in an office. Yeah, kind of. There just needs to be a bunch of cabinets up here.
It's like a gross coffee maker that nobody uses because if you look in where the water goes,
it's rusted and fucking disgusting. No one turns it on. There's the one brave soul every maybe
once a week or two that is so desperate for coffee. A bunch of you in the room and you just hear the
person going, fuck, I need coffee so bad. And they start to turn it on and then they plug it in. It's
like, oh shit, this place is actually going to use the coffee maker in here. And they turn it on.
They're like, oh, how much should I put in there? And it starts to smell. The whole room smells like
that burnt, smelly old plastic smell. And everyone's just like, shit, dude. Oh, I don't
know if you should do that. Sometimes once every couple of weeks, once every like month or so,
someone will do that. I used the Keurig at my work and it tasted like death. Yeah. And here,
okay. Here's the thing. I'm going to give you a little bit of a rant here. For an office to have
like a $30 Mr. Coffee in the corner of the office room, of like the break room or something.
But like you, you gotta like, you got employees here. Don't you want your employees to be able
to get like awesome coffee? So they're like happy and they want to like work and shit.
You pony up for like the good one. Get like the good coffee maker that like
fucking cleans itself. And it looks like espresso and shit. Get one of those. People will be lined
up at the door, like get in there and get like a coffee in the morning. And you'll be, you can sit
like in your office and be like, all right, here they go. They're going to be all coffeeed up.
Anybody want a cream? You want cream? I will be running around the office
with a fucking coffee creamer and like those little wood sticks and shit with like mugs.
Everybody's, everyone would have like their own name on the mugs and shit. I'd be like,
you need a creamer in there? I'll just lean in. You tell me when. All right. There you go. All
right. You want more coffee? It's ready. All right. We have a show. We have a microwave
that I got from my grandmother's house after she died. And we've just plugged it in over here.
Why? Like what? Why? Doesn't that make people just fucking hate going to work?
If your break room is the equivalent of like an antique shop and half the stuff is just gross
and doesn't work, nobody wants to go in there. I even have my own fucking office. It's going to
be a goddamn, this is going to be the best coffee maker that I can get. It's going right there.
There's going to be a whole bar here. There's going to be like flavor pumps. There's going to
be like fucking stirring spoons. And then my company goes out of business in like 30 days.
But you don't want to go too far being like the cool boss. Cause then I would make like a,
I would bring like clowns to work and stuff. And that probably, I can't work Mr. Albertson. You
can't bring like clowns to work like once, like Friday. It's fucking annoying. It was funny on
Friday that one time. I'm like April fools and stuff. But like, no, I don't want to like ride
the slide before I start working. Like, can I just go to work? I don't want to like get on the ride
before work and like have like a big company, like let's all scream on the roller coaster you
built in the backyard. I have like a couple of reports I have to finish. What was I doing?
Where was I going with this? I can't, whatever. I got to move on. I'm thinking of, I'm thinking
of other things that I find funny that I have to like not think of funny. I have to like move on.
All right. Company pizza party. Let's go. What do we got? We need seats. Ooh. And no, no, no,
not yet. Counters. Look, you got to put your money where your mouth is. And like, I might,
what is this? Tea set? I need a toaster oven, right? Yeah. Oh, that's ugly. Ugly. Whoa. Oh,
oh, people still do this. Does people still do that? Can you imagine doing this? This would be
fucking horrifying. This would be terrifying. Why would you, why would you want that? I remember
when I was younger, this was always the, oh, like a big bear carpet. Wow. That's ridiculous.
Like, it was always like the meme for like a wealthy person's house. They had like the bear
carpet and I always thought it was really weird. And like thinking of this now, that's like, isn't
that really strange to have like the bear's like whole body flayed out, like dead with his head on?
What the fuck are people doing this for? I can't, I could not stand on that or lie down on that and
be comfortable. It would give me like anxiety. I'd be like, this is like fucked up. Vegan Andy.
Okay. There's a difference between not eating like meat and this, okay, this is like a flayed
out, like dead bear on the ground. You can't, this is different. This is like a different,
there's a huge spectrum here. It looks like it's horrible. That's horrible looking. What the fuck?
What is that? What do you think leather is? I don't, look, listen, I don't wait. I don't have like
leather clothes. And look, look, look, if you, if you have leather, like a leather wallet or something,
okay, there's leather, right? Leather is a thing. But like, if there was like a dead skinned cow
on the ground in your house, it would be a little weird, wouldn't it? It's like you stopped at like
the halfway point. No, no, no, no, no, no. Don't turn that. I want that, I want that skinned cow
with its head on lying on the ground and I want to, I want to step on it. I want to roll around in
it. I want to like get in there and roll around on him. That's different than having like a leather
wallet in your pocket. I'm sorry. I will die on that hill. That's why Jerma uses ridge wallets.
I can't say that because you all fucking, you all just like memed me to death.
All right, I keep getting distracted. Let's go. What do I need? I need chairs.
These are all right. How many people live here? Three. There'll be no more than two people sitting
at any given time. Rule of thumb, if you have a table and chairs in your house, this is very
important. The amount of chairs you have, half of them will always be used. So if you have like
six seats at a dining table, three to four will have people sitting at them at any given time.
So you go practical. Unless it's like seven people in your family or something.
No windows. I'm working on it. Ooh, I like that. 45. Oh, wait, wait, wait. I'm almost out of money.
All right. Beds. I need a, this is $3,000. What? That's too much. Are these the only
beds that two people can sleep in? Okay. I need a bed for the kid too. That's weird. Um,
I need another room. That would be so odd. No, that would be weird. Let me make another room.
Everybody relax. Would it be like an offshoot from this one? No, but then you'd have to go
into the, no. Okay. This is the, oh, this is a kid's room. It's gotta be fun. Don't worry. I'll
make it fun on the walls. See? Wait, no. This is fun. Well, that's actually, that kind of looks
dirty. See? This looks like skin. Whatever. Among us. I fucking, I, God, I'm not, whatever. Okay.
Now we can put the bed in here. Everybody needs to get a job too. What's the comfort on this thing?
Comfort seven, energy eight. Yeah, that's fine. Against the wall here. And then I need some other
stuff in the bedroom. Lighting. Well, we need lights. I need windows too. All right. Hanging lamps.
Perfect. Put this in here. Right there. Right above the bed. Like the hanging spikes.
At least in the bathroom. What are these? It's a chandelier. Oh, how about right here? Right above.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? What do you mean? It's like a McDonald's warming lamp.
It's like a lizard lamp. Whatever. I'm going to put like a humidifier in here too. I need some,
uh, what do I need? Surfaces. I need some end tables. Hmm. I'm almost out of money. What are
these fucked up end tables? I just want a regular end table. Just a little end table. This stuff is
just so weird. Like I don't want like a big fucking wine jug in my house. Here we go. Wine jug.
Jug, jug, jug, jug. And she can get in bed like that. Oh, we need a computer. Wait, wait, wait,
couch and TV. TV is going to have to go, okay, this way. All right. We're going to have to work
for the TV and the couch. Cause I don't, how do you get a job in The Sims 1? Why do I have this?
I don't know. I don't even have a bathroom. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. A journal?
Ladder eight. If you had this in your house, I would probably leave. I would leave. I would
find a way to stop talking to you over like a few months. Yeah. I wouldn't do it outright. I would,
we'd continue to hang out. We'd, but whatever. But like over like the next six months, I'm going
to make sure I find a way to stop talking to you. Cause like long-term, I'm not sure that
you and I are going to get along. What's this? Shootout? Why would you want this?
I really want it, but it's stupid. What's the bladder? Is this, why is this so weird?
It's a, you pull the handle to flush? Why is there a big box up there? Oh, this hot tub. What the
fuck is this? It's a beach shower? This doesn't get you clean? Shower tub tank? I only have one.
Okay. No, no, no. I gotta go. I can't, I need toilet, shower, sink. I'm out of money. I have
no more money. People are going to have to wash their hands in the sink. I don't have a sink.
Shit. All right. That's it. That's it. That's it. I have $98. That's it. All right. There's
no windows. Whatever. Too bad. How are we doing? What's this? All right. We've got Arthur,
Jane, and caramel sweets. You like the room so far? That's not your bed. That's not your bed.
That's not even your bed. All right. What does caramel, what does caramel sweets have to think
about it? Oh, well, uh, well, I'm reading the newspaper around here. I'm incredibly intelligent.
Now Jones is down today. Then it, then that part of the pilot, it cuts to him like brushing his
teeth in the shower. You know what I mean? Who the fuck is this? Mystery man. Somebody open that.
What is this? Oh, making a coffee. He trash compacted the newspaper. It's time for school.
Okay. Somebody open this magic box. Magiko's magical starter kit. This starter kit is a
complimentary gift from the friendly folks at Magiko Inc. who invite you to try their
line of magical products for the home. This box includes everything you need to make your first
spell. For more information on products and ingredients consult your spell book and home
catalog or visit your new neighbors at Magic Town. Oh, I don't, what the fuck is this?
No, don't, don't, no, no, no, don't go in. What is this weird stuff?
I don't want to jump in. No, we have to like live a normal life for a few minutes.
Look up, ask about, look up spells, add to inventory, magic wand. I need to move this shit.
Oh my God. Hold on. I need to hold it. Jesus. What do I do with this stuff?
I didn't buy this stuff. All right. Um, just get this fucking over here for a little bit. I don't
know. I don't have like a weird like computer now. My magic hole to like wonderland. All right.
Put it over here. Somebody has to get a job. All right. What time is it? Eight. All right.
How do you get a job? Read the newspaper. Oh shit. You whole, you have a whole ass living room,
sir. I know, but I don't have any money. It's just in here rubbing my belly.
Let's slow dance in the bathroom. How do you get a job? Oh, come on. Paper girl.
Wait, didn't we just get the paper? We got the paper like an hour ago. Oh, find a job. What's
that? Find agent who's hot. Wait, what is that? What is that? All right. We're going to meet the
goth family. This is very important. Shake hands. The original sim city times. The only job offer
the paper today is the paranormal career of a psychic phone friend. Our 6 PM to 12 AM pay
a hundred dollars a day. Do you want this job? Yes. Do I? Psychic? Should, should Arthur Sweets
be a psychic? Wait, do I, I don't have to leave. Sure. All right. Hi everybody. Read the goth
family. How's everybody? Why they hate this room so much? Come in. Oh, you idiot. No, no,
greet. Come here. I don't like tennis. You can come in. I have no shoes on. All right. You take
a look at this. What's this thing? Read, recycle. Who's hot? It's like a magazine.
How's Caramel doing? Caramel is doing fine. When do they start killing each other? Um,
I don't have that. I don't have, that is not in this. Who's hot in Studio Town?
Superstar Jackie somebody. Celebrity. Raquel somebody. Carrie somebody. Russell somebody.
Jean somebody. Talk of the town. Gloria somebody. Ian somebody. Lindsay somebody. Tina somebody.
And Christopher somebody. Is there anybody else that is here? That seems like a really
loaded list of this family. Okay. What the fuck are you doing? What are you doing?
What are these two doing together? What was that on his hand? What's he doing?
Come to a puppet show in front of the, to your like wife? Do it again, please. You're like
massaging him? That was just Cosmo from Fairly Oddparents. Anybody want a coffee?
I gotta clean up all this shit. What time does he have to go to work? Studio Town.
Insider. Did aliens abduct celebrity Russell somebody? Our editorial staff was shocked to
learn of the 14 hour disappearance last week. Why the extraterrestrial suspicion? Long time
friends speak of an entirely new personality. 14 hour disappearance last week? Isn't that like,
not that much time? 14 hour disappearance? Wouldn't that be like, that's not even a whole day.
They could have been at like work. They went to bed. Yeah, they like went to work and went
to bed or something. All right, who is this? This is a brag. What do we need right now? I need fun.
There's nothing fun in this whole house. Can we make food?
The grill. Okay, let's grill food. This is gonna, this is gonna end badly. I should save it. I
think this is gonna end badly, right? This is gonna end so badly. All right, I'm gonna burn
this whole house down and I'm gonna jump in like the goofy hole. Why am I afraid of it? Hey,
hey Goth. Mortimer, you want to come give me a hand? You're gonna get CO2 poisoning
because there's no windows. Wait, what are you doing? What are you doing? She brought out milk
and what are you doing? What? Did somebody go in the hole? Oh, fresh burgers. Who wants
fresh burgers? That's all we have. Burgers for breakfast, burgers for lunch, burgers for dinner.
Jane doesn't like burgers. Take it out with your hand?
Well, oh, somebody knows what to do. You put the whole plate in? I don't have a roof. Oh,
well, I just need to go to work for one day. Are you hungry? Eat another burger then.
If you're hungry, eat. Why are they not eating? What time do you get home from school?
This thing's off, right? There's no sink and there's no dishwasher.
I mean, I have this. I don't like the food.
Eat. How did we? Everybody got hungrier. What time do I have to go to work? Where's the newspaper?
Jane, go to work. I don't have a roof. I don't? Yeah, I do. My god, this is an ugly house. I have
a roof. I'm going to the bathroom. What did you do in the bathroom? You took a shower?
Do I need more than one bathroom? Why are there so many people in here? This is a line to the toilet.
All right, get them to leave. All right, goodbye. Yeah, clean up. Clean up and you get a job too.
Oh, Tiffany, new resident here. Wait, come here. Are you going to my trash?
Here. So we, wait, are we both going to be psychics? That's stupid. We can't both be psychics.
No, wait for tomorrow. All right. Yeah, everybody get out. We have to clean up.
Nobody touch my weird whimsical devices out here, please.
And we need to be able to have like a party and stuff and greet people.
Oh, there needs to be food for her. Is there a hamburger on the ground?
Can you eat the hamburger that's on the ground? This is not even a house.
This is supposed to be like a log cabin. Like, there's nothing. There's like amenities in here.
What is this? Whose dog is this? Buzz.
Whose dog is Buzz? All right, what do you need? You need fun. All right, go play with the dog.
Where did he get that? Comfort, energy, fun. All right, they like hate everything.
All right, stop drinking coffee. Get away from the coffee machine.
Why do people keep getting stuck in here?
Why do people have to go to the bathroom so much?
Am I going crazy or is this bathroom just non-stop being used? Wait, the carpool?
It's nicely decorated. All right, Arthur. All right, you need to take a shower.
Everybody get out of here. Go in. Go in. Why wouldn't I go in the shower?
Why is the bathroom the coolest place in the whole house?
All of you leave. Get out. Quick shower. Hurry. All right, you schmooze it up with Tiffany. What?
Dog using the bathroom? Okay, comfort. What are you doing? Get out of here.
Naked. All right, run. I have to go to work. Get the fuck out of the goddamn way.
Kiss cheek. Just get out of the way. He's stuck. I'm gonna miss my ride. Why would I do this to this guy?
Go to work, man. Hurry up. I gotta chill out. Hurry up. Dog, get out of the way. Watch out.
What happened? Wait, what's going on?
The dog won't get out of the way.
The dog won't move. I can't go to work.
Somebody put it out. Somebody put it out quick.
The dog. Somebody do something. Put it out.
Come on, Jane. You can do it. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine. We're fine.
Jane's got it. She's doing fine. She's gonna put out the fire. Oh, no. Somebody else do it.
Put it out. The dog just pissed. Put it out. Hey, you don't have any frame to use the coffee maker.
He was supposed to make a coffee. He's just pissed that there's no furniture.
What did you put in here? Come on, Jane. You got it. Excellent work. The fire didn't continue to spread.
Let's celebrate with an espresso. Jane, you deserve it. That fucking dog being in the way.
That's the funniest shit. Somebody get this dog out of the road. What the fuck? I'm late to work.
All right. There's no damage. Everything's fine. Jane Sweets, let's give it up.
That was really, really good. We have to go to bed. This person's been here for like 13 hours.
We've just been draining espresso and not sleeping for like three days.
All right. Yeah, goodbye. It was very nice to see you. Goodbye. Goodbye. Have a great day.
It's time to go to bed. We need to clean up. Clean up. Clean up. Go to sleep. Say goodbye. Thanks
for coming. What time does she get back? 12? All right. Leave. I don't know why. I just thought
she got stuck in there. No, no. No more company. We don't have time for any more company. It was
a really fun party. Need a phone to call the police. I need more than $38. I can't call anybody
until I have enough money to buy the thing that calls people. Clean up. Pick all this up. Come on.
Ridiculous. All right. You're going to bed. That's good. Good. Energy. Sleep. All right.
Kids in bed. What is... I don't understand what keeps happening here. What is doing this? Why do
you have to go to the bathroom again? Again? This is weird, right? They keep going to the...
Is it because the toilet is from like the 15th century? All right. You're asleep. You'll be
good for school tomorrow. All right. Interest. Toys and pets. Ooh. She wants a dog or a cat or
something. Raids. B+. What do you call the dog? That's pretty good. That's B+. That's fine.
Don't need to be anyone in that. Why do I hear that noise? Why was... Why did they just play that
noise? Why did it do that? That's terrifying. I don't see anything. Was a burglar went by?
Is this the dog pee? Why is this on my screen? That's not my problem. Why do I have to clean up
the dog pee over here? What was that? All right. You need to go to bed. Bed. Bed. Bed. Bed. Time
for bed. Energy and comfort. When do I get home? 5? 12? 6 to 12 a.m. All right. I'll get back in
like five minutes. 100 bucks. Just save it. All right. Arthur, go. You take care of the stuff
outside. Clean this up. Plate and the sink. Prepare. Okay. How are you doing on personality?
You need to go to bed. He needs to be ready at 4 p.m. tomorrow. Fix the sink. All right.
Fresh burgers before bed. Come on. Fix it. Did you not fix it? Fix it. Oh, he got it. Okay.
All right. Time for bed. What do you need? You have hygiene's good. Energy. You need to eat.
No, he's actually good for food. But eat anyways. Okay. Then I'll be able... I only have $118.
Fuck. What can I even buy? All right. Cheeseburgers are too expensive.
No, no cheating. I'm not cheating. I'm not going to type in rosebud. No. All right. Now I need
comfort. Just head to bed. Then I'll be ready for work tomorrow. Then I'll get promoted. I need a
TV. Sell the coffee maker? All right. I have... Seriously, this is the hunger. She has eaten two
cheeseburgers at this point. She's still hungry. Why? Maybe that's why. Yuck. You made them. Just
eat them. Get a phone. Eat. Eating a hamburger with a fork and knife? She's not eating it. She's
cutting it up. She's pretending to eat it. Why did that not do anything? What do the burgers even do
for food? For hunger? It doesn't even... I didn't... My hunger went back down to where it was. Burgers
suck for food. Oh my god. All right. Go to bed. Everybody go to sleep now. What happened? Oh shit.
She can't get in bed. Another hamburger. Imagine eating... Imagine eating four hamburgers
and still being hungry at 4 a.m. All right. Just go to bed. Get in there now. Sleep. Oh. What?
Excuse me? Aren't we in the same... Aren't we married? Why won't they sleep together?
I mean not married. Not married. They have the same last name and they have a daughter. They don't
know each other. They're roommates. So who is... Who's kid is this? Is it our kid? We're just not
married. Another cheeseburger. This is the fifth cheeseburger. All right. Like shut the fuck up.
Like that would be so irritating. I wouldn't want to share a room with this person. This would suck.
It'd be horrible. Go sleep in a different room if you're going to be like this.
Like get out of here. Go sleep in another room. It just doesn't stop. I need more cooking skill.
I don't know why I thought she was about to eat... I thought she was going to eat the trash because
the food wasn't good from the hamburgers. All right. You need to go... All right. She got an open
bed. There's an available bed. They need to get married quick. She's pissed that all the hamburgers
are gone. Have a snack. Leaving hamburgers out. Like oh here's... Imagine stacking four or five
hamburgers on a plate and leaving it out overnight and that's what you were going to eat tomorrow
morning. Is it a bag of chips for breakfast? Wait the kid can't cook anything? Yuck. I'm going to get
up and find chips in the fridge. Is that what she was singing? Oh shit. Go to the bathroom.
I need to eat. Whether they have food? Okay. I'm just going to sell this weird shit. 100 bucks.
124 dollars I can get this for. What about the weird portal? I can make 500 bucks right now.
I need food. I need a bookshelf with a cooking thing in it. That's what I need. Don't sell the
portal. Go in the hole. Not yet. I need to at least have like a second career. Use that. Why?
Okay. We need fun. We need food. Is there no food? Is there no food I can eat? All right.
I gotta get up anyways. Get up. Get up and make like a quick breakfast. Serve breakfast. Go. Okay.
There should be enough time to eat. Oh god damn it. It hasn't eaten. All right. Well whatever.
Serve breakfast. Clean up. You grill hamburgers for breakfast? Look at all the stuff in the fridge.
What are you doing? What are you doing? I thought I was supposed to throw it away. 20 bucks. 20
dollars? That's like 20 percent of my net worth. Why was that so much money? How are you on energy?
Horrible. Into the into the toaster oven. Ow. I can't stop laughing at this shit. It's stupid.
Like what are you what are you making in here? It's gonna burn.
Oh what is it? It's like a steak. Paper girl. All right. I'm gonna get his shit all the way up.
Just eat it. Eat like three of these. Eat the sink? There's dishes in here. Where'd the plate go?
Did I just crack the crush the plate up and put it down the drain? Yeah. I don't care how bad it
tastes. Just eat it. Eat one more and then you're gonna sit. I need something fun. Is it can I just
buy like a like a yo-yo or something? Can I just buy a yo-yo? Look a stupid train set. Only views
by kids. Fuck. Go watch the tv. This this looks like poltergeist. All right now go watch tv like
an hour. Watch tv. I could put it over here couldn't I? Actually that's a great place to put it. All
right. Are you having fun? Yes. Okay. No. Oh okay. Sit down. Comfortable for him to stand. What? He was
just more comfortable standing than sitting in here. All right now go to the bathroom. What about
a job? Find a job and then eat more of this and then you watch tv. Get out. Go back to the bathroom
and take a shower. Eight dollar net worth? Yeah. I just I'll be okay. Musician career for a subway
musician. Ninety dollars a day to be a musician in the subway. Do it. Car will arrive at 2 p.m.
All right nice. This cat. It's a random cat. Hey Lenny the person thanks for the 25 community subs
and video v for 20 community subs as well. Both of you back to back. A lot of subs. Thanks guys.
Let the cat go. Thank you for the subs. Run to the cat. No wait wait wait. Cat cat cat. You love pets.
Don't eat. Don't eat. Don't eat. Don't eat. Go for you. She loves pets. Look at these animals over here.
Her fun is about to skyrocket. She loves animals. He begs. Where's this other? Is another animal?
Where's this other animal? Where's this animal? He begged? Why is she like Dr. Dolittle?
All right hit the the car is going to be. How are you having? You drink an espresso quick.
Espresso. Drink like three of them. Another one. Another one. Another one. More more more more. More
coffee. One more coffee. Why are all the animals coming into the house? Okay go to work. Hurry up.
Go. Oh stop. Oh this is the one that goes.
Right. I made it to work. What happened? What happened?
Like okay. Is she missing school? No she just got back from school.
But who is it? Pets are these. Fluffy. Starving. I'll fix it.
Okay come on come on come on. Is the animals attracted to the house because there's so much
junk everywhere? All right hurry up and turn this shit off. This is why you can't have more
than one sim in any house. If you. You just run out of money. Clean. Clean. Clean. Get everything
cleaned up. Did you just put a cat in there? Oh my god. It was like I heard the sound. I heard like
and then the cat just goes. Clean this shit up. Oh my god. Okay just relax. We need
I need food. I need food. I need food right now. I only have what costs three dollars.
I don't know what this. I don't care what this thing is. Spellbound wand charger. All right I'm
gonna at least sell the table. Truly charming end table. I don't. I don't care about that.
An end table? Who gives a shit? Okay I got 183 bucks. That's enough to make food. That's enough.
Hold on. Wait wait wait. Yeah I gotta wait till I make enough money. Sell the chandelier.
Okay all right now I need. Let's get some essentials. I need a place to sit down.
I just want a normal toilet. Like this thing sucks. Now hot tub. Shower. Okay I need a sink.
Like an actual sink. Counter. I need a counter. Go that way. Sink is going to be right here.
Okay is it expensive? Okay here we go. Finally. Okay. The grill is way too dangerous. It's way
too dangerous. I gotta get rid of it. It's too dangerous. I'll put it out here. Hamburgers suck.
They're horrible. How much is like a regular stove? If I had known that hamburgers were going to be
like you need eight of them before you can fill the hunger bar. It's 400 bucks for a stove.
All right that's it. Now I should be fine. I need a trash bag. All right get that inside.
Is there anything else? I'll just just. I don't need. No no I don't need. I don't need a trash
thing. All right now I'm ready. I'm good to go. I have a stove. Get cheaper chairs. Oh I need
something fun to do. Fun. Can only be used by kids. Creativity. Knowledge. Magic. Is this fun?
I don't understand. Can only be used by adults. The start here is spell book. I just want pets.
Oh a fish bowl. How do you get a pet? It's chicken. Holiday cookies. A birthday cake. There we go.
Trash can but I don't need this. I just I need something fun. Video. Audio. Phone. I need fun.
Where would this be? Is this miscellaneous? Recreation. Okay here we go. Here we go.
It's the chess board. Okay basketball. I need 650 bucks. 20,000 aquatic playhouse. What? I need a
bookcase. I don't have enough money. What can they do for fun? Well we'll just wait till I get back.
Why am I saying this is me? What do you mean when I get back? Why am I putting this on? This is me.
This apparently is me. Oh my god everything's broken. All right go to bed. Platter. Fun. Comfort.
You need to eat. All right get the dog out of here. Have a quick dinner. Serve dinner. Go.
You've not even talked to the child yet. Because I have. I do not burn the house down please.
I'm gonna come back with 100 bucks. It's a roommate. Good. All right time for food. Get in here.
Let's talk. Let's talk. Let's find out like what how what your daughter likes.
Oh
You're good. There we go. Okay now go with no fun.
Tease or something. Like that's like that fun right? Like a fun like oh I'm gonna like scare
you right? Like haha that's fun for like a kid right? Okay go have fun. You need more food.
What do you think about aliens? I think aliens are so cool. No you don't. That's a lie.
You don't like aliens. You hate aliens. Why are you pretending?
I remember that one.
All right time for bed. You will have fun tomorrow. I promise.
Bring it in. Bring it in. Wait oh you've just been promoted to conspiracy theorist.
They're out to get you. You just know it. That suspicious warning on the phone the other night
proved it too. Charm the locals and perhaps you'll be able to get to the root of all this
supposedly random but you know better. Chaos in Sim City. You now work from 11 pm to 5 am.
Starting immediately you brought home 230 today and got a bonus of 260. Nice. That'd be like a
podcast room. All right now we can finally afford a bookcase which would be good. That's
gonna be lots of fun. Good. Everybody start reading. Okay now what do you need for the better?
All right charisma and creativity. I need a mirror. Where's a mirror? Decorative mirror?
Where would this be? Miscellaneous? Surfaces? Lighting, plumbing, appliances, electronics,
miscellaneous. There we go okay. Which one has a good charisma? Plus charisma, plus charisma,
plus charisma. Can only be used by, all right that's fine. Toilet. Now you gotta do it in
front of the sink. I know it's in front of the sink. Get on there. All right you know what to do.
Get to work. What's going on? Jesus Christ. Um well let's go to the bathroom. There's a bathroom
here. There's a bathroom in the house. Why? All right there's still food here. Grab a plate. I know
I'm working on it. How are you untied? Okay you're not. I gotta take care of you later okay.
You just go to the bathroom. Go to bed. Stop drinking coffee. That's not doing anything for
you. That's making it worse. Buy another bed. I don't. I can't. Stop drinking coffee. Go to the
bathroom and take a shower and then go to sleep. No no take go. No no no no no no. Whatever. It
doesn't matter what order. Just go. Okay you need to eat again and clean this crap up. Sell the king
bed. I will. Don't they have bills in this game? Not yet okay. All right good. Pick up that trash.
I just put my hands in it and it was going. Okay how's this now clean? Recycle this. Hurry up.
I need like a little garden or something. All right are you good? All right eat this last meal
and then you go to bed and then he's gonna go talking to the mirror for like six hours.
What time does she work? Three to eight pm. All right so your carpool arrives at two.
All right you gotta go to bed. All right go to bed. You're gonna take a piss. Now you are going
to stare at this mirror. You're gonna practice your speech. It's a carpool for the subway musicians.
Good all right. Because you need to be at least. Oh boy. This will go up. This will go up.
Here we go. How much do I need for the next promotion? I mean one charisma. Creativity
is painting right? And the piano. Are you gonna get a piano? Put him to bed. It's 3am. Well he
doesn't work until like 11pm. Yeah he's good. He'll sleep all day. All right just sit down
and watch like tv. Oh study cooking while you're at it. Kitchen chairs in front of the tv are
monstrous. The tv is just very small. And do it again. Get a point in cooking. Oh read it.
No you're fine. Read that book. You're not allowed until you read that book and get one point in
cooking. Go to bed after that. Oh fine. All right it's almost time for school. When's the bus come?
In like 20 minutes right? Can the kid drink coffee? No of course not. All right you only
have time to go to the bathroom and wash your hands. Oh my god that was like that was horrible.
All right go to the bathroom wash your hands. Uh have a quick breakfast. I've learned some new
things. I'm gonna be able to make sure you get it. Is he good? Okay all right we're fine. He's
gonna be good. He's gonna be good. Go to the bathroom. Wash your hands. Dad oh no no get up
get up get up get up. Where is it? Did I pay for it? Where'd it go? Oh my fucking god whatever.
Put food into the toaster oven and fall asleep on the ground. She's fine. She needs to go to
school and have fun. She wants to learn on her own. She's desperate for fun. Go to school I know.
I I will build you a I swear to god I promise I will build you like a full toys room or something.
Now you need to get up because you work in what 2 p.m. All right you how you doing? Looking for
a promotion here. Comfort's not great. We're at 2 p.m. though that's fine. She's up. We need
Oh that's why everybody's going to the bathroom so much. It's because they're just drinking a shit
load of coffee. All right now sit here and enjoy your coffee. I like want one of these right now.
I want one of those right now. Don't you? All right now go sit pick up a book. What what happened?
Why are there bugs everywhere? Oh go get the bugs go get the bugs bugs bugs bugs bugs. Spray them.
Don't breathe it in. I still hear them. You guys still hear them? Oh get them get them get them get
them. Is that it? All right that's fine. Read a book. Now you need to take a shower. What time is
it? A couple hours right? Now use take a shower. Read a book for a little bit. You got like an hour
or two. Here we go. Our pool will be in an hour so all right stop. Go to the bathroom and you're
gonna you're gonna just wash your hands. That's all the time you have. All right we're in the
windscreen. This is fine. He begged. All right now he is gonna get a promotion here soon. It's home
from school. Stop. Oh my god get out of the way. Get out of the way. Is she trapped? Oh my god
she doesn't want to leave school. She's so oh oh god. Read a book. She's so desperate for fun.
She's burping into the air. Be teased. Let her read. Let her read the book Arthur. Just let her
read. Be teased. Be teased. No will you just go fuck off. Let her get some fun please. What did
you do? Oh my fucking god. Why does everything suck? Why does everything just get destroyed?
It's been like 15 in-game days in The Sims so far. Maybe 20. And every appliance is broken twice.
This house sucks. These appliances are terrible. I have to repair the sink. I've been using it
for three or four days. This is really eating into my time here. The Sims one is fucking impossible.
You got it. I'll be all right.
She's doing fine. And then after this I'm gonna 11 pm. So 10 pm I gotta be ready.
Let's make some food. Wait. Study cooking so I can make better meals. I mean uh-uh.
You know you don't uh-uh me. Go and read a book. Well um should we just both read a book together
at the same time? Reading is boring as fuck. Play video games. I feel like we're racing to
see who can finish the book faster. I mean that's kind of fun. Okay now will you learn cooking so
you can make food? Why? What's wrong? Game brought home 90 bucks. You mean what are you too depressed
to read? Why? Why don't they ever move? All right let's uh let's have like a family um let's like
have a family night. You know what I mean? Because what can we do? I know what we can do. Where's it?
Where's the toy train set? There it is. All right family let's go. Everybody get over here. We're
gonna have a family night. I don't like cats. All right family night. Stop fighting. Yes we're gonna
get everyone get her on the train and we're gonna have a family night. Here we go. Yuck. No he hates
it. What's wrong with it? No it's have fun together. Play. They hate it. Come on. Oh is this not fun?
This isn't fun. She's losing fun. Oh shit the car is gonna be here soon. All right somebody make um
food real quick. Have a quick dinner but then give it. I'm gonna make her put it on the ground. I'm
gonna take it from her. You go to the bathroom. Come on dude. No. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Put it out.
What? Oh no a skunk has decided to make your lot its new home. Better call animal control to
relocate this pest before he causes trouble. Where is the skunk? Somebody put him out. Somebody help him.
Help him. Put him out. Death is in here. What? Is he okay? What? He's all right. He's all right.
He's okay. He's okay. He's okay. Fuck death. Who cares? He's alive. He's alive. He's alive. He can't
take him. Put this shit out. Quick. Oh no it's over. It's over. It's over. Get up. Get up. Get up.
Why is it spreading so fast? Where's the kid? Oh shit. She's all right. She's okay. Deep inside
the Arthur has just died though the body is gone. Spirit will always remain. I wish death could
fucking help. Oh no. Put it out. What was that weird like marvel character move? No my stuff.
Way easier to fucking deal with with two people in a house. Way easier. Good. Fuck it. Arthur
Sweet's dead. Never coming back. Is this like is this him? It's easier to work with now.
He's walking outside into the trash. Oh this game is much harder than I remember.
It is like difficult to win. At least you have enough never have enough chairs to what what'd
you say? There's less mouths to feed now. The fact that death lit on fire too. I was like Kenny
that was ridiculous. No cheating. Oh don't worry. I'll get a I'll get a husband.
We will replace Arthur Sweet. Oh my god that was so fucking funny. And the fact that the kid why
the kid is just not even waking up from this. What okay what happens when the is this kid gonna
know that like Arthur's gone? Is he gonna wake is she gonna wake up and be like oh no like Arthur
was it even her dad? This is so fucked up. Holding it with her chin. Please get a fire alarm. Well I
need way more help than that because now I don't have a stove and I don't at least I have a coffee
maker. I can sell the coffee maker. How long is this kid sleeping for? We don't have a stove anymore.
Wine and milk. Okay well we're gonna be fine. Arthur ate way too much anyways. What should I
do with this? I have no where to put it. Hey by the way where's Arthur? And where's our stove?
Why does it smell like burnt charcoal in here? I don't really like aliens that much.
I don't think she knows. Her like fun is fine. Her social is fine. I don't think she understands
what's going on. All right well let's make oh boy okay um take a shower.
By the way wasn't there a like a raccoon or something or a skunk?
Where is it? Where is this skunk? Does it die in the fire? Okay you school soon take a plate
and then I want you to play with the toy. No oh my god what a mess. Actually eat twice
and then take a shower. No no do not go in there. Wait just wait a second get a phone.
Arthur was the skunk. Why does every fucking thing suck? Just don't even have a sink. Put
the plates outside. Like is it even worth having a sink? Honestly go out and just spray yourself
in the face of the hose. Like this is ridiculous. This keeps happening. All right just wait. When
does her thing come repeat? All right you gotta go to bed. God okay um ladder hygiene. Is there
enough time to take a shower and everything? I think there is. Dad is inside the walls.
Wait is this the skunk? School bus will arrive in an hour. Wait I can be friends? Can you make
friends with a skunk? Just go into the house. How do I get rid of the skunk? I can't get rid of the
skunk. I need to call like pest control. Where's the phone? All right it's 50 bucks for a phone
but I need oh I have to call the fucking police or something whatever call throw a party pizza
butler wait I can have a butler what if I don't what are you calling oh I got sprayed by a skunk
oh shit this is so stupid I can't like send home
okay what how I need to call I wish I could call a butler does it cost money to have
to call animal control probably I mean you shouldn't right I gotta get this place under
control you know what the espresso machine's gotta go this is it's a lot of I have to I have to get
rid of it especially I can't I need I have to fucking get this under control who's whistling
wait what is going on over here it's like an animal fight he scared him off holy shit the dog
the dog scared off the skunk that's awesome we need to praise this animal right now that was
amazing you just saved us oh god get him out of here what now they're friends wait I'm very
confused get out of here he's going to go behind the bed I don't understand how this is a nuisance
though Henry Lestank all right get up wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up wake up
it's time to call stop stop what is he doing no it's because the terrain is bumpy they can't
do anything oh what are you doing here comes another fight he's gonna spray it again he's
gonna get sprayed again whose dog is this all right call the fucking animal cops let's go
I'm just called a butler animal control get on the phone uh you like to come and remove a pest
from your lap for 20 bucks oh come on 20 bucks bullshit I want to watch this happen I'm not going
to work today skipping work where is the pest control what the fuck is that it's a cat why are
they just animals all over my lawn does this house just stink where is the pest control guy
it's been like three hours hurry up where's the pest control guy no that's not him I paid
20 for this shit where is it the cat doesn't even give a shit these must be neighborhood animals
but I'm sending them all home being sprayed by skunk I don't understand where the animal control
person is wait there's a wait what what the fuck is this can where is the animal control person
oh god no call the no it's not them this is a mess I'm not throwing a party right now I need
pest control 20 dollars someone will be right there where the fuck is this guy hello there he is
get him you've missed work today whatever is that simple okay now we can go back to normal let's
have it let's go back to our normal life this kid is oh Johnny Johnny oh I smell like a skunk
what's about the terrain is like too bumpy I can't like talk to people nice to meet you Johnny I'm
caramel um let's talk about your interests all right we made a friend how much is a butler all
right what how much things need to be repaired repair that repair all right I gotta call repairman
just you come and you do it because I'm not I'm not doing this shit you don't have any money
I need to repair him in to fix all this I need to clean up you get in the shower take a bath use
the toilet eat some food 50 dollars an hour whoa that's so much money no I'll do it myself okay
it's 5 p.m. tell this kid to leave I don't want this kid to eat any of my food he's gonna walk
and he's gonna grab a plate and he's gonna I'm gonna just gonna piss me off no get out leave
goodbye Johnny thanks for coming over goodbye out you think that's funny oh you're real funny
I told you to leave Johnny he's gone whatever okay why do they have to go to the bathroom so
much this this feels like it's mudded all right okay now you need to go to the you don't yeah
you don't know you're good you don't need these you're fine you're going to watch a little bit
of television and then you're going to go to sleep in that order now you're going to eat and
then you're going to go to bed and then you're going to entertain mom with a hands with a crazy
dance this is mostly liquid how's she doing hunger is good eat another plate clean stop
using the fucking sink I'm gonna delete it every it's like they turn on uh they turn the water
on and they grab the little hose extension that's on people's sinks and they just spray it all over
the fucking floor just don't use the sink anymore go sit down and watch like horror movies and stuff
what are you doing no stop using the sinks just to pee again oh good look it's time almost time
for you to go to bed clean up in here all right it's clean in here fix this no you can't can the
kid do it no all right the kid is almost it's good ready for bed you wanted to a kid would like call
the neighbor right before bed no it's 10 o'clock 10 30 too late go to bed you take a shower take
a piss and then you go watch tv sit down and watch tv and eat this everything is still horrible after
losing arthur it is but will we will improve which is to get back to like a baseline
we'll be okay uh let's we're gonna recycle these throw these away i still need i need a stove i
need to replace the stove how are we doing good good throwing this shit away throwing that away
now what was that wait when i play the jaws music that means something bad happens happening right
god why am i attracting all the animals who cares oh whatever you can't come in the house
can he come in the house you have to call pest control again no he's just he's just a little
asshole he's just gonna do that and leave all right it's 4 20 a.m what time do you yeah i can't have
you miss work again your work isn't okay okay okay at two by 2 p.m i gotta be ready i can do it
serve some breakfast here save it i if this burns down i'm gonna be so pissed
that was her where are you going are you going to clean up all the way across the whole street
all right whatever comfort social all right let's let's have it let's talk come on in here we need
to talk we need to like entertain uh do a crazy dance and then you um ask uh you um talk about
interests i'm gonna get the phone arthur we're fixing your phone line don't pick up the phone
the next time it rings it's scary okay i need to work on my fun switch to like cartoons all right
let's have fun sit with sit with me hang out having fun okay hunger the kid needs to eat
uh the bus is here all right just go to school my energy is so low what you just asleep not even
like six hours ago penis music they're off the penis music 2 p.m right uh one o'clock let's get
up a quick lunch and then i'm gonna pee fucking bugs everywhere shit get those bugs can you get
the bugs how did you get in here how did this cat get in here i don't understand i didn't open the
door oh go go go go go hurry go to work oh go bugs yeah i don't even know what to do
sit and what are your grades like oh c plus so fucked up he's depressed i'm trying the sim
and the sims one to like go to the bathroom take a shower and eat food it takes like six hours sit
down watch those cartoons well at least turn the fucking tv off all right now go back in there
and go like switch to action you need to watch tv for a little while wait this is
it's like horror movies all right go to bed this is our cat now the cat's hungry i'm not your i'm
not your owner the cat is hungry i mean can i feed i don't think i can feed the cat all right clean
up find agent what's that mean it's too much to do there's so many animals okay what can i do to
help this here and you're fun go read a book clean up and then read a book for a while you
have all day tomorrow turn the tv off but she's reading and watching tv at the same time
is actually might help with the fun okay not bad no social you redditor what takes the week to my
work every day animals will give social oh okay i'm going to make the kids gonna wake up soon
i'm gonna serve breakfast save it no weekends and no rest all right at least you got it done
she got it done she got it done she got it done holy shit you have to eat so much food
why does it take so much food to get the hunger to go up it's the third plate of food
yeah get up hey go to the bathroom what do you need to go to the bathroom go to the bathroom
take a shower god eat it's such a ridiculous snoring please mute the snoring i don't think
i can that's like a major part of the whole game i just have to get to a point where i'm not just
chasing my own tail i gotta get like the repair like i everything's broken i'm constantly in a
state of just complete disarray how you doing it's hygiene and bladder you're actually not in a bad
place right now you're but you have no fun fun is really dragging you down read a little book
for a little while before the boss gets here hey also arrive in about an hour all right we're good
mood is fine grades are going to improve you later please the only lights you have in your house is
the tv and lamps directly above their beds nowhere else you don't even have windows for natural light
that's why everything's breaking they can't fucking see what they're doing
uh all right let me i love it i kind of i want like a coffee i'll be right back i want to talk
about something really quick before i go brb so there used to be brb art when i would go brb uh
that is going to have to change because the amount of art because i'm only going to stream like once
or twice a week it's going to be impossible to keep up there is i believe a thousand pieces of
art that are just in the backlog which is just impossible i will never be able to keep up with
it so for the time being uh we're pausing submissions until i can figure out a solution
and there are a few solutions that i think i want to do yeah that is comic sans isn't it uh there
are a few different solutions it's it's going to become impossible because we did the math that i
will be like four and a half months six months behind always and it's going to get to a point
where there might be two three four thousand submissions that are in the backlog and they
will never be shown ever and remember i only stream once a week so showing artwork for like
a stream is impossible if i'm only going to stream once maybe twice a week i am coming up
with something to do and it might be really fun it might be really interesting i'll tell you when
i have that solution it's being worked on right now show them on multiple screens at once just
have two hour long vrbs one a second that would be so bad no but so brb art is on pause right now
until i can figure out what i'm gonna do and i do want to say this i do appreciate anybody that
sends any fan art to this channel um as you've known the channel has grown insanely over the
last year or two right i mean let's say i didn't even look there's 16 000 people here right now
that's fucking crazy i hope you're having fun but it is getting to a point where i'm reducing
the streams and i just can't keep up with it it's so much awesome stuff but it's just impossible
to keep up with i can't even like comprehend that this many people are here watching and on top of
that want to make pieces and artwork and videos and stuff it's it's a lot i can't even it's
incredible but no just know that i don't like it's not that i don't care about art and community
videos and community stuff it's just i've grown in size by like 150 percent and i've reduced the
streams by like 80 percent incredible well i said it wrong uh so yeah i'm gonna try to figure out
something to do it'll be fun it'll be interesting i hope so just know that that's why brb art is
currently like on pause we'll figure it out we always do right i'll be right back go get a snack
i'll get a coffee that's what i'm doing i'll be right back see you guys in a minute sorry i had
to make a coffee it was just i had to it did and when they were drinking the espresso it just looked
so good i had to make my own ready let's go you see it hey there we are oh phone phone phone oh
too late you're still school all right i need to i'm gonna call the repairman i have to call
repairman have him fix this shit it's gonna cost me like 300 bucks but i just don't have the time
i can't fix anything on my own hold on bring in recycle bring in there needs to be some i
in the sims one i always had a maid a cleaning service everybody does you have to do that like
the first thing you do so unfortunately i have to call i'd have to do that too if you don't have a
cleaning service it's no hello oh lights right right right right right okay so i need to have
also here's another thing another really important thing there's no paint on the outside of the house
i think that's causing a shitload of problems there's no paint that's they hate it here
wallpaper do i have something like a lime greenhouse this is too much money i don't have
enough money windows oh my god it's 55 okay i can't afford this i can't afford it you need
lights and windows i can't afford to buy these okay i got windows there is a roof i know there's a
roof whoa there's light in here now holy shit this is what the game's supposed to look like
it's been pitch black the entire time i've been playing is that why they keep spilling
shit and getting water everywhere that has to be what time do i have to get up first things first
you're gonna get up and you're gonna repair the sink in fact get up would you work 3 pm all right
get up fix the sink the cat letter let themselves in again you can do it come on do it come on there's
not much time go why do i feel like the cat just stole something all right it's fixed sink is fixed
step one this sink needs to get god damn it i'm not even close to being ready use the bathroom
ah just call the neighbor and just fucking talk for five seconds and hang up johnny burb whoever
you want to invite just talk to johnny it's nice that you got to relax at home but poor johnny's
school oh right that's the kid i'm never gonna get a promotion at least the sink is fixed it's home
oh see what is that there are no actions of it what is that all those are bills
don't pay just don't even pay them cares seinfeld base god why would you even think that report card
see it's only animals this girl has only relationships with animals no people call
somebody over look just throw a fucking party who cares maybe they'll clean up who am i calling to
throw a party hey thanks for the invite sounds great i'll be right over with some friends if
you call some more people we can have a really big bash throw another party okay um i need social
where are the kids take a witty no nothing don't like it why are people dressed like this
trying to have fun this guy's in a tuxedo everybody's dressed up i don't know the taunt
you hate me they hate us fine fuck off let's make a cry um
um
mime appearing less and less freak
the mysterious mime is that guy screaming i can't get over is i'm i have to stop for a
sec the mysterious mind can be lured out from his den by the sound of people gathering strangely
he is compelled to entertain them
is this mime
oh my god this game is there he is it's a mime everybody get in everybody get inside
um what are you doing am i just steal my like magic one machine what oh please call the police
police police police services please please please call the police call the police call the police
please now get off on arrest him we didn't he just stole from something from my house he stole my um
someone be right over get over hurry up don't let him leave don't let this guy leave
welcome home okay you brought home 90 bucks
there's a police where are the cops all right go go go go get in there rest that guy yes open the
door yes go in there and get the rest of mime this i'll hold the entire neighborhoods here
yes hello there he is he's joking
you should only call the policeman there's an actual emergency this guy stole
where's the kid oh my god i don't have any food you guys have any money
i want i need to like greet these people and i need to talk to all these people so i can
talk to them and have them come over and help me do you have them with the trash no they're
eating the trash i can't believe he took my thing
all right make this motherfucker leave please make this fucking weirdo leave okay get the mime
get the mime away from this door please get make him leave i don't want him over here
is he no no no no no the mime will not leave while the party remains so how do you say boring
is the mime his stay it's i've come to collect my child that's well past my bedtime where's
there a kid who's this is this a kid how do i end the party he's looking for his kid
order a pizza all right i'm gonna order a pizza
what is he doing he's like hanging he was hanging himself what are they in the trash
for they're digging around the trash the pizza would be there in about an hour
hey i know everyone's hungry i'm ordering a pizza i need to get the phone move out of you
i need to answer the phone get the phone get the fucking mime out of the goddamn way
answer the phone who is it
it's just trash number three is very important in your life right now nice okay thanks goodbye
where's the pizza i ordered an hour ago it should be free
i ordered a pizza an hour ago brushing their teeth in here i don't know where the pizza is
is people are starting to leave get the hell out of here i hate this and no one's gonna
even help me clean up it's such a mess everywhere why did i throw a party caramel caramel get up
i ordered a fucking pizza all right can we can the mime leave now and can colby leave why are
you still here what the hell's going on um yeah yeah you're uh you're a little late you're a
little late it's been like six hours it's one it's two o'clock in the morning and you're
delivering a pizza are you kidding me well i want the pizza come here don't let him get away damn
it no don't clean this up let me guess the sink is broken no it's not i have to pay these bills
clean clean clean the kid awake you need to help clean a skunk has decided to make your lot a new
home whatever this guy doesn't do anything just the skunk just sprays other animals
all right get up and help uh help mom clean one one in the bathroom yes what what do you mean
social you just had like 30 people in the house why would you need social interaction the mom is
gonna die not on my watch kids okay do the bills get paid what are your grades like see
shit they hate it out here i have to paint the outside okay this is fine um use the bathroom
yep and then wash your hands in this sink it's the one that's not broken oh my god why does
everything suck in this universe if everything broke everything's breaking why go to school
go school wake up get the phone what time do you have to go to work
2 p.m. holy shit this is awful everything just breaks every single device i have just doesn't
work okay you need to eat you need to be on nightmare difficulty you check what time jane
has to go to work every single day yeah i don't know i forget oh my god there's no time
oh shit she didn't go to work fuck it whatever i was skipping work was skipping school
we're getting to the point where we can not have tons of problems let's take this whole day here
why are there no weekends there's no weekend there's no you have to work every single day
in the sims 1 okay we're gonna take this opportunity clean up the house fucking god
put it out call the police call the fire fire fire fire fire fire fire
jane has missed work today i don't care call the fire department call the fire department call the
fire department call the call call call call call call call help run up run away run away
run run away run away you can't even eat i'm gonna have to order a pizza they're hungry
they don't they're stupid i need to like study cooking i don't even care skip work two days in
a row look if i get fired whatever it was i i can get another job eat stay home both of you no put
it on the ground don't wash it in the bathroom sink put it on the ground they're a mess we need
to eat four meals before we're satisfied all right now talk about interests no don't use this fucking
sink stop using the sink
this is on hard mode why does he have to eat like five times
all right so take a shower
toilet it's it's as if like 10 people live here you didn't even unclog it
oh well go you can make it fun go have fun sing like a song or make it like a dance routine or
something you could make it fun oh yeah oh no i don't have enough money what can i get rid of
sell the carpet can i do that i can make like two or three hundred bucks doing this it's gonna be
grass though no no no no no i'm all right i'm just gonna quit my job i'll get another one later
they can fire me i don't care i gotta get this under control whoa whoa whoa whoa why are these
500 dollars what what the fuck i thought these were cheap chairs oh my god oh my god you gotta
be kidding me we're good i can't believe those are that expensive you were trying to live above your
means it was the espresso machine but whatever i love i love espresso now can i afford a little
couch just a shitty one like this one okay now they'll be happy about that save the money
clean up don't go to work don't go to work oh my god i have bills i didn't pay the bills
clean this whole thing up just don't even go to work throw the bills out
she's gonna get fired anyways yeah it doesn't matter really just doesn't matter i'm at the
first entry part of the job if i get fired it doesn't matter i'll just get a new job the next
day i have 600 bucks to last like a few days in game i'll be fine i'm going to study cooking
make sure i know what i'm doing pop this up throw this shit away getting tired i know i know you're
good you're good you're good clean that up no get up you see sleeping standing up holy shit
fucking gandalf she's doing okay just have a little snack and then go pee all right wake up
and go back to what you're doing oh fuck you missed school again what are you doing
good place of love of god abandon this run everyone is miserable author is dead
house is a mess they'll have much better chance of stability if you use if you use this learned
run i'm fine what are you doing get out of the water all right i'm gonna be fine i don't need
to cheat so this game is always the hardest in the beginning they need to have like a little
bit of social very cool no i don't need to restart trust me i'll be fine fast you in 20 minutes you
tell me i was wrong in exactly 20 minutes from right now say you were wrong and i will restart
but i'll you'll see here we go get this place under control mom is gonna go sleep i'm gonna buy
something fun recreation here we go volleyball kids can play this right kids can't the sofa
and tv i need to okay i need a better tv yep yep better television how do i get this off
okay how much is tv 500 fun for versus yeah all right uh get off the seat i want to move this chair
stop sitting in this chair get out of here just look at this get get a job i did okay now everybody's
really happy we had a sick tv your poor grades are putting you in the express line for military
school if your grades do not improve quickly you may be saluting your superiors in very short order
all young sims need to study and work hard in school to get good grades students must go to
school in a good mood okay they may be banished to military school get that tv on right now
i never would i you sit in front of that and you watch television
you just watch cartoons all day and i'm gonna make you breakfast don't insult cut it out okay
good good the kid's gonna be a great mood don't burn the house down please god thank goodness
okay how you doing mood has improved eat now you need to sit in front you need to go pee and then
sit in front of the tv god damn it stop watch more tv this is purgatory sit down with mom and watch tv
watch television all right she's eating she's in a better mood this is good this mod activated just
don't even get out just just just lose your job in there you're not in a position to work right
this minute i told you 20 just give me 20 minutes that's all i need then we're gonna get out here
i'm gonna eat i'm gonna play with the dogs we're gonna talk about interests what just happened no
no no don't go to work okay go to sleep sleep forget about the phone all i care about is the
kid getting better grades look at this mess whatever it doesn't matter i don't need that
right now excuse me just yeah come on in bob what the hell are you doing here just walking
in the house can i help you what do you want why are you here one more trick no no put that down
that's very important food you're not supposed to eat that that's ours this guy came into ate a
plate get him out of here goodbye get out get up just leave i just mopped this shit up and
now you just did that unless you're gonna fix the sink then fucking get out of here
this kid is doing all the work okay now we just need to we're gonna have some more fun sit down
and watch tv switch to cartoons kids love cartoons stay there and watch don't get up stay here why
flies just why are they flying around the house does the whole house smell those bees all right
she's doing better and then around 8 p.m we're gonna go pee and then we're gonna go to sleep
and then i'm putting like a plant outside look at this she's doing well she's doing good all right
turn off the tv go to the bathroom nice okay wash your hands very good and then go to bed
you're gonna be in a much better mood tomorrow mom will get up we'll make breakfast we'll study
cooking make her study oh shit you're right study for a little bit just a little nothing too crazy
just a little that's it that's fine that's fine just go to bed where are the windows i did i just
i put them in here they're good see i miss arthur we're fine finally she's her grades are gonna
improve she's gonna go with a good mood mom will help get 250 bucks we're fine just doing it for
go to the club or something i have to make it so they're not like suffering before i take them
anywhere all right mom get up mom i want you to clean clean this all up you're good let's do a
little bit of cleaning it's asleep that's fine it's gonna be hungry all right now we need to make
food serve breakfast just fuck that who cares just get in here and make food and we can talk
and then you can watch tv all day this is like so fucked up don't burn the house down don't burn
the house down don't burn the house down okay cook go to a club i once they're not in the about to be
killed i will go after this breakfast perfect kid can wake up eat take a shower and then you're
gonna have you're gonna be it'll be perfect excellent kids gonna be in a great mood eat more i want you
in a full stomach that's how you get good grades it's not about studying all night the night before
it's making sure the morning of your test you have a full breakfast there's no time for you to take
a shower i don't think all right get out get out get out get out there's not time underwater
that was i don't know why i just made that noise all right get out the mood is not good all right
no no no no no no no no pause pause pause pause stop what do you think shit it's okay that's not
a bad mood that's what that move just that mood is fine we did it this kid is now in a better
position oh still has no roof the house has a roof how do i get rid of these flies clean the toilet
clean this room up repair the sink again no no no no no repair man i don't have time to do all this
sink is repaired repair the shower get a window in here all right let's get a window
oh it's built right okay window um something fancy i don't know oh how much is this too much
okay everything's fixed in here okay this is clean why is this flies just flying around get them out
of here what's going on everything's clean in here make her woohoo woohoo what this is also
i don't lose the kid go to woohoo island now hygiene why am i doing this because there's a kid
all right i'm gonna be honest with you the kids in the sims if you have a kid in the house
they're just it's just like a an empty sink it's just like a money sink i they just go to school
they eat and they i can't afford it there's dead plants outside comfort fun i need to get like a
pinball machine i don't know who you are but hi can we hang out for a little bit yes let's
sit on the couch and hang out and talk let's just hang out with this person i don't even
know who this person is but hello come on in she's doing fine all right should i should we
should i go should i take them into town no you don't have school till tomorrow
i just jump in the hole oh eight grades shit jump in the hole no i can't look at these bars
study all right go study yes oh my god what do i do how do i make anybody happy in this game
this bugs and shit what no she's gonna attack my bugs he's getting attacked
she can't move jump in the hole now with the kid all right we're gonna but i what about this
house i did i this is why the sims one is so hard you have to make your first house and sims one
can be one fucking square cube with a fridge and a bed and and you can't have more than two people
we're moving what where can i take you today show amusement parks whoa clown land wow holy shit
look at this place look at my fucking bars i just screamed so loud that was like a tuber scream i'm
sorry holy shit get on this ride what how much is 20 20 dollars wow let's go this is so cool
my old enough to ride this look at how much fun this is holy shit i'm not going to school
wait wait wait wait wait i missed school i skipped school to go to the amusement park
this 20 dollars this ride is crazy view look at the clown you see the clown last day of fun
before military school god crunch berries ah nice
that would hurt okay is there like a comfort machine i need to bring mom here cotton candy
well that was awesome what do you mean i was wrong no look take a look what's going on right now
i'm fine it's kind of weird where are you going where's she going
she's like went like dazed oh no she's like going to look at the clown that's okay well that was
stupid what else is here is this big roller coaster thing i need comfort you popcorn i want to
cotton candy you're wrong i'm not wrong look at look at how much fun this is look i'm going to
send the mom on like vacation or something can i live alone in the house as a kid right now what
else is over here whoa look at this play this machine this is fun insert a coin
this place is crazy i love this place what's this oh mini golf oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh what's this
oh they who spin in circles are without a route and have wandered from the path they need guidance
but be wary of getting in the way you need guidance but be wary of the obstacles in your
way insert another coin i'll tell you more just read that as rick it would have made sense it
would have been like a rick ism are you tired are you weary does life feel drab and dreary
pick your motives up my friend i see fun plus plus around the bend insert another coin
where's this clown this clown was like having a problem it was that oh there he is sonny the
clown what was what was his deal wait is he coming to hang out with me
is there any food i can eat
oh go to the bathroom somebody all right what happened it's fucking screaming your child
has created a fake reality to cope her fact that her true life is pure pain this is your
fault you pun this is like way to coping she's like walking around the living room right now
how's my social i need to bring the mother here all right she's gonna go back she's got school
tomorrow you got school tomorrow go that was fun look at that fun meter you gotta leave back home
it really was just like a made-up world this is shit i have to restart oh god
no i have to redo it fuck okay fine i'm leaving i'm making a new family and these
we'll see how these people do with my new family they'll be in the same neighborhood whatever i'm
gonna just make a tiny little fucking stupid house what are you doing all right good luck
good luck sweets family by the way i'm just making one goddamn person i'm gonna make one person it's
gonna be me and i'm just it's gonna that's it no spouse no children no just me that's it
and a cube with a bathroom and a bed oh my god no give them a call the fire department quick
no no no no no no no no no no just go here just go just go go just go go go go to your
place that you like to be in go on go on go on go on go on go to the back of the clown world
going back to clown place and go ride the rides go ride the rides remember the clown ride yeah
fuck this is horrible i hate this oh god people are coming through that's scary ruined her life
i did not ruin anything crafted gnome is a magical asset to any garden
he who denies the gnome its green thumb accepts the black and blue shin and another coin oh cool
what's this don't deny the gnome look at this place it's like a little garden this is actually
kind of cool again where's um oh go use the bathroom what was the fun plus plus around the bend um i
think it was the clown what's there fun to do here oh well wandering willow no i'm not gonna put her
i'm not gonna go into the well i can tell you let's sit down too take a look at this and then
sit down cool looking well now go ahead have a seat just relax there we go
how long can i stay here for please stop your traumatizing this child
six p.m seven p.m does this place close hi you don't want to talk to me
what can we talk about no come here talk about interests
what's the looney toons hole um if i go back in there
uh i don't i don't kind of i really don't want to see what's down there
talk about interest let's be friends
she smells well i can i'll pick you that up
oh
talk about more interests scary it just jumps out socials going well what oh wow fiona strange
let's jab her
okay talk about interests let's get this to 100
um we're having fun 36 39 jabber um let's like uh no no teasing just talk interest
so if i make a new family and then make a new house does that old house just stay there who
moves into it
okay let's so now i have this new friend this is fiona strange
can i call fiona strange like from a real telephone
okay i'm 79 okay um let's go home i'm gonna go home and i'm gonna call fiona
call the police who's just burped no call neighbor quick this lady's gonna die
no no no no no no no no no who's just what she fell asleep all right run i gotta call call the
fire department get out of the house get out of the house get out of the house get out of the house
get out of the house get out of the house get out of the house get out of the house
get out of the house now get out of the house get out of the house get out of the house
get out of the house go back in the hole god damn it i can't this is too the fire eventually is
gonna it's not be able to spread anymore the fire is gonna end here because it's not gonna be able
to keep going see see we're fine they can't even spread anymore oh come on hurry up i can't even
call anybody no do not go in there what how do i do that what do i do about this i can't do anything
i can't do this it's over i mean yeah very clearly but how do i so now can i leave
i can't can i not get out of here here we go okay neighborhood you've chosen to leave magic
town without saving you will lose all relationship and inventory changes that occur during your visit
if you'd like to save your relationship and inventory change please hold on the
jesus lives there he's stuck in the fantasy i think she'll be all right i think she'll be fine
i kind of like this for me yeah i like that all right this is me i like it very outgoing not very
active i'm very playful i'm kind of nice i'm outgoing and i'm playful and i'm active and i'm
i'm not that neat but i'm active no i'm not i'm playful i'm nice i'm outgoing
i was linked to the coffee pasta the dermacraft coffee pasta don't even i'll just do this there
you go here we are i don't want anybody else in the house i don't want any fucking friends
i don't i just want i just want to be me and exist in a cube with a i'm going to go for it i don't
want anybody else in the family what about auto maybe okay i'm done i have them finished we're
going to move into a family in no here we go nine sim lane what about auto i don't think i can make
an animal can i i think i have to actually go buy one here we go we're starting fresh same
neighborhood build mode i'm gonna this is gonna be the simplest house you've ever seen in your
entire life it needs a bed a bathroom and a kitchen done done that's it it's over living room entryway
bathroom bedroom done floors cheap as cheap as shit i can get these are four dollars three
dollar floors i don't even care oh oh i don't care cool twelve thousand dollars i'll be i'm
gonna be smarter i will i should have a pool too just like a little one a tiny one just to sit in
back door right here that's good okay wallpaper tool i don't want to mess this up windows let's
get these done first natural light good natural light in the bathroom here done wallpaper and
let's make a little a nice little walkway too right floor terrain tool how do i get like uh
just ground like a better ground floor tool like i don't know something like fucking weird like this
shit there okay now it doesn't look like dog shit out here make a second pool no i need doors
something nice something easy minecraft this is a nice little thing right here okay night right
there and then just i don't know something stupid something cool like that fine that's good i need
one to the outside too do that perfect oh oh oh almost done now we need a um like just a little
fence or something like a cute little fence like this i don't know what the fucking people have in
their dumb houses so far so good paint the outside yeah yeah yeah yeah like onyx all right outside of
the house should be something very neutral like a i don't know whatever this is is it hold shift
bathroom dark wild too separated to old lady also old lady oh no too much too much way too much
disgusting terrible awful awful wait what about this lavender bingo all right here we go
i now just need furniture this house is ready we need to add lamps i need some lighting just
something easy just uh like hanging lamps a couple of these no no i hate these standing lamps just
some just regular just regular ones like one of these right in the corner here over here bingo
all right nice cool we just need like a couple of these one in the bedroom right here done
wall lamps in the bathroom your little sconces this is cute no it's not this is cute this this
floor is horrendous looking okay they have light switches then the light switch is not in sims 1
right house doesn't have a roof it does look see roof on pool now let's start adding the furniture
i hate this floor it really is it's awful all right all right i need a good bed a really good
bed what do we got it's a twin bed it doesn't matter comfort nine energy nine need more windows
in the front i will all right i'm gonna i'm gonna spend a lot of money on a big twin bed
actually no this one's fine comfort eight energy nine thousand versus yeah this one's fine that's a
nice bed very nice bed we need a couch we need to move these windows tv's going here how about
this guy i'm for eight energy four room two no chocolate milk one comfort eight this one here
uh it's like doctor's office this one's fine nice tv no i need uh bed tv um okay what else do i want
i need wait where's the kitchen fuck the kitchen i just need a oh shit it's a bathroom i don't need
a kitchen i don't need a kitchen i just use fridge refrigerator get one of the nice ones how much is
this one 2,500 it's worth it it's worth it this is worth it is it fridge and then i need this just
just a stove right here right there i'm gonna get a good stove because these things just burn
in this game sims one there's like a 40 chance that it just burns all right that's it just a
counter i need a fire alarm and a phone where would it be yeah phone phone's gonna be right here on
this wall it's fine okay now i need a fire alarm where is it what about table um i do need like a
counter okay that's good enough i can prepare food here and then bring it here all right this is good
this is fine down the right spot it is okay uh and yes yeah sink is gonna go right here a good one
not one of these dog shit sinks that breaks every time i use it hygiene three room one i do yeah
actually looks like i don't know i don't know it looks weird hey bathroom i'm getting the good
toilet no i'm not yes i am no i'm not shower not the shitty one hygiene six height i have to get
the shitty one don't i hygiene five well whatever okay now i need a sink like look out the window
no fuck that all right fire alarm which is where i'm gonna i can i get some paintings too just like
a little just whatever no no no no what about plants it's like a house plant yeah this like i
need like some i need some character in here fire alarm where's the fire alarm trash right here
electronics there it is where's the really good one is this co2 in this game do i need a carbon
oxide detector what about tv all right i have enough of this and that's it i'm good to go i have
money i don't have to i only have to worry about myself and nobody else it's just me here there's
not like three people to juggle okay i need i need a little walkway out here just like a little like
nice little walkway like oh look at that oh oh pretty very cool okay shit that's too much
is it no it's fine you need a barbecue no i need to have at least a thousand two thousand dollars
to live this is good to go i have every essential i need am i missing anything what am i missing an
alarm i have an alarm i need a bookshelf thank you very much that's absolutely correct all right
this is fun one fun two on three that's two that's huge this shit's so big um that's all right that's
fine all right there's the fire extinguisher this is now ready to go the house has been painted
everything's good i actually have i'm working home i have a pool which are really fun all right what's
the best view probably this one okay here we go all right jeremy elbertson enjoy your new home table
uh i don't need a table dining table i don't i don't think i need one maybe a time maybe just
a little one in one single chair this is such a 90s house all right good to go i can actually
play the game now i don't have just carnage i have to use the bathroom oh shit i'm bored um
use the bathroom and then take a dip in the pool you know you're at 1200 bucks i'm fine
now the game's boring why do i not like this room oh mystery man he's going to deliver like
the mystery uh magic package i'll get auto yeah where's the pet store all right put all this
shit in the backyard back here there's like so much crap here go and visit the sweets house
um i think i'm all right right now i think i'm just gonna chill water the plants 1200 bucks take a
dip in the pool why not take a dip in the pool go save caramel i don't think i can go adopt
caramel can i i don't think it's possible ah my pool thought about that for a second
look at how much fun he's gonna have all right swim around have fun oh the goth family of course
i need to say hello hold on i'm just in my pool delete the ladder delete the ladder he's coming
around quick go to the door greet greet hello don't put any clothes on i'm gonna make bathing suit
all right where's this underwear invite to old town
invite to downtown where are we going
we going why am i on the phone this is a cab you need to ride one of our taxis would be there yes
sure so we're gonna go downtown together he's just leaving they just greeted me he's just leaving
all right let's go going downtown will save the house it's in are you sure you want to leave
yeah let's be ready to go do i not put clothes on just moved in an hour ago uh okay so this is
edgy comfortable electric just some of the world words used to describe the world famous quarry's
place mall farm square ren's day's meeting place eric's boardwalk sim city beach where should i go
beach let's go welcome to the beach is really cool uh let's talk
talk
no i can't not flirt what are you talking about
you can't just go immediately to like flirting what are you talking about
yes you can no you can't
you can't
all right 18 what do you think about this
doesn't like it put it away put the sock but put the sock puppet away put the puppet away
put the puppet away it doesn't like it compliment um talk about interests compliment admire
go
you liked it hey hey how about bobby do you need me good okay uh
no no no no no no no no no um joke
uh compliment again i'm not doing all this stuff okay we'll get to 50 first like i don't want to
like i'm not going to do like kiss hug tickle flirt like we're not doing this until like i i'm
like at least 50 or 60 um ask uh how uh how's how what are you into you're naked i'm not naked i've
got i've got robin's egg blue underwear on i'm not naked all right what are you on 26 i'm not
getting any more all right what about a hug friendly hug
and
it worked okay all right all right okay um hold on you didn't like it you didn't like it
what the hell would you do that for why would you make those noises
mortimer goff is mad oh he found us quick kiss her in front of him i'm about to be slapped
i told you his guy i had to go slower
hey
all right get this guy out of here
oh all right kick this guy's ass i'm not gonna get slapped more than once you know what i mean
you slapped me once shame on me slap me twice say good night because you're gonna get knocked out
can we take this off the street no what's wrong you don't like it
you know like you don't like them way better than you i am so much fucking cooler than you i'm so much
stronger than you just wait till i get my ability to punch him wait no no don't leave just a p oh
very okay minus 37 when can i punch him
minus 37 when when am i able to like attack him here we go attack
this one mortimer goff push him into a car he's trying to leave sorry you don't get to leave
have to come after walking over and slapping me in the face you don't get to leave oh this is just
really really weak that's not uh i i feel like you could push me over and i would die
how come there's more than this right
oh i punch him i want to like i want to attack him you're bullying i'm sorry i was just sitting
here having a conversation with his wife and then he came over and and hit me in the face
so what he he came over and he hit me in the face twice it was not just once it was twice
i think you have to be like minus 50 minus 100 to like actually punch him
see if i can't do it here then i'm just gonna let him go
who cares all right let's go let's go hang out uh get uh chocolates for somebody
oh no i don't want i don't want to buy anything going back in here
not attractive
try on um wait we can can we put on costumes
so anyways i think you're really cute how is this somehow worse
throw it in the ground oh shit i thought this person was on the ground all right what about
claire should we go say hello i need to make friends claire uh i need to greet a bunch of
people fish food rent wait is this mortimer no no stay on no what are you where am i what am i
doing get out of here are you interested in purchasing this outfit yes that'd be less than
50 dollars be teased so so he was just gonna come in and be like
me buy hot dogs forget about this guy he's i don't know where the hell he is i need a hot dog
she's following me around
are we buying hot dogs together we're on a date wait did you just buy me a hot dog
should i grill the hot dog again okay so let's talk how you doing 38
was not here all right that's going good 41 he's pissed he just senses it he slapped
awesome okay we're gonna be over 50 in a second there it is okay uh hug
i don't want to do it i don't want to go too much she didn't like that apparently
i don't think it's gonna have it's not gonna work she's not i don't think she's into us
into us why am i making this like a collective all of us she's not into us
no she's not no she's not it's not like i'm not gonna happen that's it she's not into us we were
at 50 it was worth a shot to be like hey so you know nope not gonna happen why is it trash
everywhere what the fuck i'm devastated it's a it's a married woman guys you going upstairs
oh it's like a party i need to eat something hey friends i need to like come across people
oh i drink
these for us you might need to get rid of mortimer first
uh i just want to see if we're like you're talking about i need to kill mortimer
i just loaded this game up with this file
i need to get a job first i've burnt through like 600 somehow where's my drink
all right kenny's way more fun who's this guy how long are we gonna do this for all right greet
kenny all right you get out of here no just wave all right bye that was really fun let's get
together again soon yeah no i don't think so i don't think that's gonna happen hey your husband's
really like a like a swell guy by the way we're just like dancing
this is so i love it i need to greet everybody i need to have friends so i can throw a party in
here i'm gonna go to my pool and i gotta have a pool party i need to talk to more people so
i can have friends all right greet one more person and i'm leaving cool all right let's go
i have to pee really badly somehow all right out out out i'll just go home how do i go home
do i leave how do i get the hell out of here i know beth and please you're gonna piss yourself
i don't i have to i just want to go home all the taxi cab on the phone i can't even leave
what's wrong with me oh there we go okay is this free hamburgers holy shit it is
just eat all of this food hamburger is really odd the shittiest food in the whole game aren't they
oh i'm not having any fun all right leave call a cab get me out of here i don't have a job to
get to or anything i'm fine go home all right that was fun why do i have all my energy back
oh that was weird okay all right get in the bed to go to sleep oh no a skunk it whatever the
energy is going up crazy okay i get a job now fight the skunk one on one i don't think you can
uh i'm gonna flush and then i'm gonna clean it and i'm gonna use it and then i'm gonna take a shower
and then i'm going to study cooking that sounds like a good idea let's go and queue it up what's
wrong what is that what's a raccoon well whatever i don't care it's a lobster he's just gonna come
knock the trash over it's fine too depressed to study all right well then watch tv so turn it on
the tv and to get some fun in your life so hang out watch a movie what don't watch a movie go
watch tv watch tv man what's the romance okay i keep buying snacks and putting them on the ground
eat the food you have that's like a dinner chip bag okay now study um cooking the flat lining
i have to do at least one to two cooking otherwise i'm just gonna burn the house down
it's gonna happen every time that's how the sims one works plenty of energy there we go one point
in cooking get two go for three points actually two points go for the third point and then i won't
burn the house down anymore there it is nice all right i got three cooking points kind of be a chef
okay let's put that down flush it clean it take a shower flush it clean it use it
uh have lunch clean up recycle go to bed and then i'm gonna get another point in cooking tomorrow i'm
gonna be a chef i'm into that look only me to have to worry about there's not like a kid running
around that i have to feed it's just me i can worry about my own bars there's no uh like husband
or wife it's just me otto otto no no it's otto get out there it really is otto otto he fought
the raccoon he got the raccoon away from the host this is perfect all right you and i are going to
be best friends i don't care whose dog you are where's otto on here praise otto leroy
leroy hick well at least i know leroy leroy is a class clown with a sense of humor playing chase
is his favorite activity okay get back in here i need off the tv clean up didn't i have where's
my lunch okay come on i have three cooking i want to get to a point where i can just spoke to my
bars and that's it there should be no fire anymore what's the percentage to have a fire after like
two or three points okay look at how much more that does that's so much better and now i'm going
to go clean this i think just be cleaned every day how what kind of monstrous dumps am i doing
do you need to clean the toilet every day go to sleep and then we're going to do cooking again
tomorrow then i'm going to try to find a chef job i want otto to be my best friend
will he stick around
praise otto that's somebody that actually is otto
good boy do i get any interactions after like 20 or 30 all right i gotta go to bed
all right we'll see you we'll see you next see you tomorrow get in there go to sleep
okay comfort is good energy is good we're gonna i want to get to four or five cooking so then i
can get the chef job do i need the computer what are your plans because they're gonna die
shit you're right i'm gonna get up make dinner clean this shit up whatever this is
i must not have finished and i'm gonna go swimming let's play it's fun what buns of steel and wash
bread abs germa received one body skill point really body i mean working on the exercise the
body skills especially valid in the pro athlete and military career very cool nice i should invite
somebody for a pool party jeff politics career no i don't think so toad stools toad sweat magic
coins i don't know what any of this shit does i gotta pee again all right i'm gonna pee one
more time we'll come back and we'll keep going i'll be right back okay hello uh so we will be
continuing this tomorrow i did say that sometimes there'll be two streams in a row
tomorrow is the one of those cases because i want to keep playing i want to at least try to get
at least a decent part of the game so we're playing sims 1 again tomorrow not done yet
tonight by the way uh but let's go back where we were play the coin game is there another coin
game update it was it is it more than what i played last time i'm gonna get sucked back into the sims
no i just kind of i mean look i did like the meme playthrough i didn't mean to have that be a meme
playthrough but it ended up as one now i'd like to see how far i can take germa elbertson over the
next day all right so where am i going i have i want to get the i need a computer how much is
the computer can't you search for a specific job on the computer you can right will i water all of
them or no uh i need a computer just a little one can i afford one shit i can't i can't afford
a computer is there there's a library really phone all cab services police repairman gardener
throw party call neighbor nah damn it use a library computer does that actually exist
i do that the newspaper yeah the newspaper has one job a day eat more food make another one
oh maybe not all right should i study cooking a guy here's what we're gonna do
boss why am i not flushing the toilet you guys notice that is there a reason why i'm not flushing
the toilet why i'm the only one here and then i have to clean it because it gets gross this
happens every day oh neatness i don't know i'm not the neatest person in the world and i'm pretty
sloppy and i flush the toilet after i take a shit in the toilet clean that up and then clean this
if it's yellow yet let it mellow you know i've heard that term before
but here's the problem piss stinks and it stains the toilet bowl i don't know i don't i'm not sure
i agree with that one it's staying whatever i'm getting question marks why your pee smells if you
do like a full piss into a toilet and it's like yellow smelly pee it stinks it's not what i'm
talking about drink more water i drink plenty of water this doesn't happen every day i need to
drink more my pee is fine i'm fine he stinks oh there's a cat fight never mind i jumped to
conclusions there i watched some tv for a little bit get that fun meter up what's that that's
tivity whatever i am gonna need a job though more fun more fun more fun more fun more fun more fun
go ahead and dive in and study cooking again try and fight somebody over there's a newspaper
throw a pool party all right i'm gonna study cooking i'm gonna serve dinner and then have a
party clean up a little bit all kenny over oh absolutely yo all right now we got a clean house
be begged you better invite kenny of course why would why would i not invite kenny why do i hate
it out here so much oh they drag me away why do i hate it out here this is a nice garden it's ugly
it's not ugly out here watch the toilet you fucking maniac you just dumped on top of a dump
that is fucking rancid that's disgusting all right now let's take a shower get some sleep
and then tomorrow i'm going to get cooking skill and throw a party seven a.m. eight a.m. nine a.m. good
turn this tv off what are we doing clean the bathroom use the toilet throw a party that mime
shows up put his head into the garbage disposal okay party time and then i'll look for a job
time for the party let's go get the social up and let's serve uh serve a big breakfast
and then i'm gonna after the party wow there's a lot just a second i'm currently making breakfast
i'll be there in one second uh talk i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming
wait how did you get in this person get in all right breakfast is served
it's time for brunch come on in everybody
oh there's a lot of people here morning party
oh
oh wait i'm serving lunch i need to eat
this place is sick go sit on the couch
everybody have some you didn't get me
well i only made enough yeah there's no music just
eating every family get together i've ever been to you can't do anything too fun because
you're with your family everything is gonna be like kind of nice just stand around
oh great what is he gonna do
all right party's over
hey
oh i would love to kick this guy's ass
not take any of my stuff didn't even hear him
can people see him oh pool party time for the pool party everybody out to the pool let's go
what's he taking oh no he took a plate everybody in delete the ladder i'm not gonna delete the
ladder there's no room kill them no i am not gonna kill them i need i'm getting myself in position
so tomorrow i can get to the top of the world i just barely got this nice house i need to get
a chef job i need i need social to go up can we talk i need to talk to everybody my
it's my social is terrible i'm having a party how the fuck am i not social right now my social is
going down what the hell why do i i hate everybody i don't like anybody here i don't like anyone
um
no and no one here likes me i don't like anyone at the party
i need to talk to you you're the only person i'll talk to here please give me some social
you're the only person i like
like
are we doing 17 all right
okay we're like we're getting with friends no no no no
this is the mail carrier why are they stuck stealing things in my house right
okay should i just went up we were like friends the phone's not gone it's right there
kill i would kill i would kill the mine if i could trust me i would what did what the hell happen
we were just friends we were just like getting to know each other you're not like dogs
okay she hates dogs leave just make her tell her to leave where am i going
i'm gonna kill there is no kill all right what about virginia why am i stuck over here
they want entertainment what do you want me to do all right fine i'll make more food
i'm making it i'm making it we're still here wait everybody left besides tiffany even the
mime left and tiffany's still here okay all right i get it all right all right all right
let's talk tiffany wants some dinner you know what do you what have some food you can just talk
right dog just walked in the house i get it yeah cakes birthday pizzas
is keep talking all right this is starting
keep this going she's helping she actually is helping all right tiffany tiffany you might be
the one i'm tiffany i'm calling you over tomorrow i can't i can't
uh
she's gonna leave
she's gonna leave what do you think about ties what do you think about snare drum she's 75
god damn it
conference is zero
suck
get a job i i'm gonna well okay hold on she's she stayed here till one o'clock in the morning
and she queued up like five teases it was like gonna get teased teased teased teased why did i
wake up for call her back i hold on let me just clean up let me get my shit together no no no no
don't go back to bed get up go pee flush the toilet and clean the toilet and then use the toilet
take a shower watch a little bit of tv and get your shit together while cleaning the toilet okay
watch tv mail check that for a job how do i hate it out here this is like that's nice out here
what's what's wrong with this place i don't understand why is it what i hate this why is
why do i hate it out here i need room get the llama sculptures room one flamingo room two
this is creepy didn't do anything it's not trash or anything out here right
plants are all water they look good what's wrong all right let's see pay the bills find a job here
we go come on chef slacker career for a golf caddy no i don't want that kick i hate it outside
i don't understand i'm going back to bed i need to get a job i have to find work i'm running out
of money puddle in the bathroom let's make some don't eat a snack make breakfast chop chop chop
chop go go go go go 9 p.m breakfast yeah but i mean it's guys it's breakfast for me i just woke up
me so i'm gonna take a shower then i'm going to read the cooking book
oh four skill points come on water i'll get that fourth skill point here in a minute
it's the box i'm begging you should i throw it away you're in autumn and should decorate
accordingly if you want to live most harmoniously in your house uh please put me on the do not call
list what you're fine we're talking about listen my bars are all fine did you call a friend over
what time is it 6 a.m all right i'm gonna sleep and i'm calling over tiffany 12 p.m okay have lunch
clean this shit up god i never all right here we go all neighbor bingo speed it up i haven't
saved in a long time it's probably the skunk outside oh right okay should i call someone
to get rid of them i need a job first i need a chef job master chef yeah what are the this
thing is dead oh shit oops all right now use the bathroom he's gonna piss in the bathroom isn't he
thank god you do nothing all day yeah it's called balancing bars it takes like six hours to eat and
shower in the sims one takes that long in the sims 4 too it doesn't i don't remember
anelia goth senior tiffany burb there she is all right call her i want to invite tiffany i want
to invite tiffany over i thought you'd never ask i'll be over in a minute excellent okay now
let's make some lunch i bring along a friend or two um sure why not sure sure that's fine
i guess i'm gonna make dinner yeah come on don't worry serve dinner who's brad brad come on in
dinner is served hi brad i don't know who this is wave who are you i'm gonna have dinner kill brad
well we don't even know who brad is brad could be like a co-worker or a friend it doesn't have to be
shit well just get the social up that's why everyone's here
all right let's go brad it's the husband whatever um can i please
what are they talking about whoa this break up in front of me no get out of here yeah see let it
brad tiffany don't fucking talk to that dick anymore tiffany that trust me we if we you and
i could be friends let's talk about your interest no no no no no no no she puts it like run away
you're a home wrecker i didn't do anything i just invite i invite them over for dinner and he
got he freaked out invite to old town we're gonna go to old town we're gonna have fun
i don't i hate everything that she likes
why don't we just sit and watch tv then come sit with you sit with me i'm gonna watch tv be
teased see be teased be teased be teased be teased she wants to look she's like jeez tease tease
tease him tease him talk to me talk to me talk to me talk to me talk to me talk to me all right
penis music there it is get up turn the tv off
do some gossiping and then i'm gonna check let's check her out
that's too fast too fast i don't think we're compatible
minus one we're not compatible she hates me why does she keep coming over you just watched tv for
four hours while she tried to talk to you why do you keep coming over my house to like leave and
hate me i'm about to eat this dirty food nobody likes me at least otto likes me home wrecker andy
i look at my social it's so bad can i just talk to somebody what's wrong what is it what is it
who can i talk to if any just talk to me i just want to talk just i just want to talk on phone
you're a socially challenged moron do you know what time it is oh it's two o'clock in the morning
well clean this place up disgusting eat no clean it up i thought i puked clean up you can do it
social i gotta get the social up hygiene i can get okay go to bed and invite tiffany over what whoa
what are you doing what is this sleeping i was just asleep i was asleep okay get out of here go back
to bed what are you doing please he's dying he has no friends everyone hates the things he likes
and only the grandma will talk to him just reset again no what i have i'm fine i just need a chef i
need to work as a chef get the mail clean up find a job clean up empty the trash you know come on man
let's go study cooking in a minute i've not flushed the toilet once since moving in go
and he actually liked you yeah but i didn't get kenny's number kenny townie i don't think i can
call kenny townie go find kenny that'll be the mission for tomorrow what's wrong i want to look
for a job okay well just get the area get get the area good to go shower okay have some food
you the flamingo yeah and now you look for a job i fucking hate it out here what i don't
understand it goes to zero all right call somebody over it's only eight o'clock
no is he coming over he's not coming over previous engagement all right well i gotta try tiffany again
and 10 30 no can do i have much more interesting things to do at home all right well fuck you
tiffany what else can i call i suppose i'm gonna talk to me for five minutes jenya i don't know
come on over get out of the house yeah i have to leave the house you're boring all right i'm
just going out then i'm going out ball cab i'm going out sleep for a little bit get your
shit together i'm going out tomorrow because it's already one o'clock in the morning my comfort's
good have breakfast and then get the hell out of the house take a shit take a shower take a shit
and now let's get the hell out of here call cab let's go magic town let's go we'll go i'm going
on vac- oh no no i only have 50 dollars let's go to studio town let's just go somewhere get out here
yeah let's go i need to have some fun who is it you sold your patent for a left-handed monkey
wrench i got 1300 bucks what thanks for like the community chess card from monopoly all right let's
go to studio town i got some money just leave the cartoon sounds on all right studio town acting
opportunities passion music of food service help hep cats and cool canaries know the joint is
jumping at cameron's lounge got your boots on come beat the chops of the jacks and jails are in even
earn some gravy gimme on the main kick whatever i don't know what that means it was like the back
of a cereal box god we got it's one i won i just want a thousand dollars i want a thousand dollars
again oh hey uh ask about welcome to studio town i recommend you get your start by grabbing an open
microphone or stepping up to the karaoke bar if that's more your style keep in mind that unless
you've signed up with a talent agency your performances will not be tracked in the star
chart i just want someone to talk to me it is a knife i just want to get a thousand bucks all
right i'm good hey i'm i'm one of the new movers and shakers here sing country i'm melissa this
ice cream she's just following me around people come in and listen to me i'm so nervous i'm gonna
pass out
no my social it's going down to zero i need more charisma all right go back go in here
need to work on your singing i need creativity and in charisma i okay i gotta get a mirror and
i gotta get um a painting please just talk to me i love god talk to me you want to be an actor too
i just don't cry talk to him just talk to me
he hated it
wait this guy's about to get on stage let's listen is this social this is bad this is bad too
this guy bad boo boo this guy
i want this guy to get on stage see how good this guy is you get up there if you're so good
if you're so good why don't you get up there no social i'm your biggest fan oh this is like a
famous person i'm liking this
no
all right don't do that anymore hey come here
this lady is actually talking to me
social
i'm
52 this is 50 this is almost full i got a new friend i have an actual real friend 55
okay and this is 70 holy shit awesome
let me comfort my comfort let's keep talking keep talking talk talk talk talk talk talk
all right i gotta get my social up as high as it can go because i'm not coming back
let's listen but what are you what are you singing
i'm talking way too long i'm gonna pass out yeah i gotta leave okay i have 86 relationship right
now i'm gonna call her tomorrow this is a star i gotta leave i'm gonna shake the star's hand
i'm gonna leave one more thousand dollar hit and i'm out you're going back to check on me
i won again i have like almost five grand now i can't lose let's do it again do it till i lose
i'm gonna do this until i lose all right all right that's it one more
come on hurry up one more i lost all right leave i got my social up i need to go back to bed
send me a cab time to go home
all right that was a night out i gotta go home socials all the way up that's good let's make
the tv was on like three days well i've got down to my last 500 now i have 4200 bucks i don't have
to get a job yet i'm gonna build up my skills so we're talking about clean this up take a piss
and then go to bed eat and then go to bed wake up you got used to the penis music that
it's weird having it off now full that socials full let's watch tv for a little bit
because i know cook food first have dinner take a shower and let's watch some television
then study cooking i need a mirror i need a creativity and a mirror because i want to be
like famous miscellaneous uh creativity craft a gargoyle mechanical creativity creativity
fun and creativity it's a group right now that's just too much money mechanical mechanical all
right we're gonna do creativity guitar and then i need a mirror for charisma the hell is it even
under i i always forget there it is hygiene and charisma talking to the mirror all right let's go
for it oh i can afford a computer that's right i'll get a pc shower watch some tv take shit
cooking all right i've got four points in cooking pay these bills and sit and watch tv
i love cartoons apparently i never change it
now turn that shit off clean flush clean use shower a breakfast and then go
practice speech into the mirror for like four hours
irl schedule all right one charisma point i need more than that more i'm going back i'm gonna
wow them i'm gonna be a big star we'll do three charisma points before i go back three charisma
three uh creativity come on before you need to leave get it all right three points in charisma
so far now go to bed i got money to spend i can i'm good i can live off this for like another
month in sim time you need to get a talent agent from the newspaper to be an actor in due time
i need to make sure i know i got what i'm gonna get the points first all right um flush clean
use clean shower have dinner turn on tv sit and go watch tv watch tv oh the plants are all dead
shit watch tv you fucking weirdo what are you doing have a quick breakfast i already ate you
having second breakfast what about second breakfast what about second scrumptious cake
all right now play the guitar rock on creativity or i want three of each pick that back up
oh my god it's all right i need social again i'm going back there and i'm gonna get on stage again
computer a study plus study fun seven plus study spend money with money money with computer
job seek software okay yeah this one's fine let's get it giant pc turn this off i don't need the tv
for fun anymore wait can i okay find a job let's go i want to be a chef we got extreme career look
again science career look again prime career no not what i want oh okay now i gotta go pee sleep
and then i'm getting up and we're gonna go back and have some fun i'm gonna call somebody over
what about my new friend i forgot about the new friend it's a new uh friend i have right actually
call call the the where is he our department police kid butler pizza where's the um maybe it's
not here all right what was her name anybody what was her name is it alicia anybody what was the
name alicia anybody okay uh come on over at work seven p.m. i'm just going out i'm going out on the
town again have dinner and i'm going out eight o'clock it's back up plenty it's like the night is
very young take a shower sit for like a minute chill all right all cab let's go let's go we're
going back to studio town i'm getting on that stage and i'm gonna wow them i got three points
in charisma and two points in uh creativity yeah why do i keep going out to look at this flamingo
that's weird is he gonna go to tomato town great question all right what we got oh should i go i'm
gonna go here okay here we are what's this buy the movie place act i want to be an actor all right
i'm gonna act in the emergency scene the director what's going on no no i'm getting in there first
i'm the actor i'm not a method actor i'm too upset to act upset god what act in the commercial
um did you get separated from the tour group no visitors on set
zero pose for picture i'm gonna do a publicity stunt how is juggling a publicity stunt
all right i need to talk social somebody fucking talk to me finally let's have a chat
oh sit and with me and talk with me come have a seat
okay fill that bar go god it's so low
i have an autograph thank you oh hey
come over here and talk to me
all right nice let's go
no i want to compliment i'm your biggest fan ask uh were you in that tabloid compliment i'm
your biggest fan
you're a leech
they can't find it
just give me social
social
rom whitlow
i didn't do anything for me
sociopath run i'm looking i can't get this bar to go up
i'm trying just eat all their food fuck it whatever eat eat eat eat everything
get mixed up to make food when i go home please don't get that
just talk around the table under the dinner table just talk to me talk around the dinner table
all right just somebody just just let me just talk there's too many people
the sim ai just jumps into each other and just wants to talk to like every person here
i've eaten every plate okay i've had enough food
social come on
all right well that's good enough i guess
you're too underleveled for this area all right i'm i'm fucking off back to home
me out of here oh what okay i was like that's stupid all right go just gonna let him sit there
for a little bit get off energy up and then i'm gonna do creative again and then i'm gonna call
it for tonight i gotta get up i've got to soak my back paper service the newspaper won't be
delivered since you already have too many what well i'm not done with this i want to come back
tomorrow so tomorrow around probably the same time around noon we'll continue and when i come
back next time i'm gonna be ready i'm gonna get married it's gonna be a lot of fun let me
save it here and let's just before i leave it's saved let's just go see what happened to the other
house uh where is any help can i like go over there all right we'll do that tomorrow invite
people over i don't think i there's no phone in there though all right everything's saved it's all
good that's uh that's gonna be what we call it here thanks for watching everybody we'll see
tomorrow it was a shit load of subs a shit load of community subs i missed a slime clown gave 20
uncle ossy gave five onymos gave five as well thanks guys see tomorrow same time uh that was
a lot of fun i forgot i forgot how difficult the sims one actually is we're gonna get through it
at least some of it tomorrow see you then uh we're gonna do the credits the credit credit's
probably gonna be insane let's take a look okay let's see what happened whoa broke i think i broke
it too many to show it just wow these are people that subbed today this doesn't this doesn't like
feel like right you know what i mean that's like so many people i can't fucking believe this shit
it's insane it's all resubs i know it's still it's just that's bonkers we'll see you tomorrow
thanks everybody uh tomorrow will be more progress i feel like the first three or four hours is just
zero we went to negative progress in the first three hours and i will have some not tomorrow but
probably next week there should be more grotto beast stuff to talk about among maybe a couple
other things so stay tuned for that too once a week andy you know a lot of things can happen in
a week the title of the stream is the old one oh like the sims like the old sims game right okay
grotto beast pog yeah did the bot thing affect you um what bot thing what bot thing what's the
bot thing it killed a bunch of view bots um i don't know did i have how many followers do i
have right now i have 523 000 what did i have a week ago i don't think it looks like it affected
me that much 523 000 whatever i whatever was like two weeks ago i don't know they only removed bots
from 15 streamers really that's weird which basically dealt with a bunch of bot issues
and thus the bot problem so many channels might see a decrease in subs due to twitch removing a
bunch of bot accounts like like subbed bot sub bots i lost like 3000 oh well that doesn't seem
very much xqc lost a 1.5 million followers holy shit followers not subs yeah it's still a lot
though don't forget your bedtime well you said something else but thank you all right i'll see
you guys tomorrow same time around 12 pacific i'm gonna continue the sims 1 i'm gonna play through
that and see if i can make maybe get a family we'll see see you tomorrow good night goodbye take care guys