Hello there. How you doing? Doing good. Me too. I'm doing good too. Hey, still in school?
Good. Still at that job? Good. Still hanging out with uh, good. Cool. Still, still eating salmon?
Good. Good. No, no. 3am stream. There's a late one, but there's a reason for that. I told you guys I
was gonna go four days in a row because I got a lot of stuff planned. I'm taking a vacation
and I'm not talking about, oh I'll be gone for three days. I'm taking a real, I ain't gonna be
around for like a week. I'm gonna be done disconnecting from the internet for a little while.
My mother is coming up and I'm gonna spend time with my mom. It's been a long time since I've seen
her. We have a lot of activities planned. We're gonna just do, we're gonna do some mother-son things
and there's also some other family that are coming up as well. So I'm gonna be tied up for a while.
I will return. You'll see me again. Probably on, we'll probably go, depending what we do today.
This stream was just kind of a hangout sesh, you know. Yesterday we played Gunslinger. It was great.
Had a lot of fun. Today there's not a whole lot of plans. I just knew that I was not going to be live
for at least five days. So kind of wanted just to hang out a little bit longer. So what we've decided
to do is we're gonna play Salmon Max. It's been one of the most requested games for me to stream
on this channel. There's been one guy in particular. More like two one guys. I've been really,
really looking forward to it. This Doki Doki. Now what I already told you I wasn't gonna play Doki
Doki. But no, this is gonna, we're just gonna hang out, play a little Salmon Max, relax. After
we do this, we might do an episode. Depending on if people want to keep seeing it. Maybe we'll do
another episode. I want to watch a couple videos. I want to, there's a few things, there's another
game on Steam that I was looking at. It looked cool. This is just a who, this, there are no cares
in the world on this stream today. I don't have a plan. We're just going. But let me make a tweet
about it because I am live. So see you guys in a minute. Hey, so why don't we switch over to it?
It's currently right here and hopefully it captures right and did it. Oh god, I don't think it did.
Yeah it did. So I don't know very much about this game besides that it's a point and click game and we're
in a point and click mode. This is not Doki Doki Literature Club. This is Salmon Max on the road
again. A classic I've never played. You ready? Actually playing, I'm new game. This might be a
little loud. We can adjust the volume, but just be prepared. You might get a little bit of like a
blast. An audio blast. What? Already 10 out of 10. Anytime a saxophone presents itself in video
game. It's already a fucking eight or nine at least.
When are we going to get another case, Sam? Surely the local lawbreakers must miss our esoteric
brand of personalized criminal justice. Patience is a sharp razor to swallow, little buddy.
Okay, don't scream this time. I got it. I got it. Hello? What? Leave Swiss cheese by the rat hole or
you'll never see your precious phone alive again. Jiminy Christmas even a padlock sweat box.
Some misguidedly ballsy felons napped our phone. Eerie. I just went cheese shopping. How did they
know? Be sure it's Swiss cheese, right? And be quick about it. We got some rats already. Ordinarily I
hate yielding to extortion, but I have to admit I'm half charmed by the sheer spunk of that oily
little perp. Where'd you put the cheese, Max? Gosh, it was hours ago. You know I have the memory of a
dried trout. Sadly, yes I do. Well, it's got to be somewhere in this room. Okay, so this is the two
characters. This is Sam and this is Max. I only know that because not only is it telling me this,
I remember the thing from Team Fortress. Max's head. They're worth a lot of money.
So we're gonna get cheese. This is a point and click adventure game. You get your cardboard
box inventory. Let's turn it down a little. I already tried. You crack me up a little. You crack
me. You crack me up, little buddy. What's that? You crack me up. You crack me up, little buddy.
That's probably all right. You crack me up, little buddy. Voices out. You crack me up, little buddy.
Wait, he's talking about me. Louder. Louder. Louder. Put it on low graphics. Why would I do that? I
wanted to see the cool stuff. All right, Swiss cheese. Where'd you put the cheese? What about the
wastebasket? No dice. No cheese, but about in the water cooler. Hello, Mr. Spatula. How's the
weather in there? I'm vibing so, so hard with Sam here. All right, we're looking for cheese.
Can I talk to Max? Hey, Max. When is it, Sam? Where's the cheese? You sure you don't remember
where you put that cheese, little buddy? Sheesh. You'd think I'd forgotten my pants or something.
It's here in the office someplace. Pants? He's looking for his pants. Let's get to work. I
couldn't agree more. Okay, look at her pants. Where are they? This might come in handy. Don't
do that again. All right, we got a boxing glove. Can I see it? I got a gun and a boxing glove,
but that's not cheese. All right, dartboard and a little of this. One of these days we're going to
finish that game. I'm still working on getting the rest of the darts from the police impound.
Donut box. Cheese donut. Donuts. Don't throw that out. I'm saving it for a science experiment.
You bet, little buddy. Okay, I didn't mean to do that, but you can do that, I guess. No comment.
You can just beat up your friend. 20 years worth of electric bills take up a surprising amount of
space. 20 years with electric bills? They would turn this off. Good old Lou. Who's Lou again?
The bowling ball, of course. Can I ask them? Maybe they know where it is.
Yoo-hoo, tiny hoodlums. Leave the cheese by the hole. Okay, what about the desk?
VCR, television, lava lamp. Someone once told me that the contents of a lava lamp make an
excellent hand cream. That was me. Which is why I haven't tried it. This thing is regular Nintendo.
I bought that VCR at the supermarket. So you know it's a good one. Still smells like asparagus,
though. Oh, open, what a lush vegetation. I think Hubert could use some water, Max.
I'm training him to fetch it himself. Out the window. Cheese? It looks like cheese right there.
Do cheese balls look like cheese curds, right? Look at curds, cheese curds. They say graffiti
is the poetry of our time. Just what we need. More lame poetry. Cheese. Look at the cheese. In the
closet? There's a lot of cheese. That's too much cheese. I thought that was gonna be like a piece of
cheese. Why? Oh, okay. Well, that was, that's not it. That's a gag. Okay. Swiss cheese. I want Swiss
cheese. Well, can we go to the supermarket? 2002 was a great year for calendars. This is old.
I'm glad we stocked up. We've been going through them at a rate of about one a year since then.
Pizza? Is it, there's no Swiss cheese on pizza, right? What do I have for item? Bowling ball,
boxing glove, big gun. Okay, he takes it out. Oh, you wait. I can, you, I can aim the gun?
Tempting sometimes, but I become fond of the little guy. Whoa. How many bullets are in here?
All right, you have infinite ammo. What about the boxing glove? I'd rather punch other things.
Just like cover the hole. Apart from the holes, I don't think it looks much like Swiss cheese.
Take that, you law-breaking dairy products. Got it. Sam, no, the cheese was innocent.
Yeah, it's a cartoon. I think not. Yep. You got to think of like a cartoon. Or close enough
to fool the casual observer anyway. Don't say voila. You've read chat. You've read chat. I
didn't fucking do that. Yoo-hoo. Tiny hoodlums. Leave the cheese by the hole. What the fuck is
that? I didn't fucking do that. Greetings. The members of the benevolent brotherhood of vermin
would like to thank you for your offering. The members of Sam and Max would like their phone
back now. If you don't mind, I regret to inform you the situation has changed and I am unable
to comply with your request. A list of additional demands for the return of the button is as
followed. Now, let's discuss this calmly. Let's debone the smarmy little skis and see if the
phone's in there. I ain't talking coppers. Jimmy toothy ain't no rat. Uh, well, I ain't talking.
So wait, I can decide? How about I'll feed you broken glass? I'm thinking about stuffing a
light bulb down your throat, perp. Go ahead. I've been a little hungry. Hey, dog face,
your partner's giving me a headache. I'm about ready to wring your scrawny trash eating now.
No, we're going to do good cop, bad cop. Good cop, bad cop. You can't just go full bad cop.
I'm going to strangle you. I'm going to feed you glass. No, we have to like bring you a cake or
something, right? You mentioned a headache. Would you like some aspirin? Oh, and while I'm at it,
is there anything else I can do to make you comfortable? Are you thirsty perhaps?
Lights too bright? Well, that's sporting of you. Now you mention it. I really don't like being up
here so hot. I got me a thing about heights. They make me nervous, you know? Oh, really?
I can adjust the lights. Would you like some, a smoothie? I can make that for you too. I like
that. Almost dropped my whole coffee. Uh, how about, okay, let's, let's let them up. All right. Let's
help me help you. Help me help you, Jimmy. What the heck is that supposed to mean? I have no idea,
but it always sounds good on TV. Hand over the phone or I'll make you lick my German crusted
palms. Yeah. Yeah. I've licked the worst. Like what? You don't even want to know. Not telling.
Okay. Uh, he wants to get, how do we put them down? We'll go half easy on you. If you'll just cough
up the phone. Yeah. Yeah. Never happened pig. We've met your demands. We got you the cheese.
Any honorable rodent would hold up his end of the bargain and give back our phone.
Us rodents is not known for being particularly honorable. I was going to put them down. I want
to put them down on the ground. Don't like hide, say? How'd you like it if I dangled your greasy
hide out the window? Hey, you wouldn't wait. I warned you. I'm known for my fuzzy white butter
fingers. It's true. You should see him trying to tie an ass guy. All right. All right. Have mercy.
I've had mercy. It was unpleasantly gooey. Like, well, like things that have fallen onto pavement
from a great height. I give up. Take your phone and let me go. I wish I could.
Hello. Yes. Great gouts of steaming magma on a beeline for the orphanage. We're on our way.
It was a commissioner, Max. Multiple reports. He killed that guy in the neighborhood.
You dropped that guy on the window and murdered him. Idiot. We've got to get down to the corner
store right away. Okay. Get down to the corner store. Life troubling your digestion.
Reality blocking your passages. Expel your troubles with emetics. The handbook for
multicolored happiness and separate your bliss. Hey, that's that personal color spectrum book.
Self-help for the helplessly selfish. Perfect. I'll take two. Okay. Yeah, this is cool so far.
When I got this thing, I thought it would be useful. Where else would we keep the
pieces of paper that we're never going to look at again? All right. Let's make sure I saved it
because we'll pick it up another day. Maybe like I'm thinking about maybe like a few weeks or
something. I'll see you guys later. That's it. 20 minutes. Can I just, if I stream for like 15
minutes a day, 20 minutes a day, 20 minutes a week, you would never get anything done.
It would be unbearable. You wouldn't be able to do anything if you stream for like
fucking 20 minutes a week. Money. Wait, wasn't there something over here? Remember I looked
out the window and there was something on the ground? I told you. Oh, it's just trash. I don't
think I can do anything about that. We've got to go to the corner store. I don't, I mean really
don't mean to keep hitting you like that, but what's this? Oh, you ran into it. Well, look
where you're going. Dumpster. I once ate in that dumpster. Fresh food in there. Rampaging gorilla.
I still don't know how she got out of the office. I was sure it locked the door.
That was like what the YouTube used to be like. Yeah, but the thing about the YouTube videos is
was, okay, so like for instance, if I played Sekiro for like three or four streams and I condensed it
down to like one or two videos, that's like how it worked. What's this guy doing? Say there,
unfashionably dressed street urchin. Oh, you made me mess up. Now I have to start all over.
Yeah, I had to edit. You are one ugly kid. Hey, I know you. Oh, that's right. You're one of the
lovable scamps from that old TV show about the singing soda jerks. It's called the soda poppers.
In the 70s are not old. Specs, it's you. Wow, an actual celebrity vandalizing our neighborhood.
This is great. Remember when you were famous? Remember when you were famous? You're under arrest.
I don't look. I don't care who you are. I don't care what you're doing, where you've been.
You are committing a crime. You're under arrest. By the way, we're freelance police
and you're under arrest. No, I've really got to finish this. But thanks anyway.
That's not how it works. You're under arrest because you're doing that. That's why you're
under arrest. Seriously, you're under arrest. Come along quietly and no one gets hurt.
Actually, I prefer that you don't come quietly. Must finish painting. All right. Well, I guess
you're not under arrest. Boy, you sure were a famous, oddly underdeveloped teen celebrity
at one time. I'm still famous. Are you? Um, like a million point one times more famous than you.
Well, more famous than me? More known in the 18 to 34 year old repeat criminal demographic.
I like that. That was a pretty good joke. Say, how about an autograph for my pal?
You can sign my butt. Make it out to squinky. I don't sign butts anymore. People get ticklish
and they move and it gets all messed up. I'll risk it. Sorry. I can't stop painting.
18 to 34 repeat criminal demographic is my demographic. But you guys saying you're all
repeat criminals. So specs, what are you up to these days? Any new projects? Yes. I have a new
life in my life and his name is Brady cultures. He's the genius behind the Ibo ocular fitness
program. You really should try one of his videos. Where can I get a video? Where can I find a copy
of the video? They carry them over at Bosco's. You should get it. Okay. Ibo sounds like an electronic
archery toy. Ibo is the truly visionary. Try the video today. Sure thing. We'll try. I love that
voice. I'm gonna get, I'm gonna, I'm gonna get that down. Sounds fascinating. What about enough
about that? You can never get enough of Brady culture's Ibo. Do I need money? All right,
we'll see. Well, that's nice. Now you're under arrest. Wait, what is it? What are you telling
me something about that trendy modern street art you're perpetrating? What about? What is it? How
did you select your subject matter? He looks like a fried egg. It's Brady culture. He's the genius
behind the Ibo ocular fitness program. What are you, why are you trying one of his videos?
I'd rather try a fried egg. That's a good idea, Max. Sounds fascinating. That's a really good idea.
You can never get enough. All right, see you later. Well, we'll leave you to it. But you have to agree
to paint me next. Sorry, I only paint Brady culture. Max, you've got the TV schedule memorized.
Weren't the soda poppers going to be featured on one of those grim celebrity tell-alls today?
Oh yeah, on channel 173, the child star expose network, which we only get when it's convenient.
Brady culture. Bosco's inconvenience. What about the paper box? It says they've bred a horse with
eight legs. Does it run twice as fast? No, but it does eat twice as much.
That's good. It says cloning rights activists are cloning themselves to create a bigger voting block.
It works for locusts. That's pretty good. Looks like he's got Boston baked beans in there. Oh watch
baby, watch it. They don't. Guns, beer, meat and candy. The four food groups. Have no fear,
simple citizens. The freelance police are here. So we're not actual police. Is that what I'm
getting? It's just YouTube. Where's the SWAT team? Where's the national guard? Where's NASA? NASA?
Hold on Bosco. What's the problem? NASA? It's a terrorist, a munchkin terrorist. He'll be the
death of us all. What munchkin terrorist? Where is this Lilliputian agitator? Are you blind? He's
right there. Hey it's another one of the soda poppers. Isn't he the one with the
ladder control issues? Yeah, Whizzer. He's a former child star. Oh just lock him up.
Remain calm. What's he doing? I think we got it. What's he doing? Exactly what is the nature of
Whizzer's malfeasance? He's delivering videos I didn't even order. Brady coaches Ibo. What is that?
Oh it's something bad I can tell you that. Videos. And look at that display. It's subversive and
hideous. I don't know any white guy would have throw like that. I hear that. Remain calm. Video
dumping. Any other complaints? Have you seen this Ibo video? What's on the video? Have you actually
witnessed this Ibo video with your own eyes? Only a fool would watch a strange video. You watch it.
Anything else? Any other heinous terrorist activities to report? Yes he keeps using my bathroom.
Who knows what he's doing in there? I think I know. So we've got an unwanted video dumper and
serial leak taker. Not even the national guard can help us now. Okay so that's it. So all this
Whizzer character's doing is delivering videos and abusing his bathroom. That's it. Did he steal any
of your overpriced merchandise or at least try to disembowel you with a sharpened spork?
No way I've got BTAD. The single most technologically advanced security system ever conceived by the
human mind. All right what is what what is hold on what is BTADs? Why do these all look weird? Ibo.
BTAD. BTADs? Is that one of those acronym things I've been hearing so much about? Yep. Bosco Tech
automated defense system. I made it myself. Wow I always wanted to automate my defense.
How does it work? Just pull a weapon you'll see or try and walk out of here with something.
Go ahead I dare you. Maybe we will. All right is that enough of you? I think we got it. Okay
anything else? Is that enough out of you? We'll chat more later Bosco but right now it's time to
get up close and personal. We need to now find out what the fuck is going on.
Did he just steal something? What is why are you so fast?
All right hold on hold on. Free videos? Don't mind if I do.
Brady cultures Ibo for ocular fitness. The revolutionary isometric exercise. What's so
revolutionary about it? See through walls and clothing. Grow your eyes at lightning speed.
Lose five pounds of eyeball fat. Oh good I can never seem to lose that last five pounds.
What do you say we start off this movie night a little early today? So let's get one of these
and watch it. All right Ibo video. Do I have to buy one or do I have to can I steal it?
Why would I steal one? I can get it from you. My coffee machine. I think it's the tinge of green
that makes this coffee especially appealing. I take my coffee green like my men. Don't need a
sludgy. With 100 all-natural sludge. This week's flavors wheatgrass and meatloaf.
Wheatgrass and meatloaf smoothies. All right I'll tell you one of those doesn't sound too bad.
I'm not going to tell you which one. It could be either one of them. Max I've got a great idea
involving you, our microwave, and six feet of aluminum foil. Go on maybe another time.
Am I implying that I'm going to put that rabbit in the microwave and turn it on?
Not chose. They're mine not chose. Oh yuck yuck. That was a yuck joke. I need to hear it again.
Not chose. They're mine not chose. Not chose. They're mine not chose. Oh yuck. Ketchup, mustard,
and purple stuff. As vaguely referred to on TV. Purple stuff. Purple ketchup. Bring it back. I
remember it was cool. Your brain made it taste like um it tasted like blueberries. Your brain
made you taste it. It was like blueberry ketchup even though there was no blueberry in it. Your
brain just made it taste that way. Hey there Mr. Wizard. No need to be formal. My friends just call
me wizard and so do my enemies and lots of people like you I've never met. Everyone calls me wizard.
It was the chemicals. Yeah I know. I'm not saying it wasn't.
Everybody loves your show. My cousin's wife's dentist loved your show. Oh yeah we've always
been a big hit with the dentists. Gee I wonder why. Hey kids guzzle soda like the soda poppers
and you'll need so much expensive dental work you can kiss college goodbye. So these are soda poppers.
Cynicism is like a breath of fresh air on a crowded subway. Are you anything like your
character? So are they like the this is like Snow White and the seven soda poppers? Any chance
we could get you to sing the song from your old show? Yeah the theme song. What was it called?
It was called more than jerks but I can't sing it. I'm too embarrassed. Let's do it. Come on sing
the soda popper theme song. No. Do the voice. Do the do the character. Do it. How about an autograph
for my pal Max? You could write to Max. Thanks for saving my life that time in San Remo. Gee I don't
really have time. I've got a lot more videos to deliver. No time? Don't they give you bathroom
breaks? Sure but I don't sign autographs in there anymore. There was an incident.
Huh are you anything like the character you played on the tv show? Yeah like do you really have to
hit the john every five minutes? Remember the Simpsons character? Sometimes every three minutes.
It's like having a superpower. P every three minutes. This really is me. Well that's nice.
What is? What exactly are you doing here? Delivering videos. Take one. They're free.
Here we go. What's the story with these videos? Brady Culture's eyeball is the ocular fitness
regimen for people on the go. It's gonna be like a hypnotizing program where you get like all
fucked up and it makes you paint. I was gonna say giraffes but it's graffiti. That's the word.
There's a lot of g's and a lot of f's in both those words. What can you tell me about eyeball?
Eyeball is a revolutionary new program of isometric exercises to promote ocular fitness.
You can learn to move even see through walls and clothing. What if I don't wear clothing?
You gotta watch this tape. It changed my life. All right. Who exactly is this Brady Culture fellow
supposed to be? And what kind of steroids does he use on his hair? Brady Culture is a genius
and his eyeball program is a boon to all mankind. Settle down Jeremy. You got the fucking you got
the intelligence like a large glass of water. And did you know 12 ounce iq? That's mine by the way.
I said that in pre-stream chat. It's a child star bonanza. You failed it. I was waiting. I was
waiting for an opportunity to use it. Hey you know you're brilliant. No you're brilliant. You
got the fucking iq like a glass of water. And then they're gonna be like what the fuck is he
talking about? And then on the car ride home. The car ride home they're gonna be going
wah fucking like 16 ounces that motherfucker. Well that's nice. What is? If you'll excuse us
we've got shopping to do. Take a copy of the eyeball video while you're at it. It will change
your life. We talked about that in the pre-stream chat. I'm glad I got a chance to say it.
12 ounce iq. All right so did I get a video? All right good. That joke is horrible. It doesn't
matter. I needed to say it. I am not getting in that thing again. It took me weeks to get
the fishy smell out of my fur. Tongues placed on freezer become property of Bosco. I got quite
a few tongues that week. Public restrooms. Unholy temples to all things unsanitary. I wouldn't go
in there for all the tea and tea landia. I'll do it. Tea landia. Lots of terror.
Uh oh. He's gonna pee his pants? Time out for number one. Looks like he opened his flood gates.
I hope he enjoys it as much as I did. He's playing terror. All right hold on he's not over here anymore.
Can we go over here? The crate that delivers Bosco's terror. I mean he's in the bathroom right now. I
wonder if I can do something. I don't like to use public restrooms actually.
Land mines. What the fuck? Children preserve fluids. I wonder if Bosco used the fluid sample I
submitted. I hope not. What's over here? So what would I got? I got boxing glove bowling ball.
Yeah hold on. Get back uh get back in there.
Okay can I put the bowling ball in here? Like weigh him down?
But wizard would take it and then where would I be? I was trying to like plant the gun in there.
I don't know why. Why would I want to like plant a gun?
I'll need a new skull but otherwise no complaints. Bosco is a gun free zone. Gun free? Sartre was
right. Purgatory really is a convenience store. Don't make me laugh little buddy. It jiggles my
sensitive cranium. Okay so I'm not sure I can do anything here because the crate that delivers
Bosco's terror. That's what he used to deliver. I think I'm gonna have to probably do.
I'm probably gonna have to put a tape. Okay I'm gonna have to put a tape in here
so he delivers it somewhere right? Oh hold on. Sliced cheese.
Well it is on special and we are running dangerously low. Did I take it?
Cheddar cheese this time. Okay a cheese sign on an empty table. The tantalizing promise of cheese
crushed by cruel reality. Lottery tickets. One dollar lottery tickets. Two dollars. I'm feeling
lucky already. Time is it seven? Is that clock correct? Well it's only got one hand so probably
there was a minute hand. We're going to try anything. No trash? Hot weenies. Hot weenies.
This rampant weenie cannibalism turns my stomach. Have I ever played Monkey Island? I have played
Monkey Island before. What do we have here? Organ trader? Self-loading weekly? Oh let me see that.
Hey Bosco what can I do for you? All right uh we want to we want to buy something. We'd like
to patronize your fine establishment my good man. By patronize you he means we want to buy
stuff from you not mock you. We probably will mock you but that's not what he meant. I know
what he meant. Don't patronize me. So what do you want to buy? Uh the cheese please. I was already
doing it. I already bought it. What have you got? Well I still got that big sale on cheese. Oh yeah
cheese. I want that. And I might have another item of interest behind the counter. What do you got
behind the counter? What's my what is it? I accept your thinly veiled invitation to ask about the
item behind the counter. Oh it's just a little something I like to call a tear gas grenade
launcher. Tear gas grenade launcher? Oh yeah I really want that. It's the latest in Bosco tech
innovation. It'll clear out a room of militant college students in no time guaranteed. I feel
really close to you right now. You sell cheese in in a tear gas grenade launcher? Do you have
any weasels on a stick? Nope. Do you have any two-handed broadswords? Nope. Do you have any
vegetables in the shape of famous naturalists? Nope. Do you have any candy pink fat boys? Nope.
Do you have any exiled political dissidents? Nope. Do you have any weapons of mass destruction?
Who's asking? Topical, topical humor. Do you have any topical? I've run out of ideas.
Well you can always just start over again. Good idea. Do you have do you have any weasels on the
stick? Nope. 2002 2004 topical. I already took the cheese though didn't I? Did I have to pay for it?
Okay Matt we want this cheese. Okay standard cheese background check. I'll need to see at
least six forms of ID, a valid federal cheese license, a completed organ donor card, a written
release signed in the presence of a note of republic, and your school report cards from the
ninth through twelfth grade. Uh oh. That's I can do all of those except the last one. It's okay Sam.
I can be brave. We'll just have to struggle cheeselessly onward. Do you guys remember bringing
into your report card into Chuck E. Cheese? You guys ever have that deal where if you had like
A's? Yeah Chuck E. Cheese used to do this thing like 10-20 years ago where if you brought in your
report card and you had A's, straight A's, they would give you free tokens. They would give you
a bonus tokens. So but what they didn't tell you is that really didn't matter because they didn't
want anybody to feel bad. So we would go in my mother... I was bad student so I didn't get like
it wasn't A's and B's by the way. It was like uh S's or something for satisfactory
needs improvement. There were only like three grades. A for like accomplished or something.
So I had a terrible report card but we still wanted to go to Chuck E. Cheese and we would go
and my mother would still try to get them to give the bonus credits for having a good report card
and the guy behind the counter like just didn't give a shit. So like they they felt bad because
they would get my brother's report card and be like oh he's doing great free 20 free tokens
and then they'd get mine and you could see the guy's face just be uh hey so good for you
20 free tokens. I just got I got them just because they felt bad and I don't know maybe
maybe my mother was like you give him both that you understand. I don't want him thinking that
he's like fucking inadequate and the guy's just like okay yeah Chuck E. Cheese actually used to
do that. We'd like that tear gas grenade launcher. That's really sad. What? 10,000 bucks. Sad? Give
out like a million tickets. But I didn't know. I just thought we got free tokens. White collar
crime drive. Where corporate criminals go to rejoice in their ill-gotten gains. After we
blow this popsicle stand we can go hunt us up one of those starchy cesspiles and hit them where it
hurts the most. Right in the pocketbook. That's not what I thought you were gonna say but that's good
too. The man got his token. Still a victory. That's right. I still got the tokens. Look my brother was
really smart and he like paid the token toll and then we just we're all part of the same family,
same groups. Give it to us all. Whatever. All right so I can't okay so nothing for us right now.
Okay can I put the cheese in here? See you later Bosco. Remember. What conversation? I just I just
accidentally skipped that. He's leeching off his brother. What conversation? Oh brother.
This is like a dumb like four dollar extra promotion to Chuck E. Cheese 20 years ago.
Oh wow I can't believe he did that to his brother. Unbelievable. He like conned his brother out of tokens.
Oh time out. Can I put the cheese in here? If you really love someone give them the cheese.
What does that do? Can't wait to see the look on his face when he gets it.
Oh he's trying to leave. I get it. Time out for number one. We're saved. That's a whole lot more
entertaining when it's not happening to me. It's pretty entertaining either way.
Hahaha. Oh he wet his widow pants. Who's talking? Is that Sam? Oh I was like what the fuck?
Good thing I have the other two twerps to handle it.
It's still not quite right.
Let me help you out here. You just gonna leave him there?
Hahaha. Did it for you. Actually evil. So is it that's it? I don't want to wake him up. I got the
tape. We have to go watch the tape. Nothing else I can do over here. Bosco's got a lot of interesting
if questionable products in here. I think it's the only store in town where they carry those albino
monkey crackers I got hooked on in Forneo. Let's get back to it. Why don't you get back to your
shopping or whatever it was you were doing that back there. Sometimes it's best not to ask.
I'll let you get back to doing what you're doing or whatever it is you do back there.
Hey Bosco how are you? That's like Owen Wilson. Hey Bosco. Hey you just gonna leave him there?
Close. I'll get it. How about a reward? You know we did put the kibosh on that whole terrorist
operation so. How about some free stuff? Is that why you did this? For free stuff? Was this
all a part of the plot? Yes a labyrinthine scheme in which we paid off a former child star to deliver
videos to your store just so that we could knock him out via your own security system and claim
an undeserved reward. So you admit it. Conspiracy humor may be lost on this crowd. So we don't get
anything. Nice place you got here. Where's our stuff? What's so nice about it? Nice name. Nice
security measures. Hey you got a good security. What's with the maximum security prison motif?
You've been robbed as many times as I have you do to say. I've never been robbed actually but then I
typically point a large firearm at anyone who approaches me. You crack me up little buddy.
Why that's a that's that you didn't even laugh. I don't I mean that's the line. I've heard he said
the line right. I've heard that before but he didn't laugh. Not even like a you crack me up
little buddy. No no he didn't laugh. He's liar. What were we talking about? He's liar. No he's liar.
Sleep with two eyes open. He's being sarcastic. He's liar. This game looks like borderland. Hey
specs. Hey you remember when you were french? Um okay but let's watch the tape. We've got a
don't we all. Any other things to click on? That's the office. What about over here? One way. One way
dead end. Street signs are such fitting metaphors for the human condition. Remind me to refill your
prescriptions. Dead end sign. Uh let's go watch. Hold on let's go watch the tape. They say graffiti
is the poetry of our time. I keep seeing giraffe like giraffe. Giraffe. I see the word giraffe. It's
the font that's making me do that. It's the same word without the t's or something.
Or something. Let's watch the tape before I make a fool out of myself even more. Okay Max ready for
that ocular workout. No stop. We don't have any popcorn. Sweet alligator dentures soaking in
formaldehyde. That was close. Quick before it starts. Hello I'm Brady culture. You may remember
me from culture's clubhouse. The massive worldwide television hit that ran for six episodes in 1970.
What you are about to see will change your life forever. So watch closely. Now listen up you
tasteless philistines. I knew I told you it was gonna be a hypnosis thing.
To name all your children after me. I love you. I adore you. I want to name all my children after
you. Sam look. Ocular fitness my eye. That videotape hypnotized Jimmy Tootie. I think I like him better
this way. We've got to find this Brady culture and stop it before he hypnotizes every consumer
of cheap self-help videos. Can I have his hair when we're done? Only if you keep it on a leash.
All right now we're time for some investigative work here. Let's check the entry. Nobody ever
leaves us messages anymore. Can I call somebody? Can I call the chief? Send over another gargantuan
anchovies and hot sauce special please. You know that's been a meme ever since the ninja turtles
anchovies on pizza but I've been told that it's actually fantastic.
That's the joke right? Anchovies. Apparently it's really really good. Okay so what can I get
should I take the tape back out? This is evidence right? I need to hold on to this. All right so we
know that this is a plot to hypnotize everybody and cause problems so anchovies on pizza are
very normal here in Italy and are one of the classic pizzas in Napoli. Yeah see that's what
I'm saying like I don't know where this meme joke came from. Okay there's another uh there's
another there's another giraffe over there. Fishes are stinky and yucky. Meme know what?
They say graffiti is the poetry of our time. Just what we need more lame poetry. It's not a meme
they just don't taste good. Meme is the word that everybody uses now. I would I'm just trying to fit
in. This place used to be Lefty's tool rental shop. Good old Lefty. I'll miss him. You couldn't
stand Lefty. He once poked him in the eye with the number three socket spanner. Exactly. Good times.
How do you do fellow kids? Spray paint. Hey a can of spray paint and it's not even empty.
So are we gonna go fuck with these paintings? Spray over it? This could use a little improvement.
Hey hey hey you messed it up. Oh fix it Rainfreeze. Okay so that takes me away from the other one.
What what was he doing on the other one? Was he guarding something?
Is this some kind of currency thing? I don't know. They say graffiti is the poetry of our time.
Just what we need more lame poetry. You guys like got me all messed up with that improvement.
I keep seeing that and I just remember how many times I said it.
What are you doing? Don't mess with my painting. I've got to fix it all up.
Okay so I can make it. I can move him around. So he'll he's gonna fix that one. He'll run over
and fix this one. Maybe okay so in stand here he goes really fast. I'm gonna hold the boxing glove
out and he's gonna run into my fist. And it's gonna break his like he's gonna fall down and
it's gonna hurt him. But I didn't do it though. He just wasn't looking where he was going.
Uh let's go first. Let me go in here first. Tempering with the mail is a federal offense
punishable by fine and imprisonment. As we found out after the incident with the garden hose.
Ah memories. I heard it was a little loud so I'm trying to get down.
Oh okay mailbox. This is Sybil's piercings tattoo psychic therapy.
Save it. Now it's too quiet. Oh let me check the alley way here. Is there any alley? No.
Car. Where are we going Sam? Let's go give a ticket to a rich criminal. Let's go cruise for
lawbreakers Max. And drive around. Are we getting Nicole Letagrade here? Is that possible?
By the way Sam I'm not sure if I mentioned this but I may have accidentally chewed through our
brake lines. No I don't think you did mention that. I guess we'll just have to slow down by violently
rear-ending other motorists. Already planning on it little buddy. How do I? Oh I didn't know
it is plus a full letter grade okay. Is there any consequences? Are there no consequences?
Take the wheel little buddy. Why can I do this? What? Please accept my condolences for your
table line. This is so. Where am I supposed to go? Okay I just crashed into that guy.
I'm still on the other side of the road. Office. I don't have anywhere else to go.
You can use the keyboard to move. WASD doesn't do anything. Up down left right doesn't do anything.
I think this is I don't have I only have one destination which is the office area.
That was all right that was pretty sick. We just drove around in a circle.
Okay so I'm gonna deal with this guy somehow. Can I go I'm gonna go into Sybil's.
Delivering onions live. Not a great name. Another one. Welcome you look like you could use some
therapy. Not from a wide-eyed circus freak like you. Hey it's another one of the soda poppers. Me?
Right you're um. Peepers. I don't know what you're talking about. My name is Sybil Pandemic.
Licensed psychotherapist. Fine prove it. About a little analysis. Certainly. Tell me what's bothering
you. It's not me it's Max. Hey. He thinks he's a rabbit. I am a rabbit. See. Yes well I would
recommend Brady Culture's Ibo video for this situation. Good eye health helps combat delusions.
I'm a rabbit. Ibo? Yes my runny poached egg-like eyes could use a workout. You won't regret it.
Okay well we already know what this is. Who's this lady culture person?
Brady. Brady Culture. He's only the most insightful and amazing man on the planet.
That's all. It's not Sean Penn? Not anymore. I'm so disillusioned. All right I know I've got I've
all right I got the video. Let me just see what you got. I've still got a copy of this cockamamie video.
I'm all out but they probably still. Yeah. Well you're not Sybil. Are you sure your name is Sybil
not Peepers? Absolutely. Sybil Pandemic licensed psychotherapist. That's me. He's trying to pull a
fast one Sam. Where's your gun? Violence is not the answer. Those eyes. Sam we're dealing with a
dangerously delusional psychotic here. Obviously. Uh we'll do all the options. Sybil's normally a
girl's name isn't it? Must have been tough while you were growing up. Why do you think I became a
licensed psychotherapist? You have any ID? Could we see your driver's license or some sort of ID?
Sybil. My psychotherapy license is hanging over there on the wall. How about something with a
picture on it you obvious lunatic you? I could draw one on there if it would put your mind at ease.
Draw one? Oddly I don't think it would. You sure look like Peepers. You're a dead ringer for Peepers from that old
soda popper show. I get that a lot but I'm Sybil Pandemic licensed psychotherapist. Right.
Excuse me for a minute would you? Let's take a look at this. Diplomas, uh tattoo chair.
I don't know what I have for items. Punching bag, bowling ball, spray paint, cactus. It's eerily
lifelike for a fake plant. The same could be said for a lot of our friends. It's eerily lifelike for
the same. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. What about the desk? Newton's balls. Can I play with that?
Oh it's good exercise for the eyes but Brady culture's eyeball video is better. Can I play with
that? That voice is familiar. Ah the tiki. Hold over from the days when you could sell all kinds
of cheap crap without a successful children's television show. Envious? A little. Okay intercom.
Hello is anybody there? Can't check the desk. Oh what about okay I want to go in the in the
closet there. I think those might be iron-ons. Convenient and painful. A sure-fire hit with
the average consumer. An iron-on tattoo? That looks comfortable. Oh it is. How would you know? You
don't have a tattoo. Don't I? Relax. That may be the least relaxing sign I've ever seen. Relax.
How about the one at the barbershop that says low fatality rate? I stand corrected. Oh I would
never let somebody shave me. I have this extreme fear of being shaved by somebody. No I don't think
so. Skin art. Is that art for skin or art made from skin? Your ideas are effervescent pustules
Max. I have this extreme fear and it's completely irrational and you can judge me all you want
but I imagine myself sitting in the barber chair and talking to whoever it is that's
shaving me currently and they just like and I'm just dead. I don't know why I just always think
about that. It's completely irrational. Sweetie talk yeah there's too many forms of media of that.
Plus I have a very sensitive face. I gotta be very careful like I use a very specific particular
razor. If I go and do a like a hot shave and they're just like I cut up there I cut easily
on my face. I know no they get like the thing they have a towel and they have that piece of
leather that they take the big knife it's like a machete and they go put your head back.
It's scary. I'm sure it's nice. Thank god I've been locked in that closet so long I was
starting to invent life stories for the mothballs. The leather is the skin from the last guy. Oh my
god he's still here? Call a cop. You're in luck ma'am. Sam and Max we're freelance police. What the
civil pandemic licensed psychotherapist nice to know you. Arrest that lunatic immediately.
But he's my pal. What's the charge? Assault, kidnapping, identity theft. Those are good
charges. Some of my favorites and what about mopery? He locked me in the closet and he's been
pretending he's me. Gadzooks why? Well these cases can be very complicated and delicate.
There may be repressed feelings of inadequate transference or latent unwarranted hypochondriac
Freudianism. Come again? He's a complete whack job although actually now that I look closely
I think he's been hypnotized. Oh really? What can we do? Are there steps we can take? Soothing music
or perhaps some sort of invasive surgery? Shock treatment! Shock treatment! Typically a hypnotic
state can be revised after rendering the subject susceptible to new input. Sorry I don't speak
psychotherapist. You've got to knock them unconscious to bring them out of it.
I can demonstrate on this guy if you'll knock him out for me. Consider it done. I thought he's
just gonna go do it. All right so here this is what we've got this for. I can see you. Whoa
where'd he go? Hey there he is. You a therapist? How could you? Just comes naturally I guess.
Okay so we're gonna knock him out. How do we knock you out?
Whip the door open really fast and hit him right in the head with it? I can see you. He runs. I can
see. Whoa where'd he go? Hey there he is. All right how do we keep him here? How do we keep him from
moving? Where's he running to? I can see you. What can you tell me about this? Oh it's marbles.
Change my life. You should watch it as soon as you possibly can.
I have the strangest urge to redecorate. Fight it Sam. Fight it. Okay like spray him. I don't think
that would be in. All right what are you telling me? Hello. I meant the other civil. So you guys
gonna take care of this imposter or what? Just throw the phone at him. I think there may be other
victims of hypnosis besides yours lurking around the neighborhood. Make that really really cool
unconscious as well. Oh boy when it comes off the latch it goes like it's a great audio cue
for a lot of things. What happened to your tattoo business? Don't tell me they actually
enforce those health code violations. No no of course they don't but a guy came in here and
asked me to put a ship on his chest and I misheard him and well I decided to hang it up after that.
Okay I don't think I've ever been in here. You're right across the street from us and I don't think
I've ever been in here before today. Your friend has. He's always trying to con me into giving him
some kind of weird tattoo for free. You could put a line on my head and some eyes on my butt
and I look like I was upside down. For the last time no. Excuse us we've got work to do. I'll say.
All right let me what about the couch? Let me look at the couch.
I've got half a mind to stretch out. I think you have to stretch the whole thing
or it rips. You baffle me. You crack me up sometimes Max. You make me laugh Max.
All right let's get out of here. Let me try to deal with the other guy. I think I need something
else. What do I have for items? Bowling ball, boxing glove, videotape, spray paint. So I can spray paint
that. Can I go faster? Somebody said that I could double click. I'm not doing it.
Because he's here and then he runs that way. What is he standing on here? Can I like drop him through
this? Shift click. No. Well let me paint the graffiti here. Let me just see what happens.
That gets him away from there. But I'm not sure what that does. Because that just gets him over
here. So now I can't just like punch him in the back of the head.
So they move so fast. All right so then there's another one. Wait there's two. There's one here
too. Okay so there's three.
I didn't see this. I forgot this one existed. Because then that means now he's over here.
Okay yeah watch this. He's gonna be right here. And that's when we shoot him. I'm kidding. I'm
kidding. I'm kidding. I know. I know. I know. I know. Can you believe we get paid for this?
I love this country. This would actually kill somebody. Like he's dead. He made me mess up.
That's the last words that person's ever gonna say. Now this is quality television.
Except my evil plan is in jeopardy. That person's skull crushed down into their spine. And their
brain was disintegrated.
That's two. So the third one. How do I knock out the third one?
What do I got? It's definitely something to do with this. Something to do with the boxing glove.
Put it somewhere that he runs into or let me go let me go look at the body.
He'll be out for a good while. Yeah forever actually.
He'll be out forever. Is there anything else down here? Takes me back to my childhood. Okay we got
more. We got stinky's. Stinky's diner. I can't go there. What with the van?
This one's this guy's dead too. What are you doing? Hey Bosco. Hey you just gonna leave him there?
Uh we want to buy something. What do you got your eye on? We'd like that tear gas grenade launcher.
That'll be ten thousand dollars. Oh were you serious about that? It's a bargain. Trust me.
Trust me. I never trust a man that says trust me twice. We gotta find an illegally wealthy
motorist and quick. Nothing. Okay so we gotta go. Thanks Bosco. Rest somebody for money and then
get the money and get the tear gas. I'm gonna go. How am I gonna get ten thousand dollars in tickets?
Just one big ticket. Where we going Sam? That's a lot. All right let's go give a ticket. That's
where that's for. All right here we go. Okay so we gotta pull over somewhere by running into them.
Like this guy. All right you're under arrest. This is your first and final warning. Pull over or die.
Click on the report card. Get doped. And you're not Ergo. We call the shops around here.
Oh why did you stop me? Hideously broken tail light. Indecent exposure. We're booking you sorry
hide for indecent exposure. What are you talking about? I'm fully clothed. Accept your face. Get
a veil please. Let's go Max. Having that face is punishment enough. That's two cops. Two police
officers say that to you. No one seems to be breaking the law today. I know what's the problem.
Start committing some crimes you sick bunch of reprobates. Hey you're naked. No I'm not. Well
you're ugly. Bye. Okay have a nice day officer. Jesus. What about you? Pull over or we'll be
forced to destroy your car. Greetings anonymous motorist. If you were planning to bribe us
now would be the appropriate time. What's the charge? Uh hideously broken worshiping false
idols ferret impression. This no nothing at all. Uh broken tail light. Your tail light's busted.
No it isn't. Well maybe it should be. Mental note. Try to pull over suspects who are actually guilty
of something. Again what terrible cops. Imagine a cop had to make a mental note out loud in front
of you that you didn't do anything wrong and they need to pull over for the did things wrong.
Well how am I supposed to tell him? He was doing something illegal. We're doing illegal shit. Nobody
else is. I can't like break it? That didn't break his tail light? How is me crashing into
somebody not break their tail light? Sam one tail light zero. Well just gonna bulk it. Do this all
day. God pull over. You have two broken tail lights. Hello sir or madam. You're in big trouble mister
or miss. For what? Your tail light's busted. Well you're the ones who broke it. Your point being
what's the fine for a broken tail light? $10,000. Why isn't it $10,000? What are you crazy? What? Oh
one moment allow me to confer with my legal counsel. My attorney has advised me to pay the
fine. What kind of inflation is the economy to happen to you? Bad. Jesus. All right I got 10 grand.
Yeah you gotta figure if you would just pay that fine something fucked up is really going on in
your current life. You will have to be like a super criminal. This probably like a $500,000
worth of cocaine in that person's car or something. I got a million dollars in fucking like cocaine
in this car. That'll be $10,000. Okay yeah doesn't mean you're gonna leave me alone. Yeah okay bye.
Hey Bosco. Hey that's the only reason why that makes sense. We want to buy something. What do you
got your eye on? We got your tear gas money right here. Really? All right here you go. One tear gas
grenade launcher. This is a salad shooter filled with onions. But it works. Trust me. Trust me.
Now put that away before someone gets hurt. What do you mean? The 10,000 just covered the cost
of materials you know. Oh I'm sure. It's okay everybody. I'm all right. Well you knew there
was a kind of it had to be a gag there somewhere. It's an onion. It's a salad. It's an onion shooter.
It's tear gas. It'll make you cry. When we shoot this at the shoot the onion at the
popper's face. Watch him cry and then punch him. Is this just going to be a one-off or
I'm going to play the rest of the game? I'm open to play the rest of the season.
This is cool. I'm just just hanging out. It's like a relaxing little experience. It's yeah I like it.
Oh Sybil. Yes. Uh the other Sybil. What is that? Don't worry this won't hurt a bit.
But it will make you cry. He's already crying. I can see you. What? Hey there he is. You attack
just comes naturally. They got a big fail safe in the game's engine here to make that not possible.
Oh Sybil. Now Peepers this is going to hurt us a lot more than it's going to hurt you.
Just kidding. It'll definitely hurt you more. Sweet dreams Peeps. I can see you.
Oh my that was great. That was great. Wait a second. My evil plan is in ruins.
The dog and bunny will rue the day they crossed me. Rue the day I say.
That was good. That was really good this time. Now I can try to bring him out of his hypnotic state.
Take control of your mind. I don't think he can hear you. Sure he can. He's unconscious. Not dead.
Minor detail. Destroy the intruder in your dreams. Regain control. What? Hey what am I doing here?
What's going on? Wait can we get him to sing the song? My name's not Sybil. It's Peepers.
Oh yes it is. Are you okay? How do you feel? I've got a weirdest dream. And there was someone
unusual in your dream wasn't there? Yes Brady Culture was there. He kept telling me to do stuff.
Aha. I knew it. That fiend hypnotized you to do his unspeakable bidding. Peepers what's the last
thing you can remember? I remember checking in at Brady Culture's home for former child stars.
He has his own nut house? Wow we gotta meet this guy. Where can we find this home for former child
stars? Oh it's very secret. No one must ever find it. Think of a scandal. Five o'clock shadow? But we need
to find it so we can stop the madness. I thought he was like huffing spray paint. I want to help but
I just can't remember where it is. Oh brothers might. They went with me. Hey I didn't do anything
really embarrassing did I? Nothing a simple exorcism can't fix. Oh dear. Witness him.
All right let's do it. So wait is there anything else I can do in here? Do you have anything else
for me? Hey doc. Hey Sam thanks for taking care of that wacko. Oh we could use another 10 grand.
Have you got 10 grand? I'm new at this. I have a lot of student loans. Great loan us a student. I
can ride it around like a pony. It's nice to see you show such enthusiasm. Security. You don't have
security back there. That button's not connected to anything. Max might like a tattoo. Oh yeah I
want a map of the Netherlands on my Netherlands. I get the cold shivers just thinking about
remembering hearing you say that. I'm out of the tattoo business anyway. I'm a licensed psychotherapist.
Can you fix cars? Ours sometimes makes a noise like an orangutan with the dry heaves. Um that's
my fault. I've been keeping an orangutan in the trunk. Oh never mind. I'm not much of a mechanic
anyway except with unicycles. All right well let's get an analyst. I suppose you could psychoanalyze
me. Hey yeah I could count your marbles for you. I have a license you know. Will this be painful?
Only if we do it right. Now there are a couple things we can try. We could look at some ink
plots. We could try some free association. I could interpret your dreams for you.
Let's try ink plot. How do ink blots work? And can we make them ourselves? It's easy. I just
show you some pictures and you tell me what you see. Your responses can reveal things like
obsessions or obsessions. Let's get psychoanalyzed on screen. Take a look at this and tell me what
you see. Uh that's Goro from Mortal Kombat about to do a fatality to me. It's a point of view.
See he's like fucking running at me. Uh okay pennies on the eyes of a dead mime. I don't see
a pair of oxen boxing in a rowboat. I don't see that either. Susan Lucci holding an emmy.
I don't see that either. The results of the last time I let Max drive. I mean that's it could be
like like flat. The results of the last time I let Max drive. All right now how about this one?
Okay without even looking. This is two old ladies. These are two old ladies with their hands up. So
they see like the big bun hair. Two cigarettes. Two old ladies back to back about to do a duel
with cameras. They're selfie dueling. That's what I see first of all first and foremost before I
look at anything. Okay a bunch of bacteria playing basketball. I don't see that. Pigeons
on at the marquee at a man's chinese theater. No an SUV crashing into an opulent mansion.
No the st valentine's day. I no I don't see any. I see like a mustache. No none of this is right.
Pigeons on the marquee. No SUV. I would probably. Pigeons I guess. Pigeons on the marquee at man's
chinese theater. And this. All right what do I see first of all without looking at it? This is
this looks like some type of satan or something. Like see like the face. Two eyes. Nose.
Just looming. Hovering over what looks to be potentially. This is the body. Maybe a body.
Like it's a goat head. Goat satan. Goat. It's just satan because it's like the legs and like
the arms and shit. Or it could be multiple entities at the same time. Or like a scorpion
or something. A squirrel that got run over twice. Now this one. What do you see? Okay this one
again I see two. It's either okay it's either uh oros from world of warcraft. Like the light
things. Some of you will get that. Or there's another it's the nose. The face. His hand coming
out like to dancing like dueling dancing to like circus performers or back to back here
with doing selfie selfie uh duels. The exhaust manifold of a bread truck. And this one. Uh this
is a pokemon. This is when it goes like doo doo doo. And it zooms in and then it fades into color
and they go like. Mujito. That's the only thing I can see. There's been somebody fucked up
pokemons. I guarantee if you superimpose a pokemon that looks like this on it they're
they're out of like the 16 000 pokemon that exist now. One of these matches. Pokemon
is the simpsons of monster character creation. If you think you made up something they already
have done it. It's just that joke. Do you oh you have like an original monster animal thing that
you've drawn. No there's a pokemon. There's already like 30 000 of a database has been made.
A war between two teams of abstract shapes. You seem fairly focused on cars but it's probably
nothing to worry about anymore. Thanks doc. Wait what? What's free association like? It's a test of
your reactions to things in your life. I say a word and then you just say or do the first thing
that comes into your head. Okay. Dance a samba. Recite the alphabet. Scream at the top of my lungs.
That sort of thing. Interesting. Have we started already? No but now we will. Ready? Is that the
word? No the word is tumbleweed. Vegas. Oh uh uh uh eucalyptus. Eucalyptus. Interesting. Now try
this one. Crown. King. Just do or say whatever comes naturally. Frozen concentrated orange juice.
I see. Comb. Hair. That's not so basic. A pomade. Promenade. What an unusual response.
Well this has been illuminating. What's the verdict? I'll let you know after years of insanely
expensive treatment. Anything to support small local businesses. We can always sell organs on
the black market to raise the cash. Just so they're not ours little buddy. No I would dream. This is
okay I want to do. Does this exist? Can I take like a total like evaluation somewhere online?
I want to do this whole thing like like three hours. Can you really learn anything from my
grotesque nonsensical dreams? Oh absolutely. They reveal your subconscious. It's like peeling an
onion. Now just relax and try to remember your dream. Yeah I want to stream it. Okay here goes.
Remember your dream. My dreams always start in the office but this time things were different.
Yes I can picture it. Tell me what happens. It's called Buzzfeed quizzes.
No I'm talking about like a real. I realized there was someone else in the room with me.
Like this costs money and I go get analyzed with a bunch of blots and ink tests and
questions and that kind of fast responses and we'll see what they do.
This is me. It was me. You? Hmm I think you represent yourself.
I didn't even realize that was possible. Oh sure any crazy thing's possible in psychoanalysis.
Tell me did the other you say or do anything unexpected? No the usual. Hi Sam how are you?
I'm fine Sam and yourself. Not too shabby. Fascinating. Where does your mind come up with
this stuff? See I told you me and Sam I get that vibe completely with this because you know like
hair comb. I didn't notice anything. Then why do you mention it? I don't know. Interesting.
I wanted the trash. Me then trash then the board. I noticed something bizarre in the closet.
Yes we put things in the closet we want to hide away things we're ashamed of.
Please Sam what's in your closet? A bunch of a bunch of shit stained underwear that I don't
want anyone to see. A whole stack of lottery tickets. Interesting perhaps you feel you don't
really earn your money. Don't worry lady we get paid to crack skulls and by that measure we
ought to be millionaires. I noticed something bizarre in the closet. Ah something you're ashamed
of. What was it? No that's fine lottery tickets. A whole stack of lottery tickets. Don't worry lady.
All right what else? I tell you sometimes I forget that I'm just like live and I just
that I'm streaming. I remembered that I'd just gotten something from the bakery.
Oh sounds like you and your special guest there were having a little lottery ticket today.
I got a birthday cake, a wedding cake, a fruit cake, a cheesecake.
It was a cheesecake and I mean literally a piece of cheese and a cake. What does that represent?
No that doesn't mean anything. It's just random nonsense. That's good. One cheesecake for every
death in Sekiro. Sounds good Sam. What else is here? Out the window? I prepared to leap out of the
window. Oh was that the end of your dream? Yes. Yep then I woke up screaming. I can see why.
Let's examine my obsessions with inkblots. Let's examine my okay hold on. Wait didn't I already do
some more ink blots? Oh and more ink blots. Sure let's take a look at this and tell me.
Oh we already did it never mind. Oh shit how do I get out of here? The result. All right now.
Pitch. And this. A squirt. Now this one. The. And this one. A warby. But it's probably. Next up.
I got them all. Let's go. Actually let's save the psychoanalysis for later.
Hmm. Postponing responsibilities. Interesting. Okay so now we can get out of here. Probably.
That's it for the three um. Unless that's the wrong way. He's instinctively going over there.
His dream. Remember the lottery tickets? You guys have fucking analyzed. Oh stop analyzing me.
Don't get out of here. Get out of my head. Okay so now we go back to the office. He thinks he's
streaming right now. Interesting. Where? They're very weird. He's talking out loud while lying down
on his back. In the bed. Is he still hypnotized? Tiny hoodlums. No comment.
Uh anything on tv? On this week's edition of oh is he still alive? We look at the stars of the
1970s television hit the soda poppers. I love shows that destroy all our cherished delusions
about the stars we once loved. He's dead. During the soda poppers heyday young specks was the
role model for obsessive neat freaks all over the globe. Ticker tape free ticker tape parades were
thrown in honor of the soda popper who never missed a spot. Backstage though things were
quite a bit dirtier. Speck's obsession with perfection caused massive delays in shooting
and infuriated co-workers. He famously demanded over 11 000 retakes of the line. You made me mess
up. Made all the more annoying because of his tendency to repeat the line immediately after
reading it. Following the show specks was rarely seen in public. Although he did make one ill-fated
venture into celebrity tag team mud wrestling. Getting on this show someday. As he desperately
tried to wipe down the ring with a dish rag. The meltdown utterly enraged his tag team partner
and good friend the dog from my mother the dog who stormed out of the arena without a word.
They haven't spoken since. Coming up next the soda popper who couldn't always keep it in.
Well that was okay. Mother of the dog for jerma rumble. Hey tough settle down all right now
everybody has to join. Where are we going Sam? Settle down all right let's waste precious time
driving around aimlessly. Let's go cruise for lawbreakers Max. Goodie. Pretty Sam and Max tag
team though. That seems really possible doesn't it? If it's good enough if I like it. Do I drive
to a new area? Is this the only the only three locations I can do right now? Where'd the popper
go? Where'd popper? What is this one? Take control of your mind. I have to like say the line. Is it working? I don't know
destroy the intruder in your dreams. Snap out of it you big baby. What what's going on?
Why is my outfit all wrinkled? He's back. Quick act like a chicken. No tell us where we can find
radio culture's home for former child stars. We've got to stop that fiend from hypnotizing anyone else.
The home it's 227 something. Wizard would remember this. All right let's go wake up wizard.
Can you take us there? Are you kidding? I've got hours hours of iron. Well that was helpful.
What am I doing? Hello. Oh sorry I was doing Donald Duck. I was trying to for a second. Take
control of your mind. Destroy the intruder in your dreams. It's not gonna happen though. Nicely done
Sam. You're a natural. Where am I? Who are you? Don't worry we're freelance police. Police? Oh no.
Oh hey. He's getting away in that truck. Quick follow that soda popper. Oh okay.
Driving sequence. Hurry Sam he's getting away.
Oh dropping trash. It's actually kind of hard to tune at the mouse.
Come here.
Got it. Yes. I got it. Don't shoot. Aside from the fact that we just plugged your truck
why would you think we'd shoot you? Except for the obvious sport value of course. It's just you
always see cops on the news beating up some guy just because he's a former child star.
We would never dream of hurting former child stars. We just need to find the home where Brady
Culture keeps them. Oh why didn't you say so? It's right over there across the street.
Jumping elephant fleas. How devilishly convenient. Thanks. Um does anyone know where I can find a
bathroom? Here we go. The four Brady Cultures home for former child stars. Where to go first?
Mall man. Looks like a shifty character to me. Don't they all? I think someone was sitting here.
And leaking. Okay other door admission forms. Hmm it says here they only treat patients with
something called artificial personality disorder. Sounds tasty. What's in it? Apparently it's common
in former child stars. Symptoms include uh let's see obsession with money, violent reactions to
dentistry, and an unconscious desire to see one's peers getting older. Forsooth! You don't even know
what that means dude. I went to the dentist today. No but it sounds all classically literate. I went
to the dentist today. Teeth are fucking clean. They're beautiful. They're perfect. I have two
cavities I have to get a root canal and I have to change out one of my teeth. One of them is
completely broken and rotten in the back. So I mean. Hmm it's order a pair and a disturbing
little monkey. Oh my teeth are fine. You're a monkey? Essentially. I guess this is where you
stick your admission form. We need an admission form so can I take an admission form? Symptoms form.
It didn't like it. I bet we have to get that officially filled out. Trust me. Okay so we're
going to bring this form back to uh Sybil. Home for former gerber rumble stars. All right we got
the form. Let's bring it back to Sybil. Just click on everything. We got the form. Let's go ahead and
add inflection at the end of every sentence. Back to the office. Let's get in the car.
That'll bring us to where we are now. Sybil's office. Is it time for a pee break? Not yet.
It will be very soon though. I've got news for you. Somebody said shut the fuck up. You're gonna be
in big trouble if you keep that up. Big trouble. Big trouble. Do you think I might have artificial
personality disorder? Hmm interesting. Symptoms include uh let's see obsession with money,
violent reactions to dentistry, and an unconscious desire to see one's peers getting older. Hey I know
I could psychoanalyze you. You already did. No I already did this. This took like 25 minutes.
Actually let's save the psycho now. Hmm. Oh god damn it. Symptoms include uh obsession with
money, violent reactions to dentistry, and an unconscious desire to see one's. Okay so we have
to take. Hey doc. Hey. How do you like to shrink my head a little? Of course. What? Okay ink blocks.
Can we do some more? Sure. Take a look. Okay so what was the first thing? It was reactions to
money. Pennies on the eyes of a dead mime. Pennies on the eyes of a dead mime. Interesting. The next
thing was. How about this one? The peers getting older. No it was the second one. Uh it was money,
obsession with money, and then the second one was what? Dentistry. A bunch of bacteria.
SUV crashing into a mansion. Pigeons. Bacteria. An SUV crashing into an opulent.
And this? Squirreling around an uncle moth eating. Oh they're all money related okay. My uncle Louie's
moth eating wallet. Now this one. What do you see? It's like I do money for all these. New York stock
exchange. Yeah elephants at the New York stock exchange. And this one. So we're just gaming the
system here right now to get what we want. Debit card. A debit card fed through a document shredder.
Hmm well judging by your responses you seem to be fairly obsessed with that's a symptom of
artificial personality disorder. I'd better mark it on your chart. Germa's obsessed with money.
He's obsessed with it. Very interesting. We should test you for the other symptoms of APD.
Whatever you say, sawbones. I'm not a sawbones. I'm a psychotherapist. Isn't it weird when you say
the word money? Hey I'm getting hungry. I don't know why but sometimes I don't know what it is.
Money. Like what happens on your face when you do it? Say money. Like your your nose scrunches
and you're like up your upper lip goes up like money. Money. It's a weird fucking word.
Money. I'll show you. Ready? Watch my face. Um dog. Cat. Hammer. Money. Ball. Dream. Car.
Money. Money. Money. It's weird. I don't know why I do that. Closet. Money. Race track. Baby.
Money. All right let's keep going. Let's try some more free association. That will tell us more
about your unreasonable reactions to the elements of your life. Remember I'll say words and you just
do or say whatever comes naturally. Ready? Sure go ahead. Cow. So uh this is uh what's this one?
This is not the one growing older. Dentist. Lamp black. Sample size. Travesty. Is it what what does
this have to do with the dentist? Cow. Violent reaction to the dentist. Sample size. Mm-hmm. How
about this word? Drill. Here we go. What do you think of this free association? No no no no Max.
Seems like a crack. Hmm dialogue. No no no no no no. Hey I'm not imaginary. If you say so. Dryer.
Just do whatever comes naturally. Shit. Can we stop now? I was not trying to click on Max.
Am I saying the jerk? Do you think I might? Maybe. Let's try some more free association. That will
tell us more about your unreasonable reactions to the elements of your life. A punch. Remember I'll
say words and you just do or say whatever comes naturally. Great job. You just scared the money
out of my wallet. Have a good night. Lug nut. Thank you for the thank you so much for the money.
Major clusterfuckers. That's actually this fucking lot of money. Seriously thank you.
Calorie consciousness. Really? Have a good night as well. Major clusterfuck. Fluoride. Just do or say
whatever comes naturally. Fluoride. Travesty. Fluoride. Travesty. I thought you might say
something like that. Teasing. Teasing. Aquamarine. Interesting. Well this has been. Am I? Do you think
I might? Maybe. No. Let's try. That will tell us. Remember I'll say. Ready? Ready. Interesting
choice of word. Let's go. Okay. Let's try. Promenade. I see. Polish. Polish. Whoa don't shoot. Violent
reaction. Violent reaction. You should see him at Thanksgiving. Violent reaction to the word.
Interesting. Polish. Just do or say whatever comes naturally. Sample size. What an unusual.
This has been illuminating. All right. Yes. Your responses lead me to believe that you have
podiatrists. It could be symptomatic of artificial personality disorder. I'd better mark this on your
chart. What is it? Sample size. You have two of the symptoms listed on this form. Am I deranged?
I don't want to alarm you but probably. Can I have your hat when they commit you? Sure little buddy.
I'd like to tell you about another mundane but strangely compelling dream I have. So this is now.
Right. Let's examine your disturbing subconscious desires a bit further. Okay tell me what happened.
You're scared of other people getting older. I realized there was someone else in the room with
me. Oh who was your special guest? So it's not me. Who would it be? Other people. It would be Max
right? It was Max. Ah yes your imaginary friend. Not you getting older. Excuse me I'm standing
right next to you lady. In your dream was Max doing anything unusual? Well he was seeing the pledge
of allegiance to the tune of Camptown Races. I pledge allegiance to my gun dooda dooda. But that's
not unusual. Okay what was Max doing? What was Max doing? I had just gotten something new from
the bakery. For a celebration perhaps? What did you get? A birthday cake because they're getting older.
It was an overly frosted birthday cake. Wait a second. The birthday cake? Your friend? You
subconsciously want to see your peers get older. I could have told you that. This is a definite
symptom of artificial personality disorder. Yes I mean I hope it's not serious. I'd better mark
this on your chart. Mock it on your chart. Wow it must be artificial personality disorder.
You've got all the signs. I bet I can get a paper out of this. Better ship me off to some sort of
home for former child stars then. I've signed this admissions form but you'll have to arrange
your own transportation. I'm about to be really busy publishing the details of your case. Since
you're crazy can I drive? Jumping vehicular homicide? No. I've been doing that more frequently.
God that's the wrong door. It's just so close. All right so I got it symptoms form. Let's go turn it in.
Where we going Sam? Back to Brady Culture's home for former child stars. Oh okay.
Put it in. You've been accepted. Come on little buddy there's justice to be served. Can we get ice cream afterwards?
Justice makes me hungry. This reminds me of that place where Aunt Trudy lives with the medicine smell
and the rubber sheets and the enormous mute Indian. Sounds like a million laughs. Yeah mostly after
medication time. Where is everyone?
There he is. Uh-oh. Polk Rutoot above doubts. This is Culture's clubhouse.
Jumping lawn cheney and a bottle fright wig. Brady Culture I presume. You know who I am.
Evil plans really do work. Don't get too excited stretch pants. The freelance police are here.
Yes actually. I've been waiting for you. Really? Next time try leaving the front door open.
Save us all some grief. Allow me to explain.
Uh-oh I think we just triggered a soliloquy. Good thing I have the attention span of a pinty yak butter.
I never wanted much. Just to be universally loved that's all and to be number one in the tv ratings
for the 1971 fall season. It's doing a lot of really good piano playing. Those worthless hacks.
The pseudopuppies with their matching shirts and their cute little jingles. They came on opposite
me and stole my audience. I was never offered another role and now YouTube vigilantes won't
even let a poor down on his luck actor mass hypnotize the entire viewing public to become
his worshipful fans forever. It's an organ just mashing on your face against it. It'll sound good.
I think so. You know that's true. Since you've ruined the beautiful irony of having some of the
best organ songs are just mashing. I'm afraid you'll just have to take their places. In your
dreams culture. No my friends in yours. Hey that tickles. Become video delivery man.
What what's happening? Oh no oh no what what are you doing? I don't know. I you were in on it all
along. I told you it was a conspiracy. I told you but then you already knew didn't you? You're awake.
No Bosco. I must deliver videos. Call the CIA. Call Interpol. Call Mickey Rooney. Must deliver
Mickey Rooney videos. So we have to deliver the videos? Where's Max? I must deliver videos. Hey
my beloved weapons are gone. I must deliver videos. Give me the cheese. Too far. Too far.
Uh I tried to get the cheese. All right give me the cheese. Oh don't even try it. I love that part.
Now somebody come in and tell me that everything's. Hey tell me. Talk to me. Do the spell. The reverse
spell. Uh oh either I just walked into the Salvador Dali Memorial Wax Museum or I'm dreaming.
You love me. You adore me. Become video delivery man. Do my evil bidding and so forth.
Holy brains in a blender. I'm still hypnotized. If only I could remember what Sybil told me to do.
Destroy the intruder in your dream. Oh yeah. Hey Sam I'm up here. Oh hi little buddy. Do I
gotta put everybody back together again? You stole my body. I hate when people do that. You gotta
get me down from here. Okay little guy I'll save you. All right so first things first. Let's take
your head off. Max's body. Oh and it feels good too. I just love my new furry paws and cute little
tail. Hey don't touch my tail you psychopathic body stealer. Oh just let me at him. All right
do I have any items? Like a gun? It's Brady culture on TV. Yes right where I belong. Everyone
watch me. Me! Shooting TV stars only makes them stronger. Is that? I don't know but I don't know
if I believe that. Didn't hurt. I don't want to pop him. Smoke. All right I didn't even know this
is over here. Hold on. It's just a dream Sam. Bicycle pump and the rat. Weird what is this thing?
Is it bicycle pump it? Now we got a giant rat. Sweet rodent eating disorders. That is one fat rat.
Oh interesting. What about the closet? He's in the closet too with the cheese. I will be number one
in the ratings. Now hey Brady cheese. What is it fool? I'd like to introduce you to a little
friend of mine. Make him big so he gets in there and eats him. Only has like a couple seconds to
do it though. No the cheese must stand alone. And another one bites the cheese. All right so what
did that do? Is it empty? All right the smoke probably does something.
I will be universally strange. What does he say about it? Don't worry little buddy I'll get you.
Hurry Sam I've got an itch I can't scratch. Guns not gonna do anything. What about the window?
TV can't shoot the TV. Bicycle pump. Brady culture has a knife. Enigmatic. What's he pointing at?
Why is he pointing at me? You just following me around? He's not doing it now. Dance puppet dance.
I think someone needs to turn the lights out on your career Brady.
That Brady culture he turns the world off with his smile. Coat rack is a pencil. Interesting.
Can I pick it up? It's just a dream Sam. I cannot pick it up. So what how do I get your head?
Off of that body. What is this doing here? Hey it's loose. Down? Whoa okay. That was the most fun
I've had since I lost my body. I gotta get his head. I gotta get his head off. I gotta move him over
here or get his head off. That was great but Sam if you'll know. Okay hold on. All right how do I
can I push you over? Brady's stolen Max's. Just let me at him. How do I get how do I move you this
way? I may not show it much but I love you Sam. Now go wash my car. Uh should I break this open?
Weird. I may not. Can I turn it the other way? Does it have to go down? Can I move it to the
other side so it goes left or right? Okay hold on. Whoa gotcha. All right I thought I could.
How do I get your head off? Can I just tear it off with my bare hands?
I don't think Max would like me sticking his head there. No no not like not like shove your head
down his pants. I'm talking like here. Oh Mr. Culture I have a surprise for you. Really? For me?
Oh my. Thanks Sam. A little stringy but good. Oh I just remembered I'm supposed to be somewhere.
Bye Max. I did it. Do I need to release them? I may not show it much but I
washed my car. How do I get the tv off? I can't shoot the tv now. Can I shoot the tv now that his
his brain is gone? I think I've done. This smoke is the only thing that's interactable I think
still. What the hand? I want strange. Is there a plug? I wonder what would happen to the picture
quality if I gave this a tug. This is essentially pulling the plug. I must be on tv for all eternity.
Oh yes that's much better reception. You got it. Oh no he's awake. What done for? Save the girlish
histrionics Bosco. I'm all right. I was merely the victim of your garden variety video delivery.
TV finally has a use. But what about your co-conspirator? My co-conspirator? Holy underpants
draped to the mast of a sinking pork rind freighter. That hirsuteeumaniac kidnapped
my little buddy. Why is Sam Robin from the 60s Batman? Lightning Rider just gave five community
subs. Thank you for the five subs. Coming in with five. Any community subs? Thank you.
Brady Coulter? I bow man. Stay away from him. He's got it in for me. Sorry Bosco. No can do. I've got
to save my free little pal. Can you help me? I don't suppose you have a Bosco tech device
that stymies hypnosis inducing energy beams. A hypnosis blocker? I thought about making one of
those but I would even know where to begin. I've got to find something quick. Bye Bosco. Do me proud.
There's no time for that. No don't take the cheese. Can I just go walk back in the front door?
Do I have a car? No my car is gone right? Technically. Yeah I guess I drove back.
How did I drive the car back? I'm not going back to that asylum until I've got a working defense
against that dastardly hypnotist. Okay what about over here? Maybe Sybil will give me something.
Speaking of community subs. Ert thank you. Ert for the five community subs. Ert 110 thank you.
Doc Max is gone. Well most of us outgrow our imaginary friends eventually. No that
megalomaniac Brady cultures got him. I see of course. How do you get picked for a community sub?
I think it's just random. It randomly just picks a non-sub in the chat and they get it. Hang on.
Were you implying that Max is imaginary? I wasn't implying anything though he does seem a little
improbable. But you have to do it singularly. But then I'm a psychotherapist. I forgot to find
some way to block a hypnotic ray. I don't suppose you as a brain specialist of sorts would know
anything. I've been monitoring people for months to choose who to pick. Great suffering. Oh really?
You do know something. Oh there you go. Before my synapses fuse into a milky puddle of swine.
Speaking of subs. Brody and thanks for the five community subs. Brody weapon. Thank you.
But one of my more technologically inclined patients drew me a diagram of a contraption
he claimed will block hypnosis. That's just the sort of ridiculously lucky break I need.
It's a huge violation of every reasonable code of ethical conduct of course. But you being a
policeman of sorts. I suppose it's okay to give you the diagram. My lack of solid engineering
background has finally caught up with me. I can't make any sense of this. I'd love to help but
engineering is one of the few fields I haven't tried. Sorry. Engineering. Okay.
Hey pilot guy. Five more community subs from pilot guy. Five more community subs from
German lied about Minecraft VR. Drossophilia five community subs. Now here comes the the rollout of
gifted subs. Thank you guys. I'm gonna go give this to Bosco. It's not that way. Oh Jesus.
Five. I can't. They're coming out too fast. Gnarly thanks for the five community subs.
Peek of banana five. Pixel Mike five. Drossophilia five. It's a lot. Thank you guys. What a generous
bunch of people. Even more coming in. Flug boy. Gnarly. Did Gnarly give another five?
Flug boy with five. Who now isn't a sub? Everybody's a sub at this point. Thank you guys.
That won't help me. Can you make something out of this? Bosco take a gander at this. Thank you
Kyratopia for the five even nice subs. It's instructions for the latest in Bosco tech
innovation. Buy from Kyratopia. Yeah I can build this. Just need one thing. What's that? Something
for that antenna thing at the top. Antenna. Got it. Didn't I just didn't already pick it up?
Go get the antenna from the tv. Sorry I had to new. I sneezed. I had to sneeze.
Shadows one. Disciple. Thank you for the five community subs.
One Mystica. Thanks for the five community subs. Thank you guys. More subs rolling in.
A fucking shitload. That's like 50. More.
Max isn't gonna like it when he finds out I ruined our reception.
I've got to tell him as soon as possible. Wholesome chat. Generous chat. I got a sub. I'm a lurker.
I'm glad you got it. Let's go back. Give him the cone hanger so he can fix this. Finish it. Another
five from Adventure MF Dan. Five community subs. Will a make-do antenna do as a make-do antenna?
Yeah okay. Let me just add a little Bosco tech innovation. Thank you. Here it is. The most
sophisticated hypnosis blocking helmet the world has ever seen. You guys are too much. Thank you
guys. Happy days are here again. Uh oh seems like the old moolah gauge is running on empty.
I take it. Just stop that bread culture. He's got it in for me. You're a credit to dementia Bosco.
You'll have to pay for the next one though. To wear this thing. I'll put it on inside
this neighborhood. Sounds good. What is it? Food review? What food should I review? I don't have
any food to review. I've been a sub for five years and all I got was this lousy streamer.
That's actually a pretty... That would be a funny shirt. It would be. Let's get in here. Put on the
helmet. Rule number three. Always wear protective headgear when confronting diabolical villains
with hypnotic devices. Still waiting for that clown car. When's he gonna get in the clown car?
Hand over the lagomorph culture. Sam! Boy am I glad to see you. Johann Sebastian here only knows
how to play one song. What's this? A rerun? Didn't we just see the dog getting hypnotized episode?
Well if you really want to watch it again.
What? Back into him. Another triumph for skanky ingenuity and ordinary kitchenware.
Give it up culture. Your quiche is cooked. Time out for the cavalry. You colored outside the lines
of the law Brady culture. We see you and this time we're going to get hypnotized again.
Why didn't I have headgear for them? I should have made three of them. So now my foolish pawns. Attack
the dog. That doesn't need it. Attack the dog.
Attack the dog. Well there's videos over there. Television.
They have no gun. Boxing glove. Can I like give them tape to fight over?
It's a stack of those libo videos.
Don't think that. Hey culture have you ever watched your own video tape? Of course not.
I'm not an idiot. What? Why? Why did that happen? It's a stack of those libo videos.
Attack the dog. Okay so then they attack. I pull up the glove. They stop. I don't know I want to
open the inventory. Attack the videotapes.
Attack the videotapes. That's a good idea. Attack Brady culture. No attack the dog. Hey what?
What? Become what? Become me. Summer assaulting democrats in a crate of sauerkraut.
Patience is a sharp razor to swallow. You crack me up little buddy. Who's that supposed to be?
Attack the dog. Attack the dog.
This is a good turn-based video game. All right so become yourselves right?
Become Brady culture. Become become videotapes. Become videotapes. Black wits. Attack the dog.
Ouch.
Attack yourselves. Attack yourselves.
Attack Brady culture. No attack. Ouch. You okay little buddy? How are you doing up there?
Adversary with gory high school poems while he plays that dumb song over and over.
Hey that's my theme song. Well I mean there's the videotapes.
Become yourselves. Become yourselves. Attack the dog. Attack me.
Whoops. Ouch. Attack the dog.
Become Brady culture. Do my evil bidding. Worship the videotape. Attack the dog. Attack the dog.
Attack the dog. I can't move. Telev- can I attack the tv?
Every bed's got its own tv. I feel like making a bad pun about Brady's order.
Wait wait wait wait wait. Where did worship come from? Worship? Worship wasn't here before.
Worship me. No. Worship me you minions. Mine. It's a step. Attack the dog.
Ouch. Where was worship before? Worship me. No me me. Worship me. Everything is about me.
Me me me. I don't think that would be interested enough. I don't think. Attack me. No me. Attack
me. Me me me. Yes. No wait I mean. We had to actually do Daffy Duck. Remember I told
you that before with the very beginning. We had to play like it was a cartoon. I tried to send
you semaphore signals with my ears but you know how I always get the K and the V mixed up.
You crack me up little buddy. Well I guess we should de-hypnotize these poor saps again and
be on our way. Let me. You know how I adork gratuitous violence. Caffeine rock.
Well that's that Max. You didn't break them the lenses just came out. You have to melt those
lenses down. The blind control thing didn't go any further. That could have been really annoying.
It's great to be on your show Myra. I'm a huge fan. I just can't seem to stop watching for some
reason. Hey Salmon Max. Episode two or Dragon. What do you think? Episode two? What do you think?
Personality test? Double do that? That'll be a whole screen.
All right let's take a good pee break. We'll bring it back. We'll do episode two.
They're all like two two and a half hours so that's a good time.
Now we're gonna do season one episode two. That drunk guy at car tape not killing us.
What? Who is that? Is that somebody in Mr. Credits? That was somebody's job description?
Oh special thanks I see. Well that's episode one. I'm gonna save it. Oh well I already beat it so
it don't matter. Episode two is its own separate game so we're gonna open it. I'll be right back.
Gonna grab a water. Gonna pee. Be back in like two three minutes. See you real soon. Okay let's
quit out of this and open up episode two. But I also want to make this clear. Make sure everyone
knows it's existing. That after today you are not going to see me for a week. I'm out. I'm out of
here. I will be back around this time next weekend. I'm going on a mom vacation. I will not be around.
Just make sure everybody knows. Talked about it a bunch but want to make sure nobody misses it.
It's gonna be the title of my stream for a week. Is it gonna be mom is here. See you next week.
Jerma's average dong comes in with 10 community subs. Thank you for the 10 community subs.
Jerma's average dong. I gotta mute this because it's probably gonna be pretty loud. What's episode
two called? Situation comedy is episode two. Interesting. Are they all like two two and a half
hours long or is it one of those scenarios where because it seems like each one is its own game.
Okay five more community subs from Freudian Weapon. Thank you Freudian. Thank you all of you.
Listen how loud this is. You can hear that shit but this is the gym playlist. I had to take them
out. Headphones are out. More community subs from Jerma's average dong. Oh my god. Thank you. Ten
more. Uh why is it just skipping right to this? No I gotta hold on. I gotta get to the menu.
More community subs. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR. Five more community subs.
You guys. Somebody get that phone. Oh wow a 15 sub dong. Okay here we go. I'm gonna have to restart
it. The resolution's all wrong. It's all wrong. All right that's better. Uh gotta turn full screen
off because I cannot capture it otherwise it'll lag. Apply the resolution and let's cap the
screen. What do you say? Let's get this over with huh. There we are. Okay new game. Yes I do want to
make a new game. All right let's do episode two. This is cool though. It's fun just to sit and play
and hang out. I said this yesterday but it's kind of been a while since we've just relaxed and played
a game together. Just watched and hung out. Talked about stuff. It's good to do it. We did it
yesterday. Ten more community subs from my average dong. Jerma's average dong. That that's
10, 20, 30 plus community subs. Thank you so much. I'm gonna duel to start this one. I remember
that gun. That thing was worth a lot of money too. Yes that's the what's it called? The Lugamore
print. Yep.
Oh isn't that a hypnosis thing?
Gifts against their collective will. I don't normally endorse the use of the word dastardly
but this is clearly dastardly. Pretty refined for a Lugamore. We've got to drive over to the station
right away. We're at our earliest convenience. Great I've been itching to bust some skulls since
they cancelled my so-called life. The voice actor changed? Why? The other voice actor did episode one
and that's it. More dong. Ten more dongs. Thank you so much for the ten community subs.
Not so average anymore. Not such an average dong. Local streamer gets rich off own genitals.
But yeah if you're taking off I know it's late. I started really late.
But we're gonna go for a little longer. We'll do episode two. We'll chill.
We'll probably go pretty late. So if it's uh I know I started at like seven o'clock
pacific but I did want to go live today because I knew I wasn't going to be live for a while. So
if you're going to take off see you soon. See you next week. The sauce will be set to the day
and me and my mother will have a good time. But for people that are sticking around
we'll go I'm assuming past midnight tonight pacific at least. Sam and Max 2. Here we go.
Myra stump holding her audience hostage. You watch that particular bit of daytime fluff occasionally
don't you Max? Whenever our tv's out of hot for some reason I can't get enough of her sharp tooth
maternal ranting. Holy shit. Jerma's average dong. Jerma average dong is trying to reach
Jerma's massive dong status. More community subs. You're a lovable but essentially useless lump of
Thank you for 10 more. Oh my god. On the contrary I can be a vital source of alternative insight
into the problems that plague you. Well there's that. I am the massive dong.
Oh god they're the same person.
This is all secret plot for me to talk about my dong. Why do you suppose Myra's got her
audience captive? Who knows? Last month Charles Groton put his hand on her desk and she hit it
with a ruler. She's very strict. It's incredibly generous though. It really is. Let's get going.
You lead and I'll follow hack hat. They're all the same person. It leads back to me now. Seriously
whoever you are thank you. It's a lot of money. All right so it's the same town same people same
things just new adversary. What is it? She's in the closet still? Nope. Oh it's the hair.
It makes for an unwieldy but oh so enchanting memento of our first case in a long while.
He howled like a sick wallaby when I shaved it off him. Quick times. It's the hair. More
more subs. The dong money laundering scheme continues. 10 more. 90 subs already.
What? Oh my god. Let's go. Let's take a let's take a walk over here. Newspaper. Newspaper.
Brady culture behind bars. He finally found a way to become famous. The police plotter.
Alien love triangle times. Looks like they're sold out. How do you report dick money to the IRS?
Takes me back to my childhood. Oh my god. Bringing Jerma up to a higher tax bracket.
And don't forget about Adventure Dan with five more community subs. Thank you. Not really.
It's me Bosco. What's with the planet ship strainer Bosco? Bosco? I know not that moniker.
I am Lord Reginald Rumplebottom. Earl of Dukedom. Sam what language is he speaking?
I'm not sure Max but I think it might be English. Local streamer writes off penis on tax form as a
dependent. Imagine trying to pulse him. I mean that what would you okay if you were at the IRS
and you saw that what'd you do? Would you laugh or would you be like annoyed? I'm not sure. No
really what made you convert to British? It's because everybody's got an end for me that's why.
Yeah we heard. I had to get a disguise to throw them off the trail. Oh they'll never find me now.
They wouldn't even know where to begin to look. Clever clogs.
All right so what what's the problem? The forces of evil are bedeviling you this time.
It's the skin bodies man they're after me. Skin bodies? Sounds like a pack of belligerent nudists.
Oh no the skin bodies are like skinheads but ten times worse. Sure they're not a hundred times worse?
Yeah maybe a hundred times maybe a million. Um these skin bodies what exactly are they doing to
you? They're stealing my I mean pinching my shaving cream. Of all the things of yours they could pinch
why the shaving cream? So they can shave their bodies of course. Of course they shave their
whole bodies. Yeah what happened to your security? Not to be rude but why? You're the best in the
world. Best security in the world. Stopping these skin bodies. Well after the whole video delivery
conspiracy I figured I better build something to keep people from bringing stuff into my store.
So? So I needed to borrow some of the high tech detecting parts from BTEC.
Meaning nothing's stopping people from taking stuff out of the store anymore.
Dash it all. I knew I forgot something. More dong subs. Where I think we're at over a hundred.
What did you say those skin bodies were doing? They're pinching my shaving cream. Thank you so
much Jerma's average dong. Hundred dongs. Too many dongs. Thanks Bosco.
Please don't ban me. I'm not gonna ban you.
Oh it's knackered. Ketchup, mustard, and purple stuff. As vaguely referred to on TV.
Too many dongs too little time. All right shaving cream. Is this it? Whipped liverwurst. Absolutely
not. Whipped liverwurst? That's fucking gross. So yeah I can take the shaving cream. I could use a
shave. I'll say your five o'clock shadow goes clear to your ankles. Pig, dog, pig dog. The
skin bodies rule the streets. Why are they shooting the gun in here? The little did it again after
him. I mean. They just. All right that was insane. Speaking of insane. We had 10 more coming right
there. Holy shit. Let's do some shopping. Great. Did I put the volume too low? You crack me up
little buddy. I think that's all right. We gotta chase down those hairless rats. Oh wait what about
buying things? It's for your vacation. Oh I appreciate that. Hey Bosco. This was in the rat movie. We've got skin
bodies to chase Sam. Wait wait what? No. Hey Bosco. The law enforcement here in the states
really is pathetic. We've got. I can't. I have to go. Is that them? All right well their car probably
is very very slow. I get in my car. What can I just grab them when they drive by? Where are we going
Sam? Extra dongs. 10 more dongs. After those rats. It's not an average dong anymore. It's it's too
it's too big. No I just said that. No but listen. It's a lot of money. I just hope that you're
financially able to. How do those rapidly small wheels move so fast? That's too many dongs.
The skin buddy. Try to drive him into something.
That was a bad grandpa Simpson but it's very loud. Okay hold on tight little buddy.
That's a good that was a pretty good take on that one. All right so what the hell why
what's what's the deal with that? Can I now go back in here? They rule these streets.
Took care of your rat problem now sir. Sell me some cheese.
We want to buy something. Yes quite so quite so. What have you got? Well just between us I have a
most peculiar device. Is this going to be another tear gas? What peculiar device are you so eager to
pawn off on us this time? It's the latest in Bosco tech innovation. A delightful invention I like to
call a chemical based voice modulator. Voice modulator? What's that? I do believe it's
self-explanatory. We don't really have time to explain it to ourselves. Why don't you just
explain it to us? Well it alters the frequency of your voice molecules. Very useful very useful.
Can we just have it or is it 10 grand? We'd like that. Is everything 10 grand in this game?
That will be 30 shillings. Yeah I left our shillings in my other pants. How much in dollars?
Let's see here 30 shillings would be about one million American dollars. A million dollars? No
way are we giving out that many tickets. I think we'll have to find an entirely new revenue stream
if we want that voice modulator. Worth every shilling trust me trust me. Okay so no let's
do that again. We'd like that. That will be. We'll be back later once we find out. Now we need to
become millionaires. Nothing for us. What does this do? Hands in the air Bosco. You're coming with
us. Good heavens. We're taking you in for masquerading as a man of class and distinction.
What the devil? Surely you jest. Yes surely we do. On the bright side now you can add the police to
your long list of paranoia induced nightmare subjects. Piss off. See you later Bosco. Thanks
Bosco. Hello sir. There's another option? We want to buy something. Oh is it different this time?
Do you have any complimentary fresh garlic? No. Do you have any fine leather jackets?
No. It's different every time. Do you have any gumballs the size of your head? No. Do you have
any plus two plate armor of limitless squeeze ability? No. Do you have any pes dispensers with
the head of infamous Mexican revolutionary Pancho Villa? No. Do you have any ketchup? No. Oh wait.
Got you. Blast. Drank. Dash it all. Can I have it? Nothing for us right. Let's go back the other way.
How's the uh the psychoanalyst doing? Thanks Bosco. Bombs? Rope? Lamboil? It's all yours friend
as long as you have enough rupees. That's an old one. Isn't it beautiful? Garden. Those are old.
That's seriously one of my first experiences with memology. You know what I mean? Sam, Max,
how nice to see you. I don't suppose you have any candid photos of little green men feeling
frisky do you? What? What? It's my new career. I'm a tabloid publisher specializing in the thoughtful
analysis of groundbreaking news of interest to myself and others like me. What's it called?
She's going to change careers every episode. So you're a publisher now? What happened to
psychotherapy? I've always had a fascination with the suppressed and the sensual and for telling
people too much about both. Publishing the alien love triangle times is a logical extension of
all my previous careers except maybe Vatican spokesperson. You don't do psychotherapy anymore.
Are you doing any psychotherapy on the side? Only on space aliens. I guess that narrows your clientele
quite a bit. No not really. What was it you said about a photo? My new tabloid the alien love
triangle times needs a cover photo of an extraterrestrial biological entity or alien
as the unwashed masses calls them caught getting cozy with some of the locals.
Sybil I'd like the record to show that although I support you as a friend your latest project
makes my skin decidedly crawly. Me too. I like that tie. I like that tie. I want this tie as a shirt.
I'd wear it. Psychoanalyze me again. Quick analysis for old times sake. Oh all right think of a number
between one and four. Two. Two. You're selectively audio-averse. I don't like the sound of that.
All right what about what do you need? So you're looking for a cover photo of little green men
canoodling right? Yeah though I'm kind of desperate at this point. Basically I can use anything as
long as there are three beings in the shot and at least one of them's an alien. It is the alien
love triangle times after all. So I need three people in a picture and one's gonna be an alien.
There's nothing like good hard-nosed journalism. You said it it's time to find out the real answers
to the real questions. Like what did those poor cattle do to deserve that? No what do aliens do
for romance? Do they love? How do they get their otherworldly thrills? By playing slots in Keno?
That'd explain why they're always seen in Nevada. No you got me woke up. He said fuck Keno. Keno
sucks. Have you learned anything interesting since you started this uh magazine? I learned why Elvis
had such an otherworldly voice. Elvis was not an alien. Sure he was. He just wore makeup to cover
his emerald green skin. Frankly Sybil, this project is disturbing as well as distressingly
intimate. Like seeing Stephen King getting a hot butter massage. Is that the first thing you've
written on stream? Who else is an alien? Is anybody else an alien that we might not know about? Dr.
Phil. Well that goes without saying. I can see that. That makes sense. Dr. Phil really does come
off as the kind of guy that after the show. And that's the whole thing. See you next time
when we analyze someone else. Get out of here. Get out of here. You're a you're a dumb idiot.
Get out of here. And he goes backstage and like his skin just fucking falls off of him. He like
gets in a bath. An alien bath. I can see it. In fact if I had to name you like 10 people that I
think might be an alien. Dr. Phil would be in number eight. I think. This is they knew what
they were doing. What's in an alien bath? It's a regular bath except there's an alien in it this
time. And they add like other like spices in it and shit. We'll be back. Keep watching the supplies.
There's like the coriander and like cumin and fucking like cilantro. Now let's look at some of
this stuff. She's got a story here about two hygienists from Walla Walla and an amorphous
saturnian slime mold. There's like oregano in it. Is that the one where they walk into a bar? Tabasco
sauce and shit. They put like all kinds of weird stuff in it. That's not even weird. That stuff's
like good. What am I talking about? A mima graph. I love cilantro. Yeah I do. It's so good.
Okay so we need a picture. What's my mayonnaise? Nothing useful in here.
This is not the exit. God damn it. I do it every time.
Nice cactus. Saguaro. Vinyl. Hey if you dip that in ink you could do 30 tattoos at once.
Cilantro just tastes like I'm eating grass and chemicals. Yeah only us aliens know what it tastes.
You have to be an alien to like cilantro. It's kind of weird because cilantro,
the way cilantro smells, I don't want it near me. It's kind of like the way that I think a mosquito
feels when you have off on your body. If cilantro comes near me I'm like no get that away. I don't
want it. I don't want to near me but I like it. I like the way it tastes. No there's actually new
gumballs in here. Looks like candy but I'm pretty sure it's fish tank gravel again. I've had worse.
Yeah cilantro smells like a mosquito feels when they're approaching somebody with off on their
body. You know you can just sense something that something's wrong and you just don't want to be
near it. There is people repellent. Off. OFF. Off. You don't know what off is. Off. The spray. The
mosquito spray. You put it all over your body. Off. OFF. It's the number one name brand mosquito
repellent in the world probably. You don't use raid on your body. You use off. Off and cilantro
smell the same. Are you trying to tell us you don't like this? No don't use raid. Raid. Money.
All right what am I doing? I need a picture. Can I go anywhere to get this? Okay picture. I need a
photo. A photo of aliens. There was another place over here that I didn't get to see before. Zoomers
don't use bug spray. What do you mean? What do you do? What do you do instead of bug spray?
Light a couple of candles? Where are we going Sam? The tv studio. Goodie. You guys do cilantro
candles? No what's it called? What's this? It's got a certain name. Cilantro candles. They're all the
same thing. They smell the same. Um citronello. Cilantro. Citrus cilantro. Well here we are Max.
The tv station with programs too old to be contemporary, too new to be retro, but consistently
derivative enough to be popular. W-A-R-P. Television's so mindless you can't help but
watch. I thought citronello was citrus. No it's cilantro. Mysteriously so. Well let's find this
Myra character and smack some good old-fashioned. Cilantro salmonella. Smack it into her or smack it
out of her just so long as there's smacking involved. You crack me up little buddy.
Citrine candles burn into plasma. Don't do that. Be careful.
Need a broom little buddy? I don't use brooms Sam. I necessitate the use of them. Director's chair.
Let me sit in that see how it feels. It's got a falling star. Twinkle twinkle little star.
Feels pretty good. Howl crashing burn. Uh yeah. No no don't make don't make me do it. Don't make me do it.
No. All right I died. I got it. I'm fine. Stand aside casually a tired stagehand.
We're Sam and Max. Freelance police. Fight it. Fight it. We've come to save sympathetic hostages from the
clutches of. Okay I'm gonna stop you right there. Number one I'm not a stagehand. I am the director.
The director. Number two we're no longer holding the auditions for animal cops with crippling
mental disabilities and a lust for dance. The director. We're not actors. You got that right.
I don't think I've ever seen worse acting in my entire life and yes I have seen Keanu Reeves
performance in Toast the musical. Sam I think my hypersensitive ego may need stroking. Don't look
at me. Next? Who's next? Uh we're the police. You don't seem to understand. We're highly untrained
police officers. Look hats off for dedication guys but I'm just not buying the police act.
I feel so invalidated. Where is it? We're looking for Myra Stump. Myra Stump. Do not mention that
name in my presence. Which name Myra or Stump? Either and or both. What's your beef with Myra?
Let's just say Myra and I have creative differences. I'm creative and she isn't.
I'm sorry what was your question? Um why don't you like you Myra? Why the hate? Look Myra runs her show
her way and I run every other show my way. If she doesn't want me on her set I could care less.
You mean you couldn't care less. If you could care less then you do care some which doesn't really.
No I was right. I could care less because I care even less about what you're saying right now.
Oh go ahead knucklehead. Knucklehead? What are you doing here anyhow? What am I doing here? I'm
holding auditions for Midtown Cowboys. What are you doing here? Midtown Cowboys? The critically
panned but publicly adored sitcom about two cattle ranchers trying to make it in Midtown Manhattan?
Yes well summarized. You're hiring extras? No I'm hiring the stars. The two main characters went on
Myra a couple days ago and I haven't heard from them since. I need replacements ASAP.
Right here. If we could pass one lousy audition sitcom stardom will finally be ours. Rocketing
to fame for the most insubstantial of reasons. That truly is the American dream.
Would you like to audition please? Would you like to apply for that instant stardom you promised?
You want to audition? Well if there were anybody else here I'd tell you to forget it but okay.
All right what do we do? I'm going to have you play a scene from old Geller.
Tell me you've seen it. I'm not into horror movies. It's a classic boy gets a dog. I forgot
to tell you guys this. Boy shoots dog. All right all right all right. I want you to play the boy.
Yes boy that is so me. And Sam you play the dog. Oh okay Sam. This is a dentist story. I need you
to act like you've got full-blown rabies understand. What's my motivation? You're a bad
dog. Now show me rabbit. Um no dig deep. You should be just frothing mad.
Sorry I'm not hiring a dog who can't even do a simple rapidity scene. I don't know. I was feeling
rabid. You look pretty disease ridden to me. Come back after you've taken a few thousand acting.
I was acting rabid. All right well listen hold on this is important anyways.
So uh I'm at the dentist today right. Sit down. We're going over some stuff. I do some x-rays and
I'm lying blind back and they have a a tv on the wall. Some dentists do this now. They have
you know like monitors all in each room. So I'm sitting there and there's Netflix on it.
And oh okay cool. This is very this is actually a pretty cool idea. You just have can have like tv
there. Like that's fucking ridiculous. That's really really awesome. So the dentist is just
like hey man like yeah while you waiting while you're chilling around while you while we're
doing some stuff you know you can uh just just browse and put on whatever you want.
I'm like okay cool. And you know how you can see like what people have seen already on Netflix
and the queue of stuff that has already been watched. One of the last things that was on
was a bunch of horror movies like Friday the 13th like Freddy. Why the fuck would you ever watch
Friday the 13th when you were getting dental work? That's that's terrifying.
It was like at least two or three fucking messed up horror movies. I'm just sitting there going
imagine lying there and watching like Jason tear somebody in half with like a chainsaw while
there's a guy in your mouth like with dentist tools. And I don't know if anybody else is like
this but I have this weird thing where I don't want anyone to know the things that I want to
watch on tv. Is that weird? I hovered over a show about wine and I didn't want to put it on
because it was like a wine documentary and I just felt like people are gonna judge my taste or
something. I'm trying to think of what's the most normal background thing I could possibly put on.
I'm scrolling through you've got home fiction and then sell it but I'm like that's too normal.
That's like too weird. Why would I watch that show? I'm like oh how about like a food show?
Ah those are those are really easy. Just put on like a food documentary about like sushi
but I why would I watch that while I'm getting my like teeth like looked at? No. I could it was
freaking me out. I'm just sitting in the chair. I don't know what to put on and then I scrolled
over like animation. Like what's like is the animated show? No like what if I put on like a
kid show? I don't want to put on like a kid show. Why are you watching like a kid show?
Why are you what are you weird? No no I just I don't know what to put on. Maybe that is why
people put on horror movies. Seriously I was I it was it was crazy but yeah the last thing
that somebody watched they were trying to get on friday the 13th how it's made but and what okay
what and then I was thinking how funny it would be if I did if I put on like a dentist documentary
I'm trying to think of what that'd be funny these are the dentist is like oh yeah go and put on
whatever you want and I put on like a dentist thing like a dentist show would that be weird
would they think it was fucking crazy like oh like tooth exam but go to like the app and just type
in like tooth examinations to see if there's like a tooth exam mini series what's it what is a
fucking dentist show there is no dentist show I'm just that's a whole nother question first of all
there's a ton of doctor shows house uh nip tuck you got er where are the dentist shows
why is there no big dentist drama there should be
Sweeney Todd was a dentist no he was a shaver hello again yes can we take another crack at
that audition but no I thought it was funny that let's take it from the top somebody decided to
put on a horror movie while they were getting their teeth worked on cut quit stalling and act
oh and she said I could be anymore she said the word rabbit so I clicked on the rabbit I heard
rabbit hello again yes can we take another crack at that audition fine let's take it from the top
ready sam show me rabbit show me rabbit okay cut rabbit I said what do you want me to do
I don't have to click on myself user no hello again I'm just I probably need an item fine let's
take it rabbit how diseased thank you thank you first off I'd like to thank all the little people
okay max just realized your dog is walking down and you'll have to put him down
oh my god really you're sad you're despondent your grief now
I've seen myra show more emotion and she ought to be declared a national
botox reserve grief I said give me grief grief come on oh shit oh cry perfect now the fateful
moment has arrived despite your immense grief you must put your beloved companion out of his
misery okay idiot what demonic force possessed you to do that the demonic force called acting sam
you should try it sometime good thing I had my anti-hypnosis helmet built into my hat
or I'd have one too many holes in the head brother bravo such realism such authenticity
I was convinced you were actually shooting him how did you do the sound effects
you don't want to know head to the set next door and we can begin filming immediately
let's hurry sam we only have 14 minutes and 55 seconds of fame left scaffold scaffold hey even
the scaffold is just a prop scaffold from that show about the tv crew that solves crimes around
the scaffold is here advanced forensics and overly dramatic reenactments come on
whoever heard of a crime at a tv station i'm getting pretty good at it the barrel haven
from whence comes this story from whence from whence clearly from a work of unparalleled
artistic vision and emotional expressiveness no wonder I haven't seen it once used for apples
now used for derrires sitcom from midtown cowboys midtown cowboys that away
all right people let's get the stage set up celebrity hosts will be here any minute
oh right audible boredom no I'm just fucking hanging up I'm not bored I'm not really not
this is actually fun I'm not bored I'm not bored weren't you just I think she just defied the
laws of physics sorry you'd be amazed how many times a day I have to do that things tend to be
hectic here doesn't bother us a bit sam and max consummate professional actors reporting for duty
you said duty sam I knew you guys were right for this show speaking of which could you perhaps
explain the show a bit okay here's the drill on midtown cowboy you play a pair of cattle ranchers
trying to raise a herd in an apartment in manhattan my uncle Ernie did that except it was pigs and not
in an apartment I only see one cow it's a small herd you're struggling okay okay all right you've
got this landlord mr federally who has a very strict no cows policy devilishly inconvenient
I begin to see from whence the hilarity sprouts yes federally is always barging in and you try
to hide the fact that you have a cow in the apartment lots of side gags usually something
gross winds up happening simple enough great where's the script well there's a slight hitch
the cow ate most of the script so you're going to have to ad-lib the show perfect
ad-lib go to doing that yes make it up as you go improvise I can do that yes our regular life
has given us plenty of practice don't worry you'll be working with philo pennyworth who plays
federally he's a brilliant actor classically trained globe theater and all that just set
him up to do something funny and he'll handle it from there check anything else actually yes
we did save one line from the script and it's really important to work it in because it's the
product placement that pays for the whole show one of you will have to save the line
me me pick me all right max your line is this better get the serious toothpaste oh you're
gonna go to jail i like it already what's mac what what's this show about again there's a lot to
learn with this tv business give me the lowdown on midtown cowboys is about two cattle ranchers
raising a herd in a manhattan apartment that has a strict no cows policy no cows your basic visual
hijinks and occasional grows out humor and sue as they concoct elaborate ruses to keep their cow
hidden from their landlord mr federally all right and max's line is better get better get the serious
toothpaste yeah let's go we're as ready as we're ever gonna be let's start taping the show okay
now remember your landlord's at the door and you don't want him to know you've got a cow in the
house hey what's up and i'll talk me into them doing it
hey bossy hey bossy hey i don't care if it is just a problem
i know you're hiding a cow that somebody has to hide the cow though hey bossy
if you're not even going to try to disguise the cow
cut amateurs let's get the set back the way it was i didn't hide the cow yeah well how am i
supposed to hide the cow with a couch there's like poo on the ground books television how
convenient and if the show they're watching is the show of themselves watching the universe could
fold in when i click on the cow it just goes hey bossy let's leave it turned off then okay cactus
window embarrassing idol door tv cam what's embarrassing idol door hi mom i think they put
a drape on it or something what's in here just don't see how you can sing and be a judge i don't
like the public what's embarrassing idol hey sam do my eyes deceive me or are those our formerly
hypnotized former child star acquaintances the soda poppers just leave the set sweet jellyfish
paste on a stick you're right what are the odds could we find another judge what about
one of those guys i don't suppose either of you would be interested in being a judge an
embarrassing idol can you hear me i promise i'll be completely unbiased in my abuse of the
contestants fine fine take a seat goody i get to sing welcome back to embarrassing idol the judges
are chomping at the bit so say hello to our first contestant peepers is there something you drop
into a shark and can i well that was a bit sloppy but i particularly like how you hit that high note
that always impresses me i think you'll get my vote i'm definitely voting for you after all you
are my brother very impressive you sound almost exactly like a sick cat being dragged through rusty
farm machine he was just dreadful this is a singing contest so i think i'll have to vote for
someone else um is there anyone else not so far yay um what about me with the pool of water it's
acid brain freeze don't you ever watch the show hey can i try my pipes out on this thing go right
ahead frankly we can use all the contestants we can muster thank you ladies and gentlemen please
welcome our next contestant sam hello i'd like to do a little no no
busted down hound dog blues love has a thorny backside bottleneck on the freeway of doom
just like someone else's song only somehow better bottleneck on the freeway of doom bottleneck on the
freeway of doom i am in a terrible torment i'm unbelievably happy i'm cryptic and therefore
deep i am more successful than you jump in on a crunchy silver spoon my girl is the greatest
thing since sliced bread my girl's cheating on me i solved life's greatest mystery but i'm not
telling i'm cooler and hipper than you will ever be she's at brunch today with some baboons
uh pity me admire me let me remind you that i write songs i will say anything to make it rhyme
oh and like a zephyr on again and let's hear from our judges bravo your wobbly tenor is way better
than peepers shrill squawking your stylings are quite interesting but i noticed you never really
hit a high note keepers is still getting my vote it's like your best friend you sing beautifully
and your lyrics are enchanting but peepers is my brother so i pretty much have to vote for him
oh what remember folks on embarrassing idol the decision of the judges must be unanimous
stay tuned for more exciting action after this so you're always going to vote for your brother
and we're it's okay to sing again if you want to by the way um so i have to hit a high note
ladies and gentlemen okay just like feathers in fear busted down dog blues
just like someone else's song only somehow better
hey it's me your brother that's it shiny like a new my life it's me your brother
thinking about the rings on the great racket i think i'm gonna have to do like helium or something
road to someday bits of me are true and let's hear from our judge i admire your courage even
more than your singing thanks little nice but i'd like to see some technical proficiency
no he's my brother so i have to vote for him do this professional excuse me mr simpson you
gotta get out of here you can't be in that aisle there's no way i'm voting for anyone
okay i can see that remember folks you have to stop talking during the movie
stay tuned for more exciting action oh rick rick rick hey peepers well peepers you underdeveloped
former non-psychotherapist you what a treat to run across you again i'm not sure if i ever
properly thank you for hitting me over played repeatedly virtual regality no gratitude necessary
way too tired to even turn it on in the first place it was the worst stream of 2019
how do you hit those high notes managed to hit those eardrum scarring high notes
if you're implying that i use any artificial vocal enhancements i doubt what you hear is pure
peepers that's almost exactly what i would have said the stream was fine that i had a lot of fun
on that stream that was a minecraft stream that was great but going into that vr going into
rick and morty virtual regality brought down like eight letter grades and as you know there's only
five potential letter grades you can get before an f a b down to c down to d down to f well a
counts as one i guess a b c d f and it was three under f at that point i'm dying to know is there
any truth to the rumors about lip syncing on the old show we only get that on the released version
that clip is going to be able now i will be a lot that clip will be around until i am dead
you know what i mean think about that your lyrics have an intriguingly
vapid quality did you write them yourself of course any similarity to lyrics or other wildly
popular songs is meant as homage not fast the qrs clip is will exist forever i did
unless the internet turns off it's worming its way into the stream every five minutes
really is there any trick to hitting the high notes like it's gonna outlast me i told you i
don't use any artificial vocal enhancement and i resent the implication i have a gift that's all
liar i'll leave you to whatever good luck i can smell the live breath it stinks can i look at these
sure take them i've got them memorized am i blue who are you can i fly very impressive
oh so we're going to change the lyrics is what we're saying here is that your mug
no it was here when i got here last week
once used for apples
hey hey mr paper so can you tell me how do i can talk to you
tell me old judge what gruesome qualities do you look for in a singing performance fraternity i'm
voting for papers no matter what he's my brother the one who didn't forget my birthday today i
might well there you go i said i was sorry oh birthday hey happy birthday birthday thanks i'm
glad somebody remembered i said i was sorry what more do you want a dream would be nice isn't this
also saint boniface day patron saint of carnivorous plants and spiky things i think
that's next week get him okay so i need to make my voice high and get him a present enjoy your
judging catch you later carl weiser oh jimmy coral i don't think that's gonna work i'm close
i'm close real close tonight on a few of these if i worked on them a little it's the first time
i've ever tried that all right um what do i have here i do the lyrics can i just like put his
head back and say hey whipped cream and just put the shaving cream in his mouth he's too stupid to
know okay i need i don't think i can do this yet let's get out of here but what about the cow thing
i don't have any money i need a million dollars to make my voice change um i'm trying with the cow
again where are we going sam the tv studio goody goody just become a millionaire uh marine are you
is this an alien remember those are socks oh what oh god i get it never make that noise again
is this one okay let's have another go at that scene shall we okay now remember your landlord's
at the door and you don't want him to know you've got a cow in there ready all right hide the cow
punch the wall down let's get you some sprucing up whatever happened to our cannons
i refuse to answer a spray paint oh that's not spray paint it's a plate i know you're
left this lying here okay i got a plate hey can i move uh open up hide a cow
hey open up in there i know you're hiding a cow hey that's not a cow that's our great aunt tilly
aha well well what's your guess boys that's uh there it is i told you
you this is my octogenarian uncle a retired chimney sweep from low in nebraska now he travels
the world chasing cyclones in a mobile home well it's a pleasure to meet you sir i'm something
of a twister buff myself since i saw the wizard of awe when i was a boy this is every show on
nickelodeon every like live action show on nickelodeon i think i saw this on nickelodeon
like 10 years ago so i did it i win gotta get the serious toothpaste wait uh hold on
but why do i have to say that all right comedy gag put shit on the plate and then
give it to him and say that it's food or something say what's this i'm sorry what was that you said
um why is it but why did i meow moon moon moon moot moot moon he said moon as in the cow jumped
over thee i mean please try to remember that your characters are attempting to hide look all right
so i got i got so far i got it please you're attempting to hide the cow not make me eat
shit off of a plate you fuck ready action wait that is gross humor that's disgusting
didn't you say i want you to do something disgusting let there be light oh shit okay
there we go i know uh well well well this is the french chef we hired to satisfy our inexplicable
insatiable craving for omelets and duck and broadsley i like mine extra crispy
a french chef eh i love french bread i'm not skipping i'm not pressing anything
i went to gay curry one time myself you know it was back in my army day goodness who left this
lying here plate on the ship and then put shaving cream on it and pretend it's whipped cream
is this actually what i'm supposed to do is make it like a shit pie for him to eat
say what's this i'm sorry what was that you said moot it's a french tone poem
move a delicious food it's a french tone poem either one of these right the food he said move
it's a french dish the chef is just me
i'll try some of that where's the plate so it actually is feed this person shit
this is not like like nickelodeon funny anymore they don't like feed each other
shit and nickelodeon there's a familiar flavor fennel maybe kentucky bluegrass i think
i think this moo moo whatever stuff is really good what's it called in english
chow pie really well that's funny it sounds just like hogchamp hogchamp
now better get the serious toothpaste
network's actually gonna shut it down i'll be in my dressing room and your show is gonna be
cancelled because nobody can air somebody eating shit on tv just to let you know nice work you guys
here's a clip for your reel thanks let's get the set back the way it was it was plastic doesn't
matter disgusting revolting want nothing to do with it disgusting okay so here's this is
how these yeah clip it this is how they used to clip stuff back then all right so i got my real
so where's my money midtown convoy where's my money hello again hi cooking show where's my
fucking money cooking without looking get his lard that's enough lard to clog the arteries of
a major metropolis or start a circus of greece squirrels i rue the day you lost your nea funding
max bridge pot pan plate all right it's just a good side that should be easy what's the story
with this show how are you always everywhere before us alien how do you keep it so clean in
here what's the story with this what's the story with this show cooking without looking it's a
cooking show aimed at motorhead bachelors who have never seen the inside of a grocery store
is there a big demand for that you'd be amazed uh where's the host where's the host is he in
watching the myra show no he's one of the few who isn't he got food poisoning while he was taping
last week's show right in the middle in fact was it gruesome yes and unfortunately this show goes
out live live how do you keep it so clean in here the complete absence of anything resembling food
is helpful aren't there fruits or vegetables of any sort around here just the crew i never get
tired of that one okay actually no we strive for realism and the average bachelor kitchen doesn't
contain any natural plant life except mold tell me this then lady how do you do that
teleportation trick where you're always everywhere ahead of us trade secret honey
this one can we get a tape of the show this one no it's broadcast live we don't tape it
see ya probably welcome to cooking without looking the cooking show for the typical
bachelor kitchen containing no fruits vegetables or healthy ingredients of any sort
uranium where we take a random assortment of condiments and barely edible items
and create a meal within minutes filling in for chuck flagin this week these guys
just go with it oh hello welcome to the show thanks sam it's great to be here not you bucket
head the audience oh greetings worshipal fans remember the only reason i'm on tv is because
i'm better than you we've got some furious cooking to do so let's get right to it all
right what are we making sam casserole a cake let's visit our rack of ingredients
fucking pumped up right now i gotta slow i gotta calm down i'm fucking hyped up max let's leave
the cooking to me and the eating to you how do you make a cake none of this makes cake
well hard large skimp on the lard that's right if you take the lard out of lard ass all you have is
ass well said max um asbestos sulfuric acid sulfuric acid sparingly easily overwhelm the
other ingredients and your taste buds and your asbestos sulfuric acid and lard of course who could
forget the asbestos sprinkles this is a cake you're not getting somebody on your birthday
real kitchens use it too uh and red dye too they look pretty red dye number two
if there's not at least some possibility of malignant tumors it's not real bachelor cooking
and then cook it now do we broil it sam right you are little buddy into the oven it goes
and through the magic of tv cooking show time one gorgeous delicious cake ready to be binged
upon or shared amongst friends oh boy let's take it with us why is it red it's why is it green
it should be red welcome once again without looking the show ends whatsoever and still
make some food poison thank you and welcome what are we making this today we're gonna make
chilled summer foie gras soup with goat yogurt a bunch of gunk in a dish we'll just get some
ingredients from the ingredient rack and add it to what we professionals call the yummying hot
isn't that a pot max we both know a pot is what you and i fight over when we play poker
this is the only all right this is just gonna be hair gel of course you're going to want a
few dashes of hair gel don't worry bachelors as long as you use it only for cooking no one
will think you less of a man you go to a fine french restaurant you order foie gras
it's got a bunch of sides and this motherfucker comes out with a plate of hair gel we've already
got that thing we made before no i ate it while you were looking at the ingredients
now do we broil it sam wait what you are little buddy and through the magic of tv cooking show
time tada you've successfully perverted the laws of god and man oh boy let's take it with us
oh fuck he ate the other one welcome once again to yance what food put thank you and what are we
making today we're i'm pretty max let's leave the cook what was it uh it was uranium pellets
they also go great in chex mix uh sulfuric acid use the sulfuric acid sparingly it can easily
it can easily go and your and then red lard gum skimp on the that's right well said max
and then red make sure to encode it we've already got that thing we made before
no i ate it while you now do we get right hand through the one gourd oh boy look just bad editing
that's quite an assortment they must have scoured every toxic waste dump in the state
all right dangerous tools can i no this fridge isn't even a fridge it's a fake
all right so i got the cake let's go get approval right sitcom door we did the sitcom which we got
a tape for that we got the cake for the dude i need the million dollars you want to drink that
lard bucket no you don't you just i don't think you do you don't think i mean you i don't know
if you know what that's like but as somebody that has done it before no you don't want to do that
why would i why we mean what i got dead i got dead to do in college it was like fucking 20 bucks
and i was like yeah i was like fucking a dare yeah hey peepers what do you want no wrong person
i'll leave you good luck i brought you something i brought you a cake wizard how about some cake
cake oh boy perfect for my birthday there's no tomatoes in it right nope nope
so now he's gonna like me that was delicious and a little bit scary you eat like max
so now we're friends enjoy your judging uh-huh i need a million bucks a million bucks hi hi well
you got is there any other this midtown cowboys is there any other thing to do here
i missed a door okay door door okay is it in this game show door well that's okay that would
confuse me because that's where the chicken came from i thought it was a prop door who's never
going to be a millionaire look max there's the door to my reset let's get in there and liberate
her literally captive audience sam forget the hostages there's somebody famous it's hue bliss
who bliss no hue bliss inventor of prismatology help millions unlock the power of their personal
color spectrums right the stage magician turned happiness guru i like that i didn't have enough
of those already i'd love that i'm gonna meet him fine but if he magically pulls another rainbow
butterfly out of somebody's ear i'm leaving hi hue bliss hi i'm hue bliss yeah we know and you
are somebody just as a candy corn tie how do you know do you believe in magic because i do
that looks i it looks good it looks cool it's a sunset time get it right
so you bliss what brings you to warp i too am here to meet myra how do you know we came for myra
oh don't you see i can read your mind that's a little weird but i'm doubting thomas of this
crime fighting duo i consider it my civic duty to say prove it okay think of something anything
six million three hundred and seventy three thousand four hundred eleven point nine eight point eight
fuck yourself lucky guess was it think of something else
hue bliss is a big fat charlatan was he right well we found the alien everyone thinks that oh
found the alien pennies on the eyes of a dead mime well i must have been silently mouthing the
words really think of something else enough of this ridiculous farce stop it do me do me
oh oh my and that's unspeakably depraved yeah you got it wow you're amazing say you bliss can
we get a picture with you for our scrapbook of instantly forgettable memories splendid idea
i wish i'd thought of it oh and in fact i did hence the camera now gather round
but how will you take the picture by magic okay say chocolate covered puppies what chocolate
covered puppies how would you do that the picture magic man oh my i seem to have misplaced it
hmm check your pockets maybe i left it there
i hate this guy what's your business with myra i'm to be a guest on her show silly
yeah silly i'm spreading the word about my new book in medics the handbook for multicolored
happiness take a copy when you leave can you just give us the 10 word summary instead i'm gonna
read it we're on a pretty tight schedule 10 words oh my how about prismatology is the
answer unicorns are pretty and rainbows too that's 10 prismatology what's the story on this
prismatology this guy into the sun prismatology is only the greatest intellectual emotional and
spiritual revolution ever to grace this fair planet thank goodness we have someone who can
get an impartial assessment tell us more that's a 10 join prismatology today and you too can
experience the magic of true bliss that goes against everything i've ever hoped for and yet
now i'm strangely attracted to the notion snap out of it little buddy we've got a case to solve
dazzle us with a feat of ledger domain why don't you okay i'll show you the magic of
prismatology in action pick a color any color ochre ochre no move sand three uh how about a
color i've heard of hmm pick a color as long as it's red green or blue do blue hue
oh no now we take the photo i know what you're thinking green alien photo or is it illusion
i challenge you to change colors again okay pick a color any color it's not easy being green
oh but it is with magic how about another picture you bless how about this instead of a new picture
we'll just recycle the old one save the earth alien sure whatever gather round got him exposed
ladies and gentlemen we got them right remember that one sorry to interrupt your little joy fest
but i've got a situation here never fear pretty lady hue bliss is here yeah anyway i got a video
before and he still hasn't come out think he could fill in till he gets back can a butterfly fly
yes it can oh what do i do when a contestant comes to the podium just read him a question
from the car then when he gets it wrong insult him and tell him to get off the stage oh no no
prismatology teaches us to love everyone no matter right just read the cards okay
they still love 12 months late i'm doing i'm doing an ironic bit about how like if everyone
knows that and everyone's done in a bunch of videos and stuff it's ironic it's irony you guys
wouldn't know irony only thing you know about irony is ironing your clothes in the morning or
something that's where i'd stand if i were the host which i'm not we've got a contestant people
hit it from somewhere deep within the bowels of warp is who's never going to be a millionaire
with special guest host hue bliss hi i'm hue bliss our first contestants are a pair of professional
freelance police officers they enjoy firing their guns randomly and running over things
please welcome sam and max still says episode one oh shit you're right change it listen sam
they love us welcome you know the rules if you can answer he's still green
because my brain's stuffed with enough worthless trivia to power a small chilean village for
decades it's true okay are you ready why is he still green oh happy day it's an easy one
this is to answer one question right if a man sets out from the horse head nebula in a spaceship
traveling at thrice the speed of light and his father leaves from rigel two at the same time
going half the speed how many nanoseconds will it be before time paradox causes the first man never
to have been born hey no idea no chance no hope no hope i'm not sure but i'll say
balls that's not really a valid answer you lose this is an outrage i demand a recount we do have
a fabulous consolation prize a copy of emetics by me hue bliss no thanks i'm content to leave
with just my burning shame and newfound sense of inadequacy okay find out which poor schmuck
will be the next to blow his chance at millions right after these messages okay so give me your
book i think now's the time to go in go in from the jungle he just blew his three go in go in go
in good now now now now now now now now now good nice job he's got blue hi i'm hue bliss
um give me can i have his bye emetics life troubling your digestion reality blocking your
passages expel your troubles with emetics the handbook for multicolored happiness
already got a copy i read it every morning on the can multicolored happiness and you got one
i bet you guys are gonna like that one okay so i can't i have i could probably go back
bye can i go in here it's polite to knock you do know we're taping a show here great day in the
morning it's myra stump herself yourself release the hostages can we come in are you feeling okay
your eyes look a little spirally are you feeling all right of course i am sweetheart by the way
when was the last time you brushed your teeth and you should really be flossing you certainly
sound like your normal self but why are you keeping everybody in there i'm just doing what
i always do slave and toil to put on the best show possible it's just after opening presents
from well wishes i felt so compelled to make this show extra special don't be alarmed but i'm
beginning to suspect that you might be hypnotized don't be silly hypnotism is just an excuse people
use today to abdicate responsibility i hate how this country's become a bushel of bill and betty
brainwash ease hypnotized or not that sounds like myra's patented blend of lovingly cutting
criticism and oh my god buddy wait what is that from how about letting your hostages go now what
do you say hostages they're my guests you know if there's one that fries my burger it's the rampant
victim culture in american media today oh boohoo myra's audience all got luxury mini fans
now they have to worry about where they're going to park i know what you mean myra it's like i'm
always telling people don't think of it as a bullet wound think of it as a transfusion opportunity
we go in can we come in and see the show can you don't you mean may we come in and see the show
that's much better no we're at full capacity the only people getting in now are famous people who
are appearing on the show can i can we be guests on your show can may we appear as guests on your
show i excel at talking about myself are you famous perhaps in an internet petition or there
ought to be a law kind of way not good enough i'll need evidence of your explosive star power
i blew up a public restroom last week i want to see a copy of your recording contract for one
thing well what if we recording contract and a clip from your tv show you're not anybody these
days if you don't act and sing recording contract tv clip got one of them piece of cake no cake i'm
on a diet but i will naturally need evidence of the latest juicy scandal you've been involved in
we have to be scandalized of course what kind of show do you think this is are you sure you
want us to answer that look it's very simple show me a recording contract a clip from your tv show
and some evidence of a scandal and i'll squeeze your hands okay well i got that all we're almost
there as it happens we brought a clip of our wacky hit sitcom midtown do the uh we're the
stars singing and that's it well i'm certainly impressed with how far standards for entertainment
have fallen in this country um thanks but you're also going to need a recording contract and a nice
juicy scandal oops all right see where i'm gonna go get my autograph book it's too nice to stay
indoors you boys should go play outside and you should stop making that face dear it'll stick
if you're not careful so max has been around for a long time i just never really thought to care
about it uh scandal i got the picture um really game show question apparently warp can't afford
armed guards for their game show questions that's cheating sam good thinking don't get
your pretty long ears on a twist little buddy the answers aren't on here i mean in life there are
no answers only questions another prismatology credo no i read that in a cereal box i'm seriously
deficient in riboflavin by the way you're seriously deficient all right so i have to
the game show questions can i can't see how anybody would ever be able to answer any of
these questions can i change the questions we've got another contestant oh my the questions have
vanished welcome back to staying commercial staying commercial what more commercials we'll
be right back after this yes you can just make something up all right go in now go in now
do you have it up yeah wait does that fit hey a perfect fit all right let's do it we've got
another contestant i'm just kidding welcome back our next contestants are these guys again
okay are you ready the question is am i blue um i don't think so no hu you're not blue
oh dear oh me oh my that's absolutely right yes congratulations
i don't know if the game may have thrown a curveball at me and it's like he's sad
he's so happy look at how happy he is this is awkward but we don't actually have a million in
cash sweet mother of all quiz show scandals we'll have to give you a million dollars worth
of food stamps they're right over there what hold on can you buy deep fried licorice ropes
with food stamps we'll take it one two three 174 175 999 999 and a million let's go spend it sam
it's burning a hole in my pocket it's putting quite a bulge in mine
oh
do it do it do it do it streamers on coke what i'm making an irony okay so now i can go get the
thing i let's go back glad you're making fun of chat for that no i mean i just i know what's
gonna happen okay i've been around a long time i know what do that what you guys are going to do
make a cake i already did oh he's calling oh call it out chat he's calling out chat we're so
predictable but a toxic environment streamers making fun of chat i'm not making fun of chat
i'm taking the piss mate they're different
how do you watch tv from in there i've got monitors you don't even know about
here we would like a million buy something yes quite so quite so we come bearing one
million american dollars now hand over the voice modulator blimey food stamps i suppose i must
accept them both the danish government conspiracy it's hogwash complete codswallop codswallop
here then is your chemical-based voice modulator this is a helium balloon strapped to an inhaler
but it works trust me trust me holy chipmunk aria is warbling out of a souped up 78 speed
turntable it works thanks posco can you guys fucking believe that they made an entire franchise
an entire four three four decade long franchise around people singing like that and then pitch
shifting up to be chipmunks and they brought it back too and it was still as popular it hurts to
listen to that it's like my fucking god i can only take it to 10 seconds they made four movies
where are we going sam high pitch shifted loud singing that had to have been some
cracked out studio executive goody that thought it was funny all right so let's try this again
cocaineed out so is he still is he my friend do i have to do this again because i said happy
birthday gave him the cake you should vote for me now right all right let's go do the balloon
testing one two three ladies and gentlemen please welcome our next contestant sam hello
i'd like to do a little song i call it doesn't matter what it is bottleneck on the freeway of
doom
thinking about the rings on the great raccoon all the girlies hear me and they swoon
they made vinyls and let's hear from our judges your moribund crooning is far less offensive
than keeper's excruciating slaughterhouse squalor oh let's put it this way you really
nailed that high note how many of you guys would like to listen to all the yoshis you got my vote
sing barbie girl that was i don't think you do but as long as i'm a judge peepers is getting my
oh fucking please what do i have to put tomatoes on embarrassing idol with the sighting action
after this well i need to give tomato he said no tomatoes no didn't he say i want you missing
tomatoes put shit in it no i can't do that all right is there any tomatoes tomatoes tomatoes
tomatoes i gotta pee all right i'm gonna pee i'll be right back good evening i've returned can you
wait a bit longer i gotta pee now i'll be quick hurry up let's go go go go go go go
welcome once again to cooking without lians what food what are we making this
well good i'm not going i'm waiting i'm gonna wait for i i didn't click it i didn't i clicked
back into the window and it clicked in the game i'm not gonna i'm gonna wait that's good you're
already back did you pee into the air what did you just like go that was down even five ten seconds
all right let's let's get going so i've got to come up with um what do i need to come up with
what are they doing right i gotta go back okay go back and get my scandal
and then i've got to do something with the game show questions i mean is it any tomatoes
are there any tomatoes in this room or the cooler i think this is one of those cooler things they
use on medical what's it doing on the set of a cooking show some knowledge is better over the
oven this is quite realistic like that animatronic kid on the cosby show window it's like a scene from
fighting how is that no no no it's wrong well let me go do the scandal let me just get that
out of the way let's exit oh and also i gotta change the to part two i gotta save it this has
been like fucking two hours here that would have been a blunder all right let me uh change the title
well not this one that just chilling with the dog in the hair is fine this is episode two though
called situation comedy there it is so we don't give people the wrong idea all right let's go back
and give the photo wait no i wouldn't have no this is the right way i guess it's right back here right
are you allowed just to set it to sam and max um i think so but if you're in the directory and
it's there people will be able to see it no he's on episode two let's go to the scandal who will
that help i don't know the random person that maybe sees sam and max in the directory and they
go oh sam and max what episode episode two oh there it is why why is there even a directory
in the first place sam this is perfect this photo is a capstone it succinctly summarizes over 30
years of extraterrestrial related photographic evidence civil that photo was a hoax exactly
i couldn't have asked for better now i can print the paper available at newsstands now
there it is do i get a copy of it or do i have to go newsstand all right so let's leave so we
get to a newsstand is it in boscos no news oh there we go we're famous hooray can we begin
misbehaving now begin again cool i speed run sam and max professionally don't miscategorize
them in the directory is it wrong no it's not this is episode two situation comedy i got it right
all right you got do you have tomatoes in here ah ketchup mustard and purple stuff
as vaguely referred to on tv give me give me the ketchup as vaguely oh i need to put it on the cake
well shit cake cake cake cake backtracking back and forth point and click adventure games
on optimal speedrun yeah on optimal route he's gonna reset sam the tv studio goodie
the jupiter in the chat this chat is now in kenshi only mode what are you talking about
what oh the frog i forgot i love these little pineapple juice cans they're so good
i love those little juice cans welcome once again to cooking without looking the show where we use
absolutely nians whatsoever and food poison chuck thank you welcome to the show that editing what
are we making this time sam food poison a cake today we're baking a cake and we're gonna use
max uh it doesn't matter asbestos course who could forget the asbestos sprinkles
this stuff isn't just for school lunches real kitchens use it too and uh tweed of course it
wouldn't be real bachelor cooking without queen bachelors here's a tip tweed isn't just for
cooking it also makes a great toupee and msg every chef has a signature ingredient that no one has
ever heard of or used mine's msg if you put in enough that you feel a burning sensation in the
back of the neck forearms and chest you're just about there make sure to include red dye number
two if there's not at least some possibility of malignant tumors it's not get it in there do
we broil it sam right you are and through the magic of one gorgeous oh boy let's take it put
ketchup on it come back and let's go is it msg not even that bad for you um i don't know isn't that
one of those things i think we talked about this before msg can like didn't msg cause headaches in
one person msg makes you retain crazy water yeah what that the thing about msg wasn't there wasn't
there one guy scenario where somebody said msg gave me a headache and maybe sick and stuff and
they did like a whole thing on it hello i mean the moral of the story is don't use too much salt
or any additive on anything a little ketchup is always good on a cake don't put too much salt
too much sugar bring your body down towards more natural approach moral of the moral of the story
just lower your intake of salt sodium don't eat too much cheese you can eat it eat a bunch
of it eat a fucking ton of it don't eat too much of it make sure you're thoroughly cooking your
food where are we going sam the tv studio goody paleo no you'd like a fucking hamburger go to
mcdonald's go to the drive-through right now and get like two big macs do now go do it right now
if you can if you're able to get it but don't eat it every day happy birthday
oh boy birthday cake that red frosting looks tasty
msg ads it's monosodium glutamate if you're sensitive to a gluten-based product
oh that was really oh really oh uh-oh time out for number two what the better not be going to
see myra well anyway we can't wait we'll just have to finish the show with only two judges
whatever you guys agree on goes vote for me if you're like able you know your sound body and
sound mind go grab a good feedback or something what's up to you testing one two three no don't
do too much at all testing one he's getting uh-oh he's getting like addicted to it
that's not good i don't want to do that again hello like to do a little song i call busted down
hound dog blues
thinking about the rings on the great racket and so i wrote this extremely catchy
okay and let's hear from our judges bravo your wobbly tenor is way better than people
took the same one each time i don't know i just you really nailed that high note
and you're less sloppy than my brother you got my vote hey all of the remaining judges have agreed
we have a winner deletion staff here's your recorded contact bin bottom records it's like
a dream come true specs i'll get you for this if it's the last thing i do after i get back from
mount rushmore rushmore i'd better go after him i just remembered i have to feed my goldfish
are we still taping be sure to join us next time on embarrassing idol i could probably get
to the first round i'm dead serious i could definitely if i waited in line for 16 hours
for american idol i could probably get through the first round it would be a debate you know
between um paula and simon paula would vote for me and simon would vote for me too i was going
there and just i would just fucking give my all and i would give him a crazy story i'd go in there
with the guitar wrapped around i would even play it i i think i could do it though i really do get
past that first round just go in there and play minecraft vr okay what do i got everything
recording contract love triangle the game show these uh why do i still have these
yes oh you two again well what is it well you've got the length of one commercial break to explain
yourselves uh how do i have remind me of course what if we have video games ah those things will
ruin your eyes they're awful recording contract we do have a recording contract in bottom records
take a look you should have us on as guests i like what i get to be celebrities audiences are talking
about something classic been embroiled in any juicy scandals lately something easy our landlady
thinks i'm the one who broke the dryer in the basement time was that everybody knows is talking
about you and don't forget to watch behind your ears first actually we graced the cover of the
current edition of the alien love triangle times how's that for a scandal you will have us on your
show now yes oh i suppose so if only so i can talk about america's lamentably endless fascination
with depravity stop skipping i'm just my pan naturally expects to be on the right side and be
on my fifth and i hit right click and my finger goes there off the table and use your indoor voice
what about while you're on my show you stay in your seats at all times you do not interrupt me
when i'm talking and you treat the audience with the utmost respect even if you become less sure
with each passing year that they deserve it now i'll call you on stage in a minute gosh max
celebrity is just a never-ending set of arbitrary goals one accomplishes to appease a dismissive and
distracted if not entirely absent authority figure i don't know if i agree sam but i've begun my
decadent slide into a depraved personal hell just in case okay give her a hand everyone
bessie bovine reading from her new book the heart has four stomachs ruminations on a life in hollywood
out now in all major bookstores this microphone is starting to spark from overuse but that doesn't
mean we're ready to pack it in we've got the stars of the not quite canceled sitcom
midtown cowboys who also happen to be the winner and judge of tv's embarrassing idol
ladies and gentlemen sam and math hold the hayride little pal that bear seems more than
slightly hinky in the mesmeric sense of the term shadier than a fat man's ankles let's take it down
like ducks in a gutter my guess it at that end but that bear has got you set we'll just sit where
you want us to man lovely what gives sam why can't we just grab the bear it would appear that the
laws of physics are different on the set of a talk show little buddy we're gonna have to play along
set sam and max your talented hot new celebrities who've taken the entertainment world by storm
so naturally we all want to hear everything about your involvement in the scandal detailed in the
alien love triangle times uh i'd rather talk about midtown cowboys i'd rather leave my embarrassing
about that picture in the times okay there is something you should know about that picture in
the times i'm not sure i want to know anything more maybe you just asked me about things it's
funny to flaunt your poly planetary pickups but the rest of us find alien love triangles frankly
disgusting but the photo is not quite what it seems how so it's not us we just used it to get
on here that's no alien it's hue bliss there was someone else involved it's not a picture
of an alien at all that's hue bliss hue bliss the highly respected founder of prismatology
don't be ridiculous why i've had him on my show before and he certainly isn't green what are you
really hiding how much i'm scared of being buffeted by another gust of hurricane myra
flattery will get you nowhere mister i don't know about you audience but as a girl i was
taught that flattery was the worst possible way to blah blah blah yack yack yack blah blah blah
blah yack yack yack yack bloody bloody bloody yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety yack
put that away right now
i was gonna shoot the bear humanity's not safe while that mysterious little hypno
are we part of humanity sam not technically but we're in danger too
you just heard you hear a laugh did you hear that she was breaking in the studio
blah blah blah
and why is in front of a live studio audience
i don't know
drugs on camera i have to do it
ah yes where were we i think we were discussing the alien love triangle times
and that nasty scandalous affair of yours i'd like to sing if i may is that wise
howling at that trippy old hunk of broken whoa no i didn't break the bear that was wonderful
i'm so moved i almost don't have a long hectoring screen in me oh no wait there it is thank goodness
self-referential songwriting is a dangerously blah blah blah blah no no
blah blah blah
puddle i think it's getting the bear away
electrocute
blah blah blah
okay i have to move the microphone
he's gonna die i wish you wouldn't dear i only have so many drinking
glasses and i was lovely audience men you're getting my head off the good starting to enjoy
the misplaced adulation blah blah blah blah yak yak yak yak bloody bloody bloody
yakety yakety yakety yakety yakety can't we sit over there you'll sit where you are and like it
mister yes ma'am blah blah blah blah yak yak yak yak bloody bloody bloody blah yakety yakety yakety
yakety yakety yakety yakety yak blah blah blah blah blah humanity's not safe while that mysterious
little hypno bear is on the loose are we part of humanity sam not technically but we're in danger
too blah blah blah blah blah yak yak yak got a second little buddy now that we're big stars i'd
normally ask that your people i'm gonna go crazy but since we're old friends yak yak yak yak bloody
bloody bloody yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety yackety then i shall reach
all right i have to get him ah yes where were we i think we were discussing the alien love triangle
times and that nasty scandalous affair of you okay uh i'd rather talk about that bear i'd like to
talk about that charming yet mildly insidious looking bear on your desk can i see it i don't
know sam can you may i see it please no you may not and if i may say so if there's one thing that
grills my chicken it's how our culture is in a state of modal decay can is not the same as may
should is not the same as blah blah blah hopefully she'll be off on her tri-state nagging spree for a
while blah blah blah blah yak yak yak yak bloody bloody bloody bloody yackety yackety yak
ah yes where were we scandalous i'd rather talk about our smash hit sitcom midtown cowboys
okay let's talk you two have become the new breakout stars of a flaccid dissolute sitcom
in its final days how wonderful for you thanks we brought a clip you certainly did i had a chance
to watch it and i refused to show it to my audience why it has a shocking joke involving
a cow pie it's a sad commentary on today's culture when the cow pie wants a staple of
the american diet blah blah blah blah yak yak yak yak i see why myra only lets big stars on her
show they're easier targets if you're big enough there still might be something left when she's
finished blah blah blah blah yak yak yak yak bloody blood are you scandalous i'd like to talk
about me i'll talk about let's talk about you my rap me what could anyone want to know about me
maybe they'd like to know how honored you are to have me max brilliant actor in the serbic wit on
your show are you sure you wouldn't rather talk about your alien love triangle shenanigans okay
she so badly wants to talk about the alien love triangle and when i bring it up she says nobody
wants to hear about it that's what she said i'd like to mention my pal sam and something that
happened the other day anecdotes about other celebrities even ones as dubious as you two
are always welcome well it sounds like an average person at you with a broken parking
meter and screaming die why won't you die and sam said you crack me up little buddy the point
being i crack sam up are you sure you wouldn't rather talk about your alien love triangle
shenanigans jesus there's more you should know about that picture in the times what's that
it doesn't tell the whole story there's someone else involved someone the picture doesn't show
how shocking who um bestie the cow one of the poppers i don't know who this is one of the soda
poppers oh my which one peepers peepers peepers is the one peepers is like the the weird one right
peepers well by amazing coincidence we happen to have peepers here we go
that's where you hear a bunch of fucking swears censored i knew it all that happened was they
snatched my lyrics i can't even imagine what horrifying act that's slang for how are any of
us supposed to listen to burp back rack being interviewed without blah blah blah wait wait wait
she just put the mic over here what about the puddle i think it's getting
bare with she just put the microphone in the puddle blah blah blah blah ah yes scandalous
wouldn't the microphone get shocked in the puddle there's more what's there are still
incredible bessie bovine our co-star on midtown cowboys oh my audience shall we bring her back
out again all right well why did it happen that should have happened already right obvious comment
that was shocking is she breathing a little but the creepy teddy bear is toast nuts i wanted to
ask it a few questions here and maybe use it to hypnotize katie kurik another glorious dream
bangs its chin on the dirty pavement on the bright side the audience is free to go home
oh i was just getting warmed up do you think myra will have us back on the show again soon
um speaking of unlikely did you notice we just had two cases in a row involving hypnotic mind
control complete coincidence yes i think so the cogs of the universe synchronize in ways we're
not meant to see blah blah speaking of things we're not meant to see there's a new restaurant
at the zoo where you can eat what they feed the animals empty popcorn cartons and cigarette
butts and processed bread logs loaded with tranquilizers and antidepressants bread logs
make me loki let's head back to the cooking show set and see if we can figure out how to make
fried pork rinds okay but i get the feet it's just dead episode two situation comedy that's fun
new world record speed run episode three nah i can't we can't do episode three tonight
it's gonna it's mid it's almost midnight i'm not the stream's not over but i don't know if another
two to two but they're about two and a half hours each so that would be like two to three
that'd be like almost 3 a.m pacific they get better as it goes on do you think it'll continue
yeah definitely i might even just come back with this we'll just keep doing it we'll get
through at least season one episode three is actually an hour shorter that's no it's not a
joke really what do you mean he's am i falling for is that for real it's only 45 minutes long
yeah hold on i'm gonna check it on how long to beat that's a good what's it what's it called
what's the actual name of the episode the mole the mob and the meatball let's take a look how long
it's kind of hard to search for these how long to beat 103 oh wow that's not a lie it's actually
like an hour shorter um yeah let's do it now let's go for it that actually was not people just lying
it's for real it's only like an hour long yeah because that'll take us to like one i still i
want to watch that video so if you want to what this is about it's a 20 minute video there's like
somebody made like a germa rumble video that like short film and i was interested in just seeing
him like taking a look at it so yeah we can do both now all right let's uh let's do it let's just
let's get it open i got it right here just give me a moment while i open it up let me change the
title too yeah we're getting late if you if you take it off i'll see you later see you next week
next weekend is when i will return so three there's it's the same length as the previous
episode i don't know what the other guy said if you want you can return with this and finish the
season on uh is it is it the how long to beat says one and a half hours well okay let's put
it this way if we don't get to like a conclusion in like an hour hour and a half then i will we'll
just move on we'll come back so many one guys i can't i don't know who's telling the truth
so wait have a long wait no maybe i am getting
you'll stay up till 5 a.m to finish seaman but i didn't stay up till 5 a.m
no let's let's do it let's go let's do it it's not that late yet it will be soon let's see what
happens was it actually five o'clock in the morning yeah but that was a true super investment because
i wasn't going to turn that shit back on ever again something like this it's episodes and i
can go back and forth and i could do it i can do a season then come back like in a week or two
do the other season or something right that's not seaman was i was never going to put the disc back
in that try ever again i have to wait till this gets to the menu i cannot skip it i have to wait
till it gets to the menu and then exit and redo it this is called the moldemob and the meatball
i can't get to the menu until i get in the game so just give me a second all right come on this is
a long intro let's go put it to 1280 by 960 graphics on full full screen off all right
apply that okay you should be able to hear it now there you go all right new game episode three it
should be already updated just make sure it is all right late night late night late night going
late tonight game time okay we'll see what we are after about 45 minutes of playing an hour or so
we'll see if we're getting to the end if we're not you know it's like an hour or two to go
and just save and come back it's not a big deal because i don't want this to be like a three to
four yes max i think i just gave birth to a bouncing baby hernia higher i got it i just
commissioner holy cap wearing catfish blubbing a crime we're on our way did he get the notes i
sent him yes but he said to stop carving them into the suspects he can't read them without
his bifocals what if i just write bigger forget that max we're after the most infamous organized
crime outfit in the city the toy mafia the cutthroat killers with no respect for human life
but an odd predilection for delightful children's toys the same i love those guys commissioner has
reason to believe that the toy mafia's secret headquarters are located in the one place no one
would ever suspect teddy bears mafia-free playland and casino the sallowest place on earth
oh man well it's not going to be all laughs and it's a rescue on the commissioner sent an
undercover you didn't tell me this is a casino episode he hasn't reported in weeks our job is
to make contact with the mole and see if he needs help is he a large star-shaped mole or more of a
beauty mark no idea max to find him we're supposed to give the code phrase does the carpet match the
drapes at the casino he'll say well i never across the face sounds great let's do this
somebody said hey let me guess the undercover mole is actually a mole it's a little loud you would
probably be right you would i yeah you are here right it's definitely going to be that or they'll
do the complete 180 and it'll be like a gorilla or something so infiltrate the casino where we going
the casino teddy bears mafia-free playland and casino goody all right bosco still exists that's
right i forgot he didn't hesitate for a second and he saw the word casino mafia-free playland and
casino that face my name's lovey bear boy do we have some fun and games for you here take this
token amount of tokens as our way of saying welcome and go spend a lot of money
it's the bear from the last episode i think we had a good report card is there a mole in here i hear
you have a mole problem hey it's a genetic condition you should have seen my father's back
holy cow i'm actually being too subtle first time that's ever happened maybe i should just
stick to the code phrase holy domesticated versus max lovey bear here's got the same head
as that hypnotic teddy bear from myra's talk show you think that little talk show bear had a litter
of giant babies i don't know max call it canine intuition but i think our mole discovered something
about these teddy bears he shouldn't have we've got to find him and get to the bottom of this
you're lucky this mask doesn't have ear holes or i might have heard that secret conversation you
just had right in front of me what sorry i wasn't listening do we say the thing does the carpet
match the drapes if don ted e bear says so they do don teddy bear i thought this place was mafia
free that's right kiddies 100 mafia free no mafia or anywheres come on true you give tokens to
first time customers that's right go on enjoy live a little it just seems like bad business sense
okay behind you with that you had a crazy face from now when you're trying to pawn your little
friend here to pay off the vig we can talk then about bad business sense okay we'll come back then
we're looking for somebody who works here look i just greet the guests you want to know who works
here don ted e bear he's in charge where's the don he's got uh business in the back room
does the carpet match the drapes what kind of business yeah we're gonna say that to everybody
business that gets said like it's got quote marks around it so you know not to ask
all right thanks levy bear enjoy and remember if you're not losing we're not winning
black the rats wacky rats rules they get to make all the rules so what are you talking about
you actually get to play blackjack back room guard what else is in here buffets closed buffet
closed for semi-annual food change sorry max ah semi-annual food change one-armed bandit slot
machine just pull it i don't have any money oh i have to free i have that free money gambling
addiction we won yeah we won but there's no prize you gotta hand it to teddy bear he really puts
the bandit in one-armed bandit hold it what's the password you made why is it no money doesn't make
any sense what how do you have a casino and it doesn't pay out anything disturbing bear heads
that's terrifying these rats are gonna pop up see if the rats keeping his mouth shut you don't touch
him and if that rat's singing you put a bullet in his head jesus christ in this trial i win a
souvenir magnet look max it's a beloved carnival game with a delightful mobster twist what better
way to relax than by offing fake rodents in the most violent way imaginable no please supply your
own firearm we always do insert token to play all right we'll put one in wipe the rats insert
token i can't put a token in i use my only token oh what about these guys well what do we have here
i'd say the circus was in town but i know for a fact they won't be here till next friday
so you must be here to play cards depends who are we playing their name steak charme
lennard steak charmer and let's just say i didn't rack up 10 million tokens by getting lucky
how'd you get him then by cheating cheating look rabbit lennard steak charmer's no cheat
he's just that good what's the game okay what's the game steak charmer blackjack
how exactly does one play poker of the indian persuasion you know you're off to a good start
when your opponent doesn't even know how to play you ever consider that we might be card sharks
or shark sharks you know the kind that eat people for being overconfident whatever look it's simple
we both get dealt a card which we put on our forehead without looking at it so we can see
each other's card but not our own need to guess if your don't call me denominations higher than
theirs oh yours is you that's it yep then we see who's got the highest card and then i win
like always well when you put it like that we'd be fools not to play let's play we'd like to try our
hand at a hand of indian poker you won't regret this hound by which i mean i won't regret this
oh and try any funny stuff with your partner and i'll shoot you both that seems fair we have guns
so am i higher or lower probably lower is he looking at the card i got 10 million tokens says
i got a better card than you i'm betting it all sweet second mortgages on a summer home we can't
match that tell you what pooch i'm feeling so confident i'll give you 10 million to one odds
just bet one token and you can win the whole pot those are mighty good odds no they ain't
that bitty dog because i never lose million to one you bet one token in that that's a bill
um let's bet sure well bet a token yeah sorry i didn't see the wait i just saw the card
stick jama wins mama was wrong gambling does bet i'd say better luck next time but it'll take
more than luck to beat me yeah to take a sturdy oaken staff to really do the job what was my card
deal all right you got a four my card is definitely way higher than yours so we're
betting old what no 10 million token bet nope i just always know when i got the lower card
call it my sixth sense or seven you count my so we're cheater we don't well we're certainly
never getting rich at this rate does the carpet match the drapes no it's stained with tobacco juice
what squalid yet candid normally i like that in a gambler but for you we'll make an exception
that's fucking kind of gross lennard steak charmer huh you don't look like a lennard steak charmer
oh yeah what do i look like you look more like a boris crinkle that's what everyone says
okay uh what else we got dialogue indians yeah i'm a wooden indian as in wouldn't bet against me if
i was you i'll kill him not yet kill him yeah why would anybody even play you get anyone to gamble
with you frankly you seem shady i offer great odds and i possess a certain subtle charm i hate to
break it to you but non-existent and subtle are two different things maybe charm is a euphemism for
gum disease look i'm here to play poker are we going to get this dog and bunny show on the road
or what no lennard you give new meaning to the phrase a face only a mother could love
escalated kind of mama said i was beautiful uh that's enough for now okay although i could
have sworn you were a dog not a chicken a common mistake all right let's go what about the deal
there freaky bear head wearing card dealer hello i'm cuddly bear want to play cards
no talk to you later want to play card no no i just said no all right does the carpet match the drapes
hold it mugs not mugs max i don't care if it's teddy ruxpin no one gets in without a password
i have the password that would be what again why don't you tell me does the carpet match the drapes
i don't know i set fire to the drapes i love to watch things burn that's not the password i'm
sorry i asked that's not the password the password is swordfish nope the password is rosebud nope
the password is password nope let us in only toy mafia allowed in not that there's any mafia here
okay we'd like to sign up for the toy mafia please
talk to chuckles he's the head of mafia admissions chuckles chuckles right behind this door this is
what it would be like if catch 22 had a meaner older brother look i don't make the rules i just
blindly enforced them all right well bring me the head of alfredo garcia nope i've come to
grandma's funeral nope who's on first nope who's your daddy nope i am the walrus nope how many
guesses can i have you remind me of this shopkeeper i know nope i give up will you let me in please
nope the password is nope we'll be back like i care all right uh so i need a password
i also need oh hold on meatball sandwich display teddy bear's original meatball sandwich
looks tasty the original teddy bear made this original meatball sandwich with his own two paws
in 1957 don't do this to me microorganisms that give teddy's modern meatballs their distinctive
tang are descended from the colony in this sandwich teddy bear's original looks tasty
yeah i'm so i'm so hungry now i'm gonna sneeze drink on the table lollipop can i not play the
whack-a-mole machine rubber duck it's a rubber ducky ashtray leave it to the toy mafia to make
smoking fun it's a rubber ducky leave it to the one-armed bandit you see that sam it's a little
play on the well-known colloquialism for slot machine the fun just never stops i already did
this but i can actually i have to actually go oh okay let's get this token in chat toke there's
a token in chat these rats are gonna just please read the word token you don't touch
the rat is singing how can we not okay i get it i get it gotta get them all high school guidance
counselor was right i should have become a mafia hitman missed one look there's the prize as
advertised it's an almost entirely worthless teddy bear refrigerator magnet hey let's find
someone with a metal plate in their skull and redecorate their forehead oh max you really know
how to find the right side of everything don't you yes i do now let's go shoot something
okay let's play again god damn it how do i escape
oh we came up empty that's okay a wise woman come on no i'm gonna put the gun away
let's i'll get it again how was i get less than last time looks like they're all out of prizes
it's still fun though i did 21 last time oh 20 all right well maybe it's random yeah okay
all right well i got the this thing teddy bear magnet i'm not magnet there's nothing i can do
about this i can't do it but about buffet buffet closed for semi-annual yeah hello people hands
people dance does the carpet match the drapes want to play cards we asked first want to play
cards is it gonna do anything else we're looking for someone who works here want to play cards
fine sounds like someone played a game of 52 card pickup and lost we'd like to develop a gambling
addiction starting now back for a little more public humiliation just a little more no no we'll
be back just remember all right let's say let's we haven't done anything else besides this let's go
let's go to the store there are songs in this episode in an episode four that are striked by
twitch and youtube the teddy bear is one of them well that's scary wait what how do you know that
where'd you get that info it's okay telltale is dead now yeah telltale doesn't exist anymore
hey Bosco nice flapjack son of cordem bleu who is this uh Bosco hey guys it's me Bosco
no but you may call me a jean francis sissipan the cowardly french anarchist
he changes uh like accents every single episode the symbol changes professions
everyone's out of their mind we want to buy something
what do you got behind the counter i have the latest in basco tech innovation
a device non-pareil or chocolate rats you get the joke yeah this i call a miniature
listening device it can fit in any cravat under any chapeau what's it do it listens you can use
it to hear secret conversations no no i mean yes what do you want okay 10 million sissy pants
we'll take that miniature listening device the price is 10 million dollars 10 million
wait is that 10 million in crazy fake french dollars or 10 million in regular dollars
regular dollars the market is bearish on crazy fake french dollars all right so i need 10 million
dollars probably need to win that at the casino do you have any straight tuffs of sasquatch hair
do you have any hats in the shape of a cow udder
do you have any rubber chickens with a pulley in the middle
do you have any amulets of protection against greater hypnosis
no we have to hear them all right do you have any
okay that's probably it do you do do do you do you oh my god all right for us right now
does the carpet match the drink let's ask you and you know why because the man doesn't want
them to he's threatened by their potential unification
look outside it's the toy mafia what where fools there is no one sorry bosco
just yanking your chain amigo sacre bleu i could do this all day and i intend to
why the french disguise let's let's listen so bosco why'd you get frenchified
they saw right through my british disguise i don't know how they did it but they found me
oh the mafia the toy mafia they've got it in for me take a number guys so now what's
what's the nightmarish atrocities has the toy mafia committed against you nothing yet but i know what
they are planning and it is terrible are they planning to tie you down take your eyelids open
and turn on the 24-hour midtown cowboys channel well not that bad i have reason to believe they
are planning to deliver something to my store this guy deliveries another delivery conspiracy
what could a band of ruthless toymongers possibly want to put in here i don't know but it is no
matter they will never be able to deliver anything to my store or my name is not jean franois
pants but your name's not jean franois sissy pants they don't know that what's keeping the
toy mafia from making a delivery well for one i am watching always they will never sneak past me
yeah just like wizard couldn't sneak past you and two even if they do get past me i gotta fail say
it's the greatest invention the world has seen grenades behind them i call it the bosco tech
anti-delivery system what's the acronym for that uh also btad it is btad's party
used to be just cigarettes back then i was grenades how does btad's part do work first he keeps
switching the accents in the camera it keeps a massive photo recognition database of every
inconvenient item i stock how completely impractical if anything gets placed in the store
that the anti-delivery camera does not recognize it is put on the street
okay so he's got a camera i know not this basco of whom you speak but if i see him i shall bid him
our reservoir all right there's your camera anti-delivery camera the anti-delivery camera
halt are you trying to deliver something i am watching you
no i'm not trying to deliver something all right i got this magnet what am i supposed to do the
magnet hmm are those yep they've resorted to filling the candy machine with antidepressants
holy shit how depressing what the fuck all right so civil what are you up to in this episode
what have you changed into who are you now still alien still hello sam hello max hey it's our
favorite short attention span careerist this time i found the job for me i've become a professional
trial witness uh what exactly is a professional trial witness oh it's great we give dramatic
testimonies sequester in ritzy hotels and order room service in the name of truth and justice
it almost sounds like you're enriching yourself at the expense of a different
actress over complicated legal system do you have a problem with that mr freelance police
yeah why didn't we think of it all right what's the case do you have your first case yet no but
i'm waiting for a call from the district attorney he says he's got something i'd be perfect for i
feared curtains you don't feel uncomfortable getting a case first and then being a witness for
it really is not at all you see the problem with most trials is that crimes are witnessed by someone
who's unprepared for what's going to happen or who doesn't have sufficient training or here's the
weird thing about what you just said or relate what happened with my background and widely buried
skill set i'm perfect i know what that means that makes sense but i don't know how probably
it's it's like a guy theory is his shirt or the car is that tattoo that image is just synonymous
with guy fear and i can't put on to why his shirt he wears like the fire bowling shirts
right okay all right for some reason i didn't think that was the case it's on the you know he
drives around uh there's a fire on the car does the carpet match the drapes interior decorating
was like eight months ago i'm a trial witness now we'll be back civil bye boys official flag of
flavor down wear a joint relax relax relax relax hey does guy fear he got buried is the carpet
match the drapes that's killer oh that's out of the park man we got it this charred pile of scrap
serves as a touching reminder of the fun we had at warp tv i've determined that whether for food
or for sport i just really enjoy frying things all right i need to go back to the casino
i need to go back there in real life i lost a hundred dollars a few weeks ago and i gotta
go get it back what do you mean the reception's perfect right now i have an answer all right
anything in the desk the drawers are just painted the drawers are just painted on to make the desk
seem useful i was at the roulette table and i lost 45 dollars and i want it i want it back i want my
45 dollars back so this time i'm gonna bring 50 and get five dollars interest back because i'm
gonna win where are we going sam teddy bears mafia free playland and casino goodie for a refund
go up to like the cashier hey um welcome to teddy bear i lost i lost a thousand dollars here
step right up kiddies um i kind of i'd like i can i get a refund
yeah i was gonna give this place like a three on yelp i think the the carpets were clean
but i lost all too much of my money it's a rubber ducky ashtray leave it to the toy mafia to make
smoking fun i'd rather keep it to myself i'd rather keep it to myself what that is
almost as shiny as yours keep it up and you'll get a shiner too wait a minute that is one shiny
you can see almost as hard as yours keep it up and you'll get a shiner too it isn't that interesting
the magnet wouldn't look good there well can i change seats back for a little more public
humiliation just a little more i want to be in your seat that's enough for now okay a common
can i how do i can i turn this off that is one shiny nose almost as shiny as yours keep it up
and you'll get a shiner too can i pull it can i shoot them can i pull the gun out here and shoot
the nose i need to get in that chair turn reflections off in the setting how do i move
him or block it like a blanket or a drape or something use a carpet or the drapes
uh i'm getting tired stuff like that's really fucking doing it for me
let's go why a grill master barbecue's email it's not allowed in here because that guy sucks
are you serious do i have to explain that a very disturbed individual sits here
jimmy two teeth fence it's a sad day when hard-working rodents have to make their
living as a freestanding form of enclosure uh i think that's fence and the buys themselves
stolen goods sense of the word beat it you're getting in way of my customer you're running
an illegal casino in here jimmy two teeth beat it hey an ace an extra card up your sleeve and
it never hurts except when the other guy catches you with it and decides to riddle every inch of
your body with high caliber bullets and then dump your mutilated corpse in an empty field
yeah except then how am i supposed to do this i don't know why i thought that was gonna do
anything so i i can cheat here so let him win because he knows he's gonna where are we going
sam teddy bears mafia free playland and facility goody goodies
welcome to teddy bears mafia free you know what is it against the rules to bring your own cards
sure but everybody does it anyhow hey i'm about to cheat excuse me guard i'm bringing in an ace
and i'm going to use it at this table over here i just want to make sure you're aware all right so
what about hold on what are you doing this magnet the magnet wouldn't look good there
i'd rather keep it to myself can i put the card up there wow it sticks so he's gonna think it's an
ace every time hello cuddly bear want to play cards yes we want to play cards back for a
little more public humiliation just a little more deal all right so he thinks he has an ace
he does have it he has a four okay would you look at that i'm betting all 10 million and you only
gotta bet one so you're in or out in sure well better token sorry fido you lose the dog wins
what are you talking about lennard how did we cheat you pay up stick charmer mama why
don't you watch it over me i'm ruined that's kind of sad let's go max lennard and his dead mother
need some alone time right now yeah let's go see if we can play whack the rats 10 million times in
a row without passing out so i got 10 million which gives me a thing to listen which i assume
i have to put on the door and i can hear the password through the door let's go get them
let's do it that was all he had well don't fucking cheat people you got 10 million of them
stash a million in your pocket and then be a dickhead with nine million
i don't care go put a million in the bank and then you can do whatever you want
why don't i double click to run because it's not in this game it is uh not in salmon max season one
shall we shot unfortunately let's do hey boscow all right let's uh let's take it we want to buy
something the guy that's running the convenience store here um he's making millions of dollars
okay stinky pants through your 10 million these elaborate inventions of saint gainsburg these are
not american dollars no but there are 10 million of them
well the prizes at teddy bears can be quite useful i accept and in return i give you
the miniature listening device this is a bug precise mint does this thing really work
does this thing really work that answer your question now listen up maggots i am a bug
drop me in intimate territory and i will get all the information you need you just make sure
to pick me up again and i will repeat every word everywhere i mean this one's actually worth 10
million putting you in some situations that could be a might precarious think you can handle it i
was a non-boy you don't want to know what i've been through they slaughtered ladybug ladybug
the last one was a balloon the helium in it this is a talking animal
so yeah i think i can handle it now i need some shut out before the mission
put me in your pocket in your pocket move maggot sir yes sir you are a talking animal
right but that's where they were probably worth a lot of money where are we going sam
like we're probably worth a huge amount of money land and casino goody welcome to teddy bears
mafia free somebody said hey um you know we have dogs here frequent banquets yeah we have doxins
oh cool how much is a doxin well 450 425 dollars well that's kind of expensive but okay
any of them talk english yes this one does i would expect it would be at least a million to
10 million that's what i'm saying all right let's drop the bug here i can't listen to that get in
there boy do i have to hold on somebody opens the door right still no prize we're wasting our money
hold it what's the password all right so i gotta put the bug on him
hold it all right i see is he gonna notice this and be annoyed at this or what
a talking dog without human intelligence would be kind of useless though don't you think
i mean but that that doesn't matter though we can still talk we're wasting our money sam hold it
what's the password you make
yeah it would say one word it would just be p outside pooh actually that would be bad though
because he would hear the all kinds of shit now listen up here's what they said hold it what's
the password that's gotta be what a hundred times i've come through that door today and you still
don't recognize me it's the bear heads boss they all look alike leave the gun take the cannolis
you may enter now get me in that pocket move sir yes sir imagine if all dogs were still dogs but
they walked upright like sam that would be really fucking weird give me the they're just normal
dogs but they walk around as people
oh that would be really messed up because then they could go in the fridge they would be able
to open the fridge and eat they'd get like the mustard out and stuff imagine the dog open up the
fridge and getting his face in there and just eating like a whole birthday cake still no
problems that doesn't matter they could just put their hand in and pull where would they eat would
they would they eat on the ground still or would you have to put would you have to put a plate on
a table and sit them at the table they sit at the table they stand up and lean down
but they put you know but usually a dog bowl is on the ground leave the gun take the cannolis
you may enter with the dog's payment to quote this is it where's the food surely there's a
buffet back here hey look that must be teddy bear where do you wise guys think you're going
who was we were just browsing we frown on that around here i'm chuckles the casino pit boss
i've had my eye on you uh how long have you been watching us long enough do i look any taller than
i did 10 minutes ago your win at poker was shall we say creative why whatever are you insinuating
that was nice work you also somehow got the password to let you into this room very clever
i'm impressed with the mole the toy mafia can use guys who are long on brains and short on
scruples are you interested uh great once we're in we can find that mole sounds good i can't think
of anything i'd rather do at least not for the next five minutes i've always wanted to be a thug
officially i mean the fact that you've already got your own animal costume shows great initiative
but before we can accept you into the family there are two jobs i need you to
do jackal bad news the original meatball sandwich has been stolen there are three jobs i need you to
do for us what kind of jobs oh the usual i want you to lean on somebody i want you to whack
somebody and i want you to recover a small item that belongs to us who do you want us to lean on
who do you want us to lean on a local shopkeeper who's been refusing to stock our products take
these special teddy bears and make sure he displays them on the sale table in the front of his store
no problem the store is called bosco's inconvenience um no problem
who do you want us to kill who do you want us to whack we're having trouble with a witness who
refuses to see things our way i want you to silence a certain civil pandemic silence as in gag her
gag her with a pistol jesus you want us to kill cyborg make it messy as a message to other
potential witnesses messy murder under surveillance so we'll be watching yikes
uh okay how are we supposed to wait what is it that you want us to recover it's that rotting old
sandwich right the original meatball sandwich has great sentimental value to our organization
i want you to track it down before the disrespectful slime bag who stole it
manages to fence it to some other lowlife fence that one's detectivey deal with the thief as you
see fit we'd like to preserve plausible deniability on this one okay i think we've got it do these three
things sam and max and you shall be as we are i'm gonna set our names verbally over rot members of
the toy mafia oh right we want to talk to your boss nobody talks to don teddy bear the head of
the toy mafia doesn't he get lonely except other members of the toy mafia oh that'd explain it
does the carpet match the drapes the drapes well i'll tell you about the drapes my friend
uh no that's okay maybe his hobby is interior decorating sam let's not chance it all right
we'll be back a word of advice because i like you too when you walk away from the toy mafia watch
your back so we need to kill civil do not enter under pain of death what's behind that door
none of your business looks like you can monitor the whole casino floor from there
and a few other places besides or you can watch mary tyler moore who told you about that
mary tyler moore that's a show that's a show that was on television all right what about a workstation
what is this thing mine stay away from it all right what about any of these people what is ted
where do you think you're going back there no one may approach don teddy bear that's me
the members of the toy mafia it's jeff from psychology all right let's go i feel that i'm
a little frustrated i wasn't able to work the word black and spiel into our conversation but
you're welcome so how am i gonna kill civil fake it right how do you kill somebody
teddy toy box magnet now let's figure this out i mean i know i have a gun but i'm not gonna
actually go kill the symbol i don't think i can bring myself to actually shoot her
well let's get a plan print up any titillating scandal mags lately no howdy symbol no no you've
got the wrong person i mean dame i mean dame person isn't dame person that big chin puppet
to scare children oh sam max thank goodness it's you i thought it was someone come to kill me
yes well you seem understandably a little tense maybe you should switch to decaf what oh yes the
coffee cup i'm out of coffee but i'm so nervous i keep trying to drink it anyway it's funny how
stress can reduce you to just a bundle of mindless reflexes is that what happened to me wouldn't it
be wonderful to think so how's it working how's that new profession working out oh sam the life
of a professional witness isn't all courtroom theatrics and finger pointing the toy mafia
told me if i testified against them they'd rub me out they tried to buy you off with a swedish
massage no max i think they meant murder all right time's up it's been 45 minutes it's been 45
minutes we got our task we got a thing that we're gonna do yeah it's it's getting late daylight
savings here an hour slow make it an even six hours well it's going to be because we're gonna
do some stuff uh we're gonna watch a video this video is i think 20 minutes long we're gonna do
the bits we're gonna hang out so the stream is not over let me save the game yeah this is probably
a good stopping point we got through the casino we stopped here we got the task uh we'll be back
we'll be back i know you will you're out oops really she should consider guilt slinger as her
next profession so sam and max on the stream when i come back from my vacation we'll probably
we'll pick this back up this might not be the first thing coming back because there's a couple
things that are really that i would like to do but we're going to finish season one i promise
guaranteed like we're gonna i want to see how this goes through it might be the first thing
that happens when we come back it might be a day later we'll see season two is where it gets
really good i'm all for it i'm all just to hang out and play again i want to start incorporating
more of these just chill streams when we play a game we dial it up to like a thousand sometimes
on this stream so it's nice to pull it back a little but uh that is going to be the end of this
portion i'm going to save it before it gets to be too late we got monster rancher four is another
one that i have to continue and these are all episodic so it's better this is saved right yeah
yeah all right so now let me transition to over here have you taken off i will say see you soon
i'm not going to be live for about a week what is today today's technique this is saturday
so i'm probably you're probably not going to see me until somewhere around friday
i'm going to be gone for almost a full week don't forget about me you're not going to forget about
me right you're not going to i'll be back i'll be back rest not even a week don't you forget
about me well i'm not going to forget about you guys we'll be watching grill master you crack me
up a little buddy all right so now let's uh let's this video that we're going to watch get it because
it's very intriguing if you're going to bed the stream is at a close at the moment we're just
going to hang out do the bits like we normally do if you want to stick around and watch this
community-made video about the rumbles you get it and you know let's take a final break
so i'm gonna go pee we'll do final break come back and we'll probably go for like another hour
maybe this is about 20 minutes and then we'll do the bits and everything so
i'll be back final break of the night see you in a moment i'm also gonna pull this up too see you
in a second wait i didn't i'm not back i literally i just pressed the button i've been talking for
like a full minute well that's annoying i've been talking this whole time let's get this here all
right so this is i don't know i really don't know what this is this is a fan community movie short
film kind of project it looked really interesting so figured why not give it a look and see how it
is i'm gonna put it on the screen here in just a second should work is that gonna work you see if
i can pull it through here why am i still streaming well because i started at like seven
o'clock pacific and you know i'm gonna be gone for quite a while you will not see me for a week
so i wanted to you know stay up stream later stream like four straight days in a row i'm gonna
be gone for a while so yeah here we go this is called rumble this is short film signed out of
youtube apparently i think i got it sure it's in the right spot youtube account deleted wait
what do you mean youtube account deleted oh no it's fine oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait that's me that's jeremy the errand boy that was my actor derrick the
thief that's a pretty good beer trench coat how many care how many people are there how many
characters talker tim that's not a rumble character oh there's dastardly richard
yeah let's see yeah yeah yeah i'll see you in a bit
jeremy my boy how the devil are you pretty good thanks yeah whatever sit down jeremy i need your
help man go on people who fuck with me get fucked all right what derrick you know derrick right no
derrick the fucking thief he stole my fucking briefcase he did what briefcase my briefcase
but and he defined him get the briefcase but don't look in it it's very crucial part do not look
inside the briefcase and then when you've got it bring it back to me all right understood
also you're gonna have to kill him oh okay if that's all right with you yeah i guess
my best friend derrick um so where's he gonna be well he's trying to escape as we speak probably
but he's at shea's the strip joint normally can you do this for me you got it sorted oh and don't
forget don't look in the briefcase jeremy my boy he's got your mannerisms done i act like that
is this piss derrick yes that belongs to richard uh briefcase yeah you're gonna give it to me or
what no give me that briefcase listen to me richard is a bad man he didn't deserve the money
i didn't do this is not based on reality by the way money didn't tell you a 199,787 pounds to be
exact why such a specific amount huh a small amount has already been spent
oh
you dropped me that's what these dick tats don't think richards don't trust him beware
who is this what to do don't shoot him don't do it
hi richard it's jeremy i've got the briefcase good word and eric he's he's dead yeah um i'm
kind of in the middle of something right this is even a movie that is framing you for murder
uh yeah yeah i'll um i'll bring the money to you now money jeremy you didn't look inside the
briefcase did you uh oh he did he broke the one fucking rule jeremy you're there
jeremy what was that what character was that i've heard a lot about you if you do this for me you'll
be rewarded handsomely you got till three and i'll be sending real force friends yeah get it done
all right what kind what money is that how much is that passport that was me yeah
no he's got vr reloading speed holy shit that's two murders who's who is this character
yeah just make sure you wipe your feet before you come in um
yeah sure okay all right i'll see you tonight new character it's 20 it's 20 minutes long
they do have the signature that that is true the gray shirt and jeans listen you're my last
time i need you to go to jeremy's house all right that shit that's my briefcase and find out what
happened to that bier guy as well now don't make me kill somebody else in this movie where'd you
even get that picture from tim what the fuck what what that was supposed to be a tweet that i put out
where am i fucking dead irl scream in the woods
uh bits how about a laptop bag i think i have that laptop hey is this mickey's pizza place
yeah can i order a pizza yeah yeah um can i get like ham and cheese maybe some beef as well
tomatoes yeah yeah just all of the sides as well what pepperoni yeah that'd be great
that'd be so great funky what is this pizza is this this doesn't apply that like i'm going
over tim's house and like get like getting all fucked up or something
fast hey man i've got the 10 pounds is that me doing that ah tim uh you know your front
door's open mate you can't really just be doing that uh thanks for letting me stay but what the
fuck's that smell oh why is that what you're gonna be honest with you i'm in some trouble with some
people uh i stole this thing and i just came from burying it and i should have told you before he
has to stay over i'm really sorry i got this gun uh i think you all need it for protection
so i think i might put you in danger tim i'm really sorry i'm just gonna leave oh no but i
don't even know i don't know tim i think he's just sleeping check check him are you actually
gonna let me leave check him look i'm sorry i put you in danger and i shouldn't have but don't give
me a silent treatment please just let me stay one night one night and then i'll be out of your
hair by tomorrow please tim don't be like this you want to hear it why why what's that i'm sorry
for putting you in danger i wasn't thinking straight but please can just stay for one night
then i'll be out of your hair by tomorrow morning please tim talk to me man
you can't keep your
yeah why am i walking like this okay i would be like fucking wicked confident
i'd be like it's over here relax there it is it's there trust me just take it what
boy
i don't why am i so terrible that was brutal too but now i'm pretending to be
he becomes dick dastardly richard you can take that little disguise off now boy
that was a big reveal fuck you richard it's over no that's richard jerem my boy why do this i trusted
you you are the reason tim's dead shit happens but you you're a son to me i barely know you
i'm an errand boy for you i've killed three people today because of you what's one more
going to do pull the trigger shoot me right here in my fucking heart don't do it you can't do
you get away with this and not suffer the consequences what are you gonna do about it
i'll tell you what i'll do i'll have 10 men 20 men 30 men and i'll find you and i'll fucking kill you
well if i kill you then you can't send anyone after me can you i like the storm you've got no
god damn it that's that's a pretty it's a pretty terrible day
what what
right
is this how i got here is this the story
let the dice stay hot
boston to england to vegas
a fortune one and lost on every deal
family project
all right now at this point this is this is where the this like lowers down and you get like the
coming up next on netflix
well is there an after credit scene
might be
that's pretty good that was pretty good so you watched the whole thing you watched the whole
thing okay that's the after credit scene well if you'd like to watch that again
that was that was a journey it's apparently why or how i moved to vegas a piece of a fun
piece of fiction but that was fucking that was really well done it was very well made
uh i i can't believe that somebody would you know have loosely base something around this
community and this channel that's like i said that was a 20 minute short film so i thank you
for that it was fucking that was wild let me give you a link i think i did i do make sure i get the
right one here there it is it's called rumble and with that my american accent's going really well
yeah it is now one 15 a.m pacific now there's new germa oc characters and i have fun with it
whatever it's if you're having fun with it then fucking that's great it's very late i will see
all of you next weekend saturday technically i'll see you next weekend it is saturday let's do the
bits and that was a bunch of money stream labs is currently off for us let's see it no it's not
anymore what's going on here we just gave 50 bucks peek a banana 50 dollars no 70 dollars
to be corrected here thank you for the 70 dollars peek a banana uh hey germa your videos on youtube
used to make me laugh and they helped me through my lowest point in my life it is impossible for me
to express just how much i appreciate what you do you're hilarious and wonderful wonderful person
hope you spend some great family time with your mother over the next week germa hart uh i will i
will my mother is fantastic one of the reasons why i turned out the way that i did and the person
that i am is because of my mother so i cannot wait to spend some time with it it's been a long time
it's the first time ever we talked about a little bit but um this is the first time i've ever been
far enough away from my family where i physically do not see them at all for more than you know six
plus months seven months at a time so i was always close enough always wherever i lived
where it wouldn't be that far so it's gonna be great to see but peek a banana thank you
for the huge amount of money here and we're happy to have you so thank you you've contributed a lot
so thank you so much and we're gonna go back now to about six and a half hours ago uh this
shouldn't take us very long we had peaceful hailey with 250 thanks for the two dollars fifty cents
peaceful hailey hey jeremy i'm back from my vacation in texas today i'm about to go on vacation and
you're coming back uh wow i had a really good time i went to a convention i met chris sabat the voice
of vegeta and it really opened my eyes it made me realize how much i want to be a voice actress
i was debating it in my head uh you know like uh how i do do i really want this and doubting myself
about it and i want to give up on the dream but after meeting all these cool people maybe really
really really want it love you jeremy and chat yeah go for it do your best if it's something you
really want to do try it there's no reason not to try and do it that's the thing about dreams
they're great to have but they're even better to try and do as long as you're going with the
mindset that nothing is certain and always have a backup always have another plan you can make
your dream into something else always be realistic set goals for yourself and go for it i'm glad you
had a good time in texas and it's good to hear backup plan is gamble in vegas no not that kind
of backup plan hey smelly boy thanks for the 250 smelly boy coming in and it is uh it is just a
youtube link what is this youtube link um people eating fried chicken content aware it's a i don't
know what what the fuck is this content overscaling remix height fit this is just like giving me a
headache the video is shaking around and like underwater i mean this is the video but be careful
if you get if you get like sensitive to like underwater movies shaking uh thank you for the
video thank you smelly boy hey thank you to greg nightmare for the five dollars fifty cents
sam and max is my favorite adventure series of all time you have no idea how happy it makes me to see
anybody play it these days pogchamp yeah i think it's great i'm absolutely going to finish at least
season one i like the cartoon i like anything too you know so it's cool i knew i was going to
like it i just didn't have a spot to start it you know what i mean it's it's it's hard to
let's put it this way all right guys vr we're gonna do some crazy shit in vr are you ready oh
my god look at all this fucking crazy stuff in vr sakiro oh it's fucking so hard now i'm gonna
play sam and max it's just hard to place it because it's slowing it down it's a lot more
it's an experience that you let happen on in front of you it's not some you know crazy
ridiculous thing that i'm going to stream so it's hard to find a place to put it sometimes
but like i said i want to start to pull in more of these just hanging out and doing something
streams but it was always hard to place because it always like was either right before or right
after something that was like really high energy did he play episode three i left because he said
he wouldn't well i played like 40 minutes of episode three but it looks like people that
you know took this kind of stream well right because i'm always curious of what people think
or who how many people are going to watch what are they going to say is move on this is boring
right but i think it was it was great i thought it was great so you'll definitely see it again
uh thank you to the true michi for the three dollars jeremy just want to remind you you did
forget me again as i predicted you wanted to hit me up on discord mr forgetful i know i'm so
fucking bad i really am there's like a handful of people that i'm like supposed to contact on
discord and it's just like my mind is just wipes every time i really have like a fucking boomer
memory it's ridiculous even important shit even like in my own family and friends but i'm sorry
about that okay yeah stream legends i will don't worry before the stream ends is ace attorney still
on the to-do list or has been shelved it has been shelved temporarily until i find out if it's
something i want to stream i'm gonna have some time here over this mom vacation where me and
my mother gonna do a bunch of stuff but i'll have some free time i'm probably gonna play
a little bit of the first case and then determine if it's something i want to stream
because i when i went into that house i said i wanted to do it it was not the game that i
thought it was going to be it's a lot more elaborate it's like an investigative game where
you do like detective work i thought it was just kind of like a courtroom argument simulator but
that's not what it is it's like a 40 hour long game and i just want to make sure that i don't
what i don't want to do and i want to stop doing this and i've been i've been all right with it
recently is starting something that a lot of people want to see and then realize kind of
20 percent of the way through it that i really don't think i want to do it anymore and then
don't do it so i really want to start to pick and choose if you're gonna see a game that's on the
stream we're gonna try to complete it so i want to try to do that more we'll see but thank you
frody and weapon for the five dollars they say chao what's up fellow germa mites it's your boy
frody and back at it again with the drunk bit messages but seriously germa hope your mom has
a fun and safe trip to vegas you crack me up a little buddy yeah i will see you very soon
looking forward to it when you move to his thing when you move to a new city and you have friends
or family come over it's just awesome to kind of vicariously live through their new experiences
that you've already had but you get to watch them have it now oh we're gonna go to the strip oh
yeah hey well look at that that oh that's the villaggio ah yeah take a look at that and you see
them interact with it and we're gonna go downtown right there's there's something to be said about
showing somebody like a city or really anything can i take her to hash house a go-go probably
that's my favorite restaurant in the whole city but it'll be great jesse you got it thanks for the
250 jess a psycho analyst dream would be gold i'd love to hear what a professional has to say about
your dog shit enhanced dream i want to just go get like a full personality test done with the blots
with the ink stuff with the questions they would have to be comfortable doing that though because
i told you about the lie detector shit how people did not think that was cool
i think we have to i think that whole story is on video and we it's been watched a bunch of times
about how it was absolute hell to everybody hated us when we tried to get the lie detector thing
going there's a whole stream about how we were like avoided people thought we were like dicks
for like wanting to make like a comedic piece about lie detecting we called every fucking lie
detector you know firm or attorney in two or three states and they all fucking hated us so
you don't you never want to like be hey hey you're like a therapist or you're like a psycho
analyst or you're like a scientist hey we're gonna do a joke where like you analyze me on
stream funny huh and then they're like no it's not funny oh okay call somebody else
it's hard to do that but it's definitely worth a shot i think because you never really i mean
make a joke out of somebody's profession you know i'm saying that's not that's not what my
intentions ever are it'll be interesting that would be very interesting we'll see hey mobling
thanks for the 10 bucks thanks for playing one of my favorite series you check out san and max
hitting the road if you plan on doing more have a nice break with you mom thank you the 10
dollars mobling and if we're still going and san and max is still something people want to see
after season one and it's something that i'm having fun with and i'd like to do again we'll
just keep going i'll do them all because games like that i like games like that that give the
breaks in them better uh they more of a hangout session we can just kind of talk about whatever
the fuck we want they're fun ferocity and weapon thanks are 250 again here's some more bits to
fuel your obsession with money let me say lul thank you go to a fortune teller in vegas
uh see that's the kind of irl stream i want to do i want to do like go get psycho analyzed
go get your fortune told that's the kind of irl you'll see on this stream taking a lie detector
right uh adventure mf dan thanks for the five dollars hey germ i just got back from a trip
from vegas and i gotta say there was a severe lack of you impersonators i stood on the strip
for hours yelling germa 985 but nothing happened love you bud no not very many it's germa
impersonators i don't think very many people would want a picture with me but thank you hope
you had fun vegas is a very fun city lots to do tons to do hey gnarly thanks for the five
dollars gnarly 62 five bucks hey germa love your content thanks for being funny for the last five
years hopefully that doesn't change you make me laugh little streamer i hope you still think
it's fun and funny i'm gonna keep doing what i'm doing changing changing it up every now and then
adding things trying new things i hope you still do think it's interesting here's to another few
years five years just another five years let's see what happens don't you dare stop being funny
i'm just gonna i'm just gonna keep doing me and if that means people think it's cool and fun then
i'm gonna keep doing it i don't really know how to be anybody else there you go uh we also germa's
average dong and a bunch of other people gave a ton of community subs i think they were like more
than a couple there was like 150 200 community subs just tonight so that's out of fucking control
i'm sure when we do the credits here in a second you'll see they're probably going to scorch by
why don't we take a look here are all the new subs and resubs tonight and here they go sometimes
this goes so fast that and i've been here comes i'm gonna read them all you try to do that thank
you everybody thank you for the huge amount of community subs if even if not not even community
subs if you still have you just subbed to the channel for some reason you know it's not just
about the community subs it's about everybody a lot of you guys have been subbed on your own
for fucking three four years it's a long time to be supporting somebody in their channel and some
of you guys just decided you were gonna sub today because you wanted to thanks that means a lot i
hope you still think it's fun and i hope as the months progress i hope you still think it's worth
paying for thank you we also had four dollars four dollars from tank mr skeletal for the four
dollars yo germbo just wanted to let you know i've been a fan since 2012 and i'm leaving for basic
training on tuesday and your streams have helped me with the stress and anxiousness i've been dealing
with lately thanks germa hart i wish you the best of luck take care much love to you thank you for
being part of this community for so long we look forward to when you come back thank you for the
four dollars sorry five dollars actually because they also help you i hope you have fun on vacation
with your mom germa hart thank you i'll say it again much love to you take care of yourself
and thank you again for being a part of the community for that long that means a fucking
ton good luck at basic training we have a few more come in we have five dollars and ten cents from
uh ph from frike from pike mr pike we won't forget what are we not forgetting
we won't forget what are we what are we not forgetting oh you you oh okay right right right
okay i forgot oh shit i forgot about me now i don't i don't take i mean i think the longest
besides october because october was all the internet problems and moving across the country
right so i was gone for like you know in that balloon i was going for like three weeks but
before that i'm not sure i've ever at least streaming wise for the last three four years
i'm not sure i've ever been away for that long for more than like four or five six days in a row
maybe a convention or something so it'll be nice to kind of take some time you know everybody needs
time it doesn't matter who you are yeah when am i when am i going to come back probably friday
night is when i will stream again so like this coming next like friday before the weekend
and i'll be i'll be live friday uh the 26th oh wait that's wait that's fucking
i ain't gonna see that movie on opening night no we're gonna do like a i'm not seeing endgame
stream because i don't want to i don't go to movies on opening night i go like later and i'm
gonna that that stream is going to be in like fucking question marks only mode we are locking
that on because i'm seeing it in like a day or after that or so we're going to be in like
exc we're going to be in like exclamations and like you know what i mean we're going to be in
like this mode or you can only do symbols mode for that whole string not even emotes somebody's
going to put together spoilers with emotes they will put together a string of like 15 spoilers
as emotes you'll give they'll do it somehow people are smart and they're clever on this
platform they'll do it yeah like somebody will do a string of like emotes like that like sawdust
by you right it'll be like 12 15 emotes long nope symbols only on friday uh germa lied about guay
thanks for the five dollars love you jerry thank you guay appreciate it error paradox thanks to
the 250 have a good momcation we love and appreciate everything you do for us i wish
i could pay you back for years of content and laughs i'd pay you back by making you laugh but
bits is all i have well you don't have to pay me back because i'm allowed to do this i'm allowed
to go take my mother and live in las vegas and take a week off of work right because you guys
allow it you know like this is all here because you guys watch i'm able to do that because you
guys watch and i don't like to treat this like work it's not i don't treat this like a business
as much as it's to you know potential ups or downs financially right if i treat it like a business
maybe oh i'd make more money or something but i don't want to treat it like a business you're
fuck this was the interview but no i'm forever grateful that i'm about to have my mother come
into my new city and take her around and enjoy the town and hang out with her for a week
that's only possible because of of you and i'm talking about you yeah you that's right but
thank you error paradox you mean gamble no my mother doesn't gamble and neither do i it's
fucking it's stupid why would you ever do that no my mother doesn't gamble and neither do i
i eat celery and drink pineapple juice i don't do anything else i sit in a chair and i eat celery
i'm a good boy you just said you lost 100 bucks at roulette yeah that's not me i've changed as of
yesterday i sit there and i eat celery and i fucking read books reformed no i'm just
fucking around uh but thank you shalashka for the 250 hey germa uh king rajak came back and
he started a therapy hotline to talk with people about their issues and help them i don't know
if this is i don't know if this is crazy but i think you're really good at giving advice perhaps
you could collab you seem like the kind of person who likes to help people that's awesome that
they're doing that um but i've said the same thing about collaborations i've said in the past
i they just kind of happen i usually just do my own thing on this platform and on any platform
collaborations are they just sort of organically will happen with people that i
just you know randomly talk to or come across or hey is a project that i'd like to do
i don't really plan out my collaborations but that's pretty awesome that they're doing that
a lone rat is what he is rat solo for the most part yeah and we've gone over whole
20 30 minute segments of streams where i've talked about why
though not to be like a broken record or anything but yeah good for them though that's fucking great
do a cooking stream summer summer is gonna have so much shit on this channel you have no idea
summertime is gonna be like this is gonna be so many fucking things that are gonna be streamed
i can't wait it's gonna be great it's gonna be so much fun
coolest sniper thanks for the 250 enjoy your vacation i will i definitely will tyler mike
thanks for the 250 that's what i love about you and vinnie you don't treat us like a business
opportunity you treat us like family just hanging out playing video games yeah and i mean and look
when i when i started doing this on youtube and twitch i don't want to i don't care about
fucking like making a bunch of money that i'm already making a bunch of money you know
what i mean like i don't care that's not and it doesn't do it for me like i don't like it
i would rather have people enjoy the streams and want to be part of the community than
turn everybody into these money churning numbers that i present to fucking companies and present
to people to make as much money as i possibly can i don't care about that i never have and i
never will i just it's not i'm just the person that i am i'm not going to say that streaming
and turning your stream into a business and treating like a business and trying to make a
bunch of money on your business is is wrong or bad i just did something i don't do because when
when i used to watch stuff i didn't want to be treated as a viewer as a number that was just
kind of a way to make somebody money you know i wanted to be like ah this is a place i like to
watch and hang out and i don't even want you guys to feel like you're being used to make me more
money and it's not like and i know a lot of people have said that that wouldn't be the case but i
don't even know where the hell i would start with that br josh yeah he's talked about parasocial
before it's hard to be sociable with your viewers without some of them thinking that you are their
friend even though there's no way for a big streamer to really be a friend with all their viewers
yeah the the way that i've answered that question and talked about that is kind of like what you're
saying is instead of it being you and i are here and we're friends it's all of us are here it's
not a you and i scenario it's a collective community of people that all are here and we're
all around for the same things we are many you are vessel but that's kind of true though you know
that's kind of the way it is that's the way it kind of should be we are all collectively here
we are venom we are venom i'm pretty good at that too i've been pretty good at making
impressions today don't view yourself as a vessel no i mean i know that's a joke but
i'd rather us collectively enjoy things than have it be a personal one-on-one you and i
relationship i think it's healthier that way but to put a cap on that conversation no i i treat this
the same way i treated this when i started making youtube videos let's start with the a b and c a
do i want to do this today no then i'm not gonna do it i'll see you tomorrow do i want to do this
today am i like do i have something planned do i have something i want to do do i have something
fun to try or something yes oh yeah let's go b no no no no i'm not saying like that's the like
no i'm saying like on a day-to-day basis week-to-week basis it's not like do i do i want to do this no
not like the whole thing as a whole now you're stuck in abc no it's like do i want to do this
will i have fun and am i currently having fun while i'm doing it you know i answer that question
each stream i sit here before stream starts a day the day before day two days before what do i want
to do what could be fun let's try that do i want to do that yeah all right let's go let's do it
you sit here for two i sit in the chair for two days i don't move and i just end up falling
asleep my chin hits my chest and i fucking fall asleep and i wake up screaming
okay what are we doing yeah sometimes it's like a detriment right like for instance like i built a
bird house on this stream i just somebody was like wouldn't that be fun it's i don't i'm gonna
fucking do it i'm gonna do that i don't give a shit well that's what we're doing even if it might
not be like the best idea if i'd some build a labo while drunk it's just i'm gonna do it nothing else
is in that equation besides does that sound like fun to me do the ideas land completely every time
no that doesn't mean i'm gonna stop doing them absolutely not i've been watching the archive my
first live stream was they was the game referred house stream vr josh thanks a lot man like that
imagine that's your first drink yeah but that's i will i wanted to be fun because i want to have
fun too you know it's really it's a symbiotic relationship as a collective unit of people
because i want to have fun too i want to turn on the stream and i want to do something fun and i
want to interact and come up with shit and play off you guys what you guys are saying that you guys
having fun right that's that's why i want that's why i do this let's say yeah we go we go over this
frequently right because i obviously want to make sure i'm holding up that end of the bargain too
frequently and we have discussions and talk about hey stay to the channel how things going
i never wanted to be a bunch of people that are like no this sucks now i don't like it
i why would i want that i don't want did you say that like for real and i know like
we're gonna see it right now it's gonna be like oh this sucks right all right i don't but i don't
want that to be the case and when that gets to be the case that means i'm probably not fucking
having fun anymore and i'm doing it because i just to do it uh i'm doing because i fucking
like i have to right no no this i want this to stay just how it is i'm having fun are you having
fun do we have any interesting things we want to do yeah let's do them and that's the way it is
that's the way it's going to continue to be because that's the only way that i can stream
that's it i can't do it i can't do it any other way but we got two more bits to do well one more
actually but that was tyler mike for 250 and they talked about vinnie too and vinnie has has been a
at least in this kind of sense um that's been very inspirational to me the way that vinnie treats
his twitch channel when i was just starting out you know i had a youtube audience i had a large
youtube audience right we moved over here to twitch and i was i was looking around who's who
and who's doing what and what are they doing and the whole way vinnie doesn't treat his fans like
money numbers and doesn't read subs and i'm like that's interesting that's
why you know why why is that so that's one of the reasons why i like vinnie a lot you know he's
he gets it you know large with quotes what are you doing hey castle griffinstein has like
fucking two million views germa rumble live action got like a million views i'm a million
view youtuber i can say that grab that out of five has like six million views i'm a million view
youtuber i can say that i've been on the front page of reddit more than once i'm a million view
streamer i mean a million view i'm a million view youtuber and front page of reddit video maker
that's on my resume i swear to god i'll pull it up right now
it's gonna be the grandpa's gonna be doing this you should have seen when i was young
i had four videos got to the front page of reddit with 10 000 upvotes on them
what do you do now can somebody turn grandpa around he's talking at the wall again
just spin him around largest youtube community just ask anybody all fantastic people tremendous
videos very high quality i know what that is and like it's
largest youtube community just ask anybody all fantastic fantastic people tremendous videos very
high quality videos just great absolutely beautiful tremendous channel oh you guys are
fucking hilarious but all jokes aside though i did came over here with a group of people that
were watching the youtube videos and we started streaming and i didn't know who any of these
people were i knew some of them were just because they were so popular so famous to begin with
that everybody just knows their name right but no that's vinny's a great streamer vinny's a great
dude hung out with him multiple times but with that uh internet Jorge thanks for the 15 dollars
15 bucks coming in love you lots Jeremy you really are one of the most genuine and amazing
streamers around give you mother a kiss from me thank you have you seen the clip of Vinny
saying that he highly respects you yeah i mean we i've that's fucking incredible to hear that
right like it's anytime somebody sends me a clip of somebody saying something like that
i internalize it and i'm gonna go well is that is that real like i'm gonna make sure that's
actually am i is that true like should can i do better i'm always striving to do better and it's
it's it's an it's a it's an amazing feeling knowing that there's other people that think
so highly of you but i want to keep myself grounded as well because i want to make
sure that i can keep doing the things that people like about the channel and i think that if you get
too much into your own head about it that's how you start to have you can really get in your own
way but that means a lot it's it's it means a lot close this out got like a why do i have so many
tabs open but it is 2 a.m pacific i'm keeping so many people because it's very late for all of you
there's still a thousand people i'm not sure where you are if you're just waking up
or if you're just going to bed have a great one i will see you guys next weekend i'm going to take
some time off vacation i'm going to change i'm going to stream legends feed everybody
take care of yourselves guys uh don't forget about me i'm still around
i still probably i'll probably pop in the discord and give you like a mom update you know
i'm gonna do stream legends and then we're going to bed keep an eye on the sus i will update it to
the day i would keep keep an eye put put your ear to the ground somewhere around like wednesday or
thursday of this coming next week because then i'll have a good indicator of exactly when i'll be live
again probably friday but you'll see a good indicator around wednesday or thursday let me
get to stream labs not stream labs um stream legends i'll see you guys real soon extensions
my extensions there you go three two one stream legends how's the guild doing we doing good
we are we like one of the highest guild levels on the platform would better be
i've been i've been dumping gifts here no i'm just kidding the guild is falling apart what
all right this is gonna this is gonna be the last thing you guys hear me say for a week
i guess i'm gonna make it count right i gotta make this count i'm not gonna say i'm not gonna
see you for a week see you later have a great week take care i get the last thing you're gonna
hear me say