Hello, how's it going? How's it going? He was saying you're late. Yeah, let's clear the record here though.
Well, let's clear my throat first and then we'll get into that. I was gonna stream on Friday, but I got the day wrong.
So I pulled it back to Thursday and then I decided, you know what? No, I'm pulling it back again. We're going on Wednesday.
And here we are. I said I was gonna be around three. It's a little after three, but I reverse delayed, reverse delayed into a small minor delay.
I think that's fair. That's fair. You said Friday. Yeah, well, whatever. I'm here now. And it ain't Friday. I know. That's fine.
That's fine. That's a skewed concept of fair. Well, instead of having to having to wait two full days, you only had to wait 35 minutes.
That's fair for a stop. Your schedule has given me trust issues. Well, I guess the let me ask a question.
Is there a been be honest with me? Be very honest with me because I've been thinking about this for a while and and drop some names.
I'd love to hear them. I'm curious. Do you know of a streamer that is on time?
90 percent of the time, like a streamer that's like, OK, guys, you know, Thursday, I think I'm going to start streaming around like to who is always on time.
No matter what, they're always on time. I feel like most streamers are like 10 to 20 minute late, Andy's all of us.
You're literally the only one I'm not. That's no way. I'm definitely not the only one that's 10 plus minutes.
And I have a defense, though. I don't have a starting soon screen.
I have I do. But my starting soon screen means that I'm here right now.
And the starting soon screen is at most maybe 60 seconds before I start talking.
Maybe a minute total. I don't have a starting soon that last 10 plus 20 plus minutes.
That is copium, but it's I think that's good copium. I think that's good copium.
You are a lying prick. Hey, damn, geez. No, no, let's hear about he has a point.
That's what I'm talking about. Yeah, we got the founders coming in.
We got the founders coming in. When are you going to do a Bugleberry mukbang?
Yeah, that should be kind of funny. It's wicked fucking gross shit.
It's just like would not. It's just weird. It's just weird food items.
When's Otto's adventure remake? When are you going to do the beach episode for your channel?
The beach episode? That's so funny.
Damn, that's a good one. That's such a good one, too.
Just do a sitcom level beach episode, but it's just a regular stream and it's only it's it's 22 minutes long.
I should just do an entire an entire tournament arc until I ruin the channel and nobody watches.
You know what I mean? Like I should have a like three month long tournament arc where you know I'm going to win.
You know I'm going to win the tournament and you have to watch like 70 other people lose before I just win it.
And there's a ton of drama every time I get up there, but there's no way I lose.
I'm just not going to in the end. You know it.
You know that at some point I will be in the finals no matter what happens.
End it with a time skip. Yeah.
Holly, end it with a time skip that. Oh, my God. That's so right.
There's one thing I will promise you. There will be a point.
There will be a point where I just I'm just going to do whatever the fuck I want here.
And like it's going to be detrimental to the channel.
You know what I'm saying? Like it's going to happen eventually where it's just like whatever.
I'm going to do a fucking month long tournament arc and then do a time skip and just ruin the whole channel.
You know what I mean? Like who cares? At some point, let's just do it for fun. Who cares?
You do this already? Right now, he says. Right now, he says you do this now.
Well, whatever. That's fun to me.
There's also other things that I really want to just do that I think would just be fun to do.
I want to say this so bad, but somebody will steal it and I can't have this stolen.
I this is going to be so funny.
And I know, oh, my God, he's saying his own material is funny.
No, this is this is the funniest thing I've ever seen. I've ever heard of.
Now, that's a lie. That's actually like egomania.
But I don't want anyone to know this idea because I really do think you're going to steal it.
Oh, it's the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life. I'm going to puke blood.
I got to dial it back a little. I got to I got to like dial it down a little bit here.
What if it's not fun? Yeah, that's the thing. That's that's also true.
A lot of times when I when I have an idea for something, I don't usually talk about it at all.
Because in the event that I get to the stage where I actually really am doing it and I go, this sucks.
This is awful. Then you didn't know about it.
And it wasn't funny. You guys are only seeing the things that I really thought
were going to make it to that point that were really interesting.
Lots of other stuff has fallen through that you did not hear of that you did not see.
We need our show failed idea stream.
There's a lot of you know, there's also things, too, that I think would be really, really interesting for 10 seconds.
And the problem with hiring a production crew
and spending a bunch of money on what amounts to 15 seconds,
a lot of times does not turn out to be worth doing, which kind of sucks
because there's a lot of like 30 second material that I would love for you to see.
But eventually it's just like, OK, that was oh, my God, that was I loved that.
All right. That's all I had to say today.
These would be explosive on YouTube short ticked. Oh, yeah.
Just move. Just do tick tocks.
No, upload it to YouTube, then do a variety show.
But long story short, I know we were playing Devil May Cry,
but I love the little I love the little little micro jokes.
They work so much for me. Depends.
But yeah, how do we even get on that? I don't even know.
How did I why did I start talking about that?
All right. TLDR. I wish I had one hundred million dollars
because I would just I would do one of these every day.
That's it. But unfortunately, I don't have that.
I would be it would be very really if I were too much, though.
You do. I do not. I do.
No, I do not. You don't have a billion.
No, I don't. Sorry to say play the game already.
I get my 10 to 15 minutes before starting a video game.
This is time for me to tell you about my day.
And then I will shut up and move on to the game.
But this is my 10 minutes here. I get the floor.
I get the floor before I wheel in the TV for us to watch in school here.
OK, it's been 20 minutes. It has been it has been 12 minutes total.
Come on. All right. Let's go. Silence.
Insolent viewers. Yeah, true.
Does it ever scare you how many people watch your streams?
No, no, not really.
I think that we terrify him.
What a terrifying thing.
I have a question for all the Dante's Inferno enthusiasts out here.
Should I just play on easy and just grind souls?
Is that an easy way just to get some extra money?
Why are you doing that voice again? What voice?
I'm not doing a voice. Why am I doing? I'm not doing a voice.
I just talk sometimes in different inflections when I'm talking about different things.
Just go still stay on normal. You have milk voice again.
I do not have milk voice. I know what it is.
I know what it feels like. Is this too loud?
Hard to tell over here. OK. Oh, no, we saw this, didn't we?
We'll watch it again. It's fine.
Turn up the volume. I will.
We can't hear shit. I'll turn it up.
Imagine being in a movie theater and the movie is like 10 percent volume.
How long is it going to take before somebody says that?
Hey, we can't hear shit. Turn it up. What the fuck?
Five minutes. What do you think?
It would take two seconds.
It would probably take at least five minutes.
Now, that would be really funny if for some reason the volume was turned way down in a theater.
And that was that old was it THX that sound effect.
Imagine that played at like five percent volume.
It would not hit hard at all. It would be kind of funny, actually.
Is an audio delay there? I don't think so.
Do you want to think you know what I think is the most important thing in any piece of media?
I mean this with my deepest heart.
Audio mixing is probably the most important thing.
Having audio be correct in a movie with different levels of how they're talking and different sound effects and music.
How loud there is such a fine line between this music is a little louder versus the movie is ruined now.
It's the audio delay. I don't have what I don't have. I don't see one.
What you have ruining it right now. I didn't do it.
Look, there's no delay. There's no delay. I'm fine.
The subtitles were ahead. It's very common in the film.
This person had a decent take. Let's see.
You can carry the piece very far. It's very common in film and video industry that if you have a good sound person.
Oh, yeah. Sound is even something you don't even think of like when like a bird flies by.
You even hearing like when it flies by very, very faintly at like almost like not even one dB, like minus like 15 dB.
That makes the whole scene.
You've seen something that has like had like big rock music behind it and you take the music out and it just looks weird and just looks fucked up.
And just like what the hell am I watching? This looks stupid.
Sometimes action sequences without something behind it or really good sound and music mixing.
It's kind of like this like looks weird. I don't like I'm watching a movie right now. All right, let's go.
It feels empty. Yeah, I don't think I need to change anything.
Let's just go. Okay. I had my delay. I had my stall. It amounted to 15 minutes.
Okay, everybody's going to scream at me.
Oh, the last thing I did, I just beat that and tested monster thing, whatever it was.
Okay, and now I'll turn the volume up. That should be good.
Let me know if it's better to be where it was last night.
All right, I'm ready to play Dante's Inferno. Free order now.
Use the new weapon. I will in like a few years.
It's a weird place to be fighting in a few years and a few in game years.
This works kind of like dog years.
Every second that you and I are seeing is like in their universe.
It's about like two months. You didn't know that.
What did you think I was talking about? God damn it.
This game takes place in one day.
I have you. Have you seen the movie? Did you read the book?
I mean, clearly not. Oh, man.
Chill. I'm sorry. I just said something.
How am I supposed to respond to that?
I'm in a fucked up mood today.
You can always tell when there's a reverse delay.
This is a little bit of insider information for you.
If I tell you that, oh, hey, reverse delay, I'm streaming today instead.
You need to know that it's because you know what?
Today I'm feeling I feel like I am ready today and I'm ready to go right now.
I'm in one of those moods. Felt a little froggy. That's right.
Sometimes you just don't. You're not in that mode.
All right. Where am I supposed to go here? Down here?
I'm not. Am I missing something?
How long do you think you would spend in a bouncy castle?
Zero minutes. Wait, hold on. I didn't even see this.
This is a whole nother way to go. I didn't even see it.
No, I want the. All right. If you want the real answer, fine.
How long would I spend in a bouncy castle?
What do you guys think is the amount of time that it would be?
Hey, there's there's an adult in the bouncy castle
and it's been more than X amount of time.
Like, like, hey, like, who is it? Who's in the bouncy castle right now?
Oh, nobody. Just Uncle Frank is in there.
Just that's it. Just Uncle Frank went in. OK. All right.
All right. Uncle Frank is in there.
How long is Uncle Frank allowed to be in there before the family kind of gets together and is like
Uncle Frank's been in there for more than X.
I think it's probably five minutes.
It's definitely five minutes, two days.
Uncle Frank is camping in the bouncy castle.
Let him bounce. I need to get that item.
Stop being politician, Andy. Just answer the goddamn question, coward.
I am. Not every question.
There needs to be context with this question.
How long would OK. All context removed.
If I if they gave a bouncy castle just teleported behind me and it was just there.
OK. How long do you want to be in there for?
I would say 10 minutes there. I answer your question.
Ten minutes total, maybe.
And then you'd be like, OK, I don't want to be in there anymore.
I'm done. I just got a new thing.
What is that? Oh, I got a new weapon, too. Let's try it.
You're really going to stay in there five minutes more than Uncle Frank.
Really? That's kind of not all right.
Oh, god damn it. Yeah.
How can we get to stay in there?
You all yelled at me when I was in there for five minutes.
You don't see how long Jeremy's been in there for.
How come he gets to stay in there?
All right. Well, this is obviously the right thing.
But how does this work? OK.
Tune up. Special stands used to link into certain combo attacks.
Press Y while on the ground so that you switch the stance over.
Keep the left stick neutral and press Y while in tune up mode.
Devon is super complicated.
You need to dump like 30 K just for it to be functional, and it's super hard to use.
Why is it that every instrument item in every video game is always the coolest one,
but it's always the most complicated? You need a PhD to use it one.
It always feels like that, doesn't it?
Still cool, though. What about the gun?
What is this thing? Normal shot.
Oh, just kind of like a cannon. How does it work?
Ooh, this thing might be good.
All right. Let me just use this enough to do this.
Yeah. All right. I got it.
This seems kind of cool.
I have no idea what he's doing.
Oh, you have to have a certain power. I got it.
I don't think I want to use it, though.
It does seem a little complicated. He seems to get to stand still a lot.
Go back to those. Oh, yeah.
Ooh, wait a minute. Should I?
Somebody just rocked back in their chair and was like,
Hurry the fuck up.
Go on already. Please.
No, no, just play. Please. God.
So what? Let me look at this.
Hmm. I think this is probably kind of good, I think.
I don't know.
Okay, we're going. I'm going. I swear.
I'm going. Look, we're here. We're playing.
God damn it. I can't stand it.
And you just got a little too mad, didn't you?
Mom just opened up the fucking door.
Said, You're grounded.
What?
Fucking Jerma.
Getting me grounded.
Can't go over that.
I can't believe you got me grounded.
Have you ever been grounded before?
Who hasn't been grounded before? Okay.
Oh, he's a noob.
I'm trying to think if my mother or father ever were like,
Jeremy, you're grounded.
I don't, I don't think so.
You're grounded.
Why? Okay. What's happening right now?
Are these protected? Is that freedom?
Okay, it is. It is.
These enemies are kind of annoying.
What is my? What?
I didn't even come close.
The lock on circle is also the enemy health bar.
It's really good to know.
Okay, we're good. Go.
So what's game progress here?
I was here last night already.
I had the camera angles, so scuff.
Because this is a PS2 game.
And it operates under the Mario 64 philosophy of
you can tilt your camera just enough until the game hates you.
Wait, oh, there we go.
I can, sometimes I can actually adjust the camera to go behind me,
but it doesn't happen every time.
I need to look at the map for a sec.
Where am I, where am I actually supposed to be going?
Because all the way down here is where I killed that lady was here.
Alright, so where to now?
Back to the main hallway and go in one of these doors in the middle.
I guess just keep going.
There's a map. There is a map, but I don't.
There's two doors I haven't gone in, right?
In the top left and top right of the circle here.
He hates streaming.
This game's classic.
I'm just going to go in this, where am I?
What do I end up in here?
Okay, so now if I go up, I'll be back in that big room.
Did you get grounded for taking your whole PC into the bathroom?
Um, no.
Where am I now?
Okay, yep.
Let's keep going.
No, I didn't get grounded for that.
I'm not going to hit me.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Is there shit out of me here?
Everything just jumps away from me.
I go to attack something and it just leaps across the whole map.
God, just die already.
Stop.
Set the game on easy already.
Hey, I've made it to Chapter 10 on normal in six hours.
I'm good, I'm good.
Okay, here we go.
Special power.
Oh, shit.
I didn't get the special power?
Did I really not get the special power?
It will be under items.
Stone mask?
What is this?
It's not it.
So where does this go?
Part rivers.
Is there...
I need to use that at a waterfall or something?
That would make sense.
Part water.
From here, I go up this way.
That's where I need to go?
Yes.
Here, the water.
There's water here.
No, wait.
Why am I...
Really?
I wish the indicator on the map showed where I was actually standing.
Because that yellow indicator to me is like, oh, that's where you currently are standing.
But it's...
Is it?
It's kind of like...
I don't know, it's weird.
Go this way?
No.
So is it this door back here?
I'm just trying to get to the middle room again.
I want to get into the middle room because there's two doors I haven't tried to open.
But this is weird.
Why can I not do this?
Because that's the only door that is listed here.
But is there one here?
This is where I came from.
So I should...
If I go in this door, I should be in this spot.
Okay.
So this door should connect to the...
But I can't go this way because I need the elevator to go that way.
Or that...
Open this door.
I need to go all the way around to go through here?
Somebody just tell me where to go.
I have no idea where I'm going.
Because I wanted to get to this middle room, but I can't go that way.
So do I have to go all the way around and walk all the way around?
No, help.
No, yes, help.
Help me.
Play the game.
Yeah, it's a PS2 game though.
Sometimes it's just like, oh, find this random obscure thing that is good.
You're going to walk around for 40 minutes to find it.
Wait.
I am in here.
Hold on.
But I can't...
Okay.
Yeah.
I cannot go this way.
So I just have to go all the...
I should just literally restart the save file.
It's the place before the boss fight.
Yeah, but I picked up the mask.
Where does the mask even go?
I guess I'm just going to go all the way around.
Whatever.
You're too busy talking about bouncy castles?
Not really though.
I got item B.
I need to place item B into pedestal X.
But I don't know where pedestal X is.
The long and short of it.
It's back where you missed the guitar.
So I just have to go all the way back around.
Okay.
All right.
So this is water.
I mean, there's only literally...
There's only literally two places where I could go do this.
So I guess let's see if it's in here.
Can't like...
Can't it be like the water or something to go over there?
It has to be right here.
It worked.
Is that not correct?
500 IQ.
I mean, there's no indication of where I'm supposed to go.
It just says, here you got an item.
The white glowing wall in this room?
I thought this was a statue.
Other lights like this have existed.
This white light here was in like a dozen other rooms.
Give me a break.
We've walked by statues like that a dozen times already.
That would be the 13th time then.
That light has shown up a thousand times.
Okay.
This is for the main bridge.
It's a granny game.
It's not a granny game.
So the main bridge is the one...
I don't think that...
Was there a spot I could put this in?
Milk brain.
It is a granny-like.
It kind of actually is a granny-like, but there's just nothing chasing me.
So I already got this one.
Where's the main bridge?
Does it say it on it?
The rotating bridge is in there.
So I just have to go back.
Is that where that thing goes?
That's where I couldn't power the device before?
Whatever it was.
And am I even going the right way?
I just don't even know what direction north or south even is.
I wish I had a compass or something.
Give me a compass.
Give me any indication of what direction I'm facing.
Okay.
And all the way around.
How did you forget already?
Because putting short-term into long-term memory is almost impossible for me to do.
It is very difficult.
With no guide system.
It's actually really hard for me to put into longer-term memory.
Especially when it's a very similar-looking landscape.
It's actually pretty hard for me to do.
Okay.
But we are there now.
I just have to go this way, right?
Because that...
Yes, it's this way, right?
Yes.
Because of the spider room.
And you fight the spiders.
And you go this way.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also too, you can blame the video game industry.
Because the video game industry in the last 10 to 20 years has made it impossible for you to not know where you're going.
So when that's what you're used to for decades after this kind of concept here.
The video game industry now is just like, make sure that they have absolutely...
They cannot get lost no matter what.
Back 20 years ago, it was like, good luck, you fucking dumbass.
You got to remember where that ball goes.
That was...
Yeah, I just realized how he just did that.
All right, so it can be moved.
All right, let's go.
Hey, we made it.
It only took us like 30 minutes to get to this next part.
He butchered innocent people too.
He's the most vile kind of creature.
Yahoo!
We have something in common.
I have a dysfunctional family too.
And what would you know about family?
You're a demon.
This is my father.
My family.
This was all supposed to end by my hand.
How are they missing at point blank range?
Aren't you going to shoot?
It's kind of a Capcom thing, isn't it?
That's a switch.
Like they do that frequently.
I don't care anymore.
Jesus, that was so much louder.
All right, well, that's going to be high.
And we knew that was going to be high.
Oh, that's bad.
No, this doesn't count.
This is an issue because I didn't end the chapter.
All right, listen, it's really important.
I didn't end the chapter.
When we played last night, I beat the boss.
I just kept running.
That's why it was an issue here.
Okay.
Won't happen again.
You're still alive, I see.
Is that you?
What's happening?
Where's your mother?
Mother?
You killed her, remember?
Yes, that's right.
The thing I've done was to succumb to his influence.
This is what it's going to be like when we have more microplastics in our blood.
True.
He's attempting to bring the demon world back.
The world that Sparda once sealed off.
Sparda thought he was a myth.
Flot twist?
What the fuck?
I thought he was the bad guy.
Stop him.
I one regret his talking in an evil voice and wearing evil clothes.
If only I presented myself differently.
All right, let's go.
Time for revenge.
All right, make sure I check my surroundings.
Lock it in a memory.
Get it in a long-term memory.
That hallway was right there.
I am now facing south in this room.
There's only one of the door.
It's not this one on the left side.
You've got it.
I don't know where I am.
Okay, cool.
Can I do anything with this spherical device here?
Why did you play Resident Evil 4 on normal and not hardcore?
You still on that?
You still upset by that?
I don't know.
I wanted it to be an approachable kind of challenging, but not really.
But focus on the game.
I don't know.
That felt like it.
How does that sound?
I'm not upset.
I'm just disappointed.
Yeah.
Well, it's going to be fine.
Don't worry.
Because I'm going to first try this boss.
I'm going to look over and see a ton of Pog use.
It's going to be crazy.
Where are you coming?
That's the way to deal with these.
Just shoot them.
Oh, doesn't.
Don't you just want to make the devil mad?
Oh, doesn't it just make the devil mad?
Freakish looking faces are etched into the statue.
Center face is tears of blood streaming down its face.
All right.
The middle one has tears of blood.
Where are we standing right now?
We are in this room.
This room is the one with the bloody eye statue.
Bloody eye statue in this room that has these six on it.
Are we looking for a bloody eye statue?
I would guess.
Can I do anything with this?
Does one of these have tears of blood?
I don't see it.
Be up.
How do I run up walls?
I know I can, right?
This is like sticking out.
Oh, I'm looking for bloody eyes.
I wasn't looking for a place to jump up.
Oh, I found it.
It takes a second.
Can I push?
Can these be broken?
There are two doors.
OK.
This door is a little too small for me.
I have to push it into that door.
Can you push?
There's one over here.
OK.
What?
I just tried to do that with the other one.
This is a PS2 video game and you tell me it doesn't have the lean the shoulder down animation
that goes pushing something.
I hope I've got this lined up right.
Mind bending puzzles.
I love the earth exploding rat movie 2 sound effect.
Where's my style?
Sweet.
Oh, what?
Oh, I accidentally.
Is that the pizza tower orphan of cost scream?
I don't think it is.
Maybe it is.
OK.
I don't.
I don't think it is.
Where are we?
OK.
We're still in this room.
Another part of it, too, is going room two, room three, room four without looking at the
map.
So then it's like I don't put into memory where I even am.
But I'm doing that now.
Look, I'm getting better.
How's the audio?
Do audio need to be dropped like 5 percent?
We good?
A little loud?
Is it all?
We good?
Can't wait to.
Oh, I wanted that.
OK.
Can't wait for Bugleberry the musical to come out.
Stop.
Sing the song.
Uh, this one that goes.
Yeah.
I was the one that you wanted.
I'm a super beast.
Nice.
This game looks like it's kind of fun.
I would agree with you.
I think this game is kind of fun.
You can check it out.
How come?
Why is it?
You know what I'm really not happy with?
Cerberus only has two upgrades.
Everything else gets three.
Some some get four.
What's up with that?
Change the sword master.
I'm going to lose my dodge, but it's all right.
I think I've gotten used to the A dodge.
I think I'm OK with using it.
It's front loaded because it's the second weapon.
That makes sense.
All right.
What now?
Does that change what I can do?
If I go into my.
Where is it here?
What menu is it under?
So does that add anything to Cerberus?
Yes, I do that all the time.
I do this all the time.
Yep.
Windmill satellite.
Spin your nunchucks around your body, devastating all enemies around you.
Ooh.
What's the type two combo for Cerberus?
Why?
Pause.
OK.
So why?
Why?
Pause.
Ah, yeah, ah, ah.
Ha ha ha.
Ha ha.
Ha.
Enough.
Ahh.
There it is.
OK.
So the pause is actually pretty long, tell you what.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's boom.
Boom boom.
Boom boom boom boom.
suite.
Four of course.
Boom.
So what does that one do?
That's the style button.
Right as circle.
Oh.
That's what I'm doing.
An angel.
Br e you need to do that, boy.
I'll tell you what, next time I'll try and wear some cologne, okay?
It's the stench of betrayal.
The odor of that accursed sport.
I love voices like this and it's like half the characters in the game.
I want to do these voices.
Oh, I don't have a dodge roll.
I'm trying to dodge roll around this.
Whoops.
Oh shit, what?
He hit me with his stun.
I stunned him and it hurt me.
Oops.
Alright, so I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's actually kind of hard to do those super combos during bosses.
Because they kind of just hit you out of them.
Alright, I think I did alright for a first try.
Let's go.
Dammit.
Sorry.
Let's go!
Oh shit.
Oh!
What's he doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Oh my god.
Jesus!
Ow.
Whoa!
Geez.
Oh my god, that's a huge area.
You just have to run.
I'm dead.
Okay.
Alright, so his phase two, he says crush.
And then a gigantic AOE explosion happens underneath his feet.
You gotta be careful.
One weapon, Andy.
Let's not start switching around before I know his moves.
That shouldn't hurt you.
He's staggered and his arms can be...
His LEDs on his arms hurt you.
Alright, here we go.
Here comes his bullshit.
No jump!
Watch out!
Stop jump!
What the fuck?
Stop jumping, man!
Get me out of the corner!
No!
Try to get that range.
Oh, it sucks.
God damn it.
What?
Oh, it's alright.
When you lock on and you do the Diablo walk.
I just want to get in there, but I have to do the Diablo walk.
Oh shit!
I tried to dodge, but I had my button.
My hand was on like four different buttons.
Oh shit!
I tried to dodge, but I had my button.
My hand was on like four different buttons.
Fuck no!
I'm throwing it so hard now.
I was actually...
My fingers were on four different buttons.
I couldn't dodge.
Oh my god.
I had...
I had my index finger holding right trigger.
My left finger is on the stick.
I have to press left trigger to switch to this other weapon.
I have to then press right trigger.
I've got one, two, three, four...
I've got five buttons being pressed at the same time.
Start it over.
I'm playing Bop It with Devil May Cry in my hands.
That was such a good start too.
I threw it away.
I just threw it in the trash.
That shouldn't hit you.
They should patch it.
They should patch the game.
God damn it.
What?
Such an awful camera for this to be right now.
Please change it.
How do I make sure...
How do I force this to happen?
I have to just get him in this corner.
I jumped over it.
It's killing me.
I'm starting over.
I feel like I'm going to eventually be pressing every single button on the controller and
I'm going to get an error message from Microsoft.
I'm going to hold left trigger, left bumper, then his right bumper, right trigger, Y, X,
and B at the same time.
And it's going to go...
And it's going to turn my fucking computer off.
I'm accidentally going to hit start and then press that combination and it's going to reset
the game like these old games used to do.
Turn this camera.
Turn this camera around now.
I hate that move.
It's so unfair.
Start over.
Please just do it.
The devil trigger heals.
Not very much.
I got to get to phase two with like 80% health.
Press R3 to reset your camera.
Yeah, it doesn't work half the time though.
I feel like it works when I'm out of combat, but when in combat it just doesn't work anymore.
I've been trying to do it.
What?
No, it does it every time.
All right, we're good.
Jump.
What?
Oh my God.
It's so unbearable.
What the fuck?
All right, here we go.
What's that?
What the fuck?
What is that?
What does that move?
Oh my God.
Okay.
Do I have any heals?
What does this do?
Do I need more of these?
I have.
Okay.
I've got heals.
I'm doing it.
It's not my inventory.
So, but okay.
If you can't use this item right now, it does not have heals.
It does not have heals.
Okay.
Devil star just refills ET.
So, just use it.
Do a crazy combo.
Use it.
Do it.
Just train it together.
I'm buying this.
I'm buying it again.
Did that just potentially fix everything?
That's a lot more than I had before.
Finally.
Holy shit.
I thought, I thought everyone was yelling at me not to buy things from the item menu.
I thought it was only for, only put it in your moves and weapons.
I thought I was going to be stupid for doing that.
I thought everyone was going to make fun of me.
Shit.
Oh, that was a stupid mistake from me.
And yep.
All right.
Let's go.
What?
Do you just, how do you get away from that?
Does that move completely unavoidable?
Oh my God.
This is so bad.
I have to hold down to dodge in that angle.
Contextually needing to pick a different direction to dodge to get it to do the right dodge.
Oh, it's making me want to puke.
So to dodge, you have to, you have to, you have to dodge laterally.
So if the camera is not behind you, a lot of times you have to hit down and A to do a lateral dodge versus left and right and A.
Or it just changes constantly to do a lateral dodge.
What the heck?
To do this, to do what I'm doing here, I have to like press down, but sometimes when you press down, you do a backflip.
Because your character turned around and you were locked on and the camera didn't turn around with you.
So a down actually turns out to be a lateral dodge.
This is freaking ridiculous.
And I'm sorry.
I said a swear word.
I keep, he catches me with it every time.
Oh my God.
Thank God.
I was in this mode.
Wow.
That move sucks.
Jesus.
My controls are backwards.
I don't want to fight them that way.
God damn it.
What is happening?
Oh my God.
Please.
Oh no.
I just pissed him off.
Oh, that sucked.
That was not good.
That was very bad.
That move.
I don't have any heals.
Turn it on quick.
Yes.
That fight was kind of rough.
So dodging like this and going backwards, but back to dodge backwards, it's up.
And when he's this way, you got to, it's like this way down.
It's, it's like patting your head and a, and rubber your stomach at the same time.
All right.
We're good.
Side roll suck.
You got to unlock and jump.
Yeah.
I've been conditioned from every from software game.
Unfortunately, just run back and just let go and run back.
Yeah.
I'm playing against the, there we are.
Okay.
We're back in it now.
From software brain rot.
You're not going to shoot me.
Are you?
If you do, you know, if that's what it takes to shut you up.
It's the crap.
Don't act so rashly, my boy.
I've got a doozy of a story for you, but if you snuff out my voice like that, I won't
be able to tell it now.
Will I?
You saw it too, didn't you?
That huge tower just above us.
It's really making me angry.
Everyone's saying this is me.
I'm like, no.
It sucks to have to know that.
Like that's real.
It actually is.
Like, yeah, I can't fight that.
I can't deny that.
Maybe not that part.
Try that laugh out.
No, no, I just won't play.
I can't.
Because it's going to be cringe inducing.
Let me get this to level two.
I want to level this up to two.
I'm curious about it.
All right.
He who holds this broken device is irradiated
and their soul is drained in exchange for power.
Oh, I got to go.
Where do I go?
Where do I need to go?
Oh, no.
Sweet.
Blow up.
Got it.
We're good.
This game would have given me an ulcer when I was a kid.
Hold on.
Come on.
Get it right.
I got to get it right.
What?
What's happening?
I'm losing it.
I just freaked out.
I'm freaking out.
I can't fucking get it back.
I thought it was S.
What is it?
I'm dead.
It's higher than S?
Jesus.
Press B.
Oh, I got a new orb.
Nice.
Right.
I forget what style I'm on half the time.
Got to help.
What's going on?
What was that, dude?
What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
What?
What was that?
Oh, my God.
What?
What was that?
Why did the game just do that?
You got to be kidding me.
That fucking hurt big time.
What?
Why did that just happen?
Whoa.
That was actually fucked up.
Is that a bug in the game that that can happen?
No way.
Wow.
That sucked.
I was at.
Hopefully that wasn't too bad for everybody else.
I think that was really bad.
Oh, my God.
Why the fuck did that happen?
Jesus.
Whoa.
Is everybody all right?
Like, I'm serious.
That was actually really, really bad.
Everybody like doing all right because that sucked.
I'm terrified.
I'm like scared to play the game now.
Is that weird?
Dude, it's the fucking HD remake.
Yeah.
What the fuck was that?
Really?
What was it?
I don't know.
It was something with the game.
I wish I could tell you what just even happened.
Because look, I mean, take a look.
The volume should never should not be even possible to go that high.
Even over here in my in my OBS, I have the mic.
So this is coming through desktop audio.
So desktop audio is set to I have it limited.
There's a limiter on it.
And in the game, it's only at halfway.
That was extreme.
Did you hit your mic?
No, no, that was in the game.
That was in this video game.
Fuck.
That's not cool.
It's a glitch on this level.
I've had that happen before.
Oh, OK.
Actually patch the game, Capcom.
Actually patch the game.
What?
Is that actually possible to happen here?
Dude, I am so fucked up right now.
Is it still count that I got this?
I don't want to hit the enemies.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing this till we're confirmed.
This is not going to happen again.
The shit is at five, not even three percent.
The game's muted.
Yeah.
This is the room that it happened in.
I'm not having that happen again.
I.
Oh, my God.
I'm like shook from that.
I'm going to like die again.
That's just run.
I don't think I'm going to make it.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm just going to run next time.
Wait, can I not?
Yeah, I'm going to have to like highlight this VOD and re-uploaded or something, because
I'm not having people deal with that.
That's so fucking awful.
No, I'm going to have to like do an edit to the VOD.
Can I just leave?
OK, I can.
I think I just run.
All right.
So where do I need to?
Where am I trying to get to?
Back to the beginning, right?
Come on, hurry up.
Fuck.
I don't know where to go.
Shit.
I don't have any healing.
Oh, that's bad.
All right.
I need heals, but wait, I'm at full health.
This is actually good.
That clip was blasted out.
But yeah, that's I know I take really seriously stuff like that, because I always people always
ask, hey, dude, your your game volume is kind of quieter.
This is kind of quiet.
The amount of shit that gets through the cracks in some of these games or that can blow out
people's fucking speakers.
I try to reduce it as best as I can.
But man, oh, man, something like that happening is just like, holy fucking shit.
No, where am I going?
I'm going the wrong way.
You should watch the clip.
Hold on.
We're in a cut scene.
But listen to the clip right now.
God, let me see.
Hey, is that even possible?
Why?
No, that's actually not all right.
I'm being dead serious.
I just listened to this at like one percent.
That's not all right.
Is that actually a bug in the game?
Because like, you got to be fucking kidding me.
No, I've played it.
I've never had this happen.
Dude, we know you farted.
This is the PC version.
Yeah, this is the Steam HD version.
Oh my goodness.
I mean, how?
Why did that?
I don't even have an explanation for you.
Is there something on my end?
I don't think so.
Not that I could see.
I mean, I've been sitting here playing it the same way since like, you know, two, three
hours ago since last night.
Restart the game?
Yeah, I'm going to restart the game.
The whole HD collection has audio bugs from what my understanding.
An HD edition only bug.
Are you in a Discord call?
No, no, I'm not.
All right.
Let me restart the game to get like the audio kind of recombobulated.
And one of the some of the mods have editing access.
Can some because I can't really do it right now while I'm live.
Can one of the mods go and do a highlight of the stream like two or three seconds before
that part?
And then I'm trying to think how to do this to get rid of that.
I'll finish the mission.
Yeah.
But this is staying on like one percent.
Highlight before and after and then we'll delete the VOD.
Right.
I'm going in the wrong direction.
What a sound warning.
Yeah.
I mean, a sound warning for a kind of a jump scare or something is one thing, but I just
listen to that.
I've and I've been jump scared.
I've had loud shit happen on this stream.
That's I don't want anybody fucking hear that.
That was well and beyond what like a jump scare or like a loud sound or something.
Okay.
Is there a safe point here?
Why wouldn't you play this on Switch?
I don't know, dude.
I didn't know that.
Oh, by the way, there's like ear exploding audio bugs in the HD Steam version.
I didn't know.
I just bought the game on Steam.
I'm just a consumer in this.
Okay.
I don't think I can save it.
I really hope that doesn't happen again.
It actually is freaking me out.
I'm not going to lie to you.
So I try them again.
Turn on latency mode so you can cut it if it happens again.
I wonder what the process of that would look like.
Live editing.
There's audio bugs and then there's something is potentially left in the game that can like
break people's fucking computers like speakers, headphones, even me.
There's no evidence that it was in the game.
Yeah.
Well, that's why I'd like to investigate it a little bit more.
But I have met my OBS settings have been the same from it's got to be like a half a decade
at this point.
I didn't really change anything.
Why would you settings matter if it was a bug?
I don't want to watch the clip again, but it looked like when I switched, I switched
between weapons.
So I went, I attacked with the nunchucks.
And then I in mid combo, I went, wham.
And I switched over to this and I did that this move, that one.
And I think it hit something and hit them in the game's brain like a thousand times
in a second or something.
Oh my God.
I'm going to die.
I want to die.
Hi.
What?
Oh my God.
What is going on right now?
Why did he at one HP?
Yeah.
Add to the VOD, add a thing that says like, don't watch this VOD of loud sound.
Make sure people know that before we, you know, delete it.
I could also BRB and so I could do a restart of the stream.
I think that's probably what I'm going to do.
Oh, you can unpublish the VOD.
Okay.
Then do that.
Don't watch this VOD.
Seriously.
You've been louder before?
No, no way.
When I listened to that clip at like 0.2% volume, that's the loudest that this stream has ever
been.
Once I get this kill, I'm going to restart the game.
All right.
Well, this part's annoying.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I'm going to lose again.
I actually might.
No, I'm not.
I don't care.
I am Andy.
I would have died right there.
Yeah.
Sorry.
It's been silent, but I need to restart the game and we've got to make sure that the VOD
is not going to fuck a bunch of people up.
Haunted.
Put music on.
I'll put a little music on in the background.
That makes sense to me.
How about reduce the game volume from the actual mixer?
If the audio engine is bugged out, it will ignore your in-game settings and go super
loud again.
Yeah.
I'll go right to the source here and I'll just put it here.
I wonder if that helps.
I'm going to put it at like 20% in the mixer.
Volume gate.
I have a volume gate on OBS.
I have a slider where I can put that the audio should never go over that, but sometimes it
just doesn't matter apparently.
Let me get to the end of this and save the game.
See if that fixed it.
I need a save point.
What did that even just do?
Did I get an item?
Okay.
Here we go.
Save data.
Save complete.
All right.
Let me restart this.
I'll give the mods the ability to clean up that VOD and do all this shit.
Let me get some water.
Take a break.
I'll be right back.
Water time.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm back.
I am going to reopen Devil May Cry.
I have it set in Windows for it to never be possible to go over a certain decibel in Windows.
I'll be honest with you.
I'm fucking paranoid about this now.
If it happens once, it means it can happen twice.
You know what I'm saying?
Let me get it open.
Should we remove clips of the noise?
Yeah.
Guys, if you've got clips, make sure the clips say in the title, like audio warning because
we've got to be fucking careful with that shit.
There's no way that came out of the game.
Yeah, but that's also freaking me out because it's like, where would it be coming from from
my end too?
I am flabbergasted as to how that happened.
Let me make sure this is going to happen the way that I want it to.
Mixer.
All right.
It's at 30 percentile.
I almost want to...
Yeah, we'll see.
I have no idea what happened, but I don't honestly think it probably is not a way to
ever know what actually just happened.
Okay, so now I have it set.
Volume is in the same place.
I put the volume on the Windows Mixer down.
Let's see if that helps.
Let's go back here and see it.
Where's the last save point?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
How far back did I go?
That's not terrible.
Oh, is it terrible?
No, it's not.
I just have to go fast.
I know the audio is probably a little low right now, but I'm trying to get it to a point
where it's not horrible if that happens again.
Better raise my volume.
No, don't.
Jesus.
What if it happens again?
I don't know.
That's why I'm being like super quiet and timid, right?
The energy has changed since then.
You know what I'm saying?
It's changed.
Are you just shaking?
I don't know how loud...
I turned up my speakers on my end here independently before that happened, so I got hit in the fucking
head with like a brick.
That's what it feels like.
Okay, sword piece.
Hold down right bump with the press B.
Does it have to be the...
Ooh, okay.
So it was when I used the B move for this weapon.
The fire hit somebody and it was...
All of a sudden the game just started freaking out.
Almost like the game was lagging.
Like hardware lag.
Like, oh, something's fucked up.
Something's fucked up.
And then it just...
It was as if I hit the guy like a thousand times in a row.
There's the forbidden move.
It feels like it.
I'm going to finagle with it.
The volume will increase.
I was going to get it to the right spot where it can't go over a certain threshold.
It was in this room, by the way.
I'm afraid of this room, but I'm only going to use the nunchucks.
It was that enemy right there.
And I did that B move right here.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I wish I knew.
I'm from the future, dude.
It's going to happen again.
Don't say that.
Okay.
With that being the case, what if I go like this and then like this?
Technically speaking, I have it set to...
In the Windows Mixer, Devil May Cry is set to 30% right now.
So that means that it cannot go over that by the computer's operating system, right?
No matter what.
Surely?
Well, just be aware.
That could happen again.
I don't know how or why, but just be aware.
I would probably watch the stream at fucking 50% volume at least.
Shit.
I need to just run.
Oh, I fucked up again.
I'm going to have to heal because I really don't want to do this again.
Where's my...
Do I even have heals?
I do.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait.
This is the wrong menu.
What's the right menu?
Is it down?
No.
How do I get to the fucking menu?
I'm dead.
I'm so fucked up right now.
That actually like flash banged me in real life.
Let me just start it over.
Come on.
Kill me already.
I wish there was base cam for that.
It would have been awful looking.
I had my volume so loud too because I was like, yeah, let me rock out to the fucking music.
Yeah.
Devil may cry.
Let's go.
I just had to walk in that door.
It just killed me.
Just got on the fucking switch.
How was I supposed to know?
And why do you even have to play that fucking game of merry-go-round when a game comes
We got like this four or five versions of the game.
Oh, don't play that one.
That one's fucked.
Huh?
So the audio sounds okay now, right?
You guys are getting you hearing all the sounds and everything.
And honestly, I don't even know if that was from the game.
Who knows?
Was it a thing like a bug into OBS or my audio equipment?
Who fucking knows?
I'm terrified of it happening again.
It sounded like your mic fell down.
No, I was just sitting here.
I was just sitting right here.
Just playing the game.
Oh shit.
Don't die.
Shit.
Get back down here, please.
I'm dead.
Okay.
Let's go.
Why did I wait that long?
I just wasted that so bad.
Well, I did it again, but sorry.
Watch out for the explosion.
Oh, I'm going to lose it.
I lose it every time in the last 10 seconds of this fucking fight.
Why is the game quiet?
Yeah, somebody somebody somebody tell them I did beat him already, but I had to restart
the game because I was afraid of something bugging out and fucking up the audio.
Okay, so I just beat him.
So now we go down here.
This is correct, right?
Here we are here.
This is a boss boss right after a boss, huh?
Jesus.
I wonder if there's a hmm.
It's just a attack it or oh shit.
I'm dead.
I'll be full health now.
Okay.
Let's try it again.
Hmm.
All right.
When it's fully charged, you can't do it.
Whoa.
Oh, I can't double jump unless it's out.
He's too.
Okay.
Right.
Hit the carriage or hit the horse.
He likes the carriage.
Oh, right here.
What just happened?
That's weird.
Come here.
Really?
Please camera.
Whoa.
All right.
I should get right here.
Oh, don't blow it right now.
I could right now.
Come here.
Let's just die.
Oh, oh.
Okay, please.
Almost through.
It was close.
Almost.
Why are you being so serious?
I'll be honest.
I'm very annoyed.
I'm very annoyed in real life.
I'm exceptionally irritated right now.
All right.
Quicksilver.
Is this a new style?
No, it is a new style.
Chill out, dude.
Just move it to easy mode.
Yeah, I'm just so fucking mad at the game.
I'm exceptionally irritated right now.
It's nothing to do with the video game, but it's all good.
This guy's back?
Why was it so easy for Virgil and it's so hard for me?
That makes me scared of Virgil a little more.
Is the game worth it?
I mean, I'm having fun with the game, yeah.
Oh, spoiler.
That's the first time I've gotten Damage C ever.
That's pretty good.
Put the volume back up.
I think it's safe to put it back.
I have it in my Windows Mixer all the way down, so I think I can turn it up over here
and we should be all right.
You can mod the game so it has style changing.
I saw that, actually.
People were talking about that when I first played it.
I think it's all right for now.
So this is 13.
I refilled my drink and I don't even know where it is.
All right, beer B.
I need to go pee again.
I just made a drink and I don't know what to do with it.
I brought it back.
All right, I got my drink back.
It was in the bathroom.
Why was it in the bathroom, you ask?
Because I went pee and I brought it into the bathroom.
I thought you were going to restart stream.
I restarted the game.
I don't know.
I can't give a reason why that happened.
I really can't.
Unless it was the game kind of lagged
and got fucked up in the engine with the...
I don't know.
We have to cheer him up.
No, I'm good.
I'm just...
I hate doing that to people more than anything.
There's a limit to, you know, a loud fucking sound.
And there's a limit to it, I think.
Doing that to that many people,
it really pisses me off that it happened.
I hate doing that shit.
You know, like loud sounds like a jump scare.
Holy shit.
But that was not good.
And I fucking hate that.
So, all right.
Get it out of my system.
I got a lot of money.
It was an hour ago.
Yeah, but I'm like a won't move on Andy.
I'm like, fuck.
I like hate that that happened.
Seriously, like I'm just like,
I just wish I could go back and delete it.
What is this new style?
I'm controlling style.
Well, I have to try it.
I could buy some orbs too.
I'm doing it.
What about a gold one?
No.
How about blue again?
Blue again sounds like it's not a bad idea.
I'll do purple again.
And I'm going to buy a couple of these.
I know people are going to be freaking out.
People say, don't, don't stop, dude.
What a waste of money.
It's okay.
Let's go for it.
Reset the save file.
I don't want to do that.
More?
Oh, I had a sweet going too.
You guys ruined everything.
You should add subway surfers to the corner.
No, you're not getting subway surfers.
Am I going the wrong way?
Was I going the right way?
I don't know.
What about family guy moments?
No.
Long staircase.
Hell's highway.
How do I get in there?
There's a blue orb in there.
How do I open that?
It feels like mom yelled at us for being too loud and now we're scared.
The universe just likes to make jokes on my behalf, right?
An hour before that, two hours before that happened, what did I say?
What did we talk about very specifically?
It was incredibly specific.
What was it?
It was about audio and how important it is to have proper audio levels.
And you're telling me that you're telling me that I may have witnessed a like rare one
in a billion chance bug to create an environment that makes them.
Huh?
Today, after talking about audio levels.
Why?
That's a protagonist dilemma.
Protagonist dilemma.
Oh, no.
Here comes a tournament arc.
Oh, dear.
Okay.
All right.
I got that wrong.
Let's reset it.
Reset.
Delete the explosion sound effect in the game folder.
God, I got it all wrong.
I mean, so very clearly has to go this way and work backwards.
It has to go through here.
So this can't exist up from here.
How does it go this way?
Unless it has to go.
No, I can't go from this one to this one.
Like that.
It can't be that one.
Right.
How do I get it to hit this one here to go up?
Wait, hold on a second.
What is it going?
What is going on right now?
Wait, what?
Okay.
I got it.
Again, if it was the case of I didn't even know this room existed.
Okay.
Wait, is this first part just bait?
Or can you actually do this part?
So this is bait.
Huh.
That's funny.
I would have sat here for a long time if I did not see the shadow over there.
All right.
So I got that.
Do it again.
Go on.
Swing.
Oh, that hurt.
I haven't any money.
No, but I just bought stuff, so I'm good.
So where are we now?
Okay.
It's time.
What's in here?
Frogs having sex in the pond and they're loud in front of you.
How is there someone?
What?
What was the person talking about?
Another verse.
Oh, sorry.
Okay.
Read genuine advice.
No, read frog sex.
Yes.
Okay, here we go.
Dante versus Virgil.
You could see this exclusive battle.
Only you pre-order the game now and get the Dante versus Virgil DLC pack included in every copy from pre-orders.
Okay.
Well, I didn't make no help.
It's the first real attempt.
Ow.
Come on.
Shit.
Weird move set.
Oh, what's this?
Is he going devil mode?
Devil mode?
Jesus.
Ow.
I feel like I'm playing Street Fighter.
I'm still caught in a combo.
No, I can't move.
Okay.
So if you get hit, he's going to hit you four times in a row.
Don't get hit.
Got it.
All right.
I'm going to wait to go demon mode until you go demon mode.
That makes more sense to me.
That hurts.
Sorry.
Well, I did it earlier.
It's okay.
All right.
So you just got to avoid it.
I got it.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
When you get caught in that, it's over.
I have like four frames to hit you with anything.
You just block it.
We're going back here.
I wonder if I should put...
No, I like these swords.
They're leveled up high, too.
Regular sword, maybe.
I haven't used this weapon in a very long time.
Can I upgrade it?
I don't even have air hike for it, though.
Turn up your microphone.
My microphone has been the same for like five years.
I'll try it.
Much better.
Yeah.
I'm just going to run from you now.
Fuck you.
Come get me.
Coward.
I can't hurt him right now.
Yeah, I'm a coward right now.
That's fine.
Whoa.
You transformed and I didn't?
Fine.
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
No, dude.
Come on, please.
Epic.
No, that was bad.
Get away from me.
I taunted, too.
You baited a taunt, you asshole.
God damn it.
No, don't.
Wait.
Heal.
What button is it?
Up.
What is this horse shit?
Now with 10% health left.
Don't.
Oh, no.
Shit.
No.
God damn it.
I had it, too.
You fucking dickhead.
You dick.
I got caught in a combo.
If you get caught in the combo, he's going to do like three bubbles.
Fuck.
I can do it, too.
All right.
That was better.
That was cleaner.
Don't even think about it.
Did we both do it at the same time again?
Goodbye.
Oh, Virgil.
Look out for Virgil.
Get out of here.
Fuck you for doing that with low volume.
You don't understand.
Oh.
Don't even think about it. Did we both do it at the same time again? Goodbye. Yeah. Come here. Oh
Virgil look out for Virgil get out of here
Fuck you for doing that with low volume. You don't understand
Now leave
That was close
But you've taken quite a trouncing today haven't you Virgil?
You could have chopped me into confetti by now if you were in tip-top condition
Damn you
You have lost
Because you underestimated humans
Wait what?
What's going on?
Pure and innocent
Just like you
You're spanking my dear
Somebody said how many people are in this room? Yeah, there's a lot of people in this room right now that weren't here
The fuck
Quite a ride, you know
If any of you had died before getting here our little can would have gone waste
Therefore my job was to make you battle each other in order to weaken you
But at the same time guide you here and make sure that you were kept alive
I even went so far as dressing like a complete idiot
It's time for bed Mary
You can visit your dear mother
It's time for the clown to bow out Darkum dude the show's over impressive
I expected nothing less from the devil's descendants
Why does he keep laughing then he's like I had to wear this ridiculous costume
Like you don't have to laugh anymore damn, okay. Yes. Oh
It's pretty ugly. All right, that's pretty ugly. Where are we going?
We're going up to become a god
So are we heading into the final arc of the game the last like five or six chapters, right the third act nice
I think we're safe to turn the game back up. Honestly, i'm i'm not using that style move for the devil swords, though
That's the move that I did getting lured into a false sense of security. Oh, no, it doesn't say that
All right
So let's try this because I want to see it. I want to
I can keep these although maybe I like that better and then what do I got 12 000?
What about one of these holy waters? No, no, no, no, you know what?
Fuck it. I'm gonna do it through here. I'm gonna let me just do one quick thing
one quick thing let's go with that and
See how that works. Does this sound better? Is it a little louder? I think it can stay right here. Is that better?
So the idea is I turned a certain uh setting on too over here just in case this dude is paranoid
Yeah, it's I am super paranoid sacred light
Sacred light do I have that?
What's that flash gauntlets and greaves that said boost dante's attack and speed making him well good thing
I picked these up. I almost just walked completely away from this. This is a weapon
Really?
Uh, so that's definitely for that. So where's that thing? Wasn't there one of those thingies here?
The baowolf this is what Virgil was using. Okay, cool. Okay, so you can hold it. Okay, each one can be held. What about
Upgrading it beast uppercut great level two. Let's actually take a look. I want to see the um, what can it do?
You know, why why why what I just did this one is why why pause why why?
Oh there hyper fist. Okay. Yep. So why why pause why why go I like it? I'm a fan
Why pause nice? Yeah, there's a dive kick. It's crazy
Charging does stupid damage. Oh, i'm gonna have fun with it. There's one door through here. Pretty cool
Is there anything else? It's a nice weapon for sure. We're about to test it probably right now. Yep. Okay
I got that and let's go this way. Can you do your own demon boss voice? Yeah, I will I will do
the next uh boss
I'll do all of their dialogue and you better believe it's going to be low pitched with a filter on it
That's like this sounds kind of sounds like this get off the wall. Stop turtling. Okay. Where's that door? Where's that door?
Didn't I just come from here? Yeah. No, I did I Jesus even that was loud. Are you gonna do the food thing?
Yeah, we'll take a break. Uh, we'll do the food. I I got the compilation of the data
Okay. Whoa
You so you stop time. Ah now I see why people were saying this is the best move in the game
Shit, I don't like when they block. It's really expensive on btd. Is it?
Can I do anything else here? I wonder
No, I just did it. Ooh
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, there was some oh crap. I feel like I missed there was another way to go
Go over there. I think there was right god. Damn it. It's doing this. Okay, it's
Restock restock. Okay. So I wonder if you get it wrong. Do you have to do it again?
How much is a fully charged punch? Do I wonder the dive kick is really good, too
All right, it's it slows down your play style a little bit. I don't I can't say I love it
i'm a lot used to uh spinning around with the
Nunchucks, all right. So which way do I actually want to go here this way? All right swing swing
Okay. Well, never mind. The dive kick is the best part
Everything's open now. Um
Anything special I have to do. What do I do? This is the only one that's not open
This is not open just leave go out the door like just like just leave leave. Oh, there is a door
Is this I don't know what i'm going. This is wrong. Isn't it? I I don't know what's going on. Oh, I found it
Back up watch out food mode. I don't know if this would be a good food mode candidate
No, I don't think so
This this would be pretty low on the scale for food mode
I feel like the food mode computer would be would do way worse than me. Okay. So where are we now interesting?
I'm saving money. I've used way too much on purple orbs. But what is anything here? I can do
I feel like this moves. I have no idea. Oh, okay. What's the end goal?
Where am I trying to go? He went up in the sky and then it was like, okay now
Oh, I think over there. This looks like I can go up the love planet. What the hell is this?
Wait, no, this is back. I think I made it any secrets. No, can't use those. All right. Goodbye
Okay, am I going back to the very beginning of the game? Yeah, this is like the first area dante's office gold orb
Wait, no this way. There's kill them. All right, die. How come he hasn't left the starting area since yesterday? I've just been
I don't understand guys. I keep killing the same enemies. I don't get it. Where am I supposed to go from here? I don't understand it
It's two
Dude, oh
Get behind. Oh, no. I'm not doing this whole thing again. No way
Why do you have 5 000 times more hp than usual? You die already
Cool. So is it nothing here? I guess I don't understand. I didn't accomplish anything
What is my goal right now to get to the top of the tower?
Hmm, there's another door in here. Where's this other door? Where is this other door under the stairs?
Oh, this is I didn't even this blended in with the environment. I couldn't see this
Do you get to ride the motorcycle? That'd be awesome
You should get to keep that and use that as a melee weapon. What were they thinking?
t s d c
No, I want to seize across the board. Oh, well the gate crusher control the tower control your destiny
You still are you still mad about the audio thing?
I was just I still fuming like an hour and 45 minutes later. No, i'm, all right. I'm, all right
How about a beard cam?
No
Sorry, I was reading something. Sorry. I'm reading something. I'm not i'm promise i'm reading i'm not reading a guide
I promise i'm not reading a guide. All right, i'm not reading a guide. I i just looked up tips and tricks for
Uh chapter 15. That's all I did. Hello. Oh, it's a mini boss
Hmm, oh shit two mini bosses you guys are kind of annoying
Get over here. Oh these things suck. I hate having to jump to enemies and do one move. Oh spiders
Don't die. Come here. Oh my why do they have to run away? Does every enemy run away in this game?
They all just like go far away from you. That's a sin. Stop
You don't whoa
You don't level up quicksilver. Okay
I should take it off
What is happening to my character right now?
Okay, is this it there are three indentations. Okay, this is definitely it say the line
What's which what line you want me to say? The secret's up there. Oh, you want me to say the enemy spider line
I can do that. Welcome go that way. I just came from that way an energy source has been activated
Large snapping sound like two parts locking together can be heard from beyond the wall. I don't think I'd do anything with that. Okay
Um
I don't get it
Was there something else in this room that I wasn't part of the fucking right camera angle?
So I had to I have to look at it from a different angle or something. What is this? Is this just a object?
No, there's nowhere to go. Yeah, I see these two doors, but I don't have the device to turn this on
Re-indentations, what is this? A massive force is shaking the tower. Have you ever eaten cat food before? No, dude
I can't say I have what are you distracted me? What what just what just even happened a loud sound was heard
No, I haven't eaten cat food before did this move or change or no? I don't think so. Oh, okay
Now this is moving. Oh shit. I want those give it. I want those things over there. I'm gonna get them
This will be interesting. Okay, the whole tower is
Rotating. All right back up. Where's that door?
Oh, no
No, not right now. That would be a mistake to do it here. Did it count? It counted. Oh jeez
Uh, i'm making it
That's fine. He's ignoring us. What do you mean? All right. Now I go back
Does that open this?
You're not nice. How do you get over this shit reliably?
12 000 I could do i'm gonna save it because I want to get do I want to upgrade the beowulf or not?
I think I actually might just I like the regular sword a lot. Beowulf does a ton of damage though
I'll i'll do it. I'll do it. I'm gonna get the um, i'm gonna get beast uppercut. So here we are
Activate this last one
It does it does so much damage though. You guys are right. All right now back in here say the line small
Or large giant enemy spider. There you go
This path leads back to the human world to enter the demon world one must proceed towards the heavens from the central route
Oh back down here. I think this is right. Yeah, one of these yeah, this is definitely it. All right
Let's test our new move. Never mind. I'm watching the broken audio clip. It's making me literally ache from laughing
Well, i'm really glad that you think that i'm glad that you think that i'm still very upset that it happened though
It aches
At least as long as somebody
Okay, I
Am I supposed to do that?
My chest hurts from laughing at it
It sucked it was so bad
That was exploded I
I can't man
That sucks
Oh nice
The important thing is we all had fun
And that is very important to me
Is this right?
No, is it right?
I have to go up the tower
Maybe it is right. No, it's not
Is it
Isn't so how do I scale the tower?
Find out this guy is this guy is actually this bad
Dude, I know you've probably played this game like 30 times already
I don't know where the hell i'm going
So I have to go down
There has to be a way to go inside
Or maybe not. Okay
Um, did I go in here?
How many okay?
Where the fuck do I even go?
Can I get in here somehow?
This is one of the most confusing missions in the entire series to be honest, if not the most
um
Oh, okay
I mean i'm assuming I have to go up the tower because that's where he went
He went up
I went that way. I'm gonna go the other way. It's not something to do with this, right?
Okay, I have no idea
I feel like i'm close to being in the right spot, but not really
This is the only logical way, right?
This I wish I could delete these enemies from the game and just go in the code and do it myself
It's obvious
I feel like it's not
That's not a door. I guess i'm just gonna go
but this takes me back to the
first area
I'm going back to the
The first part of the game. What the fuck am I supposed to do here? Maybe i'm supposed to go back that way
Go back to the spider room
really
um
Okay to change gears maybe I guess
All right, i'm going back to the spider room. Okay back here. This is actually pretty far back
Okay, so I have the was it like a crab in the bottom bird mushroom at the top right?
Okay, red purple and blue and what what side do they have to be on spin it again?
Okay, so this is blue in the top left. Is that correct?
There's a couple of sections in the top left that didn't go to you
They kind of got to eat corn a corn one corn of kernel at a time
I spoon the whole thing in my mouth bro. Okay, this is apparently correct
Or different somehow. I think it's different enough. Like we're doing this again. I'm gonna die. Oh shit
We're even all right. Where how far back is this? This is really far back. Oh, no, it's not right. Where am I?
No, no, no, this is this is this is lit up. It didn't make any progress progress at all. So it's fine
I almost like want to just have chat tell me exactly what door to go in
We've we've done that before. I don't know if I want to walk in circles for the next hour
All right, so does position matters here blue is in the top left purple in the bottom
This is where it was before I hit this and I spun it again
Now purple is in top left. Do I not hit it again?
I could just I wonder maybe red in the top left. It is not about rotation. You need to explore man
Okay. Well, where does this take me? I remember this part
Uh, well, I guess i'm just gonna try to go through here because I did this last time. So where does this go?
Did not see this yet. I didn't make it past geez. Don't do any more sound effects shit
That that was queuing up a sound effect. All right, so this part I have two of these now
All right, so there's top left area and then top right so I think I have to just go that way
So i'm gonna try to get to the top right area. You missed one of the rotations
It's gonna put blue in the top left
Okay, so now this is blue
Oh my god, leave me alone
Uh, can I even get back up?
How do I get back up there?
Like you guys are so fucking annoying
Right there i'm like
Get off what the fuck game why can I not what the hell
Did I still count that I got the fucking item?
I hope so
Okay, here we go fragment. Here's the all right, so I need a couple more. Okay. So technically I did not do this yet
So I have to go this way
Jesus
Come on
Why can I not jump over this?
It's fucking horseshit
All right. I need to go in here because I have not technically gone in here
Okay
This is the spider room. All right. Do I have the whole thing? I got the whole thing. Don't I I need one more
All right. That last one is definitely down to the lower left. I got it
Try spin this again. I think I have to spin this again to get red in the top left
Wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong
Is it wrong? I needed to be wait. They're wrong
Purple needs to be in the top left. I'm all right with people backstading this part
Okay, and go I can always I can do it this way, but not the other way for some reason
Okay
Um, this is it. I gotta go this way. I'm not gonna spin that
There should be an item in here and if there isn't i'm gonna scream
There definitely is
uh
How do you jump over this
I got it. Yes
I'm stuck get me the fuck out of that. I don't want to do this again
Okay, everything's good. We're fine
Okay, here we go. I have i'm buying i'm buying one of these because I don't care. I don't want to do this again
What's with your title? What does it say s ranked orb collector pondering wizards in your area with that three?
I'm to lean that three face
Okay. Now the fun part is I got to get back to the middle and good luck having me remember how to get the fuck back
To the middle
It's this way, right?
I can't die here. This is so hard. This is the hardest part of the game
These jumps these jumps make no sense
All right, i'm out
Now I gotta go. I don't know
I don't know. I don't know where to go
How do I get back to that room?
I just want to fucking fight the boss. I just want to fight the boss and do fun cool combos
Hey, what are you eating? Thank god for food mode
It's
I uh, well, i've got a chicken salad sandwich right here. I think of french fries. It's it's been pretty sick
What the hell? How do I get out of here? I don't even
Whoa, just get me out of this
I don't even know what door to go through to get the fuck back to the this thing in the middle
I need to spin it again
Okay, can I play now can I play the mission can I please play
I don't I don't want to do this
I have to eat that. I know it's stupid. It sucks, but I have to do this
I have to eat this. I'm sorry everybody. I have to
I'm not starting this whole section over again
Okay
I am now
in this room
again
like that
Is this I don't even I I don't know
Dude devil may cry free
combos
Did you do a ls dodge dodge dash dash boom boom boom boom
Rotate the fucking tower dude, just walk around this circle for fucking 30 minutes
Get out of my way
Get out of the get out of the way. They're ruining everything
No, no, no move. What happened? Oh
Get
Get away from me
If I fell off again, I was about to eat my controller
All right, get me out of here. Okay, we did we did it. We did it. We did it. I'm here
What do you mean? We I know it's oh fuck. I didn't make it. How do I get out of here? Um, and then down
And then back around
Rotate the wheel bro. I don't wanna
Defiant defiant child
I don't what did I do it? No, I have to press
I don't wanna
Take the teleporter. All right, somebody actually helped me out here. So now I have the three pieces
I need to go teleport back to the casino walk out the door and then put this in that's correct, right?
The teleported to the casino is somewhere in this vicinity. Get back up the stairs young man
Shut up. You're not getting any help. Come on. I need to go down
I don't know. I don't know how to get connected over here
I wish I could fly go down then exit the tower enter the strip club and then enter the teleport
Ban that guy. No allow that person to stay so down here and then I
I don't even remember what room the strip club was
This is right. I have to rotate this two more times this dude actually bought it. Where are you going?
Do I have to I have to rotate it again just give up dude
Um to go rotate it I have to rotate it two more times. I will believe you I would trust you rotate it three times
Stop, that's the way to get out of here rotate it three times
Somebody just laughed out loud when they heard me say that I did because I I would do it too
All right, rotate this shit's free tough two times. I don't want to go down here and hit this two more times
Do it once it's twice. It's twice. It's twice. I'm gonna try it once
This section is fucking dog shit
Sorry, but it is
dude, why
Please it shouldn't be that hard to get on here
Buy air hike. I bought air hike for a weapon
That when I do the special move has a chance a one percent chance to blow my speakers out
I don't want to use that weapon go did it happen again. No, I just don't want it to
Gate
Oh no, he's doing an evil villain rant
All right, 34 minutes. Eh, gotta shave a little time off gotta shave a little time off there
Oh, I didn't save it. That's not good. I just pressed a you can still do it here
Oh, well, I skipped the cutscene. I didn't mean to do that
Uh, all right any um, if I restart the mission will we see it? God damn it
Uh, I don't know what happened, but we got to the top of the tower save save. I know I know
Wait, where do I save?
I can't save from here save quit and reload the save data in the menu
Yeah, but I didn't I everybody told me that this doesn't matter
Does it matter people? I I don't know whether to trust this or not
People said that mid mission doesn't really do anything doesn't it?
I was told never to use that it doesn't checkpoint, but it does save
Okay, I don't have to fight I can get the cutscene from the main menu
All right. We actually have to fight now. I feel like it's been an hour since I've attacked an enemy come here already dead
Okay, cool. Hey dude, can you discharge a firearm or do your red explosive barrel again? It was really funny the first time
God damn it. I don't want to be the guy that's known as the loud guy. Oh, I already am
All right, let's get out of here. This thing's a lot lighter. No
Is it gone
Where even is this thing stay locked on when it goes off screen? I can't see it i'm going for this hit it
Fuck those things. Okay, I got an item boom stuck right in the middle. Oh, no, I didn't want to press that
Living statue room. All right, so I have this item. Does the item go in this pedestal?
Oh, there's plenty of places I haven't gone
The question is what door should I go in next i'm gonna say I have to go this way back into the
What's in here? Okay, so I gotta go all the way to the end
Now I need to go either one of these doors works. How much money do I have not enough dante versus deadpool who wins
It's an easy one
Uh, probably dante. All right. Good. All right. I gotta kill this guy now. He's annoying. Where are you?
Have you been spawning people devil star? Ooh, all right, anything else in here? Okay
So there's another door on the end here wait over here. So this is here
All right. I want to go back and then go to the end of this hole chamber of sin
He who pursues the onyx moon shard make whole the spheres. I want that
Okay, so I don't think you break these bounce into each other. Oh shit right when it went down. What the fuck
Ah, ah, huh? They're touching. Why are they not breaking into each other?
Ah, yes, I did it moon shard cool
Dude, you I I I hate these things. You are so fucking annoying
What is i'm gonna lose?
Okay, well at least I don't have to do this again
I'm just gonna do this because I refuse to fight these enemies. I refuse
Spam the air kick. Um, that's what I tried to start doing
But they just float around so much. You can't even get like a fucking line on them. Why can these enemies fly?
You and you shouldn't be able to go in the ground
Bro fight me out of the fucking puddle
Now I want to go around the corner and down when you're gonna start the granny game marathon
The uh, we were here before the ice guardians chamber, but what's going on?
Do I have any thoughts on what do more attacks than the spinning jump one? I don't but
It's okay
This game when you move forward and press attack you do that move. You have to stand completely still which
Retraining your brain to not have your thumb on the stick
Very hard. I mean there's a door here. I just tried to do that
Nowhere. Hey, dude, you're gonna finish mafia 3
Damn, that's enough. That's an old one. I played mafia 3 for like three hours or something dinner giant walker chamber
Yeah, we're really going kind of through the whole first part of the game. Hey, here we are
This thing is moving now. I gotta build up some more
Souls here. Okay, so this thing's moving any weird shit up here or anything
No, okay, leave one other way to go stand back the hell you can't do something you can reason with
It has nothing to do with me being a human and you being a demon
I'm driven inability to forgive him. My soul is screaming demanding me to kill him
That's enough motivation to keep me going
Besides, this is my family matter. You should stay out of it
Okay, lady, I get them. I can't just sit back and watch either
I'm pretty pissed at him too. You know now get out of my way or there'll be some consequences fair enough
I wasn't planning on letting any demons. Uh-oh
I'm gonna get my ass kicked. Aren't I?
All right, first try let me do it. I'll get it first try where she's freaking me out
Shooting at the voices. No, I yeah hers
What how are you so good at that?
Get her caught get her caught caught caught get her caught
Good you my weapons are so bad. All right, I just need to wait. Oh my god you
Coward, let's go. I can't look up where she is either. I just have to find her. Where are you?
Don't you have a shit in me? You are so annoying. Will you fight me and stop running you keep doing the
Claw the hook whatever up to the ceiling and then I can't you're doing like the hook claw thing. Whatever it is
Oh my god
Please just get on
I'm just gonna wait
I'm just gonna literally stand. I'm just gonna stand back here. She's gonna run away every time. Oh, hi. Yeah
Oh, well, sorry, you gotta go. I really don't want to do this again
Okay, thank god you did wait I did marge and homer in the same fight I did the whole family
Ooh new weapon
God damn it
It's just I looked over at the mod chat and I just see mischief makers. Did I win? Oh shit
All right. Cool. Gotta get them all. Oh
I want that it's worth it only um, what three more chapters?
All right, I need to stop this take away two minutes that just took me to do that
Okay
Okay, that's a b one of the reasons I didn't use an item back there is because it was gonna be s
Uh-oh combine the oh, do I get that weapon? Oh, oh, oh, oh
Do I actually get to use this? Oh, that's devil may cry one. I think I want to make a few changes
This thing is amazing. But I just don't activate it
I think i'll go with sword master and then also
I'm curious about this
17 getting close
There's only what 17 18 19 20 only four more. All right, let's go
Uh, so what's the correct way in the door the high? Yeah, I was here already
No wrong. I can go this way, but wait only I had the double jump. Oh, this is a place to go
Trial of the warrior. Okay
All right, let's do it activate it again. All right
Oh, no, one of you think I have to activate him again. I do whoop that one's yep. Oh shit
Don't hurt me get away from that thing. I want to activate it
All right, turn this on again
Come here. Really?
Is he concentrating? I am
I feel like you have to in a game like this. Otherwise, you're just gonna die
All right, it's gonna show up here in a second
All right. Fuck you, man
All right, turn it back on move. All right. Now, let's go
Do I have to my god? What the hell dude? Why do I have to do this?
Why can't I just fight the guy get off of that?
Oh, i'm gonna die
How i've hit this guy?
two or three
hundred
Million times and he's still alive. Did you do the million stab?
I feel like the opportunity for those combos is like close to zero because i'll get in i'll be like here
Okay, here comes the step and i'll just get hit
pause
Then spam. Yeah, like right here. I get hit him. I'm done
Do both or none? I know it's okay. Where is that piece of shit enemy? Okay
Shut up. Oh my god
My god, I fucking hate this thing. This is so awful. This is awful
I'm dead. It's optional. Well, I I have to beat it. I'm right there
Stop using weak weapons. There's only five in the game. I'm using two of them
Come here. All right harry. All right, come on
All right, how many times are you gonna do that?
Yeah, I don't want to grab a hold of that thing
Get away from me. No
Get out
Die
How could you still be how could you still be alive? How is it? How could you still be alive? It's not even possible
What the fuck? Come on, dude
Die
Hit the wheels if I go to the wheels he goes
It's just as it fucking sucks
Okay
Um, i'm gonna save everything to the very end. I don't like that if you just touch those
They just do it. So can somebody are they invincible if they if these are both not active?
Okay, let's go you fucking asshole
Get away from me for one second, dude
Don't he's gonna do it again. Oh
Oh my god
Just you open it
Let me just turn it on
Dude, I keep getting trapped in front of him. I don't even have any heels. I don't have any heels. I have to do this
What the hell is this enemy?
And why is it like this?
You don't even have an opportunity to attack this motherfucker before he just like to start to start teleporting around again
I just didn't want to die
Just walk behind him
Overtuned overtuned overtuned overtuned overtuned
Yeah, I know he's invincible but there is
Not a single opportunity where I can go turn on two fucking pirate wheels
He's he just doesn't stop attacking
I'm gonna turn the other
Turn the other pirate wheel can't dodge correctly. He does this move way too often
Way way too often. He does this move 10 times too often and now the thing's back to zero again. This is awful
This sucks absolute asshole. It really does
I there's no opportunity to fight this guy
You're either smacking a wheel or he's teleporting around the whole map and just screaming at you
But here we go again just admit you can't do it. It's a skill issue. It's a game issue
So how much less damage do I actually do to people I feel like I should have killed that guy by now
I mean, that's an unbelievable reduction in how these guys i'm i'm hitting the same guy
I have an idea every single enemy in this game have to have teleport
But they have to put that in for almost every enemy in the game teleport. See you later. All right, he's back
Oh my why does he parry every move in the front and then he teleports fuck this guy
Dude stop appearing underneath me and then I this is so bad
This is bad
Where is he going?
Fuck this guy and fuck this game
I'm killing him right now
This is unbelievably awful on a scale of one to ten. This is at least an eight. This is at least an eight
Why do they have to teleport every single three seconds?
Do they have to teleport after every swing?
after every fucking swing
I can't but i'm so done
And I just replaced the thing that I just used so it was for no reason to come in here
Here comes another mald's
Oh, no
I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be fine. Don't worry. Let's go. Not another one. Where are you?
Move ah, I feel like i'm in sludge half the time. Isn't that it? All right, you're gonna have a breakdown
No, i'm good. I'm good. So where the hell am I going? I I have to put the
Loud weapon on I feel like I was better with it. I sort of be careful or maybe the beowulf maybe
Uh, I have 20 000
Uh, I think it's air hike but what this
Yeah, so it's why why pause?
And then there it is. Okay, this dude bought air hike twice. I don't know what i'm doing
Yeah, but I don't want to use those swords anymore. Um
Do I want to keep this on where do I want to go back to trickster?
I feel like trickster is very helpful. I think that's the right call
There we go. Nice
Okay from here. There's nowhere else to go. I guess we're going back. I gotta go back up the cubes
This is not as bad as you guys think it's gonna be for me. I promise
I know a lot of you are expecting. Oh, wow. I can't wait. He's gonna fuck up everything
I'm gonna be all right right here so far. So good weird. Okay, I can go up here
Here
It really is the horror, okay now there was a trick to this it was four
Do I need to do this though? I feel like I don't need to do this
But I guess i'm oh my god
Wow
I got really lucky there. Did I do it? All right, we're getting close. Do I need to fight these? Maybe not I do
You're in for a cool boss fight, I'd love to hear it. Is it why pause why why or is it why pause why pause then that?
Okay, that's that it's why why why why why pause why why why why why good to know all right onto the big bridge
It's fine. All right, let's do it
Time to fight my shadow
This would be easy
Have you are you learning from all my moves because I got a d in every single level so this should not be hard at all
Oh, I can't hurt him. Uh
Oh, you don't like the light, okay, I get it go over to the light this lights this place up
Oh
Dude, you've ripped his skin off. I didn't do anything. No you come to me
I wasn't locked on I was holding bright trigger big damage. That's right. No
Come on really that I actually wasted it. That wasn't bad. Oh, no
Oh, yes, doppelganger special power used by the doppelganger enemy the style gives you more freedom to battle
Not a style. Okay
Give me a couple of new
Things to mess around with here right at the end of the game. Oh
We're just getting worse and worse 40 minutes
Well, it was 40 minutes because I spent at least 25 doing that stupid wheel encounter 18 invading hell
Break the seal and battle into the depths
Whoa, I have to fight the whole chess board. Do I have any pieces?
Lock on to this thing if they get to the end of the board. Do I lose?
I feel like that's what it's implying here
Everybody's come on. Yeah, that hurts so much. Get it. Does everything have to have a move that goes?
And then dashes across the screen
I've seen a theme here
Okay, I just have to vote. I'm gonna stay in the fists. It's way more damage
I gotta clear them out as fast as possible starting go one two three. What side happens first?
Can't combo just gets broken. I wish I had like some kind of
Don't lock on to random shit that's in the way, please
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. I still got hit by it
All right, who's left you just come over here already
Dude, check this tutorial. No, this is fucking crap. This is crap
This is crap
That's what dad says
Do you give dad the controller for like gta or something?
I drive all the time. He's going 20 miles per hour down every single road. He's hitting every single car
He doesn't get it. It just goes this is not something. This is crap
This is crap. So
Holy shit, I did it
This is crap
Yeah, at least watch the rest on youtube. Okay
I'm curious about it
What is oh
Okay, you want me to do this now?
Probably not a great weapon for this. All right. This is what I wanted to do. I didn't how did I not hurt him at all?
How do I call on the other dante?
No, they're still coming in ice
Changing the targets makes me want to throw up. I'm gonna lose
Oops
Okay, uh, I see a couple things wrong already. These weapons are not for this fight
Putting we're putting on
these
and I want
Uh, I don't want this
I was burping. I wasn't crying
Way better. We're i'm hearing those explosions again, and it's kind of freaking me out. Whoa
Get it only got to kill like four more of those or way more than that
Do I have to kill every single boss in the game?
This is gonna stink. Isn't it? This is gonna stink. Who's this one?
Oh, no
Are you doing are you gonna beat the game tonight? I plan on it. I'm gonna try to come here
I gotta hit these guys in the back too. It's just it's it's just it's you know what I mean like
This is crap
One move andy it's the only move I can do but they just run so far away
They jump around dash around and I've I've hit him and they just back back up back up fight me
He's royal guard idiot
Time that person off for one second. I don't even start. Yes. All right, who's the worst boss that I don't want to fight right now?
I don't want to fight her right now. What's this one?
Dude, why did I pick the right one bite gem and you're done. What do you mean? I'm done
Am I actually done if I do this? I forget the combo for this way too slow. Why space? Why space? Why? Okay
I'm dead. God damn it. Unfortunately. I have a question if I
Use this orb I come back if I die here
And I reset do I have to fight the other two bosses in a row very important distinction
No, okay. Thank you so much. Appreciate the uh
Whoa, who's this one?
Oh this so I can do this one. This one's easy
That's taking way more hits now. They're all buffed up. Ah
Damn it really, you know, let me get a combo in I didn't get it. Shit
Really twice in a row. I didn't get it. It's annoying. I'll get it this time
What a waste what a waste I can cancel it
I didn't even know that till literally the last 10 minutes of the game. How come he keeps
Flipping back. When do I get the opportunity to actually attack him? All the lights gotta be up. Don't it?
Why I'm gonna attack him here. I shouldn't even do it get all the lights
Wait, I thought he turned that one off. He shot a beam. I thought he turned it off across the way. He threw it
He did his move. He turned he threw the projectile. I thought he turned it off
Yeah, he did that. I what does it just disappear if it if you actually turn all the lights on
Anyone I wanted the health don't throw. I won't come over here. Okay, we got him 15k. Nice anymore heals
I don't want to go on this with half health. I wonder if this anymore
Who's this? Oh, no, no, no. No, I thought this was a this was a giant one. I was like, oh cool
What's this big one? I think I should just die here
Just kill me because I just want the full health to fight the white door
If I just have to do the white one then why is there a point to do all them or no?
I'm going the wrong way was I going you'll get more red orbs
Let's just get this guy
Come on, man. I didn't want to even dodge towards him again, but you know how it is. I got so greedy
And I still am greedy. Fuck it. Just where is he? No go go go go
Thank god. All right. I did it
I was gonna say that's not a lot. So that's three. I've made a circle
Well, i'm really glad you guys told me that because I definitely would have tried to fight every single enemy in this game
Circle like it connected them in a you know, whatever i'm tired. Wait, did this guy know?
I feel like i'm gonna have a great time
All right. This is 19 out of 20. How do you eat blue cheese? It tastes like puke
How do you eat goat cheese? It tastes like dirt and say that too popple the great beast with bates bullet great beast
All right. Where's the great beast 26 000. Damn. Come here new zone
All right. It's just a gauntlet
All right, I can't hit these guys
what is
Substance projects image and image punishes substance
Do I have to hit them in the mirror?
Excuse me
Stop the vicious circle by bending time and space looks like something can be inserted here. Something can be inserted here
Back to some of the mirror opposite this one
Stop the vicious circle by bending time and space. Can I do it do more than one?
another one
27 000
I need a kiosk or whatever. They are can't hurt them. Okay. Oh, I can hurt them. All right
Here we go. Not bad. Did I do it? I got it. I failed it really fuck. Okay. Hold on dude. How many more combos?
He died already god. Damn it
Die, please
Is he dead? Did I do it? Oh, yes
I had a triple s going almost that whole time and still took him almost to the end. I wonder what the last boss is
I bet it's a cube
All right
It's time to upgrade one more time one more blue orb or get a gold orb
I think this is going to be a big deal. This is what I would do and then
Get stream level two you already had one. I can't resurrect twice
And you're only right. Yeah, you can. Yeah, i'm just giving myself some padding
I mean, this is the correct answer, right? I guess I could do another blue orb or that what do you think blue orb or
level two to that
Okay, gotta heal now. This is it right the road to despair. This is not right go in the mirror. Wait
Didn't I come out of that mirror I came out of that one didn't I oh shit, okay
So not here go back in the mirror. I just went in the mirror. Wait. What is again? Wait, how much?
statue I have
I need to put the thing in the staff
I I feel like that was a hundred years ago. Okay. All right. Now we go back in here
End of the line. All right. I already spent things cool. Okay final boss maybe
Yeah
Okay, big giant enemy
Imagining go attack big giant enemies legs
Big enemy will fall down hit enemy and face
All right, let's do it. Not bad damage. We're good. Jesus you have to attack these
What are they doing? They're about to fucking snipe me
All right. Let's see. I got some good healing out of that. Your loadout is ass. I'm busy
I'm a little busy right now, dude
What is the strategy here rocket?
me
Oh my god. Okay. Well
That was fun
I tried to hit select to open up the fucking menu
It's it's up on the d-pad and I have not been able to put that into my memory
It's the only game in history that's ever had up on the d-pad be go to the menu
There's no it hasn't been a single game in history that's done that and not in all of history
Okay. All right, bring out the bugs again. What are the hell they are?
Okay, um, why would I ever be locked on to that are you fucking serious? Why would it lock on?
To the and I don't even kill it because when you lock on you
D, uh, you know what? I was gonna whatever
Where you at?
Do we get to play together can I switch between them?
He needs to learn the heart of battle of brothers
Okay
Where's your fall is dante's lead but still spins off his own special style
So b is virgin. Okay
So no more demon form. Oh my god. I'm almost dead
Go. Oh, I don't have a dodge anymore. I got this virgin. Watch out
Go. Whoa, a lot not more of this shit again. How do how is it possible to miss? That's like
Just six pixels where you can't hit one of those things and I found it
Uh-oh
What my virgin? I'm coming back. I'm coming back
Virgil don't worry. I'm coming back
I have the free to play currency
I love this one of these little shits just still here
Oh my god
Please just end it
Virgil do a fucking suplex
Hey, hey, hey, put me down. Hey, hey
What hold on i'm so what happened you shitting me?
I didn't know that's what was going on
No, first, okay
Turn around right now
Attack him
I didn't know that's what was happening
Oh my god, please
How did you fall for it again?
Dude, I had 10 I had one hp when he picked me up the first time and it killed me instantly
Oh, no
Classy for someone's dying words
Oh the sword there it is
dscdc
Well, whatever it is i'm
incredibly unprepared for it
Considering I just had to use two of those golden orbs
I hope this final encounter is the same encounter that capcom puts in all their games
Which is just aim the rocket launcher at the big scary thing and press a turn back to the jester
This is actually the hardest fight in the franchise coming up here
Oh, no. Oh, this is gonna be I got it. I'm not going in with a negative attitude. It's not happening
All right, i'm gonna try to do a world record here for this stream no no complaining for 10 minutes
That would be a world record in a hard game
No complaining for 10 minutes straight and you bet on that. Yeah, sure. I'll try as hard as I can
I will not complain will I complain?
And by the way me saying what the fuck is that? What is this move? Oh, this is bull. This is bullshit
No, we're talking about I have to sincerely be like and why does he teleport? That's not fair. Why does he have a dash?
All in or no, okay. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. I will not make a single complaint
I'm gonna be super happy the whole time and run a poll if you want for 10 minutes
In 10 minutes in one second, I have completed the challenge
You have to eat a blt on stream if you complain. Okay. Yeah, that sounds fun. Yeah 10 minutes. Okay
Oh, I only have 15 000
No, it's I don't have enough
I've wasted that other one. I didn't I didn't know that was it
I have to buy these
No, no, no, no, no, no that we haven't started yet
We haven't started yet
Well, this is free money if you just are curious
This is a free channel point increase to whatever you have because there's no way right like I just I forgot
No, no, no, no. No, is that it?
Is it in are we good?
That wasn't a complaint. That was me expressing my sadness
I know i'm gonna buy one of these
And I know i'm gonna buy one of these
People are going all in. Oh boy
yeah, the timer can start from when the
Inevitable cutscene here ends and the actual boss health bar is on the bottom of the screen
That is when you can start the timer when boss's health bar is at the bottom of the screen
If you lose again, if you lose this you have to eat salt and vinegar chips as well
That's fine. Yeah blt with those chips. Yeah, sounds like a good lunch and goat cheese
No, I will I refuse. I will turn the stream off. I just I will I will run from that
We're not going goat cheese yet. I haven't even been it's having been 10 minutes. All right, here we go
I am going to use the weapons. I have right now
I am going to keep the trickster. Let's go
When I play hard games like this, I feel like half of my sentences are complaints
This is gonna be rough
Yeah, wait till the gameplay starts. We're not going yet
Don't even talk 10 minutes is a long time. What is it right now? It's 10 41 specific
Okay, here we go
begins now
Timer starts now
It almost just happened. No, i'm not muted. I promise he has health back just asking a question
I asked I was asking if he has his health back. It was a question
I was asking if he heals. That's not no, it's not i'm fine. I was just like thinking wait
Does he have his health back? Is this a heal mechanic?
That's all that was
Oh, he's in demon mode my turn getting really hard to not it's so difficult right now
I'm trying as hard as I can to not say anything. What do you mean a complaint? What are you talking about?
No, I said I'm trying really hard to not it's got to be a complaint
I have just said this is very difficult to not do this. That's no it's not
It's very difficult
and
I've noticed an observation
I'm just simply observing a few things
I'm not this is not a complaint. It's just I really need to get better at timing that dodge
I'm gonna own that one better at timing that dodge is what would have been good there
That's nothing to do with anything to do with what happened. We're good
It's about timing the dodge. That's all that was
I still have six minutes. I feel like that's a million years, which is an observation. It's just it feels like a long time
No, it's not. That's not a complaint
That's an observation
No, it's not
No, it has to be a complaint
Let me start over it. Let me start over it. Let me start over
I didn't complain. I just said man. That's that's such a four six more minutes. That's a long time
It is a long time
Just
Kill me
He heals he does heal that is what happens. It's an observation
That's a heal. That's a big heal
And it's fine. I don't have a problem with it a heal at all
See
It's like it doesn't even it doesn't even faze me doesn't even faze me
Doesn't even faze me right now
Hey virgil that was
Just an observation. That was a pretty very long demon form. I'm up just observing that I don't care at all
By the way, I am i'm fine with that
Just an observation that was a pretty long demon mode. That was very interesting. I'm very interested by what I just saw
I'm just observing the game. Uh, it's fine though. I don't care
I gotta play very defensive
Everything is everything is just fine. Just another observation
I like his jacket
I like his jacket. It's a nice jacket. I need to get a good combo in here
Uh, i'm not even close to beating him. That's not a complaint. That's a fact time up time up
Is time up is time up do we count the devil trigger complaint?
Show it to me show it to me. I'll make the ultimate decision show it to me. Let me see. Give me a clip
I want to watch a clip
I think somebody just said chat. Fuck you. It was an observation
See, that's good. That's good. That's good. Okay
Okay
You tried to save it. No, did I anybody got a clip nightbot keeps deleting them gaining viewers
Nice you were complaining and then said it was an observation
I don't think anybody even has this. Okay, is this it? All right, let's see
All right, i'll put this on stream and we'll we'll go over it and we're gonna go over it
We're also gonna vote on it. I'll give you my two cents on it, but then we'll vote. Oh wait, that would be really biased
Yeah, never mind. We're not voting. I'll tell you should we have a mod council decide? All right, let's let's see
Hey virgil that was
Just an observation. That was a pretty very long demon form. I'm up just observing that
Yeah, no that I did. No the for real. That's a that is a literal complaint. That is actually a complaint
Yeah, i'm sorry. That is and do you want to know how you can tell i'm sorry everybody, but this is how you can tell
This part right here that part right there
Was me internally just talking shit about this game and then I finally just let it out
Hey virgil that was
Just an observation. That was a pretty very long demon form. I'm up just observing that
I don't care at all by the way
I I internally was was screaming about how long that was I was like that's fucking bullshit how long that demon form was
I think I think that counts, but you said you don't care. I'm fine with that
Okay, no, I think it counts you said hey virgil like hey paul
Let's do it again. How about this? How about this? Can I be can I be fucking quiet for five minutes?
Want to do it again
Can I be completely silent for five minutes while fighting and i'm not muting. I i'm gonna do this completely by the book
But i'm not i'm just gonna watch the youtube video somebody beating this guy
I'm gonna play super passively. I don't care about combos. I just care about winning
It doesn't really help me does it?
Okay, wait another complaint one. Okay, I can complain now though, right?
Oh you okay
He's got all of his health. Can somebody check real quick?
What is the playstation?
two
Trophy completion rate of this encounter. I feel like it's less than a hundred people. No, no, no, no
Okay, so when does it start? So we were we're oh, we're gonna come back. All right. What are we doing this time?
He is healing too
Yeah, that includes so no sound no noise at all. No laughing. No heavy breathing. No, no marge simpson sounds
No homer simpson sounds five minutes of complete silence and i'm not muting the microphone. I promise you he didn't even get him down at all
All right, so when i'm gonna start over here, okay use devil use dt until he does face cam
No, i'm not not not after like seven and a half hours eight hours streaming
uh, this guy is
I I never would even gotten this far in playstation 2
I would have gotten to the second or third mission of this game and been like
No, i'm done
No face cam no deal. I I don't have any clothes on
23 percent on ps3 and ps4
75 percent of us got to this part and went that was fun. Okay, are we ready?
I'm I have to be quiet
I'm not i'm how am I gonna mute the microphone? I have to touch it. All right, you ready?
Five minutes of complete and total silence the microphone. I'm gonna put it right here. You understand
Do you understand how close this is? You're gonna hear anything that comes out of my fucking mouth anything
I can breathe though. All right
Shit you're gonna hear me breathe that counts. Okay, so tell me does this count?
That's just me actually breathing. I think we'll be able to tell the difference. Okay, here we go
Start the timer now
So
I was trying so hard. I looked over at chat and somebody you fucker you asshole
somebody said
Bro, imagine stopping in the middle of a combo to shoot
fuck
Imagine stopping in the middle of a combo to shoot just like that person thinks i'm such a fucking dummy
You know what I mean?
Oh, that's so funny
Oh my god, i'm so sorry
You should have seen me pulsing
I was probably purple. I was trying so hard. It was like
And then it just came out I was fucking shit I had to have been shaking. Oh my god
This is so hard
I've been streaming for like eight hours too. I I might have to actually call it a night here
All right, i'm gonna i'm gonna give it one more try
Oh my god, that's so funny another bet
One more I was trying so hard to keep it in because I knew there was only like a minute left
Imagine stopping mid combo to shoot like oh i'm doing a good job. I got him. Let me attack him
This is so ridiculous
All right, i'm just gonna play let's go. It's it's time right now. No more predictions. No more betting
i'm doing it right now
dude
We're not even I can complain again. I can complain
There's nothing in video games that I hate more than enemies that run away or teleport away and you have to chase them
That's this whole entire video game
That's this entire video game
Trying to get the timing of the attack attack pause attack attack attack when you're when you're in a game scenario
That shit is so fucking hard to actually do how many controllers you think have been broken from this game?
Do you think it's more than 25 000? What do you think?
Do you think it's more than 30 000 controllers have been broken from this game?
I cannot beat this guy even millennia. I was like making progress. This guy just just destroys me every single time
I'm putting the bay wolf on yeah, fuck this. Give me the fuck out of there piece of shit
Let's try this
Oh
My god, dude, where is the opportunity to fucking attack this guy? What are the combos for this? I don't even know them
Pause why why why why why I don't like pausing. I like fucking going. I like person x I don't want to pause
Because
Dude, does he just parry every single fucking move he goes like
Why why how do I do that?
All right. I'm changing my stance. This is impossible. But with what i'm doing
This is impossible. I'm gonna try to parry him because how does the parry work?
Just press b when you're gonna get hit let me test it
Did it work am I doing it? I mean, it's a it's kind of a block
No, that's not gonna help me at all right now. I couldn't even do anything
I have to stick with trickster. I'll i'm gonna use the regular sword though. I did not
Uh, didn't I just change everything? Why is it back to these? All right, let's try again
Didn't want this equipped dude about that blt. I don't think i'm ever gonna beat this. I find this to be impossible
I don't think i'll ever do it. You beat millennia millennia was easier than this a hundred times easier
This has the heal from millennia and teleporting is worse also I you can summon a summons
This is fucking ridiculous
This is ridiculous
Stop backing off dude. He look what he does. Wow. I didn't back off. He did you should be yelling at his fucking chat
He's doing it. Not me
I i'm not look
I he's backing away
Oh my god, he just parries every single fucking move
There there is no exchange. He just walks and then teleports away and then does this
Look at how much slower my moves are i'm waving around a fucking toy. I'm like one
Two three four and he's already moved across the map by the time I do it
Get out of your fucking demon form, dude. I can't even hurt him. Yeah millennia didn't have a fucking form where she goes and no
Rot you can't hurt me at all. I've been invincible and I can heal off these i've been invincible for a full two minutes
Oh, wait
Oh, wait. Oh, wait. Oh, oh great. We both have the same idea
God just attacks bro. Come on, dude
Do you have any idea how un fucking bearable this encounter is you have you played it?
Have you played it? Did you play it if you didn't?
and
Silence if you did, you know what I just do. Oh, I can't even get him down to 50 before i'm just dead
I'm gonna do this three more times and then i'm turning the stream off
I'm getting out of here
I'm gonna free myself from this fucking madness
This is the first game I played when I was six years old. I am so sorry for six-year-old you
You probably had so many awful memories of this game. Look at my health
You have work. Nobody played this when they were six. They're full of shit. Don't listen to them. This may be fun
What the fuck was that where's my move that can do that dante get back to the fucking gym
Do a little lift a little more weights
He's almost back to full health again
He's he wait
He doesn't this is not millennia
He just heals when he's in demon form. What is this fucking dog shit?
He doesn't have to hit me
So do you yeah, i'm the video game protagonist
Nobody else gets those powers
Just I wish you just didn't counter every other swing like it just would be so much more
It would just be like you have to counter every move
Like dude, why can't I just attack him?
You have to damage burst him out of that
Good luck when he blocks
90 of every swing you do no matter what all right two more attempts and i'm fucking uninstalling the game
No stay out of that
Oh my god, dude, give me a fucking break
I don't have any heals. Didn't I buy one? I thought I had a large heal put it on easy
Wait
They're gone gone
If you use it, they're gone. They don't come back like when I restart that checkpoint. It's fucking five grand to buy one of those
Oh, that's awful
It's ten thousand now to buy a heal
Yeah, you have to restart the whole mission
Are you kidding me?
Oh that stinks
Okay, well
Restart the mission won't that put me through the first boss fight though. Wait optimize
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I see
Uh, so what the hell am I gonna do here?
All the gold orbs were used already. I didn't even know there was a final final final fight
I thought we were like working together and oh, yeah, we won together
Just go farm orbs. I might do that not tonight though
I wish I could not be stuck in that animation. It does so much damage. It's already over
It's a good place to get orbs. What's a good spot to do it 19 cancel out of the dive kick if you mission two
I just want to buy
Like another one of those gold orbs. I had two
I I just don't think it's possible without that without like three golden orbs and like eight heals
I'm going in there. I'm bringing a backpack full of shit into that fight when I go in there again
I'm gonna have 10 heals
And 30 revives I don't care if I die 15 times in a row
Never mind. I give up. Never mind. I just saw how many I collected it. That's gonna take like six hours
All right, that's it. I'm out of here. Uh, and i'm never playing this game ever again
I mean until i'm dead like this is not gonna happen ever again
Yeah, like they'll be they'll be like doing a funeral for me. They'll be like wait, but he never finished
He didn't beat virgil the priest is gonna go good. Fuck that whole game
Dearly beloved we are gathered here today to see our friend
We put to rest under the i'm getting weird with this one block every move andy
Damn it. You're just hailing you piece of shit
Even in demon form he blocks every move. How the fuck do you do this?
like honestly
This is fucking impossible
It took me two years
You should be jumping dude
Is this is this fucking dickhead on a top 10 list of most annoying boss fights in history? He has to be
Yeah, I get fucking exploited
What is this lock on fucking doing dude? Wait when the when you're locked on why can you swing in a different direction, dude?
It's so fucking annoying
it just like hurts just to attack him and
I don't know what the fuck's going on with this game
But like what the hell is going on here?
The game just literally turned like off and is down on my task bar four hours ago an explosion happened in my room
What is going on with this game?
I'm gonna lower the volume because i've no idea what's gonna happen here. Am I back? Oh my god
What's the point of a lock on if it just if you swing in a different direction shit, I can't no more teleporting
It's like the worst mechanic in every single video game
What the hell is this move?
Oh my god, what does that mean? Holy fucking shit, dude, dude
This weapon switching thing makes me want to fucking puke as well. What's he doing?
Where are my fucking heels? Oh my god this
2000 fucking 2 video game. I didn't
Restart the mission. Oh
My god, damn it, dude
I like just why like you've got to be fucking kidding me. That is infuriating
I literally had it. Yeah by doing the jump attack move
I'm so fucking pissed right now. I am so angry
Can I save it here so I don't have to do this shit over and over again if I want to restart the game?
Or do I have to restart every single time? Like what if I do this? Is that gonna do it?
Can I is that gonna work? No more teleport. God damn it
Oh great, I can't move. Where is he?
Okay, so I win. Game sucks. The sweat coming down my face right now. It's like all over my face
I look fucked up. If I turned on the webcam right now, I would scare you. Millennia is definitely harder
Yeah, that wasn't even that bad
Okay, I took a picture. I'll put it in the discord tomorrow. Yeah, no food quiz. Sorry
I had to beat Devil May Cry 3 and uh, I almost puked. Why is the volume so low now? I didn't turn it down
We should be fine for now. Oh wait, but they may though, right? We going again?
Oh, we are going again doing my victory lap. Oh, it's counting them. Oops. Well, that's fun
It was a a lot more intense than I thought it was gonna be
I didn't I knew Devil May Cry was a hard game, but I didn't know it was a really
Hard game. I would consider this to be really hard
DMC 3 is hard. DMC 4 and 5 are less so. Hmm. 3 is probably the hardest one
I remember 5 coming out and being interested in 5
You could probably beat DMC 2 with one hand. Really? Geez, you would really like 5
Well put it on the list
I would play at least the newer ones. I know the older ones can be a little weird, right?
The first one's like a completely different video game from what you guys said last night, right?
DMC 1 is very Resident Evil. 3 onward is fine
Hmm, you think 1 still holds up?
It probably does
But I would want to do the ones with a similar gameplay structure
Before I go back into the other ones
It absolutely does not. Oh, no
Can I get to 100? Well, if I wasn't RP walking around
Maybe I could have
Come on. Don't I get to 97? Ah, shit. Okay
Did you see how I beat that in two or three tries?
After I said I'm gonna uninstall the game. I said the same thing about Elden Ring, Millennium
That's how I know I have to beat it. That's the best way to do it
Okay
All right. I'll take an A for the first time
The entire playthrough at the last boss sounds good to me
Yeah, that that was about my report card. I'd say that's pretty close. I do hate being considered normal
So play it on hard
Okay, cool
All right. I'll see you guys later
Let's save it again just in case I want to open this up for any reason and I'll see you guys later
I'm glad I beat it. I'm glad I saw it to the end
Just had to threaten to uninstall it a few times to just to get myself seriously in that mode
I gotta pull that card out sometimes. Yeah, I'm glad I played it
I will probably play the other ones too at least maybe five
I would say five is probably would be next up before the next time you will see me live will be on the
Let's see, maybe saturday saturday, maybe sunday sunday the 21st
We'll see I might reverse the late saturday if that's possible plan on sunday, but there might be a reverse delay to
Start on saturday plan on sunday though. Thanks for watching. Thanks for putting up with my complaints
Mmm, I don't think this was not really a complaint stream not till like the last two hours
Hmm. No, I mean this was a kind of a complaint stream the last couple hours were I agree. They were observations. Yeah, that's fine
Also, I I have no idea what happened and I'll be lying if I
Was saying that didn't throw me off that like explosion shit from earlier that like really fucking threw me off big time
Uh, I don't know why that happened if it was a bug in the game. That's a really awful bug
I'm not gonna say that's what it was because I don't know. I have no idea why that happened
Who has any idea at this point?
I'm just sorry that that happened because I wish it didn't because that shit sucks
Especially when you're not prepared for it. So I don't think I mean
Look what I mean. We played I didn't change any settings. I didn't make any changes
After 15 hours in the game as the only time that happened. I don't I mean my obs is fine. My audio system's fine
I have no idea
I wonder if that really was an ultra rare bug that hung up the computer for a second and then
The audio just went crazy for those of you that thought that was really funny. I'm glad you did
But for those of you that didn't think that was funny. Yeah, i'm sorry. I I
Wish it was easier to control that kind of stuff from happening, but be careful. Take care of yourselves
I'll see you Sunday or Saturday. Take care of yourselves. Have a great night and thanks for watching as always
See you guys Saturday or Sunday. Take care. Call your mother get some sleep. See you soon