Hey, what's going on everybody? How you doing? I am doing good. I apologize for starting on time
today. I was gonna start like 20 minutes ago, but I got a text message that I had to respond to.
I had to talk to somebody really quickly. And what do you have it? How do you know? Here we are.
Well, I was texting for 20 minutes. I had to text and I had to do something
because of the text that I received. You understand what I'm saying here. Okay,
give me a second. I'm gonna play Hitman 2 tonight. I'm excited for this game because
the first one was my game of the year when it came out a couple years ago.
And I am so stoked to play this game. I'm so excited for it.
It's gonna be hard. Oh, sorry. It's gonna be a ton of fun.
As you can tell, I'm fucking excited for it. So, see you guys in a minute. Get a water.
Uh, another Labo stream. No, no, no. Kim and I built the, uh, Kim and I built the jet
with the plane and then I have the submarine that's gonna sit there for a rainy day.
So you might see the submarine built six months from now. You never actually go.
You're just sitting there silently watching chat like a creep. That's correct.
That's that's a 100% correct statement. Anytime I tell you guys, oh, I'll be right back in the
grab yourself some drink. I hit the mute button and I stand here. I just sit here and
uh-oh here it comes. Okay, there we go. Yeah, I just sit here and stare. First joke of the
night. It's weird because like you guys don't know what I'm doing. I could be doing
anything when I hit that mute button, but typically I'll sit there and make sure my
tweet went through and then I'll stare at chat for a little bit. Well, you know,
because it takes a while for people to realize that there's a stream going on or if they're
watching somebody else, maybe they stay there. Maybe they see the notification and get over
there quick. Uh, but you know, maybe like 10 minutes. I like to kind of just, just relax,
you know, you know, you could be, you could be watching anyone on Twitch. I don't listen.
You see that J that J nine eight five fucking pop up window in the top right corner
and you go like this and you can't, you do, you miss it like four times because you're like,
I can't, I have to go now. No, I'm just kidding. That's what I just did.
You think way too highly of yourself. I'm just kidding. That's a joke.
If you're new to the stream, we go back and forth both. Hey, if you're new to the stream,
welcome to one of the top 1000 Twitch broadcasters. No self-esteem allowed. No,
just a, just enough, just enough, right? Cause all my self-esteem is about to go off the window
when I can't find the guy I need to talk to in the first tutorial in the game. You know what
I mean? Oh man, like top 1000 Twitch streamer. Okay. Welcome. Okay guys. How are you? I'm
pretty great. And then I'm going to miss a blip and I'm going to drive by the same blip
like three times. So like that's probably that. And then I'll be like,
yeah. All the confidence just falls off the cliff. No, all jokes aside. Welcome. Have a great day.
That's not the button I wanted to press, but still whatever. I've got, I've got a,
I have a stream deck now and it's actually pretty interesting because I can do so much
weird shit with it. There we go. Oh, he's really scruffy. He's wearing a wig. Oh,
and by the way, I was able to pause it right at the opening cut scene. So take a look at
that. Wait, I got to make sure everyone's ready. Are you everybody ready? No, not yet. Okay.
Okay. I'll wait till you're ready. The story. Were you ready? You guys ready? Okay. So far
agent 47 and his handler, Diana Burnwood are the world's top assassins working for the ICA
when all of their recent missions turn out to be contracts at Sean Bean client,
things take an unexpected turn. There's revolver also have been operatives in an
invisible organization known as Providence. Providence has infiltrated the highest echelons
of power and secretly owns our world. The shadow of Sean Bean wages a silent war against
them. And so the constant Providence is enigmatic controller. You're going to
get sick. Track down and eliminate the shadow client. In return, he offers something
irresistible. The truth of 47 lost origins. We don't know where he's from. The man they hunt
is 47 childhood friend. It's gonna be really and unlike 47 normal, right? He remembers
everything. Oh, agent 47's past that we did not know before. Nice. He's from Ontario.
Whatever. Quebec, actually, but okay. Oh, this looks good. This looks slick. All right. I didn't
like relax. I've been looking forward to this game for a long time, though. Like the first
one was so fun. This is actually like runs beautifully. Hold on a second. I need to change
this. I'm also keyboard. You're gonna take it's always so high at fucking DPI. Wait,
wait a minute. Hold on. Can I press the DPI button? Oh, I can.
Understood. Reynard's house is just up the beach. Our intel indicates that she and her team
are laying low, most likely planning the militia's next strike. Reynard is one of the
shadow clients top lieutenants, and yet she's not a target. Not yet anyway. She's no doubt
high on our client's list. But for now, it's information we seek. Infiltrate the house.
I can't play in the water. I want to go like splash around in the water.
On my way. Search the house for Intel on the shadow client. Bones. Dinosaur bones. 47,
those are trekkie otopto bones. A land animal from the Jurassic period. This game looks
amazing. Like I'll say it again. Press C to sneak. The first Hitman was my favorite
game to come out a couple years ago. So you have to imagine that it's just more.
All right, so we get to sneak into the penthouse. I'm gonna get Intel. Is this how the UI is?
All right, I just sneak around in the grass. And if there's a brick, I'm throwing a brick
through the window. Control is the instinct. Okay, we've got a diaper up there, a diaper
over there. Depends on which diaper I want to use. Okay, I mean, that's a security camera.
I definitely don't want to walk in front of the security camera. Why go in here and
rob this guy or kill this guy or whatever? I could just come here every day and just watch
whatever movie he's watching. I could bring my whole family out here and we could just call
his house and inception shit into his head. If we wanted to watch Infinity War tonight,
bring the whole family out here. Just call them. Be like, oh yeah, sir, this is your
credit card company. We didn't want to make sure that we declined that purchase that you
made of the rental of Infinity War, one of the top movies of one of the top movies of 2018.
I just want to make sure and highly rated too. Do you want to accept those charges? Are you
sitting down tonight? Are you in front of your couch? Oh, fuck, dude, I want to accept those
charges. And then we like all sit down and we just watch. Okay, well, here's I guess I
can stop crouching. Equip your pistol. I and then enter. Sorry, I had to. All right,
destroy camera. I want to. There we go. It's broken. Oh, that feels clean.
That didn't destroy it. Got it. Good day. Now, according to the local home security provider,
the house is equipped with multiple cameras around the perimeter. I suggest you get rid of
them. But I can't. I don't want to do that. Oh, I guess. Come on. I got it. I think that
should be it. That's the that's the last camera, I think. Right. Got that one. Okay.
There's a couple of options. There's one over here. And I already saw them. I'm so excited
to play this game. Can you tell? Hey, can you tell guys? There's one over there too.
Can I get that long range? Check this to I'm so good at everything.
At everything. Okay, we got we got a screwdriver. In this case, we need it.
That's me. That's me. Okay. Yeah, guys. I'm so good at everything, even though I can't
even determine what my own reflection is. Alright, search the house into holstering,
holster an item. All right, you look at the Intel. Oh, you gotta love that noise.
They thought of everything. All right, open door G. I can't I'm actually able to go key
use the key missing. Okay, I need a key. We tend to keep looking around here for Intel.
Smash the door. Wait a minute Intel short circuit with the run over your garage.
You take your garage door opener. There we go. What's all this? What is aiming down here?
Is it a disco ball? Or is this something I need to pay attention to?
All right, G. Oh, 30s. Executed. I see them. Bastards. Looks like Reynard's grizzly
handiwork. All right. He was never shy about collateral damage. The owners don't think so.
The house is registered to a non-existing environmental NGO. This feels more like identity
theft. Like you, Reynard is known to use disguises. Toy, I'm dealing with another 47.
Nothing we can do for these people now. Okay, I got Intel f1. Murder victims. A deceased couple
of people have been discovered in the garage and the cause of death appears to be execution.
There it didn't. We just she just told us all these. She just told us everything.
All right, search the house for Intel. We've got some stuff to look at here. I don't like,
I don't like G. Masks, rope, chloroform. Looks like another kidnapping. I wouldn't put it past
them. I think I'll test it to see if it works. If not industrious. Why is he doing this?
Clearly he has an axe to grind with Providence. Big enough to surround himself
with murderers and terrorists. Big enough not to care who gets hurt in the process.
He believes he's doing the right thing, I suppose. Just like everyone else. Diana,
if I stop talking, I drank too much chloroform. Tell my son his trush fund password is 1-1-1-1.
Why am I doing all this? Um, oh, these all work. I'm just a maintenance guy testing QA.
I can't unlock. Why am I holding a car battery? I don't know. I need a lockpick.
We got, uh, expired can of spaghetti sauce. And you can spaghetti sauce people. This might be
the best game ever. You know what I'm saying? Like, all I want is to be able to spaghetti sauce
people in the head. Like, that's all I want. It's the only thing I've ever wanted in a
video game. And apparently it's here. Do I need this? Ooh, what's on TV today?
Oh, we got, looks like the window blinds. Oh, yeah, turn them off. Make sure nobody can see in here.
Piano. Close them all. Oh, this is the other side of the window. What do we got? Intel.
Phone ringing. Bathroom ventilation system. What a weird sink. Oh god, it actually works!
What? Holy shit, your sink sucks. Uh, can you come and fix the sink instead? Because I just
turned my water on and within five seconds my whole bathroom flooded. The design of that
sink is not good. What about the shower? Is it actually going to fill the whole place?
Let's do it! What the fuck? Hold on, so you can, you can like throw a toaster and you...
Okay, that's fucking ridiculous. 47, I'm trying to find Intel. Diana,
Intel on the criminal. I don't know that throwing a car battery while standing in water
is a bad idea. Eat shit!
Wait, did somebody just say frame rate? Are we losing frames? It's fine? It's all right?
Okay, it should be somewhere close to 60. All right, let's go. Well, that's,
that's an indication of what's to come. This already is my favorite game of the year.
That's all it took. Seriously.
No, I can't, I can't just do this. No, I can't! I have to get out of here. Can I get in
the bathtub and turn the water on? I don't think I can. No, I can't get it now. Got it. I just have
to sneak and get it. All right, is there anything else? He says the bathroom ventilation system,
he said, was fucked up, right? I don't even, I need this key. I gotta go in like his bedroom.
It's a nice house. Curt, I can just, can I hide in here or is this... Okay. I'm sorry
I'm taking so long doing this. I'm just, I just love this game. Okay, found the bedroom.
I don't know, I think maybe I shouldn't close up blinds. There's a lot of places to,
holy shit. All right, settle down. What have we got? A drink, glass of whiskey.
I don't even know whose this is. Oh my god, really? Like, this, there's so many things. It's
like a dead rising, the amount of random things you can just pick up here. Okay, did I miss
anything? Let's go this way. All right, there's a computer over there. Wait, camera. No,
I already got it. I can't get through this door. All right, I need to get to that computer.
All right, this way. Uh, I didn't look over this way though. Let's check the other side.
Uh, there is a bench over here. I don't know what this has anything to do with Intel,
but I have it. Oh, what's this? Coin. Why is it all the way out here? Blend in.
All right, I'm sorry guys, but like, if somebody happens to be swimming in the
ocean right now, I'm sorry. You know what I'm saying? But it's going to happen. I'm sorry.
I just electrocuted everybody that was in the ocean. I'm playing Hitman though. I had to
test it. What's this? Fire poker. Oh, more tools to fucking go crazy with upstairs. Wait.
Yeah. Think of all the fish. That's like, that's like 600 million fish that I just
fried right there. So you can see even the bird, like all the fish coming out.
They're like getting fried and flying up in the air. See, those are those are fish
that are fucking flying out of the ocean. Cause the electricity is just everywhere.
This looks like something I can do here. Maybe not. What about with this? Can I like
break this thing? Poison. The panic room ventilation. Uh, I'm just fucking up this
guy's whole house. I'm poisoning every inch of this guy's house. Poisoning. Hey,
your panic room, your whiskey. Where is this person? All right. That's okay. Panic room
ventilation. That's, this is the bathroom up here. This is solar panels. Okay. So the real
question is how do I get to the room with the computer? Cause this brings me back here. I need
to get in there. I think it wasn't already in there. Unlock the door. Come on. Can't pick the
lock. Crowbar. Can't break it open. Where's my quick like weapon wheel? Go into the panic
room and breathe heavily. God damn it. Do I not? I don't know. I thought I had a crowbar.
I did before. Where is it? No, it's a lead pipe wrench screwdriver. I can't unlock the
screwdriver. Did I lock myself out of the house? How did I lock myself out of the house?
Did I press a button and lock the doors? All right. Well, this is, I was already here.
I like went through this whole house already. Go to the garage. What the hell is their garage?
How did I, how did I do this? What do you mean the garage? What, what's in the garage?
The most, yeah, I, I know the moment the dead people, but did I like fuck up the whole
house? I can't unlock this either. Stop. Stop it. All right. Computer. This thing's got
to drive me crazy. I'm going to go upstairs. This is going to drive me crazy. 47, that computer.
Got the computer. Can't access it. Encrypted. Assuming there's a key,
Reina wouldn't just leave it lying around. Wait, according to the floor plan,
the room you're in should be a lot bigger. Okay. Might be a concealed space behind the wall.
Check the hidden panels. 47. She's still talking out there. Alexa. Alexa. Alexa, stop. Alexa.
Play season one of house. MD. Got it. This should be interesting. Panic room. Oh, oh,
wait, hold on. This is the panic room. Should I not be in there? All right. I'm ready.
Nicely done. 47. Password dongle. To move more freely. Here we go.
For the office computer, no doubt. What about this one? Okay. See, I unlocked the shortcut.
Kidnapping plan. It appears Reynald's cell is launching another strike. There's a sewer
house of a residential area in Wellington. Well, there's nothing we can do about it now.
Our priority is the shadow client. I got it. I got it. I got it. Everyone just relax.
Okay. Back up to the... I'm sorry, Alexa, but you made me do this.
Where are you, Alexa? Thank God. Until they work the bugs out. They'll send me another one.
I'm detecting movement up the road. A motorcade. Possibly Reynald's. Uploading the data. Hold on.
Receiving it now. Nothing on the shadow client or the other cells. No names. No aliases.
I doubt she even knows whom she's working for. Wait. Here's something.
A message from Robert Knox of Cronstadt Industries. And by the sound of it...
Crunk. Crunk. Crunk. A defector. Well, well, well. Client won't like this one bit.
And you can't wait to tell him. They're back. Hostiles. I see them. Damn. Here we go.
Okay. We've got all we're going to get. Go to stage two, 47. Stage two. Eliminate Reynald,
and preferably without raising suspicion. One step ahead of the shadow client.
What about the grenade I threw in his living room? Let's keep it that way.
Oh. This guy walks in. Alexa. Alexa two and Alexa three.
What a snob. Where's my trio of Alexas?
You didn't even miss out on the action. I'm sorry you had to endure all that free
champagne and cello music, Orson. What can I say? You really took one for the team.
Well, I say stick to what you know.
Drag me out into the street and shoot me.
I'm equalizing, guys. I want to make it like it's like John Wick 3. That's going to happen.
There's going to be a huge fight and John Wick is going to run out of bullets. And then the
antagonist is going to run out of bullets. And then there's going to be like a pipe on
the ground and like a butter knife on the like right next to him. He's like a restaurant.
And he's going to be like, hey, you out? Yeah, I'm out. Huh. What do you say we do this
the old fashioned way? He's going to throw the butter knife over like this.
How do you throw harder? Go and see what it is.
How do you? I want to throw it harder. Oh, come on. Oh, that don't work.
All right. All right. Okay. Still one of their cars. Silent takedown for that. What? Oh,
this isn't this is not the simulator. I'm currently concealed. What's with that blur?
Game really does not want me to be over here. That was a really good silent explosion.
Body found. Oh, no. Come on. I got silent kill. What's this blurry shit? Am I game broken?
How do I like? Oh, oh, fuck. Oh, I shouldn't have done that. I didn't even need to do that.
This is so far away. Have discovered your boat 47. They're on high alert,
combing the beach for intruders. I skipped this whole mission. Well, I did it. Wait,
this guy turns around. Should I squeak? Should I kill this guy with a squeaky toy?
Can I squeak it? I wish I could just press a button and have it go like,
oh, man, my game's actually kind of running like shit. Oh, right. Squeaky toy assassin
kill here. Squeaky toy kill. I'm going to stuff it down his throat. See it's in his mouth.
Still got it in my hands. No way to get past them unnoticed. I suggest you cause a
distraction. 47. I'm gonna have to like turn something off. A distraction. Okay. I can do
that. No, I can't. Right. Loud. Squeaky toys a lot. The thing just exploded. Shit. All right.
Hold on. Let me like turn off a couple of settings. I don't think I can. Super sampling.
Level of detail. Texture quality. 1080. Let's turn that off. Ambient occlusion.
How's that do? That feels a lot better. Holy shit. This game with the ambient occlusion
on just, just kills my frames. Well, nevermind. It's back. All right. Here we go.
Uh, I, I'm just going to throw a coin. Does it, will it make a loud noise on the,
no, hold on a minute. It's like, dude, I'm not doing something over there. Watch this.
Okay. Here we go. Got one. Well, he looked like he was about to look.
What if I just go over here? Will they see me if I do this?
Hey, you'll want to have a look. Guys. All right. Well, there it is. Flawless.
Hey, they said make a loud distraction. Excellent work. 47. Ooh. Suit only. Mastermind.
Don't tread on me. Discover a hawks Bay. So that's interesting. You can see, you could do
I saw. Okay. There's a lot of things I could do there besides the role of grenade in front
of her. All right. Well, that was funny. That was fun. I just got to, I'm, I'm streaming it
at 60 FPS right now and playing at 60 FPS. That might not, that might not be a good idea.
I might have to tone it down a little. I got one star on the tutorial. Yeah. Cause
I threw a grenade three times in somebody's living room. So here's the interesting thing
about, uh, numbering your games and redoing them and redoing them and making new sequels
and sequels and sequels. The client has given us carte blanche hunt down the militia
30 years from now. How many hitman twos in the building? Providence was a threat.
How did you swing the board? The board of practical people. 47, a blank check.
What are the four hitman twos? The shadow clients war on Providence is causing a global
panic. Someone will need to stop the militia might as well be us. And the man on the
train taking a contract for personal gain is against ICA regulations. She's supposed
to be targeting sodas would have been proud. Oh no, I thought I had a broken game. It's just
a whatever next crying at the movies. Why are you doing this? I know what it's like to have
everything. I know what it's like to lose claims to know about your past, your childhood,
your memories, everything. Old Maya stole from you and you trust him about as far as I can
throw him. But this is our best lead in 20 years. I say it's time we break a few rules.
I mean, I'm not going to give deduct points for that. I mean, honestly, in a game like
this, do you really matter if it's like a cinematic kind of like comic book style
cinematic? Like that's a lot of development times, a lot of animation, like spend the money on like
throwing bricks at people. You know what I mean? Like they did. We can see you haven't
completed your training. We recommend that you complete advanced agent training before
continuing the story. Okay, fine. I'll do my homework. I also have to walk around a
little bit and make sure that I can stream this at 60. But it's just the training from
the first game. Oh, is it really? Oh, damn it is. But let me just make sure it wasn't
just that level. Welcome to the agent program. This is running fine. I'll be waiting for you
inside. Follow the lines. Okay, how do I leave? What the hell is going on right now?
Pro tip it hit man and then hit man too. Is it? Do they have the other game in here?
Really? Hold on a second. So you get the first all the episodes from the first game,
the second game and then this other little campaign for one for the same price.
Oh, okay. If you own it already. Okay. All right. Like I was gonna say, holy shit.
All right. So we got blank check and then here's the first mission finish line.
Good afternoon, 47. Your destination is the annual global innovation motor race in Miami,
Florida. That would've been crazy. After analyzing the data from Reynard's computer,
the case is clear. The providence defectors are Robert and Sierra Knox,
head of robotics, developer Cronstadt industries, a visionary inventor and technological innovator.
Robert Knox has spearheaded Cronstadt. That's not a very good food for him.
Where's the whole grain is equally. Not only a financial wizard, but also
a fiercely competitive race car driver with a fiery temper to match
it.
Cronstadt.
BBA.
Last year, despotic ruler Jin Po employed prototype Cronstadt drones against peaceful
civilian protesters in the now infamous Tungan Valley incident. And although it has yet to be
proven, there is little doubt that the Knox's personally broke the deal, making them complicit
in a war crime. It is unclear why the Knox's would betray their masters, but likely the fear
of being next on the shadow clients hit list has pressured them to cut a deal with the enemy.
Undoubtedly with Cronstadt industries on their side, the militia will increase their attacks
tenfold. And so our contract obligates us to retire Robert and Sierra Knox and contain
the damage they may inflict on Providence. I believe you.
So let's take a look. Objectives. Let's just see. Target Sierra Knox. Eliminate using any
method and you can wear any disguise. Kill conditions and intel. We don't really have much.
She suffers from inferiority conflicts in relation to her father. Highly invested in the Cronstadt
racing team and is the company's lead driver. Okay, so this is the driver. And then we got
Robert Knox. Any method, any disguise. Let's see, let's pick out one because technical
skills and reputation catch the attention of a powerful group of people. The race's CEO
killings Knox feels the ground burning beneath his feet and so makes another bold
life decision. He contacts the terrorists through a dark web connection and offers him a deal.
And you spare him to get the digital keys to his Warcraft account. All right, planning.
Smuggled item. What do we got? Complete additional challenges to unlock. So this
is the only place I can put it and I don't, do I have anything? What do I want to put
in here? Pistols. I mean, the pale duck. There's an explosive duck in the game. Suit.
Florida suit. All right, yeah. And start of the event. We're just gonna do it the
way that it's supposed to be done. So difficulty. Professional. Assassination is serious business.
You plan, you execute, you escape, and your handler is right there giving you the guidance
you need to succeed. Unlimited saves. All mission story guides available. Surveillance
cameras active. Cameras alert. Guards have illegal activity. Spotted combat is challenging
but fair. That's fine. I'm not doing master. The missions in Hitman can be solved in
countless ways. One approach is to uncover some of the many missions stories and follow
them through. When you uncover a mission story, you will have an opportunity to get
help and guidance. Since this is your first time in Miami, you may choose to have a
guide active from the get-go. I don't think I'm, I don't think I need to do that. No,
it's uncovered. I don't want a guide. This is how the other game worked. You kind of
stumble upon objectives and intel and you can choose to act on it or not, right?
You kind of just have to walk around and look at stuff. This is a great intro
to like a real estate infomercial. The innovation race is on its last day
and it is down to the wire. Thousands of eager fans are gathered for the final
lapse of this unexpectedly close race. Sierra Knox is expertly piloting her red
Kronstadt car. Her father, Robert Knox, roams the nearby Expo building where Kronstadt
is showcasing its new prototype car. Cool balloons. The Kronstadt RK Mark III has
seen fierce competition from the Chinese Kaowoon Heavy Industries new racer.
Moses Lee, CEO of Kaowoon, has taken a dominant lead. Can I drive?
There's like endless amounts of things I want to do here.
Is this just a CEO race? Oh man. Eliminate Sierra Knox, eliminate Robert Knox.
What are you doing, Otto? What's the matter?
Okay, so I mean I see the guy in the mascot suit. I'm out of here. Who is that?
Don't ever hand me a pantslet again. All right, hold on. Otto, what's the matter?
No, don't load that. Just replay. Here, please go throw away this card.
Yeah, I know. I understand. It's like just, you know, have a big sign with all your info
on it, right? People hand out pamphlets and, how do I skip this? There you go.
Like people hand out pamphlets and, oh here's this. Take this. No, just stand next to a
giant sign and have it say, add a funny Snapchat filter if you take a picture in
front of the sign. Pamphlets, people just throw them away. What do we got here? Wire.
So the Global Innovation Race is a major sporting event taking place in Miami every year
besides the endurance race itself, which runs over the course of two days. The social aspect
of the race has exploded over the years, going from being mostly an enthusiast event,
it's now a major public event complete with exclusive areas for VIPs.
Okay, the exclusive driver's lounge features nightly parties and often sees the attendance
of various celebrities. So here's the driver's lounge and here's the entrance. So the
driver's lounge is to the right. Okay, interesting intel. Give me a second. I have
bring Otto downstairs because I think he might have to pee. So give me one second, I'll be right
back. All right, I'm gonna need to run back down there in just a minute. Let's grab something.
But anyways, okay, so here's the entrance. Welcome. Oh, no, I have no items. Okay,
that's fine. Why do I have to, I don't have to wait in line.
Okay, thank you, sir. This will be over in no time. Why do I have to wait in line?
Okay, let's go, sir. Thank you. All right.
Oh, man, this is wild. Can I take this car? Free photo shoot. Blending into the crowd. Yeah,
I mean, this is so accurate. This is just too accurate. They have those like monster
boots. Goodbye, man. Grab a can. Photo. Intel item. Let's see it. Flamingo mascot Polaroid. A
Polaroid picture of one of the race mascots dressed as a flamingo. Okay, just blending in.
So where are they? Well, there's the flamingo. Hold on. Let me see the flamingo. I have to
do the flamingo thing. You know what I mean? How could I not do the like Mario
card character? I need to like follow this guy around. He's all the way over there. She's
in the race, right? She's in the car. Hold on. I'm going to save it. Let's start a new slot
here because I'm not starting from the very beginning. I just want to look. So here's the
track. My god, this is so much. I want to get a good view. French fries, hamburgers.
How can I not do the Mario card character? I know. How much more is there? These outhouses.
Can I actually go see the track? Her car's out there.
Where does it come across? It comes across right here. Holy shit.
Wow. Wow. Can I be a crazy fan and like rush to like go run over there?
This race sucks. I can't jump over that. I can see. Hold on. There's a way over here.
Oh, there's a. Hold on. Let me just get a look. Police car down here. Exit. There's
got to be a way to get on the track, right? Okay. I'm not supposed to be in here.
All right. Parking. No, it's definitely not down here. It might be though.
Parking is the exit. No, let's try this way. I'm going to have to sneak through here up
and around. Yeah, I'm going to start over and do it again. I just need to see if I
can get over there. Oh, Jesus. No, I can't push them. All right. I'm going to put this on.
No, there's no cars to push them to do. Oh, they knew you were going to try to do it,
didn't they? They knew it. They put these barriers up here. Bastards. They put the
barriers. Oh, that's too bad. Dump. No, I want to dump them. If I'm going to dump
them, I'm dumping them like into the road. I might be able to do it. That's pretty close.
If it gets done correctly, I seem to wait for the one. Psycho. All right. Can I throw
them over though? That's the question. Nobody else on the other side here. There's people up
there. Dump. Okay. I'm going to wait for the next pass. And how about right now? Shit.
No, maybe I can get down there from here. Holy shit. There he is. Where's the guy?
That is Robert Knox. Genius inventor. Black market weapons to knocks down.
Now for the heir to the Kronstadt empire. All right. All right. All right. Which car is she?
I don't have any items. No. All right. Let's load it. Let's go back. I don't think I can
get over there. Let's try and do like an actual scenario. That's too bad. I wish I could
just like stand in the road. You probably can somewhere down there maybe. But let's like
actually try. I want to let's let's try to get some intel on the fucking bird person
brought to you by guardian. You got an imitation there, sir? Nope. I've got so much pure energy
though. All right. Here he goes. So he can go through the VIP access. We need to watch
and see what he does. I need to complain about this. This is bullshit. No, no, no.
Go get Chris. Go. You go get Chris and tell him I'm out here. Sir. I don't know who Chris
is. Chris is like he's here at the party right now. Go get him. I just I just work security
detail man. I don't know what you're talking about. I want you to call Chris. He's the
DJ's friend and he's in there. All right. What was I doing? Oh yeah. I want to try.
Oh I got I got to run back downstairs. One second. I will be actually one second this
time. Give me one sec. Okay. Sorry about that. I wanted to make another cup of coffee
because I'm having a fucking blast. Let's do it. All right. So I need to find the
I need to find the unlockable Mario Kart character. Meet the drivers. Hold on.
Complementary beverages. Yeah. Sorry dude. Leg up. In fact, fuck out of the way.
My turn next. What did you say? Do you see what I'm drinking dude? It's a noxious
energy. Hey dude. Can you sign my noxious fuel can? Such a big fan man. Hey I'm gonna
get a tattoo of you on my ass tonight. Can I get a pic bro? Fuck. My walnut desk.
Do we get a fake news thing here?
It's literally it's literally my turn. Okay. So hey bro. Can you sign my scissors dude?
I got him. I got him. I can't believe I got him. He signed him. Oh I am never
going to get anything done. Oh I'm never gonna get anything done. It's not good. I'm
gonna have to say this is gonna be like playing an emulator with save states everywhere.
I already love this game. There's already so all right so I want to like get the uh
where do I want to go? I feel like I'm at Disneyland right now. There's a bunch of rides
to get on. I just don't know which ride I want to get on. Can I do anything over here?
Oh Jesus. Furt Fernandez just gave 10 community subs. Thank you Furt. That's a
lot of subs. Here comes Tim Allen for about at least a straight minute. Thank you so much man.
Okay. What's over here? Nothing over here. All right I gotta let me I gotta figure it out what
I want to do. I think I want to follow the flamingo. So the flamingo meet the driver is
that. I think flamingo comes over here. Do I have any like any intel on the bird? No I
just have a picture of him. He comes out he dances out here. If I go this way. The true
target. The bird. So there's a bathroom. I can go over there. Let me see. Just let me walk
around again. It's a parking lot. Let's go down to the parking lot. Parking. Stands. Tunnel.
All right. We've got some options here. You've been caught by a camera.
I think I need another one of these. Fountain view.
Did I just get some intel?
Yeah.
Excuse me but it really freaks me out when people stand too close to me.
All right. Unlock the door. That door's locked. Kill employees only. All right there's a camera
up there. Whoa that just drove. Whoa what the fuck was that? That was loud. All right what
we got here? Oh we've got event area key. We've also got got a race martial disguise
and a crowbar. That's all that's in here I think right? Put this away. Conceal item is another
restroom. Oh this is the one I was just in. All right. Um let me go over here because now I
have all this stuff that I need. Let me save it. And I'm gonna also uh no I'm gonna save
it here because this that's the beginning. I need to do this too unfortunately. Roof down
like times two. What's my memory at right now? Not that bad. Okay let's just head back up.
So ugly now. I mean I got. It's all good. All right so here we go.
There he is. There he is. There he is. Nothing matters. Okay.
Look at the documents from my van.
Really? All right I gotta put him somewhere. I got the flamingo outfit. Where can I bring you though?
That's so great. I had to knock a guy out. What does flamingo call? All right I can't drag him
over here. Does anybody actually walk down this path? They might not. Let's put him in the
shadow over here. Oh he's gonna wake up too. What's in here? I don't want to be walking
around with this. Slot machines. All right I got my parking ticket so I need my.
Let's take a look here. I got. Looks like someone illegally parked a beat up gray van
with a rusty green sliding door in the basement garage. In what slot is that in? I didn't tell.
So this is citation uh under the Cronstate Bayside Center beat up gray van illegally parked.
So does it say what D A B I guess. I'm looking for a beat up gray van. Let's just take a look.
That's not a van. That's not a gray van.
Gray van. No there it is. I can't holster it. Oh well. Place what? Oh hello. So break open.
I don't need to break open. I have the keys don't I? Did I not? Do I not have the guy's
keys? Hmm about this side. Oh yeah he lost his keys. Um I mean I could try it see what happens
here. Or maybe I should just throw something. Save it right here. No no no I want to just.
I mean kidding me. All right go get it. Either we got a poltergeist
or someone's throwing things at me. Oh god. Uh yeah hey. Clear here. So I dropped this sorry.
I just fell out of my pocket on the way up back here. Thanks for that.
The race is entering its final lap. Final lap? Final lap? Oh no that's fine. That's fine. All
right I got it. A pile of Cronstate documents that looks like they might be useful to an
investigative journalist or blackmailer. A note attached the document reads Sierra Knox
after the race next to the hotel. Bring documents be the flamingo. After the race
next to the hotel. All right I gotta find the hotel. Where's the exit? Okay this is fine.
Hotel. Uh I got. Do I have a map? Do I have a map? How do I open the map? M? M didn't do
anything. All right so this is. Where's the hotel? We'll go to level zero. Hotel.
Bayside Center Expo. That entrance. Got. Look at the hotel. Oops.
It was a huge fucking map. I just gotta get out to like above ground here.
That's the flamingo. The flamingo just woke up. All right here's the center. Let's go through here.
Hey all right uh screwdriver. Race is in its final lap right now.
So where the hell am I going? Is this gonna take me up? It should take me up and out
to where though? Right here. So here's the event entrance. Now where is hotel?
Agency pick up. Robert Knox. She is not there. I mean this might be it. 47 the race is over.
Okay. Sierra will be coming off the track anytime now. Mission story updated. All right
so now. I'm just walking around in a flamingo suit. All right so here it is.
My street circuit. Bayside Center entrance. I guess I could just follow her around.
Wait where? Hey and make sure to eat your front loops kids.
All right uh I need to get.
Parking. All right oh she's all the way across the goddamn universe.
Oh man. She is so far away. I gotta run there. You know how hot this would be in this suit?
Look at how many different things there are. Parking. Oh boy. She's far. I don't want to
go through there again. I'm overheating right now on this thing. Wait am I allowed to go
through here? I'm the I'm the toucan. The toucan is allowed to go through right? Yep all
right. I don't want to go back. The park entrance. Hotel. Hotel. Hotel. Hotel. Hotel.
Hotel. All right where's the hotel? Where am I going now? Is this the hotel? Discover Miami.
Is this a hotel?
Can I go in here? Show document. Oh hey. Excuse me.
Nice outfit. Really brings out your eyes. Ms. Knox informed me you'd be here.
She asked to make sure you brought the documents. I got them. So did you bring the documents?
I just showed you. I have the papers right here. Excellent. I would be in character the whole time.
I have the papers right here. Yes Ms. Knox. There's a guy here wearing a mask.
Hey stand on one leg. Hey flamingo guy. Yep. Proceed somewhere. She'll be here as soon as she can.
She'll be here as soon as she can. Okay. So it's a great outfit. Thanks. Thinking it
must get pretty warm in there though. It's insulated. Huh imagine that. I guess it would
have to be if you're supposed to wear it for hours and hours every day. Do you you know
I get to use it at home for parties and things like that. Oh god.
I have a friend who's into that sort of thing. Do you? Cosplay?
Assuming imaginary identities. It's you. He says it's very liberating.
Takes him out of the stress of everyday life and work you know. Look really.
Look do you do you want to smell inside of the head or not? Like is that what you're
going? Sufficient. Nice. Okay. You want to like pull the head off and you want to like put it on.
All right. Um let me save it. So she is on the way. There she is. Oh god. Oh god.
Do I have any how do I I didn't prepare anything. I didn't prepare anything.
Act natural. I have a screwdriver. That's all I have. So Mr. I never did catch your name.
Flavor bird. Flavor bird the pink boy.
So she has to be eliminated but I have a screwdriver. She has two bodyguards.
Meaning because my father doesn't need to know about this. It's just another undesired distraction.
I don't care if the information is true or false. I don't care if it mentions moving money from
three bodyguards into tongue and valley damage control as you claimed in your correspondence.
I do care about protecting my father which let's be clear you and I are having this
meeting because my father doesn't need to know about this. It's just another undesired
distraction. I don't care if the information is true or false. I don't care if it mentions
moving money from the nexus project into tongue and valley damage control as you claim in
correspondence. I do care about protecting my father which is why how do you think flavor birds
stay so fit if you need us just call so here's the deal you hand over the documents and leave
and that's the end of it okay and you will do that now okay so here are the two possible
outcomes of this meeting one you will leave this place in this country for good and that
will be the end target down next up robert knocks no get up
easy as pie okay we got one guy here no that's too loud how do you think the flavor bird stay
so healthy well well i broke i broke his neck i was trying to hit him okay i'm staying with
the bird the whole time can i dump him somewhere no i could dump him back here
i have to kill i have to complete this whole thing as the flavor bird
why did i kill this guy i don't know jeez all right did he turn into a genie what the hell was
that okay now we're gonna find robert knocks who is all the way over there no this is like an
illegal item but i think i'll be fine because i'm like a cartoon bird and i tom and jerry
let's get it saved right there nice and easy drop the bat you hey what why did i put the bat
away i karate chopped him i can't have the bat i need to kill all right i need to take the
bat with me somehow no i can't even take the bat what the hell seriously i'll be forced to
take action if you don't give up the bat i gave the bat up already what hey here's a little extra
vitamin c hey what about you no don't run away from me it's good for your bones don't move you
can't be here sir see that it's not safe here okay all right all right i'm ruining child
okay i need to put this away i can't take the bat do it well do it right oh that was so satisfying
just follow your nose yeah that's speaking of your nose it's about to be broken i'm sorry you know
i had to do that i had to make the follow your nose it's about to be broken thing all right
let's go kill robert follow your nose into your brain i didn't do shit get out of here
get out of here get out of here get out of here okay possible intruder so robert is all the way
on the other side isn't he but i want the shovel don't i now he's all the way down there all
right let's try to find an opportunity to go over that way i can make it through here
take a seat oh i'm i'm sick i've had it's not just a profession it's a lifestyle
can i am i allowed to be back here i mean this doctor's schedule but
sir you're trespassing well you could have told me that i'm fine okay so that's fine i'm gonna go
through here medical staff only all right stay safe i can't be over anywhere i'm not allowed
to be anywhere as the bird she did she wasn't she didn't make it clear enough there's only
room for one bird in this fucking town is this a threat is there some kind of threat
are you threatening me everybody knows that blueberry is better than lemon lime
do you think you're gonna take my cereal from me
no god damn it all right that's it we're gonna go to robert nox
i gotta get this fucking costume off it's it's taking me over it's the costume it was the
goblin don't you understand it wasn't me i'm jeremy it was the goblin it was the flavor bird
so i can't i have to go this way what if we okay well he's coming down the alley here
can we both go out as like a tandem show i think maybe we can if he's gonna walk all the
way down here we can put on a show together we have to do it together greetings sir he came
up like right now right hold alt to slow walk all right come on man it's the same safe state
okay we go
see where the it's like the barrio brothers here we go we're gonna go together can i do that walk
too i mean i'm trying to walk slow he won't walk slow holding alt he's doing the vince mcmahon
walk we really are doing like the chad thing this is the two sides of the image right here
all right here we go let me get it there we go there was a screenshot there somewhere
connecting all right let me like save the mission here what's on the other side of this door oh
oh that's it wait okay i thought we were going to like a stage oh there is all right all right
where's where's rob all right rob let's go wait i can go to vip okay wait i gotta blend in
with my bird friend he's up there wait the security check i have a gun security's busy
oh i just left i just left the vip all right where are you like a left vip
wasn't he up here though where the hell was he flamingo parking where was his blip
did he go down he went like the actual map okay he's in here so he's in level two of the
convention center i'm over here so if i go straight and then bang of right
he left two hours ago okay so if i go this way
i wonder if i can cross over here somewhere probably oh no here's the race okay i have to
go down i might be able to get this over there do i unlock door wait what i got a key
oh shit i'm trespassing as the bird though he's over there oh young man you can't be here
sorry sorry i'm out i'm leaving i'm leaving i'm leaving i'm gone i'm gone i'm out i'm out
i'm sorry i'm out i'm out i'm leaving i'm leaving i need to get that way who found the body
can you hear me all right i need to don't hit me i need to go across this way and i'm i need
to see the bigger map from here don't hit me so i gotta go over here so i gotta get out i gotta
cross this because this is the bridge that goes across the way and i'm definitely not
going the right way from here because this is gonna take me all the way across unless no
no i gotta go this way i'm not going the right way see now i am i gotta bang or turn around go
to the entrance and then go up through the parking level right no turn around the place
only behind this point which is not where i want to be i need to go this way a little alleyway
behind here but it's no big deal can't you just let us through how do i get through here
it's like a door there's a door right i think i can get through from here
yeah i can do it i'm an employee like i'm an employee oh honestly like how is it how
would this be illegal i'm here save it no right well let's save it before i murder
everybody i didn't murder anybody and then i can bang a left no just let him leave him on
all right where is he he's right there conceal okay yeah i i can't bring a gun in here
i'm trespassing as the bird rat poison screwdriver shit i i'm not allowed to be
here as the bird i've committed to the bird and i i'm not i'm not gonna be able to do it as the
bird unless i'm really sneaky all right there's a guy there which way is he looking is he gonna
notice that somebody gonna notice that this guy's in the perfect position to stare at me i need
to throw something i have two screwdrivers so actually it might not need to do that
guys sneaking around as a bird he's over this way okay who's looking oh i can't right there
like a spot about hey you this is a restricted area you need to follow me right now no question
both targets down well done i did the mission i completed it i completed the mission that's all
that matters i can't do this as the fucking bird they didn't say i had to stay alive you know
what i'm saying i just i did it that's the last mission ever but at least i completed it
the only way the bird is gonna work is if i throw the knife at him bird or no balls
fine you can't be here who do you think you are many times do i need to tell you to follow
sir i need you to follow me please i can't oh damn it
you've got a force to throw a screwdriver into somebody's head that deep that had to have
been shot out of a cannon god i don't want to do it i can't do this with the bird guys
there's too much security oh my god he's surrounded by people what the fuck what happened
all right this is my final attempt in bird costume i'm just gonna wait i'll wait for him i
just gotta wait for him to go to the right place just get in here eventually he's gonna come this
way just hide behind the couch what do i have crowbar rat poison no i'm just gonna push him
you've had seen this you walk into the room see fucking burdo behind the couch
and he's just hanging out over there holy fuck oh that guy's on drugs that's the only way you
would say never mind to that is if you just did like three different kinds of drugs in the back
room that guy just freaked himself out i had nothing to do with it where's he at all right
he's coming around he wanted to avoid confrontation here he is again try like scare him again oh my
god i need to stop doing crack before work see he's like looking at the wall and shit that
guy's here he comes no he's above me when does he come down oh god he's like wait could i is it
possible no he's not coming down here i gotta go up i dressed up take his clothes i can't i have
to do it as a bird control the situation oh my god it's a grenade where am i oh all right i'm
doing it the normal way i'm doing it the normal way the normal way i'm putting on the suit and i'm
gonna the way that you're supposed to do this no bird suit which i'm gonna do this the correct
way no balls i don't care i don't care where is he he's right there what's wrong with me
both targets down well done 40 second head for an exit and we'll speak again soon
who's up no shit oh no just take off the fucking suit now put on this guy's security costume
right now it's important it's not meant to be done like this it's meant to be done like this
oh for the love of god where is he what
it's harder without the costume god damn it flamingo and gun i don't want to just like
shoot him there's probably so many interesting things to do let me just go into like the
the room oh god oh this is the guy okay this is the guy we're taking this guy's costume
i'm bringing this guy into this room so come on in here yep like the guy that's on acid
this way he's right here what's he doing now he's going upstairs all right come on
right here look at the knife on the ground this fucking scientist whatever this guy is
come on somebody see the ghost and come in here you can't climb up the pipe you can climb down the
pipe all right trespassing come on what get in here don't move okay good excuse me what are
you doing here hey put the bird costume on that guy and now where's he going oh hi
it's me the guy that was just here that's true that's true true true you've been recorded by a
security camera go hold up security guy searching what do you hold up security guy i'm on the same
detail as you what the fuck that is what all right i'm leaving i'm leaving what
i don't understand what i did what happened why are you wearing that get over here
that gets up is not working oh not the right suit
shoot him what in the name of god you're superhuman i hate myself i didn't have the
right security costume on i what i didn't have the right outfit on hey security guy
hold on a second there security guy and of course he walks down here this time
hey i'm a security guy i know i walk too close to him i know i don't worry i'm good everything's
good everything's gonna be just fine now i know i can't go up there so we're gonna blend in by
okay am i allowed to go that's that guy can see through my disguise oh god there he is which
way is he going straight coming this way i'm just but i'm peeing in the plant
now part of the security is robert nox genius inventor black market's weapons dealer and
providence defector both target 47 head for an exit and we'll speak against soon get on
oh i did it i did it
yeah nice shot you got the golden gun give me a break i did it oh no i tried it it was right
there it's right there i got on it i just oh i panicked a little no he's not gonna come
this way again he dropped like a bag of bricks here he comes
what are you thinking how do i get out of here how do i get out of here i'm like locked in here
i think i think i think i can cross from here yeah cross from here and then
maybe not right here how do i get that way i can say i can go to that one
that's fun save save save yep good good good call and you said i wasn't going to do it as the
bird you guys were like do it normal take the costume put on the regular costume don't do it
as the bird don't i'm like i don't die i'm trying to do it i'm compromised but i'm blending
in why can i for the best congratulations 47 you can now use that costume on every level
then i have to play the whole game as the bird let's see the inventor the daredevil
someone could hurt themselves straight shot mission story pretty in pink briefcase flamingo
backdoor engineering blackmail pink menace 21 000 xp cool well come on that's i got level four
mission rating five i'm about to be levels about to be mission rating six almost five
and a half stars that's what you get for kill it well yeah i mean like i'm not going
for perfect ratings here i'm just trying to have fun i'm probably gonna get one star on every
mission a new location mastery unlocked reach miami level four so each place has their own
leveling system all loadouts lots are available okay gives you the option to use the loadouts
lost during the planning phase of this mission this can be used to bring items you've
unlocked into the level an ica briefcase can be used to conceal illegal items a fish effective
as a non-lethal blunt weapon okay that's cool a set of lock picks can be used to open locked
doors this one has the signature mk2 look 47 has slipped away from the main race event
it starts near a beautiful dolphin fountain he's wearing his normal civilian clothes
opened up the the mara marinara sauce mission store i thought this is this is another bird
uh completing a mission is just the beginning they are meant to be played more than once
there are multiple plots to uncover characters to get to know and unlocks to earn
to get the overall story of the finish line we recommend that you complete the following
mission stories so i did this one play mission story or skip that's cool that's awesome well
i'll come back to this it's just a brother was just bird two yeah i'll skip it for now
i definitely go back and play montreal we're bleeding operatives panic is spreading and now
we are axing our own nox was a traitor caused invulnerable damage and he won't be the last
this is exactly what the enemy wants to yell to each other they can't hear you from across that
way not the symptom and i have just the tool for the job eric soders warned you about it
didn't he that's a custom made table that's a whole treat i can handle miss burnwood everyone
hates power until you offer them some who is this a weirdo ica speaks the enemy's language
we need them and once we don't cross that bridge when we get there fact remains we are
shadow boxing we need to know who we are up against that's like every was getting to that
that's every like young anime villain in every anime you've ever watched is lucas gray the late
mr. cobbs head of security cob was ground zero first of our operatives to die
it had to be one of the staff someone with military training and access to the plane i think
it was 47 grasping at straws gray is a mercenary a veteran of every backwater tragedy you've
ever ignored on the five o'clock news chechnya sierra leone the list goes on but before 89
nothing no records of any kind event three cia kg scenes funniest spies went dark after the
curtain was lifted there uh i cast a very wide net lucas gray what's the in-between between
cinematic and still image what's it called it's called something specific
quite done wetting yourselves with excitement i couldn't give two shits where he came from
animatic i only want to know animatic yeah that's that's what how does he know about us
oh this is from the first game this hearts and flowers crap will get us both killed
can't you see your so-called friend is working for them now he's not the man you knew
this is his fight too even if he doesn't realize it like it or not 47 is our last and only lead on
the partners so he wasn't even a bad guy was he a good guy all the time he's coming for us
and unlike you he won't hesitate just get me inside rico i need a favor all right cool man
i have to pee again honest to god i don't know what's with the piss bullshit that i have i'm just
pissing i wish i had a urinal right underneath me i would just mute the mic make sure the
camera's not on and just piss straight into the ground i bring it back one more i one
more i'm drinking coffee too that's why beer back okay so let's keep going uh io interactive
is not completely on their own with wonder brothers that was that was surprising actually
when the i saw the splash screen when i first turned it on wonder brothers i was like okay
so it was finally the wonder brothers game division was doing pretty well recently although
i mean i can't really say that for some of their movies is it still an episodic game or
did they release it all at once it is released all at once i believe or am i wrong no it's
here wait is it is it is it is it a swedish i thought they didn't do that this time no
because i can't well how would i be able to play this next mission all at once same format
of season one contact has shared the identity of the shadow client a former mercenary and
bodyguard that's good i'm glad they did it like this gray his past is a black void but
our analysts are digging deep meanwhile we've had a breakthrough of our own comparing the
malicious attack patterns with global shipping and transportation routes we figured out how mr
gray and his paramilitaries move around the world how's the frame rates in by the way
they're using the distribution network gotten more stable columbia's big you might be pushing
it here clearly gray must have struck a deal with it all good good consequently if we can
cripple the cartel we can severely limit the malicious strike range but to do so we need to
slay a three-headed serpent sociopathic cartel head rico delgado and his two closest lieutenants
pr guru andrea martinez and servant chemist for rey franco with equal parts guts and guile
rico delgado runs a thriving billion dollar criminal empire the word is the brutal and
volatile cartel head is hell bent on becoming the number one drug lord in the world drugs
to achieve this drug lord a childhood friend of delgado's has been buttering up state leaders
and decision makers paving the way for an expansion of the delgado logistics network
while the brilliant but aloof and anti-social franco has been hard at work developing a new
type of new candy recipe super cocaine columbia's most infamous crime lords
inhabiting a decidedly hostile environment i would leave you to prepare super cocaine
all right so we need to get rid of rico uh or hey and andrea andrea all three of them
so objectives planning concealed weapon i mean i like the chrome gear uh aluminum travel
briefcase lockpick i don't want the fiber wire give me the lockpick or the coins
give me the lockpick lockpick and coins well fish too that's a good idea yeah lockpick and
fish casual tourist that looks good starting at the village bus stop i think i'm ready to go
just got to get rid of three heads of the snake 300 serpent in santa wherever was
santa somewhere fish only you can't kill people with a fish try turning down level of detail
and turning up uh anti-osotropic filtering anti-osotropic filtering i'll try welcome to
columbia 47 the remote village of santa fortuna awaits you deep inside the columbian rainforest
an iron-fisted delgado cartel turn down the level of detail turn up its surroundings
uh security and the closed off cartel compound is extremely tight
armed sicarios patrol the streets of the village ready to enforce harsh punishments
to those who do not comply if you're reading this you're in a coma wake up
we miss you of hidden transportation wouldn't that be fucking weird in the village
the cartel compound and the hidden coco fields beyond it is a rare occurrence to have all
three cartel leaders present in the village at the same time all right expect that all
targets are protected by scrupulous killers rico delgado inhabits his fortified mansion
on the outskirts of the village while andrea martinez can be found in her village office
all around santa fortuna itself i feel like it's gonna be big and Jorge Franco is engaged
in development of a new drug in his field laboratory oh my goodness happy hunting 47 oh
my lord there's so much all right so let's go into here and let's turn down the level
of detail let's put that to medium and let's turn up anti-osotropic filtering let's see
do we need to restart for that i don't think i do that's pretty good although who knows
let's see how this is pretty all right so we got hanging out guy over there
we have three roads to go down actually two i don't know who's right in front of us but
we're gonna go into here turn shadows to low and then turn that to 16 you sure shadows really
don't just cause problems always especially for streaming all right i'll do eight that's all i'm
doing no that would that is a compromise i was gonna do four and i turned it to eight i doubled
it all right
do you know where she is she should be back any minute on a scale of one to ten how spooky
your spot did he fall where did he fall down now they care now they care he cares now oh man
welcome to columbia 47 the remote village of santa fortuna awaits you deep inside the columbian
rainforest all right let's go can i do something with this guy oh man i just really love that
super cocaine can i throw fruit people all right let's find some intel he's not there
anymore never mind let me store the apple all right so i got wait a minute wait a minute
columbia mission story follow mission story guide so the ever classy rico delgado has commissioned
a statue of himself to adorn the village square today's unveiling ceremony will feature a local
band and rico delgado will attend in person i suggest you take a closer look 47 this should
be a unique opportunity to engage delgado outside all right let's try this compound
and can i knock the statue onto him sounds good sabotage the statue
what there it is so i gotta get up there and get to the statue
sure i was at the bar last night and the band were really good both with the music and drinking
but my husband told me nobody's seen them seen so that's why martinez and the delgado
are running around like hellish chickens must grind her gears to finally know how to think
okay uh let's just i have so many save files we're just gonna go here
that's the beginning of that one is beginning of this one i'm sure they're fine hey okay
it's mine actually nope you can't have it all right town plaza there's a statue here's
the band getting ready should i blend in with the band oh my god please tell me i can play
like the guitar or the drums or something i definitely can oh oh oh oh ah ah mission story
revealing no it's up there hey mister littering is against the law just saying i've been like
smuggling this cocaine souvenir around the world right i need to get it littering is against the
law man okay i'm in a hostel room compromised i need to take this outfit off all right i got a uh
what did i just get drug smuggler man a small note with some strange writing on it seems to
detail some sort of plan to smuggle a small souvenir through customs and airports around
the world apparently the souvenir is cast from pure cocaine is to be limited back intact to
jorge franco the cartel's chief chemist for some sort of unspecified taste test the note also
contains a recipe for what looks like to be very delicious hash brownies the worst sound of the
world
well i was trying to explore he's out of bullets he was out of bullets
fuck the statue so i'm gonna go the other way because that doesn't really wrap around
very well the guns feel actually pretty fun to shoot i'm sure they're fine so i need to go
up and around there am i allowed to go this way all right i didn't i didn't put that there
somebody else did i'm just taking apricots that's all i want i don't want anything
else besides apricots i think i can get up there this should take me around i think
amazing but no it doesn't foundation
hippo holding den all right um i probably can't go through here i'll be right back
well shit i'll be right back all right this is my opportunity he's gonna come take like
a piss over here and i'll be able to knock him out what's apricot this guy do you not see the
apricot come get me what are you doing apricot wow how do you not understand this oh fuck
why why did he spin around i need to dump these guys somewhere
i could put them over here damn it come on into the woods anybody coming down
well there oh the statue the statue the statue push it on him he's standing right there sabotage
i need a wrench oh god i need a wrench i need a wrench is there a wrench you got a wrench over
here there's a shrine i should have packed a wrench if i were a wrench where would i be
down here this looks like a little work area wrench i just need a wrench i don't care who
has one wrench you got a wrench over here no poison the coffee glass no just give me a wrench
no i just i don't want to play any games i just want to wrench i don't want you that is p power
real name paul powers celebrity tattoo artist and reality tv star who wrench all i care about
and i can't find one nothing well i need i needed to have that beforehand god damn it
all right where was mr um tattoo artist guy hold on let me check over here are they still
over there talking at the statue probably not at this point this a wrench would be over here
shit good buddy
oh i just woke that guy up restart with wrench not yet not yet i could probably go this way
i mean i can unlock this nobody around that guy is but opportunity hasn't failed yet
all right come on material something damn it i'm not on the rooftop right now there's a saw
no wow this guy's like a brick worker brick workers brick workers don't use wrench of course
there's a screwdriver up here there's a crowbar crowbar screwdriver where's the wrench
that's the place to hide let's keep checking over here
do you have a wrench scissors no wrenches why would a brick worker use a wrench in case they
needed to smash one that's a baseball bat somebody's just this music just blasting over
here soda can i'm just on the lookout for a wrench i just need oh yeah all right i'm going
in here these people need to shut the music off oh it's the drummer turn it off so i got
the drummer's house key whoa what's going on who's who the fuck is he dead so i'm now the
drummer did i just take his clothes off turn off the stove hold on turn off stove is still on
i need a wrench for a gas leak turn the stove off i don't even have enough to do a gas leak
here is this guy actually awake no this dude's dead this dude died in the bed
how do i pull her in here i'm going to call security if you don't answer me
what does he want what do you want just get in here i didn't get to save it yet get
look follow me in here follow me this way follow me here follow me follow me follow me follow me
follow me follow me thank you okay we're now the band member so where is the band
there they are all right they're waiting for me fellas i'm here sorry i was just dead
uh i think that we're practicing right now is there anything i can do over here though
that's statue it's the statue i need to get a wrench there's no crowd yeah because they're
waiting for me to figure out how to find a wrench come on right here wrench anything
who the hell is this did i do this to this guy is that a wrench
oh my let's go sabotage this thing and then we're going to play with the band
he's waking up the band members did i just throw water in that guy's face
so i already took out these guys people gonna start waking up here in a minute i gotta hurry
out trespassing yeah i'm aware oh fuck am i super trespassing too much though all right just go
wait what if it just toppled over all right let's go yeah here we go
i'm here guys there play the drums i'm pretty good at this
wait is she what is she doing here is she gonna sing
nothing's gonna fall
no that's the beginning
turn it up louder here i'll turn it up louder
so oh is she gonna sing really loud and it's gonna fall do i have to press a button
and hopefully i'll start dancing and it shakes the ground
turning to night here she's gonna start going like
she's gonna hit a really high note it's gonna fall um what am i supposed to do
he's not coming down he's not coming down
come on i gotta do something
which one is this one this one is this one right trying to shoot the fall cord
uh i i know you have to wait but i don't know i figured maybe i was i didn't put something in
place like that's what's holding it
oh i see you pull the cord it's the it's the big reveal i get it okay
you pull the thing oh here's the big reveal you can still see the statue though it's a
bad job i figured she can hurry up so smart i think you could push it if you're behind it
well that's why i got up because it was we're just kind of there's no it's just we're just
sitting there to me this is like uh the the computer's waiting for you to do something
play the drums as hard as you can until it falls what's he doing over there
he was fine in the body
drop the statue whose body did i have to hide what whose body did i have to hide
man he's very preoccupied finding bodies all right where is he there's a body
pick up the fucking body where can i put these where these go
i still hear drums who noticed a crime oh god damn it i'm bringing them up i'm bringing those
guys up with where the statue is he found he looks at them both i'm gonna put i'm gonna
drag them up to where the statue is i still hear drums shit no don't touch put oh my god
the wrong goddamn button i'm currently trespassing oh my that is rico del gordo
head of the del gordo drug cartel it's a they're finding this body over here
they're finding this one aren't they how are you finding that
he found the gun on the floor oh my lord
i gotta pick up it's the guy that's i could pick up a gun i'm in a bad spot here though
well because he's like on the way over here right now the guy in the bush is hidden but is
he though get out of the way and then his gun is on the ground where's his gun just see the
all right gun here's his gun all right i got his gun and let's see if the other guy's hidden
that i that should be it right here they come got it what body are they finding what body
that is rico del gordo are they looking up here how did you see that
rico del gordo has been
martinez is down good work go back to the other save i like like before i got the wrench
let me i gotta go back like like 15 20 minutes ago i did it that body just kept fucking me
every time i hide the body over the wall like the other guy all right well i'm gonna save this
like here because if i don't give a shit anymore i'm just gonna go all right here we go
then i'm gonna take the gun on the way back they're seeing this guy over the edge hurry
up go hurry up go go go go go go go and pick up the gun on the way out go
you can go faster than that gun got it i'm back sorry i had to take a piss
sorry about that let's save it again there they go all right body not found no we're good here it
comes it is my immense pleasure to present to you the benefactor of santorini the lion
the man was taking it upon himself to destroy corruption and evil in this
i'm gonna get a two for one the way that it was supposed to be played poetic justice
coming up is he gonna tell us to stop playing or do we just play the whole time here we go
my dear wonderful grateful people it brings warmth to my heart to see what if it doesn't
get the girl she's standing off to the side for years decades we have struggled against
the oppressive forces of the outside world for years the delgado cartel has been a bull
start playing when he dies
oh man we celebrate this struggle the victories we have earned today i grant you this symbol
of freedom and rebellion may it forever light your days and nights with hope of greatness
here we go serve as something to aspire here we go do it all of you can become
as me now please if the drummer could shoot the rope oh
it didn't get her it didn't get her it didn't get her it didn't get her oh no
how did it not get her how is that possible you kidding me it only got him oh well it's me
i'm in the square now i don't see a puta mierda in here what's this well we did it the way it
was supposed to be done okay i got it grab some bags and get uh i'm i'm gonna follow her around
because it's right because man i nice day isn't it um i mean attack that's a kind of an odd thing
to ask me at the moment that's kind of yeah yes it is why did she just turn into a default npc
i'm sorry but you're not coming too well she's like she's about to fight somebody
she got her hands up why is she supposed to stop boxing someone uh she's where is your
it's show time i think she might have gone totally crazy here just shoot her no no it's
got to be something she's just kind of hanging out here now should i play all right play hey
pick that up okay sorry um mission story revealing itself
like smuggling this cocaine souvenir around the world right i need to get it to this dude
uh franco franco that's what we need to get it broke it's supposed to be in one piece when i
delivered over by some cave entrance behind the pharmacy but it broke oh no bummer maybe just
glue it together so a drug dealer from sapienza has been testing a new method for smuggling
delgado brand cocaine into europe baking the substance into souvenirs coated in a special
anti-drug detection paint solution the dealer has been traveling the globe testing the method
however he accidentally broke the souvenir on arrival and needs to mend it before going
to see franco just glue it i don't know find the broken souvenir ruin the taste test
this franco guy i need to get but you know with taste she's just freaking me out here man
seriously smell you know yeah man that's too bad i'd still try to glue you know
can i get in through here yeah there's always a side door okay where's your substance
well there it is take tamper with broken cocaine souvenir poison i need poison or any glue
oh no well i don't have either of those things shit well let's go find glue and go find
poison i can put this down okay all right look at the glue and look at the poison
and there there is an invisible wall here i think this must be a dumpster here or something it's
weird all right uh so we got this looks like somebody's just house let me take a look at the
map so we got this our target here drummer's apartment so many points of interest let's go
let's just take a left see where we end up well here's medicine unlock door we don't have
anybody well we got a guy actually looking right at me right there can i crawl through the window
can i like turn into putty and push through there oh not this time not this time oh
gentlemen give me give me give me give me a soda can soda just came out of the bush
turn around i'll get back turn around and examine there he goes okay what about his friend
you gotta be kidding me whoa turn around don't stop around i have to knock them both out
all right here we go let's see how it's gonna go down here i'm gonna fish the first guy
this area has restricted nobody's down here at all let's get him out of the way
hello actually let me see can i drop somebody here is there a ledge okay there's a ledge there
but what does it go into the water good dump them in the water chad is now in fish only
i think i the whole body exploded did you hear how loud that was all right see you later
is this gonna kill him he's gonna like wake up down river right he's being eaten by what
oh well i did not expect that germa can't see fish moly because he doesn't use bttv
that's true i don't know what that is yeah i'll get the key card too i saw it when i dragged
by it so this is like a lab down here we'll get to see it again what happens if i go down
there well i could even buy all the fishes too probably all right we're gonna clean this
place up a little bit pick up the apricot we've got gun on the ground cave key card
uh what about the other guy didn't the other guy drop okay that he dropped his gun
all right we're good save it well thank you there it is now let's break into here
currently trespassing but who cares oh that's what happens
um i already told you you can't be here come on then come yell at me out here
your window's not open oh shit pharmacy key wait where i need i need uh i need poison scissors
somebody's searching said somebody was searching somebody saw who saw that nobody did oh that guy
did oh here he comes all right wait wait wait wait who is still searching searching um i don't
see anybody searching those guys are just hanging out nobody's running around really i think we're
good yeah we're good so now let's see you can look up a poison poison do you have poison
in here you don't have any poison in the doctor why would there be poison in the doctor's
are you okay there well i did get the doctor's key i'm see i'm going down to the lab i i i guess
i could look for doctor's office well there's lethal poison pill jar got it now i need glue
prescription poison all right where would glue be they sell glue at the doctor's office no
it's in my car glue right here right you know how i know that i have the only rick show in
town i went by parker see a rick show they have to write it isn't at the blue store
see claro i remember when you offered those one day guided tours in the jungle that's a radio
only half the tour group loosen the i'm not gonna make an explosion car battery
do i know him oh wait i got the didn't it auto saved after i uh picked up the
pills right yeah right here i don't want that to come to give me low points i just wanted i told
you we're gonna have to have at least three or four of these points why was i so quiet during
that um i don't know because i was just watching all right i need glue he was having a moment
all right looking for glue anybody can hear of glue
oh
where are the police nobody cares that's right like uh
nobody gives a shit here we're like in drug town right are there even any police here
okay so i need glue let's find it for real this time i need to go to like a gift shop
or a repair shop hostel it's not where i want to be i don't know where this is what's this place
glue it's a radio glue would be right there wouldn't it by the general store well i i mean
i kind of need to find a general store what about in here
you got glue in the barber shop
glue his hair the glue isn't necessary just the poison
i thought i had to put poison in it and then glue it well this rat poison
your inappropriateness does no boundaries and you really need to leave i need my personal
space all right i'm sorry and i need you to get the hell away from me now all right my god
that's enough hey what the hell kind of outfit you think that is
really think i'm that stupid oh shit oh my god that scared the shit out of me
me i don't think it's gonna be that loud man that was loud holy shit
all right well i'm gonna go put at least do this part so i can get into the save point
otherwise i'm gonna i'm gonna get lost in hitman purgatory i'm gonna put i'm gonna do
this first poison the broken souvenir and then it'll update it that guy's gonna look
i need the glue i know at least let me put this on here
put the point lethal poison glue lethal poison get the glue find some glue will it
all that running around and it's going to show me where it is god damn it nice all right so
who's in here i don't understand okay i'll do it do i have to buy it from this guy
you have to buy the glue is that thing leaking i'd like to buy some glue please
okay thanks is that gonna explode oh no it saved it right here it's okay quick run i wasn't
trying to shoot her i was trying to make her why would i i'm gonna aim at the ceiling to
shoot her hair shot yeah kind of all right focus focus i'm having too much fun what am i
thinking stop doing that stop just oh my goodness i was trying to make like a big
firework oh my goodness just put it out just put it down how do i just put an item down
just i know my last idea didn't pan out but these beauty wheels it is lower than a taxi
all right i'd like to buy some glue you got any glue here i'd like to buy some glue please
mechanic next door has the glue thank you for your help
hey i heard you had some glue can i borrow some do you sell glue all right we're gonna
take care of this too this piranhas in every single body of water this place is dangerous
in every body of water millions of them i'm convinced that that's just a bunch of fish
that's not even water all right let's fix it repair it and i'm ready glue it together oh yeah
cocaine souvenir disguise yourself as the hippie she's still standing here i think she's broken
i'm not sure that she's gonna do anything i may as well throw a coconut at her all right
where's he gonna go here what the hell is that exposed wire no that would have been funny
why aren't you listening to me you deaf i will call security hey you look really stupid christ
i'm on to you can someone help me with this guy something really bad what the hell is wrong
with you where the hell was it 1818 it's right here is it what did i not save it
i have to get the glue again 1816 1818 damn it i just unplugged his core i just did the guy
i didn't know there was a guy sitting right there should have looked let's go get the glue
do you sell glue
oh
it flew out of my hand unconscious witness oh shit i gotta take it her she didn't see you she's
gonna turn around and find the body she didn't need to see me do it she will eventually figure
it out okay now let's go do what we need to do we're good save the game i'm gonna do it
right right here all right let's go i put him in a box well i don't know i feel like if i drag
her all the way across imagine killing someone over a tube of super glue i mean that yeah but
this is not just a tube of super glue this is a very secret this is a secret mission you know
what i mean that super glue means a shitload all right so now let's go down here he's still
standing there i know i'm his how this is gonna end guys i'm certain of it she's not gonna move
her ai is bugged out and i'm gonna have to throw a frying pan or to head from the balcony then
run hello soldier okay so what does he do here hello so he save it so he i gotta turn the
water on expose the wire i could come through it there but does this guy get up i'm headed
to distract this guy he's leaving he's gonna see me do this though right like you he's going
to watch me do this all right expose the wire and then i'm gonna overflow the sink when he
comes back turn on electrical outlet fuck me what the hell no give me this he's about to
come over here all right go check out that apricot you didn't even see me do that dude
hmm you're out you're one comment away from dying here man
yes oh my god where is he am i gonna die if i press this thanks man
hey listen you have any clue no
hold on wait hold on oh perfect this is exactly what i wanted to happen
oh come on why did he walk in it was so good that was so perfect i had it
it sounded awful is that gonna happen again
so hold on i have to do that's gonna happen again isn't it so he leaves i need the coins
let's try this again okay i i'm ready i'm ready for when he comes back let's save it here
wait what happens again okay i want to see a good view of this i i just wanted to see it
we didn't get a good view last time i could i'm just gonna go up and just snap the guy's neck
in the upstairs why do all this why go out with trouble why go through all this trouble
what am i doing this guy's dead right now oh no he's almost gone now oh come on
can you just go see what it was yeah not too shabby no no no that wasn't even the right guy
oh my god that wasn't even the right fucking guy better get your head out of your ass
double quick what's happening i think someone's in serious trouble i heard oh jeez i know it's
off i'm gonna turn it on when he gets it i don't want it down the one this guy this
once this guy gets out of the way he's gonna mop this whole thing up did he mop up the whole
thing hurry up and get in there what if i'm gonna body block him hey what why did you do this
i'm just gonna go up and turn on the alarm clock i did that because i've restarted that
i'm trying to restart it all right forget it upstairs alarm clock hey come to your alarm
clock and i could go in the room i'm just gonna kill him i'm so sick of this guy
hey you maybe you should uh come to turn off your alarm clock
where can i put them i have to steal the china there's no china to steal here investigating
distraction what distraction the alarm clock all right it's me i'm here i've got the drugs
i've got everything you need here's my magic school bus see all right where you at
oh he's very far away locate the smuggling cave isn't that what this is
you could play the pink panther theme no i thought this was i thought those were swords
hey what's up smuggling cave discovered ah you're expected have a seat francos on his way
okay all right go is on the way have a seat we've got hold on blend in a submarine crew
coke keep that there's a harpoon gun what the hell is that all right what else we got i need
a gay rat poison and what can i do with some of the stuff let's see there is a wind-up toy
but i don't need to do that right now here he comes okay uh act natural i gotta be careful
what's that um place the cocaine souvenir can i poison the cocaine it already is poisoned
but extra poison just to make sure it works hey what's up so despite an unknown
lay it's finally here let's have a look he got through customs without a problem we hope
i had no issues excellent we're not sure whether this will pass the taste test but that
remains to be seen follow us please okay there's a souvenir given test 47 and now for
franco to sample his handiwork what happened down nice work what the heck oh my goodness
listen you do not run our faces okay
you son of a pounds pal that's that's it right what he didn't autosave i thought it autosaved
right after i killed him oh shit i thought it was an autosave well sorry whoops oh well
damn it i thought it autosaved after i killed him remember this hey take a look nice 147
all right for franco to sample his handiwork because he's gonna do it and die i'm gonna
leave wait actually i need to like i need to greet him and then leave so i'll wave to him
there's the secret crabby patty cocaine souvenir recipe i've got the recipe now
all right hi hey despite an annoying delay it's finally here let's have a look all right bye
he's healed to it right i had no issues i don't want to run away just to make sure he
we're not sure whether this will pass the taste test but that remains hey look who hasn't moved an
inch look who hasn't moved even a centimeter okay there it goes and it's time to leave
franco confirmed down nice work 47 all right let's get the last one the girl that is standing
still let's climb back up here make our way i think the statue is supposed to kill her
i don't know i really don't know probably not if it was then we're at a oh they're searching
this is like a final destination moment where she was supposed to die and she still is just
sitting right there i don't i don't think we're gonna get much better than that yeah
if they're taking pictures of the stat no they're taking pictures of me so um i think i kind of
just have to throw something at her what can i do i have like a cocaine bricker to death
scissors fish she's not gonna die from the fish so somebody just writes pistol let me just
see if she moves if she does anything she's gonna move all right that guy just took a
picture show it off let's go sports do you think showing off i mean kind of so i have a car
keys to a car i'm like spraying your ankle all right what are the exit points
because wait wait wait sports car key a key matches one of rico delgado's sports cars
all right let me see the map where is the where the exits are they not listed here yet
i'm gonna assume probably this way this way let's see if i get it to move basic social
etiquette wouldn't be a miss okay she still does looking at the she's waiting for something to
happen on here hello there sir you want to play get the band back together i've just have
to kill her is there anything i can throw over there or do something whoa easy this key
i think i'm just gonna have to shoot her or throw scissors at her head and run
doesn't look like she's moving anywhere unless i can maybe activate a
do i mean like the intel or objectives of mission stories or something here we go
undying love let's follow this one see if we can get it to work that's far away throw
a bullet at her head i think i was just all the way back here
all targets neutralized this should paralyze the cartel excellent work 47 now head for an exit
shit all right this way i'll head down here oh shit well it's not what i necessarily wanted
to do but kind of had to do it watch out for the uh turn on the motor get in the boat
you arc the scissors and do that behind cover like throwing bricks people fishing there um i
don't think so i think it just bumps into them and they go home well i did two of the story
missions let's see what we get here in our roulette the boss the cook the face someone
could hurt themselves tasteless straight shot mission story on a pedestal still has a statue
the secret ingredient one star isn't it like 3 a.m right now in america um not quite
it is nine just about 10 p.m eastern like i'm gonna i told you i'm gonna get one star every
single time just because the nature of especially at least playing for the first time i've got
to try to do the weird shit okay new level cool a new hidden stash in the hostel i unlocked a
fragmentation grenade it's like a grenades now sedatives village hostel village bar
cool mission stories so i did this one there are these two that i did not do
deadly art and hallowed ground maybe one day but i want to keep looking
this next one is untouchable how many missions are in the base game status columbia assignment
successful tactical five gets neutralized six militia transport network disabled location
of primary target unknown team chasing several leads and message encrypting services well but
i mean missions as in areas are you expecting a real answer or a joke i mean
when enough people write the real one i can kind of read between the lines
i'm not as strong as you they have to pay for what they did it needs to stop you need to stop
if my source checks out we can prove the board knew about the chemical leaks there are six
new locations grounds for a retrial it won't make a difference they're too powerful they're
not the devil nancy just the company they're not above the law don't you see this is bigger than
james those bastards killed 80 people and they got away with it think about what that means
no one's untouchable no one's untouchable huh oh that's diana batwoman now we're in
south africa for cutscene park two oh he got the virus move out oh i got like a five minutes to
do this whole mission i better be quick all right continuing on to chasing a ghost i failed
the mission unfortunately good evening 47 the militia has released a hostage tape outing the
existence of providence to the world this was a fatal mistake and our analysts are tracing its
origin as we speak in the meantime we have a lead on lucas gray's top lieutenant turns out the
delgado cartel's counterfeiting unit was creating fake ids for the militia and one
operative in particular stands out wazir kale an infamous south china sea pirate better known
there the maelstrom the maelstrom and his cutthroat band of outlaws were the scourge of
the shipping industry in the post-recession years but his reign of terror came to an end
with the disastrous 2014 hijacking of the supertanker francis king chinese elite
forces stormed the ship resulting in the deaths of a dozen sailors and most of the maelstrom's
that kale slipped away unseen the maelstrom's connection to gray is unknown but we believe it
was he who carried out the audacious killing of a providence ceo in shanghai along with two
reactivated members of his old pirate gang barnier shaw a shady figure in mumbai's
criminal underworld and darwood rangin the gang's old cashier turned dodgy movie producer
shaw rangin and the maelstrom form lucas gray's eastern eastern we are a crack strike team
and stopping them as our clients most pressing concern unfortunately the elusive maelstrom
appears to have vanished into the seedy underbelly of mumbai the cradle of his
criminal legend and no one knows his whereabouts or what it currently looks like i don't know
what he looks like a bandit queen a showbiz charlatan and one certifiable ghost i shall
leave you to prepare i don't even know what he looks like how am i supposed to find him
all right so we got to find the maelstrom and verify his identity then we've got to
get rid of vania and darwood darwood any method anyway it's possible let's go to the
planning stage all right smuggling in an item i don't i can't do anything don't have any
smuggling location so concealed weapon we're obviously going to take the chrome one uh yep
fiber wire i have grenades too right don't i'm not bringing those what a mistake that would be
okay whoa whoa whoa man what are you doing that looks good give me the chrome
and i'm ready fish a duck the old aquatic animal loadout fish and a duck
you bet i'm in a robe i'm in a tank top one of the most densely populated cities in the world
home to more than 12 million people if you wanted to disappear and hide from the world
this vast city is perfect the maze-like swarming slums offer secret paths and
surprises around every path and corners the elusive maelstrom knows the city like the back
of his own hand locating him will be a considerable challenge a place to start could be the slums
where his former gang the crows has recently risen from the ashes okay darwood rangin will
be easy to find in his half-finished tower wrapping up his new film called mumbai hero
i want to do that one while vania shaw has ensconced herself in the overgrown
remains of an old train yard i want to go to the movie set your three targets call this
labyrinthine part of the city home let's do the movie one all right so we are looking for
the movie studio i want to be a star is this a giant car accident what kind of cars are
these why is this like a five car pile up golf cart that's a really strange car
oh can i play anything what do they got on here oh look at that isn't that funny
they got the original hitman 2 on here what is that oh i could i can play freedom fighters
all right why are these all points of interest on there
hmm oh damn this is huge oh god it just got bigger it just got even bigger central square
the street gang known as the crows are on high alert i don't care about the crows
what is this and will be suspicious of anyone they don't recognize i suggest you are mindful
around them in the slums so if you don't recognize me then i'm in trouble okay so
there are actual centuries now i don't think it was like that before in the other game
let's just go down here taxi can you take me to the movie studio might need this
just in case there's water somewhere i might be able to use this 47 our intel suggests the
maelstrom is hiding somewhere in the city slums i've marked the headquarters of the crows on your
map um no i don't want to do that i don't want to do i don't want to do that i want to find
the movie studio i'm sure that's the thing that you can do right away but we're not
doing that one okay thank god hello well there's a crow right here oh no don't look at me
oh fuck i just turned off their electricity shit oh i want to do this too can i do this too
yes let me show you check this ready i didn't do as good as you guys did but
pick that up i just think that with prestigious scholarship pick that up
you should go for it before they to go to discos or so sir i take it you don't
no no don't stop this i gotta like save the game right here right at the beginning
okay now let's see what happens how does this work nice so i want to see how
what's the people just pick it up nice jesus christ i was dozing off that scared me i'm
sorry why would you be interested in a duck i don't know i would be pretty interested i got
extra fish perfect why was i expecting piranhas
i can't get in there wait is fishing look at the fishing rod
maelstrom you know who maelstrom is huh
no access there's an important meeting taking place up there now beat it
so armed thugs belonging to the street gang known as the crows have evacuated a hill in
the slums of mumbai this could be worth investigating no all right here we go a close
shave a dress to die for a matter of discipline broad strokes flames rekindled
gone with the wind and then picture perfect i don't care about this let's do the dress
junkyard discovered
stop being so dramatic all right
what's up here wrench move by hills
hey you're trying to get us you stop uh wrench and face no no no no wrench and face
perfect not perfect i wish i had three thank god for the soda can no wait me flying around
my ears here man i gotta do it you gotta be both of you turn around come on what was my
plan what was my plan what was my plan what was my plan i don't know what my plan was
sick all right well i gotta i gotta have a different approach here was that homer simpson's
okay i need to put my the mission back come on armed thugs belonging to the street gang
the crows i don't want i want to do the dress let's go this way let me take a look at the map
that's so funny so well what are you what have you done where am i standing right now
i can't i can't get over it
i'll be all right i just imagine homer simpson running around all right where is this
subjective thing here find the maelstrom find the maelstrom i'm here we gotta go this way
so if i go up and then right no i could go around i'll go this way doesn't anybody have
a clip of that because i need to hear that again the tea shops it really was
band from fox studios audio band for fox studios audio now i'm discovering a lot
of districts that's good oh this game is fucking hilarious see look at this guy what is this huge
gun jesus this is this is a toilet this is the thing i wanted this is exactly what i want in my
house in my office right now i just want to piss straight down to the ground how am i i'm
gonna have to did you not hear that i need a costume what's this what are you doing here
security that's like a security guard oh i can go this way chef the hell is all right i can take
the chef well uh there's a crowbar i feel like i can take this outfit and then be able to
blend in a little bit better it's going back this dude just has food cooking here that look
does look good now i'm hungry great that's great what are these guys doing
all right i gotta i gotta figure out what i want to do here it was good of you to lightly
toss your weapon at him uh where does he go he's going this way what is that
can do something with these these are those are all explosions well i'll try going through
here it's gonna be on the lookout for these guys with the circles those dudes anybody in
oh i didn't bring the i didn't bring it an important thing i brought the ducks and the
save it here getting closer down this way and blend in don't think i need to but oh perfect
perfect anybody else perfect is this perfect tell me it's perfect is it perfect it's perfect
okay what did he have i need to have the same gun well hold on
hey what hey what why did why did i die i was staying i threw it down there okay well
i know that that's safe over here so we're good i need to close first electricity holds
no bounds all right i got the shotgun i have to be the guy with the shotgun got it okay
don't play with fire all right almost at the dress mission i'm so looking forward to this
save it right here somebody found that body what do you what are you doing down there
tailor is impossible i explained to his employee that mishal wants to meet with him but he claimed
that the tailor wasn't available so you didn't just go inside and look only the royal guard
you can do stuff like that i'm sure mishal will send someone with more hands-on experience than
me he's the only tailor in town that can make that damn i need to be a tailor happens when
you drown all the others i guess it appears vanya shah is in the market for a dress fit for a queen
she's sent after a local tailor but for some reason the man refuses to cooperate
a man of your impeccable taste should be able to fill in perfectly for the tailor
disguise yourself as the tailor well there he is okay i'm coming for you
just want to make sure you're well aware i'm coming in there wonder if i can get in
through here and then go down um i could if i had a lockpick instead of the stupid duck
wait a minute no what no why are you coming all the way why would you come
excellent let's find out what kind of dress a woman like vanya shah wants
oh why did that guy come and pick it up i just wanted i just wanted i wasn't gonna blow it up
i wasn't going to blow it up i was gonna try to have the tailor come out and pick it up and
then just go in play with permadeath no way all right so i need to get in there somehow
both doors are probably cannot be unlocked i can't get through upstairs
i can go up this way which maybe i can get on the roof and go through the ceiling
let's find out yes i can so where do i go i gotta go across this way old crosswalk
all right let's go over here save our game have you tried stealing the china i have not
i've not tried that yet maybe it'll be good
i'm trespassing who's looking at me i'm not supposed to be in here
what's this measuring tape uh okay what's this we got request to the tailor coins
fuse box all right this is pulled this pulls them upstairs what else we got i need to can i open
this this to the outside i need to blow the fuse box and then i need to measuring tape choke
the guy to death yeah all right let's give it a go that's not the tailor that's not even the
tailor where at what building am i in what he's left greetings sir can i there's got to be
who are you i just i don't know what i picked up i bet that guy breaks a lot of hearts all right
let's see it's not going away save it we have been oppressed by a false rule long enough and
someone needs to take a stand besides she killed everyone that came to her nobody knows what she
wants i can't risk it will you two get out of here there's no one else here
he switched to bluetooth
two fuckers get away from me oh you two idiots no questions asked
can you get me out of mumbai tonight if you have the best i can i'll find some thank you
hey don't just throw your
he doesn't know where he went he doesn't know where he went
he's like there was just a person here
x x x well to be fair he heard an explosion turned around and the guy wasn't here
i really need this that was the opportunity i need to oh my god these people are gonna see it
if these two weren't here i this would be so easy
you turn left i can't do it here of course they leave now
oh i i almost want to throw the duck over there no you know i get a better idea
fuck this watch this
you two don't want that nobody wants that duck i'll get it
i'm just gonna have to keep following him i'm just gonna have to keep following him
because i can't stop him here he's gonna see me throw the coin
i did no i'm gonna have to follow him again wait till i get the right opportunity
okay here we go sitting on the bench
why are you here
just give this guy a heart attack
thank you i'll be in touch tomorrow okay do you mind checking that out
yeah oh come on he turned around what what what what what what what
you messed up you know that if he didn't turn around i would have just joked him
what what what what what every time this guy finds a place to stop at a place that's
kind of off the beaten path a little somebody goes and like lies down next to him
where three people come and have a conversation i need to set up something on his path
is there something i can do here because if i if he gets too close or for instance radio
just go listen to the radio dude thank you go check it out
you should direct all business inquiries to my assistant i'm not sure a few weeks maybe a couple
okay that's bullshit bullshit man i tried excellent let's find out what kind of dress
a woman like vanya char wants i need to get rid of char wants a syrupy dress 47
perhaps you will be able to source a roll of the right fabric at the local cloth market
somebody's gonna see that
somebody's gonna see it and i can't do anything about it and i'm gonna save and it's gonna ruin
everything i need to have another save point here to make sure just in case
that that i'm gonna it's gonna be right over here because i had that one back before
he's just sun tanning what's going on
excellent let's find out what kind of dress a woman like vanya char wants
yes char wants a cerulean dress perhaps you will be able to source a roll of the right
fabric he's fine good i have i gotta get rid of the shotgun how do i throw the shotgun
what is that soda can find an appropriate cloth sample save it here that's save right
i did i clicked on save my god all right let's go over this way this way this way i need to
get cloth let's keep going through the alley just looking for cloth just looking for the right
cloth whoa whoa whoa whoa what's this guy does this guy have a sword no it's an umbrella
all right shopping district i need cloth green cloth sage cloth how much of these
best prices here what do you say i need five coins does that sound fair i've been throwing my
coins i can see you're a man of refined taste and a skilled my kids will only eat rice tonight
but it's yours for 105 rupees okay it's a deal that's a that's a pretty decent price
why are you really burning into me sir you're just looking straight into my soul
okay final offer now 90 rupees 90 rupees per running meter that's my own cost
i i really can't go to three coin i don't have that either make it cheaper still no
haggling skills are something else i'll give you that much the silence it's
it's terribly unnerving to be honest it's like you're just dead inside like there's a vast
empty space where your emotions would normally reside i can go no lower than 75 rupees really
take the offer please take the offer you know what my grandmother made these with her own hands
there's blood on the loom every night because she works so hard the fair price this is one
of those scenarios where i'm looking through him to somebody else and he what he went back up
the story about my grandmother silence is killing me just just 40 rupees that's it please
it's a fair price you beat me take it 40 rupees okay it's a deal take any of the bundles
just one just one new shirt for the office what color does she want what color does she want for
dress for when she sent after local tailor intel what color dress do you want by decree
of the generous vania you are able to present to her a sample your finest cerulean cloth
and to perform a measuring for the most exquisite gown mumbai's ever seen what color
is that make her a gown but the tail is reluctant moment make a nice tie so that's
blue so i'm gonna take the blue one great thank you come again okay make it work
well i got i got all the faces covered so i'm fine all right arrange an audience with
vania she is this way why am i still holding this can all right here we go
arrange an audience i have all the cloth ah it's you did you bring the cloth for miss
i did yes i have it right here i got green i got blue i got red come with me don't be alarmed
this shot it's a gun very seriously so the guards will search you oh my god have a gun
have a gun i'm afraid your honest look isn't going to cut it here i'm gonna have to
okay that's it don't move holy shit don't even flinch don't gamble okay come on they're
gonna bring it down i got the i'm staring and they're gonna they're gonna do like what the
cloth guy said hands over your head kill him just don't do it they're gonna do it
hold on guys let me just put my gun down
he took that he took a full shotgun blast to the chest and the back of the shoulder and
didn't even flinch come on let's see what you have in your pockets today oh wait what
about is it i do have the duck and it will be over soon are they gonna find the duck but the
duck is just a duck what now i'm not allowed to be in here don't you move i'm not allowed
to be in here now all right so sorry i like sneezed over there and then walked back
yeah just sneeze the gun out of the trash can you want to get through here all right do it i'm not
exactly enjoying this either so just stay still and we'll be done soon now pick it up and throw
the gun over the fence i i don't think i can throw the gun can you throw the gun i will
no i'm not gonna throw the gun over the fence i'm gonna go you can't throw a gun you just drop
a gun has been dying to meet you it's not wise to keep her waiting you know i won't disappoint her
then that is a good idea she's not been happy with the other tailors a word of warning
play along with eccentricities so she wasn't happy with the other tailors thank you been
recorded by a camera i'll do my best what am i gonna shoot it do well and there will be a
lot of money in it for you i know i'm gonna take it out with them here we are just go
there the queen is waiting for you in the garden in the garden that is vanya shah
self-appointed queen of the mumbai slums
no confirmed kill on vanya shah excellent work 47
are about to start flying here so move it at the location and it looks clear over
his calling card how am i walking out of here is this really happening
how do i get out of here what the fuck okay
yeah go ahead fresh honest look isn't going to cut it here i'm gonna have to
frisk you pretty boy that's okay hold that position will be done in no time
okay go on then now i'm gonna get the gun that's the dog no that's the thing that
fucks it up what's this in here i guess i'll take it all right let's do it for real
no i don't want to like fucking that was just like i want to see what happens
well the whole city suffers under the water just got it here your husband is dead is he not yes
he is two years now and your children are already working elsewhere i didn't want to like let that
be the way that it was done i want to like see this i'm sorry but water and power are
precious assets here i barely have enough for my own needs you will have to make do i understand
thank you my queen the elusive dealer here at last let's have a look at the cloth you've chosen
oh shit okay it's it's a really i want to make sure the color yes of course here it is
excellent finally some progress here come with me i want you to take my measurements while you
pay smart work 47 shaw will want to have privacy when measuring for the dress
i'll leave the final execution up to you yeah i mean it's one thing to like throw a grenade
into the group and then like fish the camera but i want to do it like the the correct way for
once you there leave us i want some privacy let's start the measuring right if you didn't
forget tape i'm pretty certain one of the other teams left this no i have what is all this
linden is a servant what the fuck what the fuck what did i just pick up relax your back please
miss shaw i'll just measure your arms now miss shaw turn around please miss shaw i need to
measure shoulder to shoulder you've probably heard about the other things how some of them
ended up in the gutters because they didn't please me this dress is important to me not
the dress itself what is this lady doing what it represents you see confirmed kill on vanya shaw
excellent work 47 no rest for the wicked however on to the next one
train key okay what is this i mean like fishback all right well that was fun
you think that was fun oh would you mind a few steps back so much than a year
wakey wakey eggs and becky who are we looking for exactly he looked like he worked in the
fashion industry like a tailor perhaps hold on i just saw that guy okay he can't hide anymore
he kind of looks like a tailor i think what does he look like i think he looks kind of like a tailor
this way come on i don't have all day
this shit just got real this shit got real what am i doing this for get down now i'm gonna go
i can go up i want to go down all right what does it get doing that guy just saved the game
thanks dude i guess there was like a save point poll that i missed i'm the npc i mean yeah i guess
all right so we got mission story let's see i want to do broad strokes this one looks
interesting why am i pretend i'm what's on my chest why don't have like an old nokia on my
chest am i this is my life now do i just sell magazines all right let's go up there
watch out for the guys with the circles all right up there all right that was i had a lot
of fun that was great we got to see it two different ways we got to like rewind and pull
back and see the story twice this game's fucking fun what a great game what a fun video game
i need to go up there uh can i cross through a demon you keep telling all the good stories
about him a freedom fighter straight this way across the beam or do i need to go across the
beam i need to get over there is there no other way for me to jump over there can i climb up
of that no really come on i can't get up there i can't traverse that damn it all right well i'm
just i'm gonna go the other way maybe it's a ladder this way what about right there i gotta
go up from here somehow there we go got it 47 this is one of the mumbai tools my records
show a few residential complaints about a new tenant in the building okay something related
to strange behavior might be worth looking into let's go pay him a visit strange tenant
i'm currently trespassing so you know how do you trespass in an apartment building
how could they not well well it appears we have a rival assassin in mumbai and he's training
his sights on darwood rangin by the looks of it i'd say we're dealing with a local operator
known as the cashmereian i'll never make the shot a local hitman known as the cashmereian
is in mumbai on business he set up a sniper nest in a tower above a stairwell in the local
tool it appears he's targeting okay good thinking 47 now if we could only make rangin
appear in that window somehow that scope adjusted with this quarter of viewfinder
why don't i why don't i just get a better view myself right i guess i'll just go over there
and then aim up into the window oh the scope isn't adjusted that's right
maybe i should take his clothes he's got a dongle laptop dongle apartment key
and he lives here not trespassing anymore all right so let me say this again so i need to
find a way to get his attention to get him to the window how do i get his attention
a coin a coin doesn't reach that far throw a soda can across the city i think they hit
somebody right in the head shoot the window to make him check the window why am i shooting
at him anyways what why don't i just take this who cares about that guy where's the guy i need
to kill he's like up there where's the other person i need to kill is it just two well there's
no okay i gotta he's inside the building just get his attention i mean i could shoot i could
shoot the window but that kind of defeats the purpose of being down here i have to
go all the way down i'm gonna try and shoot the window just to see what happens i can't
shoot it won't shoot until he's there so let's shoot with this and put it back
did you hear it shoot through his open window
and again he's here he comes shoot him what it didn't fire uh this is obviously not correct
backflip pogchamp all right well i'm gonna restart it and i'm gonna go into the apartment
building what is it shaking so violently if only you had a tripod this would go so much
more smoothly all right you all right so i'm gonna go to the apartment i have an apartment
key now i didn't shoot yet right no okay let's take a look i got a key let's examine see if i
can scream at him what maybe this probably maybe there's a megaphone in this apartment
somewhere those are some nice trees adjust the scope i did i adjusted the scope and he was like
good okay here we go apartment key 47 it appears the cashmereian is using this room as a base of
operations let's see what he's up to in here what the hell is he watching okay
we got oh lethal poison pills luggage gonna do anything with the luggage no okay pick up
picture of what picture of vanya surveillance image of vanya
overlooking the mumbai laundry business a note on the back says excellent position
meeting with foreman a surveillance image of toad rang in his tower it looks like he's
posing in front of a large canvas of some sort a note says in the back perfect shot painter
okay it's an old computer okay well that he i get that's different places i can
perch up interesting all right well it's giving me locations to where i can
nothing else open the fridge that's not the fridge that's not a fridge either this is a
fridge i can't open the fridge i can't open the fridge all right i'm going back up
i'm taking the sniper rifle i'm saying what is that an iron oh boy get and get people
out of my way good luck hiding it i'll just like drop it in trash cans and shit
let me look at the sniper rifle again so this can't be adjusted how am i going to get his
attention i don't get it i mean i i guess i can like i can use the sniper to shoot the other guy
wait a minute i can't do this oh he he is supposed to right so i can't do this well
don't tell me i can't do something um i was what i can't hide there
the gun doesn't fire i can't the gun doesn't fire
did i kill him in both scenarios
is he dead in both scenarios oh he's dead in both scenarios i saved it and saved it
fucking hell no i'm not i'm not going back all the way there it's gonna scare the
shit out of people watch i want this though okay what if i i don't want this guy's disguise
anymore i'm gonna put on the bodyguard costume wait what got it right okay
he's a traveling salesman or something 47 this is one of the mumbai chores my records show a
few residential complaints i was sitting there trying to figure out the whole time how to like
distract the guy might be worth looking into it turns out i killed the whole story mission
because i shot the guy with his own rifle that's how i'm understanding this right that's
correct did i miss the stairs okay here we go well well it appears we have a rival assassin
in mumbai and he's training his sights on darwood rangin by the looks of it i'd say
we're dealing with a local operator known as the cashmere i was wondering why the other
the hints stopped a local hitman known as the cashmereian
damn broken viewfinder if i can't adjust this good thinking 47
now if we could only make rangin appear in that window somehow oh my god this is
karen dar aka the cashmereian was born in the u.s but fled to his mother's native land india
20 years ago following an fbi investigation into a string of syrian killings in texas
he adopted a new identity here talk to the assassin as a gun for hire for local
mobsters no i'm not going to talk to who would want rangin dead how does a professional assassin
not know how to focus a scope i have no idea that's like the equivalent of knowing how to
draw with crayons as a child a toddler all right so now we have to make him go in the window
and then we have to find the maelstrom so how do i i'm going to distract him
infiltrate the apartment infiltrate the lounge save it okay so we're going to get up there
uh i could take a one of the worker outfits but not really necessary
at the moment at least any of the guards there's a security camera i don't have any fish
how am i supposed to do this oh thank god oh if that was a fish it would have happened
that's it you're mine
god fucking damn it not necessarily all right come here i need a worker spaghetti sauce
hey look what's that spaghetti what that went that scared the hell out of me
you should go see what it was yeah nobody something's going down over here i'll be in
touch you need to come out i hit garrote why garrote
you know fuck this guy i'm mad i garroted this guy and then well he would have he would have
been dead anyways i press the garrote button i don't know why they spin around oh i have the
can of peas still no i have to walk by casually wait for it to show where it's in and then run
by it okay so i need to go where am i going up there it's a lot lighter than the first one
i thought i fell off
okay one more one more i guess hold on and watch out is that which which way is that guy facing
all right we're good so now i don't have a key card can i get in through this way you
can't see me through the bamboo whatever this is hey you bullseye all right uh let me go
instead of that way let's go over here does that guy work here
i need one of those secures hold up what's wrong because i'm holding them
hey num nuts are you hearing me i got nothing i'm fine everything's fine
i can't get up what okay put the hammer down put the hammer down before i go in here
all right that guy can see through there is a cannon over here what is this giant thing
what is this what was the movie set what does it do
so can you blow somebody off this tomb my brain gets too overstimulated when i play this game
all right drop this now let me just i need a different costume or something so many people
up here that know what i look like i can't go that way so all right this guy what about this
dude maybe i can go upstairs and come down it's probably a scaffolding or something up here
let's check you're gonna go that way his office i need other clothes in here is there
nothing else in here barber's razor all right um i want to see how do i get through there this
guy's just i guess i could can i take your security come in here you i'm gonna hide in
the shower see if i can get this i gotta kill somebody with the mega fan i know really oh
do you think that was anything i think would you go check yet they say no i didn't give me
he said no he said no
what information is somewhere in the slums but there's a lot of people down there
that is darwood rangan producer of mediocre movies and a full-time criminal
his brutality is overshadowed only by his giant ego oh my god that just kind of blew everything
yes what is it mr rangan the catering seems to have delivered the wrong things
overflow sink no why is everyone's coming into an investigate jesus christ what a matter
hunted god fucking dammit why did the two of them just have to come in together it's
because i did two sinks i did two sinks so two people had to get come in there
one sink you know one guy will get called in two sinks two people come on two sinks
all right get him in here
all right give me your uzi who's what do you mean investigating
i did one sink not two sinks who cares about that there's one sink it's a what the fuck
why i did one sink not two people one sink the one sink is still on
well they'll figure it out here we go save water still going but it's all right
we're gonna go straight through how do you do how do you do
a few days off okay so where's the sniper sniper is right there
so am i gonna get myself shot
missing tube of paint i don't have that
however i'm just trying to sit on the couch
oh my fucking god
these colors are all wrong i'll never hit the right tone why did i let
come on shoot me it's jackson pollock how is that even possible i need to find a paint
that's a great question what the hell that is though
smash the other painting take the shot take the shot
with my artistic integrity this would run a lot smoother i i just can't do it wrong guy i need to
i need to disguise as this guy don't i what are you talking about disguise yourself as the painter
so i need to be i need to get this guy's disguise so do it i'm i'm waiting for an
opportunity what am i supposed there's a guy in here like literally i i know the marker is on
this guy i have to subdue him
i poisoned the champagne i was hoping he was gonna drink it
like the guy has a green marker on his back you think i'm just sitting here like i don't know
who i need to fight here who could possibly be it just says is the guy on a couch
this guy's not gonna hear that how do you not hear that
am i getting shot look you guys you guys don't actually think i didn't know it was this guy
that i had to take the disguise him i just was scared of this guy i thought this guy was gonna
hear anything all right let's go all right come on i need you down i need him i need him
where is he come on give me at least a little bit of credit when the marker is on
the take the whatever did you get a shave it was on his body come with me to the lab to you
mr rangan that is darwood rangan producer of mediocre movies and a full-time criminal
his brutality is overshadowed only by his giant ego all right work on the portrait good
one my friend so who's the man who the heck is the maelstrom
magnificent use of colors and form if the new piece catches my forceful nature like this
oh i will have nothing short of a masterpiece okay i'll be the envy of everyone there it is
perfect execution mr rangan all right let's get this done i expect these to be the final
brushstrokes mr hosam i'm a busy man you're not painting are you having a heart attack
get on with it all right 47 let's see if the aim of our cashmereian friend is true
the word done already huh i told you it was close excellent yes yes look at those
cheekbones and my manly jaw you've captured everything beautifully i know i did a good
job thank you a modern masterpiece masterpiece you should feel honored to be allowed to
contribute to something like no he's gonna drink the champagne he's gonna drink champagne
kind words from a true connoisseur of the fine parts mr rangan oh that's so lame
oh my god is confirmed killed just one target left let's get out of here
just standing in the way i was thinking maybe he would shoot and would shoot through my head
all right let's see the way it's supposed to be played out all right 47
let's see if the aim of our cashmereian friend is true
once the word gets out and my art appreciating friends see it your phone will be ringing off
the hook i can't wait hold your breath for a moment mr rangan that's the reason i told
you i wouldn't pay for the commission by the way hold your breath stingy no no not at all
but if i'm already paying you in exposure let's not overdo it you know i prefer cash
clench your fist please clench your fist who doesn't but he's a pretty good painter exposure
can be worth more than just money look in this case it's the gift that keeps on giving
just wait and see when you're done with this job the contracts will be rolling in that
sounds wonderful mr rangan here it comes okay so look up a bit that shot came from the
tools it looks like the cashmere and finally got a clear line of fire okay darwood rangan is dead
just wait hold on a second maybe we had to activate that first i just want to check just
and i want to see i'm just curious i want to just see if i can get shot in the head
because if it if he have it activates right just wait and see hold on when you're done
with this job the tracks will be rolling in that sounds wonderful mr rangan
can you look up a bit damn it short earlier than that one second earlier i gotta literally
just put it down right when he says his last line here so i'm giving when you're done with
this job the contracts will be rolling in that sound i told you it was close excellent okay
so you can't you can't do it it stops the whole thing oh well worth a try the painter just does
it so i'm giving just wait and see no fun allowed i just want to see the contracts will
be rolling in that sounds wonderful mr rangan can you look up a bit that shot came from the
tools it looks like the cashmere and finally got a still painting it darwood rangan is
dead and not even by your hand 47 how long will you think next that's a great ending pose
nice work no just leave them leave them i'm done all right so here's the real question
where is the last bit of the barber in the maelstrom okay target already eliminated
mission story complete so i can do this one this barber one the barber is tangled up
in some shady business 47 he may have seen a picture of the maelstrom who found him the
guy that finally was going to do his job oh we didn't get to blow somebody off here
okay we don't have time for this is there another day we're gonna put down here
can i open this door yeah can i get down that
find that son of a bitch turn every stone it needs me come on can i can't get down this
jump to ledge no come on really okay what are you doing it's got to be scaffolding right here
jump oh shit you guys saw me didn't you i actually need to get the hell out of here
it's like a fine stairs going down hello sons go down from here darwood rangan has leased an
industrial strength fan normally used for clearing smoke from construction tunnels
that's a beast of a machine 47 the crew have put some sort of limiter on the fan output
but maybe you could make a few changes currently trespassing well i made it out
this got seen by this fucking security tape just fucking running around in circles
i just wanted to get out well i've kind of i made it out can i tell you i need to take their
disguise you're working the set after all too close but what can you do this one vacuum
what am i doing stop it brick where am i i just said like a flash where am i
i'm streaming okay i'm live i'm currently live what game am i playing
it's hitman okay good and we are good to go i just have to go across the whole thing
down here over this way oh yeah yay all right crows hide out i need to probably be in a different
right up there blending into the crowd i'm gonna blend let's blend in the crowd for a little
while currently blending chats trying what do you mean chats really trying what distraction
investigating this who is this naked guy where did that guy have had the vacuum
all right get get me up there slump square so look at the crows hide out here we are
save it he doesn't know that his webcam is on my web my webcam is not on hey best boy
you can't go this way okay so i need that's easy thanks it's currently this way
hold on it doesn't come all the way over here does he get a fish ready i don't have one sorry
i got a razor wait i have a barber's razor i'm not gonna get rid of this i think i might need
this check my zipper i don't have a zipper okay so now from here i've got to go that's
where like the entrance is i gotta go down there almost there there are the crows
okay how am i gonna save it was the last time i shaved maybe six or seven years ago
yeah literally about to shit himself when we brought him down here
thank you thank you thank you find the picture of the mail straight into the
heart of darkness 47 good luck i don't know if this is what i wanted all right find the
picture of the maelstrom what was that i just i killed him i threw that really really really
well apparently oh shit quick no no who's gonna keep i'm in the basement
over please there's no picture of men here i'm gonna get electrocuted what is all this
okay i mean like this is okay photos over here found it a photograph and a note addressed to
sagar the barber this looks like a very recent picture of the maelstrom with this in hand
picking him out in a crowd should be possible you could also investigate the barbershop
and see what is going on there all right time to get out of here let me take a look at the photo
where is it photo a note a recent picture of the maelstrom shown to the barber well okay
why can i not see that all right so out this way the way we came who's that guy who's that
guy who's that guy okay barber probably shouldn't walk in with a bunch of guns should i
probably not click all right time to be the barber i have the barber knife
where is there we are hello you need to open the shop people waiting outside already
i can't remember what he looks like guy the crows wanted me to provide information to you know
oh you mean me showed me his picture in their hideout two days ago but i was so stressed out
i thought they were going to kill me or something i can't remember his face
disguise yourself as the assassination target and then kill yourself
what if they hurt me what will happen to you or if they decide to burn down the shop like
they did with that other guy with the metal recycling i won't do it i told you we would
get into trouble with this snitching business but you had to go in on some easy money
sharing information with the gangs this is your mess you'll fix it don't you dare throw it hey
somebody want to do it genuinely felt bad watching that they're both still alive okay we
got there's the knife i have two of these now i can do well open the shop i'm gonna need the
key to open the store all right let's go open the store but i i don't know what he looks
like though open for business all right 47 we're open for business we know what the maelstrom
looks like i don't know what he looks like i couldn't see shaving cream is what's on the
menu now 47 47 i tried to look at the he resembles the maelstrom try to get close to
him for a visual id yes finally you have no idea how important this shape is it looks like him
but that's not the maelstrom that wasn't him no any chance for a shave today i don't
who's the maelstrom cut i'm afraid i'm a little busy right now forget this not at this moment
sir not right now damn it i really needed a shave is that him is that that's no that's the
barber's store here's the here's a recent picture but i can't see it
the game's gonna tell you well here although i just i need to practice on somebody
that's not how you hold look at look at the fucking reflection that's not how you hold a
knife oh wait he's in the chair how do i get him out of the chair wait he's just sleeping
that wasn't him no my whole computer's crashing hello uh okay let's open this back up again
the hitman is currently downloading something i'm downloading something i don't know what it is
okay welcome back i guess dude hitman 3 just released the update made me quit the game
i guess some reason because the esteem was just downloading another update
for hitman and now uh what is this doing there we go okay here we are it plays the batman music
i'll tell you know you're almost there it happened to me too
am i gonna dye my hair a new color why would i ever dye my hair my hair is barely
my hair is barely functioning if i dye my hair it ain't coming back it's falling out
i'm not dying my hair what is going on here i don't don't ever ask me again you've unlocked
the unique aluminum travel briefcase what can i where's my uh can i just load game
yeah it kicked me out to download a briefcase um campaign this is just where
like aren't i just back here load game okay there it is uh where where was i 2048 2049 right here
i was about to open the shop uh okay you thought that was the ps4 home screen no that's
the game menu to shave everyone well i how am i gonna shave everybody here we go let's open
up shop i got my i need my razor do i have one of course i do can i shave it somebody for
like an iron all right open the store all right 47 we're open for business we know what the
maelstrom looks like and expect him to show up patience and shaving cream is what's on the
menu now 47 not at this moment sir that man there he resembles the maelstrom try to get
close to him for a visual id i'm ready for you that wasn't him no that wasn't him so
got any good stories to tell no okay no and that's it that is a shave one part of his
face all right next customer please 47 that man by the counter that's the maelstrom well
looks like our patience paid off how about you invite him in for a close shave uh which
one of which one is the maelstrom they both have the same like packs badge on uh shops open sir
thank you my friend got it all right i'm ready for my shave make it a close one huh hey you
can't drop your stuff oh oh shit no pick it up and get in the chair that's too bad
okay let's shave them the tides are changing my friend can you feel it in the air my bolt
damn good work my friend this was an excellent experience the infamous maelstrom is right here
what is he he's what he is what what is he i really want him to pick it up
i say i'm ready for my shave here's the maelstrom manifesto let's get on with it okay why do i have
this famous maelstrom is dead very well done 47 let's finish this one mission completed time
to find an exit don't sneak up on me like that
i got you what he just bulked his neck pinched me all right let's let's do it
let's let him talk for a little bit let him say his last piece the tides are changing my friend
can you feel it in the air my bones are creaking with joy at the prospect of what
is about to happen i don't feel anything i'm afraid little friend you have an important task
does he know i sense that about you what was that together we will all release the shackles
that have bound us far too long and rise up against those who seek to just a knife
not even shaving kareem whether those are our friends is coming does seem i'm shaving his ear
let me get that ear hair for you sir
is what side you choose to be is it hurt focus on your business and what you do best friend
that is all we'll do that we're done the infamous maelstrom is dead
very well done 47 let's finish this one mission completed time to find an exit
he's like oh no i died this is bad
is he still alive hold on i need to like
okay he's dead time to leave hands and face i can't believe you know what i can't save it here
you know what fuck you you're up sir ah good i really need a shit bring in the fucking other
one just in case it was a double what's this just in case no i'll just guys don't understand
saddam hussein had like 60 doubles right like you can never be too sure doesn't like kim jong
un have like 40 doubles how do i get out of here i i'm not even like uh i got like 12 doubles
the hands of saying i can't believe what happened to me hey complete that was fun broad
strokes you sure that was the right guy ghost showman queen straight shot tasteless someone
could hurt themselves madman mission open for business the manual fan look at all these points
broad strokes artists at work become the barber become the man become the tailor become the
painter all of my doubles doing all my work for me look at all my doubles 44 000
i got a zero i got a zero i that's worse than a yelp the yelp reviews are you have to have at
least a one there's no such thing as a zero rating germa is downtown at a five-star restaurant
with no reviews uh that's a brand new restaurant guys you have to you guys have to review me
i got the construction site rooftop beach washing stall streets on the hill meat market
a homeless tent pottery market shoe shop old tire a new shotgun a new silver oh the
silver ballers there they are there was no one to review your barber shop i see a remote
explosive the barge the boat the chals the laundry skywalk the taxi train so i did both
of these this is the only one i did not do this probably the one with the fan barge simpson oh
that was fucking fun all right i think i think i'm gonna call it there tonight
because according to the reason why this was a youth correctional facility until 1962
when the estate was overtaken by an obscure soviet research fund the institute for one
more freeze frame cutscene in the box the place was abandoned the ending the stream voice oh no
only a few weeks ago it was acquired by an anonymous investor using crypto currency crypto
it has to be lucas gray bitcoin ethereum be careful 47 the breadcrumbs were almost
too easy to follow it could be a trap not a trap it's a haunted house mission an invitation
so if you do the haunted house mission you came home i knew you would son you've come a long way
47 and even now you don't remember your own father this place this was our prison
my father trained us shaped us into killers for providence you don't remember they ripped
it out of you wiped it away but i do what do we say troy baker i remember everything
you're a terrorist with nothing to lose you'd say anything it's difficult never miss your mark
or question your function boss baby a pact what are you talking about do this and we both lose
there was an incident that boy he died he lived because of you is it me that's me right you know
this deep down sorry this is not me what was his name subject six your name is subject six
and what is our purpose take them all down a man chooses a man chooses
okay let me see your let me see that birth certificate i don't believe you that subject
six is your name it's definitely larry all right so everybody the reason why we're gonna
shop here is because that was three areas just over six hours here so well so tomorrow by the
way tomorrow the green screen is not tomorrow the green screen is gonna be friday so tomorrow
we're gonna pick up exactly at this moment right here exactly halfway so if it's been
about you know we've been fucking around a little bit we've been doing some story missions
we figure six hours six hours six hours seven hours something like that at the halfway point
here so i will see you guys tomorrow probably around the same time around five to six p.m
eastern two three p.m maybe pacific the green screen is not tomorrow why not tomorrow
because i'd rather put it on friday where more people could probably watch
and with that thanks for sticking around i had a lot of fun this is this game as hilarious
and amazing as i expected it to be so it's just more of the if you liked hitman from a couple
years ago this just they just did more it's just more stuff it's just more missions and
more scenarios which is kind of what everybody wanted in the first place so it's good anyways
uh i'll see you guys soon see you tomorrow and i'm gonna hit the escape button then i'm
gonna exit the menu and then i'm gonna put up this thing and we'll do the bits
plus there's other things to do maybe maybe we'll do two more streams of this game i would
assume there's still lots to do so it's not like i'm gonna blow through all the story
missions and never do anything else so we'll do another we'll do probably three streams
at hitman tomorrow we'll complete the story missions we'll go through the areas
and after that we'll see but anyways let us go back to way earlier this evening have you taken
off see you soon and if you're sticking around hey thanks uh elizabeth thanks for the one dollar
well that was yesterday but thank you anyways uh thank you also to six hours ago here we go
uh uh zolnog thank you zolnog for the one zero zero zero the ten bucks
ten dollars here appreciated zol that was the first bit that came in peaceful hailey thanks
for the one dollar hey germa just want to say thanks uh say how much i love what you do
also but having trouble lately with job troubles like i don't have one right now
and i want to make a career out of voice acting and it's harder than i thought but
it's what i love and i also love what you do i really hope i can be successful i keep having
doubts about it just because i feel pathetic not having a shitty part-time job right now hope i
can do what i've always wanted to do thanks my best advice i can give you is always have
always have two or three things you're interested in that you like that you care
about so you have things that you're always cool doing you know what i mean have like
at least two or three passions things that you really love so then if one works out and the
other two don't then you're still doing something that you really like to do right uh voice acting
is it's a tough gig it's a hard business to get into it's um i've been kind of out of it
for a long time but the best resource is available for you you just have to kind of
work on a demo get out there be try to uh put yourself into online cartoons try to audition for
online cartoons they still do them that's what i did and make sure you have three things that
you like to do because you'll never be disappointed like i think a lot of times people just
have the one thing that they want to do one thing and they go for it go for it go for
it go for it and if it doesn't work out it's like oh well fuck man it didn't work out but
if you still have other things that you know that you like you won't feel that way
i knew i i here's the three things that i've always always wanted to do one uh i love
computers i've always wanted to be somewhere in the field of computers whether it's with
customer support with com with uh you know computer software or and this is by the way
this is before um even like i started college so i would have obviously done more
into this if i did uh love computers love animals i volunteered at an animal shelter free like
just over a year just maybe it was like 11 months 12 months or something i really wanted
to work with animals because i fucking love animals i love dogs uh like a veterinary vet
tech or something like that is something that i always like i would be completely fine with
doing you know what i mean uh then there was like voice acting and videos and big comedies
shit you know what i mean like that was another thing try to spread out your passions
that way you're never disappointed your computer breaks every other stream you made the right
choice not going into it well but that's what i mean like but that's something i wanted to do
if just because like my computer breaks doesn't mean i what is that even components break my
ram died a stick of ram died that's not because i like peed on it but that's really
the best advice i can give i wish you the best of luck hopefully you end up doing something
that you like to do good luck to you uh div usp thanks for the three bucks no message thank you
for the three dollars uh after smath thanks to the one dollar hey germa i can't wait to
play this the last one was a blast by the way i finished building my new 700 dollar computer
about a month ago and it's a bit better than my 150 staples laptop see computers
also i've been studying you for a school project i don't want to give anything away but the end
results gonna be interesting can't wait for the green screen scream they did they actually did
write scream so the green screen scream well looking forward to that project hopefully it
doesn't get you in trouble hopefully it's uh school appropriate but thank you uh it's a
great game by the way bake me home thanks for the five dollars can't play hitman 2 because
my pc is a piece of shit but i played some of the miami before the frame drops became too
much hitman 2016 was my game of the year enjoy the sequel this is gonna be rough for the end of
this year because there's a minute least there's been a lot of at least top five at least top
six maybe games hitman it was i feel like ah it's hitman again but it very well could be
it just it's everything that i want in a video game the only thing it does not have
is cars if you could drive around and hitman actually just commandeer vehicles and drive
around and it was like an actual like open open world game with vehicles i don't think you would
ever make another video game that i would ever play ever again that's the only game i would
play i would only play that game it would go up a letter grade to to an s spider-man is was
one of the best games of the year for sure red dead 2 is so good there's been a lot of great
releases but yeah thank you bake me home thanks for the five dollars extra cheesy thanks to the
fourteen dollars extra cheesy uh disguise yourself as a race car and stab him in the ass when he
sits on you holy shit thank you extra cheesy thanks for the 14 bucks man there's a dog
hey ketty thanks for the one dollar ketty they say huh what i don't know huh that is auto
what's he doing down there uh kim is probably yeah that's probably kim yeah it's probably kim
she was probably going in and out okay cool uh fart bernandez thank you for your 10 community
subs earlier thank you so much it's very generous of you swiggity dank thanks for the
five dollars uh ben ben sheparrow just roasted the shit out of my class what are you talking
about abort abort stop reading oh i don't even know what that is but thanks to the five dollars
how do you not know how to pronounce a shapiro i don't know i have just you better off he's
innocent leave him out of this me all right i'm just gonna move on because i have no idea
what's going on so thank you though uh thank you mostly loss for the one dollar germa i kind
of hate you right now there's an errand i need to run this week but you keep going live right
before i'm about to leave and now i'm never gonna get it done do it right now or do it
right when you wake up but i'm sorry thank you much little uh thank you major bluetooth
for the seven dollars major bluetooth hey yo germbo been a fan since the tf2 days i'll never
forget the one time i managed to get in a game with you and saved you from the enemy
team on dustbolt you proceeded to ignore me entirely and take credit for it then my game
crashed good old times anecdotal anecdotal he knows you from the servers hey if anybody
anybody knows me from the servers uh yeah hi he must have found him on the servers
thank you whole of one zombie for the two bucks have a bug on my twitch app on my tablet
that makes your voice go high pitched what stranger is it made vinnies really low
that is really weird why he knows you uh thank you whole of one zombie thank you
mars gaming yt for the one dollar ghost all right what the fuck i can't read that but
like but all right thank you uh mars gaming for the one dollar fractal sword man fractal
man thanks to the five dollars fractal this is for last night's stream i had to hand over
my pet snake to a friend before i left on my couple month business trip your stream helped
with getting me to laugh so damn hard thanks man germa tv germa heart pet snake what kind
of how big what kind of snake just a little just a little guy or a big one like a boa
football python is that a huge snake damn trying to see what the consensus here is
with how large it is i enjoyed my stay night well thanks for coming out morning morning ow
thank you no they can be small okay that's cool um glad you having fun thank you so
much for the five dollars dude plank v2 thanks for the one dollar appreciate it they say pride
thank you garfield the monday killer thank for the one dollar it's the most garfield time of
the year with the garf jingle bells and all the chat giving germa 100 bit cheers it's the
garf garfiest stream of all ho ho ho merry christmas germa i'm wrapping your present as
we speak germa old friend it's a big thank you for all your years of work just to make
us all laugh hey don't peek at your present then it won't be a surprise uh auto keep your
human on the leash i'm just kidding with you germa or johning you if you were still garfield themed
thank you thank you uh two uh chalo gram for the one dollar get bt tv you psycho uh i
that's not default though i need default you said my name wrong what the it's the
capitalization there's no capitalization over here on stream labs so it's just two
patch hologram i don't know why it's like that on stream labs vttv has capitalization but does
it work with stream labs he doesn't have ad block either no i don't i do not have ad block
although i think it's like bills isn't it like baked into firefox i think it might be
but anyways thank you so much man thank you dr clay for the one dollar here's something i
made because of the steal the china moment last night steal the china steal the china steal the
china thanks a lot thank you dr clay uh thank you corbett thank you corbett for the one dollar
and 50 cents hey germa my evening class was cancelled because my state is burning oh god
glad i was able to catch a wednesday stream hopefully you're safe best of luck to you
stay safe for sure uh thanks for the dollar 50 thanks for hanging out thank you uh two
patch hologram again for the one dollar you were boss baby the whole time i know i'm gonna
call you that note forever that's just the way it is the air quality in la has been awful
recently yes those fires man it's just not fucking cool i'm safe on i live 70 miles away from the
closest fire things are being closed because of the smoke i see but still just be careful
but thank you corbett and thank you to bet three for ten dollars ten bucks coming in from
bet three might not be able to catch the green screen stream on friday since it's my 19th
birthday but i look forward to watching the vod just want to say i admire you view on life so
much i hope one day i can do something for a living that i enjoy while making other people
happy as well thanks for all the good times thank you bet three happy birthday happy 19th
birthday coming soon here uh i hope you think it's fun it should be i think it's gonna be
funny i think it's gonna be a lot of fun especially a few weeks later when we get to
see the real fruits of everybody's labor so much love to you happy birthday thank you for
the ten dollars and then finally here at the end thank you uh granola grim for the one dollar hey
germa thanks for an awesome wednesday night of entertainment thank you granola glad you had fun
if you're around tomorrow maybe i'll see you tomorrow maybe i'll see you tomorrow and let's
let the credits scroll on by of all the subs and resubs they should be making their way by
right now what's tomorrow more hitman we got halfway through so we're gonna go from the
halfway point probably to the end and see where we are after that because then the day after
that is green screen unless anything major happens which i don't think it will if there's
some kind of technical problem where i have to push it to saturday i don't think i will though
i think it's pretty locked in that it's gonna happen friday have you been following the
hitman 2 story yes i guess a little a little make it a star wars scroll what do i think of
hitman 2 so far i think it's great i think it is summarize it uh so last game the bad guy
was actually your uh like a shared of bunk beds with you and you're both subjects of
assassin of an assassin program and diana um diana's uh that way i don't know what spoiler
but diana had an issue something happened to diana when she was younger that's it that's all
i know well yeah pretty much you got two opposing forces you know you got a red and a blue
and you know that there's a thing this entity that this it's a big circle
spoiler now i know something happens with diana's in every single one of these games
they're in every she's in every game spark notes for hitman 2 but for real thank you all you guys
here all the resubs all the new subs spoilers we know she's in the game uh except for most of
absolution we don't talk about absolution absolution really is such a weird game
because it sits right in the middle of absolute perfection of video games you know what i mean
you've got like the first few hitmans were just you know genre defining pieces of video game
media right and then you have absolution which was just what the hell is this it was like
good but it was like an action game it was it was kind of linear and then you got like
these two which are fucking fantastic absolution is a vine game but it's just
like it just doesn't it just sits right in the middle in a weird place in hitman
lore and hitman gameplay because the thing that predate it and i think that succeeds it
is just so much better it's just odd but i will see you tomorrow we will talk more about hitman
because we're gonna play it again tomorrow is absolution a good starting game no i think you
should only play absolution if you really really love hitman and it's one of your
favorite franchises if you want to start somewhere it's just i mean it's just hard
at the just start at the first hitman from 2016 you'll get it or hitman 2 i would just
start with the one that came out in 2016 blood money is the best one so far or the best one
in that originals yeah it is but i would just start with just get a good taste of it start
with the best you can play blood money on browser that's kind of weird but with that
see you all tomorrow have a great rest of your night take care sleep well goodbye