All right. Okay, everybody settle down. Settle down. Hello. Yeah, and guess what? You can hear me, huh?
You can hear me pretty well. Not like it was before. I'm not gonna drink a- hold on. Hey,
how you doing? So not like it was before, right? You can actually hear me talking. I've got a little
clip here. Previous times I've been in front of the green screen. You couldn't hear a single
goddamn thing I was saying. Not this time. Now you can hear me. And by the way, we're in full 60
FPS. Not 30. Not the 30 bullshit. This is 60 FPS. And I got a lav microphone and I hope it works
because if it doesn't then we're in big fucking trouble. Oh shit, I got a tweet. Does everybody
hold on? Hang tight. So you can hear? All right. I need to test this shit because I have no idea
how this sounds. I literally got these microphones like a day ago, not even 24 hours ago. If these
things work, this company's getting a major shout out. Like huge shout out. And by the way,
high quality camera this time too. High quality camera. Does this sound good? All right, hold on.
Let me just tweet that. Yeah, so hopefully it sounds all right. These things are pretty cool.
Let me try a scream test. Can I try? Hold on. Can I scream? Can I scream in your ears? I'm
gonna scream in your ears. Seriously, like I'm gonna scream in your ears and let me know how it is.
Ready? Why would I not do this in front of the green screen? All right, ready? This is an audio
test. What's up? Audio test. Testing the audio. I'm gonna scream, so turn down your volume. I'm
being dead serious. Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. That was probably horrible.
I don't know. I just got these microphones like fucking a day ago. Is it bad? Is it okay? I mean,
we're peaking, but I mean, is it all right? You should smoke cigarettes. I'm not gonna smoke a
cigarette. Is it okay? Dude, my little brother's head just, whatever. Oh yeah, we need to tell
Discord we're doing this. I've got my wonderful production assistant Holly here. You understand
how much of a pain in the ass this was to do alone for the last fucking three or four years?
You understand how hard this was to do alone? What a pain in the ass it was. I promise, I'm not,
I'm gonna, it's gonna peak. It's gonna happen, but let's see, I got the gray shirt. I'm good to go.
So what's the first thing I should do? She's gonna be here to help me. This is gonna be so much
easier. All right, so what I have to add, let's get some classics. Let's get some classics out
of the way first. Do I still got it? Do I still got it? Medium shot. That's not how I do it. What
am I doing? Hold on, wait, that's not, that's not how I do it. I gotta come into frame with it.
I gotta see if I still got it. All right. I still fucking got it. Sorry, mom. All right, so what's
the first thing? There are like 300 fucking things I have to do right now. I'm not doing this ever
again. This is the last time, so we're gonna blow through these like a million times a second.
Wait, what? How? Why? Who? How? How? Why? How much? Where? Why? Huh? Who? How much? What was the
other ones? What are the other ones? Are you ready? Why are you ready? Into the camera or just off?
Are you ready? Are you ready? You don't look ready. Hey, how? Are you ready? They didn't hear that.
They didn't hear that. You didn't hear that. You didn't hear that. I have a lavalier microphone,
but you didn't hear that, okay? What was I asking you? How? How do you do that again? Okay,
are you ready? Because, I mean, very clearly we gotta go. Did they hear it? Answer? There are
answers. All right, give me. I have both of my hands in my back pocket. Like, oh, yeah, all right.
Yes. Yes. Yes. No. No. No. Absolutely not. No. I ain't gonna do it. No. No. Sorry. No. No. Why not?
I feel like I'm at like a weird audition. I feel like I'm at an audition right now.
There's like three people with clipboards over there, and they're just like judging every word
I'm saying. Why not? Huh? No. No. I'm sorry. No. I ain't gonna do it. Oh, fuck you. You see what
I got dealing with back here? You think I'm gonna do that shit? No. You do it. You go do it. You deal
with this. No, I'm not dealing with that. I may have caused it, but I'm not gonna deal with it.
You are. You're the one with the money. All right. What's next? Yes. All right. What is
backroom Jerma? Yeah. What is it? Come around the corner, stop and stare at the camera like a madman
for a few seconds before sprinting at the camera. All right. Why is it? How is this back rooms? What
does that even mean? Like this? They can hear all these burps and it's gonna be fucking embarrassing.
They're gonna hear literally every single one of these burps. They're gonna hear every burp and
it's gonna be, they're gonna clip every single burp I've done and it's gonna be embarrassing.
All right. Don't listen to my burps. Just fucking delete them. Don't listen to them. All right. So
around the corner, stare and then run at the screen. I just lost a shoe. Hold on. Take two.
Take two. Take two. What fell? Okay. We're good. Is that the only thing that fell? I think it bumped
up. I didn't, nothing happened to me. All right. Are we still live? We're good. Oh, that's an
expensive mic. No, it's not. Wait, that's yours? Oh shit. I'll replace it. I promise. Now the worst
part about that is you didn't get to see that, which actually kind of sucks, but I full sprinted
back there and there's a million cords here and I tripped over one of the cords and took an
expensive microphone down. I'm gonna replace it. I'm gonna replace it. There's so many cords back
there that I almost like died. All right. We'll do it again. Here we go. There you go. Okay.
I'm not gonna, thank God it wasn't the ethernet. Okay. Ride a roller coaster. What are these?
Okay. Roller coaster. Should I be in a seat? Does this work? I hope this works. I wish that
was on camera. God damn it. It sucks that that wasn't on camera. So I'm gonna roller coaster.
Should we do this from two different angles? Okay. I've been waiting to ride this one, man.
Yeah. You know, I heard this is the scariest ride at the park. I'm not scared though. Are you scared?
Yeah, I bet you are. I bet you're scared. I'm not scared at all. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Whoa. Hey.
Hey. Hey, you can see the whole park from here. Can you see? That's crazy. Dude, look, you can see.
You can see the water rides. I didn't even know the park had water rides. Okay. Yeah, dude. Hey.
Yep. Okay. Yep. Now I ain't gonna scream. You're gonna scream though. Okay. This is really how I
know. Why is every wooden roller coaster do this shit? Yeah. Holy God. I was trying to be spinning.
Why am I spinning around? Dude, I got it. I got it. I'm all right. I'm all right. This thing ain't
safe, man. This thing's not even a safe ride. I don't think this has been raided. Has this
ship even been raided? It's all right. I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Oh, we. Let me give you a
better one. Let me give you a better one. This is what I would do on a roller coaster. I wouldn't
be saying we. I'd be screaming. All right. Here we go. Stop turning. Hey, man. Hey, you know what
I mean? This is a big drop coming up here. I don't like doing that. I feel like I'm gonna fall out.
Okay. Nobody uses for anything else besides what we're doing this for. There's no way anyone's
gonna use this for anything else besides riding a fucking roller coaster. All right. That's enough.
Evil villain monologue. I feel like I need to be in an evil villain costume. What do we have for
costume? Do I want to drink poison? Oh, I was like, what? There we go.
Gary's mod rag doll animation. Okay. Is that better? You can hear me, right?
Gary's mod. What is it? Gary's mod rag doll. There's also family guy rag doll, right? All right. Let
me see if I can try it. There's so much shit back here. We're going to be here all night.
All right. The family guy thing is this, right? You go like that. Oh, it's like that.
I'll do it one more time. One more time. I got to like duct tape this around my neck.
All right. All right. You cartoon monster.
Yeah. Yeah. Thumbs up. Okay. Oh, God. Get it off. All right. Oh, God. Get it off me.
You guys feel like there's bugs everywhere. My diet coming out here because there's bugs everywhere.
I don't like when the bugs are everywhere. I can tolerate them when they're in small doses,
but dude, is this something on me? Is this something on my back? Is this something on my back?
Just tell me. Get it, get it, get it, dude. Get it, get it, dude. Come on just get it. Get it.
What is on my back? What's on my back? Dude. Get it. I'll stand still. Just hit it with that
with a baseball bat. I don't care. Oh my God. It's huge, dude. It's huge. Please.
Come on. Just get it off. What the fuck dude? Please get it off me.
Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. Get it off.
Come on. Yep. Hit it, please. Oh, my God, dude.
My rib cage! You just hit my fucking ribs!
That was my back rib, you fucking idiot!
Ow!
You didn't take me to a doctor!
You didn't take me to a hospital!
Please!
You hit way too hard!
What?
They can hear my heartbeat?
Oh, it's because it flipped upside down.
Move it to your shoulder.
They can, wow!
Alright, hold on, give me one second.
That's fucking crazy!
Somebody said, dude, we can hear your heart murmur.
Can you still hear it?
Are we good? Is that better?
No more heart palpitations?
I can't move.
Alright, so what have we got? What's next?
I'm on TV. Alright, that's probably up here.
They're filming.
Are you filming? I'm on TV.
They're filming, right?
Get out of here.
Hi, Mom!
Hey, Mom, I'm on TV! I'm sorry.
Can I have the mic?
No, you don't have to give it to me.
I'm on TV, Mom! Look at me, I'm on TV!
I'm on the television!
Channel 2!
I'll leave, I'll leave.
That's so cool that you guys are here.
That's awesome that you guys are here.
Do you guys come here a lot?
Maybe once every few months?
That's cool. Can I talk on the mic?
No, it's okay. Alright, I don't need to.
Can I talk? Okay, alright.
Bye, Mom. Pasta tonight.
Pasta tonight, Mom.
I hope so. I'll be okay with McDonald's soup.
Alright, now what?
Cartoon splat?
Oh, like I'm running into the wall.
I'll do that one.
That hurt. I'll do it again.
Let me come from this angle this time.
Okay, what's next?
Yell at God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Real funny.
Real funny stuff.
You did this.
You did this, and you can fix it too, you know.
What a real piece of work you are.
Oh, you created everybody.
Did you though? Sure it wasn't me.
I could have been up there. I could have been up there and I could have done it.
You're a real piece of work.
You know what?
I can't even say it to you, but you know what I was going to say.
I was going to say,
Forget you. That's better.
Forget you, G-O-D.
You know, you have the power to fix all this.
Where are you?
We're all down here waiting for you.
You are a real piece of work.
Hopefully you can hear me.
So what? I'm standing in the street.
I've got something to say to you.
And hopefully you listen this time.
Not like the other 30 or 40 times in the shower that I've done this.
You know what? F you. For real.
I said it. Yeah, I did.
How long do you want me to do this for?
AI Andy, okay.
Ah.
Hmm. Hmm. Uh-uh.
Uh-uh. Hmm. Mmm-mmm.
Ah. Yes. Yes.
Ugh. Ugh.
Ugh. Sword?
Oh, Oblivion, okay.
Stop, criminal scum.
I've never played Oblivion. I don't know how this works.
I've never played one minute of Oblivion.
No, I stream for like a day.
What do they say? What do you do?
It's stop criminal scum, right?
Is it stop criminal scum?
Stop, you violated. Okay, you violated the law.
Stop, criminal scum.
You violated the law. You will pay in blood.
Let's go.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Ugh.
Stop. Did I do good?
I want just some sword shit too, you know what I mean?
Swim? Well, I got the sword. Hold on.
Oh, they walk into chairs. Yeah, they do walk into chairs.
Is my flight on? Yeah, I keep it here.
Make sure MPVs are shit like you and end up
doing something fucking dumb. I get you.
Is this Oblivion? Why is this not Oblivion anymore?
Hold on. What was that?
I don't know what that was.
But it was weird. Okay.
Yeah. Hey, how's up?
I heard you were talking about me and my kingdom.
Just a little too, a little too harsh.
You know, this was welded with Dragonbone.
I don't know if you can tell by looking at that.
I remember I was there
when this almost fell backwards.
I remember I was there when this was crafted in Dragonblood.
They call it Dragonstone Steel.
You think you can handle that?
You think you can handle that? Let's find out.
You want a duel? You and me.
Dragonbone Steel. With whatever you have there.
Whatever that is. What's that again?
Stainless steel? Yeah.
We all know how, we all know how sturdy that is.
Why don't you come over this way and let's see.
Come on. Why don't you come here.
Dragonbone technique.
Come on, come on. Easy, easy.
Ew. Ew. Ew.
Ew. Oops. I may have just
cut my finger. Oopsie. Oopsie.
Oopsie. Oopsie.
Oopsie. It's okay. I'm fine. Come on. Come on!
Do it already. Let's go.
We can't just stand here all day, dude.
I got shit to do. Come on. Come at me.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Look at me.
Look at me right now. Yeah.
I won. Stainless steel. Would you get it off
the fucking god damn TV?
Get it off the TV. Clean him up.
I'm peaking.
Yeah. It's going to be peaking.
I can't help it. Do some twerking?
Alright.
This is poison. Drink poison.
Alright. This is poison.
Well, not really, but you know.
Oh, wow. A magical potion?
This is for me?
No way. Thank you.
How much do I owe you, stranger?
Ten pieces of gold?
That's a steal.
Okay. You can use that one if you want.
What is this? Potion.
Clear. Clean.
Crystal. Don't mind if I do.
That's an option?
Or, I already had it on me.
I'm going to have to take a health potion for that
after that one. Redo.
I'm going to need a health potion after that one.
Good thing I stocked a few of them.
That hurts. A little. Does that supposed to feel like that?
It feels. My whole face hurts.
My face is burning. That burns.
A lot. What the?
What is that?
I feel actually alright.
I feel warm. I feel really
warm though. What the?
What was that?
I'm going to lie down.
I don't know who gave this to me.
I can hear my heartbeat
through my own head.
Okay. What's next?
What else we got? I love people clapping.
Twerk?
I'm going to twerk.
Yeah, I'm going to twerk. Yeah, I'll twerk.
I don't care. I'll twerk with the fucking
crown on. The king.
I want everyone to understand
that the king made a lot
of good things happen today, don't you think?
You little jester over there.
You're so funny. I made things happen.
I raised taxes on everybody.
Every single person now owes
40% more taxes. That means more money for
the kingdom. Oh yeah.
How many people did we kill today? 60?
Yeah. That's a lot. Could have been 70
though. Could have been 70.
It was a good day. What's that?
What's that? What did you say? Okay.
Feed him to the lions.
Yeah, feed him. Feed him to the lions.
Don't you think? I don't know how to twerk.
How do you twerk?
You have to go like
that. That looks like I was about to start
like jamming. Get the
crown off. I don't
fucking know how it works.
Oh god. Okay.
Goblin time?
Alright, hold on. I got to do
a wardrobe change. What was
that? I don't know how
it works. I really don't get it.
I'm 37 years old. I don't
twerk.
That's alright. Do I have
like a thing to put on? Like a drape?
Oblivion guards? Didn't
I just do that?
Skyrim guards? I don't even know.
I don't play Skyrim. Yeah, we'll
put that on. I'm going to mute the mic while
I get into some different piece of clothes.
I'll be right back in two seconds. Yeah,
I'm changing clothes. It's going to be all awful.
You're going to be able to hear awful noises.
Because I have this lapel
thing on. Give me one sec.
Can you guys still hear me?
Do I sound okay? Can you guys still actually
hear what I'm saying? Do I sound alright?
Okay. I don't think these little boots
are going to fit on.
Let me take my shoes. Yeah, there we go.
I'm going to look like such a dickhead.
What am I supposed to even be
doing in this?
A jester?
Entertaining.
Just entertaining as a jester.
All they're going to be able to hear is
the sound.
I need to confirm how much of an asshole I look like in this.
Do I look like a fucking asshole?
I need to see the mirror.
Okay, this is literally
just a shitty Halloween costume that somebody got
last second from a bag.
This is like, oh yeah, dude, there was a Halloween party.
You coming? Yeah, yeah, of course
I am. And I just went and got a bag Halloween
costume. Let me see the flute.
Let me see. This is going to be
fucking loud. Yes, Sia?
Of course.
Am I blowing the wrong way?
How do I do it?
That was kind of cool. Somebody make me fly away
like Zelda, you know what I mean?
Alright, wait, wait, wait.
There's some junk. Oh, no, that's okay.
I'll do that. Let me do this dumbass
routine. Hold on.
Oh, yes, yes, of course. Yes.
You're in trouble. You're in
trouble. Get him.
Yes, yes. Kill him.
Kill him. Why am I hunching over?
No, they don't hunch over like that, do they?
Well, I'm like, oh yes,
kill him. I'm like a goblin.
I'm supposed to be like funny. Okay.
Sia says that you're in big trouble,
Harry. Harry Potter.
I'm not supposed
to be in this movie.
I don't know why I went to that. I just feel like I belong
there. Don't you understand? I feel like I belong
in that universe. Alright, let's try it again.
They don't even have kings. Alright.
Oh, yes.
Of course. Of course.
Sia says you're about to be in very
big trouble.
Oh, he's very angry.
Sia. Sia.
He's angry.
Was that loud, Sia? I'll be softer.
When do I get paid? Hopefully soon.
Would you like to hear a song?
I know Metallica.
I know the wind song.
The song of storms from
Zelda. That one?
Is that more than one note?
Oh, you mean the juggle?
Nobody does it as good
as Jester the Great.
And thank you.
Thank you, especially you.
The family guy death.
This motherfucker's
in jeans, too.
Yeah, let me
put this up. Kill the Jester.
Twerk as the Jester.
Alright,
might as well.
It's twerking time.
Sia, get down.
I've been a Jedi agent the whole time. Get down,
Sia. Back it up.
How we doing?
Okay, yep. This is gonna do. No, it's okay.
So pantomime each note.
I'm probably so red.
I'm like hot.
I'm like holding my breath to do that.
Because I can't breathe. I can't breathe
into this fucking thing. I can't
breathe. I have to hold
my breath to do this.
Oh, just pantomime every note. Hold your fucking
breath.
Do what you want with that.
I don't care. Do a bong
rip? Oh,
okay, right, yeah.
Should I do?
I don't want to get out of this unless I'm gonna do everything in it.
Oh, yeah, wizard stuff.
This thing's just jingly fucking
thing out of here.
Of course,
I'm gonna do fucking Harry Potter shit
again, right?
Should I be more like the mouth oils?
I need a mustache, too.
That's important.
I have to do the Harry Potter shit
again. I'm gonna look like such
a moron. Hold on.
What are the mouth oils?
Let me do this.
Hold that for a sec. Balls
exposed? What are you talking about?
My balls are not exposed.
Oh, I see.
They mean those balls. I get it, yeah.
Wait, what is that?
Do any of the mouth oils have
beards?
Who owns mouth oils family?
Who's like that mouth oil, the head
of mouth oil?
Hold on.
I kind of feel like I could do this in the camera.
You know what I mean? Who owns mouth oils family?
Is it like Dave mouth oil?
Hold on. How's it look?
Like a judge.
Should I just do judge shit instead?
I look like a fucking judge.
This is not a wand.
Harry. I don't think I'll talk like
Harry. You're not as
smart as all of us. You're not as smart as the rest of us.
They all look like this.
Get him. Seize him. Take him away.
My son
is way more intelligent
than you'll ever be, Harry.
And you prance around
and act like a little boy
while my little boy
also prances around too, apparently.
Wait, this is actually
okay.
I don't think I could put this on.
Should we tape it? I need my wand
too. I'm just going to tie it like a
regular knot. I don't care. I don't care.
That's fine.
Okay, how's that? If you aim to
duel somebody, go for it for real.
Harry Potter.
Wonderful to see you
here. Don't you have class, Harry?
Class is in session
right now. Potions.
Heard you're quite the student.
You and Ron
and Hermione. Hermione.
I'm keeping an eye on you,
Potter. You mess up
one more time and you
talk to my boy
Lucius
Malfoyle again like that.
It'll be the end of you. And if you're going
to use your wand, I might as well suggest
you use it. No bluffing
this time, Harry. No bluffing.
You're a little shit and you
always were. But you didn't
know, Harry, that I have lightning hands.
Oh.
Oh, I killed him. I think I killed
him. Oh, I
Harry. Harry, are you okay? Harry.
I need a doctor. Hold on.
Ividicus.
Okay, he's all right. He's fine.
He's fine. Everyone's laughing. If it's fine
it's okay. Harry's fine.
Hello,
students. Welcome to the Defense of the
Dark Arts class. My name
is Lucius Malfoyle.
I'm the new teacher in town.
And yes, I'm aware that your old
teacher has perished.
Dr. McGillicuddy.
Let's go ahead and open this. It's a great
peppermint schnapps, by the way.
I'm sorry.
If we could all open up your
textbooks and go to page 200,
please. We're going to be
using, yes, yes,
Ron, please.
Page 200, we're going to be making a frog
breath potion.
You know all about that, don't you, Harry?
The one you used
when you killed Lucius?
Open up your textbook.
I'm in the middle of teaching, Harry.
That's not the time to use that spell.
Didn't they ever tell you
you only use that spell if you mean to
kill another wizard? Never
use that spell, Harry.
And now you're going to be floating in the air.
There he is. Come around. Down.
Swinging around, he's swinging around, he's swinging around.
Down. Never use that spell
in my classroom again. Turn to page 300.
We're not doing that spell anymore.
Fucking gross. It tastes like
fucking Pez. There it is.
You know,
when I spend far too long
on this, people take
the shit that's not even funny and then they turn
it into something funny, so I'm very hopeful.
Okay, here we go.
Uh, no, no, period.
Well, class, it's been a pleasure.
Absolute pleasure.
But you all don't
understand the power of the Dark Lord.
And for that reason, I'm out.
Just like that show shark tank.
Yeah!
Oh, nice one, Harry.
Almost got me.
Holding onto my fucking balls.
This looks fucked.
I gotta go the other way. Does that work?
Hey, Harry. See you tomorrow on Potions, class.
How fucked is this?
Is this fucked up?
Do you look like the Witcher?
The Witcher? Hold on.
We gotta change into the Witcher.
Does the Witcher have an eye patch?
This tie is
so long. Can you see this?
I look like a
10-year-old wearing dad's suit
to work. Do you see? This is ridiculous.
This shouldn't be like this. I feel like I'm
two feet tall. What's a character's name
in The Witcher? Anybody that's not The Witcher
could be anybody.
Geralt.
Geralt of what? Rivia?
Geralt of Rivia?
I'll take a drink. You don't know who I am?
Geralt of Rivia. You should know.
Two orange juices. I'm gonna drink one now
and one later. Thank you.
Any witches? You seen any witches here?
No? Oh, I hate those motherfuckers.
Hey, you. Come here.
Heard you were a witch. I got a letter
from the King of Rivia that said that you were a
witch. Are you?
I've never played this game.
I've never played this game. I have never played
any of The Witchers. Do you want to know what I know
about The Witcher? Okay.
Here's what I know about The Witcher. I know about
The Witcher is this. I know that the first game
and the second game especially. Hey,
yeah, sit down. You're gonna want to hear this. Sit down,
witch. I heard that the second game
had four to five
minute loading screens when you
went outside or inside of a building.
So that's why I never played it. I never really
cared for it. I actually tried to load into
one building and I couldn't get in. It took about
four minutes. So I installed the game.
The game that I'm in. You're right. The Witcher
me. You got something to say about that?
We fixed the loading times in the Enhanced Edition.
Yup. Yup.
That's the guy that played it. That's the guy that
played the one before the Enhanced Edition.
Yeah, I remember. It sucked. What you gotta say
now? Witch. Wait, hold on.
Let me do my, like, let me do my patented move
that I do. That's what I did in all those games.
Rick Sanchez?
Give me a gun.
I can't.
Wait, it smells. Goblin
Time? Alright, let's do Goblin Time.
Yeah, give me the beard. The whole
thing smells. It all smells.
Why does everything that comes out of a costume bag
smell? They smell
like chemicals.
Like this? Gandalf?
Oh wait, no, Gandalf. Alright, I want
someone to put me in the PlayStation 2
Lord of the Rings game. Is it right-handed or left-handed?
I just want someone to do that.
Oh.
You shall
not
pass.
You are
not gonna go by me.
You are not passing
any time soon, Buster. I can do that
better. You shall
not pass. What's next?
Goblin Time? Okay.
Yeah, I'll do the chef stuff.
What the hell is this?
Peer into the orb?
Do we have an outlet?
How am I gonna do this?
Oh, I heard. I see
many things in here.
Frodo, I see you.
I see Sam. And I see
Hawaii. I want to go there
soon. After all this, of course.
After all this. You need to go
to Mordor.
Which, if I had to guess,
is a place
which, if I had to guess,
would be in this location
here, covered by all
the smoke and spout.
Why don't you take it? I'm
sweating. I'm sweating my
ass off in this thing, Frodo.
Take this from me. It's very hot.
As you can see, it's burning. It burns
my head and my face and it's making me red
and sweaty. Take it, Frodo.
Take it from me. Please.
Take it now.
Ow! Ow! It hurts, Frodo.
Take it!
With this?
Oh, no, no, no.
I see something horrible.
Come closer.
Tomorrow afternoon,
a dire thing will happen to you.
It will spill your
water on the table.
And it will drip, drip, drip over the edge
down to the ground.
And it will keep dripping
to a point where you have to wipe
under the table because water
got under the table side
and you need to really wipe under there.
And then under these where the cabinets are,
it drops into the cabinets kind of.
You need to open the
cabinet door and wipe the side of the cabinet
and it sucks.
Be careful. Also,
next week,
you will buy a lottery ticket.
Yeah? Oh, yeah.
And then that lottery ticket,
you'll scratch off the first three numbers
and you'll be a winner.
And you will scream victory. You'll be so happy about this.
Unfortunately,
it's a $2 winner.
That sucks. That's really horrible.
Not even a $5 winner.
And it was a $5 ticket, by the way.
Oh, the gods are getting angry now.
They're getting very angry, Frodo.
One final thing
that I've heard, that I see
in this device
that was given to me
by a goblin, Frodo,
next weekend,
you're going to get invited to a party on Facebook.
You're going to say maybe.
And you're going to be kind of excited to go.
But they're going to cancel.
They're going to cancel it
right before you say
yes. Because you would have been
the tenth person which made
them have the party in the first place.
So you were the asshole.
If you had just said yes, you would have been
able to go. Oh, yep.
That one is bad.
Hot, hot, hot.
Yeah, let me get out of this.
Reddit wizard.
Nice shoes.
Rconfessions wizard.
What is that?
Rconfessions.
Consult the Funko Pop.
You need to do
Deckard Kane.
Sit in a stool in front of the green
and order an adult. Okay, I'll order some beverages.
Yeah, actually, let me mute
so you can, as I said, this is not horrible.
Do Sephiroth.
Every white-haired bearded
person, I can't do them all.
Hold on, give me one sec. Okay, coming up next
we're going to do, I'm going to do Solid Snake.
Somebody said get in the box and
do snake stuff. So I'm going to do
some snake stuff. I need the little gun too.
Dun dun.
I picked a great time to do this.
Like in the middle of the dead of
summer in Vegas. A hundred plus
degrees out right now. Actually,
yeah, we do have water. I'll take some water. Dun dun.
Dun dun. Yeah, I'm getting Solid Snake stuff ready.
So, eye patch.
Which eye does he have it on?
Does it matter? I'm so sweaty.
I'm like
sweating through these clothes.
Is it the left eye or the right eye?
I just broke the fucking eye patch.
Ow, fuck.
Yeah, I'm alright. Shit. Well, how
am I supposed to put it on now? I'll just get in front.
You just guide me. Um,
does he have a headband? Okay. I got it.
I got it. Solid Snake doesn't have an
eye patch? What? Doesn't Snake
have an eye patch? Is that like a scarf?
It's a shirt. Does he look like
this? Does he have a sword?
It's Big Boss. Is it messing
with the mic? Alright, so the idea
is that I get in this and do the Solid Snake
stuff. Alright, I'm going to try.
I hope I don't knock anything over.
Okay, so it's like
there's no way I fit in this thing.
Okay. Oh! Oh,
shit. Gotcha, gotcha,
gotcha. You thought I was a box still.
Dumbass. Oh.
I still have these on.
Oh yeah, remember Solid
Snake with his like
goblin booties? Alright,
what do we got next? Uh, yeah.
Oh god. That's going to be
hard to do. Alright, I'll do it
though. That's going to be so awful. People are
going to freak out at that one. Where are the
teeth? I'm just keeping the boots on. I don't care.
Should I like slick my hair back for this one?
Teeth? Yeah. Yeah.
Might as well get this one out of the way.
I'm just sweating. There's no way it's going to fit.
I'm going to look like such a fucking creep like
this. Should I
have? Okay, this one is called
The Vampire at the Door.
Oh, hi.
I'm new in the neighborhood.
I notice you have a really nice house.
I'd love to come in.
Could I come in?
Could I come in your house?
I'm new in the neighborhood. Me and my family
just moved in down the street.
And I'm just trying to meet the
neighbors. Just trying to meet the neighbors.
That's all. I love what you did
with the yard, by the way.
That beautiful grass. The grass
looks beautiful. How do you get it that
long? I don't know. Maybe you give me some
pointers.
Can I come in?
Let me in. Let me in your
house, please. Can I come in?
Oh, yes. Okay.
Right, of course. I had some
dental work done and they
added extra length. I
wanted width. I didn't want
length and that's what I got.
Can I come in your
house? Could I come in? Can I come in
your house? No? No?
Okay. All right. Call me.
If you want to talk, call me. Call me.
Can I come in? No?
I'll wait here until I can.
That's all good. Don't worry about it.
I barely sleep.
Good night. You want some DVDs?
You want some DVDs?
I've got a lot of DVDs. Sharknado,
for one. Loaded on DVDs.
You like drugs? Do you like drugs?
I've got a lot. Just let me
in your house and I'll give you whatever you want.
Bleed. Coke. That's all I got.
I don't got anything else.
Call me. Let me in your house.
Let me in your house. Let me in your house.
This is a fucking TikTok video.
This is a TikTok video
at this point. Can we? It's a TikTok
video. You know what? I got a perfect
here you go. Perfect, perfect video
if you want to submit it. Just add
the TikTok UI
to that whole thing and it'll be a
fucking 10 out of 10. It'll be a literal 10 out of 10.
And add music to it and
put like a little like a chat.
Do Morbentime? Okay fine.
How would he say it? I don't know. It's Morbentime!
Huh! That's kind of like Power Rangers
right? Doesn't he like
It's Morbentime!
I'm Morbius.
Go see Morbius 2 in theaters
this July. Or
at the $5 bin
at your local Blockbuster.
Either one will do. I got paid either way.
Alright.
This man went to college.
Yeah, long time ago.
I'm still in these stupid
shoes. They're getting so dirty.
Holy shit.
You should Morb in front of the camera. I just did.
Okay. Oh my god. These are
so beat up. Say I'm Dr.
Michael Morbius.
Interested in the camera?
Actually, I probably should do some normal ones, right?
Like, hey!
Hey, what's up? How are you? Yeah.
I just moved in. Yep.
New to the neighborhood. Me.
I love your house. I love what you're doing here.
You know what I mean? I love this house.
Really, really beautiful lawn
you have, too. Yeah.
I got kids. Yeah, we all got kids, right?
Look, if you ever
it might sound weird, but if you ever want to hang out
and just kind of do something, just you and me or whatever
or we'd have to get the families together or whatever, that's fine.
Like, I would just come over. I would come over.
I would come in your house. I would come over your house.
And you'd let me in, right? Like, I would come
we'd do a thing. Would you be interested?
Okay. Okay.
Mmm.
Get some mojitos.
I make an insane mojito. You don't understand.
It's so good.
You know the trick for a mojito?
Extra mint.
People don't like the taste of mint usually.
Can I come in? Can I just come in?
Okay.
I could show you how to make a mojito the right way
and not like the way that everybody else makes it
without the extra mint.
I have to come in, though. Can I come in your house?
And that's when you do the teeth thing.
Okay. Oh, I know.
I'm sweating through this like crazy.
We're getting sweaty back.
I can't put a
clean shirt on. It would ruin everything.
Alright, fine. I'll do Goblin Time.
Jesus. Give me those.
These are perfect for Goblin Time. You're sweating.
Yeah, I know.
Alright, what do we have for Goblin Time?
You gotta look sexy.
Oh, I got you sweaty.
Oh, be careful.
Whoa, there's a lot in here.
Do I have anything else besides this? I have to put a mustache on for this.
Alright, let me get in the mirror and put this on.
Put on a twirly one.
I think this one will be alright for a little while.
Why is this a goblin? How is this a goblin?
Goblin Time?
Should I have something weird besides the two
like sacks of money?
Hey, fellas!
Now I just got in the dungeon!
Oh, yeah, that works.
I'm going to look like Barney Rubble.
Alright, I'm just going to put it on here.
In fact, this is a Barney Rubble costume.
We? Who?
I don't know who that is.
What is this going to look like?
Hey, Fred. Hey, Fred.
Oh, yeah, Fred.
That sounds fun to me, Fred.
Oh, yeah, working at the rock plant, Fred.
Yup. Okay, Fred.
That's good to hear. Good to hear, Fred.
What was I doing? Goblin Time?
Yes!
Oh!
I can't believe I stole this from those
adventurers!
What do we...
Coins! Gems!
Don't mind if I do.
What's this? A crown?
Whose crown could this be?
I think this is King Leonidas's.
No!
Looks like I'll be shutting off.
I hear adventurers.
Okay.
These are heavy.
The King's treasures are so heavy.
There must be so many things in here.
Let me take a look.
Let me see.
One is...
Look at...
Oh, my goodness.
So many things for me to play
with. So many things to try.
How many?
These are golden
doubloons.
The world's most valuable treasure.
I'll be taking this back to my den
immediately.
Who's that? Who's that?
Try this on for size.
Oops.
Try this on for size. A power gem.
Oh! Explosive!
Oh, another one.
What do we have here?
An explosive gem.
Oh!
Righteous!
Absolutely righteous!
I'll be off then.
Oh! Don't...
Walk from off frame?
Hold on, I gotta get all this shit out of here.
You know what? We can move to caveman after this.
A caveman wouldn't have a mustache, though.
I know. I mean, I threw them everywhere.
Isn't that what they wanted?
Okay. So I'm just sneak?
Alright, what's next? Caveman?
Grandpa? Do American Psycho.
Alright, hold on.
It's time to drink some water.
Oh, let's do this on 120 degree Vegas day!
Nah, I'm just kidding.
Hell yeah, water.
Alright, I'm gonna mute because you're gonna hear my throat muscles.
That's gross.
I can't. I don't know about this one.
I don't know about this one.
I'm supposed to be discovering fire?
Discover fire as a caveman?
Why would he be fighting people?
Why would he?
He's just beating the shit out of everybody else?
He's just so fucked up that he can't handle it?
They're stealing it.
Beating up a dinosaur.
The caveman wears jeans.
This is what you do in your spare time?
Yeah, kind of.
That's kind of what we're doing right now.
Alright, give me a sec. Costume change.
Alright, just drinking some water.
So what do we got? We got cashier.
Yeah, we'll do artist.
So this is artist?
What should I do for a mustache?
I can't wait to do that. That's gonna be so fun.
Should I get these out of the way?
Just cause they're here.
Do the guitarist. Yeah, I'm gonna do the music stuff right now.
I can't believe I twerked as the caveman.
You find fire so you twerk.
That feels like a Geico commercial, doesn't it?
Alright, so I'm just gonna do this from various angles.
This shirt is gonna be a different shade of gray.
It's gonna be so wet.
Alright, coming back.
Okay, this one's gonna be interesting.
So this one's play the piano in a band.
Alright, let's see what I can do.
I should probably be sitting down for this.
You probably all just heard that, that's fine.
Alright, here we go.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, thank you. Thanks for coming out.
Yeah, we got a new song that we're gonna play for you here.
What was that?
I think I just dropped a jam out of my pocket.
Well, maybe I should trade it in.
Alright, yeah, we're gonna play a new song.
This one is something we've been working on for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy it.
It doesn't have a name, it's currently untitled.
So that's what we're gonna do.
It's an untitled song, and I hope you enjoy it.
Maybe you can help us come up with a title after the end of the show.
It's gonna be peppy, it's gonna be a lot of upbeat.
So I'll hopefully see somebody out there dancing.
Okay, and a one, two, a one, two, three, four.
Okay, alright now, speed it up.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you so much.
No, sit down, sit down.
No reason for that.
Okay, if you're gonna stand.
Thank you, wow, thank you.
We've been working on that for like, what, two weeks?
Three weeks now.
Yeah, John came up with the lyrics.
You don't have to stand.
Sit down, sit down, no, sit down.
Alright, okay, thank you.
Thank you.
This thing's clearly inflatable.
Alright, let's do the next one with the fucking guitar.
Sitting or standing, what do you think?
I should probably be up for this.
Probably standing, right?
Stand, yeah, yeah, this is the guitar.
Look, I didn't, I'm not gonna go
and buy like a $500 acoustic guitar.
It looks fine on camera, it looks alright.
So do you think knee?
Knee like this probably, like that.
So it's gonna be like bang.
You can use this part if you want.
Didn't like ACDC do this shit?
ACDC would be like,
wait, what, we still have close ups?
Oh yeah, yeah.
Alright, any more instruments?
Should I play the accordion when I have like
the chef outfit on?
Okay, we'll do struggling to open a jar.
Give me, give me it, I got it, give it to me.
God.
You may get a little bit work in here, but alright.
Put your sink on.
Hot water, works.
What did you fucking do to this thing?
I'm gonna break the jar if I keep doing that.
Do you have one of those things you can open it with
like a bottle opener thing?
You can't look at me, don't look at me while I do it.
Don't look at me when I try to do it, cause I get nervous.
I'm just sweating.
It's already open.
Huh.
Now that's interesting, isn't it?
Ship was already open.
Ah, there it is.
There it is.
See, I can do it, I can open jars.
I'm strong.
Nice back.
Nice back sweat.
Somebody said you let out the wasps.
Oh, that's a good one, alright.
Well, I gotta be in the gray
in the jeans to match all the other
things.
Oh yeah, this is gonna bounce around if I do that.
Actually, it should go inside.
Yeah, let me mute for a second
cause I wanna put this back in.
These little things are great, these things are awesome.
One sec.
Somebody said back piss.
Do a western standoff, okay.
Oh, that's already one, okay.
Yeah, there's a lot of stuff that we're gonna be going through.
And I got plenty of time, so I don't wanna like
rush through everything and get like
winded in three hours.
We're here for like five hours, so there's a lot of
shit I'm gonna do.
Should I do the artist stuff right now?
I think that makes sense.
Oh, the scout ton. How do you do it?
You check your pulse.
So I'm like, I'm not even winded.
Oh, I need a head.
Oh, headphones, yeah.
That's gonna look so funny.
I'm not even winded. What's the engineer stuff?
Oh, should I just be like on a construction yard?
Oh my god, super fucking Mario.
Super Mario?
A guard hat?
Wait, hold on, hold on.
Alright.
Super, I'm gonna be Super Mario
with a, this is gonna be
fucked up, isn't it?
Alright, let me change. Let's get the Mario shit
out of the way. Costume change.
Do a backwards long jump.
Oh, you better believe it.
I'm gonna do all the speed run shit.
I'll be right back. Hold on a second.
What is this costume?
What the fuck
is this costume?
This is a Super Mario costume. Why is it
like this?
Okay, well,
I'm
muting. Oh, this is fucked up.
This is fucked up.
Alright, I'm back. Can you guys hear me?
Where's the hat?
Is it the engineer or do you want the Mario hat?
It's just the Mario shit. This is way too
low. This is weird.
Alright, what was it?
I need a Mario mustache.
And I gotta get the voice down too, like, oh!
Whoa! Whoa!
It's a me!
Mario! Hello!
Oh! Oh!
Okie dokie!
Hello!
This is my big role. This is my big break.
I feel like I'm in the wings
during a theater production.
And they just, like, the kids can't wait
to watch me.
Should this be this, I feel like, I'm like in a clown
costume. I'm just gonna wear
socks. I don't even care.
How does it go? Like this? Does it go up or down?
Like that? No, no,
the other way. Oh, can you help me? Yeah.
It goes like that? Yeah. Alright.
Are you needed? No. Oh.
Oh no. Hello!
You should be in bare feet.
No!
That's wicked funny though.
That's wicked funny.
He's in bare feet.
Oh. Just bare
ass feet. Okay, how's that look?
Do I look alright?
Yeah, it's a little scorched.
It looks like I have, I don't, this is like
down too low. This looks
inappropriate.
This looks inappropriate.
Doesn't this look inappropriate?
This is inappropriate. Oh, hello!
It's a me, Mario!
Oh! Okie dokie!
Oh! Ha ha!
Hee hee! Oh! Bingo!
Oh! Ha ha! Hee hee!
Ho ho! Oh!
Where's Luigi? Where's
Luigi? Can we get this out?
So what are some of the, I gotta, okay,
let me do some Mario stuff. Alright.
Hoo! Hoo!
It's like, meep!
Meahoo! Take that audio.
Meahoo! Meahoo!
Take that audio. And it's like
Hoo! Meahoo! Meahoo!
Meahoo!
I'm probably fucking up this audio so bad.
Meahoo! Meahoo!
Meahoo!
Hoo!
BLJs! Be careful!
I've got a big stomach, I'll be fine!
Alright, let's get some walking.
I'm gonna burp. And I can't hide it.
Hoo! Meahoo! Okie dokie!
Oh no! Bowser!
Bowser!
Meahoo! Kicka coo! Meahoo!
Kicka coo! Meahoo!
Fuck outta here! Sit the fuck down,
Bowser! Kicka coo! Meahoo,
motherfucker! Okie dokie!
Alright, let's get in the Mario Kart.
Do we have a steering wheel?
It's a circle.
Oh, nah, I'll just hold it
like this. How's it, does it look good?
This is kinda comfy, I like this.
Do we look alright? I'll do a bunch from the other side too.
Alright, I gotta center. I've got
to center, I've got to center.
Ok, welcome to Mario Kart.
I'll select your player.
It's me, Mario.
Here we go!
This is a big turn!
Bingo!
It's a red shell!
This is very
hard on Mario. This is a hard
car to drive. Mario!
Mario!
Very close!
Very close! Here I go!
Here I go! Here I go!
Here I go! Here I go! Here I go!
Oh, mamma mia!
Hey, Toad! You little shit!
Hey, Toad! I'm
passing you again for the third time this race!
Oh, no!
Mario need an alibi!
Oh! Oh, yes!
Oh, I'm selling
Cookie Monster. I'm doing Cookie Monster,
not even Mario. Alright, reset.
Three, two, oh, just here I go!
Oh, I love
cookies! Oh, cookies!
Let's see if you can
deal with this! Mario will drive
on his feet!
Get away!
Get this away from me!
Oh!
Super moves!
Toad! What else do you want from me?
Hotel Mario? What the fuck?
Walk in? Oh, okay.
No! No!
No! How do you do it?
It's like, no! She's looking at me
like I'm fucking crazy. No!
Toaster goes in
the toaster! Toast
no! Toast goes in the
toaster! Is that in the same thing?
Is that in that? Tuck that in?
There's a tag!
There's this song?
When you do the Mario, it's
swing your arms from side to side.
Come on, it's time to go! Do the
Mario! Okay.
Swing your arms from
side to side. Come on, and everyone
go do the Mario! Swing your
arms from side to side.
Come on, let's go! Let's do the Mario!
Is that the Mario for you?
Yeah, who that one?
Hey, yeah, who that one?
Bowser. Does he go like this?
He's like, I don't know the whole song.
Any more Mario shit?
The accordion is Mario?
Wait.
Hold on.
I wrote this song
for Luigi.
And every single person watching
wanted to turn the audio off.
That was for you, Luigi.
I can't wait to be the annoying waiter.
He'll be like, oh,
how are you?
And I'll take an extra tip, by the way.
At least 60 percent.
Enjoy your dinner.
Any more Mario?
The car's just in the corner.
You already just did this, right?
Yeah, go up the stairs.
Do you want Mario drug PSA?
Biyahoo!
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Bwah!
Hi, ladies and gentlemen. I'm Super Mario.
We've made a lot of jokes here today.
We've had a lot of fun. And I'm an actor.
But let me just be the first to tell you
that, you know, it's not fun. What is not
is totally biyahoo. Drugs
and alcohol. Stay away from them.
If somebody tries to pressure you
into drinking or smoking,
tell them with the hardest
of hearts, no,
I don't need to do that. We can get back
to the playing and games now.
But I wanted to make sure that that was a big biyahoo.
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
I saw you laughing in the corner.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with me?
I thought I had like residue on my face.
Okay.
Let me try again. One more time. One more time.
Bwah! Bwah!
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Hi, boys and girls.
I'm Jeremy Albertson, aka
the actor of Super Mario.
But you know what's not biyahoo?
And what's not cool? Drugs and alcohol.
If somebody pressures you
into smoking or drinking,
tell them no.
And you can tell them so long.
So long, King Bowser.
Take it from me.
I live a pretty cool life, don't you think?
Fuck!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
One more, one more, one more, one more.
Oh! Bowser!
It's a Bowser!
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Woah!
You know what's not funny? Something that's not completely
biyahoo. Drugs and alcohol.
Hi, everybody. I'm the actor that plays
Super Mario, and I just want to make sure that everyone's aware
if you're ever pressured
by drugs, alcohol,
or anything naughty at all,
say no.
There's no pressure at all.
Don't let somebody pressure you
into taking something you don't want to do.
And with that, it's time to so long, King Bowser.
Woah!
You can use one of those.
Whatever you want to use it for.
Do one in Mario character?
Okay. Okay, alright.
Okay.
Oh, god damn it. Alright, I'll try.
Biyahoo!
Mustache is so fucked up.
Okay, I think it's on.
I got it.
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Bowser!
Oh, boy.
It's impossible. I think it actually
might be impossible.
I'll give it one more try.
Oh, fuck. Okay.
I gotta like, just shut up and get into it.
God damn it.
Because I just imagine watching this on TV
and it's just like, it's so stupid.
Biyahoo!
Oh, Bowser!
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh!
Boys and girls, it's a me,
Mario. Let me tell you
something. If somebody wants to tell
you to take drugs,
you always say no. You say,
Luigi, try to drink
and do drugs one time.
And I said, no! And he said,
Mario! And I said, no!
Fucking god damn it.
The mustache came off.
That one was the one,
too. That was the take.
And I could feel it come off.
Oh, fuck. I could feel it
come off. Alright, I'm gonna give this one
more attempt and we have to move on.
I'm so sweaty. Okay.
Hello!
Okay, you can do this, Mario.
You can do this, Mario.
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Bowser! Hello, boys
and girls. It's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something
about drugs and alcohol. My brother
Luigi would also say this,
too. We both would say this.
Shit!
Biyahoo!
I gotta give it more than that.
Biyahoo! Biyahoo!
Bowser! I'll deal with you later.
Hello! Boys and girls.
It's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something about...
Just cut them together, okay?
Let me tell you something about
drugs and alcohol.
You should never take any drugs.
Never. Mario wouldn't. Luigi
wouldn't. Toad? Maybe.
But we don't need to talk
about Toad. Oh!
Oh!
It's a me, Mario. I want to talk to you
about drugs. Boys and girls,
don't do drugs.
You don't have to do them. Don't feel
pressured to take drugs or drink.
If anyone ever pressures you,
tell them Mario said,
so long, King Bowser, and they will
leave you alone. No!
Hello!
It's a me, Mario.
I have to do a drug
PSA. Okay. I'm done.
I can't.
I can't do it. I can't. That was
the end.
He's on drugs.
He's like
fucked up. He's fucking crazy.
He's running around like a psychopath.
He's
on something. Oh my
God.
Do the Bowser throw?
Alright, fine.
Yahoo!
So long, King Bowser!
And somebody that's King Bowser needs
to understand. Boys and girls,
don't do drugs. If you do
drugs, you'll end up like King
Bowser over there. Dead.
Is he dead? I don't know.
So long.
Is that what he said?
Oh my God.
Alright, any more Mario shooters? Is that it?
So long, King Bowser.
Anything else
we want to do as Mario? Happy Pride Month.
Yeah, it's the last day of Pride Month, right?
Oh my God, I'm going to take the whole thing down,
Luigi.
Luigi, I almost just took down the whole
camera.
Did it move? I don't think it did, right?
Let's just make sure you can still see me.
Did the camera move? Maybe they
can tell you. Did it move or are we good?
How about now? Am I good here?
Okay, good. So, that's fine.
Any more Mario stuff before we move on?
Lose a life? Do a ground pound,
okay. Yeah, I keep trying to go this
I'm so stupid. I keep trying to go
to the left. Okay, ground pound.
So it's like,
like that?
Like, Luigi. I'm fucking
done with this job. Never fucking doing Mario
ever again.
No, I can't. I can't.
So what is that? What is that
image of? I hate this. It's a fucking
pregnant Mario thing.
Oh my God.
That's a meme. That's a meme
right there. Whoopsie daisy.
Whoopsie. Alright, so should I
do the hard hat Mario? Wait, wasn't
this like Mario Odyssey?
Hey, look, bud. I'm an
engineer. That means I solve problems.
I solve practical problems.
So wait, does the mustache
off as the engineer? I guess that's
true, right? Build a sentry
That's Mario? This stomach
is going to get me in a lot of trouble.
Oh, hey, look, bud.
Sentry going up. Glasses?
Oh, yeah. Uh, these ones are good.
God damn it.
Damn it. Oh, damn it.
Sentry going up.
Good night, Irene.
Building a dispenser. I'm going to push
that car. Teleporter going up.
Ow. Ow my leg.
Let's get a teleporter
up here.
Ha ha ha.
Guitar?
Oh, sitting down.
Sentry down. Oh, alright, yeah. Let's do that.
Sentry down.
I can do better.
Hey, let me do it like every player does.
Right.
Sentry down.
What's next? Oh, get backstabbed?
We need a teleporter
right here.
Oh, I'm on fire. What does he say?
I'm on fire. Fire, fire, fire.
Fire, fire.
Oh, fire.
Medic, medic.
You can edit that in.
You have sound effects editing capabilities.
What's hillbilly?
Should I sit in a chair? Seeing a tornado.
Hillbilly seeing a tornado.
Maybe no gloves.
With the Mario gloves on.
Hillbilly seeing a tornado.
Is this the beard? No, that's the
hat. Isn't this what Mario just looks like
without his hat on? If Mario
doesn't have his hat on, this is what he looks like, alright?
When Mario's hat comes off in the games,
he looks like this. No gloves?
Oh, man.
What's that? I think that's a tornado.
Oh, that's a tornado
right there. That's a tornado.
We gotta get everybody
inside. Get everybody.
Wait a minute.
I gotta save him. I gotta
save him from the tornado.
Come here.
I got you. There you go.
You landed in the bed.
It's getting closer. It's getting closer.
Oh, we're gonna get
the cows in or the chickens.
Get the chickens in. I'm done with
this one. This one's over.
None of that is usable.
So Mario can come off.
Give me the Mario hat for a second.
Alright, stuff the hair in here.
This is important.
Yeah, but try to get all the hair in here.
As much of the hair you can get in there
as possible.
I gotta nail this, otherwise
this is the only chance I have to do this.
Can you do your front? I'll do your back.
Where's the mustache?
Thank you.
I'm gonna give the...
What? What's wrong?
Yeah, they are. That's fucking gross.
You didn't hear any of that.
Alright, I got one...
Oh my god, these are gross.
It's like as if you dunked these in water.
Alright, I gotta try this once.
I don't know why I'm so into the drug PSA
thing.
Oh!
Hi kids.
My name's Sean Stevenson.
I'm the actor that plays Super Mario on TV.
But what's not funny and what's not
bia-hoo is drugs and alcohol.
If anyone ever tries to press you into
taking drugs, you just give them a no.
A no!
And if you get older
and you decide to drink when you're 21,
make sure you do it in moderation.
Be very careful. Honestly.
This fucking hair!
Whatever.
The actor revealed
that's not Mario's hair.
You look like you just got out of jail.
But honestly though,
don't do fucking drugs. Don't be an idiot.
Alright, what's next?
You're on drugs.
Marijuana in moderation if you're old enough
and you can be careful with it.
Alcohol if you're old enough, be careful with it.
Understand? Be careful.
Real PSA. Be careful.
Don't be dumb. Is it really that bad?
I should probably have, yeah.
Let me give you a new shirt.
Alright, costume change, I'll be right back.
Almost back. One sec.
Dude, these little things are insane, by the way.
These things are awesome. This little guy right here.
So this is a microphone.
This is like a little wireless...
I know, I know.
This is a microphone.
You just clip it on and it works.
I actually really like this.
Hopefully it's been sounding okay.
Vincent van Gogh, yeah.
Probably this one.
Oh, spoilers, yeah.
Chat, does that sound fine? Does that sound okay?
Did we sound good?
Yeah? It's okay?
Yeah, I'm telling you, if these things worked out,
I'm going to shout this fucking company out.
I swear to God.
Not yet though. Not yet.
Not yet.
This is a painter routine.
Comment on what I'm painting on the big screen or whatever.
Yeah, what was the description?
Okay.
Take a little bit of this.
A little bit of this.
Oh, that looks good, don't you think?
How do you say it? Looks very good.
Looking pretty good.
It's masterpiece.
No? No?
It's masterpiece, no?
No?
What do you know about art? You know nothing about art.
You don't know anything.
You know nothing about art.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Add a little bit of this.
A little bit of green.
Extra green.
Just a little final touch.
What do you think?
Let me get a little closer.
Why would I need to get closer?
That was right here.
Alright, now let's do a big one.
Look at what I have for you.
Look at what I've made for you.
Oh, it's beautiful, no?
The colors.
It looks fantastic.
One of the best I've ever painted.
Finishing touches. Add a little bit more red.
Looks very good.
Very good.
I don't like this.
I don't like this part.
Right here. Let me change it.
That's...
Magnificent. Absolutely
Magnificent.
Last final touch, I swear I will not touch it again.
Oh, beautiful.
Beautiful painting.
You don't like my art work?
But you are stupid. Very stupid.
She threw this at your face and you turned your fucking head.
That is a masterpiece right here.
Fucking dope idiot.
I got like really into that one.
I was like into that. That was like fun.
I was really into that.
Alright, what else?
Cashier. Should I?
Tired, fast food, miserable one.
A fast food one?
Should I still be with a mustache
and a palette?
This doesn't work for this.
So I'm working at like a store.
Same mustache?
So am I
scanning items or what am I doing?
I'm going to be scanning items.
The fucking Saul Goodman shit is going to be in there.
How are you?
I'm doing great.
This is all you have? This is it?
Get the cart back there. You're going to have to bring it in.
Right.
Look, I don't care.
I don't care about that.
Call somebody else.
I'm literally just here trying to work.
Why are you telling me this?
I don't want to hear this.
I'm literally just trying to help you.
I'm trying to help you. I'm just trying to get you out of here.
Put up with these fucking people.
I swear to God. Just screaming at me.
Okay. Yeah. Sure. Whatever.
That's it?
That's $49.
Thank you.
Put your card in.
It goes the other way.
It goes the other way. The card reader, it goes the other way.
You have a chip on it, right?
The chip goes, chip facing in.
How many stores
have you been to in your whole life
that you don't know the chip goes the other way?
Fast food, what?
A fast food?
A barista?
This is like, oh, do checkout items.
Okay.
I can't work with that.
All right. Barista. Here we go.
Man, oh, man. Yep.
Hey, what's up, man? Hey, what's up?
Yep. I knew you were coming.
This is yours. That's your extra
soy latte. Extra whip.
Extra sugar.
Yeah, man. Just got a new machine. Hold on.
Hold on. Let's do that again.
Oh, yo. What's up? Hey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I knew you were coming.
I got you ready. That's your extra whip, extra cream, extra sugar,
extra not coffee.
There you go. Take it, man.
How you been? It's been a hot minute since I've seen you.
Yeah. You want another coffee?
Do you want one, too?
Hey, let me guess. Extra whip,
extra cream, extra sugar, no coffee.
Yep. I got you. Don't worry.
Let's go ahead and put the coffee
aside over here because we're not going to use it.
Let's do cream.
Okay. A bunch of sugar.
Okay. Interesting.
Let me go like this
because it keeps folding in on me.
Hey, let's try that one more time.
Oh, yeah. I need those, yeah.
Hey, here we go.
All right.
Looks really nice.
Hey, hey. What's up, man? How are you?
Yeah, I got a pot brewing for you right here.
Was it on?
Yeah, I think this thing is pushing down.
Is that better? We good?
It keeps, like, folding in on itself.
Hopefully it sounds all right. Good? Okay.
Hot coffee. Hot pot.
Let's brew that coffee. Nice, freshly
brewed coffee. There it is. Throw it away.
We don't need that. There we go. This is the cream.
There we go. There's the sugar.
And there's the milk.
Hey, what's up, bro? How are you doing?
I got a coffee for you brewed right before you got in.
I know your order. Come on.
I don't know your order or not. There, take it.
Is it good? Give it a try.
That's freshly brewed, by the way.
Yep. Do you want one, too? You want a coffee?
Hey, let me guess. Cream.
Sugar. It's syrup.
And no coffee. You got it. Yep.
I got you. Is the weather out there?
Was it hot? Yeah, it's always hot out there.
Yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Really? No, dude.
Really? Hey, try this, man.
Try this. I call this
Hey, you know what I call this, man? I call this
the shit that's after
you eat the cereal, the milk you drink.
Here you go. Take it, man. Try it. Give it a try.
What do you think? Give me your honest opinion.
I want another real deal. Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Tasty, isn't it?
Very good. Yeah, it's very good.
Wait, what do you want?
Do you wish you wanted a black coffee?
What's that? You want a black coffee?
Fucking weirdo? What?
What did you say? What did you want?
I don't know if I even have that. Let me see.
I've got milk. I've got
a bunch of cream and I have sugar.
You want coffee?
All right, I guess that's fucking weird, but
I'll make it for you. This is on the ground, by the way.
All right, there you go. Here's your coffee.
Freshly brewed. There it is. Put your cup out.
There it is.
Weird that somebody ordered a fucking coffee. Usually people order milk,
sugar, and cream, and then they mix it up and they
stir it up and they add like fucking hazelnut syrup to it.
What's going on here? What the fuck is going on?
That person's a fucking weird person.
And I want to get him out of my store now.
Hey, yo, uh, you gotta leave.
You gotta leave now.
I'm not into you here. This is fucking
big, big, big
dicks coffee. I was going to say this is big
dicks coffee. You get the fuck out of here.
Do anyone want some coffee?
Oh, the
coffee, really?
Hey, coffee.
Coffee. Anyone want some coffee?
Coffee. I just brewed a fresh pot of coffee.
Hey, coffee.
Who wants coffee? Hey, who wants coffee?
I just, I got a fresh pot of coffee
here. Hey, who wants coffee?
You want coffee?
Hey, you want coffee?
Hey, who wants coffee?
I got coffee. I just brewed a fresh pot of coffee.
Fresh pot. You want coffee?
I just got a fresh pot of coffee. You want coffee?
Coffee. Who wants coffee?
I'm doing it right, right?
Fast food worker. Oh, God.
I'm going to say all the fucking fast food workers out there.
You should be making way more money.
Dad grilling burgers.
Well, I probably wouldn't be wearing this.
I'll do dad grilling burgers.
It's a beautiful day. Just on grilling duty.
Be careful over there. Be careful.
Don't be too rough.
Let him like a beautiful grill. Beautiful day.
Yeah. Yep.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
It's a worst job, by the way.
I don't know. Nobody can hear me, but still.
Just sit up here all fucking God damn day.
Fifteen patties here.
Four of them are going to get eaten.
Stupid fucking idiots in this family.
Yep, I can see you.
What are you doing?
That's a funny hat.
That's a funny hat that you have on.
Yep, you're my boy.
Yeah, you are.
The kid's a fucking idiot.
Does anybody want a burger? Burgers are almost done.
I mean, I shouldn't be flipping these as much, but I am.
What do you do up here besides just flip?
Flip, flip, flip, flip, flip.
You just wait for somebody to come tap you on the shoulder.
Nobody's fucking around me.
Oh, hey, dad. Oh, there's the grill master.
There he is, the grill master.
Yeah, yeah, because nobody else wants to fucking do it.
So I do it, and I sit here all day.
You're going to think I want to be back there.
What's that? No.
You're doing a great job out there, son.
Don't climb that.
Don't get down from there.
Don't climb that. Do you mind?
Don't climb that.
He's a maniac, I know, right?
He's my son, right?
You ready for a dog?
You don't want a dog.
Does anybody want dogs?
No one wants a dog.
What did I put seven on here?
It's stupid. It's stupid.
When I take a tally, when I take a tally,
and I say, what do you want?
Do you want a burger or do you want a dog?
And I hear, dog, dog, dog.
I take a fucking dog.
What's that? Yeah.
Yeah, that's awesome.
You threw them in the pool?
When I say how many fucking hot dogs I'm going to make,
it's seven, and nobody eats them.
Nobody eats the seven dogs.
You know, I'm going to eat one.
Those are fucking gross. Those are raw.
That was pretty much raw.
That was a raw hot dog that I just ate.
I wish somebody else could be.
We should hire someone to do this next time,
so I don't have to sit here and do this in three hours.
What's that? Yeah, you want a burger?
You do? And you want a dog, too?
Yeah, come on over here.
I got buns, I got ketchup,
I've got mustard, there's relish right here, too.
Please, go for it.
Whose kid is this?
He's going to Harvard. I'm telling you.
Little Michael's going to Harvard.
He's going to Harvard. Thank you.
You like it? It's delicious.
This is what it's about.
It's about grilling out here with the family,
with the friends, and yeah, alright.
Okay.
How much longer do I do this for?
Who's going to use this?
No one is going to use it.
I can't just sit up here
and just fucking do a
one-man monologue show.
Do you remember when I did
the whole saw routine?
I was in the chair.
I was five, ten minutes
straight of doing this whole routine.
Out of
four or five hundred videos,
I think one person
used it, and it was for five
seconds total.
I'm just doing an acting
study. Who's going to use it
for anything?
So this is a driving instructor?
Okay.
I need the mustache back on.
Let me see what it looks like.
I'm just
doing it for like ten minutes.
Nobody stopped me.
I looked at Holly. Holly was just
sitting there staring at me like,
she kind of gave me the, are you still going?
And I'm like, I guess.
I don't think so.
Okay.
So this is a driving instructor.
I look like a fucking weirdo.
Okay. Driving instructor.
Look at the clothes.
All right.
So should I be this way?
If I'm sitting down with a clipboard
and I'm writing? I don't know.
Should I be facing
a few different angles?
Okay.
Let me know if I'm in frame
when I get over there.
Okay.
How's this?
My fly is not down, right?
I'm not going to get in trouble.
So like from here up?
I'm going to hold it here.
So I'm going to say, if I'm a passenger,
the driver is over here.
How are we doing? How are we? Good?
You can begin at any point.
I'm going to be paying a lot of attention to what you're doing, by the way.
You can come out here and take a right.
Easy on the gas. Easy. Hold it back.
A little on the gas there.
You can get on the highway here.
Stop.
Slow down.
I'm going to have to take off a few points for that one.
But you didn't signal.
You didn't signal when you went right.
And that's the first thing that we're going to do here.
By the way, if you get four or five points wrong here,
your license is not going to come through.
And I am a stickler.
Very much so for these points.
Just keep that in mind.
You can merge over here if you want.
Slowly merge.
Way too fast.
Actually too fast.
Okay. I don't know what that was.
Just stay in your lane here, please.
Thank you.
Very nice.
That was a good one. That was actually a pretty good merge.
Good. Watch it.
Keep your eyes on the road here, please.
Be careful.
Do you mind?
Just go ahead.
This is my car in the glove box over here with me.
See if I can grab these glasses.
Just keep driving.
You're fine. You're fine. Keep driving.
Keep driving. You're all right.
It's a very big car.
Yeah, that's why I have it.
Just make sure I can see what you're up to.
Could you pull this way and park for me, please?
This is the parallel parking part of the exam.
Over here,
parallel parking this spot right here.
There's two spots available. Not the one in front of the red truck.
The one behind it.
Behind the red truck.
Use your eyes.
Do you want these?
Do you want to put these on?
I told you I was a stickler and I'm going to be that.
Right there,
parallel park behind the red truck.
I'm not going to say it another time.
Get up there in parallel park.
You hit it.
You bumped his bumper.
Get your tire perpendicular to the window.
Tire perpendicular to the window.
Back up at a 40-degree angle.
Turn around.
Back up. Drive straight.
Turn right at 45 degrees. Pull in.
You learned this already.
I am very much unhappy.
That's going to get you two grades off, I think.
You're not getting your license today, by the way.
I think that very clear.
Very bumpy.
All right, that's enough.
What I have here is I have
two bumped cars.
Would you like to see the notes?
You can see it if you want. Would you like to see what I've written down?
Go ahead and look.
You bumped a car.
You went 40, 50 miles per hour
getting on the on-ramp to the highway.
And not only that, you don't know how to parallel park.
And guess what? I don't either.
But I'm not the one getting this test taken.
Is there anything that you can pass?
Give me the wheel.
Let me show you how it's done.
Here, you hold this. Yeah, you grade me.
You grade me.
You go ahead and grade me.
Easily let off the gas.
Put the brake on. Let go of the brake very, very easily.
Easily, easily.
Thank you.
Put the gas on. Oh, shit.
This is how you do it. This is how you drive a goddamn car.
You can go to sleep if you want.
I got this.
Very nice. Pull it in.
Parallel park it. This is how we parallel park.
Step on the gas.
Step on the brake.
Step on the gas again.
And we're in the spot.
What did you do, coach?
What did you put down for me? Did you give me an A?
Get out of the car.
Okay, so now I have to be going
this way?
Okay.
Am I on the right side here?
That pencil.
The doctor of God.
So this is for you guys to do
cuts if you want to do cuts.
I'm sure about that.
Okay.
What you need to do is you need to relax.
Put your gist up on that gas.
You screwed that up.
What you needed to do there is you had to...
Not happy about it.
Very much unhappy about that.
You're pretty dumb.
Can I just tell you? You're dumb.
No human drives a car like this.
No human.
You could get a chimpanzee in this car and you'd probably do better than the test than you did.
In fact, you'd get an armadillo
to do this test and probably do better than you just did.
You'd get an ant.
You'd get me an army of ants
and get them up to the wheel.
Four or five thousand ants.
And I could train them to do a better parallel parking job than you could ever imagine.
Keep going.
You don't think I could do that?
You don't think I could train ants to do that?
You don't think I'm smart enough to train ants?
They'd be running circles around you, by the way.
Oh, what a terrible...
Stop sign. Stop sign.
Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign.
Do you see what's in front of us?
You do, right? What's in front of us?
Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign.
Stop sign.
Keep going.
I think the microphone's fucked up.
There we go.
Now what I want you to do is I want you to pull in that McDonald's.
Very important part of your test.
Driving through a drive-through is actually very hard.
It's a very narrow road.
It's a very narrow part of...
It's hard to kind of navigate in there.
Pull in smoothly. Smooth it out.
Stop.
Roll your window down. Get out of the way.
Yeah, I'll take
two double cheeseburgers.
Three McChickens.
Yep.
Two double cheeseburgers.
Three McChickens. Yep.
Can I have no sauce on the McChickens?
No sauce, please.
They don't...
You can't do that here?
I'm working that down on your exam.
Took me to a McDonald's without any fucking sauce.
You can't take it off?
No, that's okay. That's all right.
Can you...
Do you want anything?
And a small drink. A small...
One small Coke, please.
And that's it.
By the way, they rented my sauce.
They rented my szechuan sauce.
That's all going on your record here.
Yeah, pull around. Thank you.
Hey, howdy. How are you?
Yep, I'll take it. Can you put it over here?
I'm just doing a fucking acting class.
Every character
is mean.
Every character is mean.
Farming minus
twos.
What are you talking about?
I gotta end this one. I gotta end this bit.
So I'm gonna get out of the car.
All right, that's good.
Not a bad showing.
Let me get out of the car and take a look at the car.
Okay, let me see the car.
Turn around. Turn the car around.
Back it up. Good job.
Good job. Pull it back here.
Right here. Right in front of me.
Right there. Keep going.
Stop. Nice stop.
Nice, commanded stop.
Okay.
Well, you got an F.
And you're not gonna be getting your license.
But if you want to share some McDonald's,
I'm your guy. So we go ahead and do that.
End the scene. No one's gonna use that part.
Okay, what's next?
I can't
get hit by the car.
God damn it, I keep going this way.
Why do I keep going
that way? I just
keep going the way I can't go.
Hold on. Let me move this.
Okay, that's fine.
Playing musical chairs by yourself.
This one's fine.
That's a very quick one.
Should I put the mustache back on?
You know
what it is? It's when I put a mustache on,
I'm like a mean guy.
I think this is the excuse to be
kind of like a dick to everybody.
I don't know why.
Musical chairs with one person.
I got it. I got it.
I got it.
I got it. Thank you.
Alright, there was musical chairs
with no one. Doctor?
Am I in the same office?
Hey.
Let me tell you something. Let me tell you something.
Fuck face. I got a mustache on. I'm pissed.
This is a weird ASMR
video. This is an
ASMR video.
Okay, this is actually...
Those latex
gloves are terrifying.
I mean, give them to me. Why not? I guess.
Why would a doctor walk in
like this?
Okay, let's go ahead and start your checkup.
Like every other ASMR
video. How do you feel? How are you doing?
Oh my god.
Hello, patient.
This is an ASMR. I can't do this.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
How are you?
How are you feeling?
So it says here you have a little bit of a tummy ache.
Yeah. When did it start?
Last weekend. Okay.
Any bloating? Any gas?
Any flatulence that I
need to know? Okay.
How often are you
using the bathroom?
Me, me, me, me.
I fucking can't do this one.
I can't do this one. This one's too
weird. I can't do it.
This one's
fucked up.
I'll at least do this.
Ow! That hurts so
bad. Oh my
brain. Ow, my brain.
Okay, take
this. This is a real stethoscope.
Ow, my fucking head.
Okay.
Let me check and see how you're doing.
Very, very healthy sounding.
Very healthy.
Can you follow my
pen, please?
Very good, very good. Excellent, excellent.
Can you
stick both my fingers up your nose?
You said you had a runny nose?
I think you might have the cold.
Anything else bothering you today?
Okay.
A little fast.
Well, it's not the common cold.
I unfortunately have to diagnose you with
cringe. That's what you're suffering
from. Get a prescription for
it. The prescription is
at least four to six hours
of call of duty
every day. Make sure that
you're not as cringy as you are.
Take some of that cringe off.
And by the way, that is for Xbox 360.
No other console.
Not on PlayStation.
You can just take this whole thing.
Go ahead. Take the whole thing.
Ow, my fucking ears.
Somebody said what?
That I'm a slut?
Wait, I didn't hear you.
Somebody called you
a slut.
What?
All right, who's next? What's next?
Sleazy selling what?
There's that over there, too,
if you want to wear it.
It's kind of funny, actually, if somebody
used the doctor's stuff for
he's listening to his own penis.
Wait, like, is that
because
I feel like
there's going to be some combinations.
The best part about doing this stuff is
people are going, you know, people are saying,
dude, what the hell are we going to use this for, right?
But the creativity of the community
is just, it blows me away.
Because last time we said the same shit
and you guys combined
a bunch of things and made it into
the same video.
So I'm very excited to see what the hell you guys
can come up with, especially with the weird shit
that's happening today.
Okay.
All right, so walking around with a briefcase.
I think this is a fine outfit.
Oh, smash it.
Yeah.
Hold on, let me get rid of this chair.
There's a whole Spiderman costume
here now. All right.
We're doing sleazy like
stockbroker. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. I ain't going to be
doing that. You're going to sell that one.
Sell it. Yeah.
Who is going to buy that? Are you serious?
No, that company's going
under. There's no way they're going to have, no.
Their earnings are probably terrible. Sell it.
No, I think, honestly,
look, I'm going to work. I'm
on the way to work right now.
We can talk this later.
But I want you to buy
any company that makes,
makes, what the hell
are they called? I don't know. The kids, I'll
watch it. TikTok. Can you buy
TikTok? How do you buy that?
My son's into it. Big time. Yeah.
I mean, I think, I don't know how to buy it.
Is it possible? Not really?
All right.
Find me a company that is just
like TikTok then and buy that one then.
Go fuck yourself.
Why would somebody do that?
Wait, hold on.
There's a message. Hold on. Wait.
There's a special message from Mr.
Giraffe. I've got
to answer it. Hello?
Mr. Giraffe. Oh my goodness.
I'm so glad to hear from you. Did you
find that company? Yeah. Yeah. No, no.
I didn't mean to hang up on you that hard.
I didn't mean to hang up on one of your employees.
No, of course not.
Mr. Giraffe, I don't want
to buy Google stock.
I want to buy the TikTok company.
Okay.
All right. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine.
This is way too big for a briefcase.
This is a fucking
huge briefcase.
Who would have this?
This is fucking ridiculous.
Look at how huge this is.
What is even in this?
What is in this thing?
Well, I got mad. There it is.
All right. Let's do the mime stuff.
All right. We're going to do another costume change.
Do Saul Goodman?
I don't even know what to do.
What do you mean Saul Goodman?
He's Cinnabon.
Didn't I already do that?
Saul Goodman.
What's the line?
Guys, I haven't seen past season two
of Saul Goodman.
Just say Saul Goodman.
What is it?
In the...I'm in a Cinnabon
outfit.
I haven't seen past season two of Saul Goodman.
I don't know.
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
And do you know that you have rights?
Call me.
What is it again?
Oh, yeah. What is it?
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman. Do you know that you have
rights? The Constitution says you do.
And so do I. I've lived until proven guilty.
Every man, woman, and child in this country is innocent.
And that's why I fight for you, Albuquerque.
You better call Saul. Saul Goodman.
This is like a long thing.
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
And let me tell you something about Saul Goodman.
Did you know that you have rights?
And so do I, Albuquerque.
I'm here to fight for you
and to fight for your rights and fight for you
in a court of law. Give me a call.
Better call Saul.
Better call Saul Goodman.
Close enough. Print it. I'm not doing another take.
I'm an actor. And I'm a good one.
A good actor can take a script
and can change it and make it sound better
in front of the camera.
I'm an actor. Are you an actor?
Can you do this?
No, you can't. You can't do that.
Prove it to me if you could.
I'm an actor. Can you do this?
I'm an actor.
I act for a living.
You're embarrassing yourself.
Welcome to the last 12 years of my life.
Alright, what's next? Chef?
I feel like dad grilling burgers and chef
are going to be pretty similar.
Alright, how's that?
I need like a thing to
sit this on, like a table or something, right?
Or would I just be holding it in the air?
We could move one of those over.
What do you think? That could be like a
burner. I wonder if you could
clip that out.
Should I be back a little more?
I need two chops.
I need two chops. Two chops.
I need a little more.
Pass me the salt please.
Thank you.
Two chops coming up. Two chops.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Behind. Behind.
Yes, chef. Yep.
I'm looking for the pork chop. Yep.
Behind. Behind.
Can I use your burner?
I need to use your burner. I need to use your burner.
Thank you. No, it's not there. It's not there.
You didn't say behind.
Say it when you go buy somebody.
You just bumped me. I don't even know how much I put in.
All right. How much time? Very good. Very good.
So far so good. Yes, chef.
Yeah, I'm currently trying to make
sure that I have enough of the
seasoning on here. I'm also trying to make
sure that I have two. I'm looking for the
wontons. Where are the wontons?
Where are the wontons?
Chef, where are the
wontons? You closed the fridge
at the beginning of the tournament. Where are the
wontons? I need them for my wonton soup
thing that I'm doing. Where are the
wontons? Can I have? Okay.
You got kicked out of chef school.
I didn't. They got kicked out of chef school.
I didn't. Fuck them.
I know I can't say swears on TV. I know. I'm sorry.
I can't. I know I'm not supposed to say swears.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. I got it. I got it.
I got it. I got it. I got it. Yeah.
My risotto is going to be in the oven in just about
five minutes, chef.
I've got a creamy cheddar risotto and I
also have a creamy broccoli risotto
and I also have a creamy mushroom
risotto. And then
pork chops. Yes. I only
know how to make risotto besides that. I don't know.
This is done. All right.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Time.
Okay. Yep. Hi chefs.
What I made for you today is I have
a creamy mushroom risotto
and a side of creamy broccoli risotto
with a hint, a small
portion of a creamy chicken
risotto. And then on the side
of that I also have two pork chops
that I have created and I seared to perfection
and then finished off in the oven.
Yes, chef.
Yeah. Well, I mean,
ever since I was on my own, I
you know, started to cook
for myself ever since I was on my own.
And I learned how to make
mushroom risotto and yeah.
And that's what my mom
taught me, you know.
I call her every Sunday.
Yes, chef. Yes,
chef. Yeah. I understand.
It's not good.
What do you mean it's not good?
It's a perfect risotto.
It's perfect.
You like to talk like you know food, but you actually
really don't. You're just a mean
guy that got a bunch of TV shows.
You're just a mean guy that got a bunch
of TV shows and I'm not
going to stand for it. I'm not leaving.
No, I think I deserve to win.
It was a creamy mushroom risotto and you
don't have a fucking palate to save your
life, you fucking idiot.
It's so good.
It's so good. Whatever.
I don't care.
What do we do with this?
Okay.
One of me winning. Okay.
Yes, chef.
What I have for you there is I have two seared pork chops
with a side of creamy cranberry sauce.
And I know that you're
a big fan of chocolate, so
I added some chocolate flakes on top.
Yes.
I had a limited amount of time, so
I want to make sure that I got the pork chops out
when the shavings went on to the risotto.
And the cranberry.
Yes. Yes.
You've got it. You've got it. You've got it.
Yes. I did it.
I did it. Yes.
Thank you. Thank you so much, chef.
Seriously.
Thank you so much, chef.
When I get to the next round, you better believe
I'm going to cook my ass off.
Yeah. Thank you, chef.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm the fucking man.
What do you got? Nothing?
That's me. I won.
I'm going to the next round.
Something about that I didn't like.
Hold on a minute. Yes, chef.
Yes, chef.
I actually just had it before you did.
I just had some before you did.
I may have undercooked it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I think yours might be done
more than mine.
Mine was a little underdone.
Yours will be okay, though. Yes, chef.
Cowboy?
You should act as the chef.
The critiquing chef?
I don't even know how.
Fight a chef in the outfit.
Do the Wellington bit.
I don't have the outfit.
Ugh. Dodge an axe.
Let me see.
Please do the stop it thing.
We got time.
Don't do the Wellington thing.
I'm not doing the Wellington thing.
What do we got for the next costume?
I'm trying to stay in the same
clothing for a lot of them in a row
because obviously it's easier
to cut into.
There were so many requests
and so many different costumes that
I've seen so often.
Move this. So you want to draw?
You tell me when. Draw.
I must have lost.
Should have been more careful.
I've got one from this side.
I've got my eye on you. Be careful.
I've got one from up here. Let me tell you.
You be on your best behavior.
Why don't you give me a wink when you're ready to go?
Now!
I just shot myself.
Oh, panty for gold?
In this pan?
Fuck up this pan.
Should I wear the chef's hat for that too?
I've got like gold chunks.
Yes, chef. Oh, behind.
We'll get a new pan. Yes, chef.
Yeah, I'm currently cooking a
gold nugget.
You're probably wondering where the mustache came from and where the hat came from.
I change my
outfits sometimes.
Hear that sizzle?
That's a sizzle right there.
Why does the chef have a gun?
Okay, nod occasionally and go
Yeah, yep, yeah, yep.
Okay, well I want to do the
yeah, yep one.
Yeah. Yep.
Yes, sir. Yep.
Yep. Yeah.
Very interesting.
Yep. That's right.
Yes. Drink out of this thing.
I don't care.
It's full of flavor.
Yep.
What's this one?
Get out. Get away.
Get. Crash.
Get out. Get again. Get out.
Yeehaw.
Oh, you. You over there.
Throat.
Anybody else have something to say?
Didn't think so.
You missed one. Table.
Oh, okay. Write silent
in a notebook.
I'm taking the hat off of this.
This is the mustache guy.
I love how the notebook is Bugleberry's cauldron
book. Okay, so just write silently
in a notebook.
Read it. Pretend not to understand
and throw it. What is wrong with this guy?
This mustache shirt
guy has been doing a lot of
fucking weird shit.
That can't be right. This can't be
right. No, no, no, no.
I don't understand.
I'll do one more violent.
No, what is what?
I don't get it.
Any more for the guy with the mustache?
Is somebody going to do 23?
He's reading
the Bible.
Eat plastic toys
at a table?
I kind of did that one already. Hacking into the main
frame.
Oh, I did the keyboard already.
Oh, with the
keyboard, yeah.
Slowly stroke the mustache. I can do that.
Not that way.
Slams hands.
Tick-tock
dances.
What are these tick-tock dances?
It's like do tick-tock dances.
What are they? I don't know
any tick-tock dances, really.
I definitely want to get into Spider-Man soon
because I think that's fucking hilarious.
No, what is this?
The power of God
and anime on my side.
I mean, should I
just do it in this?
Yeah, I took the jeans off because
it's like 110 degrees.
I had that gray shirt
for continuity and the jeans
and I was like, I always wanted to puke. It was so hot.
Alright, so I have the power
of God and anime?
So you want me to just do that?
Like this?
A weapon?
So I dance around and move around and I go, I have the power
of God and anime on my side.
Who is this for?
I have the power of God
and anime on my side.
Scream?
I have the power of God and anime on my side.
Is that good enough?
I still have to do the accordion.
The mime outfit?
I'm just going to stay.
I'm just going to stay in this.
In the boat?
I feel like I should stay as the same guy
for a while. I learned this one.
All of you.
This water is so
dirty.
I learned this one when I was traveling
abroad, right?
Please clap.
Don't splash me.
Don't splash me. Throw him out. He splashed me
with water. Don't splash
me. Splashing. You can't splash here.
It says it on the sign before we walked in.
Don't splash people.
Don't splash.
Fucking idiot.
Don't splash you.
Throw him out. Throw him out.
Toss me there.
I'm getting away from him.
Those of you that want to hear another song,
follow me please.
This one's called
The Train Tracks.
No. This one's called
The Mandalorian Theme Song.
Give me that
pigeon.
This is a goddamn
children's toy.
What'd I get?
Oh.
That's a big one.
It's getting tangled.
I'll get one more out there. There we go.
There we go. That's a bite.
There it is. There we go.
That's
a big one right here. That's a huge one.
I'll take a picture of that.
Whoever's got a camera. You got one?
Take a picture of this one.
Cheese. I gave you the finger.
You can't use that anywhere now.
Can't put that on fucking Facebook or anything.
I'm here on vacation.
Shut up.
What's next?
Any more mean guy with the mustache?
You should walk on water.
Apology?
Oh, like an apology video.
Should I do an apology video
as the guy with the mustache on?
For all the things he's been doing?
Oh, in case I don't see you.
That's
some of my shit I've been doing.
The guy with the mustache
is just heinous.
And has to make a YouTube apology video for all
this stupid shit he's been...
Good afternoon. My name is...
My name was not in Borden, actually.
Good afternoon.
I just want to make this video really quickly
to say
I'm sorry for
the way that I've been acting while I was on vacation.
There's been various videos
around that have been surfacing out about my
time traveling.
And I just want to say
from the bottom of my heart, very sorry
for the way I've been acting.
Very sorry for the dumb things that I've been saying.
And a lot of people
have coined me the
mean mustache guy.
Mean mustache guy.
I gotta say, that hurts.
I don't think that's very fair.
I think everything I said was
I was very angry at certain things
and certain people has splashed a few people, but whatever.
I don't want to be that.
I'm not the angry mustache guy.
My name is
Sean.
That's what you can call me now.
Not angry mustache guy
that you see on YouTube.
Sean.
Anyways, I'm sorry for all
the things that I've been saying. The things I did.
Hopefully I can
get back to normal now.
I really just hope so.
I've been very, very
the last five or six days have been
a little interesting.
So I'm sorry.
What else do you want me to say? Do you want any more than that?
I'm very sorry.
I'm incredibly sorry. Do you want more than that?
That's all I'm going to give you.
But I do apologize.
So good night. Have a great rest of your evening.
And keep
keep going.
Whatever you're doing.
I'm going to go back to being a good person.
You just wait. Good person Sean
is what you'll call me. Not this.
I'm shaving this. Good person Sean
is coming up. It's me.
And the funny thing is immediately after that you could show
another TikTok UI video of me
being terrible.
Shaved Sean.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm shaved now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I hear. Shut up.
Shut up. Yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
Stupid. You're all stupid idiots.
You're dumb.
You're the dumbest one here.
Turn that off.
Turn that off. I'm shaved Sean.
I'm a different person now. Turn that camera up.
Hold on a minute.
Back up. Everybody back up. I'll prove it.
I'll prove to you that I'm a good person.
What's your name? I feel great.
Ever since it was...
I feel like a completely different person.
Your name? Dave?
I'm Sean. Shaved Sean.
From now on. Do you need help?
I could help you guys with anything you need.
I could help you move that furniture.
Shaved Sean here.
That's right. Yeah.
Much love to everybody here.
I was going to do a routine where I shaved my balls.
Never mind.
Fuck. Have we been doing this before?
Have we been doing this for four hours?
What? What the fuck?
I think we should end on this maybe.
Yeah. Let me get into that right now.
Yeah. We're going to do another costume change.
This is an important costume change.
I feel like this is going to be somebody's...
some of you guys' favorite of the night.
Another change. I'll be right back.
I can do this one real quick. Somebody said please do the Truman Show thing.
Alright.
I need the briefcase.
Howdy. Hey.
In case I don't see you. Good afternoon, good evening, and good night.
There you go.
You forgot good morning?
Oh, whatever.
This one...
Let me just show you what I'm changing.
Everyone that's like, oh, that must be the end.
No, it's not.
We got a lot to do with this guy.
Can anybody hear me?
How do I work this fucking thing?
Put it all again, Steve.
This is not my fucking video.
It's not like college dorm room.
It's just...
It's just that college dorm room video.
I want to...
Okay.
It's going to be that college video every time.
Whatever. Why would I have a tricycle this small?
Why wouldn't I get one for adults?
Get one for adults.
Not ones for children.
Adults can't ride these.
Hello again, Peter. It's me, Saul.
You're probably wondering why you're here.
What you're doing, locked up down here.
Well, I'll tell you.
Six weeks ago, you had
over 40 pornhub tabs open at the same time.
And you crashed your computer.
So now you have
40 computers with
40 different porn videos on them.
40 separate pornography videos.
You need to go and
close them all before the knock on the door
of your mother finds you.
You have one minute. Make your choice.
Oh, by the way, Peter,
forgot to mention. I know you only have 45
seconds left. The room
is about to fill with gas.
Nerve gas. Oh, I know
nerve gas very well. I said
nerve gas in SAW 1 through
5 over 200
times. You don't think I know?
It's a deadly nerve agent
and it will poison your
blood. Make your choice. You have 10
seconds. As the poison courses
through your veins, as the gas
fills your lungs.
Will you be able to succeed?
Oh, you did it. You did it.
Hey, Pete did it.
You actually did it.
Steve, what's your name again? I forget.
Good job. Go through the door.
Go out the door. You did it. Nice
job. You actually did it. Outside
of that door is another 50 computers
with 50 pornhub tabs open.
You must.
The hair is getting into my eyes.
No, I don't want them to know my identity.
Inside of this room, 10 bear traps on the ground.
You have three minutes to find
the key. Unlock the bear trap
that's around your head. Traps
everywhere. So when you step around, you have to be
very careful that you won't step in a bear trap.
You step in one of those, your leg will be
severed at the knee, John.
Also, the room is going to fill with gas.
At the same time, tons of
gas will fill the room. Gas!
And you'll die. Make your choice.
I'm not going to twerk his jigsaw, I'm kidding.
Any requests? Is the bowtie fucked up?
Oh, is it? A drug?
No!
No, dude!
Yeah, you want to fix it?
A drug? The drug?
A drug PSA? Oh my
god. Alright. Hello again.
It is I, Jigsaw, here to tell
you that you have a choice to me.
And it's time for you to me. We're talking about drugs.
How you should not do them. We all have a choice.
Hi, everybody. I'm the actor that plays Jigsaw.
Jeremy Albertson. I just want to make
sure that everyone's aware that if you
are approached with somebody offering
a drug or an alcohol, you can
refuse. There's no reason to do it.
So, if we could all have
our own Jigsaw's
puzzles to complete in our heads
to Western Pennsylvania
as the most patriotic.
I'm just like finding words.
I'm just
kind of like stuck. Hello again,
Internet. No. Hello again,
John. What you see before you
is a choice. A very important
choice. One that will live with you forever.
But you can make it. You might be able
to save yourself. I'm of course talking about
drugs and alcohol. Hi, everyone. My name
is Sean Albertson. I play the character
Jigsaw on the daytime TV
show. Jigsaw is coming
for you. I wanted to make sure I did
this quick little PSA that
we all have a choice
to make. And that's drugs and alcohol.
No reason to do them. Drugs are something
if you ever approached and pressured, make
your choice and say no. No to
drugs. Thank you. Now let's get back
to the show. There's a key
inside of your eyeball. You need to
dig it out with your bare hands and then eat it.
And then shit it out. When you shit it out,
then only then can you use the key
to unlock the bear trap that's around John's neck.
Wait, wait, wait. How did he get in here?
How did he get in here? How did he get in here?
You're not supposed to be able to get in here.
Ow. Ouch. No.
No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. You didn't make your
choice. Your choice is if he killed me.
Hi, everyone. My name is Sean Elberton.
I'm the actor, writer, director, producer,
and main talent of the daytime
television show Jigsaw is Here.
And I just have something very
important that we all have to do. We have to make choices.
And one choice is for you to watch this show
because the ratings have been very poor
and I believe that we are
below reruns of infomercials at this point.
So I figured we could give you a
quick little, like maybe you could watch the show if you want.
For the
six to seven hundred of you that do watch
the show, thank you so much.
It means a lot. The cast and crew,
we obviously put a lot of time into this show.
So we'll get back to it though. Let's get back to your regularly scheduled
programming of Jigsaw's Coming for You,
written and directed, starring, and produced by
me, Sean Elberton.
What is it?
He isn't pretending.
He's playing a
kid actor.
Do a family guy rag doll as
Jigsaw. Oh my god.
It's okay.
I'm going to be dead on the ground anyways.
Oh, yeah, they're having a hard time hearing you. Oh, it flipped.
That's why. Oh, it flipped. Can you mute it?
Oh, it should be. You know what? The batteries are dying.
Should we go with the other one?
I think I got another minute. I still want to do
Spider-Man. This is like too much
fun. Okay, here's the problem.
Like, I always come to these things
with so much shit.
And I just, like,
I have so many more things here.
Don't make it the last one.
It's
too fun. All right, we're going to do some speed runs.
We'll do speed runs. All right, all right, all right.
Here's the deal. I'm going to do
I'm going to get out of Jigsaw.
I can't believe I did that college video.
Okay, let me get into Spider-Man and we'll do some Spider-Man
stuff because I need
to be, we've got to be out of here in
two or three hours.
It's going to take about an hour or two to pack up.
So really only have like another 45
minutes to an hour. So let me
try to speed run some stuff.
We'll put on Spider-Man. I'll be right back.
Let's do this real quick.
Uh-uh. No strings.
Ta-da.
Hey. Where'd he go?
Where's the bunny?
Where'd the bunny go? I don't know.
Where's that rabbit? Uh-oh.
Jigsaw's
tricycle. You know what's really funny
about that though? We built that.
We put the tricycle together and I actually rode
it around my living room
for like 10 seconds and it was fine.
So of course it like blows up here.
You were, you rode it too and it was fine.
I think I put way too much
weight on it because I couldn't see.
Yeah, put that on a birthday card. I don't care.
Do, use it whatever you want.
Oh, let me see that.
What? How did I tie it in a knot?
I don't know. I tied it in a knot somehow.
What is going on?
How does this work?
Oh, I get it. Alright. I get it.
I get it. I get it. Okay.
I get it. It keeps bunching up.
It's bunching up. I don't know what to do.
Is this thing still on?
Can you hear me? How am I doing this wrong?
I don't understand how I'm doing this wrong.
I'm doing it wrong apparently. Is this a regular deck of cards?
Alright, what do you got?
There you go. Pick a card.
Pick a card. Any card. I don't want to see.
Pick a card. Pick a card.
This one? That one right there?
Pick that one. Gonna stick it back in the deck
right here. Check that out. Cut it.
Cut it again. Cut it again. Cut it again.
Cut it again. Cut it again.
What was it again? What was that card?
That one. Right there, wasn't it?
Bingo. Wanna pick another one?
Pick another card. Take another one. Which one do you want?
Anyone. Anyone. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Which one? Which one? This one right here? That one?
That one? This is your card? That's your card right there?
Let's get that back in the deck.
Tuck it in there. There it is.
Cut. Cut the deck. Cut the deck. Hold on now.
I'm working on it. Cut the deck again.
Cut the deck again. Spin that around.
Cut the deck again. Okay.
And guess what? I'll put it behind my gosh darn head.
See? I don't know.
I don't know where it is. I have no idea.
Not a clue. Not a clue.
Is that the card right there?
Oh.
It's a joker.
Bingo. Here's your card. Thank you.
You're right. Absolutely.
Let's do this now. Ready? Check this out.
Is that your card? Oh yeah, it makes it.
That's funny. Let's make the
chair disappear. Oh, I didn't even do any
lightsaber stuff. There's so much
lightsaber stuff from the other couple of times.
You guys can figure out what to do.
Watch. Watch. Watch.
It's gone.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. A rose.
Oh, I missed. What do I do with this?
I don't get it. What is this? What do you do with this?
You light it on fire?
This one's called, this next one's called sit down.
Sit down and stop talking during the show.
This next trick is called
fire rose.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Don't be alarmed. Don't be alarmed.
Don't get out of your seat. Thank you.
Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, what about this one? You want to see some real magic?
Boom. What's that in my hand? Look at that.
Catch it. There it is. It's really heavy.
Who in the audience can hold it? Golden
Sphere. There.
Who wants to see a dove? You ain't going to find magic like that
anywhere else. Sparks.
Who wants this?
Somebody wants the hello my baby,
hello my honey, hello my ragtime
gal? You mean like the
hello my baby, hello my honey.
I can't kick that high. I'm going to
rip my pants. My pants are going to rip
in half. This is actually a nice suit.
Hello my baby, hello.
No, I'm not going to do it. I can't do it.
One more time. Can I
dub over it? I'm going to dub.
Here you go. Here's the dub. Just take this audio
and you can use it. Hello my baby,
hello my honey, hello my ragtime
gal. Send me a kiss
my wife. Baby, my
heart's on fire. And if you refuse
me, baby, you'll lose me. And you'll be left
alone. And tell me, tell me
that I'm your man.
Okay, there you go. Just dub it.
He's going to tear his groin. Where's Spider-Man?
I know, I know. Spider-Man's coming.
Let me get this off. Alright, actual
clothing change. I'll be right back.
What do you want? Patrick Bateman?
Like, dressed like this?
Every single day I put on a
mask with apricots,
negros, shell stocks,
and bonds.
And I chase people who change their
lives.
Your microphone's over here.
Oops.
Sorry.
Oh well, just use that one. Who cares?
Alright, changing.
Alright, guys, we've got a problem.
We've got
a problem. Big problem.
I don't, I think
this costume,
I think it's two left hands.
Like, can you, hold on.
Am I crazy?
Right? I'm like, I'm crazy
or not, right?
This is too, my thumb, I can't
put the thumb over there. What the fuck?
Hold on, can I like,
hold on, hold on.
Hey guys, I'm telling you.
Oh my god, am I
a good Spider-Man? Let me fucking
tell you. I don't know, I can't, how am I going to
hook this thing, how am I, nobody's going to be able to hear, okay.
This is going to be with no audio.
I'm going to have to move around as Spider-Man with no audio.
I can't clip this thing to anything.
Can it, no way.
Alright, I'm going to,
there'll be a little bit of audio, I'm going to put the microphone
like over here. But excuse me.
Excuse me, fucking Peter Parker just showed up.
Peter Parker's here. Excuse me.
Peter Parker, thank you.
Peter Parker's here. Give me that fucking job.
Give me that role. Alright, let me,
I can't,
you guys are going to have to sit over here.
You're not going to be able to hear anything, but whatever.
This is just for Spider-Man anyways, so
whatever.
See you later, man.
Green Goblin! Gotcha!
You know, it's not a gotcha.
Drugs and alcohol.
Hi everyone, I'm Peter Parker.
A.K.A. Spider-Man.
Can you guys even hear?
No.
MJ, everyone knows I'm Spider-Man now.
What am I going to do? Don't you stand
like they've been thinking about my identity.
We're going to have to go underground, we're going to have to hide for a little while.
Listen to me, MJ.
We've got to hide for a while.
Everyone's going to know I'm Spider-Man.
MJ, come on, let's go.
All these people,
they know I'm Spider-Man.
MJ, tell them I'm a good guy.
What I was thinking is,
what if I, what if I put a different
costume on, a different suit,
and I wasn't Spider-Man?
What if I was a different character, and then everyone would know
that I was a different superhero?
Doesn't that fix everything?
Can't I just put on a different costume?
Well, I don't have to be Spider-Man.
I can be Mothboy.
No one's going to know I'm Spider-Man. There's so many weird
fucked up people in these universes that doesn't matter.
They'll just think,
we'll just say that Spider-Man got hit by a train
and it exploded
into blood and stuff.
I'm Mothboy.
Doesn't that fix everything?
Well, he already did that.
Mothboy.
But you're marketable.
You need to address the, I'm not addressing anything.
Yeah, hey, address this.
Nevermind. Did you hear the thing where I go,
oh, everybody goes like this, everybody goes like this in the movie.
Oh yeah, whatever, okay, everyone goes like this.
Edit that in. Alright, let me do some more spider moves.
I have to confront somebody. Who am I going to confront?
Jigsaw.
Hold on.
I'm just going to put you there.
Activate. I can see everything.
Activate laser sight.
You're not going to get away, Green Goblin.
Wait a minute. That's not Green Goblin.
Who's that new man?
Jigsaw. I just imagined Jigsaw flying around.
Wait a minute. Who's that?
That's not the Green Goblin.
That's someone else. Who's that?
A new villain.
You know what this is funny? This is implying that
Spider-Man had 40 Pornhub tabs open.
That's why Jigsaw
got him. I'm going to put the mask here.
I'm going to put the mask here
because Jigsaw got me
and he put my mask away
because everyone knows my identity.
Jigsaw took my mask off.
Because that ain't moving.
Is there a chair
I can put this on?
Give me the other mask too.
I don't know
where to put this.
Do I just hold it?
Maybe I could
set it here.
God.
Hold on.
I have to go this way.
Everybody don't look.
Nobody look.
Sitting down is like no fucking way.
Where am I? What's going on here?
Do you have an idea who you're dealing with?
I'm Spider-Man.
Well don't...
Usually I thought I cleared all that.
So what do I do? One minute?
One minute? Okay.
I got one minute on a clock. I can do this.
All these computers here?
Okay.
The clock is going on now.
Which one? Which one do I start with? First this one over here.
I'm going to hack into that.
I hacked it.
This one too. Got it. Got it. Got it.
There's only a few more.
Now that's thinking with webs.
I did what you wanted. I shut them all off.
What?
I did it? I won?
Okay.
I can't move the mask when I'm sitting down.
Don't you get it?
You look like an old man.
Hunching.
Hunching over.
That's so fucking stupid.
I love this
bizarre
fucked up shit.
Because everybody says there's no way it's going to get used
anywhere.
But it always does.
And somebody creatively uses this shit
and makes an insane video.
I can't fucking wait.
Twerk as Spider-Man?
It always works.
You guys are too creative.
Let me do some more stuff with Spider-Man.
Just like moving around and stuff.
When do I get to wear one of these?
When I stand up it's fine.
You don't need audio for this.
Can I see the lightsaber?
Those crazy Spider-Man Elsa videos.
You know what I mean?
Spider-Man with a lightsaber is like
coming around while he eats my hamburger buns.
This new technology
that Tony Stark made for me
sure is cool.
I'm here representing the Avengers.
Oh, you gotta get me doing that.
Bang! Bang!
This new technology that Tony Stark made
sure is interesting.
I wonder what I would call this.
An electric sword.
Who needs webs?
Start to cry?
It looks like you shit your pants.
Jeremy, you're gonna drop dead.
I'm alright.
I'm kind of at the end here.
Oh, do a superhero landing, yep.
Am I late?
Sorry I kept you all waiting.
You gotta cut out me laughing too.
It's too stupid.
Can I wrap this around?
I have a solution.
Where's the other hood?
It's time to fight some crime.
I need some adjustments to my suit.
I feel like it's a little more appropriate.
Let's go!
I hope this is okay.
He deserved it.
Why did it explode?
It fell four or five inches.
No, I'm taller than that.
Alright, I think it's like
I don't even know where this came from.
Whatever, it's fine.
Alright, what else can I do
in the next ten minutes?
Baseball Spider-Man?
Oh, I kind of did with the car thing.
This is so fun.
I'm so happy to do this again.
It really is so fucking fun.
What do you guys think?
Out of all the three times that I've done this
do you think you got enough to do some stuff?
Another ten minutes of stuff?
Because remember, you can use all footage
from every single time.
It's not just this one.
What other separate streams you can pull from now?
Do Patrick Bateman?
Do some more dancing.
You need to do more Star Wars.
Virtual ASMR murder.
I already did that though.
Alright, let me get a few more things out of the way.
What are some more things?
Honestly, you know what I'm looking forward to more than anything?
All the Super Mario shit.
Honest to God, I feel like the Mario stuff
combined with a few other things
could be gold.
I'm just telling you.
Yeah, there's a lot of other stuff to do.
I think we've got probably half the list.
Maybe a little bit less than half.
There were, what, six or seven
hundred suggestions.
This has taken down to like two hundred.
We did probably like fifty in five hours.
Do a bong rip?
I'll do a bong rip. Do the walk?
I'll do the walk with Spider-Man.
Oh, the pointing meme, right?
I'll do the pointing meme.
I'll do the walk.
I want to do a couple more things with Spider-Man.
I'll do some Spider-Man stuff.
Alright, you're not going to be able to hear me very well,
but I'm going over here.
He's going to puke?
No, I don't want to do it right into that.
It matches.
I don't know why I'm Spider-Man while I do that, but it's fine.
The hair. Do a bong rip?
Alright, fine. Here's your bong rip.
Do we have a bong? Yeah, I'll just pretend it's this.
You know, hold this.
So bad. You fucking...
He doesn't have to do the drug PSA.
Oh, the drug PSA.
Okay, what's the Miku dance?
The act out?
The death from the Thanos snap?
Oh.
That's sad though.
What does he do? Alright, I'll do it for you.
He's like lying down and he goes...
He just says, I don't feel so good.
He goes...
I don't know.
Mr. Stark,
I don't feel so good.
I'm still here.
Whoa.
Well, I'm still here.
Mr. Stark, I'm still here.
No, no.
Mr. Stark, what? Mr. Stark, what is this thing?
Mr. Stark, what's this little thing, Mr. Stark?
Why am I holding this, Mr. Stark?
Let me see what this is. I can't even shout the company out because
it's not focused.
Here, can you see?
This is Road Wireless Goes.
These things are fucking awesome.
These things saved the stream, by the way.
This is not sponsored.
I literally bought these
about, like, hours ago. These things are fucking awesome.
They're so little.
They can do anything.
Alright, one more thing and I'm going to clean up.
Road. It's the Road Wireless Microphones.
They're fucking awesome.
You get two.
It's been five hours, six hours. These things are still going.
This one's still going.
R-O-D-E. You can plug other shit into here, too.
Yeah, it's still...
Alright, guys.
We got to clean up. We have a hard exit here.
There's a hard stop here
in the next 40 minutes and we got to clean up.
We got through a lot.
There was a lot of shit to go through today.
So, the next time I stream
I will give you some really clear rules
because I can't really give them to you now
because we got to clean up.
Are you going to do a day two? Probably not.
Not soon.
I feel like there's a lot of
supplemental weird shit.
Yes, you're going to be able to use all three of the streams
and on top of that, you're also...
In the Discord
it will put some rules out.
We're going to have to be...
Let me just say this.
We're going to have to be insanely selective this time
because there's no way we're going to be able to get through the videos
that people are going to submit.
So, there's going to be... I really hate to say this
but there's going to be a really heavy, heavy
content quality filter.
Otherwise, it would just be dozens
and dozens and dozens of hours of videos
that we would never get through, ever.
So, we're going to have a pretty strict quality bar
that
is going to have to get met.
But that doesn't mean that funny, jokey, short
meme stuff won't get through.
It's just that we're going to have to make a lot of hard decisions on
what can actually show on stream.
Because even if I do an encore night, if we do a four to hour,
five hour, six hour stream
and do another six, seven hour stream
encore for these videos
we probably wouldn't even get through a tenth of them.
So, I've got to try to get
at least a quality bar
that's going to have to get passed.
And it will be in a playlist. The playlist will be available
a few times we've done it.
But yeah, I hope you guys had fun. I did.
I'm very tired though.
I forget how fun it is just to kind of be a
wacko and do all this.
So, hope it was entertaining.
I hope you can get some footage out of this
and combine it with the other two streams.
We'll see. Thank you so much for watching.
I'll see you guys later. The next stream will be
what's today? Today is the 30th.
Okay, so
maybe I'll be back on Sunday. Sunday the 3rd.
Oh, we're going to play Cuphead. Cuphead's DLC
Well, that's what I'm doing next. I'm going to stream Cuphead.
We're going to beat the DLC. Maybe in one day
I'll do two or three days, however long it takes.
Cuphead DLC coming soon.
I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching.
Also, thanks to Holly. Holly, doing this by myself
the last few years was fucking unbelievably
hard. So, yeah. She did
a lot of help here. Just helping with props
and costumes and compiling stuff.
So, that was a big help. So, it was a lot of fun.
Thanks everyone.
I'll see you guys on
Sunday. Good night.
Goodbye. Take care, guys.
Call your mother. You know the deal.
See you later.