I'm getting my ass kicked. This guy's beating the shit out of me.
How you gonna learn if you keep getting hit in the head all the time?
Dude, this is what happens when you drink like a shitload of vodka and you get in a fight with somebody.
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you. See this hand up here? You see this hand? Yeah, you just got clubbed.
You just got fucking clubbed by this shit-faced vodka salesman. You wanna fucking go?
You like this one? You like this technique? You like this technique? You like this one?
You know what I got for you? You like this? What do you got? You wanna go fucking with me?
What's that? Tell your mother. Tell your father. You ain't got nothing on me.
You motherfucker. I'll take you down. One more punch. Up a cut.
What the fuck? Go down. Will this guy seriously go down? Look at his health. This is bullshit. This is bullshit.
Look at this guy's health. Will you seriously go down?
I got one for you. I've got a punch for you right here.
You wanna go? I've got you.
Fuck you. I just took your ass out.
Keep your damn feet in place. You'll break the game if you keep running around.
Any other body part you wanna move is okay. But not your feet. Not unless I tell you. You got that?
It's all about the blocking. You gotta stay true.
Give him a couple of gut punches. Here we go. Looking good. Looking good.
I didn't do any damage to him right there. What the fuck was that? What the fuck was that?
No, really? What? Why did he just do the shimmy in front of me? Is that his taunt?
How am I supposed to beat this guy? This is the second round. I'm like trying to move.
I guess I can like duck around a little bit but it doesn't matter.
I gotta think of some like secret technique. I gotta do something about this.
Here we go. Give him the wrist punch. He can't handle it. He can't take it.
This guy's having a lot of trouble with my like pat on the back you did a good job at graduation son move.
He can't do it. He can't handle it. Yeah, he can. No, no. It actually might be working a little bit.
Then I gotta change this into something else. Here we go. We're gonna change this into a punch in the face.
Like that. Damn it, it didn't work. Get over here. I gotta rethink my strategy.
I gotta rethink my strategy. We're going double punches. I'm gonna go two haymakers in his face.
God damn it. Can I please just fucking hit this guy?
And if you crouch down, you get a good angle for hitting the body.
Hey, you want some free hits? Come on. Is that all you got? You piece of shit. Is that all you got? I'm the man.
Do you know who I am? Look at me flex. Yeah. That's working.
We're doing good. We just gotta keep this going. Just pretend like you're in a marching band.
Go forward and back. I'm not even gonna attempt to do anything else. I'm gonna just do this.
I'm just gonna like wash his face. What a terrible fight.
Imagine if you were some of these guys that came here and paid for this fight and you saw this dumbass.
You'd be very disappointed. In fact, I would expect for this guy to get like beat up in the parking lot after this.
You maybe paid 20 bucks. I bet 20 bucks on you and you did like the dancing marching band move. You're a fucking idiot.
You know what? We gotta do some more. There we go. Right in the chin. Gotta get him right in his chin.
I gotta swing that up right in his chin. Quick ones. Quick ones. Quick ones.
Just fucking hammer his head. God damn it.
You don't fuck this. Now I'm fucking pissed off. You thought you were gonna fucking beat me in this fucking game?
Now you got me fucking angry. Because I've been trying to fight this same fucking guy for the last like 10 straight minutes
and I cannot beat him and I'm fucking gonna win no matter what.
I'm gonna fucking die. No. Don't lose. I don't want to do this again. Use all your power. Use everything.
No.
If you mess up, get back in the guard post and press the circle button. Quick.
I'm gonna give him the ear punches. This is actually working. This is working.
This shit's gonna work. Come here. Just pretend like you're dragging a brick across his face. That's all you gotta do.
Just strangle him with the piano wire. Take him out Hitman style. I'll fucking strangle you.
What the fuck am I doing dude? What?