Hey, what is going on everybody? Jirva here with Scare Saturdays.
I know it's been quite a long time since you've seen a Scare Saturdays. It's been at least,
god I don't know, maybe three or four weeks since I've done a real Scare Saturdays video.
And if you didn't notice, I'm not in my typical place right now. This is a hotel room.
And if you saw my last video, I'm currently not in North Carolina. I'm in Virginia right now.
It is my sister's 30th birthday party. I was actually, I was gonna get her up here
to like get in front of the camera, but she was like, no. So that's not happening.
So let's just get right into this here. I'm gonna play Grey, which is a Half-Life 2 Episode 2 mod.
And let's get started. I heard really, really good things about this game. Heard it is terrifying.
And also, before we really get started, this is not my typical setup. I'm using my laptop's webcam
and this $10 microphone that I got at Staples like an hour ago. So if the audio quality and
the video quality is not what you're used to, then I do apologize for that. But it's what I'm
working with. It's all I got right now. So let's just start a new game. Are you sure you want to
start a new game? Uh, yeah. Let's start it. Pickle tea. I can't even pick hard, so normal.
All right, let's go. Door open. Hi, door. What the hell is that? What the hell is going on?
I hear noises. Oh, what on earth? What is this? Like a head shrinker? What's going on here?
Can I open this? I don't think I can open that. Oh, my God. That guy's got a knife. That guy's
got a knife, man. Oh, my God. This is, I don't even want to go down this hallway.
This guy's just got a knife. He's going to tell you. I guess we go in here. Am I falling down?
Do I have a flashlight? No. What the hell? What have you done? I don't know. What have you done?
You're running around like a freak. Reminds me of Nightmare House. It's the girl running in front
of you, scaring the absolute crap out of you. Can I close the door, please? Blood all over the walls,
which is never a good thing. Hey! Am I? Do I have the same hair color? Do I have the same
facial features? Wow. This is very, very morbid. This is terrifying, guys. The atmosphere of this
game is really just absolutely terrifying. Whoa. This is some art deco going on here.
What is that? What is that thing? What on earth is this? If this thing touches me, do I get hurt?
Oh my god. I feel like I'm in a haunted house. Get me the hell away from these things. Do I get
like a weapon eventually or something? I hope so. And we're going down the checkerboard hallway,
where it looks like it's going to be forever. X. Touch that. Oh, I already knew what I had to do.
I already knew what I had to do right there. That's how much of a pro I am.
What is it? Are there more X's that I have to hit? I guess so. There's plenty of them. Let's push
them all, baby. Okay. That's all of them, right? I think so. I think so. Oh, no. No, we missed one.
We missed one. I just heard the unlock sound. There we go. God. This is just, this is just awful.
Like just disgusting and ridiculous. I'd hate to be that guy. Oh,
this is the creepiest game I've ever played. Oh, oh my god. Holy god. That was my whole brain.
You know, when like your brain, when things just like snap and you feel like you just got hit by
a car, but you're sitting in a desk and you're fine. That's, I just feel like I got hit by a car.
Wow. All right. Now where the hell are we? All right. So I'm dating that girl
and she doesn't like me anymore. I don't think that's the right character.
I feel like something's gonna jump in my face right now. Oh, is this just,
oh, okay. So I am this guy. All right. Let's go, man. Toilet. Gotta take a dump. Hold on.
Excuse me. I don't want anyone to look at me while I'm taking a dump. Can we please
close the stall door, please? Let's go. What the, what the hell?
How come I have hands now? I didn't have hands before. Make sure I'm not missing anything here.
I'm, I've been known to just miss things. Okay. This is cut scene.
Currently in some weird room. My face is pulsing. Whatever. Where is everyone? Did they close up?
Voice acting. Pretty cool. Hold tab periodically to see your current objective.
Figure out where everyone is. That's pretty vague. What should I do? I wonder where everybody is.
Find everybody. That's malarkey. Oh, swear word. Swear word. Cut it off.
Maybe I'll find something useful in the tool shop down the alley.
Really? You could have told me I could have needed that. Can I like just call somebody on the phone?
I'm going to call somebody on the phone. Let me get, let me get some help from burger boy here.
Burger boy? Yeah, it's Jerma. How the hell do I get out of here? All right. Where is it?
Did I like walk by it? Oh, wait, wait, wait. Is that like a saw? Can I pick up the saw?
Can I pick up the saw? No, I can't pick up the saw. Of course I can.
They're both. What am I supposed to do here? This is like, this is the tool shed, isn't it?
I see a saw right here. I should be able to pick that up and like throw it at somebody.
All right. No map. Don't know where the hell I'm going, but you know, we're going to get there
eventually. What happened to this door? All right. This looks like it's a repair shop. I see a car.
Or did I just come out the same way I went in? Oh, I totally did. All right. Hey, you learn
something every day. Where, where has my little. Oh, there we go. What does that say? Tool shop.
Yes, I will open that door. Yes, I will. I'm looking for some tools. If you got any tools,
I'll take them. I'll take one of the monies in the register too. Ooh, found it. Excellent.
Excellent. A bolt cutter. Let's go open that door. Let's go open that freaking door. Hold on. Let
me take a drink of my delicious water. Let me take a sip of my delicious water. Let's go.
It was this way. I think I remember. I think it was this way. I've been wrong before and I
am totally wrong. I wish there was a sprint. I'm kind of just like, I'm going to meet my maker.
Let's go meet the maker. We're going to meet the maker. I'm going back the way I came.
Meet your maker. Meet your maker. Burger Boy's Baker. Meet your maker. Meet your maker.
Meet your maker. Where is Burger Boy's Baker. All right. That's enough of that. I keep on going in
like the same. I'm literally going back and forth in the same directions. I need to like pay attention
to the game. Too busy making like a song about Burger Boy. Can I go in here? Nope, I can't.
That's this is the way. This is the way. No, this is the way over here.
Yeah, right. Yeah, right. This is the way, right? I'm so confused. Yes. Excellent. Excellent. Let's
go. Cutscene. Tip. Don't forget some useful gray key bindings such as mouse two for iron sights.
There's iron sights in this game? H to open memos and tap for eject. Okay. So apparently this is
like Call of Duty Half-Life 2 mod episode horror Modern Warfare Black Ops 4. Let's go. Oh, frame
rate. Oh my God. I'm getting a bad frame rate here. I'm getting like eight frames a second.
Here we go. What you got for me in here? What you got for me in here? Why can I not pick this up?
I think this flashlight has batteries. Does it have batteries? Yeah, it does. All right.
Let's kick this off here. Let's go. Oh, we love this. It's jammed. There's an arrow pointing that
way. So I'm going to go this way. Don't know what that is, but I just picked it up. What about in
here? Ooh, back outside. Every single door is locked and now I'm at a dead end. Where am I supposed
to put it? What can I turn on the AC? It's getting hot in here. Kind of is getting hot in here in real
life. Oh, okay. Through block 12. Sounds easy enough. Okay. Through block 12. I'm going to push
all this stuff over. Why am I stuck in here? Oh, through block 12. I have no idea where I'm supposed
to go. Block 12. It could be any of these jammed up doors. Is it like a trap door? No. Actually,
kind of is. This door I dropped. Well, definitely not in the storage room. I don't know. I just
don't know, guys. What the hell is that? This guy's going to turn around. He's going to run at me.
He didn't run at me. That makes me happy. He's probably going to be behind me now and I'm going
to be scared and I'm going to freak out because he's going to be right behind me. Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I thought these things were bad guys, were like scary ghosts,
but they're just pillars in the ground. Oh man. Fine with me. Every door is locked. Don't expect
to. That thing had long arms. That was like a slender man. Woman. Oh damn it. God. That's
supposed to be my mother. This is horrible. Hey mom, sorry I was late for school that one time.
Don't like rip out my eyeballs and feed them to me. Where was I going this way? Where like mommy
went? I heard something. I hate these little enclosed person. It is a person. This is where
it starts to get really messed up. Oh damn it. I hate when it gets like this. He's going to like
stand up and pee on me. Okay. There's a key. Let me go. Come on. Let's go. Give me the key and give
me his label for the back exit. I've got to hurry. How'd that guy die? Anyways, can I like, no, I
can't go over there. Oh, this way. Oh, I don't want to see this. I don't want to see this thing
again. It's like slender woman. Turn my flashlight back on. All right. Sick radio. I don't care about
your dumb radio. Let's take a bath. Wash away the hatred I have. Anything in the fridge? Any like
burgers? I'm just, I'm delaying right now. I'm stalling because I don't want to see that thing
again. Can I go this way? Yeah, there's nothing in here. Nothing in here. The stairs. I don't
remember going up the stairs, so I'll go down them. That's fine with me. Any hidden stuff? No.
There's the key. Cutscene. Batteries increase your flashlight's field of view while also reducing
its chance to flicker temporarily. Good to know. Good to know. All right. Let's end episode one
right here. Phil, I've been playing for a little while now. I can try and get this out into one
episode. Thank you guys so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And if you, did you hear
that? If you want to see more Gray, let me know. If you guys want to leave a like on the video or
a comment or something, just let me know if you want to see more of this because I heard it gets,
it can get pretty difficult later on. So if you just want to see the intro, which is the
thing that in the very beginning, which is really screwed up if you ask me, yeah, just let me know
and I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care everybody.