Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Nightmare House 2 Chapter 4. I probably should not be doing that because I need like the bullets to shoot people.
But this is Chapter 4, Operation I think is the name of this particular chapter.
You're probably going to see Nightmare House 2 Chapter 5, 6, and I believe 7. I think there's only 7 chapters.
You're going to see those more often than only Saturday now. I want to try and get through this series a little quicker so I can do more scary games on Saturdays.
So expect more Nightmare House 2 soon. But in the meantime, let's go.
Now I remember from last episode, there's a guy right here. No he's not.
What? Where is this guy? I swear to God, he was right there last time. Where is he? Where's my light?
That guy was right here. Yeah, okay, great. Glitching out of the side of the wall there.
Alright, where the hell am I going? What's going here? It's locked. Looks like there's only one way to go.
Hello? Elevator? No, don't work. Straight through here. No, just walk. No, no, this blue area thing. What's going on? What is happening right now?
I'm like breathing in gas. Get me out of here. Oh my God, please tell me there's an exit. There is.
Do I have like a gas mask or something? I don't think I do. Geez. Breathing in like somebody farted in that hallway. Oh, that was immature.
Maybe I can drink the Drano and get immune to it. Nothing even in here. Is this? No, this is like looks... Can I turn this off or something?
This looks like where it's originating from. Maybe. Just don't know. What if I shoot it a bunch of times? That's not going to do anything now, is it?
Okay, I have to go back out into like the gas room. Why am I stuck? Get out of my face.
About what? What? Oh my God. What a troll. Since when does this lady decide she can do that to me?
I thought she was like an automated hospital thing.
Okay, yeah.
I'm not contacting the main desk. I'm breaking into somebody's room and stealing their bed pan. I need to recharge the flashlight.
Somebody's bed is gone. I don't know why, but there's nothing in here. Let's keep going.
This one? Anything in here? Oh, wow. This was a failed operation. If I do say so myself. Bullets, that's a good thing.
Hey, how are you, doctor? You are taking way too many hits than you should. Just go down. Only one place to go. Are you serious?
What? My God. Oh, it's all about tapping the... I'm out of bullets. I can't even... I'm out of bullets right now. I just said, I'm out of bullets.
Are you telling me I'm out of bullets right now? This is great. I only have three shots in this thing. Great. Fantastic.
That was a bad idea. You know what? When I shot those bullets in the very beginning, that was a huge mistake.
Because it's going to be like a mini boss. I'm going to have to kill him. It's going to take two or three bullets that I don't have.
Can this elevator work yet? Where the hell am I supposed to go? Yeah, I knew that was going to happen. I already knew that was going to happen.
You fooled me once. Shame on you. Fooled me twice. Shame on you again. Because you shouldn't be being mean to people like that.
And what's in that vent? Definitely have to go in that vent, but I'm not going to do it yet. I want to go down here first. Yep, it's locked. I could have guessed.
Vent time. And we all know how much I love going into vents. I love it. It's my favorite thing in the world.
Here we go. Vent time. If I can even get in there. Jump in there. Can I pick up one of these stacks of beds?
You, bed. Go over there. Get up. Will you just fall over there? Oh wait, there's a chair. I can do this. That's much easier.
Alright, here we go. Get the gun out. Because this chicken bone is going to attack me.
I hate vents. Can I open this? Nope. Even my character is going...
God! Is he dead? What's he doing? We're like having a tea party. Oh, my whole face hurts from that.
Let's go. Am I going to drop down here? Not. Should I? What was that? There were just two dudes right there.
Should I keep going or should I drop down? I don't know. But I'm going to go this way just because...
What the hell is going on? What just hit me? What is going on? Am I stuck in here now? Where am I?
What is happening? Why am I sandwiched in here now? Am I here for eternity? I think I'm locked in here forever.
No, I'm not. I'm just an idiot. So I do have to go down here. Okay. Let's go. Come on. Break it.
You might be a fat guy. You can break through this, can't you? So what am I supposed to do? Go back? I can't even go back.
What is happening right now? It's like a maze. Do I put my hands on this to put my name on there?
Okay, so now it really is just messing with me. I thought for a second that things were wrong and they were.
No, back down in here, I assume, the place where I can't see anything. Isn't this where all the walls were closing in on me?
What's going on? Oh, my God. It's so dark in here. I have no idea what's going on. Please get me out of here.
I can't even. I can't. I bet you you guys can't. Hi. All right. Good. Friends.
Okay. So I'm a patient of this hospital. At least I got like a crew now.
Before it was just me and some dumb doctor that didn't do anything. These guys are like SWAT team.
All right. Don't worry, bro. Let's go. Let's do it. Let's take out some zombies. Four guys. Oh, this is a squad.
Let's all go, buddies. You're all my friends. Look at all my friends, all my friends.
We're going to have so much fun. We are a squad of friends. At least I feel safer now. Did you hear that?
I didn't. It's a flare, though. I'm putting it down. Oh, hang on to that flare. Okay.
Good thing you told me that before I activated it. You guys shoot. You shoot. I don't want to use my bullets.
Yeah. See, I don't have to do anything. I don't. I can hold my fire. These guys can do it all for me.
What? What? What do you mean incoming? Oh, you guys have assault rifles. Why? Why are you so concerned?
Yeah, I'll light the way. I'm not even going to shoot one time. Oh, fine. I'll shoot. You know what? No, screw that.
Oh, these guys. These guys are bad shots. You guys have like automatic shotguns and assault rifles.
Maybe I should be shooting because they die. Oh, I think they are. One of them is down. Oh, crap.
That's not good. All right. I wait. Oh, that was a zombie. Or was it? I'm confused. Let's go this way. I think.
No, it's over here. Bullets, bullets, bullets, but flares everywhere. Yeah. Hey, check out my new fireworks.
Sick. Oh, my like frames per second are going down like crazy. My screen is like a lagging like nuts.
Which way are we going? This way? No, we're going this way. What the hell was that? It was like a spider.
Are we going after the spider queen? No, apparently not. We're going through this door. Get out of here.
That was a pretty, if I do say so myself, that was a pretty good reflex headshot. That was pretty sick.
No, take that out. I want my regular gun, but I don't want to shoot any bullets because I don't want to waste them.
Nice job, Jerry. It is all quiet. OK, I got to name these guys. Jerry, Steve, Rick and Dugan. Let's go.
Hey, watch out, Dugan. I'm definitely going to forget those names and call them to completely different things later.
I knew that. I knew I knew I wasn't going to get to that door. I knew it. His name was Dugan. All right.
Let me look around. It's an empty open room. Oh, what's up there? Grab his gun. Oh, yeah. That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, it's these things. Finally, I get to see them. These little freaks. Oh, what are these things?
God, these things are wicked freaky. What is this? I'm running out of ammo with this.
Probably shouldn't be just spraying all over the place. But you know what? You only live once.
I'm right. I don't know. Don't use those bullets. Just attack. Where am I? Oh, it's this stupid zombie.
Shoot him. Shoot this guy. What a way to just burn through bullets. Who did I lose? Did I lose Rick? What's going on?
What's going on? Oh, my God. There's so many. Where did he go?
Well, yeah, you go ahead. Run out of the room and leave me here for dead. Thanks a lot, guys. Oh, there's only one of you.
Hey, find a way to meet us, even though it's only one of you. I got the rest of you killed because I'm an idiot.
I'm running around swinging an axe. Let's go down here. I guess I think where am I?
Down below the depths of hell. Chapter five. OK. Well, that was pretty intense.
A little gunfight there at the end. Thank you guys so much for watching. Really do appreciate it.
And like I said, chapter five is going to be probably in the next couple of days.
I want to get through this playthrough sooner than every week. You'll see another episode soon.
So, yeah, hopefully there's no jump scare right here in the very beginning. Oh, there is probably.
But yeah, I'll see you guys all soon. And of course, take care, everybody.
Oh, it's hot out. I got to get like some breeze from the fan.