Okay, I work out today.
Working out today. How's everybody doing? Good afternoon. I'm running around.
Maybe, maybe ran a little too much.
Up and down the stairs. I noticed what time it was. Oh, oh my god. I'm pressing buttons.
I noticed what time it was about
Maybe six or seven minutes ago, and I was kind of not ready. So I just had to freak out and I ran around the house.
I gotta get coffee. I've got to have something to eat. I've got a pee.
Sometimes you gotta do the other one. Sometimes, not every day, maybe like a few times a week.
Maybe like once or twice a week. Give me some break. Give me a slack here.
He's very, very constipated.
He cares about his life more than he cares about us. He hates us.
He hates us.
This guy had to go to the bathroom. He hates us. Once a week exclusivity.
You know, that's a good point. Do you guys have
I care. I care. True. He does. No, I don't.
No, no, I can't. No, no, no. No, no, no, no. Like I hold on. Wait a second.
I'm saying he hates this thing, I don't.
I was referring to he hates us. No, I don't. I just read that, and then I read the accidental next one, which is
He cares, and then I said no, I don't. Don't worry. Don't worry.
It was a fucked up slip, whatever they call them.
He cares. No, I don't.
What will this person say?
Last time I was this early to a Jerma stream,
I wasn't under audit for evading federal taxes.
Keep it up, Jerma.
Hey, well, hey, your taxes.
What are you doing?
We're gonna, today we're gonna just chill.
Been kind of in a chill mood recently.
We're gonna, I got a lot of back when we played flash games.
Tons of people said, dude, you gotta get on Nitro.
I was like, you know what, yeah, I'll check it out.
So we're gonna chill for a little while.
This is not gonna be a long stream.
I have some work to do later
and I have some things to do later.
I've got a very busy, very busy day, very busy weekend,
very busy everything from here going forward.
Lots of stuff has to be ready for the 31st
and among other things.
So what are you gonna play?
I don't know, I guess what's a good one on Nitro?
Work in a hundred quotes.
Well, I'll just tell you what the work is.
I'm gonna start making Rumble characters.
That's the plan over the next few days
and next week or so.
So, I mean, you could put that into like super quotes,
but there's gonna be a lot of holiday things
that I'll be doing.
So I have to, I gotta get a lot of stuff done.
I've been putting it off and I'm like, I gotta go, let's go.
By the way, if you haven't done it already,
in the Discord right now,
somebody just called me a fart streamer for three dollars.
I'm not supposed to read those,
but it just popped up on the side of my face.
What was I saying?
I don't even remember what I was saying.
What was I just saying?
Discord, right, okay.
So the nominations for the end of the year awards
and the discussions for those things
are currently happening right now.
You've got about another probably two or three days,
maybe three days or so before that's done
and we start to compile the nominations
and I give you guys something to vote on
for a week and a half.
So if you got nominations for any of those categories,
make sure you go talk about it,
make sure you go nominate them
because after this weekend, gonna be closed.
Ah-ee-oo, what's the mystery game?
We've got a lot of mystery games as you can see.
I'm on the website right now.
I don't even have that recorded still, it's gone.
This is available on Switch, PS4, Steam and mobile.
What?
HTML5 games are now here.
Oh, that's good.
So I don't know anything about this website.
What's a good one?
People were like, get on Nitrobe, get on Nitrobe.
You gotta play this, you gotta play that.
Just top games, top games.
Be Ice Cream, Be Ice Cream 3.
Okay, Ice Cream apparently is very, very popular.
Why are these so popular?
This is the most popular game ever.
Should I play this one?
I'm gonna play the original Be Ice Cream
because this is the top game on the whole website, right?
I got it.
This is the worst game.
How is the worst game the top game?
Because it is.
Wait, Flash should be on.
I turned it on before the stream.
What the fuck?
What about Be Ice Cream 2?
Please wait, this stays for more than 10 seconds.
You don't have Flash installed.
Where's the little puzzle piece?
Just click it.
I am, click this.
This is gonna take me to get adobeflashplayer.com.
I'm not doing that.
Play a different one, okay.
Not, it says not secure up here.
Just click it.
What, I don't know what's gonna happen.
Oh, okay.
That's, wait, Be Ice Cream 1.
Here we go.
Credit card info.
I don't know, man, I gotta be careful.
I don't wanna click random shit anymore.
That's how you get in trouble.
Okay, this is Be Ice Cream.
Can I zoom in?
Is that, is this good?
You can give me your credit card info.
What do I do?
Is this Be Ice Cream?
Is there any sounds?
Everyone doesn't know that Nitroam's co-developing
a Shovel Knight game.
That's pretty awesome.
What is this stupid shit?
It's a, I don't know, it's a screen saver.
It has to load it.
It's loading the game.
It has to load it, hold on.
What is this shit?
It's a, just relax.
Refresh the page.
All right, I'm gonna refresh the page.
Here it comes.
Hello, buddy, um, hello?
What?
Stupid flash shit again, Omega Lo.
Stream the game boards again?
Let's just redo it.
All right, come on, let's go.
Be Ice Cream one.
What's going on here?
This is why they're killing Flash.
It's your Java.
Be Ice Cream two waiting room.
It's working for me.
Well, what's going on with me?
Wait, what does it say?
Flash was blocked on this page.
Hold on.
Run.
Run it.
How is it blocked?
It's fucking blocked.
Stop blocking the, stop.
All right, hold on.
Wait, allow it.
Yes, allow.
Fucking bad Ice Cream one.
What the fuck?
How would it be blocked if it's currently showing this?
These tech illiterate.
How much is on a website, man?
I can't even play a game.
All right, I'm gonna play,
I'm gonna click on Twin Shot two, okay?
This is gonna work?
Plug in blocked.
I have it set to allow.
Why?
But do you know how long it's gonna take
for this Flash shit to,
this is like 100 years of Flash.
It's gonna take,
we're gonna have to get extinct
by the time this is ready to,
okay, here we go.
Humans are gonna get extinct
and then Flash will be finally weeded out.
All right, trick shot two.
Good versus evil.
Why does it look so bad?
Why does it look like this?
Zoom in.
I did.
Hold on.
This is really loud.
Okay, play.
Select players.
This one.
Press space.
Okay, all right.
I wanna play.
Well, you can't.
All right, can I pick my character?
How about this one, Garfield?
All right, it's arrow keys to space.
Ready.
Good or evil.
What should I be?
Good or evil?
There's a screamer in this.
Well, whatever, I'm gonna get scared.
Evil.
Okay.
Evil level one.
This looks, down below they plot and plan
the next time they will invade us.
This time things are going to be different.
This time we're gonna come in and invade them.
He hates good, I do.
Pretty evil guy.
And break the cycle that has,
just let me play.
This is as loud as hell.
Okay, what do I do?
Oh shit, it's like Bubble Bobble.
Why am I flying?
I should play Bubble Bobble right now.
How do I play Bubble Bobble?
Where do I get Bubble Bobble?
I wanna play that right now.
You have wicked bad A.G.A.
Get an N.A.S.
Shit.
What do I play?
Drop the spiky monsters onto the hot rocks.
Okay.
Ow.
Fuck this game, fuck this game.
Stop, it's fine.
Where do I get Bubble Bobble?
The music too, reminds me of it.
Drop the spiky, how do I do that?
I drop, how do I do this?
Oh.
Oh sick, that was cool.
How do I get the coins?
This game is a frog dump.
No it's not, it's fun.
I wanted to play bad ice cream, but it wouldn't load it.
Bubble Bobble, Bubble Bobble, cool math games.
Bubble Bobble.
It's not on cool math games.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do you got?
Are you kidding me?
You don't have that right there, do you?
Is that real?
Come on, everyone hold on a second.
Oh, calm down.
Holy, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, stop.
I got it, I'm gonna go.
Ow, my ears.
How do I play?
Enter, G, period.
Is it just a, did you just link me to the title screen?
It's just the intro, you just linked me to the intro.
I can't play it?
Why would this exist?
Z, why does this exist?
Hold on, what did I do wrong?
Press one, okay.
Left and right, control and alt, okay.
It's one.
Oh my god, here we go.
Dun, dun, dun, A, E, O, O.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun,
dun, dun, dun, dun, yeah, yeah.
That's, I'm doing Peter Griffin, stop.
Oh, freaking sweet.
Oh, this is sick.
All right, what's the next flash game?
All right, I'm dead.
Move your mouse.
Wait, you can do this, remember you can do this?
Whoever's playing this game, you can do this stuff.
You can like bounce on the bubbles.
Yep, I still got it.
Buy the new Bubble Bobble game.
I'll buy them all.
There's like 10 of them.
I own them all.
Ow, I own Bubble Bobble for the NES.
I own Bubble Bobble, Bust a Move, right?
Bust a Groove, whatever it's called.
The one where it goes, ready, go.
I own all those games.
E, you should play Toho.
Can I do that?
Wait, is it, can I, can I do that too?
What should I do?
Okay, all right, all right, all right.
This is supposed to be a mystery game stream
and we're just kind of driving down
like the video game highway.
I'm just pointing at fast food restaurants that go by.
Oh, but stop at McDonald's.
Oh, no, no, no, wait, wait, we'll see what else is there.
There's Wendy's up there, I can see it.
Uh, yeah, pull in.
No, no, get back on the highway going south.
I wanna go back to McDonald's.
Wait, is that, is that a, is that a Carl's Jr.?
Oh my God, dude, Carl's Jr.'s on this highway.
They got everything.
Dig Dug.
No, I don't like Dig Dug, too stressful.
No, it's too stressful, it's too stressful.
You suck.
Oh, I was just standing, all right,
I'm done with this one.
Now, what's the next one?
That was cool to go down memory lane for a little bit.
All right, we're back on Nitrome.
Can I try, I wanna play Big Ice Cream.
I'm trying, I'm trying to do Big Ice Cream again.
I'm gonna try, or Bad Ice Cream, whatever it is.
Click maps, click maps.
All right, well, oh, wait, wait, wait.
I wanna see if it loads.
You need to rename this ADHD gaming, Icebreaker or Riot.
Where's Icebreaker?
All right, let's go, hold on.
Let's go back to the main page.
Drop this, you don't see where we are.
I don't even know where we are.
Double Night Dig, what's that?
Okay, should I just browse all games, turn on click maps?
Rust Bucket Vault, okay, more games.
All games, okay.
All right, let's just start right here.
Let's get click maps going.
Let me make sure I have that right, okay.
Okay, you ready?
Where are we going, where are we going now?
Stretchy Poop.
I'm not following them on Twitter.
Territory War, Territory War.
We're just gonna scroll down.
All right, so we have Silly Sausage and Meatland.
This looks like what everybody wants, by a lot.
Okay, that's it.
Silly Sausage and Meatland, is this good?
How is this one?
It's very good, okay.
Opera, Opera.
You want me to go get Opera?
I used Opera.
Give me another one.
I don't think Opera is even installed
on like two or 3,000 computers.
Scroll down, all right, well,
what the fuck, can I even play games on here?
Well, I guess we'll go here.
Can I even play games?
All right, go ahead.
Use Firefox.
Firefox has problems capturing through OBS for some reason.
I can't, it never works.
Okay, we're gonna try Colorblind.
Can I play a game?
All right, I'm gonna try Colorblind.
Looks like a fun one.
And I guess it's fun just hanging out.
We're just chilling.
I like hanging out with you guys.
Come on, you don't like hanging out with me?
Use Brave.
All right, let's go.
Okay, here it comes.
Initializing, 64%, 73% of that fiber connection.
That's why you get fiber.
That's why you have fiber.
Oh, okay.
Right eye versus the dusty pirate clouds
from industrial landscapes.
So, I gotta change this a little.
So, is this a good one?
You can see it.
Get all this crap off the screen.
All right, let's go.
So, let's play.
What's the premise on this one?
Unstretched.
I didn't even stretch it that much.
Okay, so I'm in this eyeball
and I'm in a world with no color.
Didn't they make a Mickey Mouse game about this?
Okay, so how do I move?
Left, right, and jump.
Okay, space.
I feel like I'm playing on a Game Boy.
But that was, all right.
Is this a puzzle game?
How did I fucking lose?
I'm so mad right now.
How?
I got really angry.
That's the maddest you've heard me
in probably like a week.
I got like very mad.
I like, that was mad.
I gotta calm down.
I was so angry.
Okay, you can't jump on them.
Good, here's a note.
I was like just so angry for no reason.
I have red paint.
Okay, so when I have red eye,
I can walk on red material.
Oh, this blue here.
If I have blue paint, I can go on the blue structure.
Oh, this is cool.
Oh, I have red and blue eye.
Wait a minute.
How do I get those spikes to turn off?
It'll be nice to see them.
Wait a second, how do I turn the spikes off?
Oh my God, there were blue spikes.
I understand, wow.
That was fun.
Age of War, we'll play it.
We got plenty of time.
This game doesn't have any guns.
No, it doesn't.
No, game doesn't have any firearms.
I don't wanna even be here.
This is kinda fun.
I actually like this.
This is a good pick.
He admitted it.
It's cute, it's really cute.
Not every game has to have a machine gun, okay?
And how unrealistic, by the way.
Can we be honest?
Unrealistic, oh yeah.
I'm gonna unload an entire magazine
and just reload it in one second
and then fire another magazine at somebody
and reload it and just fire another magazine at somebody.
It doesn't work like that.
Oh shit, what even killed me?
It kinda does.
No, it doesn't.
You fired an entire magazine at somebody.
Like, okay, I'm dying by the tree.
Cloud, it's you dying by the cloud.
Oh, okay.
I gotta wake him, I'm good.
This game kinda reminds me of Jump King.
Doesn't it remind you guys of Jump King?
You guys love that game.
Everybody loves that game.
Icebreaker, moron.
God, what is icebreaker?
Is it good?
All right, let me get to level five.
Play Dolphin Olympics 2, you dipshit.
I don't think you guys,
I hope you guys don't like order food like this
at like a restaurant or something.
Like, will you guys relax?
Oh yeah, I'll take the Reuben with french fries
and can I get a Coke with that, dipshit?
Sure, sir.
What the fuck is your problem?
This jack sent me.
You did this joke already, shh.
There's a lot of new people here.
We gotta use the old material that was like funny.
Age of War waiting room.
I promise I'll play Age of War, I promise, I promise.
Oh my goodness, I made it, okay, good.
Oops.
Play Solitaire, I don't know how to play Solitaire.
I can't do that, I don't know how to play Solitaire.
No, what do you think about that?
I'm dead, wait, how do I?
I don't know how to play Solitaire.
How do I, I'm gonna need to learn how to play Solitaire.
This is the first level, this is Mario one, two, yep.
Thank you.
All right, good, what does that say?
I wanna get to level five, this is fun.
End this bit, it's not landing.
What bit?
Playing color, the color stream game thing?
Playing the color eye color game thing?
There we go, blue.
No guys, I'm not gonna play Solitaire.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not going to play Solitaire, I don't know how.
And I'm not gonna sit there
and have you guys teach me how to play Solitaire.
That's not gonna, I'm not, I know I'm doing the thing.
I'm saying the words, I know we're doing this.
Like I'm not gonna do that, that's not fun, that's stupid.
I'm not gonna do it though, I'm not going to, I promise.
Not gonna play Solitaire.
Okay, what's the next one?
Ice cube, the ice cube game?
Oh shit, okay, I'm good.
Age of War, right, I promised everybody
I was gonna play Age of War.
I will play Age of War coming up next.
This is the last one, I'm gonna beat this.
This game's fun though, I actually like this.
Reminds me of a few different games.
Where do I go from here?
Oh, oh shit, okay, I get it.
It reminds me of a boring game.
No it doesn't, it reminds me of a fun game.
This reminds me of a fun game.
Oh, by the way, I'm gonna reveal
a Jerma Rumble character for you
because I know people just keep asking,
they keep talking about it and I'm gonna address it, okay.
So one of the new characters in Jerma Rumble
next coming up is, I'm dead.
One of the, okay, I gotta stop for a second.
I can't do two things at once.
My brain can only focus on one thing at a time.
Okay, Jerma's ass is gonna be a,
oh my fucking God, I'm not gonna move.
Jerma's ass is going to be a character, there you go.
Now let's see if I can beat this.
Ass by itself, yes.
So let's see how, I hope you guys root for it.
Oh shit, I got it.
Will there be 2019 characters in it too?
Yes.
There's like two years worth of people to pull from
so this is gonna, that's why I,
what's the next one, Age of War?
How do I get there, is it on here?
Age of War, where do I get it?
Oh, here we go, okay, I got it.
Addicting Games, this is the one, right?
This is Age of War.
I'll do Dolphin Olympics after this, I promise.
Max Games, oh shit, yeah.
That is old, that's really old.
MaxGames.com.
I heard, I don't think that was allowed for you
but whatever, okay.
Instructions.
Goal of the game is to survive and destroy the enemy base.
The game is divided in five ages.
With the next age, you need XP points.
To gain these points, you have to kill enemy units, okay?
You can also gain XP points
when one of your units is killed.
You can also build defenses.
Finding the balance between defense and offense is the key.
Wait, is it intentional, what?
What did I do?
You'll also be able to use a special attack.
This attack will, what did I do?
This attack will need time to be available again
after you use it.
Each age has its own special attack, sure.
You cannot repair your base but it will gain health points
every time you evolve to the next age.
Protect your base at all costs.
Okay, like, 1998 flash games are the same thing
as 1998 video games.
They're insanely hard.
And if I do impossible, it's actually impossible
and you can't win.
Your volume is down?
No, it's not, it's not.
I'm doing normal.
All right, here we go.
What do I do?
Train units menu.
15 for a club man.
Oh, shit, get out there, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Slingshot man.
Oh, yes, this is gonna be so much fun.
And then I can also do dino rider.
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Get more people out there.
Build turrets.
Okay, rock slingshot.
Let's go, yeah, build it.
It's one of these games, I love these.
Get up there, get up there, get up there, get up there.
I need a dino rider.
We're losing, we're losing, we're losing.
Dino rider, go up.
Slingshot.
Only slingshot behind the dino rider.
DMCA, is it?
Here we go.
Yes, yes, yes, keep going.
I want another dino rider.
Want to help the CF?
He's dead, all right.
Another one, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Okay, I can queue him up.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god, what?
No, dude, that's so many.
Use your special, what does it do?
Does it hurt me?
Oh, wow, that's powerful.
Wow, that's powerful.
That's incredibly powerful.
Okay, go back.
Just make five dino riders.
Get in there.
Get in there, get in there, get in there, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, fuck.
What?
What, how did he get that?
How do I do that?
Add a turret spot.
I only have dinosaurs.
It's the star, where?
Evolve, 4,000.
Fuck, I'm behind.
All right, we're okay.
We're all right.
I kept up.
I need an archer.
This is actually gonna work out fine, we're good.
Another archer.
Can I make a knight?
500 bucks.
Okay, we're good.
How much experience do I need?
1,400, all right, I'll get that before him.
Don't use your special.
What about a turret?
Okay, sell a turret.
Buy a turret, add a turret spot.
Catapult, it's 500, should I get it?
Fire catapult, sell this one.
Sell, okay.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta get in there.
All right, turret.
I'm gonna go with a catapult, let's go.
Done.
Eat box remix, okay.
All right, I couldn't do it.
My throat is fucked up still, I can't do it.
Give me a horse.
All right, go in there with the guns.
Use the shotgun.
Shotgun in the head.
Violence, finally, people are waking up
and paying attention, violence.
I need one of those.
Experience, I need 14,000.
All right, let's go, go, go, go, go.
Horse, horse, horse, horse, horse.
Two horses back to back.
Use special.
Double horse coming in.
He upgraded, he upgraded, he upgraded.
Sorry, he can't take me, he can't take me.
He upgraded an age.
I need 14, all right, go, go, go, go, upgrade.
Dueler, a duelist.
Oh shit, he's like just running me through.
Cannoneer, you're fucked.
No, I'm not, I'm not dead yet.
Wait till I, I'm gonna get a cannoneer.
Oh god, I'm in trouble.
Is this a heal?
Oh no, no, no, no, no, I thought it was gonna be a bomb.
It's not over, it's not over.
I've got a cannoneer.
What, shocking in the head.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Another one, he's dead, fuck.
I need another turret, I need a turret spot.
Shit, they've got cannons, I'll need a large cannon.
Use this again, I need a cannon.
Quick, get a cannon, get a cannon, get a cannon, 1500.
Sell all this, give me the cannon, large cannon.
All right, you're fucked now.
How much experience do I need?
45,000.
Losing in a kid's game.
Holy shit, how does he have all that stuff?
We're gonna get in there.
Get in, evolve, evolve.
I don't have enough.
Add a turret spot, that's what we're doing.
Smash up.
This game's sick.
Okay, I have another turret spot, a little turret.
How about a, let's get a small, no, no, no, small cannon,
yeah, I need to upgrade.
Maybe just two mediums?
Fuck, I have no money.
I have to evolve to 42, 45.
Gonna do it quick, he's already ahead of me.
Shit, I'm in trouble, go.
Special, how much is a tank?
Seven, get a fucking tank out right now.
Tank, tank, tank, tank, get a tank.
Okay, sell this.
Little turret.
Oh, you're in trouble.
Rocket turret, how about a, okay.
Yeah, I got a tank.
Shit, they killed him, tank.
My computer crashed.
Hello?
What?
I was having so much fun.
Oh, come on.
My graphics card can't handle an explosion in a flash game
from 25 fucking years ago?
Hold on, can I, let me just force this to quit.
All right, hold on, coming back.
What the fuck, that's so annoying.
Hold on.
Turn the music off, extras.
Here's a sweet drawing I made.
I mean, it is pretty sweet.
That's pretty sweet, it is.
Oh, I know what to do now.
All right, it's about kill.
Get us in there quick, I'm gonna win the first stage.
It's a, yeah, I'm rushing to start.
I want the money.
I got, I got Dino Rider first.
All right, what do I need?
I need 4,000 sprints.
He wasted money on a slingshot, what an idiot.
Big mistake.
Again, do it again, it's a Dino.
AI gets unlimited money, do they really?
Oh, I've gotta push back really far.
Little turret, idiot.
I don't need a turret until the next stage.
He's not gonna even get past here, what?
4,000, he's still in a line.
All right, now I'm gonna save a little bit of money.
I'm gonna build a second turret swap.
That's way too much, hold on.
Do the special, there's nobody gonna do it to him.
Okay, Dino, Dino.
Oh, all right, all right, okay.
I don't wanna waste any money.
Evolve, I can't evolve yet, it's 4,000.
And special, go.
All-sling shot.
What are you spamming?
I've been in touch with Healy and he said,
you'll be seriously considered a trending gamer next year
if you screen more solitaire flash cams.
He said your content is funny and random
and a family guy sort of way and he sort of
needed a good representative for the solitaire community
going forward, something to think about.
Oh, fuck yeah, how did he already evolve?
How much is the horse?
All right, I need a turret.
500, I want a fire turret.
I'm gonna hold off.
Hopefully I can make the money.
Kill, shit, do it, kill him.
Oh you dick.
Oh my god, what do I do?
I can't do it yet, I have to do this.
Special, fuck, I know, I'm so bad.
I'm sorry, I'm so bad.
Another knight.
I'm actually dancing in my chair this game slaps. It is really cool
So behind I know I am fire catapult. That's what I wanted. Okay now I'm good. I'm so far behind but whatever. It's okay
The world record for this game is 42 seconds how get out there a fire cannon
This is hitting me in the head. Special
14,000 come on. Come on. He just did it. Come on. Hurry up. He just did it. Come on 14,000 hurry hurry hurry hurry
hurry
Get out there. It's a good start. I got look at these look at these riflemen. Cannon
Special. Cannon
Guler mosquito you're doing I guess spamming weird stuff
Hilarious chat. I don't even know what's going on
coffee pasta incoming
All right, if I've read it, will you stop?
Big fan. This is a really good indie game from Japan strides called hoho. There's 16 games to play
I know you're a huge fan of anime. I saw you ayayaya, but I think you'll love the art style
I'll now continue to ask you to play this game every stream from now on
It's the quickest way to get me to never played again
Like just absolutely never even play it not even open it once
We're getting close I don't like this
We 40,000
The new tarp so I'll just tell it
I'm gonna put in
I'm gonna put in I want this large in
Come on kill somebody
No
I want to Canada's back-to-back
three cameras back-to-back
Ball time 45 45 let me go. I'm gonna go first
Come on. Hurry up. 45 45. Let me go first. I'll be ahead. I'll make up so much ground
So loud, I'm sorry
infantry
This is a good spot
for the can
No, I'm gonna deter it sell this
How much is a single rocket turret rocket rocket rocket rocket rock
What how much experience 200,000 keep me keep me honest me get a tank
I'm gonna save it for double turret. Oh, look at that. Look at that
Are you a dumb? What are you a dumb guy?
What about double rocket? I had to do it. I had to do it. I'm gonna now I'm gonna do double turret
Alright, I'm in a good spot. This motherfucker just has a red cannon
Hank who tanks?
No tanks in the machine gun
Tank again machine gun all machine gunners as much as I can do ball. Oh fuck. Oh
Going on. What the hell is this?
What kind of youth is this?
Super soldier is a hundred and fifty thousand
What are these?
War machine
I'm ahead
Okay, I need a new target
We got laser cannon ion gray
Titanium shooter titanium shooter
Yeah, you're not getting close buddy. Good luck
War machine coming in and I'm gonna I'm gonna get a super soldier. No, no, let's get some blasters
and oh
He's in trouble
I'm yeah, I'm encroaching. I'm encroaching a little what's the next day? Uh, is it endgame?
Shit, I'm okay. Okay
and then I want a
blaster behind the tank
About a bunch of blasters and then I want a super soldier. I'm saving
Turn this down. I hold on. I'm in the middle
Oh shit
Can I kill this thing?
Alright, hold on. What if I don't just let it it'll die from the curse
Alright, hold on and a super soldiers coming up
150 wait
Super soldier. No ion ray. I'm gonna sell this and I'm gonna get the ion ray. How much is the ion ray?
I hope it's not that much. I'm good
Holy shit, you never touch my base dude. You're never gonna touch this. You know, let's do a bunch of tanks
I want to do double ion ray. Oh, you know, my base is gonna be untouchable
It's super soldier
I'm gonna
What's next? Super soldiers coming in next
Evolve evolve. I can't evolve anymore. I'm getting super soldier
All right, super soldiers coming in
Here he comes. It's Captain America
Yeah, I'm just gonna do only super soldier
How oh he was not worth it. He was not worth it. That was not
Okay, I'm gonna put another super cannon in here how are we ever gonna do this neither one of us can fight each other
Just farm them. I guess
Don't use special unit till later. I hold on I need to get
Just go AFK
So how much money do I need to win?
I'm assuming we do tank and like three super soldiers to save it for a super soldier army
This is fucking loud
Okay, I can make almost two
Hey, no, I could play the drums two soup. Somebody said one tank two supers to tank three tanks and then two super soldiers
Why am I my left ear is ringing? What happened? Why?
Hello place the red turret. I don't think I even need to okay. I'm going for it two big tanks
Two super soldiers
It should be enough
There we go. I don't have another super soldier cute up it in there
Come on get in and get in get in get in get in get in get in
Win you need a shit ton of fodder. All right, hold on
This is I feel like I'm playing a game of Starcraft
We both is 1v1 and we both own
50% of the entire fucking map each we have thousands of units at some point. Do you just call a truce?
Like after like four or five hours when it's like the game balance makes it impossible for anyone to win
The only way you win in a game like that in Starcraft or Warcraft
Is if something like up somebody's parents called them because they're like concerned because it's been like four hours
You know what I mean? Like like like Dave David
Mom, what do you that's all takes that time? That's the amount of times it's over. You lost when that happens
That's how you decide so I'm just gonna spam God's blades
Just make a million basic units, okay, whatever I'll try it
This is feeding the feeding
It's not a good plan
So just what it feels like to be lane minions
There's two giant fucking structures too huge. But wait, why are they damaged?
How did I do that damage?
All right. I'm going in with super soldiers only
Your towers are killing him. How how the fuck is that happening? It's overshooting people sometimes
tanks only tanks
There must sell the ions and use the cash for soldiers. No, that's not gonna keep me alive. We're just waiting
Just waiting to kill each other
sell replace them
No, I
What the fuck just let him die. I'm just gonna farm to like five million gold
Now by the super soldiers, I can only get one
Idiot can't even win a kid's game. This is our kids game
You may have played it when you were a kid, but it wasn't made for you
Quick evolve to solitaire. No, that's not yet. I have to win. Tell me he's almost dead
Holy crap sell the red one
What?
You go happy. I don't know. I did that. It was available
Just open up another game in a different window and come back in like a half an hour
All right. What's next? I'll just mute this. What's the next one? Are we going after this?
learn to fly
Age of war 2 have age of war 1 going in the background farming while age of war 2 is actively played and switch between them
Give me a sec. Okay. I need age of war 2. I think I broke it
Wait a minute. That's not gonna work. It freezes. How's it? Yeah. No, I can't it freezes like raft wars
If it's not the active window, it won't do it
Oh
Whatever I'll play raft wars. All right, that's the next one. Oh no dolphin olympics. All right, here comes the one. I'm gonna do a
Tank tank. I'm doing tank tank tank tank tank
super super super super
super
Super and then a bunch of blasters
Blaster they go. Here they go. Here they go. Here they go. Watch this. Oh, here we go. This is it
This is gonna win. Here it comes. This is it. This is it. This is it. Come on
Why don't you get in there and shoot? Get in there
No, are you both dead?
Get in there. He's got like two health
All right. We're good. Congratulations. You won the war and destroyed your enemy. Nice. What's two ends? N-E-M-E
Enemy enemy. I feel like I write like that. So what am I? I can't make fun of it
I've spelled enemy like that with last week. All right, what's next? We're going to raft wars
Is that on addicting games or I said we're playing nitrome and I didn't even play one game on nitrome
Raft wars. Sure. Let's get it
Raft wars is on addicting games. There it is. This one good. Okay. I just need to allow flash
Comes raft wars. I don't think if I played this one meet Simon a cheerful little fellow
He's having a fun afternoon at the beach. Okay. He's about to make an amazing discovery that will change his life forever
solid gold
friggin diamonds
We're rich
Good news soon found its way into the papers
The treasure is mine
Time to team up with your brother and defend what's rightfully yours
Go level one par six shots. I'm gonna make this a little bigger for you guys
Okay mouse click to begin. What do you do?
Instructions but you have to get power and then fire
Those pyres are toast. Well, that was in this
That's one of these games. Okay
It's angry birds. It's angry birds that you can't see. All right, hold on. What if I just go?
It's just worms
Yeah, ain't got nothing. Yeah headshot. Oh
Oh
Too close too close too close. You're dead
That's a fucking off-the-wall
Tell you later
Our six. All right. I got 1632 credits. Oh
cool
by grenades by
upgrade the raft
What should I do?
Upgrade the raft. Okay. Yeah, I'm good. I'm pretty good with tennis ball shot
Par six is just a guy up on the hill. Okay. I think I got this
Watch this guy in the hills done. Oh
That's gonna hit right in the head. Sorry. He's not as good
Right in the tummy
The axe is probably good. Oh, what's that right in the head?
What are these babies saying? Oh
We're okay. We're okay a
Headshot only does 81
Headshot again get out of here
Only one more. What's the par? I think I only one more shot. He's done
Is it par six credits earned? I did it right shots fired. Yeah, I got it
Okay, buy missile or buy grenade. I'm gonna buy a grenade two grenades and one rocket
Level three guy on a jet ski. Okay, can't do the thing. I was doing before we're gonna go like this and
That's gonna miss. It's okay
You got to go over the hippo fuck. There it is right there. Oh
No, I can't otherwise they're shooting a real gun the dog no the dog
Fuck damn it. I said every spot, but you're both
There we go. Yeah, it looks like they look like like South Park character. What the fuck was that dude? What the hell was that?
Go full power. I can't I'll shoot the bug. I'll hit the hippo in the face. Oh, that was bad
This might be a loss. This is a loss
Way too fucking much. Come on right the guy's jet ski
God don't ever buy those
Stop using moving your mouse between shots
Baby
No, the baby could hit the head by like a metal slug
Get him off that. Oh, that's it game over. I already lost the par
What the fuck was that? I didn't move my mouse. Oh you bad. This is hard. It's intelligent
Easy
It's not easy
There it is. I
Beat this when I was eight. I'm sure you did
No, what happened is which you miss remembering things in the computer lab when you were like fucking 13
You played this for like five minutes and then the teacher came over and said
you kind of what you're trying to gauge how long was gonna take for the teacher to go around the computer room and
Come over and put the hand over on the desk and lean over and look at what you were doing to see how good your
Work was doing
You timed it, you know
It was about four or five minutes from when they were in the corner of the room
They went and checked on every single person you timed it a few times. It was about four and a half minutes right there
That's gonna hit me around the head. Thank God. There it is bounce
Okay, but I actually beat it when I was eight
Oh
Stupid all right, let's do it again. Oh
All right, it's a par five. Come on. I can do this. It's not even that bad
It's got to go slightly over the hippos head. Let's try this ready
There it is. Okay, right after that got one guy dead. That's a good link. Hold on
single
He was actually pretending. No, I was afraid of hitting the hippo
Oh
Click the link. All right. Hold on. That's a six out of ten link. All right. Well, we'll find out
Yeah, this is a six out of ten, but it's still all right
It's all right. It's not bad. I would call this a quality six. I
Still can't believe you guys hit me right in the face. I got really didn't even move. That was just stupid. I was just yeah
That's so ridiculous. Whatever. All right, let's go
level four seven shots
There's a guy in the dock in the raft got a jet ski. Oh, this would be easy. Okay, here we go
See ya I stepped into it. I know I didn't step into it
Fuck it's gonna hit him. I want up three. Oh, it was a baseball
Fuck I'm doing
There I'm eating a sandwich. Do you want half of the dams? What?
Are you talking about?
Yep, that was the strategy
All right, I like going hard and just shooting
There was dead. I really want oh, I just gotta hit it a
Little bit higher right there. That's it. No
Come on
Lower a little bit lower a little bit lower like right
Right here. Oh
Shit in my fucking pants, whatever
He missed again, sorry
That was more than seven shots though, yeah, damn it
All right coming up
Is that more than seven shots?
This is five shots. It's not moving the mouse. No, that doesn't help. That's like they can't come back and kill us, right?
Oh, that was a triple
fuck
All right, what's up after this? What's the next one?
That's double
dolphin, right
Dolphin Olympics
One more don't die
Stay alive
Okay, come on baby up to you one two three got it right there I
Got it under par under par five shots you gotta play some nitro games. Yeah, I know half of them didn't work
Thought I had it if you get the next one in four, I will sub. Okay. Oh
Too high. Oh
Oh shoot, you said the next one not this one
nice, okay
What a bizarre concept. Why would they pick babies as the protagonists? I don't know
No idea
The baby found gold in the beach
He's digging in the beach playing and he found a gold nugget and then a bunch of like pirates came to kill him. Oh
All right. I gotta land this cuz it gotta be clean. What you fall?
All right. I have to land this I'm thinking like right right there
Completely wrong, but whatever that was totally wrong 100% inaccurate
He's gonna guess I'm dead. Yes. Okay, a little bit higher
This game is fun. What a cool game. Let's go
All right, if I skip if I skim the force first one here, this is gonna be this would be solid right ready
One, two, three skim it hit both
raft wars
There it is
Bounce headshot like balloons. We played balloons a long time ago
Remember chat put every balloon and everywhere it needed to go. It's gotta be higher than that
Yep, I remember
All right, if I do this one in four then that person subs whatever was the name
Okay, I got four shots to do this coming up one here in four
Okay, your shot number one. It's one
Please turn on once again asking for bullet wave on it comes to
Your I die get that credit card ready. I would get that credit card ready
Here comes to the hiccups three. No, I
Got one more shot. Okay
Get that credit card out and buy yourself something nice buy yourself a
new PlayStation 5 if you had can afford it
Get yourself a new pair of shoes or sneakers or something. God damn it. It was in a five. Oh well
Damn it. Okay. Last one then we move on how about this one if I can do this one in four I get
No, I'm not doing this anymore
I've changed my mind. Okay, what is it? If I do this in four I get what how Oh mega low
They've landed so many shots, this is fucked up that's fucked up dude, come on
That's fucked up, dude
Okay, I was gonna say that would be fucked up didn't work. I think I did now. I got one more shot
Get out of here. I
Was gonna say that didn't land that be fucked up
Fucked up
No, I can't upgrade the wrath. I don't have 2,800 credits. It's maxed. Oh, this is by bunch of this
All right, dolphin Olympics is what I'm gonna play next
Next one in par and I will sub. Okay
Next one in par and you will sub. Okay, I'm gonna go for it
Oh
No, listen to my like reaction. I think I lose
There it is. Yeah
All right. This one in four or five. What's part? Okay. The next one is coming up
Seven par level ten par seven. I have to do this one in part. Okay one. Oh
No
That's horrible that everybody's dead everybody's dead
No, stop pretending to react to the what that was me going like, what am I doing?
It was way too hard. Ooh
Somebody said half-life reactions
No
Bounce again
I'm with the science team
Well, you don't have to stop because I'm gonna lose
Well, you don't have to stop congratulations listen next game
Please Gordon. I'm rather busy right now. Oh
Crazies he went crazy. I lose. This is the final level. Oh, is it really? Let's go. All right, I hit the people though
the bad
Two three one, two three. So your parents
And didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't I'm missing subs
Thank you dat B for the five community. I'm not even looking what thanks to the five community subs dad. I
Will win raft wars invented the floss
Did it? No, I thought it was the backpack kid a
Little bit lower and I'll be fine
There we go, that should be a kill that should be a kill thank you
He's saying you my you're a tall one. I
Can do that? However much I want because I don't have any constraints on me
Keep your feet on the ground. Give me some more. I'll do them all I
Don't care if I get minus two. I don't care. I don't care
This is the last stream I ever do because you hate it so much. Give me more
It has to be Alliance thought I didn't play word play skywire, please
Oh, no, that was just you asking me to do that. The dwarves don't say that at the flight path
Play sky. Oh, I lost. I'm not to beat this first. All right, I'm going for it. No more fucking around
You must beat this. I'm going to beat this
I was about to refresh the page to restart
How come they have these big explosive devices? There it is bounce off that jet ski die
Die kill him. It's the final boss. Yeah, I'll beat it. I'll beat it. It's gonna take a minute
I'll do it again. I have to hit these guys first. He's gonna miss
God Jeremy, what the hell are you doing? It's okay. I gotta go up higher
Didn't you upgrade the units?
You can't
Hire I'm going way too low. God. Damn it. How do I hit the only people I'm not supposed to hit?
Ball they've all there it is
Dead dead dead play evolve
Um, I don't have there more than a hundred people that are playing that on steam right now. I'd be surprised if they work
They keep moving me around they bounce me around and my shots are wrong. Okay, that's that's too. This guy's dead. All right
We're fine. Just as long as he doesn't kill us right now. Okay. Well, it was probably inevitable
I have to take care of this guy first. I got it exactly in the right spot that I want it
There it is dead. Okay, good. Good. Good. Good exactly what I wanted headshot miss
That's good. That's okay
Okay, this one needs to be a little bit lower like right here
Got a bowl knock him in the water. Oh, come on. That would have been sick. There are nine people playing evolved right now
Is that even enough for a full party?
How many people play that game?
Yes, he's dead that's enough of one game
overshoot
Goddamnit. Oh
Come on
Use missiles. I don't have any I don't have any money. I can't I have to beat it like this
I don't know. I can't buy anything
No, it's not softlocked. I just have to get the shots
like that
Good good. Now they're gonna be in a bad spot here. Same deal bone
It's gonna be up a little bit higher. They're gonna miss he's gonna overshoot the whole thing under
It's okay. Why is that instantly? It kills you instantly. This is gonna be
like right there
the guy that God
I was trying to get the guy in it. They just have these bombs. I just grind for money. I can't even do that
Alright, I this is doable. They don't hit me
These guys hit like direct hits every like what the fuck you have direct hits it with bombs. I
Only get three shots because I'm dead in three shots
Come on bounce off bounce off knock him in the water knock him in the water. Yes. Okay, this is good. Oh
Yes, all right everybody relax that was purpose exactly what we did miss
That's okay. Don't bounce him in the water. Good the lip. Okay, we got it. I just I gotta get the guy in the jet ski
All right guy in the jet ski is got to be a little lower than that like right there
I'm saying right there. There it is dead hundred headshot. Come on
Miss fuck don't kill this one
Miss miss, please miss miss
Why
It's a I can't win. This is unwinnable
They have huge splash damage grenades and I have three characters. They have four even if I kill three people in three hits
I'm dead
Get him off that boat. They hit the same exact spots every time
Reset reset would be reset. Oh my god, damn it. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me. Kill me
Just do it. Blow us up. Just kill me. Just kill us
Tell us
If I gonna win accidentally
Just I'm gonna win. I think
Have a chance. I got a chance. I got a chance. I got a chance. There's my chair. There's my chance
Just pray and shoot who cares this one done. All right. Now just miss just miss. Don't hit me directly
That that's I'm okay
No, don't fall
It's not fair
Not in a bad fit. Okay, this is where we potentially went. I've got to knock this fucking guy off
Don't kill us both
All right
Have to hit this guy in front of the tree. I have to there it is
Thank you very much. He's dead. Now. It's gonna deal with the guy up top
We have never seen the guy up top fire a weapon. He might miss
He's gonna miss he missed as it does it seven damn. We're fine
All right, gonna hit this fucking guy in the tree. I can hit the guy in the tree and I'm gonna save with blind faith
It's right there
Way over way over that's not gonna be seven damage. I'm gonna be fine
It's right there. It's right there miss, please
I've never had to fire at this guy. It's been like ten times. I'm going for him first. I'm going for that guy first
I'm going for that guy first. I have to get that in the right spot right there. Oh
my fucking god kill me
Stop flailing your mouse around
Like I can't believe I lost
I'm not moving at all. I'm staying completely still
Just kill me. It's a wash. I'm doing it again
Just remember the background. I should have won that last one, but it was just there's too far. I
Gotta kill the guy up top first. He's the biggest pain in the ass
Okay, we're talking we're talking about like the trees but right with like the tree is the trees bending over like this
The trees like but trees but with this much power right above the trees, but all right like right there
Okay, all right. It's all right, and then look at worked out. Just fine
We're gonna go a little bit lower now from the trees, but we're gonna go down to the trees
You know down the trees like thigh right here. Okay. Let's say like right there right there
Yep, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
That was the thigh
And we could go to the back the trees back is gonna be a good one right there right them jet ski. Yes
Yes, yes, knock them off knock that motherfucker off the tree
Okay, right there
and three
Get him out
Get that guy off. Come on. No what?
That's all right. Holy shit. They missed
Okay, I'm gonna say it's right. It's right there. That's the one
It's gonna bounce
Listen listen hit him buzz buzz him. He's alive. I have to start the whole thing over. No, I don't
God that was a little bit
Okay, we're okay
Hold R to restart does that work?
How is a hundred damage if you get hit by that directly what the fuck I just hit R and it didn't do anything you lied
God this whole game has been easy until the final level that rent. I just ran out of missiles
My money, I'm not paying attention anymore. I have to just restart do it again. It's ctrl W. No, I don't know don't do that
alright, I'm I
don't
Didn't think I was gonna be here for this long. I didn't think I was gonna do this for this long guy in the jet ski
restart just uh, oh
I don't even care
He's losing hair. It's so stupid
Why?
All of a sudden they're just bad at the game now
eek a shark
It's gonna hit the guy in the tree and some knock him down. I'm just
How can I be fucking this like malding at a?
2002 flash game. I'm just like I'm tilted
What the fuck did that even hit man? What did that even hit turn the face cam on?
No, I'm done with clothes on
When are you gonna gamble on Pokemon cards? I don't I can't do that
No, fuck that I'm just gonna go get a bunch of baseball cards and open them on screen
I'll buy a bunch of like baseball like booster packs
See if we can get like a King Griffey jr. Or just there it is knocking in knocking in that couldn't have been a worse outcome
God
Put clothes on you're a grown man, but a grown man can't sit his own house with no clothes on
Did they both how'd they both die? I didn't even look
He's a grown man in his own home cannot wear
I have to wear a t-shirt and like pants in my house
No, I could literally run from back and forth from like bedroom to office bedroom to office
Naked just balls hanging. It doesn't matter. This is my own place. I can do whatever I want. I
Could just sprint back and forth and like breakdance in the it doesn't matter
That's political
Oh
And that's how you start the big one
I can literally just go down and I could just go to my fridge
Open it up and open up a fucking fresh almond milk new just naked and just chug the thing
I could chuck almond milk down in my kitchen. I could just chug it naked. Would you would you get what are you gonna stop me?
Good stop talking about this. I will
Eventually, all right. This guy is a little bit up. That should be it ladies and gentlemen
Everybody relax. We have just killed them with this guy
What this dickhead in the tree this last guy in the trees the only guy I have to kill
Just do not kill us both in one shot
Didn't this is my opportunity. I have to hit this
Have to hit this guy right now
Have to hit him. I think it's right here right there
This is it. Yeah, I have to hit him hard in the head. I think that's it. Maybe a little bit lower
I think that's it. I think it's like right here
Right there. Oh power higher. Is that too high? I feel like that's too high lower lower. Oh
die
Yes, we did it. Hey, wait, I got a par four man
Excellent. I am so happy after clearing the coast Simon is happily reunited with his parents
Did it raft wars?
Hey, thanks for the five community subs
Thanks epic epic slayer, but then I mean but then
Sadly mom and dad have turned against you and I after Simon's treasure as well what that's bad
He laid dad. Oh my fucking god next game. I am screaming at my screen
You need to relax
Just imagine two hands on both sides of the monitor just screaming into it
I just want to make sure I can I can tell you I gotta you gotta be aware of this. I can't hear you
That's it. I won. Well done after fighting off the bad guys and withstanding his parents greed Simon is happily digging gold again
Nice. All right, I won
What's next? How do you keep on? Why do you keep ignoring?
Icebreaker and learn to fly. Those are the only games. I want to see you play angry son face
Why do you hate me personally so much?
All right, let's do learn to fly. How do you hate me personally?
Okay, learn to fly a lot of people are saying this
Kind of P to check a P. Yeah in a minute learn to fly. Okay
It's saying flash allow flash, of course
reload the page
Can you see it just a moment while the game loads?
I
Continue and skip all ads go premium
No, no the penguins this penguins had enough of life on the ground and wants to learn to fly
Slide off of the ramp and buy upgrades so that you can make it over the water
Use the left and right arrow keys to control your angle in flight
Once you buy rockets press and hold spacebar to activate them move this little
You can actually see what the hell's going on. I remember this one. I don't think I played this one cool math games
a game by light bringer
Somewhere in our inartica. This is a club penguin
Read chat. Oh my fucking god
I'm gonna play to please play to play to wrong one wrong version. How what why please do the
I'm playing this one first
Lightless bird who is so much better. Well, I just wanna see if I'm an end of the concept
I'm into the concept and yeah, let's go
Learn wait until you reach the jump use left and right to adjust your angle hit the water with your belly fast enough to bounce
Okay. All right
ramp height on
17 cost 10 height of the ramp above sea level. Let's do that one
Achievements. Oh good. This is awesome. It's like stage five
Okay, then we got to get the angle right. I'm doing this wrong
acceleration a cleaner surface for a faster acceleration
reduced air resistance, okay
Play to play to play to all right. All right. All right. I just want to make sure I like it
Let me make sure I like it first. All right. That's all right. I like it. Let's play learn to fly to
Where is it learn to fly to this is it? Oh, I heard it's like three
What ads was flash allow ads? Oh
Okay, fine. Okay. Oh kind of regret doing that
You can't see but I can
Here it goes learn to fly
Start muted. I'm under cover. What is that supposed to mean?
Is this like I'm at work and I don't want my boss to hear no, they thought of everything they're at school
All right, learn to fly to this is after the first game. I assume he got he flew away
Story mode I gotta turn this up. It's a little low graphics are much better
Hey slide and wait until you leave the ramp. Mm-hmm tilt with the left and right arrow keys
Or use the mouse to control everything change control in the options menu
Destroy the five obstacles ahead of you by hitting them payloads increase your damage and cash
By you're saying play one. Why are you saying that? No, you guys you guys have fucking demons
Earn cash by scoring distance speed duration. Okay, let's go. Let's launch. What's wrong with him? What do you look a bag on his head?
Day one. All right, I got it new record
Backspeed I earned $30 today. This is the shop spend your money on upgrades
Look here to upgrade your ramp length ramp height and boost fuel
well
Like these buttons to shop for upgrades in the catalog
When you're ready click on the right. Oh cool. All right ramp length. How about an upgrade? Oh, I love upgrades
I'd love upgrades. I'm ready
Snowman to destroy destroy the snowman
tilt come down a little and
They learn to Yakuza zero
Get out of here. Okay. How about more length? No a
sleigh
Get the plank. It's 25 bucks
I'll get the plank. You can see more items
Every upgrade has different types. We should have tried them all
regular is a
speed increase
Activist Springs
Explodes to boost the launch and then gliders. Okay. Well, let's just go boosts toggle when the button
Huggled on when button down off when lifted
You can do one shot for burst one burst regular adds weight to the obstacles explosives
You guys gonna have to help me out here, but I'm gonna get the plank
Nice. Okay. I'm ready. Let's go. Let's fly. Oh
Yeah
That was a big one
New record, that's a lot of money 54 bucks. I got a big altitude. All right, $84. I'm gonna increase the
increase the length
length and height
Go again. Oh
There it is. All right, cool. Get a fucking glider dumbass
It's right to
Not even like a hey just want to let you know, you know
What was the last time somebody wrote in quotes like hey just want to let you know
Like the glider is really good not in all capitals get this thing stupid person
and by the way, I
But it's my game. What if I want to do what I want to do. I'll get the kite. I go any any further
What fuel?
And I'll get it. I can afford it
Am I flying? Oh, all right. It's working pretty well fly
Did I get more distance?
24, okay
Same saving it. I'm gonna save money. I got to kill the snowman. All right, stay like this. I was awful
Why was it so bad?
Use the boost. Hold on. Look at that. Look at that top speed. Oh
Wait, I can fly
Does it work like Mario and Mario 3 or Super Mario World where you go like?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Is that how it worked?
All right. Okay. Let me see kind of a new record for altitude. All right boost
Pellar okay, I have a propeller
And then a payload is power sand
All right, let's go. What's the button for um, you have a boost use it with spacebar
Each glider has a red zone
Flying faster than a glider max speed will increase wind resistance meaning you won't go as far if you go too fast
Okay. Oh cool. This is so fun. I got duration. I'm gonna go again. Let's go. You have to destroy obstacles, okay?
Forty-seven forty-six forty-five forty-four. All right, that's that's first I've ever gone. It's not okay close. Oh shit. I got a medal
all right, how about um booster fuel and
That's all I can do
That looks pretty good. That looks like good speed good speed
Good play sonic inflation adventure. I don't know if that is good speed right off the bat. All right, stay right there
I'm just gonna float a little bit. Where is he? He's close. All right, that's good. We're getting progress
114 all right, I need more um about I need a ramp height and
Maybe none of these 125 plank to
Nice, I got it. This is extra speed
Yeah, that was good. There he is. All right, I gotta hey, I gotta kill him. I got a hit
Alright, I'm gonna save the money. Maybe what about another thruster?
Okay, I need $250 for that we're gonna do power our iron pellets. Come on get them
Command you to rise from the snow and fly what what the fuck just happened
What where is he? Where's the snowman? Is he dead? Wait, what?
The arrow was pointing down here. Didn't have to kill the snowman. You wasted it, but I thought I had to destroy the snowman
Pulse jet you wasted it. I what I thought I thought I had to kill snowman
There it is done
Destruction 75 bucks. This is so much fun. I love this
Bonus shop. Oh what you're looking for
by persistent upgrades with your bonus points
Earn more bonus points by earning medals playing arcade mode or completing story or classic
You like to have more days in a month. This calendar starts on day zero
Nobody gets rich by earning their money
The real way to make the big bucks is knowing how to make more from what you got 5% more cash every run
I'll remove the
Genuine Phoenix feather this will reduce the speed loss when flying by 10%
Okay, whose deficiency booster 5% more power. I guess I'm just gonna look at the money one. I can do it again
Holy shit. Okay. Um, I guess I'll do the speed loss to the money money and speed loss temperature money
Okay, and let's go
All right. I have to destroy the snow mound wherever that is
Okay, that was another those snowman, let's get the snowman going pretty far but we're uh, where's the next thing?
That was good distance
154 old glider. Okay, I'll do this one. Whoa. Oh my god. I'm just going I'm just going man
I'm just going there's the mound. Oh
My god, I didn't get it. I need more damage in a photo. I was a thousand
All right ramp height
Need more DPS. Yeah, I'll get some
How to keep it in here. Don't go in the red
All right. I'm gonna fly into it. I'm gonna fly into I'm gonna fly into it
And fly am I not am I not do I not have this feed? Oh, you married into it
Sure, come on. Come on. Come on float float into it. Yeah
All right, one more
Yeah
We married into it you married into it sir, I don't understand
How much have you lost on a coin toss? How much I don't I can't understand what we're putting up here
You have to call it. I can't call it for you. You have to call it. Okay. I guess it's heads then
Well done. Well done. Don't put it in your pocket. That's your lucky quarter
We're playing something right do that for two hours, I don't think I want to do that for two hours
Check the later pages in the shop. What's in here? Oh my god. There's a boom box
Just reenact the entire movie
Do it for one billion do the whole thing for one billion off the deck. I
Get into it. I could really go for it
This thing's coming down speed get it
What oh I went over it
Give you a little more. I'll give you a little more
You live out back. Yeah, we live out back there. We've moved from Temple, Texas could come back later
What time do you close sir? What time do you close? I'd say around dark
Dark is not a time. What time do you close? I'd say not 930. So maybe 930. I could come back there
Why would you come back then we'd be closed you married into it. You married into it. How much for the gas?
No, no, no
How much how much how much for the gas?
gas, gas, gas, gas
How much have you ever lost on a coin toss?
Have you ever lost on a coin toss? How much have you ever lost on a coin toss? How much have you ever lost on a coin toss?
Speed I don't go over it this time crying, please. Okay. Why are you crying?
No, I missed it again shit
It's still on oops
Somebody already commented on the clip from the movie
Whatever. It's a great scene. It's a great scene that movies fantastic
By the way, I'm the best fucking acting performances. I've ever seen in my life
Read chat what?
We're talking about what I'm they put you in
What do you mean? They put me in?
We can't watch this we can't watch this
I'm gonna get in trouble if we watch this. I'll show a little a tiny bit. I'm gonna get in trouble
What does it say?
VPN
Saves the day again
VPN saves the day again. Oh, oh my god and have it twice. Oh, it's wonderful
Yes, wait it. Yes
Oh my god
Thank God for the VPN. Yes, we're good
Anyways, uh, what what is this telling me? It's the day again. It does
It's showing why I like got it in the first place
Why the fuck I can't even all right, whatever
Don't call him dumb
Holy shit, dude. I just signed into his computer. I'm on his computer right now. Okay, so
Let's get for the zone
Dough I
Can't show this I
Can't show this. Oh, thank God for the fucking VPN man. I was I'm so happy. Why was it doing this?
Okay, let's keep going. You never said would VPN you use
No, cuz I don't know if I'm gonna make sure it works. No computer. Don't tell me don't tell me
What? Oh
Hit it hit it hit it hit it. I have the wrong booster on white. What? Oh, oh shit. It is worse
All right, I have to break this
There it is. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good destroyed by the spring that help
There's literally nothing but thick picks of German on his computer
Why would I have my own images of me like that? That's weird
What are the next page?
How do I get on them? Is there a next page here?
Okay, I need to destroy the wall. I'm gonna glide for a little bit. I want distance
All right, we're gonna go over that. I cleared that
Out of fuel, but it's okay
What's in front the wall? Stop stalling. What I'm trying to stay in the trying to get the distance award
Yeah, look at distance duration three
How much have you been lost? I would need it a plank about good old sled
Or how about wait L bouncy?
This is fast takeoff L bouncy another glider hang glider
ultralight trike hop speed in flight
umbrella
Are the tricycle?
Pricycle. All right, let's go. This is huge. Oh
my god
Okay. Well, I mean I burnt all the fuel
scary
Like the music changed
Whoa
Oh, that's the wall
Don't slow down. I'm trying to stay in the air. Wait, what about bonus shop? Let me see
10% reduction of the drag effect with red zones. Yeah
That's gravity
fuel capacity see how far you've traveled. Oh, it's a little
ommeter
Stop going up. Oh my god. Did you hear that? No, I see
Who air balloon rocket firework? Yes
Try it rocket. Holy shit. Oh
boy, oh
Too fast too fast too fast too fast too fast too fast too fast. I need more damage
need damage there we go cast iron, let's go and
Fire speed right into the wall. This should break it. This is gonna break it. It's gonna break it
150 miles per hour. We're getting close to
happening
Where am I? Did I go through it? I
Guess I went through it. I beat the mountain. Oh nice. I got tons of extra gold. Try to go higher
All right. Hold on. Wait
Should I put this into? Oh
I want that one. I need to destroy the iceberg in the wall
Somebody's gonna try to go higher. I flew it. Oh, okay. I guess I've got
Honey speed for okay. What's this shit? All right, even it out. I have time
I'm still really high in the air. It's the mountain. What did I do? I didn't break the mountain yet
Yeah, and I break them on already. Oh, I did. Okay. Nevermind
Yes, okay, I'm at 200 feet
150 speed very fast
Get me close to the ground though. There's the iceberg
I'll hire you the children's game is perplexing. I'm doing just what I'm doing fine. I think I need to do this
Yeah, let's go again in a new thruster
Ever to the rocket re
I like this pace. This is a good pace. This is very fast. Oh my god. I'm breaking the barrier here. Come on
Where is it? It's right there. Oh
What all right get rid of the firework this is a four-shot I'll try this oh
Wasted kind of I'm pretty high. I'm hiding either. Okay is worse. That's all right. I'm good
Look at the speed kidding me getting close to the ground. There it is. Just right it. What's next the wall, right?
Okay, I need what do I need?
1500 that's good. What do we got? Ooh
high tech
ultralight aircraft
propeller
whirly bird 512
Trying this one. Let's give it a try
uploading ads
What does happen
Going I'm 700 feet in the air
Um, I can't not how do I fly I'm going into space. Okay, uh
What happens when I run out of propeller fuel I just fall oh my goodness, okay
Where's the eject button? I actually hit it. I want to get different booster
The lift off. Yep
Okay, let me go back to the bonus shop and I want to do
Adjust the angle of the ramp. That sounds kind of ridiculous. I'll try it. All right. We're doing a mega ramp
increasing power and and
There's the iceberg more of an angle. Oh
Jesus, there's the wall
Distance five we're gonna I might hit it. Come on. It's gonna be close. I hit it. Okay, let's do
No, no damage. Should I do?
Let's just back this out
I'm not gonna waste all my shit
Anyone or after that and then let's go
Propellers always gonna be doing this. So, you know, again again and more more more more speech me speak me
Sorry, I can demon took over for me. The Goblin took over more speed more
More is that wall?
Here it comes right there. I'm not gonna hit it. I might actually know I think I might
200 200 feet 150
200 oh
You have boosting down
Shit, it's okay. I got some money
umbrella
color
zeppelin
Ultralight aircraft. All right, I'll get ultralight aircraft save the money
Let's go 700 feet in the air
fast as fuck
I'm crashing into that wall right now 200 miles per hour. It's gonna break. Am I angling down?
Um, I don't know the easier to smash into stuff
600 come on go go go go go
No
Lift I can't lift. It's alright. I'm getting a new thing. Anyways, fuck just do a front flip
I just wanted money to get the other thing anyways. Okay, let's get it
ultralight aircraft and
But it's the best thing I can get right Bob. I guess I could do like boom box
What thrusters is the best thing I can get? I know. All right, let's give it a try. This thing's going over 300 miles per hour
Holy shit. Oh
My god, it's going so I've missed the iceberg
What happened? I skim off the ground. I'm not trying to hit the iceberg
Again
What is going on here?
Change the ramp. Oh, that's a good idea that right like this. We're in the middle. Yep. Oh mega. Oh mega
All right, we're gonna just skim for a little bit. There we go. Look at that
Look at that
Okay, a couple more times I need fuel just bomb testing a theory out here
Theory busted theory busted theory busted theory busted
Get the thing that's get the Omega the Omega catalog one extra upgrade in every possible aspect. I need a thousand points
Alright, let's stay at around like 250 300. This looks good to me. Hey good. Oh shit
370 okay crash right into it going so fast. All right. Okay. What do I need? I got 10,000
Okay, I need a little more a little more. I need some more fuel. All right, save it
Hey load German. I will I will I'm gonna save two rockets. There's one I'm gonna do it right before we crash
Boy, okay. Pull up
Pull up pull up pull up pull up right now
Okay payload, but uh
He's on him just get the payload it's power power power power power
Why'd I do that?
Really? Oh, okay. I'm gonna get some speed and they're gonna pull up. All right. I destroyed something
What I destroy iceberg?
Got all my rockets go through all
What just happened I skipped off the grout
It's a break. This is gonna break three two one. There it goes. They went
nice a penguin
Revenge on those pesky icebergs mission accomplished and would stink
What kind of stupid non-flying animal cause of a bird give up and die?
What is this?
Congratulations, haha, not bad. It's alright. Cool classic mode has been unlocked
So what does that do I'll play learn to fly free
No, I let's look at it. Let's hold on to that one. I'll do that one another time
Where else we're gonna go skywire? Yeah, I promised I was gonna play skywire
Just guy what here it comes. What other time flash is going to end. We'll do this again soon. I love flash game nights
This is skywire
Okay, how do you play choose a level of one
Ready oh
You just have to move
Okay, I get it
Easy
Go just up and down. Yeah, it's just bits of accelerate and break. That was so slow. Come on, dude
That was so slow
That was pretty fast. What are you talking about? Oh that was tricky. Hold on good. Okay good. Oh
That was bad, it's okay. I got one like we died what
And go what look at a chat play rubble trouble you need to be more patient
I'm not patient at all. I have no patience. I gotta go for it. I gotta go
What is rubble trouble trouble trouble rocks? Well, hold on. Let me give this a little more time. There we go patience
See patience beat him. I can beat him play meet and no, thank you. I won't say the rest of that
Watch out. Oh, this is fun. It's kind of fun. Just to like speed around the wire
Oh
Good why is chat so rude? I don't know
They just sometimes they could be a little mean
Like icebreakers. Oh shit. I was gonna play icebreakers like an hour ago. I'll play ice break in five more levels
Would you literally suck at this game?
Look I the first time I ever loaded this up on my computer
The best part about that comment is you little you literally suck
Not like metaphorically or not like, you know possible. No, no, you literally suck
Literally
Nitro was amazing chat, you know nothing
One of our chat members said them. I like night room. I think it's cool. Oh
Wow, I literally suck. You see how fucking close that was. All right, hold it up. Hold up right here. Hold up
Hold up. Oh god, you're so bad at video games. What the fuck is a germadillo? I
Don't know I just activated it two days ago for fun. Yeah. Okay, that was bad
Let's trip. This was tricky. It's an opening. Oh
Worst 2020 emote nomination is free shit. Just go power through. Come on. All right, I have to be level 10
That's a little 10
Have a D. Yeah, everyone loves pep a D. I got it and then this people snow too, right?
I see some Christmas spirit with people snow, please
Almost lost it. Oh
All right, go
Go, what was it? Oh icebreakers is after this right? I'll do that. You won't beat it. Your brain is too old. I
Am why
Kids game. Yeah kids games can be challenging
Just because there's fun colors and cute noises doesn't mean that like all children can win
This doesn't put square into square peg whole thing and look and I'm now getting annoyed and I'm getting hit by the bats because I can't
Touch I have to I gotta go. I mean, I can't sit around. I hate the one who wants you to wait
You why still here? Why still here?
Why are you still here? Why?
Why are you still here? All right, I'm gonna be quiet. Give me a fucking break. Come on, man. I
Got it. Just fucking straight like there's no stopping
Why this is a hitbox hitbox is like five pixels wider than the fucking cart. Oh my god
Get over that
Get away from me. I'm trying to go get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away. Get away
Get away. Get away. Slow. Go slow. Go go. Oh
Fuck where's the other guy? Oh
My god, I'm so dead. I'm gonna lose right here. That's fun
icebreakers
That's fun
Where is it icebreakers flash game a spewer? Oh, it's also on my trim. Okay, cool. I like this one already
I like the way it looks already got my attention
icebreaker
now available in the app store
level one
What do you do? I play
the X
Click wait. Oh, I can drag across the ice to cut it in half get the Viking to the ship. Oh
Okay, okay
Get him in what's wrong with you. This is rock
You can't cut rock if the Viking captain can't break a big chunk of ice cut it down to make it smaller for him
Where's the other Viking? Why is it not broken? All right, what's next? I see the map. We got one there
Where's the ship down here? All right, there's a ship
We need to put see that I cut you
Why can I not cut you
Okay, that's weird. All right, then you go. Oh, that's not good. Okay
He's gonna slide, right?
It's okay. He made it. Did he make it? No, he didn't shit. It's okay. I'll push him in with the other guy
All right, dude, you know what? I'm trying to do like what the hell, but you know what I'm trying to do cut it
It's happening. I push him in
There man
Get it in get in
What the hell is this in the way get him in?
All right, we'll do you first slide down the whole thing. Hurry go go go go go break him out save him
Okay, next guy. Oh, he made it. Why is he hitting him? Okay. This one is so they drop
We can just drop them from here. That's you and that's you
Now these two I'm gonna have to cut down here. All right, what if I do this?
Okay, cut that and then cut that and it's just we can slide it out
Okay. All right now slide out there they go. All right, easy easy easy easy easy easy easy
Easy, we're good. Break him out smash this shit. This game is really cool. This is fun
What is this? We get two balls. I have to drop. What is this?
Okay, so that is they're on hinges
We go the boat was closer, sorry
Shit do again. So wait, I have to do like this
No, I don't get it. I had to hit him with a hammer. You like knock him out, right?
Soft brain tissue. Hey, it's a knockout. That's what I tried before. Yeah, I did it
Now I gotta do this this one's gonna knock him over like deep like smash him
Okay, this is guy gonna go like this. There's only one
Okay, so we have to smash this
Into here and then that will dunk this
What about okay that he went kind of high
He's fine
All right, who's next?
this guy in the all right, let's snap that and then
Break this so it's a little thank you very much. I'll take a first try
Break it, okay. What's next?
Yeah, there's a rope here
So I'm gonna assume we got to cut this and it's gonna swing and then we cut the rope and there it is
Okay, can you break that?
And then drop this motherfucker right here
Wrinkles are forming
What about this one? Oh this big gap here
Well, and then we got to break this
It's gotta make a bridge so if I go like this will fall that way
All okay, hold on all right, oh
shit bad
Hey, it worked. Hey, I have to get rid of this
It's gonna be good this shit's gonna get in the way. Don't get out of the way
All this crap's gotta get out of the way
That okay, and then oh shit. He's gonna wait. I got a
About here
We're right there. It's breaking
This actually might be good. He might go off of it like a round like a jump you're going
over that
Over the jump. Yes, it worked. Oh
Off in Olympics. No, I will I will hold on. I'm just I'm still playing this one. Oh shit gonna save those, right?
Okay, we're gonna lift him hit him with the hammer. So it goes blink
These ruins are very powerful and dangerous. These creatures are also harmful
I don't know why I did that. I don't know why I'm doing this
All right, oh
I gotta kill this thing. All right, kill this guy. It's dead snap. Sorry snap this
Really not really
This guy's got to go. What if he gets on the boat? Can he get killed?
He kills him. Oh nice. Okay, that's cool. We'll kill this guy to kill this guy
okay, now I can push him down and
Hold on a second. I'm in trouble, but not maybe not. Hold on. I'm okay. No, whatever. Fuck it. Who cares?
Now, what do you move? All right, that's fun. What's the next one dolphin Olympics?
Dolphin Olympics 2 or dolphin Olympics 1 which one yeah, am I gonna get yelled at to play the second one?
To okay dolphin Olympics to let's go you pop Tropico you can do that another time
You're not smart enough for the second one. Thanks for the confidence. Okay dolphin Olympics to get this in the right spot
Okay, I'll play basic techniques accelerate turn left turn right and roll use left and right arrow keys to flip your dolphin while airborne
Where as many points as possible in two minutes land nose first for a nice entry bonus
Artifacting on JPEG hold down while approaching the water to do a tail slide
Press up. Well tails. Let me jump out of your tail slide lead fish out of the water for points
hyper advanced techniques
letters
Let's go
Come into the ring and cool. All right
That's why that's why you have those warnings on the pools guys
That's why the warnings on the pools exist tail slide
nice
Times three. It's Tony Hawk
Finish it
What you need to play scum music?
Holy shit, what happened land it land it land it. What just happened? I don't understand. This is so cool
Hurry nice good finish good finish. Oh
Bad finish. What the fuck was that? Where those gold rings? Oh times up. All right do again flips
Now the free trial ran out I gotta get in some of those rings. Oh got some fish friends fuck on speed
No, you need violence
More fish friends. I need where those rings at
Some over there. Hold on
All right, I'm gonna get this ring ready should I missed it. All right, it's no it moved. Fuck. I got too concerned
It is the flip. I have to get to space. I need to do a hyper advanced technique
Wow, my chest that hurt that actually really hurt. I don't know why I thought that was that funny
All right, one more try last try. That's good
Fuck
I'm just bad. I can't do this shit. I don't like using the keyboard
Me a controller finish it finish it. Oh
Fuck that hurt. God. Damn it. I messed it up. Oh, well one more time. I want to one more time
All right, one more time. That's the last one fish good got some fish friends get up there get up there in the space
What?
Where are the firearms games?
I'm playing dolphin diving you can do with some no less violence today. Okay, I know I gotta keep combos going to get out of
the water faster
Fuck you game. Fuck you
What's the next one? What's the next one? This game's so fun, but I'm done. I can't do it. I don't like the keyboard
I hate using people for everything
He's dead. You didn't make it to space. I can't I can't do it. What's like what's a good like quick one
I only got like 30 minutes before I gotta go rubble trouble. All right. Yeah, that's the one we were gonna do
We're gonna rubble trouble. Yeah
Murloc RPG hold on to some of these. I love this. I love streaming
I'm acting like I just started. I love streaming. Hold on some of these new games guys
Maybe I'll come back in a couple months kind of like it. All right. This is rubble trouble, New York
What do you do? All right lads, we've got to make $1,100 to complete the job
Okay, boss will trigger the explosives with sticks of nitroglycerin
Just remember we get money for every bit that crumbles to dust. I'll destroy it all
It's the tool button at the bottom to use the nitro
Okay. Oh
I have less of the game. Okay, I'll click this button select your tool like anywhere to create an explosion
All right right here right in the edge
Like anywhere to create an explosion right here on the edge. All right, that was easy. You just cropped it
Real time serious damage coming up boss
Mary the drill is too expensive. Don't waste it
Drill can be used from above as well. Neat, huh?
Drill will target the nearest block that is to the side or below the mouse pointer. It explodes when it can't drill
Okay
cool
Very cool
Try again
cool
again
Cool. He doesn't know this is a video game
Boss, I've done a modification to the cement mixer
Gary, what have you made this time?
Cannon a cement mixer that fires cannonballs
It's easy to use just put yours in the cannon find a good angle and hold down the mouse button until you have enough power
Oh
Dear try to destroy just the building this time and keep away from my van
Okay, cannonball. Okay, so just destroy the just the building. Don't touch my van. I did something wrong
Where'd it go? Oh shit, did I do it? Hey, hey, I'm doing it. I did it
Fuck in there. Just give me a break more
whoops
Omega-Lel raft wars to Barry use the heli-wait one
Cool, thanks boss. Remember it runs out of fuel quickly Barry because it's heavy. It'll smash through every glass everywhere
This is the wrecking ball with the mouse pointer click to begin. You have a limited amount of time to use the wrecking ball
So get swinging
There
You killing me
It moves around way too fast. I got it. All right. I got it. All right next little
What Barry look what is it boss? Oh, ah, sorry guys
I can't get down. We have no time for this. Get your silly brother to the floor without injuring them
Should I actually kill them? All right, so hold on. Oh, wait, wait, he's okay
He's not he's almost on the floor. Hold on. I don't I don't like these kind of games
Because I've found a missile launcher and then finds a lot of things. Yeah, I'm gonna lose my brain
I just want to sprint as fast as I can into a wall and smash my head into it. I
mean I
Do puzzles and like figure out what to like what like pillow did no no no head down run as fast
I can and head into wall break through the wall
Okay, position the launcher with mouse pointer
To place the vehicle then click again to launch missile steer the missile with the mouse
Okay, that's fun. I like that part. Oh shit. It already went like metal here solid
I like that one. That was fun because I was just putting my head down and running into a wall as far as I can and
exploding it
And the shitty music off that's not that what?
I'll let any debris hit the that's what they meant. Okay, you guys don't like that
Don't don't
It's complete right? Yeah, okay
Cousin Ivan found a plane. It can destroy a lot of stuff quickly. You don't blow me up, bruv
Hmm, I'll help push stuff around with a helicopter
Okay, but Gary you can only bomb stuff in the yellow barriers
Yes, and I guess you should get
Gary down from there
He's British
Watch out watch out watch out watch out
Watch out Larry Larry Larry Larry. You're fine. All right, he's gonna come he's gonna come down nice and softly
Okay. Now. I just need a wrecking ball
only
Damn it. I knew I was gonna do that. Damn it. I don't like this
Give me another one. Give me another one. Give me another one
Save him. I thought he was gonna say fuck had ice cream three. I tried to play that earlier
I couldn't get it to work. Just trying to kill him one more time. Yeah, I'm done with this one. I
Don't usually don't like to play these kinds of games. They're like they're cute and they're fun, but now enough for me
What's next?
mother load mother load
Other load
Flash game it also a nitro. Okay enable flash
Alright, this is a tiny fucking window. I like full screen this
This is so small
Mother load with a little gold edition back when monitors had 640 by 480 resolution
Okay, you need to move this that looks good. Alright, what is this game the full screen button?
Mini clip says switch to focus mode to concentrate. This will restart your game. Okay full screen mode. They work
I mean it sort of worked
Little better exactly the same though. How's this one? Is this game good?
Meet and fuck I'm not gonna play meet and fuck adventure. I'm gonna get you. I will be removed from this platform
I'm not gonna play that control your pod using the arrow keys, or if it's more comfortable the WASD
Okay, your drill deploys automatically if you move into diggable material
You cannot drill straight up you can trade minerals in your storage bay for cold hard cash. Oh, I think I'm gonna like this
Let's go
Transmission
We forgot to refuel you on the way over drive over to the fuel station and fill her up
But almost impossible to hire decent miners on Mars since all the strange activities started happening around here
That's why we're willing to pay you at a premium for your services
I've given you a basic mining machine to get you started with
Unfortunately, you'll be on your own from this point onward as the settlers who were lucky enough to escape with their lives have fled
Safety, however, all the shops here have been computerized
So you'll still be able to sell your minerals you'll up upgrade your pod and buy special items
Remember your job is to collect minerals and bring them back to the surface for processing the deeper you dig more valuable in minerals
You will encounter don't forget to refuel. Good luck. His mission terminated refuel $20
All right, five four dollars purchased. It's time to dig. All right, what's over there? Is that lava or is that minerals?
Okay, it's minerals. I'm doing all right. Ow, it's like dig-dug. It's like dig-dug. We can sell stuff
ironium
silvarium
bronzium
Whatever it's it's okay. It's all right. We'll be fine. I went down gold over here
Much money. All right, just be careful
Argo Bay full. All right. How do I get out of here? Oh shit, I can fly. Oh
Oh careful mineral processing huh sell all
$620
Okay, so how do I upgrade? What's over here junk shop? Welcome to the upgrade shop?
Okay
real oh
this hole
17 health
30 health or drill
750 I don't have enough. Okay. Well, I know this is here
Pair oh shit, I should repair
I'll be okay. Hold on. I'm just gonna get a few more
All right, I'm coming back up. I have how much money?
It was low. All right, sell all this
refuel
the tank
Where do you put your pair?
Save your game. Yeah, sure
You explode if you run out of fuel it's all it's right, okay
There it is
This reserve fuel tank you can't afford any this art repair I could have just done that. All right
I'm gonna buy that the drill
this is the
sylvi drill
nice
Nice. All right, let's go. It was incredibly inefficient. Hey, how much I gotta get out fuel
Anymore I pick a fuel tank
Hey
Get me out of here
No, I want to do the oh
Oh good, okay going away. I want to go down here. This is expensive shit 500. Oh
Cargo full
Back up. What's this game called? I?
Don't remember. I actually have no idea. It's like
Load up or something. No, don't get the fuel yet
600 bucks. That's it
I'm always on fuel every second
Okay, yeah
Need a bigger tank any money
Okay, I gotta be careful with the fuel
These three and I'm going back. All right. All right. All right up careful. Don't smash your head on ceiling
All right process this shit
300 that's it junk shop. Oh
Engine
You'll tank. Here we go 750. Yeah
I'm going this way. How much how much was it 50% 20% or something?
I'm just gonna dig straight down and I'm gonna go straight up
Yes, oh my god, I haven't gone to the bathroom I completely forgot to go to the bathroom
Well, I'm right. Whoops
Forgot. All right. Let me I'm gonna pee and I'm coming back. I kind of want to keep going for a little bit
Let me see. I'll be right back. See you time first time like ever back and you are suss
Sure
All right, I'll probably be maybe like another 15 20 minutes and then I gotta go. You got a lot of stuff to do
Hey, well
It's just make it a little smaller
What's that? Why don't I hear that? I'm running out of fuel. Oh
Shit, okay
I'm going back to where I was over here. I want to go straight down
Wrong one. Oh fuck you. I need a bigger cargo. All right, that's it
Don't die here don't die don't die easy
Repair that's so much money
That's so much money don't break it then I'm trying not to all right, what's the best place to go?
I feel like I'm not getting anything. I'm going straight down. It's gotta be better minerals and further you down you go, right?
315 320 360
This is gonna go
Something expensive. Uh good. I see you're adapting go to the Martian soil. Is it less something to help you on your way?
Why did you do that? You distracted me and I just got smashed on that. Oh
Yeah, Goldonium
All right, I'm going back. Holy shit. I thought I crashed into him. Okay, Goldonium cool
And filled the filled tank up. I have 2,200 bucks. All right, I can mix do some upgrades
What do I want drill hull?
engine
Cargo bay, right which one 25 or 15
Or 25. No, you fuel fuel fuel fuel
idiom tank
25 liters. Oh
I'm going back down. Oh what I was being so careful
Alright, we're getting to it. Alright, that's new. This is blue onium
platinum the gold
Shit get it. I don't think I can I missed it. No
Shit. Alright, I gotta go back
Wired a bonus. Hey, holy shit. Go back. That's 3,200 bucks
Hope I can get out of here, right?
Don't explode
All right. We're good. Wait minerals
750 that's pretty good
Worth a lot. All right. What do I want our go?
Radiator was a radiator do get a better hole. Okay, what about a drill? Yeah this one
Nice, I gotta go all the way down. Is there a fast travel eventually or something? Just dig down
Why are you digging on the opposite of the world?
I don't know still sucks. How is this drill any better than what I had? It's the same exact thing. Just one block
Well, there's a lot down here
Go back. I'll be okay. I think I can get out. I can get out. I can get out. I'll be fine. I'll be fine
Get the purple thing. Not yet. I got something else going on man that I can be aware of
Right at the wire every time thousand bucks. Let's go
Save it. Yes, I will
Uh, can I afford anything else I could probably afford the new engine
Yeah, I'll get a new engine. I don't know if does but I'll buy it. Whatever money cargo, right?
Go straight down
big straight
I will eventually when I get some more money. I'm gonna just do this though. I'm already down here
Oh
The streams almost over. I know I know it is
I'm done 1500 feet and it's all just this white stuff
Why was all the expensive shit? I'm gonna dig straight down next time. I swear to God. I gotta like go
I gotta go. I gotta get out of here. I go. I gotta go. I do have to go. I have to go. I gotta go
I do I have to go
But I'm addicted to this game. All right next flash game night. I'm gonna play this like two more hours
Let me just save it and then I gotta go
Seven o'clock is when I was gonna stop
But it's ten past seven. So I gotta go
It was really fun. It's always fun. Flash games are really fun. I will see you guys on
Say look, I'll see you guys on I'm gonna be doing stuff the next couple of days
So I'll probably be back
On Monday, maybe we'll do something on Monday and then I've got some stuff to do on Tuesday and Wednesday
We'll go maybe Thursday Friday Saturday. Well, it's gonna be all over the place. I got there's a lot of shit going on
I'll let you know
Thanks for watching as always everybody
We'll see you
We'll see you on on Monday. Have a good weekend. Hope you have a great weekend
Thank you everybody. They hang a room next
This is something with a million games we have millions of games
Where are we raiding? That's a good idea. Let's see. Where are we raiding? We could go
It's a good question tonight, how about right somebody knew um
Somebody knew oh shit. I read. Okay. No, I said I'm good. Who's new or we could just dump everybody on a
Mmm, let me look. Yeah, I'll dump you. I'll dump you guys on Ludwig, you know, we don't worry
We're gonna hey, I've got we're gonna surprise raid Neanderthal like next week. Don't tell her. It's a surprise. Hey how
Yeah, he's playing minecraft. I was playing my version of minecraft. You shouldn't have said it
sorry, I
had a little wig and then
I'll see you guys on Monday and
I'll see you guys wait Ludwig and is ending his stream
He's hosting somebody now
Shit all right abort abort abort abort. He said he's now hosting somebody. All right abort. All right. All right. All right
All right. All right. All right now
surprise
Surprise Neanderthal raid. All right. There we go
We raided Neanderthal like four or five days ago. She's gonna be like, what the fuck are you doing Jeremy? Here it is
It's a surprise
Hey
Hey, hey, hey
Sit down everybody sit down
Everybody sit down. No, it's all right. I'm fucking fucking delete you
We were gonna raid Ludwig and it's it turned out Ludwig was turning the stream off. I selected
I'll see you guys Monday. I'll see you later. Have a great rest of your night. Wait, what they're you ending the stream?
Wait, what? What do you mean?