Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with the man vs. machine update for Team Fortress 2.
Now playing as the medic on the screen, I'm gonna get into some live commentary here in just a minute, but I do want to explain this mode,
because a lot of people still haven't been able to play this yet, and I know that when Last Night With Us came out,
it was very difficult to even get into a server, and we actually had to join a private match to even play the game.
So I do feel your pain if you were trying to play Last Night, because we all were trying to play, and it was just pure chaos.
Hopefully today, these servers are a little bit better, and that's... I'm assuming they will be.
So anyways, let's talk about the mode, and what I think about it, and how much fun it is, and all that jazz.
So first of all, guys, this is incredibly fun. If you can get like three, four, five, six of your friends,
or five of your friends actually, because it's six total, into a game, and get on Skype or get on Mumble or something,
you are going to have some of the most fun you could ever have when you load up Team Fortress 2.
Now that's a very bold statement, I know it is, but remember, this game is quite old now, guys,
and I'm happy to see that Valve is starting to try some really, really drastically new ideas.
And this is definitely a drastically new thing to Team Fortress, a wave co-op tower defense mode.
So it's very exciting, and what's also really exciting is modders, the future development of this game mode.
This could go in so many different directions, guys, and I just am giddy. I can't wait to see what's going to happen with all this.
So let's talk about the mode now. The very general basics of this game mode is kill robots, pick up money, upgrade your character.
That is the pretty much gist of the entire mode, but here's the real kicker,
and this is something that I didn't know when I first started playing, every single item in this game,
whether that be an unlockable, whether that be a stock item, everything has its own upgrade tree,
and I'm pretty certain on this that all the weapons fall into a certain template for upgrades.
So let's say you have a pistol versus a Mad Milk or a Jurati.
The Mad Milk and the Jurati will have the same available upgrades rather than the pistol.
So the amount of builds you can make are pretty much through the roof, especially because there's a character tree as well,
which does things like run speed, jump height, bullet damage resistance, fire damage resistance.
There's a lot to this. I am pleasantly surprised by this, guys, and although we did not get any new weapons,
all of the things you can unlock in this game mode with the Tour of Duty tickets, they are all cosmetic.
So we didn't get any new weapons, but still, it's an awesome update, and I'm sure they're working on stuff right now anyways, guys,
because they're always working on stuff, but I'm going to let the live commentary kick in now, guys,
playing with guys like Shibby, Boo, Italics, MLC Stealth, and John.
So enjoy the live commentary playing as the medic and go have fun with the update, everybody,
and I'll see you guys all soon, and of course, take care, everybody.
Oh, yeah, got them heels.
Yeah, you should always Italics before you before you charge in to grab like some money.
Just come back to me. I'll make sure to get you get like an overkill.
All right, sweet. Oh, wow. Oh, my God. It's got the bomb.
Oh, yeah, buddy, getting some head decapitations from the robots.
All right. Stealth. Oh, God. Oh, God. Just do it.
Smash people. Oh, they snuck down the stairs with the bomb.
I fall down. Shit, there's more, there's more, there's more.
Oh, my God. Heavy is dead.
I just screamed at that. Heavy is dead. All of them.
Wow, this is actually going pretty well. Still alive.
What if I get like attack speed with the Persian Persuader?
No, that'd be amazing. Last one alive. Lock that aura.
Oh, geez, man. Come here. Heals.
I got to get the next thing I'm getting is it is healed, right?
Definitely. All right. We're almost done with wave two.
They're just coming across the bridges. They're coming on the right side.
They're all sneaking across the right side.
It's all right. We got to Chris here.
Oh, there was one sneaky scout that almost got in there, but I killed him.
Heals. Heals. There we are. Nice mini centuries. There we go.
Excellent. Wow. Wow. I just get it from a little spittle.
I need health. Where is he? Where are they? They're all up there.
I took out the soldiers. I got a guy. I'm sorry. I'm not healing.
I just got to grab health. I'm going to lose this Uber.
They're all coming across the bridge. All right. Oh, shibby.
Nah. Get him. All right, John. Here we go.
They come right bridge, right bridge. Got him. There it is.
Money, money, money. Turn around. Turn around.
I was just like, yeah. Money. See you.
We're not doing so hot on the money collecting.
Back when Boo was a scout, he was just running in there.
So scouts are actually very, very, very useful when it comes to money.
Particularly good with bunk if you want to get all the cash.
You don't want to run behind super pyros. Yeah.
I'm not going to use it right away.
I'm going to wait until we get the heavies to drop down because those are scarier.
So now. Oh yeah. Now we're talking.
Yeah, it's Alex. Yeah, buddy.
I'm going to do it when these guys drop right now. Yeah, right now.
Oh, they finally got me. And I fell off, but it's okay.
This guy's just trying to swing at me.
Get the money. Somebody get the money. I'll get it.
Oh, I sacrificed myself for the money.
No, I'm a spy. Spy's general.
No, D's not stay alive. Oh, wow. I was clear. I couldn't get it on you.
I'm going to die too.
Spy is me. Spy is me. I was clicking on you.
I don't know. I think what was happening is I was running into the bots.
Like I was hitting the bots with the beam. They were blocking you.
Oh my gosh. Heavy weapons guy. I'm falling back.
Give me a stealth. Taking out the heavy weapons.
Get rid of that.
Get down there and get the money. So much money.
Where is it? Oh crap. Nice.
Ow, ow. This guy's got the bomb.
Spy's sapping sentries up there.
We're not going to be able to get all the money.
Scout, there's a bomb.
I fell down on them. Oh, they've got the bomb.
Oh God. I got it. Nice.
Should see how fast this SMG shoots.
Hacks. I'm just going to use it.
Just get rid of these guys so we can get our bearings.
There's two scouts left. Nice.
Excellent. No, give me a stealth.
So many scouts. Yeah, there really is so many.
I can only Wrangler with one sentry.
There's so many scouts.
Spy Boo, no.
Give her italics. Hey, heals.
There it is. Get the money.
Get the money. We don't see any money.
Sorry, we did alright. Oh boy.
Let me get this heal right even further.
One huge heavy with scout support.
You know what? You guys can all just get over it
because I readied first this round.
This uber charge rate is going to be ridiculous.
After I get this heal right.
Max overheal. I don't know what to do.
There's so much cool options.
They're spawning on the left side.
There's a whole bunch of them right up here.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
I think I should start the back.
I'm going to get that money up there.
That just startled the crap out of me.
I just used it.
Oh, John, you're going to get overwhelmed here.
I'm going to get the money.
I'm getting it. I'm getting it.
I'm getting the money. Oh God.
Oh, snipers, snipers.
So many people.
I'm crushing as many as I can
before they can get through.
Hey, boys.
We've got to get that money.
Here they come.
I need ammo.
I've got a dispenser up here.
All right, get it.
No, that's cool.
Everyone's out of ammo.
I have a hack and slash machine.
Jeez.
Are we going to get this money that's over here?
They're up here.
I'm going to get the money at the beginning.
Got it.
They're shooting so fast.
Oh, come here.
Get the money.
Oh, sniper taking my sentry guns.
Oh, ow.
Stay alive.
I've got bullet resistance,
so I'm doing pretty good against the scouts.
And I can one-shot them now.
Which is the swing? Yep.
That's pretty beast.
Smoke them. The hard part is hitting them
because it's so fast.
Oh, my God.
That's so ridiculous. Are you shooting?
You're shooting like six bullets on top right.
Behind us.
The mini sentry just destroys
everything.
How many can you have? Two or three.
I'll get that last 20 right next to your boot.
Oh, I got it.
Oh, sorry.
Money.
I have my ammo count at 600.
And then I'm getting ammo on hits,
which they penetrate.
I can just keep shooting forever.
It's insane.
Let's see what I want to do here.
Definitely this.
Scouts, medics,
super tank.
Definitely doing a refill clip
and ammo. Oh, wow. That's a lot of scouts.
Hey, buds. Oh, my God.
Get that money. Get that money.
Oh, stall.
Super heavy came down here.
He's not taking damage.
Yeah, they came down here.
Geez, Louise.
Oh, my God. Oh, my goodness.
Got him.
Oh, soldiers got him.
Scouts got behind.
Two, a couple of them.
Heals, please.
Where are you? There you are.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God. He killed me, too.
He's carrying the bomb.
Scouts and spawn.
Doing work on him. Got him.
Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Just body block.
Now there's a tank, right? Tank's the last thing?
Oh, shit, yeah.
Stop that tank.
So much damage. I'm going to give you the crits.
I'm doing a hundred per hit.
And let's see how much damage you do now.
And...
Oh, that's nuking it.
Wow. Insane.
Yeah, each of my swings was doing a hundred damage.
F.
We got an F.
There were so many scouts.