Good morning. What? Good afternoon is what I meant to say. How are you? Good afternoon or evening,
wherever you are in the world, how are you? Morning makes no sense. Today, we have an interesting
stream today. I decided to get Freddy Fish 3 and a search for the kelp diamond. Now this is green
screen movie night. Let's, I'm gonna wait because we need people to trickle in here. People have been
waiting for this for a while. So I want to make sure that I don't just go. Let's go. Hurry up.
Hopefully you have some something to snack on. Maybe I've heard some of you have made some popcorn.
Pretty cool. Maybe you've got a beverage. I've got a green tea. I was thinking about having a little
bit of alcohol tonight, but I think I might have to not do that because I'm sick. Still having
problems. Probably a bad idea. I thought about maybe just drinking like a couple of beers.
But it's probably not a good idea for how I am now. And how I am now, I'm still coughing. I'm
still having issues and you probably hear it from time to time, but I'm, I've been pretty good at
muting and muting the sneezes and shit too. So dude, come on. Aren't you like 20? I don't know why
anybody ever thinks this. No. Aren't you, aren't you 20? Okay. So here's what happened tonight.
If you don't know how good you're not, we've been hyping this up for like a month now.
This is green screen movie night. Over the course of the last two or three weeks,
we have had people submit videos using footage from the last three and a half to four years of
green screen footage. We recently, last month, or not last month, maybe three weeks ago, four weeks
ago, just about under a month, went in front of the green screen again. I did a bunch of weird shit
and there were almost a thousand submissions, almost 1000 submissions came through.
And I wanted to make a point of this because we, I got, I have to say this, right?
If your video is not shown, don't be discouraged. It's just, there was a lot to go through.
All the videos were vetted and put in, and we're going to do maybe two nights,
might be able to do three nights. So even if you don't see your video tonight,
that doesn't mean it was a bad video, right? That means that you might show it. It probably
will show up during an encore night, which I'm not even going to call it an encore night because
there are so many, so there are so many good submissions that we're just going to do this
twice. There's no way we're only going to do this once. It's physically impossible. Out of the,
I think, what were the total amount of submissions? Submissions? Submissions. Yeah. 800? 900? We'll,
we'll probably show at least a third of these or if not more, but I can't show them all, right?
Even if it's good, even if it's, it's going to be hard to show all of these.
So if you watch this tonight and you go, where the fuck is my video?
Um, don't because it could show up on the next one. And if it doesn't show up on the next one,
then don't be discouraged, please. It was just a lot to go through. And we had to just select
ones based on how much effort went into this one or who thought, all the mods and community leaders,
did they think this one was funny? Cause I didn't, I haven't seen any of these. I have not seen a
single one of these. That's a lie. I'm lying to you right now. I've seen probably four,
but that's what I need to say. That's what I need to say. I'm a liar. Well, I'm very excited. We have
how many videos are there? Let's see. Uh, there are, there are one, there are almost 200 videos
as of right now, still cleaning the playlist up a little bit. The 198 videos on this playlist.
Are you fucking kidding me? I hopefully can get through this in the next four to five hours.
So we'll find out. Yeah. The consideration for videos that we're going to be shown were how
much will chat like this? How much will I like this? I'm, I'm hyping this up. We're hyping this
up. I'm not just going to go guys. 300 million people have been waiting for this stream.
Divide that by like a thousand or 2000 or whatever, or 10,000. I'm it's been a long time since we've
watched any of these. Are you guys ready? It's been about the, I should wait for about 10 minutes.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let me wait for 10 minutes. Did I tweet?
Did I tweet? I did. Right. Just making sure I tweeted. Oh yeah, I did. Oh yeah. Hey, hey,
you guys, you guys ready to laugh? You guys ready to laugh it up? Let's go, go, go, go, go.
All right. All right. Without further ado, ladies and gentlemen. Oh, wait.
Sorry. Also the audio on these, we did make a rule where you couldn't have abrupt loud sounds,
but none of this stuff is equalized. So just be aware that some stuff might, some videos might be
way louder than others. Some videos might be at a certain decibel level. I have a limiter that I
can turn on. So if it gets to be too crazy, then we'll, I'll turn it on, but I don't think I'm going
to need to as of right now. Okay. We're just going in full blast. Yeah. So it's probably going to be
loud. Some of these and some have jump scares, by the way. Some of these have, they do. All right.
Some of them have jump scares. Okay. Thanks for the warning. Cause I, some of them have jump
scares. Be ready for jump scares too. All right. I'm not waiting anymore. Adjust your volume as,
as you see fit because it's going to, it's going to get loud here. Here we go. It's w we, we are T
minus two minutes away. Also be ready to dance too. Be ready to dance is what I've been told.
Remember, why do you hate EU fans? I wanted to like drink like three drinks of vodka tonight
to this stream. And I'm not drinking at fucking 10 o'clock in the morning. Okay.
But I might have to have to cancel my drinking tonight. We'll see. After like an hour,
we'll see how I feel. Refresh. Yeah. I did. I got it. You're a coward. No, I'm ill.
I'm physically ill. That did sound fake and it may have been. Okay. That was very loud.
That was a good test. That's a good test of the, of the, uh, the sound system. I'm so excited.
I'm so excited and I just can't hide it. I know, I know, I know, I don't, don't, don't,
whatever it is. I, I'm not waiting anymore. We're almost at the 10 minute mark and everyone's
already here. Everybody's here. Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to green screen movie night. The final of maybe two or three green screen movie nights.
Got to do it in a trilogy. That's how it works here. Here we go. I'm ready. Are you ready?
Oh my goodness. Begin. Hi. Oh, here are your friends. Oh, it's Otto.
Well, this is the fucking. Okay. I'm going to shut up. Hey, Dr. Spikes. It is awesome. Oh,
all right. Cool. That was cute. From all of us, banana bros. All right. That was cute.
That's a good intro. Let's move. The middle one's not even a twerk.
37 years old. I don't join. That was an original song, by the way, if you were curious,
it's called German's new friend. Oh shit. Please clap. Hi.
Don't splash me. Don't splash me. You can't splash here. It says it on the sign.
We walked in. Don't splash people. That was it. That was 3D animated. Hold on a second.
That was. Hold on. This was 3D animated. It's probably took like a week to render.
Don't splash me. Don't splash me. I love it here. It says it on the sign.
Don't splash people. All right. What's coming up next? That was so good.
German remix 10, part one, unlisted. Oh shit. The same person made them before, right?
Come on. Oh shit. I get it. This is awesome. Damn. Holy shit.
One, two, three, go. Oh Jesus. Holy shit. That was a pogchamp right there. Wow. Wow. That was sick.
We'll give the playlist at the end of the stream and everything too, so don't worry.
Wow. Pretty good start. Pretty good start so far. No cam. I'm not going to put a cam on,
by the way. People have asked for it. I don't want to mess with the integrity of the video files.
I think it's better that way. So we can get engrossed. You don't have to look at my
fucking ugly mug in the corner. I might pop in from time to time. You never know. By the way,
people are like, oh wow. Hooray. Good. That's it. There's 192 more videos. So sit down and strap in.
The sus experience. Don't let them see you. Find the exit. Don't die. Status hidden. This is a
whole game. Warning. Jumpscare coming. Heartbeat.
The soft part. I want to see the soft part again. Nice job. Oh, no shit. What? Dr. Clay.
No shit. Dr. Clay's a mod here. You don't know. This part is so dumb. I need to see this again.
The best part about that is when the gas hits. That's when the bicycle falls apart. That's
perfect. Well done. Well done. Well done. Oh, my God. That was funny. All right. Let's keep
moving. We don't stop. We got to keep going. No stopping. Be careful. Things could be loud.
I'm just warning you. The battle of Home Depot 2. Oh, God. What? Sire, get down.
I've been a Jedi agent the whole time. Get down, Sire. I have the power of God and anime on my side.
Oh, God. It's fucking Spider-Man. Why would Spider-Man be in this game?
Let's go. You shall not pass. Yeah, that's right. Gandalf. Always pick Gandalf.
Oh, my God. Oh, shoot. It was a Boomerang. Boomerang mode. Don't use that one.
Ow. No. No, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Now, I think, honestly, look, I'm going to work. I'm on the way to work right now.
We can we can talk this later, but I want you to buy any company that that makes makes
what the hell are they called? Tick-tock. You buy tick-tock. How do you buy that?
I can't. What? How did you do this? Seize towers. Topple them.
Wait a second. Wait a second. I I just hold on this. There was a lot to there was a lot to take
in on this one. This was it was a lot to take in here. This is my favorite part of the whole thing
is the fact that you put it in. Did you put a cheat code in to get a lightsaber or is it to
unlock? Oh, it's to unlock the jester. OK, sorry. I get down. I've been a Jedi agent the whole time.
God, that's so fucking dumb. That's so funny. Brilliant. All right. Moving on to the first of,
I would say, probably at least 20 Super Mario drug PSAs. That was amazing. My voice is going to be
gone. I'll deal with you later. Oh, boys and girls, it's a me, Mario. Let me tell you something.
If somebody want to tell you to take drugs, always say no. You say, Luigi, try to drink
and do drugs one time. And I said, no. And he said, Mario. And I said, no, you should never take any
drugs. Never. Mario wouldn't. Luigi wouldn't. Toad. Maybe. What the fuck? Don't do drugs.
If you do drugs, you'll end up like King Bowser. Boys and girls, don't do drugs. You don't have to
do them. Don't feel pressured to take drugs or drink. If anyone ever pressures you, tell them,
Mario said, so long, King Bowser, and they will leave you alone.
This is called Germstraction Do's How Bees Make Honey. This is Crash Box.
Distraction with your anchor person, Dora Smarmy. Good evening. I'm Dora Smarmy,
and welcome to Distraction News, where we give you the news and then ask you questions about
what we've just reported. So make sure you're not distracted. Pay attention. Now for our top story
today, how bees make honey. The female worker bee flies from the hive to a flower. When she arrives,
she climbs in and using her hollow straw-like tongue, she drinks the nectar. The nectar enters
the bee's crop or honey stump. She mixes it with important proteins called enzymes, which keep the
nectar fresh. When she is fully loaded with nectar, she returns to the hive where she pours out the
enzyme-rich nectar into a small waxed cell. We call these wax cells the honeycomb. Because the
hives are warm, a constant 95 degrees Fahrenheit, the water heats up in the nectar and evaporates.
What we're left with is sweet honey. Okay, now let's see how well you were able to remember the
facts and be sure to count how many you got right. Where does the worker bee get the nectar? From a
flower, the fridge, or rotten fruit? I don't know. The answer is a flower. In the honey stomach,
the nectar is mixed with proteins called bee juice, honey mix, or enzymes. The answer is
enzymes. And finally, bees wax, pollen, or water. The answer is water. So how did you do? Honey was
a pretty sticky topic, eh? Okay, so I'm a cardboard anchor and not a cardboard comedian. So sue me.
Well, that's all the time we have for today. But remember, don't ever let anything distract you
from watching distraction news. So long. This has been distraction news with your favorite
cardboard anchor person, Toro Smurmy.
Oh no, it's another Mario drug PSA. Hold on, hold on, we gotta go back. Oh my goodness,
this man got his son stolen by Super Mario. Okay, okay, let's check it out.
Bingo. This is in, look at how huge this is. Like, what is even in this?
What's that? No, no. You're doing a great job out there, son.
Don't climb that. Don't get down from there. Don't climb that. How do you mind? Don't climb that.
He's a maniac, I know, right? He's my son, right? Yeah, I know. You want, you ready for a dog?
Oh, I come into your house. You like to talk like you know food, but you actually really don't.
You're just a mean guy that got a bunch of TV shows and I'm not going to stand for it.
I'm not leaving. No, I think I deserve to win. What? It was a creepy mushroom risotto and you
don't have a fucking palate to save your life, you fucking idiot. Oh no. Sorry, I kept you all
waiting. They'd be running circles around you, by the way. Oh, what a terrible. Stop sign, stop
sign, stop sign. I'm going to use your wand. I might as well suggest you use it. No bluffing
this time, Harry. No bluffing. Last final touch, I swear I will not touch it again. Oh, beautiful.
Oh, that looks good, don't you think? You don't like, you didn't like my arm?
It's masterpiece, no? No? It's masterpiece, no? You know nothing about art.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Let me get a little closer. They're going to hear literally every
single one of these words. That one was crazy. That one was amazing too.
Oh, okay, we got Jerma attempts the Mario 64 any percent 16 star, but I can't wait for this one.
They're going to hear literally every single one of these burps. No, toast goes in the toaster.
Is that in the same thing? Is that in that? All right, let's get some walking.
Where is he?
Oh, mama me.
I'm running out of time. I saw you laughing in the corner. What's wrong? What's wrong with me?
When did I put that fucking wig on? I don't even remember that. Honest to God.
Mario? What?
Hold on, I need a moment. They're going to hear literally every single one of these burps.
I'm so confused. What's with the hair? Who is it? My mind from this one. What is this?
Why? What is this from? Why did I think this was a good idea from Mario? It was his real hair.
Oh, you were being a farmer. Oh, because of the overalls. Right, right, right.
Right, so you just, okay, that's really funny. This is, man, that's a fucking 10 out of 10s.
Honest to God. God, that was so funny. All right, let's keep going. Here we go.
Get it. What is it on my back? What's on my back, dude? Get it. Just get it. I'll stand still.
Just hit it with that. I'll hit it with a baseball bat. I don't care. All right, you cartoon monster.
Ah, hmm, hmm, uh-uh, uh-uh. That hurts a little. That's supposed to feel like that.
It feels, my whole face hurts. My face is burning. That burns a lot. What the? What is that?
Oh, my God. That was fucking wonderful. Jerma makes his musical debut. It's so scary.
It's so unhinged. No, sit down. Sit down. Don't reach that. All right, okay, you gotta stand.
Thank you. Wow. Thank you. You don't have to stand. Sit down. Sit down. No, sit down. All right. Okay,
thank you. Thank you. I'm probably so red. I'm like hot. That was awesome. Good work.
New cowboy western ass of steel. You look like you just got out of jail. What the hell is this?
Should have been more careful. You're welcome. You're very welcome. But okay, my very part of
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, spoilers. What happened? Wait, wait, wait, wait,
what happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? What'd I do? What'd I do? What'd I do?
Okay, we're good. My favorite part about this one is me going to pick up the gun.
This is the best part of the whole thing. What the fuck are you doing? Turn around. Let's go.
You're aware. What? Episode one. Here it comes.
I can't believe that happened. Oh, God. How did you pitch it up?
I'm going to put you in a meat grinder. Got him. Let's see where it goes from here. But yeah,
thanks again for watching. See you all next time. Take care everybody. That was cute.
This is German Lord of the Rings. You are not passing anytime soon buster.
You shall not pass.
Why did you turn off all the audio? All the audio turns off.
Oh, that's fucking funny. First Gandalf. Well, actually, no, we've seen two Gandalfs.
That's how it happens in the movie. Well, copyright. Let's go over copyright real quick.
One of the things we want to make sure is that we add a very, very transformative material.
These are obviously parodies and satires of these movies. Trying to get as close to
fair use as we can, obviously. Very, very transformed media. This is not a typical
Lord of the Rings. This is called German Noir, Murder on 985 Street.
Hey, hey, what's up, man? How are you? Yeah, I got a pot coming for you right here.
And it's drinking or smoking. Tell them with the hardest of hearts. No, I don't need to do that.
I don't care. Freshly brewed. There it is. Put your cup up. There it is. Give me your honest
opinion. I want to know the real deal. Tasty, isn't it? That hurts a little. Very good. Yeah,
it's very good. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Oh, shit. You got me. Wait, how was it? What? What the
fuck? What that? What was that? What was that? What was that? I'm gonna lie down. Oh, no.
Right through the birch bees. That was awesome. Wait, what? What was it? Thanks to Jerma for
providing all the mocap, even though he ripped the suit like 16 times and ate all the wires
like spaghetti. That cannot be confirmed. You don't have any evidence that that actually happened.
Oh, man. That's funny. That was great. Glue man appearance. Jerma is a wizard. I knew there's
gonna be a shitload of these. Well, class, it's been a pleasure. Absolute pleasure. But you all.
Oh, my God. Understand the power of the Dark Lord. And for that reason, I'm out. Just like that show.
Shut up. Holy shit. What the fuck? What the fuck? Jerma had an exhibition. What the hell? That was
so fast. What the hell is going on here? Oh, come on. I can't. Dante and Virgil.
Okay, I gotta ask a question. Do you want to hear my laughs over all these? Or should I just mute?
I don't want to ruin these because these are so goddamn funny. No, we want to hear it. We want
to hear. Okay. All right. I'll keep it on. That was Jerma's at an exhibition.
Jerma 95 green screen rare VHS recording. Jeremy Albertson as Mario. What the fuck? Wait,
hold on. We gotta start this over. This actually has- I'm Jeremy Albertson,
aka the actor of Super Mario. But you know what's not Yahoo and what's not cool? Drugs and alcohol.
If somebody pressures you into smoking or drinking, tell them no. And you can tell them so long.
So long, King Bowser. Take it from me. Have a pretty cool life, don't you think?
Swing your arms from side to side. Come on and everyone go do the Mario. Swing your arms
from side to side. Come on, let's go. Let's do the Mario. Is that the Mario for you?
Yahoo that one. Oh my God. Jerma in the middle. Fuck on his head. Is that the bus?
Why did you miss it? That's not the bus.
Ah, idiot. Okay, let me see the car. I can do it.
How are we doing? How are we? Okay. Easy on the gas. Easy. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You screwed that up. I'm not scared. You bumped his balls. Hey, that's crazy.
You're pretty dumb. I'm not scared at all. You're dumb. You're not good. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're very clear. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, right.
All right, that's enough. Oh my God. Mean mustache guy. Mean mustache guy. I gotta say that hurts.
I think that's very fair. I think everything I said was, you know, I was very angry at certain
things. This can't be right. Hey, I don't want to be that. I'm not the angry mustache guy.
My name is Sean, okay. I don't get it. That's what you can call me. Hi, I'm Saul Goodman.
And let me tell you something about Saul Goodman. Did you know that you have rights
at So Do I? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what I hear. I'm here to fight for you. Shut up.
Shut up. Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Shut the fuck up. Stupid. You're all stupid idiots.
You're dumb. You're the dumbest one here. Yeah. No, no, no, no. Turn that off. Turn that off. I'm
ashamed, Sean. I got, I got buns. I got ketchup. I got mustard. This relish right here too. Please do.
I've got a creamy cheddar risotto. Whose kid is this? Creamy chocolate risotto. And I also
He's going to Harvard.
Gravy, potatoes, meat, cheese, onions, tomatoes, peppers. Yes. Oh, I had a long day at work.
Let's go. Tasty, isn't it? Very good. That hurts. I'm dying. It's going to kill me.
Holy shit. Steven. That was so fucking crazy. I don't even know where to start with this
one. Jesus. This whole thing was just nonstop. It just never stopped. It never turned off.
My favorite part. Let me just go over my favorite part. First of all, it's, where is it?
Right here. When we get in the first car accident.
So you screwed that up. Of course he did. He's got a clipboard. Oh, caveman. And they're hitting him with the
I don't want to be that. I'm not. Yeah. And the principal talking about, I don't want to be the
one of my favorite things about doing the green screen stuff, honest to God is when people take
shit out of context and use it somewhere completely different and have it make total sense. Oh man,
different and have it make total sense. Oh man, that was good.
My name is
okay. Don't get it. That's what you can call me. Hi, I'm Saul Goodman. Oh my goodness gracious.
Oh my God. Whose kid is this? That's a double clap for me. That's clap, clap, clap. All right.
This next one is, I haven't seen this movie. So I don't, is this from the movie? I don't
know. This is from the trailer. I have no idea. But, um, this is apparently, um, I'm, this is the
audience reaction to this. Who cares? Well, I mean, I do. It's not a spoiler. What, what do you want?
Is this somebody who records in the theater? Stephen Strange. Wait, wait, hold on. You are now
called before the Illuminati. Our first member, Saul Goodman. Hi, I'm Saul Goodman. Did you know
that you have rights? It's warm. It's warm and time.
And finally, the most iconic streamer alive. German. I need five.
Yeah. German lied about TF2. What did I do? This is terrible. Nothing about this is good.
What is going on? Okay. Yes.
Oh, I'm going to get chucked up.
All your days are belong to us.
Oh, my God.
V6 engine. What do you got back here? Not as good as mine. He's dangerous.
This is so strong. I chopped you up in a meat grinder. The only thing that comes out is your
eyeball. You're probably dead.
In moderation, if you're old enough and you can be careful with it.
Alcohol, if you're old enough, be careful with it. Do you don't need to do anything else?
God, that was fucking crazy. We're going to be watching some more infomercials.
All right. This is long lost real men of genius Bud Light advertisement.
There's been some crazy ones. Hey, let's go. I have a bunch of queued up here.
First one seems very, very interesting. And I'm very curious how it plays out.
Non-specific alcohol brand presents real germas of genius. Real germas of genius.
Today, we salute you, Mr. Clinically Insane Green Screen E-Clown.
Mr. Clinically Insane Green Screen E-Clown. You could play video games like a normal streamer,
yet you let your unhinged mania take the wheel and twerk in a dollar store crown to an audience
of 20,000. 20K Andy. Your community. Hey, 35K Andy now. Not to share your horrifying
tales of everyday life, but you do it anyway. This guy is insane. Some may ask,
there's no way this guy's real, but unfortunately you are. This is a cry for hell. So crack open
an ice cold red wine, oh, King of the jungle, because your reign of terror won't last forever.
Mr. Clinically Insane Green Screen E-Clown. That hurts a little. That's supposed to feel like that.
Jerma joins the Cruelty Squad. All right, I've never played Cruelty Squad, by the way.
Oh, these are fucking great. If you've never played Cruelty Squad, whatever the name of this
game is, if you've never played Cruelty Squad, be careful. This might be a spoiler. And I think
the game has flashing lights, so be careful. Okay, three, two, one, let's go.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, okay, hold on. Jerma auditions to replace Jerma.
What do you got for us coming out here? All right.
So you're going to do a routine with the nunchucks and okay. Yeah, for sure. Number 13, whenever
you're ready. All right. That was a tease, but that was good. That was very good. Wow. Well,
that's interesting because if you think that you have what it takes to be me,
then you need to have what it takes to beat me. Because you're going against the master now.
This is incredible.
Okay, you want to fucking go? Hey, Jerma985 here.
Jerma, real Jerma. Real Jerma. Let's get this imposter out of here.
Hey, in case they don't see him. Good afternoon, good evening, and good night.
Oh, by the way, I think it's a good time to bring this up. So somebody had a submission
to green screen movie night and they were like, oh, is this okay? And we were like, oh, yeah.
I was contacted by one of the mods that said, hey, so somebody made this green screen edit.
It's way longer than three minutes. It's in fact, the entire movie, The Truman Show,
the whole runtime of the entire film, but you are replaced in every single scene.
And it's like, well, no, we can't do that. First of all. First of all, I can't do that. And second
of all, why? Why the whole movie? My favorite part about it, though, is there was a back and forth
where it was just like, hey, it's just like, I mean, I kind of went a little overboard
or something, right? It's like, yeah, it's the whole movie, dude. I don't want to talk.
Obviously, I cannot show an entire movie here, right? But that's all I'm going to say.
That's hilarious. It's absolutely hilarious. Let me just take one second. I got to make sure
that we have the right amount of movies left. I can confirm. Yes, Grump is DMing me. That is
correct. Correct number of videos. Oh, man. But that's so funny. OK, so here we go.
Jerma Psychotic Adventures in the Elder Scrolls Oblivion. Here we go. Oh, Oblivion. OK, let's start.
You are the one from my dreams. I've never played Oblivion. I don't know how this works.
I've never played one minute of Oblivion. Then the stars were right. This is the day. Gods give me
strength. Take me like three times. I'm crazy or not, right? This is two left hands.
Die, you motherfucker. Stop. What do you do? Stop criminal scum, right? Stop right there,
criminal scum. Is it stop criminal scum? Stop. You violated the law. Stop you violated. OK,
you violated the law. Stop right there, criminal scum. Stop criminal scum. You violated the law.
You violated the law. Now pay your fine or it's off to jail. You will pay in blood. Then pay with
your blood. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. What little patience I have is wearing thin. Stop. Stop. I
have no time for mindless blather. Oh, looks like you are in some trouble. Don't worry. I'll look
the other way and take care of that fine for you. Stop. Now that you've given us a taste,
you're going to lose this group. All this Gregor's want more. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's what I hear. Shut up. Shut up. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Shut the fuck up. Stupid. You're all
stupid idiots. You're dumb. You're the dumbest one here. Yeah. Now get to turn that off.
Sachet away. You're the driving instructor. Hold on. This is a real one. This one's filmed in real
life, by the way. We got another real one. You're the driving instructor. All right. Could you
pull this way and park for me, please? Over here. Parallel park in this spot right here. There's two
spots available. Not the one in front of the red truck. The one behind it. Behind it? Behind
the red truck. Use your eyes. You screwed that up. What you needed to do there is you had to.
I'm not happy about it very much. I'm trying.
You just hit it. You hit it. You bumped his bumper. You're not getting your license today,
by the way. Make that very clear. What I have here is I have two bumped cars. I have, would you like
to see the notes? I don't. You can see it if you want. Would you like to see what I've written
down? I don't want. Go ahead and look. You bumped a car. You couldn't go more than, you went 40,
50 miles per hour getting on the on-ramp to the highway. And not only that, you don't know how to
parallel park. And you guess what? I don't either. Am I on the right side here? Yes. You're pretty
dumb. Can I just tell you? You're dumb. Do you want me to stop? No human drives a car like this.
No human. You could get a chimpanzee in this car and you'd probably do better than the test than
you did. Okay. In fact, you'd get an armadillo to do this test and it probably would do better than
you just did. You get an ant. You get me an army of ants and get them up to the wheel,
four or five thousand ants, and I could train them to do a better parallel parking job.
You don't think I could do that? You don't think I could train ants to do that? You don't think I'm
smart enough to train ants? They'd be running circles around you, by the way. This is ridiculous.
Terrible. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign.
Do you see what's in front of us? You do, right? What's in front of us? It's a stop sign. Stop sign.
Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign. Keep going. Now what I want you to do is I want you to pull
that McDonald's. Very important part of your test. Driving through a drive-through is actually very
hard. It's a very narrow road. It's a very narrow part of it. It's hard to kind of navigate in there.
Stop. Roll your window down. Get out of the way. Yeah, I'll take two double cheeseburgers,
three McChickens, and a small drink. By the way, they ran out of my sauce. They ran out of my
sauce, my Szechuan sauce. That's all going on your record here. This is fucking crazy. Hey, howdy,
how are you? Thank you. Yeah, I'll take it. Thank you. Can you put it over here?
That was seriously unbelievable. Oh, God, that's so fucking funny. Oh, the fact that you did,
because the funniest part about that is that dude's just kind of driving around and just reacting to
this weird guy in his passenger side, right? That's acting right there. God, that was funny.
All right, this is Jerome. Here's again. Hello, I'm John Lugamy from Look At This
News Network. In a previous exclusive, we shared the heartwarming story of Jeremy Elbertson,
a man who had shown us his first time hearing in over 30 years. Wow. Half a year later,
we caught up with Jeremy to see what he's been doing since then. We set up an online interview
to get a glimpse into the life of a born again man. Thank you for being with us today, Jeremy.
Thanks for having me. It seems there's connection issues, but that's okay. Since we're gaining his
hearing, Jeremy has been working in numerous television roles, such as charity work for drug
awareness campaigns. But let me just be the first to tell you that, you know, it's not fun,
but it's not totally Yahoo. Drugs and alcohol. Stay away from them. As well as AMC's hit series,
Better Call Saul. Better Call Saul, spoilers potentially ahead. I need a little more. Pat,
pass me the salt, please. Thank you. Very good. That's a patty. Two chops coming up, two chops.
He's even auditioned for the next Spider-Man trilogy featuring Spider-Man
and series newcomer Michael Morbius. Oh God, it's Mormon time. Let's go. Jeremy has been a patron
of the local arts, performing at open mic nights, teaching upcoming stars his knowledge. He's
displayed talents in magic. It's a joker. Bingo. Here's your card. Thank you. And show tunes.
Misery. Every single person is my enemy. It seems Jeremy has been busy these last few months
and goodening the lives of others. We asked Jeremy how we too can end good in lives,
and he left us with this advice. If you're not feeling great, but you can make somebody else,
you know that you can make somebody else feel good and be like happy. Do it. Wow. Inspiring.
I'm John. Look at me. And this has been a look at this news exclusive. Thank you for watching.
With the first table already seated, Rachel seems agitated. He's not ready and there's hardly
anything on the menu. So he's not ready. I've never seen anything like this. I've not seen anything
like this. I only know how to make risotto besides that. I don't know. It's burning.
You like to talk like you know food, but you actually really don't. Oh, he's very angry.
Sire, he's angry. Welcome to the madhouse. Stupid, you're all stupid idiots.
You're dumb. You're the dumbest one here.
Is this normal? Yes. It's very hard to control them and that is a problem.
This nut has lost his marbles. This is so sad, you know.
Coffee. Hey, coffee. When do I get paid? Who wants coffee? Let's go. What's the matter?
Let go. You will pay in blood. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in. It looks like I'm going to have
to take Jermad to the nut house myself. What the fuck? The goo-goo nest ad? It's more than that.
With the goo-goo nest doorbell, know if it's a cycle, a corvius, or Jerma. Security with
goo-goo smarts on the goo-goo nest doorbell. Do you like drugs? Do you like drugs? I've got a lot.
Weed. Coke. That's all I got. I don't got anything else but you know, common.
Really, really beautiful lawn you have too. Yeah, I got kids. Yeah, we all get kids, right?
Look, if you ever um, it might sound weird, but if you ever want to hang out.
With the goo-goo nest doorbell, I've got paid either way.
Oh my goodness. Okay, this is the J-985 incident. My voice is already gone. It's only been an hour
and a half. Okay, this is a scary one, I think. The J-985 incident could be scary.
We are currently receiving numerous reports of hostile activity around the country.
A certain person has been seen near the places of the incidents. They are usually described
as unusually short by Psycho or the Suspy, but do not be fooled by its appearance. In fact,
it is an ancient entity of an unknown origin that has already been known to us,
but recently has started growing its influence and is becoming aggressive.
In the scientific community, it is referred to as J-985,
J for its ever juvenile appearance and 985 being the year of its first occurrence.
If you live within the highlighted area, please exert extra caution.
I'm seven, seven.
Hey, hey, what's up? How are you? I'm doing great. Yeah, I just moved in. Yep, new to the neighborhood.
Right. Look, if you ever, um, it might sound weird, but if you ever want to hang out
and just kind of do something, just you and me or whatever, I don't, I don't, I don't care.
Can I, can I come in? Can I just come in and we'll get some mojitos? I make an insane mojito.
You don't understand. I don't, I don't, I don't care about that. I have to come in though. Can
I come in your house? Oh, by the way, in case you didn't know, I'm the sus guy.
What the fuck was that? Was that the sus guy? What was that?
Amazon logo on the side of the box. Holy shit.
Oh my God. That, that was crazy. Very good. Very good. All right. This is a Super Derma
64. Derma's amazing adventure. The Mario ones have been legit so far. So window jump. Yeah.
I, I, that got me off guard. Okay. Here we go.
Okie dokie. Oh, ha ha. Oh, hee hee. Oh, bingo. Oh, ha ha. Hee hee. Oh.
Hey Toad. Oh no. Oh no. Mario need an alibi.
Come on, let's go. Let's do a little Mario. Oh, just here I go. Oh, I love cookie. Oh, cookie.
Okie dokie. Cookies? What am I talking about?
You can't stop me from doing drugs.
Oh, that was great.
What's next? Saw, saw 22. That's okay. Here we go.
There's a key inside of your eyeball. You need to dig it up with your bare hands and then eat it
and then shit it out. When you shit it out, then only then can you use the key
to unlock the bear trap that's around John's neck.
John, John, John, John, John, John, John, John. Wait, wait, wait. How did he get in here?
How did he get in here? How did he get in here? You're not supposed to be able to get in here.
Ow. Ow. No. No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Make your choice. Your choice is you can kill me.
Hi everyone. My name is Sean Elvington. I'm the actor, writer, director, producer,
and main talent of the daytime television show. Jigsaw is here.
And I just have something very important that we all have to do. We have to make choices.
And one choice is for you to watch this show because the ratings have been very poor
and I believe that we are below reruns of infomercials at this point.
So I figured we could give you a quick little like maybe you could watch the show if you want.
For the six to seven hundred of you that do watch the show, thank you so much. It means a lot.
Cast and crew, we have to put a lot of time into this show.
So we'll get back to it though. Let's get back to your regularly scheduled programming of
Jigsaw's coming for you. Written and directed, starring, and produced by me, Sean Elvington.
Oh my God, that was fucking great. How did he get in here?
Oh, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful work. Germaland, a lost episode.
You got another cart back there. You're gonna have to bring it in.
Right. Look, I don't, I don't, I don't care. I don't, I don't, I don't,
I don't care about that. Call somebody else. That's not, I'm literally just here trying to work.
Why are you, why are you telling me this? Why are you telling me this? I don't want,
I don't want to hear this. I put up with these fucking people. I swear to God, just screaming
at me. See, that's it. That's, that's $49. Yeah, put your card in. It goes the other way.
It goes the other way. The card reader, it goes the other way. You have a chip on it, right?
You have a chip. The chip goes, chip facing in. How many stores have you been to in your whole life
that you don't know the chip goes the other way? So mean. That was cute. That was cute.
All right, what we got next? Remember the X-Wing pilot, Reed E.
Hey, maybe you could get us, maybe get us a few rounds and we're done with this,
you know what I'm saying? Holy shit.
Deepest, darkest, like Star Wars fantasies.
Watch your status. Watch out, watch out, TIE fighters, TIE fighters coming in.
Left side, right side. I can't see him, I can't get him, I can't get him, I can't see him.
This is crazy.
Paper, Jerma? Jerma's Big Adventure, wait, hold on a minute.
Jerma's Big Adventure 2 development reveal. Wait, what? What?
Real game. What? Holy shit, this is insane. We've seen a few games come through here.
We've seen probably like five to 10 games and they're all awesome. Damn, actually awesome.
Jerma's Big Adventure 2 now in development. Wow, hell yeah.
There's other games that I have not shown. There's just, honestly, there's just so much.
Wait a minute, what the hell was that? That was terrifying.
But what I was going to say is people in this community are so creative
that so much shit like this comes out. It's just, it's just hard to even believe sometimes.
So there's other things, other games that have been in development that
are kind of focused on the community that I have not even shown yet.
I haven't, you haven't even seen it. Really, really cool, really cool stuff.
Here comes Spider-Man 4 teaser trailer. Very real, emotional.
Here comes, this is going to be probably Spider-Man spoilers for the, you know, you know the deal.
But I did put on the Spider-Man suit, so here we go.
Have you crashed your computer?
I'm here to tell you that you have a choice to make, not do the makeshift.
Excuse me, fucking Peter Parker just showed up.
Oh, you have an idea of who you're dealing with? All right, Spider-Man.
Who's that new man?
There is nothing out there like the Turbo Quicker.
Oh, I can't wait for this one. Why was Saul in that movie?
Right, why did Saul have to be in that movie? Oh, again, Peter.
Oh, man. All right, this is, that was great.
This is fucking hilarious.
Kathy Mitchell's Turbo Cooker, featuring real testimonials.
Okay, let's go.
Because there's nothing out there like the Turbo Cooker,
we decided to give Turbo Cookers to a number of people to use in their own homes.
Let's hear what they had to say.
I can take frozen meat out of the freezer, frozen vegetables out of the freezer,
and have a meal ready in 15 or 20 minutes.
It's healthy, it's good, and it's good for me.
You can really minimize the amount of oil that you use in cooking.
Well, I mean, ever since I was on my own, I, you know, started to cook for myself.
Ever since I was on my own, and I learned how to make mushroom risotto, and yeah.
You get the properties of the frying, and you get this remarkable tenderness to the meat.
I never thought that you could steam a cake on the top of the stove,
and it turned out so moist better than anything I've ever had.
And that's what my mom taught me, you know.
I call her every Sunday.
It's just easier, it's much healthier, and it brings everything together.
I like to be able to taste the food that you've just eaten,
and have that flavor come through.
So I would much rather do it this way here than to use all that oil to cook it.
I may have undercooked it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Kathy, thank you, thank you, thank you for bringing us the turbo cooker.
This is great, it's a complete system.
It's never going to leave our stove tops.
Never.
You knew I wanted it.
The incredible turbo cooker.
There is nothing out there like the turbo.
The whole point with these products is you can't fuck it up.
You put a steak in, and you come back in six minutes, and it's done.
You can't undercook something.
These things are foolproof.
You can't mess it up.
I may have undercooked it.
Oh my god, Jesus Christ.
All right, let's keep going.
This one is a Spider-Man versus Jigsaw.
Here we go.
It's me, Jigsaw.
You have no idea who you're dealing with?
I'm Spider-Man.
Six weeks ago, you had over 40 Pornhub tabs open at the same time.
And you crashed your computer.
So now you have 40 computers with 40 different porn videos on them.
40 separate pornography videos.
You need to go and close them all before the knock on the door of your mother.
I usually, I thought I...
Find you.
You have one minute.
One minute?
Make your choice.
I got one minute.
All right, I got one minute on a clock.
I can do this.
All these computers here?
Okay.
All right.
Now, clock's going on now.
Which one?
Which one do I start with?
First, this one over here.
I'm going to hack into that.
Oh, by the way, Peter, forgot to mention.
I know you only have 45 seconds left.
The room is about to fill with gas, nerd gas.
Got it, got it, got it, got it.
Oh, I know nerd gas very well.
I said nerd gas install one through five.
Will you be able to succeed?
I did what you wanted.
I shut them all off.
Oh, you did it.
You did it.
Hey, he did it.
You actually did it.
I did it.
Steve, what's your name again?
I forget.
Good job.
Go through the door.
Go out the door.
You did it.
How did he get in here?
You're not supposed to be able to get in here.
Ow, ouch.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You didn't make your choice.
Your choice is to be killed.
Dude, all right, I have a question.
Why has nobody actually made it a lightsaber?
It's just nobody has put the the light blade at the end.
It's just a stick.
You let you open the door.
That's so ridiculous.
I need to do that again.
How did he get in here?
You're not supposed to be able to get in here!
Ow!
No, no, no, no, no!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
You didn't make your choice.
Your choice is to be killed.
What was the- there was a part in the beginning
that was funny too.
God damn it.
That was a good one.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, thank you.
Thanks for coming out.
We got a new song that we're going to play for you here.
Hi there.
Alright, yeah, we're going to play a new song.
This one is something we've been working on for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy it.
It's going to be peppy, it's going to be a lot of upbeat,
so hopefully see somebody out there dancing.
And a one, two,
a one, two, three, four.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is hot, how does it go?
Hello, my baby.
No, I can't, you do it.
I get nervous when we're on a frog.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
I got it.
What will I do?
Check your seat.
Fucking god damn it, it was so close.
It was so close!
Oh my god.
Arjo, huh?
Wait, how was it?
Okay, I can try one more time.
Switch controller.
Oh my god.
Stop.
I've never played Oblivion, I don't know how this works.
I've never played one minute of Oblivion.
No, I streamed like a day.
Yo, it's a me, Mario.
Oh, okie dokie.
Oh, haha.
Oh, hee hee.
Oh, bingo.
Oh, haha, hee hee.
Oh, where's Luigi?
Where's Luigi?
I love all the Mario ones.
They're like so fun.
Ok, I think it's on.
Uh oh.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
I'm fucking done with this job.
I'm never fucking doing Mario ever again.
Boat rage.
I learned this one when I was traveling.
Oh no.
Please come.
Don't splash me.
Throw him out. He splashed me with water.
Splashing, you can't splash here.
It says it on the sign before we walked in.
I'm getting away from him.
Those of you that want to hear
another song, follow me please.
This one's called the train tracks.
No, I don't care.
What'd I get?
That's a big one.
I'll get one more out there.
That's a big one right here.
That's a huge one.
I always have to be traveling.
That was awesome by the way.
Oh shit.
It's wrapping for this one.
That was awesome.
That was fucking awesome.
Wow. Nice work.
Germania 2022 character reveal.
Madness update out now.
Wonder what that means.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the second ever
Germa Roman.
I hope you're ready for some newcomers
as well as some old vagabonds.
The cave grew into groceries in a good world.
That's what he typically does.
Tell them you're the sus guy.
Brrram, brrram, brrram.
I must find out what happened.
I must uncover the secrets
of my old family.
The secrets.
Oh my god.
No, no, no, no.
I see something horrible.
I'm close.
Damn.
Holy shit. Hold on a second.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. We gotta go back.
I wanna see that combo.
That combo was sick.
Look at this, watch this combo.
I must find out what happened.
I must uncover the secrets
of my old family.
The secrets, the secrets.
Oh no, no, no.
I see something horrible.
I'm close.
Dude, that was awesome.
Alright, we're gonna exit.
It has to be a big shot.
Deltarune.
Damn.
That was awesome.
Dump truck studios.
Holy smokes.
The mod chat is lighting up here.
How did some of you guys
do this shit in two weeks?
You know what I mean? Some of you made these in
four days. Huh?
Unbelievable. Alright, after this one we're gonna take
a quick intermission. I'm gonna go pee. I'm gonna refill
my water and I might
get a little bit of an alcoholic beverage.
This is a German 95 RPG.
I wonder, I'm curious.
Are you ready? Bald coins.
Got it. Auto. Auto.
The giant rat.
Alright, you cartoon monster.
Okay, now I kill you.
You shall not pass.
I can't just stand here all day, dude.
That one is bad.
Let's go. Look at me right now.
I won.
Nice. That was awesome.
Alright, one more. One more and we'll take a
pee break.
I'll leave. I'll leave. I'll leave, but
that's...
Are you ready? I bet you're
scared. I'm not scared at all.
Where am I?
What's going on here?
Yeah. Okay.
Are you ready? Because, I mean,
very clearly we gotta go.
You have an idea who you're dealing with?
Alright, Spider-Man.
Are you ready? You don't look ready.
It's alright. I'm alright. I'm alright.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey. How much?
Huh? You're the one with the money.
Hey. You know what I mean?
How much?
No, I ain't gonna scream.
You're gonna scream, though.
Did you know that you have rights?
I'm struggling to identify what the hell you're doing.
I really am.
It's Master Chef, not Master Bait.
Hello, students.
Welcome to the Defense of the Dark Arts class.
My name is
Michel Malfoyle. I'm the new
teacher in time.
If we could all open up your textbooks and go to
page 200, please.
We're going to be using...
Yes? Yes?
Ron, please.
There's nothing in here about using defensive spells.
Page 200, we're gonna be making a frog
breath potion.
You know all about that, don't you, Harry?
Open up your textbook.
I'm in the middle of teaching, Harry.
That's not the time to use that spell.
No, fuck you.
You see what I got dealing with back here?
Hello, boys and girls.
It's-a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something about
drugs and alcohol.
My brother Luigi.
Okay, nobody used this for anything else
besides what we're doing this for.
There's no way anyone's gonna use this for anything else besides
riding a fucking roller coaster.
Alright, that's enough.
Alright.
Let's take a quick two, three minute break.
We're at the two hour mark.
I'm gonna take a look at the videos. We'll see how much we have left.
I think we have another solid, probably at least two, three hours.
Let's go pee.
Go get another snack, maybe. I'll be back in about three minutes.
See you guys in three to four
maybe-ish minutes.
I have returned. Hello.
My stomach hurts. My stomach hurts.
Every time we do one of these,
I get an ab workout, unlike any I've
ever had before. This one is called
We're Coming Back. Everyone good?
Are we settled? That's also another reason why
I mean, we can only really do this
for four or five
hours, you know what I mean? Cause otherwise
I'm gonna die. I will literally die.
So don't worry.
We're gonna do this another one or two more times
and get through these. I promise.
Alright, you guys ready?
Let's bring it back. Bring this back too.
And let's keep going. This one's called
I found an old recording of Derma on
MTV. I wonder what
it is.
Hello, my honey. Hello, my
ragtime girl.
Send me a kiss, my
baby, my heart's on fire.
If you lose me, baby,
you'll lose me. And you will have to
load and tell me, tell me
the lie. Hello,
my honey. Damn.
That was some clean editing.
Derma goes to Mordor.
This is gonna be fucking loud.
Hiya.
Turn them back off!
My brothers!
We're going the wrong way.
I see in your eyes
the same fear that would take the
heart of me.
When the courage of men
fails. When we forsake
our friends and break all bonds of
fellowship. But it is not this
day.
An hour of woes
and shattered shields when the age of
men comes crashing down.
But it is not this day!
This day we fight!
We have bees on this planet.
Think about what a bee does.
Hold on. Pause it.
Alright. That was so
stupid. It sucks. It's not even
funny. What? This is terrible.
You're a bad editor hand. You're ugly.
I didn't say that. That's not true.
I didn't say that! Nothing about this is good.
That's not me. That's not me talking.
I don't think I'm gonna
skip this one. I hate this. This is terrible.
I don't know. This one's stupid.
Let's see what kind of a shot
you are, pilgrim. Take a crack at this bottle.
Let's see what...
What?
I need to see that again. That honestly freaks
me out. I was like what?
Why do I hear myself? My head.
An hour of woes.
This day we fight! We have bees on
this planet. Think about what a bee
does. Think about what a bee does.
Hold on. Pause it.
Alright. That was
something else you need to be aware of
is the balls here.
They're here.
They didn't edit these out.
There's just funny balls here.
Alright. That was stupid.
It sucks. It's not even funny.
Person editing this is terrible.
You're a bad editor hand. You're ugly.
I didn't say that. That's not true. This is stupid.
I didn't say that! Nothing about this is good.
That's not me. Not one thing. I'm not...
I don't think I'm gonna
skip this one. I hate this. This is terrible.
I don't know. This one's stupid.
Temporal up here.
Mario!
Medic!
Medic! Medic!
How many times you joined a server
to realize there was nobody in it and you
just did that for like 10 minutes. You refused to leave.
Oh my god! What the fuck
was that? What was that ending?
What the hell?
Holy shit!
I'm in trouble! I'm keeping an eye on you.
It's warming time!
Let's go!
A rose!
Oh.
It's warming time!
Huh!
Fucking Morpheus.
Try again.
Oh, these look so
good. They really are.
How are we doing? How are we? Good?
Driving school? You can begin at any
point. I'm gonna be paying a lot of attention
to what you're doing, by the way.
You can come out here and take a right.
Easy on the gas. Easy. Hold it back.
A little on
the gas there. You can
get on the highway here. Stop.
Slow down.
I'm gonna have to take off a few points for that
one. But you didn't signal.
You didn't signal when you went right and that's the first
thing that we're gonna do here. By the way, if you get
four or five points wrong here,
your license is not gonna come through.
And I am a stickler.
Very much so for these points.
Just keep that in mind.
You can merge over here if you want.
Slowly
merge. Slowly merge.
Way too fast.
Actually
too fast. It's a very big
car. Yeah, that's why I have it.
Just making sure I can see what you're up to.
Could you pull this way
and park for me, please?
This is the parallel parking part of the exam.
Over here, parallel parking
this spot right here. There's two spots available.
Not the one in front of the red truck. The one behind it.
Behind the red truck.
Use your eyes.
Do you want these?
Do you want to put these on?
I told you I was a stickler and I'm gonna be
that. Get up there in parallel park.
You hit it.
You hit it. You bumped his
bumper. Give me the wheel.
Let me show you how it's done. Here, you hold this.
Yeah, you grade me.
You grade me.
You go ahead and grade me.
Put the gas on.
This is how you do it.
This is how you drive a goddamn car.
You can go to sleep if you want. I got this.
Very nice. Pull it in.
Parallel parking. This is how we parallel park.
Be careful.
Be careful. Be careful.
You mind?
Let me go.
Step on the gas.
Step on the brake.
Step on the gas again.
And we're in the spot.
How did I do, coach?
What did you put down for me? Did you give me an A?
Get out of the car.
King Andy's evil reign
reaches far and wide.
He has obliterated his entire
bloodline for selfish gain
to be the true germite.
What he doesn't know is that there is
one left of his kind.
Who seeks revenge.
I'm not scared, though. Are you scared?
Yeah, I bet you are.
I bet you're scared.
I'm not scared at all.
Whoa, hey!
Hey, you can see the whole park
from here. Can you see?
That's crazy.
Hear thee, people of the parklands.
There is a dangerous creature stalking
the caves. Who is brave enough
to kill the monster?
Hello there, germite.
You seem ready for a quest.
No, no. No, I'm sorry.
No, I ain't gonna do it. Are you sure
you don't want to kill the monster?
No, fuck you. Fucking hell.
You see what I got dealing with back here?
You think I'm gonna do that shit? Well,
this mission does progress the story.
How? Well, I don't know.
This is the starting mission. No.
You do it. You go do it. You deal with
this. I'm not dealing with that. What are you talking about?
I may have caused it, but I'm not gonna deal with it.
Wait a minute. You put the monster in the cave
that's killed thousands of children?
Yes.
Jesus Christ.
Hey. How much?
Look, I'll just give you a potion. Can you please kill
the monster? Yes. I can tolerate
them when they're in small doses. Whatever. Just
take the potion, man. Thank you.
Oh my God!
No.
No. Absolutely not.
I want everyone to understand
that the king made a lot of good
things happen today, don't you think?
The jester over there, you're
so funny. How do I do it?
I made things happen. I raised taxes
on everybody. How many people did we kill today?
Sixty? Yeah.
That's a lot. What'd you say?
What'd you say?
Feed him to the lions.
Oh, Jerma's revenge on King Andy
was sweet. He made one fatal
error in skipping
the first mission that your monster
made its way to Jerma and hit him over the head
with a big wooden mallet
marking the end of the
Jermite bloodline and paving
way for the destruction of the
world.
Terrifying moments for a downtown Las Vegas
homeowner who posted this video on
social media showing the suspect
making threats. The homeowner
who we won't be identifying posted
this on social media and asked her followers
to share the video widely so
people could be aware that the man
is out there. At first,
you can see the man just not making much
sense, repeating himself.
Could I come in?
Could I come in your house?
Could I come in? Yeah.
Could I come in?
Let me in your house, please.
Could I come in your house? This really happened?
Holy shit. It's terrifying.
That is disturbing. Afterwards,
the man escalated things.
Do you like drugs? Do you like drugs?
I got a lot.
Just let me in your house and I'll give you whatever you want.
Bleed. Coke.
That's all I got.
Let me in your house!
The post-lemon neighborhood
and people all over the valley
shaken. That man has since been
arrested. What the
fuck?
Jerma Ware, Incorporated.
Oh!
I heard so many people use
the hee-hee shit.
Hi, ladies and gentlemen. I'm Super Mario.
So what does someone
look like? Okay, let me do some Mario stuff.
Brian Griffith.
Yahoo! Uh-oh.
I hope I can keep the viewers.
The caveman routine.
I love it's only shown up twice.
Boy!
Where's Luigi?
God of the game.
There's no way I fit in this thing.
Where are you?
Absolutely terrible.
I learned this one when I was traveling.
Jerma and Danger.
Brod, right?
My god!
I'm going out to sea.
Don't splash me!
Don't splash me! Throw him out!
He splashed me with water.
Don't splash me. Splashing.
You can't splash here. It says it on the sign
that you walked in. Don't splash people.
You don't want to splash
you fucking idiot.
I'm going to splash you.
Throw him out. Throw him out.
I'm getting
away from him.
Those of you that want to hear another song,
follow me, please.
It's not how you...
It's called the train tracks.
Going the wrong way.
Good. Good. I hit him in the fucking head.
I don't care.
The accordion just sitting
in the water.
Oh my god. Jesus.
Mario tells...
Is this a hare?
Oh, boys and girls.
It's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something.
If somebody want to tell you to take
drugs, always
say no. You see
Luigi tried to drink
and do drugs one time. And I
said no. And he said Mario.
And I said no.
Fucking god damn
****. Let me tell you
something about drugs and drugs.
Oh no. You should never
take any drugs. Never.
Mario wouldn't. Luigi wouldn't.
Totally.
Maybe.
****.
Get the **** out of here.
Sit the ****
down, Bowser.
Bowser.
It's
so stupid. It's jolly.
Your arms from side to side.
Come on, everyone. Go do
the Mario.
OK. You can do this, Mario.
It's a me, Mario.
Let me tell you something
about drugs and alcohol.
My brother, Luigi, would also
say this too. We both
would say this.
****.
No.
How do you do it?
She's looking at me like I'm fucking crazy.
She was.
I saw you laughing in the corner.
What's wrong?
Just cut
them together, OK?
This job.
It's a me, Mario.
I want to talk to you about drugs.
Boys and girls, don't do
drugs. You don't have to do them.
Don't feel pressured to take drugs
or drink. If anyone ever
pressures you, tell him Mario
said, so long, King Bowser.
And they will leave you alone.
No.
Hello.
It's a me, Mario.
I have to do a drug PSA.
OK. I'm done.
Jesus.
Oh, ****.
Holy ****. That was good.
The duck story?
A duck
walked up to a lemonade stand
and he said to the man
running the stand, hey
got any grapes?
The man said
What?
Then he waddled away
until the very next day
when the duck
walked up to the lemonade stand
and he said to the man
running the stand, hey
got any grapes?
The man said
Now **** you.
I'm killing you.
I don't care about anything else.
I don't give a **** about anything else.
The very next day.
Here's the duck.
This is the duck's face.
Hi, how are you? Good to see you.
And I can't imagine improving on what's already
my most used kitchen helper.
But I've heard improvement is exactly
what's happened. And there's only one
person in the world who's qualified
to let us in on the news. So let's join
my friend, Jeremy Elbertson.
You're just a mean guy
who's got a bunch of TV shows.
You're just a mean guy who's got a bunch of TV shows
and I'm not going to stand for it.
Free me much from risotto
and you don't have a **** palette.
**** you.
Shut up.
Yeah.
You're dumb.
You're the dumbest one here.
Turn that off.
The smoke.
So much smoke.
Where's the meat grinder?
You're dead.
This is Lucio
Malfoyle teaches the dark arts.
The defense of the dark arts class.
My name is Lucio
Malfoyle. I'm the new teacher in
town.
If we could all open up
your textbooks and go to page
200, please.
We're going to be using...
Yes, yes.
Page 200, we're going to be making a frog
breath potion. You know
all about that? Open up your textbook.
Wait, aren't I supposed to be Lucius?
I'm in the middle
of teaching, Harry. That's not the time
to use that spell.
Oh, oh, I killed him.
I think I killed him. Didn't they ever
tell you you only use that
spell if you mean to kill another wizard?
Never use that
spell. The book can tie his backwards.
You can see the little slot.
You're going to be floating in the air. There he is.
Down.
He's swinging around, he's swinging around, he's swinging around.
Down. Never use that spell
in my classroom again.
Well, class, it's been a pleasure.
Absolute pleasure. But you
all don't
understand the power of the Dark Lord.
And for that reason, I'm out.
Just like that show,
Shark Tank. Dude, that's fail
RP. I'm calling an admin.
Yeah. Oh, nice
one, Harry.
Almost got me.
Hey, Harry. See you tomorrow on
potions class.
Hahahaha.
I figured I was going to be flying.
RDM.
Stop.
Criminal scum.
You violated the law.
You will pay in blood.
Let's go.
You're in trouble.
Stop.
Stop. Stop.
Yes.
You know, I kind of hope this is the only playlist aliens find
in like a million years.
Don't you? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I hear. Shut up.
Shut up. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Shut the fuck up.
Stupid. You're all stupid
idiots.
You're dumb.
You're the dumbest one here.
Yeah.
Turn that off. Turn that off. I'm shave Sean.
God damn it. I'm a different person now.
Turn that camera off. I learned this one when I
was traveling abroad.
It's so true though. It really is.
Dude, I'll fall asleep with autoplay in a Karen
video. We'll just play. And then somebody gets punched.
Life feeling empty.
Is joy no where to be found.
You need yourself a brand new set of
old tummy cowboy cookware.
Look at that value.
Order now.
Getting on free.
It's warm
It's warm in time.
How do you feel? How are you
doing? Oh my God.
Hello, patient. This is an ASI.
I can't do this.
How are you?
How are you feeling?
Hey.
No. Mine.
Oh.
Oh. Oh.
Jeans on. You're a found
footage. Uh oh.
Oh no.
Mario speedrun.
These are like my favorite by the way. I love these.
We did so much Mario
content. I'm so happy there's like
50 of these. 7 hours and
15 minutes. Holy shit. Okay. Let's see what happens.
I'm gonna burp.
Okie dokie.
Toaster goes in the
toaster. Toaster no.
Toaster goes in the toaster.
Bring your
arm.
Why would you do BLJs with 120
stars?
Fuck out of here.
Fuck down Bowser.
Flex yeah.
German 95 show.
On TV.
I'm on the television. Channel 2.
Bye.
Pasta tonight.
Alright. Yeah. We're gonna play a new song.
This one is something we've been working on for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy it.
It doesn't have a name. It's currently
untitled so.
That's what we're gonna do. It's an untitled song.
And I hope you enjoy it.
Oh. Please clap.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
No. It was scary.
Oh come on.
Bowser.
I know what to do.
Tell you to take drugs.
Always say no.
My brother Luigi would also say this too.
We both would say this.
You don't have to do them. Don't get the pressure to take drugs
or drink. If anyone ever pressures you
tell them Mario said if you do drugs
you'll end up like Pikachu over there.
Somebody definitely got a bingo right now.
You've been waiting for the Jojo
intro. Bingo. Bingo.
Damn.
That was damn good.
It was.
Awesome.
All of these have been absolute
complete bangers.
Do not plank the blank.
Okay. I'll voice the subtitle.
Records of the simulation of the target's memory.
Advise watch with at least three trained
agents. Watcher must avoid...
Okay. I'll do it.
Oh my fucking
god. I thought that was in real life.
Was that in real life? What the fuck? That was in real life.
Why?
Was that in real life?
Okay. What the? Come on.
Jesus. Oh my god.
Stop doing that.
Stop it.
Turn on captions?
I think we can hear it.
Should I do it?
I'm about to turn off the TV.
People are too high for this.
Oh.
It's ruining the video.
God damn it. No.
Who's knocking at this time?
I gotta calm down.
That was just a dream.
I am coming. Sorry. You can come back tomorrow.
Maybe. Maybe next time.
What a weird guy. What the fuck?
Wait. Hold on. I feel like I've
seen that guy before. I'm keeping all
my lights on tonight. I'm keeping the
lights on.
What the fuck is that noise?
Someone trying to break in. I'm leaving this fucking
house right now.
I need to get the fuck out of here.
You got me.
That was very well made, by the way.
NeuroStory pizza floor.
What is it? German? NeuroStory pizza
floor, chef.
Baseball ass.
Hi, boys and girls. I'm Jeremy Alphaxson.
I have to reel it in
in 2022.
You know, it's not Yahoo. True.
It's not cool. Baseball
ass.
I feel like I hit my head.
Is that the law and order sound?
What's happening?
Where am I?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Hi, Bob.
Hey, Bob. I'm on TV. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Can I have the mic?
No, you don't have to do that.
Channel 2.
I'll leave. I'll leave.
Funny stuff. You did this.
You did this.
And you can fix it too.
You're a real piece of work.
You know what? I can't even
say it to you, but you know what I was going to say.
I was going to say
forget me.
So stupid.
God damn it. German auto
C adventure.
They're going to think I'm crazy.
Don't splash people.
Yes.
Terminati.
Thank you.
Good.
Hit him in the head. I don't care.
Oh, my God.
What I get.
Oh, that's a big
one. I'll take a picture of that.
I'll get one more out there.
What was that?
What the fuck was that?
We play at night. We stalk at night.
We're the rats.
What the? I don't know what that was,
but it was weird. I'm the giant
rat that makes all of
the rules. You want to duel?
You and me.
Come on. Easy. Easy.
Come on. Do it already. Come on. Come at me.
What the hell was that?
Auto.
Look at auto. That one was great.
What's your name?
That's so horrifying.
Quiet.
Here comes the car.
You're dumb?
You're the dumbest one here.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
Those pants. Hey, are you ready?
Follow me up to the office and they'll
finish your release.
Fuck you. Fucking hell. You see what I got
dealing with back here?
You were talking about me and my kingdom.
Just a little too, a little too harsh.
I don't like
you much.
This was welded with
dragon bone. I really don't
want you around here. You want to duel?
You and me. Dragon
bone steel. You don't deserve
to live.
Hey, look, bud. I'm an engineer.
That means I solve problems.
I solve practical problems.
Teleporter going up.
Ow.
My leg. Mission begins
in the century. Going up.
Good night, Irene.
You know, building centuries
sure is tough work. A lot of people
don't realize the amount of
craftsmanship that goes into making one
of these things. You need the right kind of aluminum
alloy metal. That takes a while to get
and it's very stressful. Look at that. You got all
kinds of scouts fucking with you. Can't you see
how busy I am right now?
Sensor down.
Ah.
Victory.
Hey. Hey, what's up? How are you?
I just moved in. Yep. New to
the neighborhood. Me. I love your
house. I love what you're doing here.
You know what I mean? I love this house. What's that?
Really, really beautiful lawn you have,
too. Yeah. I got kids.
Yeah, we all get kids, right?
Look, if you ever, um,
it might sound weird, but if you ever want to hang out
and just kind of do something, just you and me or whatever,
we have to get the families together.
Like, I would just come over. I would come over. I would come in
your house. I would come over your house.
And you'd let me in, right? Like, I would
come over. We'd do a thing. Would you be interested?
Okay.
Can get some mojitos.
It's like a purge movie.
You don't understand. It's so good.
You know the trick for a mojito?
Extra mint.
People don't like
the taste of mint usually. Can I come in?
Can I just come in?
Okay. Yeah, but I mean, I could show you how to make a mojito
the right way and not like
the way that everybody else makes it without the extra mint.
I have to come in though. Can I come in your house?
Nice netcode.
Anybody else have something to say?
Very interesting.
Are you ready? Yeah.
God.
They put something in it to make you forget.
I don't even remember how I got here.
I've been drinking water out of the sink.
This whole time.
Like, literally like drinking the toilet.
Like the water in the toilet.
They have like a water thing
here.
Like in the other room.
Sure. You're a scientist.
Pick up that can.
I said pick up the can.
I'm something of a scientist myself.
You have no compliance with it.
Whoa!
This water is
so dirty.
Don't splash me.
Throw him out.
I love your house.
I love what you do in here.
I didn't do it.
Really, really beautiful lawn you have.
Good. Stop.
Slow down.
I'm going to have to take off a few points without
what that was.
Stop sign. Stop sign.
Stop sign.
Stop sign. Stop sign. Stop sign.
Stop sign. Stop sign.
Do you see what's in front of us?
You do, right? What's in front of us?
You're pretty dumb.
Can I just tell you? You're dumb.
What was that? No human drives a car
like this. I hate coming out here
with bugs everywhere. I don't like when the bugs are everywhere.
I can tolerate them when they're in small doses.
But, dude, is
there something on me? Is there something on my back?
Is there something on my back? Just tell me. Get it.
Get it. Get it. Dude, get it.
By don't move, it won't
see me. Clear!
Sent her down!
You got something to say?
That was awesome.
That was fucking awesome.
Germa and the Germas.
Untitled bug song.
We got another band video. People are utilizing
the driving instructor very well.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Thank you.
Thanks for coming out. Yeah.
We got a new song that we're going to play for you here.
I think I just dropped a jam out of my pocket.
Maybe I should trade this.
Alright, yeah. We're going to play a new song.
This one is something we've been working on for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy it.
It doesn't have a name. It's currently untitled.
So, that's what
we're going to do. It's an untitled song and I hope you enjoy it.
Maybe you can help us come up with a title
after the end of the show.
It's going to be peppy. It's going to be a lot of upbeat.
So, hopefully see somebody out there dancing.
Okay? And a one,
two, a one, two, three,
four. Uh-oh.
Here we go.
Come to me. Come to me. Come to me.
That was crazy.
The songs have been
just so good.
They've been fantastic.
Walking through the woods.
Is this another real one?
With real actors?
Oh my god.
This is terrifying.
This show is brought to you by Grotto Beasts.
The exciting new trading card
game coming soon.
And now, a word from our
sponsors.
Are you ready?
Road Wireless Goes.
These things are fucking awesome.
They're so little.
You get two.
You can plug other shit into here too.
This is a scientist.
This is a real scientist.
This is a real scientist working
as a senior scientist at Road
Laboratories.
We at Road Laboratories A,
to deliver the best possible microphone
experience for all gamers.
We use the latest high-tech
equipment to assure the Wireless
Go can succeed in all areas of
usability and comfort such as
shock absorbency.
I'm gonna scream in your ears.
Hey whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa!
Noise compression.
And fashion.
All combined to give you the clearest,
pleasing sound possible.
But wait.
I know you're probably asking.
How much?
For the low low price of three money.
Wow!
Of course, I don't hate microphones.
I like microphones if they're
Road Wireless Go
2. The best microphones.
Am I okay?
Besides the fact that
first, be aware.
Hey, are you ready?
Are you ready? You don't look ready.
You know, this was welded
with Dragonbone.
Oh shit, okay, yep.
Something so simple as to go to a hotel room.
Two, three,
two, three,
three!
Yeah, yeah, I'm up.
What's that on TV?
Oh shit!
It's fast German purple alien.
German purple alien.
Hey!
Put it all again, Steve.
Why does that scare me so much?
To which we added the world's finest
resort facilities, a spectacular
amusement park, and succulent
seafood.
If you ever pressure, drugs,
alcohol, anything naughty
at all, say no.
Uh oh. Wait, what?
I have to choose it?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait, I have to actually choose
the video. Okay, hold on. I don't want
to spoil this. I gotta make sure I keep my place
here. I'm going yes. Hold on. I don't want
to spoil anything, but I don't want to lose my
place. One sec. Okay.
This is yes.
Alright!
Okay!
What? Oh, okay.
Alright, let's see what no is.
So this is no.
Oh my god.
What is that picture even from?
What's that picture from?
This one here. Is that even my face?
I don't even think this is my face.
Go on up next. He's logged into second
German, not the main channel.
You violated the law.
Finally, somebody has the lightsaber.
Guilty gear strive
German DLC.
It's woman's rights.
German F5 eye-witness museum intro.
What the hell is this?
Oh my god.
That was amazing.
Hold on a second here.
Cartwheel Jerma and Orange Troglodyte battle
for the origin mirror. This is a shortened
fight scene from a longer video. It's from a
dumb meme series I've run over the last two
years called Cartwheel Jerma
and, yep, wait, hold on.
This is the, oh, this is the spinoff.
Right, this is the spinoff series
from Fast Jerma and Purple Alien.
Well, let's see.
What the?
Holy shit.
God damn.
Gonna need a health potion after
that one.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, that was
fucking believable. That truly
was remarkable. Nice fucking
job. Holy smokes.
I tell you, when
we do Encore Night, well,
part two or whatever, we're gonna have to check out
some more of the Cartwheel Jerma
series. That was awesome. Good show.
No human drives a car
like this. No human.
You could get a chimpanzee in this car and you'd probably
do better than the test than you did.
Do you see what's in front of us? You do, right?
What's in front of us?
Stop sign, stop sign, stop sign, stop sign.
Keep going.
Over here, parallel park in this spot
right here. There's two spots available. Not the one
in front of the red truck. The one behind it.
Behind the red truck.
Use your eyes.
Do you want these? Right there,
parallel park behind the red truck.
I'm not gonna say it another time.
Get up there in parallel park.
You just hit, you hit
it. You hit it. You bumped his
bumper. Okay.
That's gonna get you two grades off, I think.
You're not getting your license today, by the way.
That very clear.
We sat down?
My name is
Sean, okay? That's what you
can call me now. Not angry
mustache guy that you see on
YouTube. Sean.
I'm very sorry. I'm incredibly
sorry. You want more than that?
That's all I'm gonna give you. I'm gonna go back
to being a good person. You just
wait. Good person Sean is
what you'll call me. Not this. I'm shaving
this. Good person Sean is coming
up. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I hear. Shut up. Shut
up. Yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah.
Shut the fuck up. Stupid.
You're all stupid idiots.
You're dumb?
You're the dumbest one here. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. Turn that off.
Turn that off. I'm shaved Sean, god
damn it. No, I'm a different person now. Turn that camera
off. Somebody used it. Somebody actually
used it.
Dude, I just got
a warning on my Twitch dashboard
that said there's a copyrighted song.
That's what triggered it. This whole stream.
Oh my god.
Alright, time for another pee break. I'm gonna get a drink.
I'll be back in like two minutes, three minutes.
I think we are, we're getting
close to a little bit more than the halfway point.
I think a little bit more than that. I want to see
how many we have left. My whole body
hurts by the way. Let's see. No
spoilers, no spoilers.
We have crossed the halfway point
and we've got a solid
another probably hour or two left.
This has been absolutely
hysterical though. These have been some of the highest
quality things we've seen
at least in the last three or four years.
My whole body is aching. My face
hurts. Real voice.
Alright, I'll be right back. Give me like two minutes, three minutes.
Okay, we're back.
So we're gonna, I'm probably gonna go for like another hour.
Hour and 25 minutes maybe.
Do like another 30, 40.
There's so much here.
I'm definitely hitting that point where I've been
laughing and fucking just choking back
here for the last three and a half hours.
God. Okay.
Let's go to the home stretch. It will
be a part two, don't worry.
There were 800 videos guys
and we're not gonna show them all.
We'll absolutely get through at least
two, three, four hundred of these.
I would imagine. There's just too much good
content. Okay, let's get
back to it. I just double tapped the screen
to skip the pee break.
Alright, let's keep going.
Let's get another solid hour or two in here.
Here we go. Next one coming up is Jerma's new
CSGO tactic.
I've done this before.
Absolute perfection.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
Fucking Wizard of Oz.
Oh, you wanna fight?
Don't fuck with that.
We're three.
We're all gonna put our guns down.
You think you can do me?
Stupid.
One, two,
three.
Wait, wait, wait. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
You're going down.
Sun fact.
He's gonna get banned.
Bomb has been planted.
It's not there.
Where is it?
I got it.
Terrorists win.
I love this part.
Coming up here.
We need ten seconds after
that one.
That was very, very good.
Well done. That was very, very fun.
This is super Jerma rumble
melee. Let's check it out.
Fuck you.
Burn in
smoke.
This is terrible.
Imagine an earwig looking up at you
and he's like
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Everybody hold on a second.
Didn't we talk about this
like three days ago?
Like four days ago? Did you do this in
one day? One day?
At the deadline?
Holy shit. What?
You did this in like four hours?
Okay. Well, let's go.
Imagine an earwig looking up at you
and he's like, and I'm like, oh, get the
envelope. Save him.
And I get the envelope and I get him
on the envelope and I put him outside. And then the
next day, it's like three that you see.
And you're like, oh, wow, cool.
Let's save these three. To the same
fucking soundtrack.
Oh, save us.
Here come another
50 in your house.
And they're all dancing in a line.
Doing one antenna, two antenna, one antenna,
two antenna, top hat, top hat,
top hat. It's like, well, 50 earwigs.
Oh my god, they're so cute. Get the envelope.
They all start crawling on it.
You get them out, you save them, save the
earwigs. And then
me lying down in bed three
days later. I'm drifting off to
sleep.
What a nice day that was today.
The second that I fall asleep
and I go into REM, they can sense it.
And two thousand earwigs
just make a trail up the bed
and just go into my brain
to this music. And they all
going in, digging in, like
eating pieces of my brain matter.
And I'm just asleep.
And some of
them are still dancing with top hat.
I love earwigs.
How did you do that in like
a day? That was awesome.
Okay, Jerma owes the precious two point
oh god. I hate
this image. That's the image that pops up.
It's just so ugly.
And minus fifty.
Don't get up, don't get up.
Can't be the one with
the new earwigs.
Don't get up,
don't get up.
Why, why, why, why, why?
I miss you a lot
for ever.
She feels like one.
Throw down that hole.
Hole, hole,
hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole, hole
bro, you're Should I Use That?
Dude, did you get that?
thank you.
thank you so much.
I don't listen.
I'm the only one that didn't say no.
I thought that was phenomenal.
I thought you did a great job.
I don't.
I don't listen to any of these jokers.
I thought that was great.
We've been working on it for like, what, two
weeks, three weeks now?
Well actually,
Sure. Well, my problem was it was a bit too fast. You see for Elise was wrote in for Elise
And it was actually really supposed to be a tender loving song that picked up at times like the heights of relationships
But also slowed down like the lows right and I didn't feel the passion come through although the notes did
Right. It's not good
He's got a point
number 14
That was a phenomenal phenomenal time of the piano, but after hearing what do you mean? It's not good judges
I only know what video game music is. What do you got?
Well, I mean, I just
Don't really listen to it. I thought that was quite lovely. It's perfect number 14. I'm so sorry
You got a great look. I think you look at the great. Look you got the look of the part
Apparently having a piano is an automatic no from like two people, but I don't want you to quit. Okay, what is it?
Who's this arcade? Joseph? Sorry. It can be a big thing
It can be a big
Shut up. It's arcade one day. Shut up. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, shut the fuck up
Stupid you're all stupid idiots get the fuck out of here man dumb. You're the dumbest one here
The best part is Ludwig saying Oh Joseph's arcades gonna be big one day. What are you?
Oh, that was great got another copyright warning by the way
They're not happy. My favorite movie is frozen
Okay
Yeah, sometimes I like to smoke down here
No spider
Spider-man
You know don't
What do we have here retro tech, huh?
So you're the spiderling your spider-boy got mad skills
Why are you doing this Mrs. Arc
Don't feel so good
Jesus Christ, I'm gonna it's gonna kill me. I'm gonna fucking die like on camera. I gotta relax
These are so ridiculous. I don't even know what happened in that whole video. What what happened in this entire video?
I don't even I couldn't I couldn't tell you if you paid me 50 grand right now to tell you
Anything that just happened. I wouldn't be able to do it. I don't think I would oh my god
That was fucking hilarious. Oh
SpongeBob was in it. I guess that I smoked weed and died. Oh my goodness. Should we do it again?
I think we have to do this one again. I think I think it has to be played again. It does
Okay, now finding me. No. Yeah, sometimes I like to smoke down here
Aren't you no spider
Friendly me clown spider-man any cash money for a picture of spider-man
Sure sounds like you guys are having a lot of fun on the friend team
Is that donkey by the way, it is
Hey, how about you suck a pot out of my ass
This part is so weird. What is even happening? What movie is this from?
What movie is I what movie is this from I never saw this story?
Submission army so do this spiderling your spider-boy got mad skills
Why are you doing this you
Mrs. Arc, I don't feel so good
No one has used this clip so far
So is this acting like this is a video that I uploaded like eight years ago. Oh my goodness
Nobody used the mr. Stark. I don't feel so good until right now. We've got we've done a hundred videos. Oh
God damn it. That was funny. Let's go. No, I'm not gonna play it again
There he is coming down here. Nice and confident nice and cocky. It's star
Real funny real funny stuff
You did this you did this and you can fix it, too
What a real piece of work you are, huh? Oh, you created everybody did you though? Sure
It wasn't me. I could have been up there. I could have been up there and I could have done it. Forget you
god
My head my head hurts you are a real piece of work
Why are they getting better? You know what I mean? Like what the fuck dude? Why are these getting funnier?
I'll leave but I that's so cool. You guys are here. That's awesome that you guys are here
You guys came here a lot
Maybe like once every few months description. That's cool. Can I can I talk in like hours? No, all right. Yeah, I don't need to
Can I talk?
Okay
Pasta tonight
What is happening they've gotten more unhinged as the night has gone on
What tonight I'll be okay with McDonald's soup
All right, they've gotten weirder
All right, okay already settle down
settle down
Hello
Yeah, and you can guess what you can hear me, huh? You can hear me pretty well
Not like it was before
What the fuck dude? I I'm not gonna drink it. Hold on. You guys are killing me. Hey, how you doing?
So not like it was before right now, you can actually hear me talking. I've got a little clip here
Previous times I've been in front of the green screen. It's bit you couldn't hear a single goddamn thing. I was saying
Not this time now you can hear me. And by the way, we're in full
FPS
Not 30 not the 30 bullshit
This is 60 FPS and I got a I got a lav microphone and I hope it works because if it doesn't then we're in big fucking
Trouble. Oh shit. I got a tweet
Does everybody hold on hang tight? So can you can hear all right? Yeah, I need to test this shit because I have no idea
How this sounds I literally got these microphones
Like a day ago. They were awesome 24 hours ago
They actually worked really well if these things work
This company's getting a major shout out road wireless huge shout out road go wireless, too
I mean, they were by the way high quality camera this time too
Genuinely that I mean that high quality camera does sound good. All right, hold on. Let's tweet that along
Yeah, so hopefully it sounds all right. These things are pretty cool. These things. Well, let me try a scream test guys
Right. Hold on. Can I scream? Can I scream in your ears?
Seriously like I'm gonna scream in your ears and you let me know how it is
Ready? Why would I not do this in front of the green screen? All right, ready? This is an audio test. What's up?
audio test
Testing the audio I'm gonna scream. So turn down your volume. I'm being dead serious. Hey, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
That was probably horrible. I don't I've tried. I just got these microphones like fucking a day ago
It's bad. Is it okay? I mean we're peaking but as I mean, is it all right? Oh my god, dude. Come on
Come on, you should smoke cigarettes. I'm not gonna smoke a cigarette. Is it okay, dude?
Oh
This hurts
The only thing you did oh you motherfucker
None of that is usable. Oh
Was he talking to so Mario can come off?
What's that yeah
Yeah, that's awesome. Don't you throw them in the pool?
Nobody eats the seven dogs, you know, I'm gonna eat one
That was pretty much raw that was a raw hot dog that I say there it is there we go
I would it's honestly I just like how long is this video? I was like we hit the three minutes yet
That's a big one right here, that's a huge one. Oh, I'll take a picture of that. Whoever's got a camera. You got one
Chair
The person that made the video
Responded in the discord. They said somebody said how long did it take for you to render this? They said two days
Why did it take you two days to render this? What the fuck? Oh, thank you. Thank you. Thank you
a
Rose oh I missed
We have to stop now. I'm gonna die on his chair. Oh
My goodness gracious. Okay, all the three times that I've done this they can do anything
All right, one more thing and I'm gonna clean honest to God. I didn't get it
I it took me three minutes to get it. God. Okay, we're gonna move on
You should do it in times two speed. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, let's move on. I can't do times ten speed
This is German German goes to Raven home. Well, let's take a break first
No, like I'm not gonna go BRB, but just let me take a sip of my drink
Who taught I'm not gonna sit for three hours and watch the whole vaude
Two-day render magic like your power went out or your computer crashed. That's insane dedication. Oh, let's go
Real funny stuff you did this
I'll keep my eye on you. You know what?
Can't even say it to you, but I mean know what I was gonna say. I was gonna say forget you that's better or get you
You're still eating that doesn't bugs everywhere
By the hate coming up here. This is bugs ever. I don't like when the bugs are everywhere
I can tolerate them when they were in small doses
But dude, is this something on me? This is up on my back. Is this something on my back? Just tell me get it
So many people use this get it get it. Come on. Just get it. Get it. What is on my back?
What's on my back to get it? Just get it. I'll stand still to hit with that. I'll hit the baseball bat. I don't care
Say it again man, say it again
I fear I deliver you to a darker place. May the light of lights illuminate your path
No
No, fuck you
Fucking you see what I got dealing with back here. Oh
My god, that was so loud. Thank God. Thank God. I had that down to like 50% on my equalizer here
Holy shit, that was so loud for me. I'm glad it wasn't loud for you
Jesus that hurts my head my head actually hurts now. I turned that down 50% for you. Not for me, by the way
I was sitting here laughing to
Leather jacket in the in the mod chat said that video the one before this one
That was five hours probably took like a two hundred dollars in electricity to render
Dude, they're getting more and more fucking unhinged, right?
Indescribable feeling we get and we go somewhere
Oh, excuse me in seat 1a we've got a farter here. We've got a farter in one day
Me wait me
That was it
That was the whole video just so you just so you understand that was the entire video
Indescribable feeling we get
That was it you lost 30 seconds of your life
Oh, excuse me in seat 1a we've got a farter here
And why would it be some random dickhead with a webcam on and sitting at his desk?
Who who is this person? Is this a producer of the movie? Who the fuck is this guy?
Why is this webcam video? We've got a farter in one day
Me wait me
Shut up
Wait be hard to
Be our Josh, did you make that one? Did you make that video boy? Why are you in?
No, what the fuck
Shut up
All right, everybody stepping up to the podium is Jeremy Albertson shortstop and outfielder for the Boston Banana Bros
Please raise your hand if you have any questions to ask him
Hey Jeremy Dean dingus from burger boy news you had a pretty rough day at the plate 0 for 5 with 4 strikeouts
What are you gonna do to improve for the next game?
Shut up
Shut up. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Shut the fuck up
Stupid you're all stupid idiots
All right
Thank You Jeremy
Hello, Jerma Anthony Banthony from mr. Green Gazette your team give up a home run
I gotta pause this because this is like an old-timey radio mic
I'm not even a press conference booth and that you had a shot at catching at the wall
But you weren't able to catch it. Do you think your short stature had an influence on the way it played out?
Listen I'll give you this. I'm not I'm not tiny. I'm compact
Huh? Can you give me that? Can you guys give me that?
Well, Jeremy it says here that you're officially listed at five foot two
I ain't five foot two five seven. All right. Sorry forget I asked
I've eight with shoes. Hi Jerma. You had a moment where you dropped an easy fly ball in the infield and
One of your teammates he told me that your manager BF bugleberry
He confronted you about that play and you allegedly told him to quote suck a fart out of your ass
We actually have the audio for that argument right here. I'm just gonna play that right now
How about you suck a fart out of my ass?
Pretty rude. I'd say I didn't say that apologize to your manager. No, no, I'm sorry. No, I ain't gonna do it
No
No, fuck you. I might have I may have caused it, but I'm not gonna deal with it. You are
Hello, Jeremy Rick Johnson from autos big news one last question for you. We have exclusive footage of you throwing up
In your dugout
after eating a whole sleeve of Oreos
What are your thoughts on that?
If I chop you up in a meat grinder, there's nobody else on the team comes out that's left of you is your eyeball
Okay
Thank you
German. Oh my god, it's so fucking funny
The Las Vegas Drew crew the day after this conference good. I'd rather be on the Drew crew
You know, it's not a gotcha
drugs enough
What happened
I want to talk to you about drugs. How do you get it boys and girls don't do drugs. You don't have to do them
Part of what we wear from those eggs. Oh
Yeah, okey-dokey
So low down
Here to tell you that you have a choice to make
Feel like I'm watching this in my head in a dream
Shit my pants here right now
Jesus Christ, so I take the driving test. Okay
Ready? I've been waiting to ride this one man. I'm not scared though. Are you scared? No. Yeah, I bet you are. No, I'm not
But you're scared, okay, it's a yellow so stop the game. Okay, you gotta make sure yeah, you've got to stop when it's yellow. Okay
Yeah, dude. Hey, I'm just saying. Yep. Okay. Yep
You look like you're gonna scream. No, I ain't gonna scream
You're gonna scream though
Okay. Well, this is really how I know
Oh
Okay, Jeremy you're driving on the road back on the road
Why am I spinning around on the side of the highway I got it I got it I'm worried you've got to turn around
This thing ain't safe man. This thing's not even a safe ride. I don't think this has been rated. No, you're not safe
The car's fine. Okay, drive back on the road now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
No, hey, what are you doing? Oh
Hey, man, hey
Well, you know what? I mean, what are you doing? What are you doing? This is a big drop coming up here, Jeremy
So I
I've not rid a roller coaster yet at all
Um, I'd like to ride a roller coaster if I could in in one of these maybe two of them
That's possible the go grill the grill and family gatherings that give us a thrill
But most grills are too big and bulky to carry around and who wants to use that rusty old grill in the park grounds
Would it be great to have a grill that goes anywhere with you? Well now you do
Introducing the go grill the foldable portable grill that travels anywhere you go
This spacious grill has a 5g bone capacity. Oh, the dating sim. The grill is so compact
It folds to only 18 inches long 13 inches wide and just an inch and a half T
On weighs just eight pounds
With the go grill you can barbecue anywhere anytime with anyone
Excuse me fucking Peter Parker just showed up now
You can be the MVP to your winning team make your tailgate parties a delicious pregame feast or grill a seafood delight
When you go to the beach, it's a must for camping or when you go RV and it's perfect for the boat
When you go fishing this look profile fold away grill tucks away almost anywhere
It's perfect when space is tight
You didn't say behind okay say it when you try buy somebody behind your go grill can make
Burgers sizzle all at once or grill 24 hot dogs for an incredible lunch
Does anybody want dogs?
No one wants a dog
Maybe you're the guy that likes baby backs
The go grill can handle a full man's-size rack the goat grill will feed your family and all of your friends
What do you like to grill chicken steak or lobster?
I have a creamy mushroom risotto the list never ends the go grill is the most unique grill
You'll ever own take it anywhere you go or enjoy it at home
You might expect to pay up to $100 for a grill this versatile
But if you called out your grill grill is only
1999 order now and we'll add this 11-piece stainless steel voice-over been edited a separate processing
Long with this it's $80 value all for the incredible low price of only
1999 so whether you see the bottle tuned only join friends at the beach the go grill makes grilling easy
It always within reach order now
You know I'm gonna eat one. Oh
That was pretty much raw. That was a raw hot dog that I say
This is probably the oldest and still intact
Burger King restaurant in the world closed
for over a decade, but
still intact
Bobby I just brought a fresh pot of coffee. Hey you want coffee. I just got a fresh pot of coffee
Peter Parker
Peter Parker, thank you Peter Parker's here. Give me that fucking job. Great. It's just some random guy
Let's go wait, hold on I need to watch that one again
By the way, lazy purple. Thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody watching green screen videos
Thanks for the raid dude find Peter Parker. I
Got to see this one again though. Seriously, Peter Parker. Thank you
Hey, I want more lightsabers
You know what I mean?
Like I want more lightsaber duels the jester had a lightsaber Peter Parker had a lightsaber
Saw had a lightsaber. Parker's here. Give me that fucking job. Great. It's just some random guy
Bat-chest
It's dumb
Okay, that was a video
Those are the really nice house I'd love to come in could I could I come in could I come in your house?
Hold on wait, there's a special message from mr. Giraffe. I gotta answer it. Hello
Mr. Giraffe, oh my goodness. I'm so glad to hear from you
Did you find that company?
Yeah, yeah, no, no, I didn't mean no I didn't mean to hang up on you that hard
I didn't hang up on you on one of your employees. No, of course not
No, I don't know. Mr. Giraffe. I don't want to buy Google stock. I don't want I want to buy the tick-tock company
All right. Well, you find me a company that is just like tick-tock then and buy that one then
Yourself yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I hear. Shut up. Shut up. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, shut the fuck up
Stupid you're all stupid idiots. You're dumb. You're the dumbest one here
Yeah, I'll get to turn that off and I'm different person now turn that camera
Jesus Burger King incident. Hey, German on a five-year
Yeah, I'll take a two point five billion double cheeseburgers
fifty McChickens a
2.5 billion
That no to to yet 2.5 billion double cheeseburgers and can I can I have no sauce on the on the McChickens no sauce, please?
No
They don't they don't wait. They don't you know, I can't do that here
Ah, I gotta go
Early man first ever fire. Oh goodness. I'm fine. Someone's using the caveman. By the way, this is definitely a caveman video
Without a single doubt long before homo sapiens began to populate the earth
Another human species had established itself across much of the Eurasian continent the Neanderthals
Fossils discovered during the last two centuries in the Atlantic Ocean and in Siberia have shed some light on these mysterious
Archaic humans I was in VR for like eight hours. Okay, that's why I look like that. They had culture they had
Social systems they had intelligence
Recent archaeological finds in England and France have helped researchers find out more about these early inhabitants of Eurasia
First stream my nose is like congested from laughing. What the hell happened to me? I
Don't I don't know. No, I don't know. It was pressure. Maybe I don't know. God. Fuck you. Stop putting that in
Yep
Hey, hey, what's up? How are you? Yeah, I'm I just moved in. Yep new to the neighborhood me. I love your house
I love what you're doing here. You know what I mean? I love this house
Really really beautiful lawn you have too. Yeah, I got kids. Yeah, we all get kids, right?
No, it's not weird
But if you ever want to hang out and just kind of do something just you know
We'd have to get the families together whatever that's fine
Like I would just come I would come over your I would come in your house
No your house and I would you'd let me in right like I would come we'd do a thing you would you be interested
No, okay
Okay
Can get some mojitos I make an insane
Here you know the trick for a mojito
Extra mint people don't did they did people don't like the taste of mint usually can I come in?
Can I just come in and we'll know?
Okay. Yeah, but I mean I could show you how to make a mojito the right way and not like
Let's see how you handle an old-fashioned quick draw
That's loud
My partner you tell me when one you you know your best behavior
Okay, nobody uses for anything else besides what we're doing this for there's no way anyone's gonna use this for anything else besides riding a fucking
roller coaster, oh
No
Yeah, dude, hey
Yep, okay. Yep
No, I ain't gonna scream
You're gonna scream though
Okay, this is really high no
Why am I spinning around
Dude, I got it. I got it. I'm all right. This thing ain't safe man
It's all right. I'm all right. I'm all right
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
Hey man
I don't like doing that. I feel like I'm gonna fall out
My sideburns a different length. It's hard to do. It's actually hard to get this right
You're a you're a fool's pen and teller
Let's go
Where's the bunny where's the bunny go I
Don't know where's that rabbit? Oh
What how did I tie it in a knot I don't know I tied it in a knot somehow what is going on
Rose
This next one's called sit down sit down and stop talking during the show this next trick is called
fire rose
Thank you, thank you very much don't be alarmed don't be alarmed don't get out of your seat
This is the greatest act i've ever seen
Here I go
Okay
Video game
Is this like an f1 video game? What is this?
This is like forza. What is this real life? This is a big turn
This is real
No, it is it is it's footage. It's real footage. Yep. Oh goodness
Okay
Okay, okay
Okay, all right jesus why oh my goodness, okay
That was insane jerma may cry 5
I think weapons within this cartoonish arsenal
Okay, i'm not even winded
damn
This game good
Did I play them?
Yeah, okay, should I start at one god an anime on my side
Hey, what is going on everybody jerma here with alien isolation?
Let's go ahead and go
Oh
Fuck no one sucks
That's him. Can I get away without him seeing?
That's psycho. I'm trapped in this spooky game. What do I do?
Oh, I guess I could climb in here
Achievement nice, you know, I love getting achievements, especially when there he is there is again. He's in the bank
Hey, oh by the way, it's just in case you don't know i'm the sus guy
Filming are you filming on tv? They're filming right?
You did this
And you can fix it too, you know
You're a real piece of work
You know what?
Uh, I can't even say it to you, but I you know what I was gonna say
I was gonna say
Forget you that's better. Forget you
Uh
Now i'm excited to announce kujima-san
Thank you, phil
Hey, konnichiwa kojima hidou desu
Uh, there's a game I've been wanting to make for a long time
That's something no one has ever experienced or seen
It's completely new
I've been waiting for the day when I can make it
Top you up in a meat grinder and the only thing that comes out and left of you is your eyeball
The crypto bros podcast
Gotcha gotcha gotcha. You thought I was a box stone dumb ass
Oh, yeah, remember solid snake with his like goblin booties
Rat heaven fever, let's go. I felt that one. That was awesome
Oh god, here we go
Open up your textbook
I'm in the middle of teaching harry. That's not the time to use that spell
Didn't they ever tell you you only use that spell if you mean to kill another wizard?
Never use that spell harry
And now you're going to be floating in the air. There he is
down
Swinging around he's swinging around. He's swinging around down
Never use that spell in my classroom again
The g-mod harry and you always were oh, I thought it was different radio different vertigo
Oh, hi
Uh, i'm new in the neighborhood
I noticed you have a really nice house
I'd love to come in could I could I come in could I come in your house?
I was i'm new in the neighborhood me and my family just moved in down the street
And I just was trying to meet the neighbors
Just trying to meet the neighbors. That's all
new salad fingers
I love what you did with the yard, by the way
That beautiful grass
The grass looks beautiful. How do you get it that long? I don't know if you give some pointers
Yeah
Can I come in? Yeah, let me
Can I come in?
Let me
Let me in your house, please
Can I come in let me in your house?
I had some dental work done and
They added extra length
Let me in the house
Can I come into your house? Just let me in your house and i'll give you whatever you want. I barely sleep
You like drugs? Let me in the house
bleed coke
That's all I got. This is a fucking tiktok video
This is a that's a tiktok video at this point. Can I come in your house?
Well, hold on you could i'm a pretty normal guy. I like jazz music. I like scotch, you know
Uh, not what i'm drinking. That's a green tea by the way. Why is this copyright?
I got another copyright warning here. Why the beeps? I I don't I don't understand that at all. I really don't
Are you ready? How are you?
Are you ready? You don't look ready
I'm doing great
Can I scream? Why are you I don't I scream in your ears. I'm literally just trying to help. I'm gonna scream in your ears
Put up with these fucking people I swear to god just screaming at me
I'll get a big back and then like a 10-piece see that's it two mcdoubles two mcchickens. So you have
Two mcchickens
10-piece nugget
and two mcchickens
That's uh, that's 49. The 10-piece is for the party
Why are you I don't why if you're eating with more than one person the 10-piece is to be shared with whoever else is there true
Look, I don't I don't
I don't care. I don't I don't I don't I don't care about that for the card in here
Flip it's it goes the other way
It goes the other way the card reader. It goes the other way take this
Take this from me right now. Take it from me. You have a chip on it, right?
You have a chip chip take it from me, dude
I don't want to fucking hold it anymore. Take it from me. Take this thing out of my fucking hands before I freak out
How many stores have you been to in your whole life that you don't have the chip goes?
Holy shit
Die you mother fucker
Hi, my name's auto
Let me introduce you to all my friends
Diamonds are forever lol
Unfortunately have to diagnose you with cringe. I only know how to make risotto
It's a me a mario
Let me take a sip of my apple cider. Oh, that's good stuff ever since I was on my own I um
Started to cook for myself. Oh, no
Bowser his bones are literally everywhere. I feel so bad for this dude right now. It's twerking time
Sit the fuck down bowser. They got kicked out of chef school. I didn't
Where am I what's going on here?
That you have a choice to make and it's time for you to make. Oh my god. Am I a good spider-man?
Everyone knows i'm spider-man now
Will you be able to succeed?
A breathe in the scented candle
Oh, by the way, peter the room is about to fill with gas
What is uh?
Oh
Here we go. I want to go home
Not to be confused with the real movie potion don't mind if I do
That hurts a little that's supposed to feel like that
I don't know where I wear who gave this to me
Don't mind if I do
But you know, it's not a gotcha
Drugs and alcohol. Hi everyone. I'm peter barker
Okay spider
No, enjoy everyone knows i'm spider-man now
We're gonna have to go underground. We're gonna have to hide for a little while
You know, you have the power to fix all this
Where are you?
Oh
How these are heavy
Sorry, I kept you all waiting made some adjustments to my suit
I feel like it's a little more appropriate
It's time to fight some crime
Let's go
God damn it. Uh
final remix
I love the rhythm heaven ones. They're so funny each one of these scenes takes like
Six hours to make by the way
If you were curious
Half-life two again
Jesus
What he's a fan
Going on
Okay, all right, we're gonna do one more
Uh, I think it's time to close this out five hours of this one more we got part two. Don't worry
We got part two coming. We're currently at
Uh video number 131
We've watched 131 videos. So uh, I will keep that where it is
Oh, we're gonna watch one more. I'm just my whole body hurts. It's been too many emotions for the last five hours
Uh, we are gonna play the last one though. I've been told please play the last one
So here is the final one of the night
We will be back, but we'll talk and we'll talk in like two minutes
So here it is. This is the last one of the night. Thanks for watching everybody
If you're gonna leave then see you see you soon. I uh, I am at my pretty much limit of laughing and uh,
The smile lines i'm developing on my face are huge. So I definitely have to go take a bath
Uh, this is the last one. I'm not even winded right here. My name is germo
To start doing 15 people thousand subscriber extraordinary our guys in germany here for the 4 000 subscriber videos 15 000 subscriber
I don't know. Oh spoiler
What a messy fucking room. Holy shit. That room was a mess
Oh, by the way, let me make this really clear i'm still alive
Okay, let's just make that very clear. I'm still alive
Are you done germa here with smite sunday, oh my dog just fought it
You hit a heavy man. Yeah, sometimes I like to smoke down here
Center down. Oh shit the giant enemy spider
That's somebody's asshole welcome ladies and gentlemen to the first ever
That's right, it's super mario. Fuck that. So it's gonna be the chicken and someone's coming from the rafters
Somebody just splashed off of the titan
Don't do it the real winner germa rumble live is the disco typer
Oh
Second germa something i'm gonna train and love that fucking haircut. What the hell was that?
Damn tricked you it's egypt and we're both vlog pyros
Uh, that was really nice, um
We got way more to see by the way, that was just part one part two will be pretty soon
Not I want to get through sorcery part two. So we'll do that first. Maybe uh next weekend save the date
Next weekend, maybe saturday, maybe sunday. Who knows? Uh, that was amazing
I know i'm a broken record
But we haven't even gone through half the videos yet
There's still so much more fucking awesome hilarious shit to watch and
God damn you guys knock it out of the park every single time every single time
I honestly can't believe it every time we do this. It gets better. The videos are funnier how
I would watch more. I really would but i'm i'm at that limit of insanity, right?
Uh to all the people that made a video anybody that submitted it. Thank you
All you hear now the 30 000 plus people that were here almost the whole night. Um, that was a ton of fun
It always is again blown away by the creativity and just what you guys can come up with with
Me just being a fucking random dickhead in front of a green screen. I I don't know what to say
That was fucking hilarious
We will return to do more of this next weekend. God. That was funny. I I can't even tell you what my favorite I
Have no favorites. That would be impossible, but i'm
Blessed to have a community that's this talented and this funny. I really don't I don't think there's anything like this
I really don't anywhere else and I mean that I really do thanks for all your submissions. They've been phenomenal
Uh, let's let's do it again. The next time I will be live will be
That's a great question next couple days. Maybe thanks to the huge
By the way, huge thanks to the mods and community leaders. They um, they vetted all these videos
They had to watch all these I didn't see any of these, right?
So can we get a clap for the mods and community leaders, please?
Because they went through the last week plus of watching these and getting some uh, giving me the playlist and everything
So i'll see you again in a couple days two three days. Keep an eye on the sus maybe on
Not sure maybe tuesday wednesday. We'll see but blown away again. Just completely mind-blown. That was so much fun
It always is and thanks for watching. Thanks for sticking around all the subs that came in
Thank you. Lazy purple came in for a raid. Thanks for the raid. Lazy purple. It's a good dude
Go folly, uh, go follow lazy purple, please been around for a long time almost as long as I have but yeah
Dude, I keep thinking about the five-hour vaude. It's killing me. Uh, let's send you guys somewhere though
I haven't raided anybody in a long time. Who's who's streaming right now? Who could we go to? Uh, we could go to
Hey, let's go to vinny. Vinny's playing half-life. We literally watched like 10 half-life videos
Let's go raid vinny. Say hi to vinny. Vinny was in like three of those videos videos too. So that's funny
I'll see you guys in a few days. Thanks again. Much love to you. Obviously. We'll see you soon
My whole body hurts. I'm gonna take a bath and relax for a day or two. We'll be back with more sorcery
Kare part two
Maybe uh, maybe some more multiverses. You might see that too. That's a possibility. Take care of yourselves. Good night
Thanks for sticking around. Have a wonderful rest of your evening. Goodbye. Call you mother. See you soon
Uh, I want to say also real quick the vaude is probably absolutely destroyed
I would be surprised if you could even watch it. So in the event that it's absolutely just
Decimated I might have to just delete it. It depends. So be aware of that. It's a half. It's probably muted
Uh, if you weren't here, i'm really sorry, but
Uh dmca copyright, that's where we're
Okay, we just moved to vinny's channel
All right. Goodbye