Hey everybody. We're gonna try a test. We're gonna try to do it again. Who knows if this
is gonna be functional or not, but I am, you know, I'm willing to give it a try.
All you can do is try. You guys having a good day? What is today? I've lost all track of time
has been deleted. What is today? Thursday, November 1st. He's, he's, there he is. He's
Well, it never really went anywhere, but we've, we've had some solid green
over the last 24 hours. So I figured I would try because we've been dealing with, obviously
Cox has been trying to get infrastructurally these problems fixed. And this is the first
time in probably two and a half weeks where we've had internet for more than like four
hours straight. So we're green for the moment. Let's see how, this could be 45 minutes or this
could be six hours. I don't know. I'm willing to give it an attempt though. And well,
we will update some information about the green screen stream. So you're gonna have to
stick around for that. There's some updated info. Here comes a 30 minute stream. All right,
give me, give me one second. Also funnily enough, there was, I turned on the PS4
because this is where I was Red Dead 2. And I don't know. I think the, the PS4 must
have gone into rest mode because we're at the same screen I was at like four and a half
days ago. So we're just here. I don't really remember what I was doing, but I know that I
exist here. I got to remember the controls too. This is gonna be fucking hard. Even the game was
waiting. Yeah. It's like nothing ever happened. You guys just woke up. We all just woke up.
And we're here four days later. We got 50, 50 bucks right off the bat from Pocket Pauling.
Thanks for the $50 Pocket Pauling. Finally, my dad is back from the war. Hey, Jerma,
how sad, relieved are you that you missed the Red Sox parade? Oh yeah, the Red Sox won
the World Series. That's right. That happened. What else has happened in the time that I haven't
been awake? I mean streaming, you know, Red Sox won the World Series. Super Smash Brothers
is coming out and they did a direct today. And excuse me. Excuse me. Where's my favorite
fucking character? Excuse me. Plant? Oh, I thought you guys were calling me a plant.
Well, I don't want to give any spoilers for people that haven't watched the direct,
but I'm missing somebody real important there, I think. Jerma's a plant. That's right. I'm
working. I'm working for him. Minecraft Steve. No, no way. What do you mean I wouldn't let
that happen? I don't work for Nintendo. No, I would never let that happen. This is not like
me playing Red Dead right now. What am I talking about? I would like I would talk to somebody.
Oh my fucking Jesus. Hold on. Thank you. Thank you. Jabba dab for your 10 community sub.
Thanks a lot, man. Thanks. Also, by the way, pocket Pauling. We didn't really touch upon your
$50 here. Like for real, thank you so much. Pocket Pauling for your 50 bucks and jabba
dab for your 10 community subs. And I think we I think we can go. You know what I'm
saying? I think we can just go. I got it. How do you ride the horse? I forget. Here we go.
What was I doing? Okay, I'm back in it. Is it x? I forget how to play. Do you just I just
woke up from a fucking dream. Okay, stalling. I don't remember how to shoot. I was in the
middle of the tutorial and I went into cryogenic sleep to get the train. You want to
head down? See how he's getting on? Okay. No, I remember. Okay, but I'm getting some
memories. Check on Bill. That's a gun. Okay. How do I take out the
doctor binocular? What was benign? Was there a binocular button? Do I do I go? Am I going
down? You know, I have to leave. I'm holding a knife. L one and R one. There we go. Okay.
Let's check on Bill. How's he doing? All right, put him up. Get on the horse.
This is I didn't even get to fucking do this. It's been four and a half days.
No, god damn it. Okay, zoom. Where are you, Bill? This is this what I'm supposed to be doing.
Guys, give me a break. There he is. Okay. Where's he on the hill?
Okay, there he is. All right, spotted. I gotta I gotta move my horse out of here.
Set up the detonator by those rocks over there. Okay, sure. Now just unspool the wire and then
attach it to said detonator. I'm going to explode here. Pick up the spool.
I'm gonna I'm gonna like acme this guy. You're about to get wily coyote.
How much slack do we have? All right, here we go. Attach it.
This is attach the thing mini game or what? Okay. Okay. All right. Now stomp on detonator.
What if I just jump on this? Imagine if it just fucking blew up.
All right, I'm going. I'm going. I'm going. Put the horse on the tracks. I just got this
horse. Why would I do something like that? I just bought the horse. All right, so I
have to detonate it. So I blow up the train. He says all fine. We'll soon find out.
Put yourself on the tracks. I think so. Okay, cover your faces. Train should be here any
minute now. Weapon wheel. So now we're looking for the detonator. The light.
I thought I had to like throw the fuse. It's not radio controlled.
Gentlemen, it's time. Good luck. All of you. You all know what to do.
I don't know. I actually don't because I saw the first part of this mission and story
almost four and a half, five days ago. Here we go. All right, that just didn't work.
Why are we getting off the horses? Wait, why would we get off the horse?
Jump on the train. How am I supposed to do that from here?
Okay, I've made it. Oh, running a train. All right, give me a Lenin. Pull, pull him.
Wait, oh, did he fall or did I fall?
Come on, this is what it's supposed to be doing, right? What? What am I doing?
Okay, I think I figured out what I'm supposed to do. What's the uh, okay.
All right, let's go. Stop the train. It's not TNT barrels here, right?
I like the repeater. I was going for a tackle. All right, quick. I got to need something.
Give me some cover. Wait, wait, no, we gotta go. What the fuck?
I just got hit in the face with a shovel. Reverse the grapple.
Is this Abe Lincoln? All right, give it the front of the engine car.
There's more. Right in the face. I have dead eye, so I don't know why I'm not using it
for some reason. What's the reload button?
Can I get like an ammo toss to me? That's it, right?
That guy. I need to pick up stuff on the ground. Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Is that a person in the back? Is that an animal? That's a person. Oh shit. Oh shit. Get behind
this little fucking slab. Wait, this is our guys? Oh, these are our guys. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need to. It's a rock. It's a slab. That's a slab. Okay.
Assume yellow tonic to fortify your bars. A fortified bar can be used for a short period
without draining. This tonic will fortify your dead eye. Listen to me. Okay. We don't want to
kill any of you. Any more of you. I give you my word, but trust me, we will. Boys,
okay. You asked for it. Five, three, two, one. Seems our friends have gone deaf.
I don't, I don't know what the, what the world war two plane sound was coming from outside.
Are we going? I can't rapid fire this time. Mr. Williamson, give Mr. Morgan and Mr. Smith
some dynamite. You two boys go blow that door open. Why don't we do that? Thanks bill.
Much to us, but you boys in there might want to take a step back.
Place dynamite. Seems good enough. All right. Here we go. Like the views. Here we go.
All right. Now step back. Unless you got a death wish. I'd step back, fellas. Yeah,
I did this. I did this. All right. Now go in and just start firing.
Blind him. Get on up and search that train. What's the punch button? I want to punch. It's
all right. Let's search the damn train. Look at this place. It's like a, it's beautiful in here.
You two got the safe. I'll search the rest. Oh yes. Should be easy as cake.
If I'm going to hide something, I would hide it inside the lamp.
Shut up. Me and Arthur did all the work. Yeah, kid did good. Didn't see you rushing to jump on
that train. He's king. I'll give you that. On receipt of funds, we proceed with phases two
and three of the project and present you with a detailed report of our findings within
the month. Yours, respectively. Okay, let's see if we can get this open. Now that wasn't part
of it. Getting there. What's in there? Cigars? I can't carry any more of this item. I need
to sell some shit then. Any codes? No, no codes. You can screenshot that and read it later if you
want. All right, there's brandy. I'm going to need to do something eventually here, food wise.
Can't carry any more of this item. Why not?
Can somebody else hold something? Money? That's money. Those are IOUs. No, it tells you. Bond.
Is it really a lock box if it's unlocked? That's true.
What did you find? These. They worth anything? Oh, sure. Bearer bonds. I think we can probably
sell these pretty easily. Oh, wait, is that Ethereum? Well done. Now, would you get rid of
all of this? The train? Yeah, get it out of here. What about them? What do you think?
I don't know. It's up to you. Kill them, leave them here, take them with you on the train.
Just make sure they don't send our folk after us. Wait, I get temporary party members?
Okay, see you back at camp. What do I do about these three?
We'll be moving on. The rest of you, let's ride. What do I do with my temporary party? Guard.
Deal with the guards. Can I pick who I threaten? Okay, get on the train. Quick.
Wait, I gotta get you too. Hey, what's going on? What happened? What are the boundaries?
Why are the boundaries here? Oh, wait, wait, wait. Somebody gave 100 bucks.
Mega Mube just gave $100. Thank you so much, dude. Haven't been able to watch you stream
very much recently, but still love every second of the VODs. Hope this helps a little with
settling into the new place. Thank you. Thank you so much, Mega Mube. Well, you
haven't been able to watch very much recently. I haven't really been able to stream very
much recently. So all right, so let's do this the actual way I'm supposed to do it.
Okay, get on the train. Quick. Any bright ideas? I kill all three. Yeah.
Oh, I don't have, I don't have anything else. Well, I want this instead. Get on the train.
I hear so much as a footstep from this car. You'll end up like all your friends out here.
I have honor level. I told you to get on the train. Look, all you had, I'm not,
if you follow instructions, you're gonna be fine. How do I take, I need to go to the engine car?
What do they leave? What if they run away? I'm supposed to leave them back here? I don't know
if I want to do that. No, I'm not gonna, these guys listen. These guys follow directions.
Can I climb? What, what's going on? What was that? Okay, my horse is fine. How do I know
that they're gonna stay? Well, if I'm that guy, I'm just gonna walk off the train right
now. I'll know where to be found. They are running. What are you talking about? They're
running. No, that where? No, they're not. They're gonna remember this. That's fine.
I want them to. One person said that. It doesn't matter how many people say it.
Let's get this thing moving. Why don't I stay on the train? If I'm one of these guys,
I'm gonna lean out the window and be like, sucker. I would throw a rock out the window at
him. As you're gonna get, you can catch the train. There's a bunch of heavy books in there.
I'd whip a book at him and try to hit him right in the head as hard as I could.
I'd probably miss. You ever try to throw something as hard as you can at something
and you just do way off? That's what happens every time.
Not very nice. I'm an outlaw. You want me to tuck him into bed?
Yes.
Tuck him in nice. Well, that's a nice icy waterfall. I'm glad we're getting to the title
screen song with lyrics because that's definitely where we are. This just sounds like somebody
that's at karaoke and they don't know the lyrics to the song for a whole portion and then
she's going to sing the chorus. I don't even know the fucking chorus. Wow.
That sounds pretty good. No, it's too easy. That's too easy. It's too easy to dump them
during the song. It's too easy. Wait. Oh, I thought the horse went through the earth. Hey, go.
I thought that the horse went all the way through. That was a preemptive.
I'm laughing. What the fuck? How do we lose a wheel?
Okay. Let's take a look.
That's supposed to happen.
What's going on? I broke the goddamn wheel.
Let's get it fixed. You need help? I reckon we can handle it.
Okay. Lift it up. I'm playing house slipper again. That's all it takes. Oh yeah. This
is back in like the 1100s, right? The wheel was just invented.
Of course they're going to have technical problems with it.
Here comes the whole story. Back to the wagon.
You can switch between different radar sizes in the compass by holding that.
Expand. No, no, no. Regular is fine. I'll keep it on regular. That's fine.
The Indians in these parts got sold a very raw deal.
This is the heartland we're going to. Good farming and grazing country.
We're just browsing around right now. We can take our time here.
Every blade of grass killed or heard it up to the reservations in the middle of nowhere.
It's not different from anywhere else. This is more scenic. Maybe it's not.
Kangaroo. Kangaroo. Get the kangaroo.
I'm sure some of the army out here was particularly
That's a four legged kangaroo. How do I take out my gun?
I fear I was perhaps trying to simplify something more complicated
for the benefit of our block headed driver here.
Hey, hey, don't blame it on me.
Never forget. This here's a con man, Charles. Born and bred.
Just because it sounds fancy don't mean he knows a damn thing about what he's talking about.
I'm trying. I'm just going regular speed.
So what happened to your tribe?
I don't even know. At least not that I can remember.
My father was a cousin.
Yes, the southern kangaroo. We just ran a squirrel over.
A number of freemen did.
Move from our land. Three of us fled.
You got to know a family of like four is going to drive by then.
They're all going to turn their heads and go, oh, no.
A couple years later, some soldiers captured my mother.
Took her somewhere. We never saw her again.
We drifted around. He was a very sad man.
Where clothes appropriate to move around.
I'm 13. I just took off on my own.
That was about the age we found young Arthur here.
Maybe a little older. Delinquent.
You never did see. But he learned fast.
Not as fast as Marston, apparently.
Wait. I don't understand.
What's the problem between you two?
Nice shot.
It's a long story.
Do a flip with the carriage.
We still heading the right way?
That depends. Are we still heading west in search of fortune
and repose in virgin forests as we plan?
No. Are we heading in the correct direction
on our desperate escape from the law eastwards down the mountain?
We're going the right way still.
Yes, I believe so.
You know this area?
A little. I've been through a couple of times.
There's a livestock town not too far from here called Valentine.
Cowboys, outlaws, working girls.
Our kind of place.
This is boring?
Hey, we're doing the tutorial, man.
We're just trying to enjoy the game.
In this place, we're going.
Wait, what's it called again?
Horseshoe Overlook.
I don't think I can even control this.
Is this a good place to lie low?
It'll do for now.
I can't go anywhere because I'm straight.
How long do you think Dutch is really going to lie?
It's just, you know, maybe it's me who's changed, not him.
But we kept telling him that fairy job didn't feel right.
You and me had a real lead in Blackwater that could have worked out.
It just isn't like Dutch to lose his head like that.
When do we fight the wild west orcs?
Things go wrong sometimes. It's the way it is.
What?
It always has been.
This isn't like Skyrim.
Dutch, abandon this line of work.
We're still here, so I figure we must have got a ride to hell.
Who's eating?
We work here anyway.
Just some yarrow and ginseng.
Good for the health.
Better than that stuff you buy in the store.
Yeah, you can have all this.
I'm at the point where I can do it with my eyes closed.
Why don't you just wish sometimes that you could just eat this and be fine?
Eating sometimes is just a pain in the ass, don't you guys think?
I mean, I love food, but they're going to be annoying.
It's something you have to do.
It's like sleeping.
Think about your entire day.
Like 60% of your whole day is eating and sleeping.
Come on, man.
Like, where's the science there?
Let's go.
Oh, boy.
This discussion again.
So just stop eating.
What's the big deal?
Oh, stop the wagon.
Turn and stop.
Stop.
Do I have to back it up?
All right, back up.
Where is he?
He's right around this rock.
Telephone's ringing.
All right.
There he is over here, right?
Where is he?
Oh, my God.
Wasn't he right here?
Look at the map.
I mean, yeah, but oh, there he is.
He just he got stuck in my shit, so he started walking.
All right, get on.
Can I beep?
Run him over.
No, I have to be like at least a decent person.
All right, get on.
Get on.
Where's the beep?
How do I beep at this guy?
Where is he?
Where did he disappear?
All right, we made it.
Home sweet home.
There we are.
Good thing you made it.
He made it before we did.
I've never seen somebody fuck this section up.
Well, have you ever seen somebody do that whole section in cinematic mode?
Now you have it.
Every last one of us kept us together, kept us alive, kept the nooses off our neck.
I guess I'm just worried.
I ain't got that long, Dutch.
I want folks safe before I go.
Me too.
And now we are stuck east of the Grizzlies and out of money
and a long way from our dream of virgin land in the west.
I know, my brother, but we are safe.
We make a bit of money here, then we move again, head out around
Nice.
West of Uncle Sam.
That's really hard to do by some land.
I hope so.
Would you just look around you?
This world has its consolation.
Gentlemen, I'm going to head into the local town and, you know,
see if I can strike up a little business.
Of course, hair strows up for robbing banks to usury.
Seems more dignified somehow.
Now, everyone, put your tools down for a moment.
Come on, gather around quickly now.
I'm going to get a speech.
I know that things have been tough, but we are free.
Oh, coming in with five community subs.
Thanks a lot, man.
For everyone to get to work.
Get to work, but stay out of trouble.
Remember, we are itinerant workers.
Laid off when they shut down our factory to the north.
Now, get out there and see what you can find.
Uncle, Reverend Swanson, no more passengers.
It is time for everyone to earn their keep.
There is a town a little way down the track named of Valentine.
Can you play?
I'm playing the game.
This is the game.
That seems a decent place to start.
And we need food, real food.
That means every day, one of you.
Now, remember, whatever it is that you find.
Can't have gifts, gifts, slice.
Now, be sensible out there.
Now, the girls have your tent ready, Mr. Morgan.
Come with me.
You threw away the shorty.
We put you over here.
I'm sure everything will be fine, Miss Grimshaw.
It should be.
Most of your stuff from Blackwater got saved.
Everything apart from my money.
Oh, don't remind me.
Well, we can always make more money.
We're going to have to.
Miss Jackson, I've seen shit with more common sense.
Sleep shame or change clothes at your tent.
Burz, I don't know why for a second,
I thought he was going to burn his clothes.
I'm done with these.
I think I'm going to get rid of them.
Horseshoe Overlook, chapter two.
That was chapter one?
How many chapters are there?
That's not how you guys change clothes.
What did they do before?
No, never mind.
That's a stupid thing to say.
What did they do before?
Laundry.
They just left this clothes on.
You rinsed it in a stream.
Funny guys, funny number joke.
So this is a few weeks later.
Eat, drink, play at Dave and Busters.
You got to maintain your course, don't you?
Half price Wednesdays.
Oh, by the way, half price is actually what it should be every day
because it's like four dollars to play one game here.
Don't come here.
What are you saying?
You guys don't have, you never played, you went to Dave and Busters?
Camera.
Your games can't be shown by a symbol on the map.
Eagle talent, talisman.
Okay, so your beard is getting long.
You can use the shaving kit beside your tent
or visit a barbershop to maintain your facial hair.
Okay, there's lots of details here.
Hold on.
So we got permanently increases the time
that eagle eye can stay active for five seconds.
Crafted from rare legendary animal parts.
Permanently decreases the damage the player receives
while on horseback by 10 percent.
Okay, that's interesting.
You can make little charms.
178 animals.
What?
There were like four in the last game.
Deer, bear, coyote, and like rabbit, right?
Six gangs, 30 fish, 74 pieces of equipment.
This seems huge.
Hey, I discovered the deer and the bears.
Where's the bear?
How have I not discovered the bear?
I literally shot him in the face with an arrow.
It's easy to track them.
Okay, I see.
All right.
Bring Pearson animals to supply the camp.
You can use the meat for food
and the skins to craft satchels with increased capacity.
All right, there's a lot going on.
Let me take a look.
I don't care what that guy has to say right now.
Let's do some shaving.
Now, is this like...
Is this like the...
You guys remember...
No one's going to know what I'm talking about here.
The magnet face thing
where you have the magnet hair on the guy's face.
It was like a 14 cent toy length.
Oh, you actually can do this.
Hold on, chin.
I think I just want a dirty chin.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Just gigantic chops?
Hmm.
No, I just want the piece of hair
from my chin to go down as far as it can go.
Yeah.
I'm going to look like an Amish guy.
Thanos.
Can I dye my whole face purple and my beard purple?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay.
I like it like this so far.
I'm going to keep that going as long as it can go.
The current stock levels are shown when near the tithing box.
All right, let's take a look.
Now, that's perfectly balanced facial hair.
Here's something to make a stew.
You can eat from the pot.
I'm getting a lot of info here.
They demanded no.
It's like lore in case you want to see it.
Let me just like take it in for a second here
because here's the donation box.
How much money should I give?
Contribute.
How much can I contribute?
Are you going to serve them?
If I don't give money.
It'll be ready.
Okay.
I did my...
Somebody's...
Somebody's slurping out of a big gulp?
What the hell was that?
It was a radio.
I thought somebody said like a giant soda.
Let's keep looking around.
Hold on.
Food.
Let me eat some stew.
That's less than a hundred bits.
I ain't going to read it.
Let's see.
It's a stew.
What kind of stew is it?
Is it not done?
I want some of that.
How do I get some of that?
Oh, okay.
I have to take...
I have to actually pick the bowl up.
This is the two parts here.
I only get to eat once every few days.
I can just walk around and talk while eating.
All right.
This is pretty cool.
This is good.
Can I throw it like acid?
Can I throw it in somebody's face?
I want to talk.
All right.
I'm going to sit here.
Am I allowed at this part at the lunch table?
What the fuck?
Nobody wants to talk to me.
I can't sit with the cool kids at the lunch table?
Hey.
No, I wasn't done with that.
Sit back down and eat the rest of that.
Okay.
I can talk.
I can see anything when you rode ahead.
Nothing we need to worry about.
Okay.
Good.
That was a...
That was as shitty as a conversation as
what's the weather like in this...
Look at that weather, huh?
I only get to eat once every three days
and I'm going to leave half my plate.
What am I?
At the olive garden?
Okay.
What's over here?
Oh, this guy.
This is the guy shaving the turkey.
Crafting upgrades.
Donate.
I'm going to meet here soon if we're not careful.
Well, let's get some meat so we get a feather.
You can have...
You can have a bird feather.
Thank you.
I'm getting money here.
Donate all.
Donate for provisions.
I think I want to do that.
Donated.
Just bring me meat.
I'm just going to give it to him.
This is fish meat.
Two pieces of meat.
And we got some venison here.
Can I like cook on the...
I'm just going to give them all.
Just take it all.
Don't say like I never gave you nothing.
Just take it.
Oh, shit.
Okay, hold on.
Can I not give these?
All right, so crafting upgrades.
Let's see what I can do here.
I'm very into my crafting at the moment, Mr. Morgan.
Okay, so craft satchel.
Increase carrying capacity.
Tonic satchel.
I can't do any of these.
Oh, god damn it.
I need like...
Fusion cannot craft this yet.
I can't craft any of these.
Okay.
So I need to purchase leather working tools
and upgrade the medicine wagon twice.
I got so much work to do.
There's a lot of work here.
I can make my own house.
I need one perfect ram carcass.
Cleaned up ram skull to be displayed at your tent.
Rugs.
I don't have anything.
Upgrade the main camp's campfire.
I don't have any of this shit.
I need to like play the game first.
All right, well, thanks for the money.
What about you?
Oh, there's a guy over here.
What do the exclamation points mean?
Oh, these are provisions or something, right?
I can take a certain amount of provisions every day.
I'm assuming they're not grayed out.
Right, that would make sense, wouldn't it?
Needs to be restocked.
Okay.
Well, I'm just gonna go.
Let's do a mission.
Where's my horse?
Do the mission, do the mission.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
How are we doing on our stamina?
You can command your horse to stay, flee, or follow
by focusing on it with the L2 when it's nearby.
Yes.
I, I'm on it currently.
All right, so we got G, E, U, or R, S.
We're gonna, we're gonna go towards G, E.
Galloping horses cause stamina to drain.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
173 bullets.
41, 173.
Okay, I have ammo, so I'm just gonna go.
Hold X to maintain the horse's canter
and punch some stamina.
Sounds good.
The world has opened up now.
We're going to the first mission.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, an animal.
An animal I can, I can take and bring back to the,
to the, what is it?
It's a turkey.
Study the turkey.
Where is it?
There it is.
Study it.
Can I talk to them?
How did you, I ran it over.
All right, let's go study them.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Bird meat.
When you skin or pluck an animal,
you take meat from the car cause you can cook
and eat this meat at a campfire.
I, we need to take this back.
Can I like throw it at somebody?
No, that's a gun.
All right, we're going to take this back.
All right, there's another one over here.
Where's the other turkey?
Pick up and examine.
So it's a random wild mushroom.
Parasol mushroom is a health herb.
It can be eaten to refill your health core
or be crafted to as bait.
What can I eat?
What do I eat?
This is dangerous.
I don't know why.
I don't think anyone should do this.
Oh, we're fine.
Okay, give me the other turkey.
This time I'm not going to skin this one.
I'm going to bring this back to,
but I don't know what his name is.
Who's that?
Who's this guy?
Come on, boy.
You think I got a problem?
He ain't getting either one of these turkeys.
I'm guaranteeing you that.
How many turkeys can I put on one horse?
Get lost.
I'm all in mess with you.
I'm just messing with you.
I'm just messing with you, dude.
Like I...
Hey, move it.
Hold on, you can...
How do I rob him?
Calm it.
I'll shoot you like a sick-ass...
Oh, no, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I didn't...
Just stop moving.
Where's it going?
G-E...
That guy.
Wait, that guy might have something.
Oh, there's a witness.
The horse is the witness?
It's this guy.
Stop.
Hands up.
Get your hands in the air.
Stop.
Stop it.
I don't want to have to do this.
Stop.
Stop moving.
Come on, now.
What do you have?
Hey.
All right, I gotta get rid of this guy.
Is this like Hitman?
Do I have to like bury him somewhere?
He's hidden in the...
He's hidden in the trees.
No more witnesses.
We're good.
What was he doing?
Oh, this way.
Okay.
You can't skin a person.
What are you talking about?
Wait, we're going this way.
You can't just like rob and kill every person.
There are turkeys over here anyways,
and that's what we care about.
Where'd they go up here?
I don't see anybody.
No, they got away.
That's okay.
Study.
Wait, I can study sheep?
Ooh.
Hold binoculars while looking at them.
I don't understand.
Does that work?
I don't think it worked.
Don't eat them?
What am I, the big bad wolf?
Okay, slow down.
No, no, no.
I'll get in trouble here.
Animals attached to your horse will decompose.
Sell them before this happens.
Oh, shit.
I need to sell these.
Study quick.
Come here.
No.
Got it.
All right, let's go.
That was a shot in the dark completely.
Made it.
I don't know how fast I can like full sprint over here though.
There we go.
We're good.
Pitch the horse.
Now we're at the general store.
I need the turkey.
Turkeys.
I need both.
I need a turkey.
Okay.
I got fresh turkeys here.
And I'm willing to sell it for a moderate price.
What?
Hey, what am I, what are you, what?
I'm trying to sell you a turkey, man.
Oh, don't do that.
I'll kick you out.
You can interact with the shopkeeper
by approaching the catalog.
What?
I just got kicked out for bringing a turkey?
Where's the butcher?
Pardon me.
God damn it.
Come here.
Let's go.
All right, here we go.
Hey, I got a...
You can interact with the shopkeeper.
All right, let's go.
I'm gonna throw it down on here.
I got some quality meat here.
All right, I don't, I,
I don't have to walk it over here.
Okay.
Sales of turkey meat.
Salted beef.
I'm gonna keep that.
Turkey feathers.
50 cents.
That's not bad.
That's pretty good.
To sell a pellet stored on the back of your horse,
take your horse close to the butcher.
Oh, I gotta get the horse.
Native.
All right, horse cargo.
What does he got on there?
Ooh, look at all this stuff.
I have so much shit here.
I got two championship belts.
I don't think I can sell any of these.
Maybe I can.
Time game?
I feel like I shouldn't sell these.
I'm probably gonna need them.
All right, let's go find Mr. G.E.
Glips indicate optional stranger missions.
Speak to the stranger.
Question mark, Glip.
Do you see, I don't see one of them.
Do you see a question mark, Glip?
I don't see one.
All right, let's just go.
Let's go find this guy.
I don't think he's in the store.
Probably down here.
I need new clothes.
I don't know.
I guess it is.
He's in this saloon.
The psycho in me just wants to throw a chair in here.
But I can't.
No, not yet.
Yes, he's a pussy cat.
Ain't that so, Arthur?
Whatever you say.
How much you cost, anyway?
Ain't that a nice way to talk to a lady?
Oh, I didn't know I was talking to a lady.
Excuse me.
Well, I must say,
you got a fine way with the women, amigo.
They're dandy and a charm.
What's in there?
Chocolate milk?
Oh, man.
I dread to think about it.
Hey, you motherfucker.
Barroom brawl.
This is where it starts.
This is what you came for.
This is for me to get my ass kicked.
What do you got?
Oh, what's that?
You just got dodged?
How do I pick up a chair?
Come on.
There's going to be something I can do here.
Wait, who's that?
Who is that guy?
Uh-oh, here's the boss.
Uh-oh, a chair.
Can I rip off the gas line and just throw a match in here?
Nice.
Pick up.
No, I want the hat.
I want the chair.
Hello?
Oh, didn't even break the table.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ear grab.
That's not cool.
Oh, he's bigger than me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Scripted.
He blocked everything.
Uh-oh, I'm in trouble.
All right, am I missing something from the tutorial five days ago?
Wait, am I not doing something right here?
I think you hold the block.
You can dodge, too, can't you?
Counter attack.
So you hold square and then hit left or right right before he swings, right?
Remember, I did the first half of this tutorial five days ago.
I haven't turned it on since.
Just pressing the direction while holding the block.
Save the goatee?
No.
I'm going to not shower for the rest of the game.
Can I stay like this forever?
Can I just be the guy that got slimed the whole game?
Come on, it seems.
Tom, you found him.
Yes, I have.
He's being held by some bounty hunters,
trying to see how much money the government will pay them.
I know he's in Blackwater, but there's talk of them moving.
We'll get a second here.
I'm going to update you guys on the green screen.
We've been live for about an hour.
There'll be breakertons all over the place.
But if he's alive, we've got to try.
Updates on how that's going to happen.
Yeah, of course.
It's you they want, Dutch.
Always is.
Charles, go find out what you can.
Carefully.
Josiah, take Javier.
Arthur, go get yourself cleaned up.
Join them when you're ready.
What about me?
Well, exactly.
What about you?
What does that mean?
Oh no, never mind.
Okay, so let's talk for a second.
So if you missed the stream,
let me just put the camera on because we're here.
If you missed the stream from three or four days ago or so,
my plan was because we were having a bunch of internet problems,
and we still are.
It's not completely fixed yet.
So wait, is this my my desync here?
I might be.
Let me sync this up.
All right.
Come on out here thing.
There we go.
All right, so because the beard's growing,
I haven't had time to shave.
That should be good now.
But anyways, because of the internet problems,
my plan was if we didn't get it back,
I was going to desperately try to get the green screen stream done like tomorrow.
But now that they're actually working on the infrastructural problems
that were in this area,
I think I'll be able to stream now.
I don't quote me on that, but like I did just say it.
This has been green here for a while.
No drop frames.
It's looking all right for now.
So the green screen stream,
if you don't know what I'm talking about,
I'm going to get in front of a green screen for like an hour or two.
And I'm going to do a bunch of actions that you guys ask for and that we vote on.
But here's how I'm changing it though.
Because I'm including props,
you know, I'm only going to we're going to set it up probably in a couple of sections.
Like you'll be voting for props, you know, prop actions.
You'll be voting for regular actions because every prop action will just win.
And I'll have to spend like five grand on like two day Amazon stuff.
So we're definitely we're definitely going to have to split it off into different sections.
So you have to vote for your favorite one.
This is such a good idea.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
So we're not doing that like tomorrow
because I need some more time to go through and section these off.
And I'm going to present in the discord a series of polls.
We're going to vote on them.
This is not I'm going to I'm going to try to get this done from tonight into tomorrow.
And I'd say by this weekend you'll have a poll to vote on.
But with three different sections in it.
And then I'll be streaming periodically hopefully if the internet stays fine.
Expect now that the streams are able to happen from here.
We'll push this forward a little bit so people have time to participate.
And we'll get that stream probably going next week.
Like probably like six or seven days from right now.
I have a studio that I'm currently in contact with
and working with so it is that it's happening.
We just need some more time to get it prepared.
Because I know I'm going to need to buy props.
And that's going to take at least two days to get that stuff here.
So now hopefully that's a decent update.
It's no longer a secret anymore by the way.
Because I need to know what props I have to get.
So that this is the whole secret thing.
Like I'm not going to know is that's not happening anymore.
So I'll be in there browsing and perusing.
And JabbaDab just gave five more subs.
Five community subs from JabbaDab.
Thank you.
Can't you just paint one of your rooms green?
Oh I mean well I could.
But you have to remember something.
A green screen studio is like 50 feet up and down.
If I were to paint a room back here it would just be like by...
It would be impossible to do let's say me sprinting and sliding into home base.
I wouldn't be able to do that.
With an actual studio I'll be able to do large scale movements.
Full body, feet, everything.
It will be keyed out.
And thank...
Kazzy101 just gave five community subs here.
Thank you.
Here's another one.
Thank you so much guys.
Both of you.
Five in a row here.
Five in a row.
Yeah so like you'll be able to see full body,
complete green over like a 40 or 50 foot space.
It professionally lit.
It'll be perfect.
Because you either go hard or go home with this.
You know what I'm saying?
Like I don't want to put like just a green screen behind me and like
do five Fortnite dances.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Like there's gonna be a lot of shit that I'm gonna do in front of this camera.
But regardless that's kind of the update with that situation.
We're gonna do that probably next week.
Give some more time to get more suggestions
and for me to make some polls
and you will hear about it again over the coming couple of days.
Here we go.
Okay back to John Marston or no Arthur.
All right multiple missions are available in the camp.
These are shown as the that thing.
All right I need to take...
Maybe I should take a bath.
Can we have a peek at the recommendations?
You can go look at it right now.
You got your act together.
There's a channel in the discord that is...
I don't have anything in my...
Okay well just please can I...
I don't want to aim weapon.
Browse catalog.
No more nonsense from you.
Here's the catalog.
There's a green screen discord channel.
Okay ammunition, hunting and fishing, horse care, clothing.
Here we go.
Clothing department outfits.
Let's take a look at the outfits.
No 85 bucks.
The valentine 113.
It's locked.
Custom tailored apparel of distinction.
That one's not bad.
The dewberry creek.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Uh dude please.
Worn flat cap.
Oh some of these are nice.
Big city hat.
Derby hat.
Duster coat.
Oh wait wait wait wait wait wait.
Can I...
Mosea blackwater possum skin hat.
Did I get the rat hat?
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
With items from our sewing department.
Can I not select it?
You need to bring the rat.
Oh I need to go kill rats?
All right I need one that's gonna be cool.
I'm overheating right?
Am I getting like the crotchless pants?
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Okay these are just pajamas.
Ranch pants.
Thin and ranch pants.
Button fly.
Durable friends.
These are bargains.
But please go ahead and turn the page in an inconceivable act of cowl.
Well now I have to buy it because...
Should I be like...
Get on with it.
Can I be like a big candy cane?
All right I'm gonna be a candy cane.
The Halloween's over.
It's time for Christmas.
Okay.
Which one are the cheapest ones?
Well these ones are 16.
We're going with the dog shit ones down here.
Worn...
Well actually riding boots.
These are probably...
These are all right.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
I can't do green?
I mean this is kind of green.
I can't do green boots for like Christmas?
That's as close as I'm gonna get.
Anything else?
And I have to get a different coat.
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
Our special attention.
Okay we got gloves.
There's a lot of shit here.
All right these are big like cleaning rubber gloves.
Let's check these out.
Oh those aren't Christmas.
There's so much shit here.
It's like overwhelming.
All right hold on.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
What am I doing?
Oh no no no no no.
Open that back up.
Press square.
Square just reads.
Okay here we go.
Coats.
Get the rat hat?
I can't.
This is a classic one.
Let's take a look.
Damn it.
L2R2 for free pants.
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
I just want a red like candy cane coat.
Shotgun coat.
Get square when you're looking at the clothing.
Square is read.
Like go like this.
I don't understand.
Like square I just select the price and then it's like a view is x.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
There we go.
Looks all right.
That matches kind of.
Oh well that okay.
How much is this for 16?
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
I'm just gonna look like a court jester.
It's gonna have to be this one.
All right now we're gonna go back.
We're only gonna do this once guys.
Don't worry.
I need like a Santa hat on.
That's not really a Santa hat is it?
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
All right which these ones are already kind of red.
I'm spending a lot of money.
Is that it?
Is there any more red stuff?
Like striped candy cane stuff?
All right vests.
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
Oh boy.
Here we go.
Okay now I just need a shirt.
See what we got.
Maybe I don't have a shirt.
Maybe just no shirt?
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
Does this make sense here?
Let's see.
Yeah that's fine.
Blue?
No no it's just gonna.
Well this is like the union.
Yeah hold on.
Is there another one that's like oh this one's striped.
There we go.
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
Kind of candy cane.
Am I done?
I mean it's not really a holiday.
It's more.
I need gloves.
All right I need.
I'm gonna this is gonna get ruined anyways.
Oh boy.
I just need a green horse.
All right gloves.
Accessories right?
Okay all gloves.
I mean that's that's as close as we're gonna get it.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Get down to business.
You look like the cowboy joker.
All right so we got spurs too right.
Gurdon spurs leaked multi-toned border stamp.
Leather bootstrap and Paul's steel heya bed.
That's a run-on sentence.
Shank and point ten point Rowells.
I don't like those.
That's not bad.
I got things to tend to so get on with it.
Those ones are big.
These have jingle bells on them though.
That's important.
Let's try these ones first.
No that's not bad.
Are there any others besides those ones?
These are close.
Those are good.
I ain't gonna stay patient forever.
Okay.
Get down to business.
All right I've spent like half the money that I own.
So that's it.
All right my outfit is now done for the rest of the game.
Okay well I've got something to tell you.
From behind here we just look like a grandma.
Especially with like the side purse.
Yeah look.
Oh Jesus would you look at that.
There's a sale on flowers over here.
Oh my aching back.
It's time to go to church.
Just wait this is this is not my horse.
Oh shit.
Is it?
Is this my horse?
It's not my horse.
Fuck.
Where's my horse?
He's coming.
Come here come here come here come here come here come here.
All right let's make it out.
You were wanted lawmen and now searching for you.
They ain't gonna find me.
Because I'm almost out of the GTA circle.
All right we're good.
Evade the law by escaping from the red search area.
Which is what I did.
Oh not yet.
Hold on not yet not yet not yet.
What am I stuck on?
Yep.
I'm out of the circle now right.
Don't no no no no no.
Stay right here.
All right I don't know if that's fair.
If I just sat on the horse and I didn't realize what I was doing.
And I got off the horse.
Doesn't that me admitting that oh I didn't sorry I didn't mean to do that.
That's like walking out of a store with an item that you didn't know was still in the cart.
And you turn around and bring it back and go.
I didn't know this is the bottom of my cart.
How's that any different?
That's a fine horse you got there.
Appreciate it.
All right be well now.
See you.
Hey mister can I have a word?
Easy there.
Give me your money now tough guy.
You're a dead man.
You're gonna give me a call to use this?
Don't think I won't shoot you.
I'll close you.
Fuck was he gonna give it to me.
Oh it says a witness.
Oh god what do you have for me.
He moved too much.
You can't have a fuck with a snake man.
No sudden movements.
He reached like he went.
What is that thing?
I can't I can't study it.
Oh okay can I take them?
Give me this one too.
Wait wait no R1 R1 R1.
Squirrel what?
Why does it keep saying squirrel?
Is there a squirrel here?
Where's the squirrel?
Did I run a squirrel over?
Oh well let's go back to the what we were actually doing.
Yeah slow down slow.
What is this?
Hey mister.
Uh he's like I'm not gonna fuck around.
No just like let me go.
I'm not gonna rob this guy.
Let's go to the mission.
I need to get back on a path.
The one guy this is this red.
Is this like an area where they're gonna find me?
Oh oh oh where uh where the where the hell is it?
Where did it go?
Let's go boy.
It ran?
I ran I I ran him over.
Well stop getting distracted.
Uh oh uh oh there come the hyenas.
I'm gonna go back to camp.
Let's get this meat here.
No thank you for stopping me.
Down here.
No you can't get down that.
No he can't.
Pitch the horse.
Don't kick me backwards please.
You're fine.
I'm gonna pet him.
He's fine.
There's the path I want to go.
Right here.
He's all right.
I didn't know that was gonna be that far drop.
Special horse reviver.
Okay let's go.
I'm gonna just trot for a second.
Although can I kind of make like a waypoint?
Do those do those exist?
I'm so far away.
I'm all the way down here.
Holy shit.
What the hell was I doing all the way up there?
Out of options eat the horse.
Fast travel?
Should I fast travel or should I run?
Feed the horse?
Christ.
All right what does horse break?
Is it like square?
Like how do you slow down?
Arb one.
Okay.
I think those are bad guys by the way.
Horses dirty and causes health.
You gotta brush your horse or ride it through water.
Here we go.
Helpful all right.
I'm gonna brush him.
Sorry pet him.
He's nicely clean.
Robbery in progress.
Is a bleeding animal on its back?
Oh fuck.
What the fuck?
All right now how do I?
Can I like take everything?
Satchel's full.
Kind of wedding ring.
Hold on.
Two chewing tobacco.
Does this guy have a gun?
Maintain guys.
Hold on.
Pick up.
Carbine repeater.
Open eyes provide half the benefits of new items.
Should I just leave these guys here?
Can I go in the back of this?
And I just take seven repeater cartridges.
Revolver cartridges.
Baked beans.
Is that it?
Why am I doing this?
Why can't I just go in like a normal person?
Just go in.
Why do you have the Spider-Man around this?
What is the ground poison?
I don't understand.
Get in there.
All right this is mine now.
Santa got his sleigh.
I can, can I sell this?
What the hell is going on here?
What happened?
I'm just getting attacked by a random...
Come on horse, let's go.
Is he coming?
He's going?
Wait, okay, I thought that was a guy running.
I need to eat something.
What do we got?
Dead Eye Tonic Baked Beans.
Can I throw it to the horses?
Turn off the fan?
What the, the PlayStation 4 fan?
That's impossible.
That's the thing.
That's the PS4 just churning right now.
I gotta turn off the PS4 fan.
Just turn off the PS4.
What are you waiting for?
Who's this?
I mean, who's there?
What are you doing?
What's happening?
I'm here.
What?
Everything wagons to the camp.
They'll be available again when you leave.
Oh, well, I can't bring that in here.
I still got my, my fox corpus.
Where, hey, can I talk to him?
Camp funds, 30 bucks.
Yeah, you left me to deal with the big guy.
Drive the wagon off.
Don't give me ideas like that, man.
I will derail this whole stream for an hour and a half.
And I'm dirty, too.
I got my new Santa suit dirty.
I can't even get on it.
They won't let me get on anymore.
They took it away from me.
Red's not a Christmas color.
What?
Santa is red.
He's a big red guy.
I've read that wrong.
I did?
Bring him animal supplies to the camp.
We can use the meat for food and skins to craft satchels.
All right.
Let me, hold on a second.
Let's go to the butcher.
I want to, where's my, okay, I got my wolf, right?
He's still stowed.
So then he should show up, right?
I'm going to actually give some real money here.
I'm going to donate some money.
They said it is a, okay, give item.
Ooh, watches.
No, well, these are worth a lot of money.
All right.
I'll give one clamp.
Buckle.
All right.
That's fine.
Well, they only, I have more money than the whole camp combined.
That's not, that's not okay.
All right.
I'm going to give some money.
What do I get?
88 bucks.
I'm going to give $10.
No, I'll get $15.
$16.
That's got to be worth something.
Go to the butcher.
Thank you for the 1600.
All right.
Donate.
We could really use some more meat, Mr. Morgan.
Okay.
Provisions, the coyote meat.
Let me see.
Coyote pelt and some meat.
Well, I'll take what I can get.
Okay.
Many thanks, Mr. Morgan.
So let me see.
What do I need to do to upgrade my satchel?
My satchel sucks.
I'm more than happy to craft you something if you bring me the right materials.
Okay.
I need to purchase leather working tools and upgrade the medicine wagon.
So I need leather working tools.
And then donate five animal carcasses to Pearson.
So I need to buy leather working tools.
Where the hell do I get those?
I reckon I'm going to think about it.
Where am I supposed to get that shit?
All right.
I can eat from the soup, right?
Because I get one soup a day.
All good.
But what if, well, what if I want an extra serving?
It's not allowed.
Okay.
Well, we've got a mission right here.
This guy's like tied to a tree.
Let's see what his problem is.
What's this going to end?
Speak.
Don't cry, boy.
Speak about your gang.
I can't.
I have to beat this guy up tied to a tree.
Boy.
Whoa.
Horses there.
It seems the cat has got our friend here's tongue.
I was thinking Mr. Williamson could have a word.
Be ready to talk, boy.
I told you, mister.
I told all of you.
H1 and his chief.
They ain't no friends of mine.
I've just been ridding with them for a while.
Horseshit.
You see, we heard that part.
So how about you tell the truth?
That's what you want me to do.
Heard him.
So the next time he opens his mouth,
it is to tell us what is going on.
Who am I kidding?
One old Driscoll's boys couldn't open his mouth,
but he'd tell a lie.
Screw it.
Let's just have some fun.
Well, why don't you carve out his brain?
Eat his brain.
What's he doing?
Where's he going?
And then close your eyes and sleep
and see if while you're digesting it,
you can hear his thoughts.
It's not a bad idea, I don't think.
You know, an imperial mix was among the happiest
and most loyal of courtiers.
Are you kidding me, right?
Of course.
You sick bastards!
What are we doing here?
Well, you are going to talk.
The only question is now or later
we got these little fellas off.
OK, listen.
I know where old Driscoll was holed up.
And you're right.
He don't like you any more than you like him.
He's at Six Point Cabin.
I'll take you there.
Serious.
I don't like him.
I mean, I like him even less than I like you.
None taken.
OK, then, partner.
Why don't you take a few of us up there?
I got this, Dutch.
Should be fun.
I was going for Santa and I ended up
as like Willy Wonka.
Somehow.
What did I get?
Wild West Wonka.
All right, throwing knife.
A small knife with a straight blade
designed in balance
so they can be thrown with ease
can be used to silently take down
any of the range
or use as a melee weapon if required.
It can be purchased from some less
than reputable sellers to save a trip
by recollecting the knife after throwing.
OK, come here.
We got a social call needs making.
Where are we heading?
I'm sitting down for Santa and underwear.
What are you talking about?
John, you take this little rascal.
I mean, like, what are you talking about?
Any nonsense, kill him.
Mount your horse.
OK, horse.
Let me pet you first.
Good boy.
OK, let's back it up.
I'm breaking things already.
I don't understand.
I just tried to move out of the fucking way.
All right, let me get.
How many knives do I have?
Just one.
Beat that up.
Telling you about Willy Wonka.
He's our man somewhere.
Hoping the opportunity comes
up to mention it last goddamn thing.
We was fucking terrible.
Hey, if I got my rings, it's over here.
Yeah, country.
Take this track up through the rocks.
No, no, no.
The Gene Wilder.
Willy Wonka was good.
But Johnny, they're talking like this.
The whole movie was kind of like, I don't know why.
I think the chewing gum is disgusting.
And I guess you're good here.
Unless some soft-handed feller comes along
and tells you you've gone too far.
What are you talking about?
Watch that whole movie.
It's just that you think beating the man to death
when we supposed to be laying low.
I saw your eyes, Morgan.
You didn't go clever.
You went soft.
That's how you talk.
Excuse me.
This is how I'm talking right now.
Do you hear this?
Does this sound?
Do you think I sound like that?
You're listening to me right now?
Yes.
That's what you hear.
You sound just like Johnny Depp.
All right.
Speed it up.
This guy moves a muscle.
Brain.
You know what I mean?
Hot knife through butter, through brain.
Maybe I know more about you than you know about them.
So tell us then.
Brain through butter.
You're outlawed like them.
About to survive like you live rough fighting the law.
I'm trying to fuck this up.
Get back up there.
You're already too close, man.
Dutch is more like a teacher.
From where I've been, you just look the same as all.
Then you looked, but you ain't seen.
Shut that boy up.
There we go.
Shut him up.
Does it like road rash, this guy?
We're almost on him.
Those of this son of a bitch we got with us is talking true.
But if it's what he says it is, and Cole Modrisko's here,
we can end years of fighting here and now.
Okay, now cut.
Skid turds?
What?
No, no.
Hold R1 and X while moving.
Why did I go right through that?
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
I've unlocked.
Hold on.
There we go.
So if you hold R1, he's going to move around.
It's a handbrake.
I wish I had that an hour ago.
Good thing I unlocked it.
It's an ambush.
Look out.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I got my knife out.
Who am I going to have to throw this at?
Just the other side of this hill.
Okay.
Off your horses.
The console is on PS4.
You're going to get them knives.
I said easy.
Off the horses, got the knife.
First person.
Follow me.
All right.
It ain't far.
We might have shared a horse, but we ain't friends.
Remember, watching you.
Every one guy.
Well, that's interesting, isn't it?
How do I throw?
Is this not throwing a knife?
Hold on.
The cabin's in the clearing down there.
There'll be a bunch of fellers hiding out there, too.
Are these fellers armed?
Armed?
No, it's by the rope.
Okay.
Where are your strangers?
Yep.
In Mojisco?
He'll be holed up in his cabin.
Stealth mission incoming.
Stealth?
Who's blind?
Likely is not.
And over there.
Someone's coming.
So, uh, is this going to tell him
we got another bit of pot?
I'll catch up.
It's a good idea.
All right.
So I got a throwing knife in his body's pain.
So you can tell him yourself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If anyone's actually going to shoot the messenger,
it'd be that mean son of a bitch.
Okay.
What are we doing about the pisser, Morgan?
By the tree.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Okay.
I had to clean off.
How did he survive?
How did the guy to the right?
How did he live through that, man?
Take the lead.
Throw a weapon.
How do I aim this?
Is it like a bunch of drop or anything?
You want me to take him?
Nothing else from you.
Throw?
Stay here.
Don't you damn move.
It's on.
We move quick.
Let me start it over.
I want to like do it correct.
What are we doing about the pisser, Morgan?
All right.
So this was going to happen.
You, uh, Bill.
Bill, you're going in.
Okay.
Nice work.
No, I don't want these on.
I want like the regular knife.
Let's get close to these two.
Make sure you're going left to right.
I don't, I don't know how to stab somebody in the back.
Is it R2?
I've not, I haven't done this yet.
Oh, god damn it.
I don't know how to do it.
I was about to greet the guy.
Hello there.
Stab.
Got on the log.
Don't shoot Bill.
I've okay.
Come on, John.
Go for it.
Brutal.
All right.
So we're each going to throw knives at everybody over there.
Okay.
Let's do, hold on a minute.
Stay there, John.
Stop, stop, stop.
Should I, oh, I warned him.
Whoops.
It's on.
Let's do it.
Dead Eye.
Time for Dead Eye.
What happened with that?
Okay.
Watch out, John.
John, get out of the way.
Okay.
John, please kill him.
Thank you.
Who's left?
I got a tomahawk?
Ow.
That guy fucking comes from.
I gotta get a better spot.
Give me a better weapon, too.
Give me this thing.
What?
I just pulled the guy's head off.
Okay.
Got him.
Where's my shotgun?
That's even better.
There's a guy in here.
I'm ready.
Once this guy opens the door,
I'm going to tomahawk him right in the head.
Hello.
What?
I was going to do it to you.
All right.
Browse the place.
That's a good point.
So it's the first full body shot we've had in like an hour.
Come on.
Let's get the camp.
So you got the cash then?
What cash?
Here's usually some cash in the chimney.
I'll check it.
Rest of you boys get the cab quick.
See Arthur?
I ain't so bad.
Hey, Bill.
You tell Dutch old Karen ain't worth killing just yet.
You're right.
You are.
All right.
Cash in the chimney.
You got it.
Slugs, shock and shells, biscuits and all that stuff.
Kill that guy.
I'm not going to kill him yet.
Pots and pans?
What's in here?
Kentucky bourbon?
I can't carry any more Kentucky bourbon.
Well, why the hell not?
Now I can.
Just replace it.
Chimney.
Money clip.
How much is in there?
13 bucks.
That's not bad.
More money.
How many money clips are over here?
12.
There's another one right there.
Damn.
They're going right into the donation box.
No, donation box.
Box.
Why can I not say that word?
Search the draw.
Snake oil.
Can I take any more snake oil?
I can.
Anything else?
Box.
Money in the chimney.
Ooh, double-barreled shotgun.
Yeah, I believe so.
Oh, man.
Clean the double-barreled shotgun.
Cleaning weapons with gun oil will improve their condition and performance.
Okay, cool.
That's cool.
Any more dust on it?
It looks good.
Looks really good, actually.
All right, let's put it back.
All right.
Search the chimney.
Chimney.
Six.
Holy fuck.
That's a lot of money.
$600.
Let's see.
Mission complete.
Under the threat of torture,
Ciaran leads Arthur, John, and Bill up to Six Point Cabin
where he claims Old Driscoll is holed up.
I got an F.
Now, let's head back.
Okay.
Anybody?
Actually, this body's to check over here.
Redo.
No, we don't need a redo.
We don't need a do-over.
What is that animal?
That's like a skunk wolf.
What is this?
No, no.
What is that thing?
Hold on.
I got to catch the skunk wolf.
Study.
I thought I could have had it.
There he is.
God damn it.
Next time I'll get the skunk wolf.
It'll happen.
I can't.
I'm trying to jump.
Trying to jump inside of his cabin.
Oh, shit.
It didn't work.
Hey.
Why is it still going?
Wait.
Ooh.
What is in here?
Why is it still?
Yeah, it's not a car.
What am I talking?
It's not like you're stepping on gas.
Seven repeater cartridges.
Pistol cartridges.
Damn.
What else you got in here?
What?
No, don't stand on the box.
Chest.
Herbivore bait.
Predator bait.
Shotgun shells.
That's a lot of stuff.
That's it, right?
It's a bunch of vegan food.
What about the horses?
These look like good horses.
Can I?
What about this guy?
I can throw this guy off and loot his body, right?
What?
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
What if I pretend it's mine?
Hey.
Wait.
What?
Oh, jeez.
It's just too many people here now.
Who are these?
Hey, get.
Come here.
Get up.
Where's my horse?
Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right.
Settle down.
Wait.
I found him.
Where?
Where is he?
Where did he?
There he is.
That's not it.
These are two different animals.
Sorry.
Study.
Got it.
I thought that just said threaten.
Almost got it.
All right.
We're fine.
Let me pet the horse.
Yeah, good boy.
You're just, you're doing fine.
You're good.
That guy, I could loot that guy's body when he was on the ground.
I thought he was dead.
That's funny.
No, I can't go this way.
It's not a car.
Why can't it just be, why can't it be armor on his legs?
Yeah.
Calm down.
Everything's fine.
I got to go home.
New mission.
Why am I dead eye?
Study.
Big animal.
All right.
Let's get a way point here.
What the hell am I?
Okay.
This is bounty $25.
Where did I end up?
Am I, I still have a bounty?
Do I have to pay these guys or get rid of these guys?
I think I have to get rid of these guys.
Now I got to get rid of these guys.
All right.
I'm going to go pay it off.
So I'm just going to go this way.
So can I talk to them or is that a bounty hunter?
No, I think he's just, oh, well, it is.
It is these guys.
No, it's not.
Robin Hood.
Sheriff Nottingham, you're done stand a chance.
Okay.
I need to heal.
Let's go with the, let's do some more Kentucky bourbon.
Why not?
Your health core is empty.
Oh yeah.
You need to eat.
Okay.
We got, I thought I could eat the glove.
I'm hungry.
Smoke a cigar.
Canned peaches.
Okay.
There we go.
We're good.
Maybe one more of those back to what we were doing.
Health is fine.
Stamina is not great, but now that my bounty is taken care of,
I don't want to work them too hard.
Don't work the horse too hard.
He doesn't deserve that.
How do you feed the horse?
Everyone's saying feed horse, feed horse.
Excuse me.
Oh, I got to get, I got to kill five rabbits on horseback
and I got to unlock a super move.
Here, eat this.
Why am I getting the gun?
See, he's fine.
Rabbit meat.
I'm going to skip the rabbit.
I want to do this.
Let me just get five rabbits.
Holy shit.
Okay.
I just revealed the Scooby Doo monster.
That was pretty wild.
All right.
Let me do, let me do a few more rabbits.
I want to get the four more rabbits so I can unlock something.
Tell me if you see any rabbits.
Just scream as loud as you can if you see one.
I've seen a lot of people scream.
I don't see any rabbits though, unfortunately guys.
I don't know what the fuck this bullshit is that you guys are doing.
I don't know what kind of bullshit you guys are running here.
I almost PUBG'd that guy.
That would've been pretty crazy.
That was not that far.
That was not far.
That really wasn't that far.
That was maybe eight feet.
This is going to be like an RPG.
Anytime I play a turn-based RPG,
I'm so bad at managing everybody's health
that instead of buying the thing that heals a party member,
I just buy like 60 revives.
Because they come back with full health.
Just, you know, let them die and bring them back.
Let's take this scenery in, for God's sakes.
He wastes...
All right, wait, wait, wait.
I'm critical with stamina right now.
Let's see.
I got canned peas.
I need something more substantial than that.
That's all right.
Did I...
Canned strawberry, did it.
I can't use...
I can't eat strawberries when I'm on a horse.
Why?
Because the horse is stamina.
Well, then let's feed him.
God, come on, man.
Feed him.
There he goes.
He's fine.
Let's clean him.
Wait, I can clean him like this?
Let's...
I can brush him from here.
I can study him.
Oh, I learned about my horse.
Okay, let's go.
Not with a saddle on.
What is a horse core?
Uh, that's...
I don't know.
Almost back to camp.
No scenic route.
Let's just go.
Intel horse 2 duo.
Pretty good.
Pretty close.
More things to study.
I hope I didn't have the stupid Bambi on my back.
We're going downhill.
This is going pretty fast.
What are these?
Is it a pig?
Got it.
Well, I learned about it.
This is gonna be okay, right?
Yeah.
Almost back.
How many giga horse does it...
What's wrong with them?
What?
Bill.
We're fine.
It's me.
What?
They don't know what I look like?
I guess everyone looks like they're in the same clothes.
We're far away.
These guys have binoculars though, right?
All right.
How we doing?
How's the land doing here?
$53.
We're doing pretty well.
Not yet.
Let me bring the carcass to this guy.
Is there no running rule in camp or something?
Why can't I not run?
All right, I've got something for you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Satchel rule.
Perch leather working to upgrade.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't...
Perfect deer pelt.
Perfect buck pelt.
Perfect elk pelt.
I can't.
I need...
Well, let's bring it to him.
Good rabbit pelt.
That's not perfect.
Poor deer carcass.
Zero dollars.
We'll eat it.
I'm gonna keep that.
Good job, Arthur.
What do I got?
I got 200 bucks.
I could give some more money to the camp, can't I?
What do we got?
53 bucks?
But is...
Am I doing this right?
20 bucks.
20 dollars.
74 dollars total.
I'm unlocking more things, right?
Okay.
Big bits.
It upgrades the camp.
It seems that way.
Let's eat.
The more you donate, the better your ending.
Interesting.
Let's eat it quick before it goes bad.
I don't need to clean that?
Okay.
All right.
Where's the ledger?
Somebody said the ledger next to the donation box.
Is there one here?
No, it's not unlocked yet.
Okay.
All right.
I'm gonna just go do...
There's a lot of missions here.
D.
Dutch.
Or...
Damn.
Minimum just...
I'm standing right here.
I might as well do it.
Dutch?
Miss O'Shea?
Well.
Feels like we are finally getting back on our feet.
You, uh, find a buyer for them bonds we stole?
Not yet.
But Jose is working on it.
When we heading west?
Soon?
I don't know.
Feels like...
Things have changed.
The whole world's changed.
And they don't want folk like us no more.
We're being hunted.
We are smarter than them.
Only the feeblest of men take jobs in the government.
How do you decent?
I hope so.
Trimby?
Trust Dodge, Mr. Morgan.
You have to.
They got Micah!
Dutch!
Upper!
What's going on?
They got Micah.
He...
I'll test it after the, uh, cutscene.
He was in Strawberry and...
It's okay, son.
Breathe.
They nearly lynched me.
They...
They got Micah in the sheriffs in Strawberry.
And there's Tarka hanging him.
Here's hoping.
Arthur.
What?
The fool brought this on himself.
You know my feelings about him, Dutch.
You think I can't see past his bluster to the heart and side?
He is a fine man.
No.
I ain't saving that fool.
I can't go.
My face will be all over West Elizabeth.
I am asking.
He would do it for you.
I don't think he would, but fine Arthur.
You okay, Lenny?
Yeah.
Of course I'm okay.
You don't seem okay.
You take that kid into town.
Valentine, not Strawberry.
Get him drunk.
And Arthur?
No crazy business.
I'm giving that up.
And you get Micah out of that jail.
Jailbreak?
I think I can handle this.
Come on, son.
I'll get to it, Dutch.
Just can't drop everything.
All right.
Jailbreak.
Who's driving?
Both of us.
Hold on.
Let me make sure.
All right.
I need someone to break this down for me for just a second here.
Like just somebody human being.
So what Deadeye is both sticks together, right?
At the same time.
And then you move it around and then press R2 and you're done.
Or how is it?
I remember.
I don't remember.
It's just R3.
Okay.
And then you just aim around.
Do I have to hold R3?
R3 and then aim around and then press R2.
So I have to hold in R3 the whole time.
Okay.
Just click it and then I aim around then press R2.
Don't need to hold anything.
So my apologies.
I just kind of threw myself back into the game.
R3, set shots, take shots.
Cool.
All right, let's go.
Run him over.
Run these people over.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chad.
Appreciate it.
Look like you've been through it.
I'm gonna get off that mountain then this.
He's got a crazy side off him.
What are you boys?
You're supposed to be scouting ahead for us.
I kept asking him what we was doing but he was...
You worried too much, kid.
Just just some business.
Practice on animals and minerals?
You know how he is.
I see a rabbit.
I gotta shoot it.
Before we even got there.
Then we ran into some fellas.
One of them, Micah New.
Drank some more.
And this is supposed to be a dry town we're in too.
Man, he shoots one of them.
I don't know how that goes.
With the swiftness here, man, why would we be taking our time here?
Happened like the strike of a match.
The Lord was on his fast too.
Practice Deadeye on animals.
But I got a way.
Just about.
All right, I got a host of this.
We'll take care of it.
So you're gonna go get them?
I'll come with you.
You leave it to me.
For now, let's drink some.
This game is about taking your time.
It was Trent that started all this.
That's true.
I didn't see the train go by yet.
Because you know if the train had come by, I would have.
I would have rowed into it.
Okay.
And gone.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Put it away.
Put it down.
Oh my.
Study.
Okay.
Kentucky Sadler.
Got it.
What about that thing over there?
Let's go.
Nice work.
In fact, I don't want the bow out.
Give me the carbine.
Double barreled shotgun.
Who am I kidding?
I just got this.
So we're gonna jailbreak this guy.
Is this like a stealth thing here or are we just riding in?
Should I holster this?
You guys are just in the way.
Okay, we can move a little faster here.
Weapon shop right here.
I will remember that.
Pitch.
Oh, we're not.
We're not.
We got a different.
We gotta find a different parking spot.
That one doesn't work anymore.
Over here.
All right, we're good.
Go to the bar.
Surprise.
Oh, it's a surprise birthday.
All right, this is what we drink.
This is a drinking contest.
I was defending myself.
Tommy, he'll be fine.
Have one for yourself.
Thank you.
All right.
Micah seemed to know a lot of people.
That was the problem.
How you mean?
I mean, I don't seen a lot of crazy, crazy stuff.
Like a crazy, crazy stuff.
Will you shut up?
Be quiet, buddy.
This guy's just being a dick.
You menace.
Dull.
Lead his fool alone.
Lead the fool alone.
I'm bored with being left alone.
Charming.
Listen, buddy.
You're a charming fellow.
One of the best.
But me and the kid hero, we're trying to talk business.
Chat.
Could you possibly leave us alone?
No offense intended.
Ain't no pleasing some folk.
The telltale game's choice.
That's too many.
Where'd my friend go?
Where's Lenny?
Tommy, where's Lenny?
Jen, you know where my friend is?
All right.
He's not back here.
Hey, whoa.
Hey, are you serious, buddy?
You're lucky I don't have control right now.
Otherwise, I would drive a horse in here and run you over.
Lenny.
Okay.
I've got my wits about me again.
What?
I don't understand.
Why did I end up back here?
Power of teleportation.
Wait.
Why?
What?
Did I get Luigi'd?
I actually got Luigi'd, I think.
That's what happened.
No.
Did I lose him again?
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Go down the stairs.
What is happening?
Whoa, don't look at the dick.
Don't look.
Okay.
I'm in first person mode.
Oh, boy.
Find him in the saloon.
All right.
We're having like a great time.
Are they all Lenny?
What?
Turg.
Who's Turg?
Can I sprint?
Can we fight each other?
It was going to be a slap contest.
Oh, this is so stupid.
I love it.
Oh, we got tankards now.
It's gone?
I'm just dropping the guy.
Why am I doing this?
There are pigs in this game.
Oh, that's not good.
Is this the law?
I have control.
How do I?
Can I jump?
Got it.
It was blurry, but I got it.
Is that it?
Do I get to wake up now?
Ooh, weather change.
It's raining now.
You missed a sex scene.
Good job not getting banned.
Oh, that's all right.
I did lose the hat though, didn't I?
Do I have to buy another hat
or do I actually get to put it back on somehow?
I need to eat something.
Jesus.
Okay, I need to eat.
Now, let's see the details.
Did I do this one all right?
I think I missed it.
I need to eat.
What do we got?
I need canned sweet corn.
Hold triangle at rest.
Set up camp craft.
Show coffee requires a campfire.
Okay, hold on.
Let me set up campfire.
Do I need materials for this?
Craft and cook requires a percolator.
You don't have enough ingredients.
Am I slowly putting my face in the fire?
I can't make anything.
I can make health cure.
I can craft seven of these.
Potent health cure fully restores health
and fortifies moderately.
Okay.
Well, snake oil is the...
Fully restores deadeye and fortifies...
I'll get a bunch of these.
Can I fuck this up or do I just hit X?
Stow it.
Make another one.
It's idiot proof.
Hey, watch it.
How's my health right now?
I guess it's...
I'm gonna use it.
Just drink it.
All right, I'll make one more.
Nice gameplay.
Thanks, dude.
This is the game.
Excuse me, elite red dead streamer coming through.
When did I ever say that?
I need tobacco.
I'll make it.
I guess I could just fortify it all, right?
Would you say this game is good or worth buying?
Yeah, I would probably say so.
Because I feel like I haven't even scratched the surface.
I feel like I've gotten maybe like 1.8% through the game.
What about...
I need to fortify stamina.
Potent bitters.
So I need a burdock root.
All right, well, whatever.
I'm just gonna sleep.
Well, I just picked 20 hours of sleep.
PC version.
Yeah, I wouldn't hold your breath on a PC version anytime soon.
First one never came out on PC.
When you gain or lose weight,
up or down will be shown in your health form.
It's a tear cap down.
All right.
So, where's my horse?
Is this thunder and lightning?
When am I gonna play with Ster?
Ster and I are gonna play Lethal League eventually here.
We've had no drop frames at all in about three hours.
So the reason why, you know, I don't want to be like,
oh, hey, man, ready to like stream Lethal League?
It's gonna be so much fun.
Hope you're ready.
And then the internet turns off in 20 minutes
and it's just like, okay, well, that was a waste of time.
What's going on here?
Riding down.
Slipped on a rock today.
Moss is slippery.
Be careful.
Back hurts.
Throwing knives.
You didn't know I was up here.
Like, let's be honest.
It's fucking raining right now.
Hey, I don't know if he's a reliable way for me to get down here.
You have to go all the way around.
I'm stuck here.
Right here is okay.
I should be able to slide down this, right?
It's not that far.
That's like two feet.
At least try and mitigate the damage, man.
Okay, where's my horse down here?
Oh, someone was on the ground there.
Pick and examine.
Pick up.
Pick and examine what?
Plant.
My horse is in town?
Well, how am I supposed to?
I have to have to walk back to town?
Okay, hat.
Pick up hat.
This shit ain't even my hat.
This is dealing with somebody's horse.
All right, it's kind of what's gonna have to happen.
Herb, pick up.
Herbalist.
Let's take a look at the map here.
Reverend Swanson.
I can run here.
I'm just gonna walk to Reverend Swanson's.
Let me take a potion.
We're good.
This way.
God, it's slippery up here.
I unlocked an herbalist challenge.
It's right here, right?
All right, is this guy wait?
Hello.
That's not the Reverend.
In this room?
Reverend?
Reverend Swanson.
Come to meet you.
Mr. Borg, sir, I took your advice.
And your God has finally deserted you.
Who is not without sin?
I took your advice, sir.
I have removed myself from Morpheus's embrace.
No more shall I think, sir.
I am free.
You don't seem free, friend.
You seem drunk.
Sit down, Reverend.
We ain't finished.
You ain't finished.
Look at him.
He's finished.
None of us forced liquor down his throat, friend.
I just want him to play.
Now, firstly, we ain't friends.
Don't make no mistake on that subject.
Now, secondly, he can hardly see, let alone reason.
Now, reasoning ain't never been one of my strong points,
neither, but seeing I do just fine.
You want to step outside or do a business here?
I just want him to finish the game.
Why can't we all just get along?
These are good men, Arthur.
They're children of God.
They are children of God.
He's down.
There's a pool of blood under his head.
Is that fair?
Fair?
Sure.
You want a game?
I'll play a few hands.
We're playing.
Well, sit yourself down then.
Goldfish.
Luther, this is Marvin.
Okay.
Fortunate for you both we're being gentlemen about this.
Who has the best hand or bluff for the weaker one?
So, now you two know each other anyway.
Don't seem like the likeliest of friends.
If you don't mind me saying.
We go a long way back.
Arthur has a queen and a ten, a promising starting hand.
I guess it's something like that.
Can we play?
He can't be no real clergyman.
He committed about five cardinal sins just in that chair you're sitting in.
Think he used to be.
He's
community guards.
It comes to flop and then there comes a river.
Ooh, look at that.
Can you imagine him at the pulpit?
Got a pair.
Queen pair.
On the forest day, he turned water whiskey and I don't remember much after that.
Here comes the turn and then we got the river card.
He's a decent fella going through now.
No, no, no, no.
What if he has it?
I owe him again and you'll find yourself in a bad time too.
All right.
Just trying to have a little fun here.
It is a game after all, Mr.
In your own time.
I reckon I'll go all in.
Oh, I think you're going to regret that call.
Come on, queen, river queen.
Oh, I win.
I win it.
I win three dollars game over two pair.
I win.
Check.
It's always it always comes down to the river.
You've unlocked the gambler challenge.
Check your large for more.
You lucky son of a bitch.
I'm doing this shit again.
All right.
I'll do one more.
That was kind of a shitty shuffle though.
I will tell you.
Okay.
Look, look at the aces.
Look at two pocket aces.
Get out of here.
What do we got now?
You shuffle this time, buddy.
I must say you have a lot less stories than your friend did.
Are you lucky or not?
You ever considered that?
All right.
Give me pocket aces.
Is it three, four?
Nine queen.
Okay.
All right.
What do we got?
Well, you should go all in.
Now you're talking.
Okay.
Hold on.
We got queen.
There we go.
That's the way it goes.
Excuse me.
Shut up.
I didn't lose that much money.
This has been quite the eventful day.
Just not the same without a slurring clergyman, is it?
Queen six.
No, I'm not going all in.
I'll call.
I'm gonna play slow.
Oh, come on.
This ain't kid poker.
We need the flop to happen here.
Come on.
Deal it out.
Five, four.
What do we got?
Six.
We got four, five, six, seven.
We need a seven.
We need seven.
Come on, man.
Some time before we all grow old.
Let's be brave.
Give us seven.
Okay now.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Seems it's us again.
Close one.
Give us a seven.
Straight.
Do it.
Robbed there for real.
No, I'm not going to shoot him.
I'm going to come all the way back.
No, he's didn't.
Okay.
I didn't want to do that.
Go ahead.
Okay.
King.
Follow.
Good.
Let's start this low for now.
14.
Give us a full house.
Don't do this to me again.
King.
Yeah, I know.
Pretty pathetic.
Ten.
No.
Forgive me.
That's all I can afford.
Ten.
Oh, you want to check that?
All in.
What is this?
No, you fucking lose, buddy.
It's ain't what you call finishing strong.
Yes, yes, yes.
Got the ten.
Not much I can do about that.
Okay.
So we're back in the game now.
See?
What do I got for money?
What do they come in here with?
Are you kidding me?
I just got to win two more hands, right?
Now I'm just going to play it safe
and I'm going to just win two hands
and get the achievement.
The people we've met at this table.
Can you win without a straight?
I hope your friend's still breathing.
He's very quiet.
You can win with a pair
if nobody has anything.
Two ten is not...
Yup.
I mean, they could get like a pair.
I'd give it two pair though.
Not just a little wager.
Okay.
Well, if somebody has a six
then it's just unfolding here.
That's too dangerous.
Right?
This is just...
Yeah, this is it.
Come on.
Jesus, you play like my grandmother.
When do you guys get a fucking six
as the game's over?
Okay, whatever.
That was two pair.
That was two pair
and I shouldn't have fold.
But if somebody has a six, we'll see.
That was two pair.
What do you got?
Check.
Can't check.
I thought I was going to...
Sorry to do this, fellas.
He got a six.
See?
I would have fucking lost.
I folded at the right time.
It was the correct play.
If you were sitting at the poker table
you would have had to do the same thing.
Okay.
Guys, I've made like 10 grand playing poker.
Now granted I've also lost 40 grand.
But I've won 10 grand before.
What do we got?
Clean three.
Well, I just need to put a couple...
Come on.
All right.
Well, that's fine.
That's like...
Let's fuck them up a little bit here.
Let's break them up.
Give me...
Give me a two pair here.
There's the three.
That's a pair right there.
Just need a queen.
Oh, and another three.
That ain't too exciting.
Good.
I'll call it.
Just give me a queen or a three.
Come on.
Give me three of a kind.
I don't think I'm going to win.
This is a pair of threes.
And another check.
Why don't that surprise me?
Fuck.
Come on.
River's going to be like a three.
River's going to be a queen or a three.
He doesn't have his three.
Oh, fuck.
Now maybe he does.
I could win this with a pair.
Screw it.
With three.
He's bluffing.
This is bullshit.
Eighty-four cents.
Ace high.
Pair of threes.
Pair of sevens.
God damn it.
I would have won.
That would have been it.
I just got to...
Oh, look.
I can come back.
Just give me a few more minutes.
Just give me like another hour or two.
I can come back.
I'm just going to run to the ATM.
I'll be back in like...
I'm just going to get like another $400.
Queen six.
Why do I have a queen every time?
Is this rigged?
Seriously.
Do I have a queen fucking every hand?
Flip him.
Damn it.
I'm trying to fluff him up.
Come on.
No.
How do I go to the ATM?
This is getting too rich for me.
Sit down.
I'll be right back.
I'm just going to go to my horse.
I'm going to get my debit card.
Come on, Rip.
Where'd he go?
Who?
Excuse me, gentlemen.
The tutorial AI never holds.
Who's the stranger?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
You see a drunken idiot priest wandering about?
It wasn't done.
Hey.
I'm just screaming for him.
God damn it.
I'm not trying to kill anybody.
Jesus Christ.
What?
Find him.
Who is this?
Who?
He's still alive.
This guy is a fucking super human.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, get the sheep out of the way.
Come here.
Live spirit.
Is he going to the train?
What is he doing?
I can't jump that high.
What the fuck is he doing?
The train's not coming.
We're fine.
All right.
Come here.
Oh, the train's right there.
All right, got him.
Come on.
What the hell did you do, man?
That was just the heavy from TF2.
What the hell is wrong with you throwing me bridge like that?
There was a goddamn train, you crazy bastard.
Have I been bad again, Mr. Morgan?
I'm sorry.
We're just different.
Good on you for not doing the cheap YouTuber joke.
Home.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
I've done enough stupid shit the last three hours.
Margaret.
Who's Margaret?
Yeah, y'all thought of...
By the way, those of you that have very keen ears, I pressed R2.
Let me try.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
No, drop.
What a classic.
It's a classic one, you know?
One more time.
Dude, it's a classic funny YouTube joke.
Come on.
We fell off on the...
What the heck?
You have to do it for the YouTube joke.
No, I'm not doing it.
Told you I wasn't gonna do it.
Just bail on the last second.
No, no, we can't do that anymore.
There's way more funny, interesting things to do than...
Look, I fell off the cliff again.
You know?
Wait for the train to go through the length of the entire map and then get hit by it.
To do any of this.
Here comes another one.
Don't need to do this.
He's coming without him.
Hey, hey!
Is he out cold?
I think he's knocked out.
I think it ran over his head.
I think he's dead.
Is he dead?
Don't mind if I'm dead.
He isn't.
Okay.
He hit a horse.
Oh, hello, sirs.
Oh, he got in an accident.
Hello, it's a fatty!
Let's hitch.
All right, Reverend.
What do you think?
Where's it going?
Where are you going with him?
Drop off in bed.
I am babysitting this guy, huh?
Just leave him on the horse?
Can I put him on the horse and then put the horse in bed?
No.
Drop in fire.
That's not gonna happen.
Drop off cliff.
Not gonna happen.
You better sleep your way to salvation, my friend.
What happened?
Just the usual.
Poor bastard.
Exactly.
Well, thank you, Mr. Morgan.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Comedy license revoked.
He was lucky this time.
Real lucky.
All right.
Who is not without sin completed?
Donation.
Let's get it to 100 bucks.
A companion activity is available in the camp.
Talk to companions marked on your map.
Where?
Companion activity?
It's now marked on the map.
What?
Which one opened up?
Five finger fillet with Lenny.
Not this shit again.
I couldn't do this before because it was an Xbox controller, though.
Remember?
I should be fine.
Lenny?
Hey, Arthur.
That knife's sharp enough, ain't it?
Depends.
Why?
You feel lucky?
Do you?
Before me?
At least six generations were born and changed.
And for the last three years,
I've been running from every lawman and bounty hunter west of the Lanahassee River.
So yeah, I feel lucky.
I'm the living embodiment of luck.
That is one way of seeing things.
But I'm also skill.
And in this game,
I think I'll be all right here.
You've got to have luck and skill.
And stupidity.
The outlaw's trinity.
Luck, skill, and just a dose of stupidity.
Come on.
You ain't too loyal and too sly just yet.
After you.
As you wish.
You know, we should head back up that mountain sometime and make Jenny a proper grade.
Okay, who's turning?
So nice.
Don't worry.
Does this work just like the other one?
I'll send a wire to the doctor for you.
Oh, he just cut his hand.
Oh, he's setting the time I have to beat.
Here goes.
Got it.
Keep it loose.
What are the buttons here?
Okay, it's X triangle, so it's triangle.
So it's X triangle.
X triangle.
I'll do it like in five seconds.
Check it out.
Ready?
Get the hell out of here.
What do we got now?
So this is X square, X...
Okay, just X square, X square, X square, X square, X square.
No other variables here.
Record time here.
Watch this.
Now we go on round two.
So this is...
Okay, so this is circle, circle, circle, square, square.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is so boring.
So this is square, square, square, triangle, triangle.
Damn it.
I gotta do it again.
Oh, I'm freaking out.
Another one.
Try this in real life.
Okay, I gotta slow down on this one.
This is circle, circle, square, triangle, circle.
Let's get paid attention.
It's gonna be before a second.
Triangle, circle, square, circle, triangle.
Triangles, circles, square, triangle, circle, square, circle, triangle.
What was it?
Okay, what's this next one?
Let me see.
Square, triangle, circle, triangle, square, square, triangle, square.
square triangle circle triangle square square triangle circle triangle square
square triangle circle triangle square fuck out of here everyone
i'll take that be i'll take that drink it out here
finally all right what's next we do i want to do this guy's mission
go hunting oh i don't think so no i gotta learn some time right you want to go hunting
what are you hunting an elephant i wish no i saw a huge bear one of the biggest i ever saw
i reckon nearly a thousand pounds my god get a good item from doing this need me to come with
well i'm definitely gonna do it then let's go where are we heading exactly up near the river
i am gonna go get a water i could do with a break from this place me too
was it it's been a rough couple of weeks you need anything after this cutscene i got all i need
let's go then so you still ain't replaced boat to see you no i miss her she was quite a horse
this one's okay but ain't no boat to see i've been meaning to offload this big shire
horse for a while now unruly bastard where'd you get him some big loudmouth bastard tried
what am i touching so i well you know how it is a visible force let's take him to valentine
it's on the way sort of there's a decent dealer there we'll unload him you could buy yourself
a new horse put your saddle on them let's get going okay that horse is huge there's nothing
wrong with two horses look at how big this thing is okay well i'm gonna take that saddle
and put it on the giant one don't be rude about this magnificent creature
i'm gonna study him first put your saddle on him and let's go what's what's wrong be on the
other side saddle up i promise you don't want to ride that one okay horse bonding achieved
level one so what about this guy okay see if you can get your leg over that group
i want to pet him all right just get on
let's head into town all right hold on give me a second i'm just going to grab a water
i will be right back see in a second did he go to the store to buy water no i'm right here
ah okay back to it so how is no what stay out of the saloon this time what are you talking
about yeah that's probably a good idea they got a good range of horse attack at the valentine
station is now your main horse is represented as a horse on the radar i used to have a real nice
one yeah what happened to that what are you doing got stolen outside that saloon in deer creek
welcome back from the store just about it was a really really quick store run
into a long day yes is that noise in the background you ps4 thing yep went crazy
threatened to kill it is and davy was passed out this thing is like burning up there came
back in the next day and he woke up started right back drinking again it's not even near
the microphone either it's across the whole thing it's just for some reason it's being picked
up bad it must be pretty hard on lenny you could tell he was sweet on her
lenny and jenny could never have worked vacuum out ps4 oh yeah this is not i can't do maintenance
on this is i don't know i don't know just feel a bit like it's alex had a ps4 pro
and i had my ps4 so we would have had three ps4s i hope so you find a way to
mine sounds like a vacuum when playing this not yet it probably has to do it
i don't know maybe how hot your room is or couple of leads i'm looking into
that big bastard get the better of you there yeah yeah calm down calm down calm down
calm down stables are just up ahead your bonus horses it will be available to collect in the
stables all right go sell that big brew sell it buy yourself a horse okay don't i want this
i'm going off to the general store i want to keep this guy to lure that bear out with
meet you back here in a bit hey how can i help you this is dlc for a new horse
i did buy that stupid 20 dollar package you're in the right place i got some beauties in at
the moment what about this one here looking to sell i show you you got papers no no papers
well of course that's gonna affect what i can pay but thank you for that i got a fella who's
been looking for a decent workhorse like this for a while otherwise i can always stable them
here for you yeah take a look all right hold on a minute stabling your horse allows you to
store it into the stables so you can access it later if you sell the horse you'll be able to
you'll be paid the sell price this horse is five dollars and 20 cents what that's that is
terrible i'm going to stable it okay buy a new horse american standard bread dutch warm
blood thoroughbred and ardenis he's free oh shit is this the horse that i got for
a pre-order the game for 20 bucks is this my 20 dollar i paid for this like
i get the fast one my horse i'm pulling up the keyboard that's not going to work
okay uh gotta be good gotta be good uh it's something about like a 20 like who's in the 20
jefferson oh who's on the 20 it's andrew jackson okay chuck schnell as well
no it's okay wait it's female okay how about uh whisper oops track tack and surfaces okay uh
grooming mane who all right can i make it a christmas horse again
again natural regular short long braid mohawk dreadlock i think i want long long and red
okay tail braid a big braided tail oh man big gold braided tail i like i like it
to the hair be gold oh that just looks fucking this i don't want that red's fine okay tack
saddles do any of these is this just for aesthetic purposes or does it do anything
i mean this one this one matches my outfit kind of so i'm gonna go with this one wait no
never mind now it does improved oh i like that i just spent every cent that i own did i yeah i
did look at that extra speed what do i want for a joystick the lizard or the enterprise i'm
a star trek fan so i got to go with this one blankets uh i guess this one matches that kind
of i can't afford anything else i don't have any more money bed rolls all right i'm ready
services horse care package that is waste five dollars all right horse provisions i think i
already have some but i want an apple though i want like a few apples all right partner
you got yourself a deal and a fine new horse i hope so well i don't sell anything other
than good animals you have my word on that 35 cents left it's all right i'm just going
to go back into the donation box and take my money up here are your papers i can do that
a new grooming brush and some treats appreciate it i can't just reach in there and pull it back
out you treat this fellow well i know he's gonna look after you just fine it's all right i'll
sell i'll sell a few things looks like a nice animal you got there all right look at this
look at this beautiful voice boy i got new saddles i got new hair wait why was it was his
hair okay hold on let me like let's start the bonding process brush i'll find up there let's
go i want to brush the horse oh you're dusty that new horse of yours or not hold on
over bread okay here we go all right let's get going you got quite a ride ahead of us
so like this i don't want this horse to die but i want to test out of speed zero to 60
run up in the mountains east of cumberland this is quick i just hope i can remember how to get there
back into the mountains i sure didn't figure on that but this time we're doing the chasing i
fucking hate the tail why so how are things with you what's wrong with it i mean it looks
kind of like a scorpion tail but that's fine
the tail is fine it just looks like there's a snake up its ass
if it dies i lose it forever
well then that's very good reason for me to keep it alive
long hair it's the color not the braid get gold okay time to go i think we need to head right
up here we're gonna go up all the way up yes i remember i'm not in control anymore am i
moonstone pond what's what's wrong with my golden tail red hair do i prefer flathead
screwdrivers or phillips well depends on what the scenario is we made it let's loop around
the other side you can't have a favorite screwdriver depends on how big it is here
you know this this screwdriver is a phillips head i can't undo my table without a phillips
head might as well go get a flathead no i mean phillips head definitely is cooler but
did i do cinematic centrist streamer is scared to take a side maybe we should catch one to cook
sure try and shoot one you don't want to use anything too powerful on a small animal like that
just ruin the meat you can probably put a paint can with a flathead
you can probably put a paint can with a hammer as well slow down well there they all are i did
i thought thought we were still in a cut scene why don't they just i got one
not very smart rabbits i will say you are correct on that
yep good job all right getting late that's it we should camp here oh i thought we were
going home yeah that's it get us set up well i'm finished cook that rabbit then
they're delicious on an open fire like this just like monster hunter right to spin it
i ever had been in this menu it's just teaching me how to be in the menu
and cook six of this plain game let's go can i burn it you want something no i'm fine
i don't like eating this late okay what after all that so i'm gonna eat a whole rabbit
myself i guess i probably could do that i could probably eat a whole rabbit put this one away
rabbits are 30 pounds are you sure about that no they're not 30 pounds is is like a medium-sized
dog a rabbit is like maybe two pounds this isn't a shibu inu what do they call
shiba shiba inu a rabbit is how many pounds is a rabbit siri how many pounds is a rabbit
how much does a rabbit weigh how much does a rabbit weigh okay let's see ranging from
adult domestic rabbits can have a healthy weight ranging from two to eleven pounds two pounds
eleven pounds that's huge that's a hair that's not even a rabbit first like to find this
monster choose a time to sleep until sleep until morning he better be worth all this drama
eleven pound absolute unit rabbit five five five you ready no give me a minute coffee sure there
you go so what's your plan well we'll see if we can track them but we might need to lay
bait to draw them out i want one of those cups obviously but they all can you get one
of those one of those old school tin cups i'll drink out of that every day shoot from the
trees but i prefer to hunt on the ground more dangerous but we'll have a much better
chance of getting good shot in and if he bolts we can start right off after him why is my
author arthur santa because halloween was yesterday and now we've gone it's christmas time tie it
up in that rag when you're done i hope you know what you're talking about i grew up in the
predator bait select the potent predator bait recipe
that was virtually weaned on bear meat okay i think i got this done good pack up and we'll
get going i gotta shave what's the hold okay let's go so how are we gonna take down we're
gonna bait them this is my horse okay yeah i can always tell
okay how's that horse treating you so far so good you know i was in this area with bessie
years ago really i don't i imagine you still miss her every day did you two ever
think about getting out fix the audio hold wait is it really like an audio sinking problem
right now or am i getting yelled at for no reason you should be hearing like don't don't
don't don't don't don't do a test with a gun this is a better test right when you see the
highlight it should go it's a half second behind it wasn't it normal at the beginning of the
stream the audio is playing first hold on let me try this that's weird tell me if this fixes
it already i wonder why that happened that's weird because it wasn't doing that in the
beginning i don't know why why i'm just desyncing after playing for like three or four hours it's
weird okay let's go now we did briefly you don't remember guess you were still young i had my
sound off how would you know there was a problem she understood she knew what i was
i've been around for a while things were looser back then truth is there's never really any
out the audio is at the wrong angle i gotta like tilt my audio you know that but bessie and i
made it work you thinking about getting out hey no of course not you can braid your horse's tail
yep duchess grand plans work and you can paint it gold we can make enough money to go someplace
new really new maybe we can all have a new start anyway for now let's try and chase ourselves
shall we let's slip by the water here see if he's been fishing again sounds like fred from
scooby-doo yeah an old version is it fred uh what's his name fred wilker what's his name
there tracks dung bones any sign of him you have entered legendary animal territory
follow clues distract the animal you can find legendary animals throughout the world
oh all right we got like a stink bomb here
okay let's hope it's him can you there he is there's the trail which way he went
this way don't i need a much better gun we're down here tracks go into those trees
wait i gotta make sure do i have that this is not gonna happen here man hold on just just
wait a second i need the horse oh yeah i need i need a like a shotgun or something double
barreled shotgun thank you and what else do i want from you a knife i have the knife sawed off
shotgun i wasted all this money on the saddle all right well whatever do i have anything
else i need light i'm gonna bring the light too okay now i'm gonna make sure i have this
equipped so i can shoot the bear's face off of his head let's go am i crouched
look at those tracks this way this way follow me sniff the ground just drag your tongue
against the ground and you'll be able to taste it cool over here happy eating fish
must have been left by our friend i reckon come on see if there's anything else
um okay keep my eyes on it did i hear bear use the safety light tracks dead no there's another clue
looks real fresh reckon he's got to be close there is a close
can i stealth kill the bear hold on hold on which way
dead trail looks like the trail and see we lost him for now how little optimism arthur
well we're gonna hear the default bear sound you guys know what i'm talking about
split up and each look one that goes like this
it's in every single video game let's bait here fine by me let's leave the bag over there
those boulders up ahead looks like a good spot for it
that was pretty that was close that was kind of close i'm not a bear though so i can't
make it completely you know so uh we need the bear bait which is this one sausages
come on wait for the bear
more or less there's a bad view scar down his face hey did that bait look okay to you
i think so you're the expert ready with your gun there i'm good you're okay you seem nervous
so do you no get the fuck out of here i'm fine here we go get the gun let's just take
a look at that bait no he's gonna get he's gonna happen only just said it i was there
i know here it comes he got it he ate it got your knife here comes easy do it whoa
he didn't he didn't do it you're all right you're fine old man of course i fight
thank you i think that was fun you know what arthur morgan i'm a little old he did he tried
to do the bear noise too he was that's what he was going for what is it it's a map a man in a
bar gave it to me well i stole it from him but that's another story he said it told him
where to find some real big animals thank you it's a pleasure there's the map saved my life
i think i'm going back to camp to lick my wounds you coming or you gonna track that
monster well you coming or not i'm gonna track it i'm gonna stick around here for a while
i'll see you back at camp yeah i hear him i hear him where is he
did i shoot the horse i didn't shoot the horse accidentally right
wait what am i eating whoa all right i want to track this thing
i'm gonna kill this bear train train train which way train train up here train
what your horse is agitated by a predator what predator
all right let's find the bear don't go that fast well i need to open up the
the thing here because maybe bullet showed on them all right there we go
okay so this is king bear territory i don't no no no remove those i just defined them up here
so where's that thing that he gave me i don't see anything is it in the maps
lure the bear into the train not a bad strategy don't walk off here what happened
what did i just get clothesline it's okay whisper it's okay girl oh and i haven't bought
get up you're smarter than me it's for sure how much does it get up here to get i want to board
the train okay come over let me feed you an apple come on up here come on come on up
here go go go go go go go see you're fine now it's time to feed you later all right
what do we got here we're kind of all the way up into no man's land what's this that's a bounty
bear i mean but is that where he is do i have to go just down here
find the bear i'm what i'm gonna try just punch this i punched the horse in the head
i didn't want to punch the horse in the fucking head and like lost the scent of the bear
just go down it's not as easy as you think
let's try to be a dick and get out of there as fast as possible
go back the way you came up
jesus christ
hey go fuck yourself turn around he's eating shit what am i doing i'm going back i'm trying
to get down what i'm trying to go down all right where where where was it up here
like here author down guys i'm in the middle of the mountains i gotta go down the whole
mountain to get out of here all right we're gonna play hot and cold you ready
starting now it's ice cold warmer getting getting lukewarm cold cold hot warm hot hot hot hot hot hot
hot okay hold on i'm on fire on fire this is where that's where i'm going this is where
i'm heading right now that's where i'm going right now what that's where that's what the
waypoint is the what yeah i got away with that one just press o near the horse's head i don't
understand wait i'm sorry i don't know why i don't understand i i just somebody told me to do that
i'm now cold while you're cold i'm not oh no no that's just a chat thing that's not
i'm i'm hot right now with chat
no please i could have just been a crazy person where the fuck am i now
what this is not the beginning of wait hold on no no no wait this is this the beginning
before no my horse is right here thank god oh you can tell by the tail
i made it it's right here fucking jesus fucking christ i had to pay attention i swear to god
okay it needs to be you have to avoid the rocks well this game i like this game this is fun
game slow down i'm this is where i put it on okay i wanted to back in punch that guy
in the ear and fly him off the cliff so bad your words can't even describe how badly i
wanted to do that i was holding x honest to god i was holding x it's supposed to keep you
at a steady pace on the mountain right holding x keeps you on the road get away from me
that's only if it's in a cinematic oh for the love of god well then fine fuck it let's do it
cinematic mode now i can like actually drive around on the roads okay i think i'm getting
close you can ride as fast as you want in cinematic mode because no i don't believe that
where are we at now getting close i remember this slow down
all right everything's fine you actually can should i believe people in chat or should
i just play the game holy shit they weren't lying okay all right so thanks guys
okay all right almost there how much further down do we have to go i don't know what to think
about that tail great i got i'm reading reading chat that time every minute that's
because i was looking at chat hey stupid come on okay how close am i to killing the bear
oh yeah yeah see we have to go around the whole mountain you guys thought i could just walk run
up the mountain that's not gonna happen i need to heal a little bit here you know what i'm
saying get away from me what what was that somebody was screaming i don't see anyway
oh hey what is that thing i'm freaking out the lasso
oh you're right here take it what do i do what do i do
what does he need wait everyone asked me i knew he was dead i in my head i internalized like
that and that i want to make sure it was quick you know like i i don't want him to
you know be suffering there won't take long to me like i did that very quickly it was like
like done okay i got some wolf meat what did he have on him oh what did i just sever his leg with
that what he got a bait good rabbit pelt just in case his brain stem was still spinning data
you know what if he wasn't dead completely burial let's see it you know i don't want to be
suffering in there you missed his brain well how do you miss somebody's brain if their head
is gone legendary animal territory here we go i'm ready him hey can i give it an apple
something else do like an apple no i don't want to give him any more baklava give him a
fucking apple there classic oat cake classic oat cakes okay let's give him a nice little rub
that's a she if we're gone so you just stay safe daddy's gonna go kill a legendary bear
oh i just smelt something freaking times a dead eye herb okay what do we got nothing
around here what's this shit no just eat it actually i need to take a potion or something
here yeah look at my health it sucks you can eat like beans and shit i have my core is terrible
okay what am i dead on my dad i sucks too slightly damages the dead eye core
oh who gives a shit all right i'm ready not quite any clues yet do i have any bait
i don't think i have any bait do i can i make any come on can i make bait here this is where
you hide this was hanging out here i have herbivore bait i didn't see any clues of him being
right here anywhere come on if i was fair where would i be right here somewhere i need to make
master bay and that's how we sing the song the thing that we're singing right now okay let's go
i don't see any tracks or anything there's no point of interest in the smell
let me actually see if i have i don't think i do herbivore bait predator bait okay so now
can i just put it down here i mean the horse hat kind of has to get out of the way
move out of the way yeah wait bear okay no what does that sound
did i gotta go further back i thought the shadow was the jib was the bear shadow behind
me standing up all right i gotta get the horse out of here let me get that bait actually we'll
see uh it's flee right flee me is that that means he's gonna go back to town right when i press
flee or does that mean hey go free how do i make them go home this way come on come on
all right stay there stay over there let me just pick the bait back up where is it where is the
bait it's like right here right what didn't i just drop it like right here what are these
stink lines is this me oh that's my body all right i'm going back down here let's go right
to the x i'm gonna drop it right here so am i pushing the bear away by smelling strongly
i mean right here i'm gonna put some bait right here or would that be a stupid idea
there's a clue i don't see i mean this is this this is not a clue this is just
flowers on the ground i don't see shit the bear is scared away so i can't get him to spawn again
i can just come back later there's activity in the areas the bear won't spawn
oh ginseng what is going on over here oh what's this i think that's the elk it was just right
here right yes deer tracks yeah i'll come back later let's go do another mission in fact where
am i gonna go from here i'm so far away from everything oh how do i how do i get over here
faster uh i'm gonna go across the whole world what's this we're going this way
no
easy jesus what uh does he have any gold let's see i'm i'm waiting to see i'm gonna wait and
watch we're talking about one shot headshot if he if he goes gold sure looks like another
can you take pictures why can you do a selfie
i can't can i like help him do whatever he's doing i don't
oh
found ourselves some gold gold nugget some hobbyists buying these cars to be
collectors items keep an eye out for more i'm just kidding i'm not gonna do it
can i have his outfit i want to dress up like this guy can i look for gold with his stuff
i just saw a hat on the ground where is it right here prospector hat pretty good look
all right i can't i can't use this stuff so a gold nugget that's gonna fetch me some money
you want it i gotta get back over this way well that's cool let's go how much does that
sell for a lot 20 bucks in this day and age probably you really
uh
44 cents that's it force medicine hold on i need the let's get this out
this could be iqibod brain what did i gain 44 cents like a canadian mountain
44 cents in a spot in hell no too many animals we're just going south i see some light down
there is that safe safe trek down here skip i can probably slide here very gently
nice very good all right back on land is there a body of water right here there's not but what's
this new handover what is i've been a bounty here somebody wants to kill me here okay
so i should just go in there and just shoot them in their beds hello well somebody already
did it i don't have to do anything nice halloween house there ghost in here this is
fucked up inspect the letter let's read this at the second hour under the half moon by the
great love and grace of our savior co-coaba voyager of time and galaxies we cast off our
corporal shells so his vessel can take our spirits to the promised realm to live in
peace and power until the 2000th year when we will return for the new chosen worship once
again at the peak of mount shan and his lovely rejoice always the second hour that is what time
is it right now it's in the night stand potent medicine what time is it 10 30 p.m. hey i know
what we're doing we're hanging out here till two cigarette card oh i need these dr hawthorne's
poet card okay well whatever one of 12 cards gone okay that guy has a thing on his head
so he might just get up snake oil i'm gonna heal up too i'm not having that happen
are you kidding me i'm not gonna deal with that bullshit he doesn't read chat rewrite what what
i hear something is it 2 a.m. look up i don't understand what you want i got pranked
uh what the fuck wow okay get the fuck out of here you goddamn aliens i told y'all it was
real i told y'all it was real i've been abducted four times just save the fucking earth well that
was interesting is it even 2 a.m. like what time is it right now 1 a.m. it's 2 a.m. is that
mountain time eastern time i don't know but we only have another check the chimney all right
right i did i could check the chimney all right what's in here alien time aged pirate rum
okay increasing stamina xp that's pretty cool time check 149 here we go i'm ready 2 a.m. it
already happened yeah but uh but it's at 2 a.m. okay all right come here horse yep yep it
already happened why does it look like 6 a.m. it's probably not two cool things that happen at
this place yeah you'd probably be right now it was pretty cool though is that like harping
back on the joke that there's always some kind of ufo in every rock star game that's pretty
funny all right we got a little settlement up here i'm not going to be bad guy i'm gonna be
a good guy i'm gonna greet them with respect i have a dump count there's a mailman here
what is this here for how am i casting a shadow at 3 a.m. that's a good question
let's get doing some kind of problem huh what oh this is the back door this is the back door
never mind my friend never mind hey uh hey how you doing pay bounties i'd like to pay my
bounties please i don't have enough money train tickets this is your fast travel
but i can't do anything it was nice talking to you hello sir hey it's lonely out here
sometimes don't it uh-huh anyway don't let me bother you see you around mister what you want
how's things for me worser is the day goes by nope i'm not gonna do it what's that hold on
people jump to wagon oh right where's my mask i'm trying to jump to the wagon
what happened to jump to wagon an option wasn't it i just pressed it
hey wait what oh i can't why did i get off why would i just get off oh dear oh boy oh boy
oh i'm sorry that was my fault that was my fault that guy blocked like three punches it
was like clap clap clap my ear diary i got knocked out i fuck with the guy i ran over four people
okay we're gonna get that that's what that is we're gonna keep going now
hey partner oh wait wait wait wait 30 bounty here i haven't even been here
i haven't been here one time morning morning what did i do wrong here
well besides just trying to open that guy's door on an uninvited but damn this is so big
i gotta go back here i have to wrap around here uncle okay i'm gonna put uncle on the map
i'm just getting too distracted there's too many things to do dog get up and yeah whoa
hey boy good dog study can i can i have the dog
get out of here damn it you bet the dog likes me let's go what you son of a bitch i'm petting
your dog right now just hold on well you've got such a beautiful coat okay what did you need sir
that really all you got to hit a lane okay girl no that's a thought what he got off
this is championship right here man oh that was championship level fucking jumping
i wanted to hit my head on it i was also so i've been telling like a 50 dollar bounty i'm
gonna sell all my shit i gotta go i'm going back to where i mean this is a long way but
like i have to get back here i'm gonna just stop and eat here though
what's going on over here is that our camp or is that something else
okay hold on there's people here okay mask on no no no mask on i got it i gotta straighten up
here a little bit guys we're gonna make a friend what's he up what's he up to barnard
how are you sure hey thanks man thanks plain big game this dude is dead i'm not gonna kill
this guy same time weather i'm good let's do some venison can i give him some
need one more thanks for the fire man
i'm just kidding what does he got in here though nothing nothing really abuse
well let me i want to feed the horse
hit him far away with the throwing up if you see me try to attempt that like 30
times now i can now rear with this horse i can do this nice all right let's go
i was trying to yell at him almost the camp what's the point of the rear that's a good
question i'm actually not sure fuck i made it hold on a second here
am i dead he's dead what am i tracking unknown animal unknown animal interesting
so am i going this way i guess we're going this way still on the right path right yeah
is that it right there that's the animal what is this thing is it a bug oh it's a rat
it's a rat okay well cool somebody else died here study the rat i didn't kill this lady pick
up strip who died how did you guys die out here i didn't kill these people did i i mean
there's no loot option you got anything in the buggy no okay well i found a rat
people die jeremy well yeah but there has to be a cause somewhere what does this want
me to do in here my control is vibrating right now i'm not sure why follow the rat focus on why
am i focusing on the rat track i'm trying to catch a fucking rat in the field and this
bandit's about to come stop and yell at me all right i was trying to catch a rat out here
mister where'd he go there's like there's so many trails now there he is there i caught
the rat just gonna put him in my pocket okay there's another animal over here
oh it's is that my animal i dropped a few frames well we've been going for about five hours now i'm
actually happy with how stable it has been i can keep going does motor investigate at the body
is there definitely these people here the first one no the dead guy the everyone over here is
dead they're all dead guys oh i can inspect that what am i doing my painting this chapter
show gang savings creeping time alaskan ginseng why did i want to draw this dinosaur bone
okay that's pretty crazy your dead eye bars increased trick shots hunting grafting and other
survivalist related activities yeah you found a dinosaur bone look out for more of these
under travels they might be of use to you at some point one of 30 that's pretty sick
i could loot something here it was on the other side what could i loot there it is this guy
letter from cornwall inspect the document very regrettable that you've rejected the
various extremely generous purchase offers presented you by cornwall and be very concerned
about a company of your size being able to continue to compete in a price of the state
of new handover to secure acceptable rates for railroad transportation so they killed them
that's unfortunate that's not cool that's the guy that i robbed what
yeah that's what i got robbed three horses huh which one is fast he robbed his train
oh okay did he find the unknown animal yeah it was a rat it was really nothing uh
spectacular will they just shoot you oh look look who it is i ain't even gonna ask where
you been how you feeling hi john well glad you're on the man sounds good crafting fire
into the edge of camp we've got uncle 122 camp funds let's go ahead and i'm gonna sell some
shit
please son for me yeah okay dad put your oh wait but this uh this reverend
variance of my crafting at the moment have i not figured this shit out yet
i need to go to the medicine wagon perfect perfect perfect pronghorns
go and wrap it don't need for funds uh yeah just take it make sure you get a good price for
rat meat many thanks so this is the little casino table is opened up here
okay so contribute no i need money morning i need to go like a heist or something let's go to uncle
i do still only have 79 cents i'm not gonna gamble with my last 79 cents over here
somebody over here oh hello uncle careful not to work yourself one way to do it
i was thinking yeah does it pay well eventually so while the rest of us are busy stealing killing
wait this is the actual first mission you get to think all day are you serious where
are we living arthur morgan now you want to head into town see if we can find anything out
sure i got some errands to run great go check the horses are ready you gonna take the old man
you can take us too well what you got planned nothing we'll find something for y'all to do
we always do we're bored out of hydra i got a water right here cooped up here for two weeks
now karen's about ready to murder grimshaw can miss grimshaw spare you can miss grimshaw spare
you was i just fucking off for the past four hours young healthy women want you to take
them you're going back i was doing missions i was going to places i was doing things it was
sure you'll see real civilized let's go all right you know the way yeah
me and the boys got into a bit of a let's go let's have some fun hive them all off a cliff
almost just caused a wreck right there it was close they just got whipped right in the face
letting the top left oh shut up i don't want to hear this anymore slow down oh no
his coach broke down very serious so do i what's going on down the really right there friend
oh you couldn't help me get my horse back from over there could you
i'd really appreciate the help you can give me money this one here will bolt on me too
if i leave them i might make some money here no problem that'd be good thanks it's the white
there all that whoa easy back to the owner come here come here come here this way see you're
good come on well it's a pet and then press oh standing behind the horse you're good come
on punch the horse i'm not punching the horse you don't have to look at it i well i just
i'm trying i want to look at it you don't have to look at it here you go money
trying to impress the women well anyway thank you so i did a good thing see
everybody thought all i do is bad things i just like shoot people
throw people off cliffs and everything that was a good deed
i was holding down r1 to make whatever oh my stomach
how do you fuck up dying by dying i don't know man i went a little too far and i was holding r1
tipped over at the last possible second and i i didn't i and i have to say help that guy
again no i'm just gonna run him over fuck me in a good guy i already did it we know we
we're not doing it again he didn't give me any money
right before no we're gonna hear this again do it again to punish yourself
all right get over here i'm being kind i didn't even do to get the mission yet
here here you go he was checking for the train
no i was just trying to impress the women okay back at it again
i thought i was gonna throw them off i'm just like no don't do it
you're turning into a regular old fairy godmother there arthur what's that supposed to mean
train's not even here guys no just do the mission forget it forget it yeah yes
there there's the train yes it's here i'm trying to hit the guy god damn it
i was trying to run away
i'm just driving by the guy again i thought i could hit the guy and knock him out like
extract a tooth out of the train oh we're going right for the fucking mission man no
bullshit go do it okay well it's not the end of it help the guy bring the horse back
right just go don't the train is gonna i have this one track fucking mind get the
fucking just hurry up and get him calm down he's fine agitated horse easy easy easy you're good
study come with me is there a reason why you're what the fuck was that get it turn on the facecam
why where did he go here here you go thank you you're a gentleman sir a gentleman
ah not really i was just trying to impress the women
to valentine regular old fairy godmother there are means you gotta forget about the
fucking train and you haven't you're hit the guy off the train i'm not gonna hit a
guy off the fucking train
well you did smell those sheep no or is that uncle very funny this looks like a decent little
town people okay we're fine sure don't want to be back up there you think we should have asked
molly to come with us miss oshae is far too high and mighty now for the likes of any real
stop it stop that see what we got main street get some bounties
let me push the guy over that's i gotta push that guy over i gotta knock into that guy
no not on this boy will you remember that though why am i in hell i don't know what do you mean
why am i in hell watch where you put in that thing i'm not getting like arrested right now
am i all right why did i just whip the horse just like i said cultural center of civilization
man at his finest oh here i'll change the uh i'll change the scenery here
we're gonna do what any self-respecting maniac does what do women do work with pleasure we'll
start of the salute okay just stay out of trouble don't get yourself we'll see at the
general store when you're done this is still on my phone come on so that's how you see
yourself is it it's a maniac follow uncle i used to be known as the one shot kid
they're blue no let me stay that was better i'm not gonna ask why it feels more western
doesn't it sad man arthur morgan desperately you're my favorite parasite that's better
no we look like we belong in the west favorite parasite you're my second favorite parasite
very funny i lied it's too dark then rats with the plague then you shut up i mean i i
could turn on like the nintendo switch mode if you want like i got switch lights i got xbox
lights i've got ps4 lights i mean which one do you think i'm gonna do here come on i'm not
on the switch though so why would i do that are you joining me or not all right i don't
fucking fail this mission morning what a fortnight colors so what do you need drop a whiskey for
start something to pass the time while we're waiting on the women yeah that guy should
probably steer clear of the saloon this time yeah i got no okay wait for me outside when
you're done i'm gonna wreck it let me know if you have any questions fellers all right
shopkeeper i need to sell i have i'm selling a ton of shit here all right sell
coffee what else i got a lot of random shit here don't i you won't take any of these the rings
and shit okay miracle tonic what about the gold will he take the gold cigars i have a couple of
these what is milk what do you reckon lamb or sausage well this here's a sheep town the
lamb's the best in the state i don't know what the smell is well that's a ripe cheese health
core moderately just a stamina core you're actually buying for once 75 cents for one of
these horse medicine got no respect for their elders no more go to a fence that's selling
look at this a jaw harp what is this list of yours i got a lot to replenish that's a full
heel but awful time in the mountains all done thank you kindly ah this should do the trick
yep that's fine whiskey just keep one of everything let's go wait for the that's
probably a good idea i sold it okay back at 25 bucks and then take the free money out of the
register right how did i fuck that up because i said two would i just i don't know hair pomade
what does it pomade do slick back hair yes i'm gonna take a bath get bath and i'm gonna
slip slip my hair back oh here's your good health sir and being down here off that
mountain absolutely it's a funny world you know this time my cell miracle tonic by hair greased
to an heiress gentleman he's taking a nap right here got something good what what snuck
into this fancy house acted like a servant girl usually works someone was saying her sister
was taking a trip from new york or someplace it's like too big right rich tours heading to
and then cruising off to brazil okay a train laden with baggage and passing through a bit of
desert country i don't like doing this in time for the tides in some place called scarlet meadows
yeah i know it yeah scarlet meadows right it's real quiet out there sounds good we're still
in care i think at the hotel they were picking up some drunken fellas that they
was gonna rob why it seemed easy i haven't gone for quite a while not here like in the game
i'll hear too but there's tilly over there just not look ideal excuse me sprint get in get your
hands off her friend who are you a friend of mine get off her or what exactly you want to
find out you're making a big mistake tilly jackson just get lost
dickhead i feel that that was a i sucker punched him he was being a bad guy so i
wanted to push the bad guy over
if you don't get out of here right now good timing your mate tilly jackson stab
i ain't cross the street okay thanks arthur face game is in the way of options
all right let's go to the hotel Jesus holy shit that was an entrance uh i'm looking for
somebody i'm looking for a girl who came in here earlier with a drunk feller mid-20s blonde
you'd remember her yeah they're in 2b upstairs are you uh a friend of his a friend of hers
friend of hers no the options move your face how about i just get out of here completely
what purpose no that's like ammo and shit i can't be anywhere
can i not i can't be up here right can i be up here
get the hell out of here sorry wrong room how did you lock it that quick bust through it
hey get out of here buddy i paid they paid the hitter you goddamn animal come here hey
i thought that guy was pathetic trying to play him not very well okay fine you sure
yes let his face fucking smash into the ground
but stupid bastard stupid bastard was boasting about the bank bank sure i know small town banks
are usually a waste of time but desync is back stock town why okay keep investigating i will
okay he's the peanuts okay another nothing i don't know why i look like dante from capcom series
dante uh devil may dante may cry dante devils may cry i can't open this door
dante may cry thank you arthur i don't much like being saved but when i have to be
i understand you okay sure he only punched me arthur punched him a lot harder all right now
hey who's that guy over there looking at us weren't you in blackwater a few weeks back
it's benny from uh vegas you were well i definitely saw you with a bunch of fellers
me no impossible listen buddy come here for a minute i saw you come here come get
what i don't like this me neither go get the girls home i'm gonna go have a
word with our friend be careful are you my horse this isn't that's not my horse where's my horse
get back here please not a horse man okay well that's far enough let's lasso this guy
yeah
why are you telling lies about me no no i've got it wrong partner i gotta bear it wrong
now please step on his fingers i ain't never been in chasing me i've got an unfortunate face
yes yes me too now please pull me up please all right i'm gonna step on his fingers all right
come on i don't know what's going on here you okay partner no no balls what
i literally like i've been throwing dynamite at people and fucking running people over with
my horse truck all day i help one guy up and all of a sudden i'm a coward jimmy brooks
i think it's best for both of us if we pretend this never happened i agree you saved my
you're a good man and i uh here you want a pen it's one of them steel ones
that belt is not even on that is four sizes too big jimmy brooks not usually you see i kind
of look like a clown i wasn't black water i kill people and maybe i should have killed you
i definitely should have should i have killed you jimmy brooks i never saw you no not now
never i think we have an understanding of course we do jimmy brooks i will remember that i've got
a good memory i haven't haven't not not one lick not one sense in this year old mind
come on come on you have a nice day now sir
so i'm not gonna do it you can return the horse you stole to its owner and valentine to gain
honor i'm gonna do that i don't want this thing this thing's where's my horse all right i need i
want to go back to valentine back here please 32 bounty what is this comedy tragedy face here
show all right we're gonna do that first show sounds like fun oh that would have killed
the horse for sure hello mister figure that track real beautiful country around this area
got it there you are sir which one was the guy that needed the horse
you you whose horse is this whose whose horse do i have whose horse is this
give me my actual horse please i don't want this fucking guy do i have any more meat no this is
mine i can't fucking help it i'm sorry it doesn't matter what game it is open if you give me
freedom to do whatever i want i will never do the thing i'm supposed to do it's it'll
never happen i just i accidentally complete missions in these games okay uh i got everything
thanks mr there was a bar fight over here at the saloon this is what is in here uh savings bank
look out you've lost it optional mission is available i can't have my fucking way
not okay the skull definitely gonna be a way to gain honor okay let's let's run right here
i didn't i i thought he was dead isn't this back in the day you if somebody's dead you
think you take their shoes and shit there were no rules is the guy gonna shoot me
i picked up blood on a guy's body who's this what i've lost control i've lost control
i've lost control 67 dollars just die whose horse is this
just just come get me just come get me just come and get me just come and get me how do i say
i surrender who's screaming but i know i'm not having a hundred fucking dollar bounty
anybody in here don't i cowered i don't have any money to pay for this this is how red
i have to just die i had to just start punching the guy don't just don't do it i did i started
slashing people okay i this is all because of the horse discovered i didn't have my horse
they gave me this fake ass horse and then i saw the guy lying on the ground
dead so i looted his body and apparently that's illegal why didn't somebody go pick him up
pick him up and if it's so illegal pick the fucking guy up off the street
bro that could have been a family member for all you know
97 dollars and then i got i got like panicked and i was in the bar and just started blasting
that whole kind of face he was unconscious well okay there we go now i feel at home
whisper let's feed the horse the whole guy and then i just started slashing people
i can't help it like whenever there's a scenario same thing when gta man i would just be in on
mission and i would just drive full speed and hit triangle and dive out of the car
it was so fun to me i couldn't do it i had to do i had to now let's do this little side mission
sheriff's office let's do a bounty here for me well look here maybe this is our man
you a bounty hunter mister maybe make uh i'm gonna this is like the equivalent of when you
go to a restaurant and you just go there for some reason you don't have any money and
oh well you owe 140 dollar bill to the restaurant you're gonna go wash dishes now that doesn't
happen if you don't pay if you just sit there and you go to eat for fucking free and you go
well i could go in the back and wash dishes and cut to you in the back of the squad car
mister tracks delinquents and reprobates like flies now i'm not a feller to pass a quick
judgment and i've been around long enough to never sink to catch a sinner that's that true
me what i need you're gonna be working in the back of the kitchen and i won't ask no question
there was no money so what is it you need why don't you have a look at that poster on the wall
over there he's a low down huckster some poisoning folks with his miracle cure from here to
ansburg killed morton land in the rickets without even pulling a trigger that's not the
guy for the first game is it sick satisfaction out of it a filler over at the saloon says he
thought he saw him by the gorge straight north of here you think you can bring him in
the money's good i need him alive though i want to make sure the women he just gave
the eyes like oh fuck i don't know what this guy playing that's gonna be tough i'll see what
i can do we don't hear asking and we need him alive it's an important point last on
location of the bounty is marked with a skull let's take a look he is far a 97 dollar bounty let's go
but before i don't have any money what am i talking about buy some stuff