Hey, what's going on guys? It's Jerma. I want to show you something. I want to show you something.
We can't do this at the same time. This is a walk-in bath.
Alright, so you just film. This is all I want. I just want the walk-in bath button.
Hey, what's going on guys? It's Jerma here. We're in the hotel room right now. Orbe's behind the camera.
Hello. I just want to show you something.
You ever had a goddamn walk-in bath before?
This is a walk-in bath. This place is fancy.
It's fancy.
I've never stayed in a hotel where there was a walk-in bath. Ever.
Have you ever stayed in a hotel where there was a walk-in bath?
Actually, I have.
This is awesome. I feel like I'm in like heaven.
One thing that's really important about my channel, we got to show the coffee maker that's in the hotel room. Look at this, baby.
Oh yeah. That's like single cup coffee. I don't know if this is like gross. Wait, if I touch this, is it going to charge to my account?
Picked up in room 600.
Look at this. This is Boston. Look at all these cars. People are going places. People are coming places. Where are these people going?
Well, that's a delivery truck, so he's delivering something, apparently.
When you're seeing this, it'll probably be Saturday, I'm thinking, I'm assuming.
Or if you're coming to my channel and you just like got here like yesterday and you just subscribed, this is when we were at PAX East.
That really is true. Hold on, I got to get this.
It's snowing badly.
This is, all right, hold on.
They're huge.
All right, guys, right now it's snowing. The snowflakes are so huge, it looks like paper.
Like, ready, look at this. It looks like pieces of paper. Can we get like a good shot of this?
Come on, come on. Give me a good one. Give me a good one. They're like pieces of paper. Look at that. Look at that. Look at how big that is.
Do you see that? Can you believe it? I can't believe it.
What time is it right now? Saturday morning, day two, PAX.
Solo POV.
I'm stretching with my leg. I forgot I was wearing these. Look at these. I look like I'm 75 years old.
Oh, it's just grandpa. Grandpa decided to come to PAX today and I go, oh baby, that's a tough walk right there.
What the fuck?
Oh my God, star pass out from all the drinking.
I haven't been in a minute.
We found him at Four Prostitutes.
He's running in his dream.
Oh wow, he's looking. Don't wake him up. He's like running.
It looks like you don't have any arms.
Yeah, it looks like you.
You're a fish.
Oh shit.
Oh my God. He's going to die.
Don't forget arms shut up.
And work in it, eh?
Don't forget arms.
Let me show you the time right now, guys.
Right now, it is five after ten.
Hey, I'm doing a Facebook update.
It's five after ten and Orb is still sitting here like talking to people.
So, wait, doesn't Facebook deserve an update on what's going on?
You could just do it on your telephone. Oh, that's right, you're from Schweden.
You can't like do that up here. You're from friggin' Schweden.
Don't forget our meat app.
He's also in his underwear, look.
I want to see the blizzard conference. We only got like 20 minutes.
Let's go.
Oh, real life argument on camera.
So right now, we are en route to Dave's Bar and Grill and get smashed into like a telephone pole.
We're going to Dave's Cheetos Bar and Grill.
Get on my level.
There's the other person who's recording. It's like, screw you for recording.
It really is true.
Let's ruin it.
We're really going. We're going to Burger Boy's having a party.
We're actually walking down the street to his house.
And Chicken Fingers actually said that we get free VIP beers.
We only get one and it's like the cheapest dog shit beer you can drink.
Can you hold this?
This is my love for dream running.
I'm playing copyright infringement.