Everybody's gone crazy. They've all gone crazy. I look over at the chat. I just see I see just like a huge
wave of fire
a fucking fire
Uh, hi guys. Yeah, sorry. I
There's a lot of videos to get through
I had to load them all up
I've been doing it. Uh, i've been doing it all day
I left my room in fucking 16 hours
Why don't we have wine on me already? This doesn't make any sense
And this isn't even this ain't it's anybody
Can hear it. Oh shit. You can't hear it. It's cuz I have like 40 scenes set up. All right, here we go
Happy new year everybody if you've already uh
If you've already celebrated it if you're from, you know forward in time rather than backwards in time like we are here in america
This is going to be
Sort of like the thing we did last year
if
You remember that
we
Chilled up for a little bit
We did
the worst and best things of the year
We're doing it again
This time there are there are almost twice as many categories this year
Almost double the categories
double the fun
half the categories
Uh, the half the categories are
for instance i'm just gonna get i'm gonna just no spoilers, but a best auto moment
was just
Each time my dog actually appeared on stream and it was like five times
so
They all right. There you go
If you're new to the channel
You're probably going to be like what kind of a sick ego fucking maniac has like a look at how my stream awards
Well, uh, it's most of these are the worst things i've done on stream this year
I'm talking worse joke worse noise worst impression
Worst overall stream. There's also a few best ones. There are some best ones. We're not going to go all bad
because you know, I mean come on we got we got worst joke of the decade on here too and
best joke of the decade
a lot of categories
Number four might surprise you
23 in total
That's a quick minus two. Uh, yeah, it was intentional quick. It's just a just a quick quick intentional minus two. Not a big deal
Anyways, thanks for voting. Thanks for participating
We're gonna do something first before because I want people to trickle in
We talked about this yesterday
Let me actually make a tweet saying hey this fucking new year's stream is going new your new york eve
What new year's eve?
Is it new year's eve 2020 or new year's eve?
2019 it's new year's eve
2020 or is it notes? What is it? What should I write?
new year's eve 2019
Hang out new year's eve 2019 awards. Yeah, that's better
We're gonna do the pre-show
And the pre-show is uh, look at all the bootleg dog shit that people have made illegally of my image on redbubble
Should be fun
There are quite a few things in here that don't make very much sense. But you know
We saw this yesterday figured we have to do this
Give me one more second. I do apologize for being late, but you know, we got we got it
We got until at least the ball drops guys
I didn't play the right music either
Budgets were cut this year as you can tell
I'm not in the studio
Not even close
in fact
I
Wait, I in fact not in the studio this year
I in fact
What's that? What?
Who's who is
This year instead of being in the studio
I'm the same fucking place. I was yesterday
Good to see how is everyone I should be in vr
Already drinking wine. That's right
We got a bug. Did I get a haircut?
What do you think?
What do you think did I get who's fucking calling me on new year's eve
So i'm just trying to facetime
What time is it?
Was I getting like new years? It's what time is it? Okay, it's set. It's seven pacific
I was about to get a happy new year facetime
anyways
Welcome everybody. We're gonna start we're gonna move on to the next we don't need music again. It's just a fucking intro
Uh, we're gonna move on to
This thing that I said I wanted to do until people trickle in here
What do you think about the suit?
I got this. Do you know what? I got this
I got this suit
It's the same suit from last year
That's how you can tell
It's way too long and the arms are too short. I didn't even buy you only who cares
All you see is from here down. Anyways
What's on the floor of papers?
What's wrong with that? So I got some papers on my floor. Who cares? It's a messy room. It's not no, it's not
Those are footprints
These are these are these are not these are
He's a footprint
Look, it's a it's a carpet guys
see
Look, I look what I can do
Look see
It's it's just the way the carpet is. It's a long fly carpet. My fly is up, right?
See
It doesn't just like that to be dragging my feet across the ground
You want to see what's on the paper?
fine blank
I dropped the package of computer
And this one this one is not
It's all it is like but it has dog hair all over if you want to see this one
here
I dropped the dog hair all over one on the ground
All right, i'm gonna come clean
My fucking printer is on the ground
Why is there a printer on the ground? Well, look, it's very simple
I don't have any room in in my office for anything. I have this big really nice desk right here and that's it
There's nothing else here
so I
I have consoles here. I have consoles here
I have
monitors and shit
I thought there's no room for a printer
Get a larger desk. This is one of the biggest desks you could buy but what before it being a pain in the ass
This is like 72 inches long and like
like 60 inches wide
This is all right. Let's go
Let's go. We're moving on. Welcome everybody. Let's go. Let's check out redbubble.com
Redbubble.com
Let's just see what this looks like
Okay. So if you type in the word germa into redbubble
You get a you get a really really really cool
But none of this stuff is mine
we have
The giant rat from rat movie. Oh, is this a sticker?
Uh, leon the lion just gave 10 community subs. Thank you leon the lion
All right. So these two these two are exactly the same
The only difference is this one's low res
This is a these sticker I don't get it
16 dollars and 15 cents. Here's a fireman
This actually may be more expensive than just buying it from the actual
Jackbox link
It is isn't it like 20 bucks. Is it cheaper? What was that?
Otto
Hold on. Let me get it. Let me get auto is like, hold on. Did you hear that? He's like hey, hold on
Wait, give me one sec
Yeah, he wanted to come in the room. He was like, let me in. All right, so
Oh, we also have t posing german a 95 classic
T-shirt. I don't know what that means classic
The fireman sticker. This is 250
show auto
He just wants to lie on his little bed
All right here. How do I there you go? There he is
Hi, dude pog auto
All right. Let's go back to this
Uh t posing the 17 bucks fireman sticker. Okay
This is where it gets interesting though. So we have germa fear sticker 250
This is the life is pain shirt by boomer usa
miserable mickey
I need to click this one because it's I don't understand what this one is
So this is a germa 985 official mug
Okay
You gotta be kidding me
There's a emote sized
That's it
This is just a white mug. We saw this yesterday. I can't fucking believe it
This is
$15.76
You could go get
50 of these from target
the exact same mug for probably
30 or 40 bucks
And just put a sticker on it. That's unbelievable pretty good. Uh, pretty good. Uh, germa 985 branded merchandise
Hey, this is coffee cheetos chicken shirt
What is this?
The germa rainbow
This has doesn't have anything to do with me
What does this have to do with me?
It's just like a weird knitted pattern
What was what? Oh, it's a it's my face
That's my face
How do I like we're gonna zoom in how is zooming in zooming out? Hold on. Let's enhance this
You can barely even see it. It's my face though
It's little tiny little faces
I'm not going to buy this. Why would I buy this?
I'm what i'm just gonna encourage
image theft
Uh, this this is my face
Why would I buy the product that's taking my likeness and selling it? Why would I do that?
I do like this, uh, like the default guy that's just uh here though. It's pretty funny. All right, let's keep going
They're apparently like 60 of these
This is a life is pain
Right here pretty standard 22 dollars. Uh, germa 95 blue germ case
That's all right
Get that out of here, please
11 hour seaman lockdown long sleeve t-shirt
I survived the 11 hour seaman lockdown. I watched germa stream seaman for 11 hours 9 minutes and 58 seconds
All right. I i'll let this one i'll let this one slide. I'll let that one slide
You know, I mean that's I like that one. I like that one good slider
Sweet genius, not even my content. That's the star
German logo tri blend t-shirt. Okay with the rat's long sleeve
What this is germa 985 germa 985 have a nice day
Have a nice day. Don't be an accessory to make the 100 billion plastic bags in the u
Wait, what is this?
Why is there a plastic bag warning?
Oh, this is hold on
Look at this
Did a bot just rip this somehow and put this on here?
Why would the bot algorithm say do all this?
German 985 germa 985 and has nothing to do with rats
Have a nice day
Warning to avoid danger of suffocation keep this plastic bag away from babies and children
Do not use this bag in cribs beds carriages or play pens
The plastic bag could block nose and mouth and prevent breathing
In fact, this plastic bag is so destructive to the environment that if you really care about the future
You could seriously just reuse paper bags from here on out. This bag is not a toy
Don't be an accessory to make the 100 billion plastic bags in the u.s
Each year it makes it 12 billion barrels of oil
I mean
That's not that's not that's not a bad message, right? But I what do I have to do with?
plastic bag
Are they implying that I use them all the time?
Why have to why am I on here? Oh, I don't whatever let's keep going
And they say this is a plastic bag. It's not this is not a plastic bag
Uh the spies that's a classic. Okay spies
The germa 985 do they cover?
Interesting
This is 86 bucks for a twin
All right. Well, what is uh, what does a king look like?
131 dollars
I feel like this is a scam though. Are you even gonna get it?
But what if you don't get like what is it? Are you even gonna get this or is it just a bot in?
I'm so confused
Read the reviews all the reviews are copy pasted. Remember we looked at this
Love the new duvet cover love the new duvet cover, but it did not come with matching pillowcases
Probably in the fine print but I was a little disappointed because the duvet cover was so cool
Extremely nice high quality high quality with beautiful graphics
I don't I don't know what this is
This product was just what this product was just what I hoped my daughter absolutely loves it
You see this same shit on ios
We've gotten to a point
On the internet where nothing is real
If you if you go to a review site and fucking
5,000
Comments 5,000 reviews are on a product
Maybe 25 of those are real, right? I mean, how can you even tell there's no way?
I mean you can tell because
But what if these are real people?
These might be real people
I don't know. Well, i'm not buying it. Uh, germa slim fit t-shirt. It's just the
I'm not small. I'm compact acrylic block
I mean, this is
Anybody could say that
I'm not small i'm compact was this made it's one of those glass things that you
Look at that font
Yeah, what's with the old west font?
That's just making sense
By the way, didn't even get the quote, right?
So this is truly bootleg
Is i'm not tiny i'm compact
Didn't even get the quote right
Come on, you're gonna gotta get the quote, right?
germa
This is mature content germa the dick what?
I don't know what that is. I'm not clicking that one
I'm not clicking on the dick one
Why is there
Germa a dick something i'm not clicking that
Wait, I okay i'll click it
Display mature content
I don't understand
I don't get it
I don't I don't I don't get it but i'm this is it's okay. It's an i it's an iphone cover
No, it's a samsung galaxy case
There's like a weird camera pointing
Show it. I feel like i'm scared to show this. I don't know if this is I don't know what this is
The the dick and there's a camera I don't get it. Why is this not why is this not safe for work?
Look at the edges
It's just the dick and it's a samsung galaxy cover
It's just it's really yes. It's very crusty
Well, okay
Cool. That's a star case. It looks pretty cool. Although I think doesn't even I didn't have one of those already
coffee cheetos and chicken t-shirt
I don't know what this is
Uh, this is I think this is tf2 logo
German t-posing flim slim fit t-shirt
Ding wall tapestry
Ding wall tap ding
Oh supposed to be my teeth
Look at how stupid this fucking looks
This you dressing up this whole room with all this cool artsy stuff
And then this is on your wall hung up with two thumb tacks
This is awful
This is a bed sheet
We're a pillowcase. This is so bad
ding
Add to cart. There's wait. There's even this bigger ones. How big
It just makes the sheet bigger
64 dollars, by the way
All right. That sounds good
cool
German 985 you are now cursed meme coasters
This is from yesterday
This is yesterday
What how did you?
What somebody made this in the last seven or eight to twelve hours or something you are now cursed coasters
I mean they're reasonably priced but
I wouldn't buy them
Dripping out 85 kill bill frame
That's so stupid
84, all right. Hold on 84 bucks. There's only small frame style flat frame
Looks a little better frame color
but uh
Black. All right. I don't hate it
Look at this shit on the left
Oh my god, it looks like a worm
This is terrifying the large. How big is the large?
Look at this. Okay. Look at the image on the left. That's the best thing about this. Do they even they don't even have a small
Okay, there it is
Okay, let's take a look at the medium
That image on the left just keeps getting stranger
Why though? I don't know
I I have no idea why anybody would do this
German 95 clown face
Terminant five. Is this me?
board print
This is fathead
the greekie grinner
German 95 greater than or equal to five eight slim fit t-shirt
funny
How it feels to chew five gum classic t-shirt
You guys are quick. This is
You guys are quick
This is literally again from yesterday
Okay, if I do three x does it change?
No, it'd be so funny if it was just a huge guy
It feels to chew five gum. All right, let's keep going
We said german 95 giant
You can not all swear on red bubble. What are you doing?
German 95 golden tall mug. All right
German 95 classic bowl cut, uh fitted scooped shirt
This is the same person the same fucking person has done like a hundred of these
German 95 crot. Is it supposed to be Napoleon? Yeah
German 95 minecraft. Let's play coffee pasta german 885 zoomer
No more heroes classic bike shirt. Look at the price of the golden mug. How much is the golden? Oh my god
tall mug
Holy shit. Are you out of your mind?
All right, let me I got I got here. Listen to this
Don't you think that red bubbles should have some type of system?
that
Makes it so you cannot have a coffee mug be more than fifty dollars
You know what? I mean, like don't you think that should be like a system in place where it's like, oh hey, uh,
You're selling a coffee mug for a hundred and seventy five thousand dollars. Um
Well
It's golden you get 20 up the free market
But seriously
600 what if somebody accidentally downloads this you know, what if it's already like an old lady is like i'm gonna buy a present for my
Grandson, I know he loves german at eight five and he loves the color gold
Let's see this one. That's uh, six hundred six hundred and sixty nine cents. That sounds good to me at the car
What if it's an old lady?
You're gonna get scammed. Jesus christ
Stretched face shirt is a shower curtain. I actually really don't hate this one
This one could kind of work somewhere
I don't want anyone to wear that shirt in public
Where does it work?
Wait, did we get big bits?
Did we? Oh fuck. Yeah, we did
Vilemi gave five. I don't have my notifications on because of uh videos we can play. Uh, Vilemi fifth five thousand bits
Thank you. Vilemi fifty dollars. Hey, sorry. Jeremiah missed the money stream last night
No one's ever obligated to give me money. I was busy checking out vr anime games on my new oculus
Anyway with the will the green screen doctors be making a return this year?
No, because that was nominated for worst joke of of 2019
So, um, i'm bringing them back
What another wait, what do you mean one came up right now?
What are you talking about?
Dirty dirty carpet. Oh, no. No, we'll get we'll get to it. We'll get to it. We'll get there's like still like 20 more
There were stretched face
It's elliot man elliot elliot. You gotta relax. You gotta relax, dude
I don't want to have to do it like what is all this?
Let's put it on a king. This is a minecraft skin. This is freaking me out
germa 95 red bubble skin
What the fuck you you can't you know, you shouldn't be allowed to do this
All right, stop this
What it's why you have all these?
The most interesting man in the world t-shirt germa 95 solar system. I already have one of these
I already have one and it's it's not just the cutouts of emotes
I already have one of these
Free nvidia swag bag. See this is going into copyright territory that i'm not even capable of removing
Free nvidia swag bag. I can't I can't even get this removed if I wanted to
Stretch face and oh another about penis apparently
cool
Holy shit guys
I survived the crate depression t-pose assert dominance rat movie giant rat st. Germa palace hotel beach
Burning team captain hat
Now I have no no, I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this
I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. We got we have
We have new year's eve stuff to do. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this. I ain't doing this
I'm gonna do i'm gonna get one more. I ain't doing this
What is that?
How is it a penis what okay, this is freaking me out. All right. All right. All right. All right
All right, i'll look at the dirty carpet and then we're gonna go move on to the ceremony
What is this?
Wait a minute. What how do you even make don't you have to go through like a
Don't you have to go through a process to?
What is this?
Don't you have to go through like a process to get these things like approved or what?
Is this a carpet?
Or is this an image?
It's fucking peter griffin down
By the way, it's really hot in this room and i'm already sweating my ass off
Do you okay you saw the beginning of the string?
Look at this shit
Oh my god
I'm fucking sweating
Look at me
I'm already i gotta get like a wet towel. Oh, i'm just knocked over the wine. I haven't even had one glass of wine
all right
Again, uh, thank you. Welcome. That was that was the small little pre interlude
Put on a shirt
What I have here in my hand and wait till you see how thick this stack is
Let's do the thing. We don't have enough categories this year
uh
We do I know they're little I know I know they're little they they looked bigger on the amazon
List I thought they were going to be big and elaborate and made out of gold
Uh, they're not they're
They're very very small
There's a lot here. There's 23 categories to go through
They're perfect
All right, you guys ready?
Ready to do the first category of the 2019 new year's eve. Welcome to new year's eve stream. I'm gonna start off
with the best
New character of the year
Now a character could be anything character could be somebody that was brand new on your screen
A new person that we created or or an entire character that we didn't even create that just kind of came into our lives
so
without further ado
Ladies and gentlemen here are the nominees
for best
new character
Stop you're hurting him. What name the automaton?
She she she toe
she toe
little she toe
s h e e
t
Awful name. Why?
This little she toe. Hello and welcome
to germa's first ever
spooky trivia night, uh
I'm your host shannon sharon. How tall are you?
What how tall what do you mean? What?
How tall might you be five six?
Six feet tall six one. Are you sure?
Yes, any empirical system
I think we have goosebumps books part two goosebumps one goosebumps for
1600 goosebumps part two. All right, let's see what the question is here
What do we got?
Nice job is naruto's father germa
Might you have an opinion?
Please please give an incredibly warm welcome
to the amusings
of cuddles
And paulie polite
Got one. Okay. Well, why don't we show that there's a special audience member here that we're gonna be let's see who it is
Are you ready? Who did you paint?
Nobody voted for the clowns by the way, nobody spoiler alert nobody voted for the fucking
Well, thank you so much to cuddles and
Which I play here i'm thinking um, maybe
Enter no, I don't think so. I think i'm gonna play the greeted grinner is a new card
I can still hear him
Person in that car somebody said the music's gonna be loud on all of them by the way because they've baked into every video
Yeah
Music's too quiet
Any further for further ado?
the winner
Of the 2019 best character of the year
Cheeto at thirty one point nine percent of the vote. Congratulations cheeto. It was it wasn't even a contest
Cheeto absolutely fucking destroyed
Uh, I was actually I thought the rumor might have taken that the rumors maybe it was it wasn't that close though
There were a lot of people on that list in 30 plus percent
Cheeto wins by a mile
moving right along
Let's continue
With the best auto moment. These are the categories that you know, you gotta you gotta get through them pretty quick
Does that who actually?
I can't say that everyone says she way she does what do you mean cheeto sucks?
She does what's wrong with talking about thirty percent of you
More than thirty percent of you. I disagree
anyways
Here are the nominees for best
Otto's my dog if you don't know and
sometimes he shows up on stream and these are
This was not supposed to be a category, but it is
For some reason you have a dog. Yeah, I mean there's eight thousand people here
Best auto moment that could be like that could be like somebody that lives down the street
If you've never been here before so
Over I know I I showed him already
Where is he? Oh, he's blending in with the with the blanket. All right, the nominees for best auto moment are
Okay, all the twos are done. So this these are both forwards. So this has to be like this
What the fuck is that?
Why is this playing?
Is this supposed to be distraction?
Did I do that right? Oh, this is playing the whole video or this
That's it. It's just doing the video. Okay
three
Okay. Oh wait, can you show a dog shitting on stream? This is no you can't right? It's not inspired three one
Three three one three
Three three one three four four
One four four three one three three
There's too many sounds
You asked for it all night
There you see there's the dog. Where's the auto?
See you guys woke him up to do this shit
There you go, there's our toe look at how tired he is
Okay, put him to bed. Well, he belongs in bed
That's not that's my that's not a paid actor. That's my girlfriend. Good night. Just like that dog
Doggy like babies
maybe just like
That was cute
see
He's too perfect for this world. He is fancy. He's so good
He really is he's like the best dog ever
He is eight
He's eight years old. He's fantastic. I love him
Hey, I don't
Hello, that's just a clip right behind me
This category sucks. I was I was bullied into putting this in. I was bullied into putting this in
Yeah, it's me
He's like, what are you doing?
There you go
Auto spotted. This is just what he does guy
Hey
Hey, hey, what are you doing? This is sad. This is a sad song. Are you napping in here?
No, it's not
Look at that tail ready. Hey, thanks for the subs by the way. Hey
What are you doing?
Uh glucose amino chondroitin
Oh, what do I do? What do I get?
Uh, yes if you um
When your dog only shows up four times on stream you have to reach for something else to put in the category list
Uh, it was the flash in the corner and what am I gonna think?
That was auto
uh, and the winner for best auto moment of 2019 is going to go to
Who cares
Picross interruption auto picross 27 percent of the vote
What do you mean rude? Well, I I love this dog
But all those clips with the same clip and with all the besides there was all the same video
Otto, would you like it? Would you like to say something auto?
All right, zoom in on that and put it on the list for next year. We saw the tail wag. Yeah
All right coming up next is I don't think I do I need to introduce this one
Are you sure you want me to introduce?
it's uh
ladies and gentlemen the nominees
Uh for worst speeder of the year
Parker griffin and dinklage all famous faces sharing this common name. Dr. Schmoinson. Yes, I believe that is
Beater who is beater?
Who what is beater?
Why is he not talking? I I mean
I'm just trying to focus to get back to the 500 beaters in seven and a half minutes six and a half minutes
Still not big enough to get these
It's a goddamn maze beater
It's a maze beater
Okay, that was kind of funny. Not really
I think I got it. We're good. Hey, but we're in the end game here
How do you leave your voicemail on a public phone?
Later, uh, this year's worst feeder of the year
What do you think what do you think what was the worst? Uh, what was the worst budget?
I told you we're getting this shitty
Okay, auto was a fine category
Best question. So that auto was the only one that didn't make sense
What do you think?
Dr. Schmoinson beater for 32 percent of the vote by a lot actually
What was in second place? Let me see the schmoinson beater was apparently the worst one
But I don't know if I agree with that. I think I disagree with that one
The academy I think was got that one wrong
Uh, what came in second place?
Because that was 30 32 percent
Worst beater. Where is it?
Anyway, no, it was close. It was pretty close
So voicemail peter
Was the next one
Which was at 23 percent of the vote
so
Not a huge spread
By the way, this category will not return next year. I promise. I know I said that last year. I
I I promise this will not return next year. Please clip this and save it somewhere because don't let me do this again
in fact
Now that means I can't ever do it again this next category
Lying. Why is that a lie?
Not quite not yet. Not a lie yet
anyways moving on to uh
Hold on. Let me like burp internally this next category is
No, actually the next
Two categories in a row have to do with my physical appearance
Uh, we're coming up with next worst hair of 2019
worst hair
uh
I like having long hair
I like having
It shaped and be able to lay back behind my ears and have it. I I like having hair like this
Maybe not this long in particular, but
uh
Sometimes especially when it gets hot in here if i'm doing something or if things get a little
I've been streaming for six seven plus eight hours in a row and I don't get up and I go to the bathroom
I sit back down. Sometimes it gets a little messed up and there's not much you can do about that
And these are the times that people said was the worst it's ever looked on string
You I could throw water in my face into my hair, but then it gets all wet and stringy. I don't like it
So here you are. Here are your nominees for worst hair of 2019
Doesn't need that much more of an introduction
Why do you have braided hair? I'm leaving it. I ain't gonna fix it. Fuck that
It's a fucking drunk
God
It just it just happened. I don't know how
I have no idea
I don't I don't know why that happened. This is drunk as i've been on stream
This looks as I don't even care
You know, like you sometimes you give a shit about your appearance like when i'm when the when the webcam goes on, right?
And I know the webcams on usually i'm a little self-conscious, you know, I want to make sure that I look okay
How's my face looking? Do I look all right? Do I look okay?
I don't care right now and you can just tell
And this is like these images are gonna come back to haunt me in like fucking two years
Or one
Like I don't even care. Like I just don't
Typically i'd be like, oh hold on before I turn the camera on let me like okay
I know my hair is wicked fucked up because I was in the wind
I I know my hair looks like fucking al dente spaghetti today and that's because I was out in the wind
I was in the wind
sire
You have so many dropped frames and my family needs to use the internet and go to amazon
And buy cases of ocean can I nominate this for worse zip 2019 because that's and small small figurines of
Venom we need to and then he looks over
And he finally makes a decision right is filming off my camera
Hey, thanks
Thanks lock coke gaming
The room is in my room not on this video
So what do you guys want to do? I can I can barely do anything. I I really don't want to lie to you guys
Hey, how's everybody doing? How are you? Yeah, it's been rough, but it's all right. I'm doing all right. I'm doing good
How are you doing? How's everything going? How are the kids?
Yeah, I don't know. I'm on the kind of screens of people under the bridge now, you know, that's what I do
It's been real. I just didn't get the job done
a lot of uh
A lot of good cat a lot of good nominees there a lot of good nominees, but they can only be one winner
Unfortunately, they can only be one and the winner for the worst hair in 2019 is going to go to
this
Won by a lot with 35 percent of the vote
Freud on red wine hair
With 35 percent of the vote guy under the bridge came in with about 27 percent
Worst hair of the year if I were to pick that one if it were going to be me
Uh, the vr trainwreck hair was disgusting
That's not only the worst hair i've ever had in 2019. That was and that didn't even I mean it was up there
The vr trainwreck hair came in third place
with 19 percent of the vote but
My god
It was un it was ridiculous. It looked like it was made it looked like it was dirty
It was dirty and greasy and looked like somebody put a bunch of hair gel in it and squished it together and held it
Tighten and fucking let it go after like an hour
Oh, it was horrible
We got another category to do
This is worst face
Worst face
Uh, we we do worst hair last year didn't do worst face last year. This is a new category this year
And it's a worst face
This is the worst face i've ever made on stream
In 2019 whether it's being shocked or trying to make do something funny that doesn't come across as funny. It's just ugly and strange
Uh, this is the cat these are the nominees
for worst face
of 2019
I hope you're proud of me. I hope you're proud mom the worst face of 2019
The big lipstick with 36 percent of the vote
It kind of destroyed
Yeah
It really wasn't close
after big lipstick
farting and screaming playlist
was
In second place at 13 percent and then the greedy grinner
at 13.08 percent which was farting scream was 13.2
Everything was very close recent bias. Maybe
maybe
But it is written down there very sloppily because you can tell the stream was late today, right?
We started we started the appointments like and there's a few reasons for that reasons are for what you're about to see
I had to get these written down and i'm just like
red lipstick
Because I got I got these
From I told you from amazon and i'm going do I just fucking do do I just like
Do I go to a store right now and get some more of these do I go to a store?
I freaked out and I was like, I just got whatever it doesn't matter
I was like about to get in the car and about to go. Uh, no, whatever. Okay
Just put them on the little ones
He's a professional streamer, by the way
No, I told you there were budget cuts this year that last year we were in a studio and I had all like that
A big allowed of trophies
We had to cut a few uh corners this year. What are you doing? What are you doing? What is this?
Why is we're spamming this? What is this?
This is spamming so fast. I can't even
All right. It's not january 1st, by the way
so
this uh
You can't uh, you can't nominate this
I'm such a fucking cartoon character
I
Can't even replicate that
That's apex twin
Do wait, did we say who it was? Yeah, it was a big lipstick. Of course it was moving along
Now we're moving into categories that
Potentially have a lot of nominees
Last year, this was an incredibly last second thing besides being in the studio
Uh, this was an insanely last second thing last year and really try to get as many good high quality
Categories as possible first, right?
This year and people only had like two or three days to nominate stuff and it was because it was bang bang bang
It was really quick last year
but
This year people had about a week and a half or so to figure out what they wanted to nominate and
There were a lot of nominees in some of these worse noise had like 25 nominees
We had to shave some off
It's a lot of nominees in some of these categories and we're going to show I think this one's doesn't not quite yet
But moving on to worst singing of the year, this is a new category
by the way
Both of these categories are the same category
The nominees in this category are no better than the nominees in this category
They I could switch these in my hands right now and you would not know the difference
so
We'll go ahead
And start with worst singing of the year
Let's see what the nominees are and this is the one that goes rolling around at the speed of sound
Right something like that
Sing him a song. Oh
Holy fuck that was horrible
Oh canada
Our home and sacred land
True patriot side and all thy sons command
with
Street rat street rat. I am not a street rat
Gotta go to sleep gotta have some cheap gotta have some fun while I have time
Oh
I love the music in the background of the music
Worst singing of the year, apparently
Oh
This one wasn't even a fucking contest
Not even close not even close
This is ridiculous how unbelievable this was skewed
the winner of worst singing of
2019 with
50 percent of the vote and you have to remember
There were one two, three, four five six seven nominees in this category
The category the nominee after that had 13 percent
And it was eehee never gonna give you up
uh
Also, by the way
This is the first win of i got a feeling singing stream and second nomination of the night for worst stream of the year upcoming
That's on here a few times
That stream is on here
More than once also nominated for worst stream of the whole year
Okay, uh now it's best singing is now this is best singing
By the way, you'll see what i'm talking about when I say they both get the same damn category
I should have just had a singing category where like two people won
Here are the categories and the nominees
for best singing of the year
I will never stop it
Uh
You got a friend in me
with
I told you I told you
I'm so fucking angry right now
I can't even tell who's talking i'm gonna lose again. I was singing you can't you can't hear this is all fucking
Why is it like this
G
Of the 1,400 people that unfollowed tonight, um, I hope to see you soon. Hope to see you back
Only 17
You can dance you can laugh having the time of your life
All right, you know
Shit plays back to you
And you know, you've seen it you've heard it before
And you just you're looking at what you've done over the last year and you just kind of go
I now I understand what people think I do drugs on stream
You know what I mean? I got it. I get what you mean now when you say like, oh, hey
Is this dude like do fucking drugs?
It's kind of hard to defend
Against these nominees
anyways
The winner of best singing you already know what it is. Do I even need to do the fanfare?
Do I ever need to tell you do I it was if it was on the list it was gonna win, you know that
Qrs from the mind show stream at 30 percent of the vote
This was not as uh as far away as you thought it was
30 voted for qrs
Uh green day was after that
Somehow singing a katamari song was in third place with 16 percent of the vote
Which you couldn't it was me going like this. I know people are gonna fucking freak out
People are gonna be really upset with me and they're gonna tell me to stop but I need to show you what people are gonna say
Don't fucking do that. Don't stop doing that. But I need to you just need to hear it
That's what I was doing i'm not I do it I didn't do it for long I didn't do it for very long calm down
That's what I was doing. I was humming that to the beat
Apparently 16 percenting it thought that was the best thing i've done all year
I that's just what i'm not gonna go i'm not doing anymore
Those are new categories, by the way, this next category is
One of my favorites
best one guy moment of the year
Best one guy what is one guy moment for those of you that might be new to the channel
uh one guy
Is especially a one guy moment is when one person in the stream in the chat
Can either throw off the entire stream or can dictate the conversation exactly where it goes
I'll look over I will read something that somebody says
and
It will change the course of the entire history of the channel
so
If you stay on this stream
There's a possibility that you will one day be the one guy
That I would look over and say hey dude, like eat a ghost pepper on stream and i'll go. All right fucking cool, dude. Sure
I mean i'm not gonna do that, but I can at least pretend to right?
Uh best one here the nominees for best one guy moment of the year
A couple of these chicks shouldn't even fucking be on here, but I they made me laugh for a second. So they're on here
Oh, okay. Here we go
Nominees for best one guy moment of the year are as follows
Yo, germa, you're going to poppin gamer this year. We'd love to see you there
popping gamer
What's popping gamer? Oh, this was are you going to twitchcon?
One guy strikes again, and this is actually one guy from yesterday the day before
so
Somebody said this and it's just hey dude nancy drew. I would love it
I'm like, oh two days went by or day went by I slept on it and I woke up and i'm like, yeah, okay
Everybody loves fortnight jimmy legs germa my legs
Is what the official germa 985 popsicle would look like that's pretty good
Ice cream bar, please read this, please imagine germa's real name is harold or something. What why do they need to read that?
Give me like some credit just look
I don't know
How tough it is to be able to determine what's fucking real and not real?
This is the image. This is the original actual image that for those of you watching the vlog
This is the image
somebody linked this
Like really like that could it could be but it's not even though it could
Best one guy moment of the year
Oh, this is uh, this is a landslide
Uh germa thinks a photoshop of his face is a real face
47 of the vote. Yeah, uh, that was that was I was outrageous
I really truly thought that it was real at first
This next one is very close
But if you pull up that image
seriously
Pull up that what what what's that? What are you linking? What's this tweet? Somebody says no two
What is this?
Breaking news twenty one twenty thousand nineteen twenty the year 2019 is getting a sequel that's said to replace the year 2020
What and this number replies? Yes, and it's the rat
This is like three thousand likes on twitter. I didn't see what what what?
Wait, what?
I didn't see who I didn't see what that was
Lil Nas
Giant ratted
What?
What the that's this?
Is this a fake account? No, it's not this has three and a half million followers
This can't be a fake account. Is this a fake account? No, holy shit
And the award for best tweet of 2019 goes to
Oh my god, that's kind of fucking crazy
Uh, that's pretty cool. Is it fake?
It's not is it fake did I get faked out?
I'm so confused right now of what's happening. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right
Hey
You know, i'm available
Just saying i'm available. I'm always available. I got nothing going on right now. I've got fucking nothing going on right now
besides just
Sweating in my shirt
For what i'm i'm kidding. I'm kidding
Uh the next category
I'm people saying the music's a little too loud. I'm sorry about that
Uh, the music is baked into every video
They were like 30 they were like 30 editors making these so like we try to get them as quick as we could
Can't fix
Sorry, you'll be all right
just
Fucking go like this
Okay
Uh worst vroom of the year if you don't know what a vroom is
a vroom
Is when I live in a place in by the way live in las vegas if you don't know, uh, I live in las vegas
and
I live in a spot where people like to either mod the fuck out of their cars
Or blow by the street that I live on
And it's really really irritating and it ruins streams. Sometimes it gets in the way
One actually happened about 30 or 40 minutes ago. So it happened already on this stream
it
I lose concentration. It's it's really fucking annoying
so
these are the worst times that they happened on stream this year and
I'm not even sure how accurate these nominees are
because
There's been so many of these that I think people forget just how fucking loud and obnoxious they are
There are some real good ones on here
Really good ones. What are you looking? He's like it's got the same hair too. He's got the same mustache hair
This could have been me
But if you know, you know, what's what's that joke like? Hey, i'm gonna tell my kids that like this was that that per
Just tell your kids that I was the mask because look look at this
It really could be that
That that's just me with makeup on
That is it's just me that's me with makeup on my nose is too pointy and big man that guy
All right, let's move on
This is worst room of the year coming up. I can't fucking
That's that's crazy. It's crazy to me. All right, uh worst room of the year here in the nominees. Well get there. Let's go g
Take me to the bary center. What the hell is going on here? Here we go
Does it say if there's life on it?
All right, there's life on this planet or life on this one
where's my little like the
Seismograph meter don't have one of those
Look up are those motorcycles in my room? I'm in vr. I can't tell
pistol
Shotgun shotgun. I don't like the shotgun
Pretty good timing pretty good time
It was a one minute and 12 seconds first lap
See you again in a minute and 15 seconds
I'm gonna give the shotgun
When I get the money
All right, I just I felt like somebody was just going to just drive into the house
Like I really felt like somebody was going into the window like I thought that was somebody in a little drone
Flying and crashing into my window. That just scared the shit out of me
That was in the house. Yeah
That sounded fake if somebody's in a pod racer out here. That was a star wars fucking pod racer
That wasn't even a car
You you give her a little thing like oh say goodbye. You don't just like
flush
Whoa
Keep her in a box. You really can't do that. Gabby will start to smell up the drawer
I'm glad I cannot fall down this unless I really fuck this part up right here
All right that fucking guy driving the car the guy in the fucking car that just sped by at a thousand miles per hour
It's just screened in my ear
What the fuck man?
That's so annoying
Whatever. That's two that's I
Give me a break though. Seriously. I get to be mad at that
I get to be upset about that. That's so annoying and somebody's screaming outside your window as loud as they can
Like somebody just threw a glass bottle at my house while I took that jump
I'll get back up there. All right, you can hear that one was real
Yeah, I know you hear the fake one right now, but that one was real
that was not a
Uh, yeah, it happens all the time. It's such a pain in the ass
and
It really it really is starting to become a pretty major problem. It really is
What would you guys say? Um, I would say
Probably two or three times a stream, right? It has to be it has to be at least two or three times a stream
soundproof your house
Okay
Worst room of the year. This was very close
There is the closest one all night by the way
at
24.9 percent of the vote
right on time
Distraction jump king pod racer. No, that's not correct. I blew it. Uh distraction jump king
Pod racer was right below it
Distraction jump king was at 24 percent pod racer was at 22.5 percent
There you go. That was very very close closest one all night. It was lala land
I'm, not looking forward to these categories coming up
Because these when now we're getting into embarrassing territory like we haven't already apparently we haven't already
I like to do impressions off the cuff. Sometimes they're good. Sometimes they're bad
Uh, most of the times they're bad
The hair was pretty embarrassing. You're right. Uh, most of the time they're very bad
um
This is another one of those categories where there's two of them for some reason
worst impression and best impression
Another interchangeable list and some of these nominees don't did you no you didn't okay. Yeah, you i'm good
Uh, a lot of these nominees just kind of people nominated I think just to just to be funny
One of one of these nominees in particular and we went through and we were like, all right. This was this was nominated
This was nominated like six times
So we yeah, we have to put it in we can't just like leave it out, but it's not it's it's barely anything
You'll see the nominees for worst impression of the year whether of a video game character a celebrity
or a
That's not there's no other impressions. There you go. Worst impression of the year the nominees are
Hey
Okay, hey, oh boy, I need a uh, I need to get myself some ice cream and some extra cola
Hire me i'm available. I am available. He's gonna rage a lot this stream. Why the simpsons?
How can you get mad at homer simpson seeing all these toys makes me wish I was a kid again
If it's any consolation, I still think of you as a child. Thanks. I wish the court
Shot I do that. I love how they have the combine voice that like
Like that was just delete that whole clip it was not even worth watching
Dude, what's the best peter griffin impression? You got it. Hey, uh, no
Why don't wait did I just do I have to walk behind the counter and make the change goofy?
What the hell do you do here?
Well, I don't know anything about mad donald that's okay goofy i'll take care of you
Hey, okay. It's your thing. I did all the time
Oh, you're all about sex aren't you quagmire?
Yeah
All right, let's go gonna jump oh I can't wait to fight
No, I can't it's too early
I don't know how it's possible that this this one last year
This one whatever who cares this one leg
It's donald duck donald fucking duck
17.8 percent of the vote donald duck won last year for worst impression. I just thought just I should just not do donald duck anymore
I'll just i'm never gonna I will never do donald duck ever again
I'll never try
Take a quick wine break
Try try it now try it now. All right
Fucking it's it's 2019 still fuck you donald duck was 17.8 percent by the way
This was very close
Canadian homer simpson was at 16.7 percent of the vote
17.8 for donald and 16.7 for homer simpson. It was all awful. There's two peter griffins
Just like the bad ones. There are also some good ones. I do have at least
Like half a tank of talent. Okay, i'm not gonna say i got a full tank of talent
I got a half a tank of talent
Look, you gotta know what you have
Best impression of the year coming up
Here are the nominees get off the screen
I see some of you guys in this chat with your moms going
You bit your controller because you lost one of these missions like 15 times in a row. I know it jerma
How is it possible that you could be this bad?
It's it's joe rivers
Oh children
Absolutely, it's unbelievable. Oh darling. You look so beautiful right now on the runway
Let me tell you something about just how I forgot about the fuck
I forgot fucking let's go. I can't fix it. I think I have this voice forever. I have this voice forever
I did I fucked it up. I coughed too much and now it's over. I actually have this voice forever
This is it. My career is over
you know, that's that's why this game is so difficult actually now that I think about it because
If you it's like triangle triangle triangle triangle l right that's easy triangle triangle triangle l but the way that he talks
No, I know what we stop the target. It's just uh, it's not doesn't add up for my brain
Jerma, can you pretend to be elmo thanos for the rest of the stream?
Reality is already
Mr. Noodle reality is often disappointing. Mr. Noodle. That's all you get
All right, what if we can do a bit of gallop impression, uh wins the contest. Okay, uh go
Go your turn go go go
It's gonna be a post post human post human poggles i'm telling you post human
What's gonna happen is the seaman are gonna come up here and they're that's where
Seaman are gonna come up and they are gonna totally just absolutely wipe us out and they're the globalists
We're gonna take over with the seaman and then it goes real high. It goes real high joe
sorting algorithm noise
Oh, yeah, I know what you're talking about
The things they yeah. Oh you're killing me. Yep
Oh, I have to listen to it now then it goes like
Oh, I have to hear it right now, let's go
For 15 pm
Don't you think your mother has had enough aggravation carrying you in her belly for nine long months
Stop being a freeloader and step out into the real world
Do it man, come on, okay, let's go
I I cut that one off accidentally
Like I said, I have to take it out
The winner is best impression of the year. Why I don't what do you think thanos elmo?
With 22.5 percent of the vote elmo was there last year too. How many times have I done elmo on this stream?
Elmo here's what I don't understand. Okay, let me give you I want to break down some data for you
so
apparently
One of the worst things I did as an impression for last year was torture me elmo that got
Like 15 percent of the vote, but also thanos elmo
won best impression
How could I be on two different categories? I don't understand
Uh sorting algorithm was in second place followed by ed ed and eddie
Uh both at about 12 percent
respectively thanos elmo
All right. Now we're getting into the real the real stuff here
Still plenty of categories to go still a lot of categories to go
Coming up next is
We make a lot of jokes on this stream. First of all, some of them are better than others
Some of them take a lot of time
And they either land or they don't
These are the nominees
For the worst joke of the year that took more than five minutes to set up
You good? Are you good ato?
Yeah, he's good
Uh, yeah, so this is the worst joke of the year that took more than five minutes to set up
whether that's finding clips and images or
Getting sounds ready and then all right. It's been like 15 straight minutes. Let's try to make something funny happen and
Didn't work out so well
Here are the nominees for worst joke of the year that took more than five minutes to set up
I'm here with my friends. I've got my friends here. We're all doctors here. This guy's taking up my fucking limelight
All right the nominees
for
best
Joke taking more than five minutes to set up
Does that be real?
But so how do I prepare for how do I do I prepare for this everyone be laughing your ass off, right?
Like I I want like I want only luls in the chat
The cat is seriously up up in the tree
I'm trying to find a way I put on swimmies right to try to climb the tree better to think maybe there's gonna be grip
I know it's crazy
Wait, did we get a raid?
Hold on. I'm in the middle telling this crazy crazy story that happened to me when I was like fucking 19
Hey, hey edna
Okay, does the tv work yet?
Maybe just adjust it a little to the left
Say hello
Teleport to the tractor sleep for a week
Teleport to the truck say hello teleport to the tractor sleep for a week until it's all until I marry this person
This is bullshit and i'll tell you why I don't think anybody's played this game. We're seeing this
There's no way since one game hour is about five minutes. That means 12 hours in game. You can talk to the ladies. Wait, what?
You can only complement them once per real hour
Of the youngest one
There's so much science as to what the heck is this even is it energy is it a time paradox
Is it aliens? Did aliens make this? I don't know. It's so many questions that I have
We'll never know the answers to so before I real the real before I reveal the winner of this category
I have to make something very very clear
Sometimes you spend some money and time and resources and you you think something's a really great idea
and
Fucking rumor get the fuck out of here
Uh, sometimes you have some ideas that don't play out so well, even when even if you hope they do
and with
39 percent of the vote
by a majority
And this fucking kind of annoys me in a way and i'll tell you why
Bugleberry making pottery with almost 40 percent of the vote
Now here's where this is bad and this is why this sucks the most for me
because
I had to take pottery classes to learn how to do that
You notice how I knew what the fuck I was doing
I went to pottery class
To like know how to do that
And it turns out it was the worst thing I did all year
It's okay. Hey look like I said as if you play baseball if you're a baseball player and you strike out seven times
As long as you hit three home runs, you're one of the best players in baseball
That's a 300 average that took five days to set up took more than that. That was more than five minutes. That was uh,
like three weeks
Of learning how to do pottery and then setting up all the but that I love that stream. That's like I love that stream
That's that's by the way
That stream is nominated for best stream of the year. So
Look, you can have a bad part of one good stream
And I know everybody fucking hates bugleberry bugleberry won worst character last year. He ain't going anywhere
He ain't going anywhere. He's gonna be the next big event
He ain't ever fucking going anywhere. I mean he's gonna be at every single event and I will those of you that it might be
New to the channel
When I did that segment with bugleberry, I think we had 8 000 concurrent viewers, right?
The second that bugleberry came on stream
We dropped I believe
3000 viewers
We went from 8 000 concurrent down to like 5000 concurrent instantly
I don't even give a shit. He's coming back
Just like there are bad jokes that take more than five minutes to set up. There are also good ones apparently
Here is the nominee category
For best joke of the year that took more than five minutes to set up
We'll see
Oh, it's beautiful jack
It sure is
Oh, it's beautiful. I know
Oh
Oh my fucking god
I've got it. You're that pit boss from the toy is he wearing lipstick. I smell a conspiracy
You smell a nosy dog who's going to get smacked if he don't stop asking questions
Fucking set on the package that wasn't gonna come off
Bro, I can't this is an acting. Okay, this is this is an acting class
You want to learn how to act and you want to learn how to compose yourself during a scene?
They should do this in workshops. I should run a workshop and do this
And again, but sometimes the right one for you
It's not working
It's not working. I just like ate like I just ate like a person
I wouldn't I eat right here?
Get off. What do you guys want to do?
I can I can barely do anything. I I really don't want to lie to you guys
But I seriously fucking can't do shit right now story three was really good somebody asked in the chat
Let's make sure that I got I answered it
Story four was okay, too. I didn't I didn't I I liked it
Okay, i'm not i'm not even kidding on january 23rd i'm gonna like final destination movie my house
I'm serious
I just fucked myself three minutes
Right here i'm gonna lie just lie down
I was relaxing
Here's the thing kids
When you buy used games make sure very very important kids
Always under every circumstance make sure that you get exactly what you paid for in that box
Because if it doesn't come in there you end up in a scenario like this
Yes
And he doesn't have the other yes
I hope that one wins. That was that what a great game. It's close. It was close
Farting and screaming playlist at the gym
With 29.4 percent of the vote
Uh very closely followed by germa dies
At 20.9 percent
There you go
Best joke of the year that took more than five minutes to set up titanic was robbed. I'll get you know, that's a big category
So i'll give you
Uh worst joke by the way
bugleberry destroyed
But after that at fifth, oh god people fucking hated that
People hated that shit so much
40 for bugleberry for worst and then trying to get married in farmer's dynasty was number two
oh, yeah
Uh, best joke taking more than five minutes was farting and screaming playlist and then germa dies and then right after that
Was the iconic titanic scene at 17.8 percent
this next category
This next category
Is one of the biggest categories of the night. I got 10k viewers
Holy shit. Hey
What's up?
That's pretty that's pretty good
Pretty cool. That's fucking awesome. Uh, welcome as you knew. Hi, i'm jeremy and this is the worst
You came at the right exact moment that you probably to leave
This is the category that had the most nominations of the whole year
This is the worst noise that I made on stream in 2019
Whether that's exclaiming something loudly whether that's making of being upset about something
Uh, this is the worst fucking thing I made out of my mouth
and
This had the most nominations
There were let's see one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
14 official nominations
There were 23
Actual nominations that we had to shave down because this fucking category was huge
Please enjoy the nominees
For worst noise of the whole year. I'll see you in a minute
Oh
Oh, I fucking dropped it lower your volume i'm not kidding seriously do it right now
Lower it i'm serious
Did I break the internet?
All the noise this would make
Who's my favorite streamer
Talent are you talking about like who I think is the funniest or most interesting
Uh who?
Uh, Vinny
Joel
They're always doing something fun. They're always doing something different
Vin vine
Cinematic look enjoy
Why
What if I just start going like
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
We've been playing the chicken game since july, please stop
I did it. Yeah, he said it
Fucking black hole danger black hole
Pop up windows 1998 internet pop-up window
Uh, let's go you could do it if you could awoo for me
Holy fuck the worst thing that came out I spent an hour apologizing
the worst noise of
The noise that I spent an hour apologizing for this is real if you watch the vaude
I fucking said sorry like three times
I went over on like a rant about like i'm fucking really sorry. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't mean to
It was real close
the winner
of the 2019 worst noise of the year is
Oh shit
the worst noise of 2019
real life fall joke
I did that on purpose. Don't let anybody fucking tell you I didn't
Oh
Fuck me
Oh, yeah
real close
At that actually fucking hurt that was not that didn't make that that actually hurt me
My elbow this elbow fucking hurts now
And it's the worst because I have this wooden panel on the ground so I can roll back and forth like this
It's on a carpet here
Fucking ayaya for 23.5. I believe bugleberry's noise was right at 21
23.5 percent for ayaya
Fuck
21.5 percent for bugleberry's scream also
one of the worst jokes of the year
How bad was that? Let me see that shit. That's 10 000 fucking people watching and I fell back on my chair
Oh shit
That looks like right into I looked into the camera
All right. Ah, so coming up next we have best
Noise
Coming up next is best noise of 2019. Who knows if they could be in the same category who cares?
I'm so embarrassed to
Who gives a shit? It's 2020
Uh ho speaking of fucking holy speaking of 20s
Uh, hoagie supreme just gave 20 community subs
I fucking can't believe it is spelled on
It's like the most viewers we've had in like fucking three months
And I literally fall down
Like that this is like wine glass number three like that's not
best noise of 2019
Fuck me, man
God damn it
Shit
It's I'm not by the way. I want to make this really fucking clear. That is
No, you can't nominate that for anything because it's it's
Nine ten eleven. Wait, hold on
Nine ten eleven twelve
Holy shit, wait, it's almost new years
It's almost new years. It's almost new years
Oh, wait, we got like 15 minutes. Holy shit
All right, let's go
best noise of 2019 coming up
Goddamn, most viewers have had like fucking two months and I fucking fall down on my goddamn fucking chair
Oh, you want to fight you don't fuck come out don't
What you got to come like I just get go grab a chicken in the woods and like go on all fours
No
It's not resonable to call of duty modern warfare for best strategy game
Focused on those nominees are 10 years
You're standing at the built-in
With all the buttons to press right? Yeah, go like this
What is that go like what
Turn I just uh
I'll tell you uh, uh movie uh tv show
Uh sign film
Elaborate elaborate elaborate got it. Yes. How many points is that?
And if it weren't for nosy characters like you
We practically own this world
So, let's see you deal with this
Holy shit relax
Uh
Uh wasn't even close dickhead driving by fucking fast
Uh, what didn't even close?
the best noise of the year the slap
at
43.4 percent of the vote
Not only the best noise of the year, but the probably the worst thing i've ever done to myself on stream
There's no way I can
Explain that clip
There's no I can't explain it
I told you i've seen threads on like reddit and shit where people are like he fucking did that on purpose
To make to like what do you mean? I I I fail
Fuck that's the new slap
Like people say like dude, he fucking did it on purpose. He hit him. He slapped himself in the face to get like views
I didn't and like whatever I I like I said before I probably should just own it and say that I did it on purpose
Because how do you explain that like oh I was looking at like the fucking preview monitor and trying to cue up a sound
You can't there's no I can't look that had to be on purpose
slap past the torch to the I I I fall
God damn it and I look in the camera too when I fall
Like it had to be on purpose. It had that had to be on purpose
Coming up next coming up next. Uh, who?
Is uh, this one had a shitload of nominations
best scare of the year
Whether I was scared by something in game or scared by a video or scared by a jump scare best scare of the year
That's the new slap good. I'm glad it replaces once a year. We'll replace it with something else
Uh best scare of the year coming up jump scares any scares, you know, you know the deal that's not correct
He's allowed by the way
What the fuck it's that guy, you know, it's not
What a fucking idiot I am
Get away, please
I thought it was the fucking guy with the hat on
Oh my god, that would have been the war out that would have been one of the scariest things ever in a video game
It still kind of was and i'm gonna die. I need to heal
It's jack surprise
Is that code for how I have to?
Oh my fucking jaw hurts I can't get in the back room. What do you think you're doing?
That was uh, nothing just keep your fingers to yourself
Okay, bye there's a little one hanging out somewhere
God damn it
That's just that's the fucking worst thing that ever happened to me in a game
Without a doubt. That's the scariest because I know I have zero health and there's like 30 minutes of
That was really really really real that was real that's because that's what would happen if a monster tried to kill me in real life
I can't believe it. I can't believe it
I spawned in here as well. You've got to be fucking shitting me sir
Okay, well that was fun dad the party the fucking scary people nice music
With jets on your hands
Oh boy, I need to sit down I think I have to sit down for this
Suck my fucking bum
And facing this way long
What are you doing isolation ward key run
Oh
The best scare of the year
I mean, come on. Come on. Someone's get 50 bucks. Hold on kim scaring germa and vr. That's me. I'm germa
Uh, the vr scare just took it. It was 43 44 percent of the vote
It crushed it that I I thought I was gonna die. I really thought I was gonna die
Because when you're in vr, you have no perception of anything around you
And when you feel physical violence on you, you're just like i'm dead. I'm fucking dead in real life
Six minutes until new year's we got plenty of categories everybody calm down with eight
Yeah, it's we got like six minutes we got another category to do just relax
How much more wine do I have?
Did I drink this much wine already?
I guess I did
He's drunk. I'm fucking drinking. I'm it's new year's eve
It's not like july
22nd, okay. It's new year's eve. I can have a few glasses of wine
Yeah, kim vr. What was the net? What was after that far away?
Uh one hp in the vent on the thing
Yeah
18 that was the worst
To give some context on that clip
The thing is a fucking it sucks the thing sucks
Uh, it's one of the best that's one of the best streams i've done all year. I love that stream. I hate that game
um
The first like 15 hours of the thing is okay, but you did it because of money. That's not even true
not even true, uh, but
In that game the save points
I had one hp and I played that same fucking routine over and over and over again
If I died by that little monster, I would have had to come back and play 40 minutes of the game again
Oh would have been horrible
People are spamming a link. I don't even look like this
I really don't even look like this
Jesus
That's not even the same person
Uh coming up next on the
New year's eve festivities
We're gonna count down the new year. It's almost midnight eastern
We're I don't think we have time
I could open a clock
It's three minutes. We have like fucking
10 categories
All right. I'm not no. No, we gotta wait. We gotta wait
We have to wait
Don't spoil categories two minutes
Until it's new york time. I live in fucking las vegas
What do I care if it's midnight eastern?
We're close
We gotta
No, no, don't play that yet
Uh, we gotta sit here
Your most p look I thought that every it's all eastern
Oh, that's a good one
It's almost 12 a.m. Eastern time. Happy new year everybody coming up here soon
You betrayed boston
I didn't I didn't betray boston. I live on the west coast now. I live in las vegas
Countdown to start here we go. All right, you ready? I need like I need fucking music
We have we are t minus 45 seconds away from new year's eve
new year's day
30 seconds
Hey
Here's to 2020. You're fucking bastards. Here's 2020
Hey, you want a kiss too? Okay
Here it comes
nine eight seven six
Five four three two one
That's it
Hold on old land get it. I don't why don't I have this ready?
It's a fucking guitar version fuck you where's the real one?
What is that? This is like somebody on instagram. Where's the gimme old lang syne
every night
This fireworks outside lang syne can hear ten's be for god
He rules us all with
Love and all acquaintance be
Forgot where we all sign up for the fucking fortnight season three
Happy new year guys, seriously happy new year. Do you hear the fireworks? I wish I could show you happy minus two year
Ten community subs from flies and bergen
This is perfect time because we're getting to the best categories of the entire year. We have best and worst gaming moment
No, we don't. Yes, we do
we also have
Worst meltdown of the year worst stream of the year best stream of the year
and then worst
worst
joke of the decade
And then best joke of the decade. I've been around a long time. I've been around a very long time guys
And i'm shocked at the nominations that I see here. Thank you everybody. Hope you have a great 2020
He's bald fucking ban everybody that says the word blad
Are you ready?
Happy new year those in eastern standard time
sometimes
Uh on this stream we uh, I can't get over the fact that I fell down in my chair
Apologize for falling. I what the fuck i'm sorry
Don't look at the fucking winner
I know the winner
gaming is
Synonymous with twitch.tv. Okay, he's drunk
Whatever. It's fucking new years. Who cares?
Twitch.tv is synonymous with video gaming on this category
I play games. Okay. Look I beat fucking dark souls 3 on stream. Who else has done that like fucking three people on twitch?
I'm one i'm one of three people cool
me
shroud
That's it me and shroud beat fucking dark souls 3 on stream. I'm all right with that
Uh, yeah, I I fuck up a lot in video games and we're gonna show you some of the worst times
I fucked up in video gaming history in 2019
These are the worst gaming moments
of 2019 the worst
I'm gonna have to solve it, but I don't know with what?
the g
And then it's all vowels
prank
Lee leo frank
What is this name?
Frank keep it in the photo. Yeah, I don't want to see what they have to say about that
I want to name i've been thinking about this and
If my calculations are correct, you must be a virgin, right?
I sorry. I know virgos are very sensitive. I hope I didn't hurt your feelings
No, i'm not so it's none of my business what you do in your free time
Okay, I have two health. I'm gonna do this right
Just throw a grenade out there
Oh, you gotta be shitting me. They went double time on this one
You got is that three?
There's no way that's three. Holy shit. You went out with a bang. No way
three
one
Where is it?
Wait, what?
Wait, this is all you got. I understand
Well, when I understand I understand
Did I make it?
Do I drive a car over this way?
Help me
God damn it protect me protect me. Oh god
I gotta sneak up on somebody and we have to
Do the cool thing the desperate thing to have five million. He's lying around
Because they want you to do this and i'm gonna do it
Well, I didn't know you were gonna be here wait barrel
I'll be right back. I I gotta be a million. Oh fuck
I'm not gonna do it. I didn't do it. I didn't do it
No, no, please. No
I'm trying to turn
I'm trying to turn it
Wait go in
Go in go in go in. Where is it?
Where's the level?
I just said you told me one million. You told me one million
You said one million
Who said it? Who said one million? Oh, i'm gonna turn to dust
Look you can't do them all well, okay
but
There has to be a winner
the unforgivable minecraft sin
Digging right down into the ground. What the fuck was that?
24.5 percent of the vote right underneath that was failing the catamari final level four times in a row
leo peepance should have won
uh
Is that worst gamer moment or is that just germa is a fucking moron?
Like germa is just an imbecile. That's not like worst game. That's not like gamer moment. That's just germa sucks
Just like there are bad moments of the year. There are good moments
Here are the nominees. Oh, this was really this is the closest one of the whole night. Yes, it was absolutely
best
Best gamer moment of the whole year. This just like worse. There's best
Sometimes I beat jevil first try who else to fucking did that sometimes I beat
The last boss of fucking sakiro first try
Sometimes you do that shit the true boss of sakiro beating first try you do that. That was last year though
Sometimes you do that shit. Here are the nominees
for the best gaming moment
Of 2019 that was lat that was not last year
Uh, we got 20 community subs right now from ishanji
Thank you ishanji for the 20 fucking subs
Here are the nominees for best gaming moment of the year on the channel
Yes
Oh my fucking god. No
No god, I can do it with a jump
Bart where is he?
Bart
Hey, I hate this game. I hate this. I hate it. I can't I hate it. Give me a delete
I did it. I did it. I can leave I can leave I did it
Come on come on just think
Of just think of uncle ben wait, no, that's spider-man. Yes
Wow, yeah, that's a strong wizard. That's a two
hp wizard
countered
It's one again. Don't fuck yourself by bringing it and it's a slow swing guy
Sometimes sometimes you do it right half tank
the winner
Jevil jevil was last year
That was 2018, man
Did it win 20 you have to watch 2018 vaude
The winner of the 2019 best gaming moment of the year on the germany 95 channel
Beating han solo on expert
but beating jump king
and bart
Were at 20.9 percent and 20.7 percent respectively. It was close
Uh playing just dance apparently is more impressive than beating the shinobi hunter in fucking first try with no damage
All right
We are at the final
Five categories of the night. It's because you stuck with han solo. Yeah
this next category
is
interesting
Because uh, those I have issues
whatever, uh
Sometimes I lose my mind sometimes I have problems on stream. Sometimes I get a little too upset
Sometimes I go too far
These are the nominees
for the worst meltdown
in 2019
Meltdown means very mad very upset
Just like actually want to turn my stream off
so pissed off
That like i'm fucking going i'm i'm done. I'm not I don't want to stream anymore
The molding category that is true. Here are your nominees for the worst meltdown
stream of 2019
My god, oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. He used the cheat code
Show me shut up, please
I'm gonna turn off the voice
My fucking god. No
No, god, I can do it with a jump
Bart
Where is he?
Bart, I don't understand how that's possible. I'm doing that the fastest anyone's ever done this
Oh
You can't win. You can't it's not possible to win. You can't win
You fucker
No, what?
Get out of my way
What the fuck is going on
down
Right. She doesn't understand the word right now
I'm watching a fucking youtube video at the end of this game. This is dumb. This is D U M B
dumb
Okay, can I please just get this jump before I start to have a little bit of a problem?
I'm gonna have a okay
Okay, okay, okay
Video games suck video games suck video games suck video games suck all video games. None of them are fun
All of them suck all video games suck. I've never played a video game ever again
Did I make it?
Do I drive the car over this way?
Again
What no get in this
Get in the wheelchair, please I stopped to puke get in the chair
What are you doing?
Fucking display every machine your chances increase
Oh
What the fuck happened?
No, the first person camera was not in the right spot and it was one hit what?
What the fuck was that
No way I just like wasn't in the right spot you've got to be kidding me that was dumb
Oh, no, I hate it
Whole thing has to be ice the whole course
Sonic racers didn't even have this shit mario kart doesn't even have a level like this
across the entire like
16 mario kart game
Yeah, I got called out it's okay
Uh
the worst meltdown of the year
Not even close
Another category that just blew everything out
simpsons hit and run
With fifty one point seven percent of the vote
That's a lot
That's one of the longest streams i've ever done
And I agree that's the most fucked up i've ever been on camera. That's that's like the most angry tired and annoyed i've been
In probably five years
Simpsons hit and run was the worst meltdown by far if you want to know the uh runners up sure we can do that
The next one was jump king
And after that was the thing
Simpsons hit jump by the way jump king was fifteen point nine percent of the vote
All right, we are at the final four categories and these are big ones. These are really big ones. These are huge
This next category
Is the worst stream of the whole fucking year the stream that was not even funny
That was a waste of fucking time that was like why did you turn it on in the first place?
The worst stream of the year. Yeah, get a better joke. You guys said this last year, too
Oh this one. This one's the fucking worst. You said that last year and look at i'll turn it out for you
No, you said that last year ain't gonna happen this year. No 2019 2018 same damn fucking story
What was the worst stream of the year? I know what I think it is
But maybe you have a different maybe slightly different story. This is one of the big categories
You motherfuckers
This is the category of the what the worst
stream
Of 2019
What is the worst stream of the year?
Here we go
Fuck be so fucking mad right i'm so mad right now. Does anybody see jay? I don't know what to do
No more
What he didn't let squeak in sausage? You didn't like this? Do you want to do another fucking card game?
No, no, no anything but that do anything else. I don't want to see this again
Me
He is he he's a normie I know you're gonna scream I know that I already told you you're gonna be mad
What's happening? Oh the
Get out leave don't don't come to this stream. This stream is not a one you want to watch
But i'm not very good at this game and I look over here and I see
Like a wall of people fucking holding up notes
They stick it into the wall. Hey, look at this
But you have to do it like this quick
I know we're supposed to play halo reach on legendary difficulty
But what if we just this is what we're talking about
What if we just make the ground that we're walking on made out of bodies?
Show you a video
You're gonna go to my stream go into go on to your
Watch my stream right now. No, you already you already pressed the button you pressed the button
Okay, well the fucking button
Hey, yeah, you don't want to talk about reaching into the toilet like pulling up like drain pipes
Oh
The worst stream of the year
of all of 2019
halo reach with joel
halo reach with joel with 30 percent of the vote
below that was
The hearthstone stream
I can agree with that
I think the worst stream of the year was the unlock card game stream
Try to do something different
It was so bad
That's the worst stream i've ever done
Regardless of what everybody says
That's the worst stream i've ever done on this channel
call joel
Would he like to know that he won worst stream of the year?
Is he here?
Joel hey you hey, we won
Worst stream of the whole fucking year
I'll call him right now. Is he on discord right now, but let's get a fucking comment from joel. Sure
Joel are you here joel? It's 4 a.m. In sweden
This no, he's not gonna answer
It's not gonna fucking happen
He blocked you
Uh the joel the halo reach. I was so into halo reach. I wanted to play it so fucking bad, too
That's the worst part about all this is I was so I was like hey guys
I've never played halo before in my whole life. I can't wait to play halo
It's gonna be so much fun, man. I've never played fucking halo 1 halo 2 halo 3 halo
I've never played any fucking halos and it's the worst stream i've ever done. I can't even go back. I can't go back to halo
It was you know, it was the card game. It was fucking unlock card game. That game sucked
All right. Yeah, it was me and joel playing halo. Okay, just as there are bad streams. There are also good streams
What
Was the best stream of the year? I know but do you
Here are your nominees
For best stream of the year joel answer the fucking phone
Okay, okay, okay, okay
No
I'm gonna turn off the voice. Thank god. No. No god. I can do it with the jump
Third time we've seen this clip. Where is he?
Hey, hey, hello
Let me park this thing
You want to make that joke so bad
And act you actually did it. I can't I actually can't fucking believe you did that
I didn't even need to tell you anything man. Stop photocombatting me, please. This is supposed to leave please
please
Dr schmoyzen
Disgusting
Soaring and slithering how high can he go? This is the point where the streamer gave up
You want to otherwise just fly this guy. Oh, I don't know that
Oh shoot my frog quick zoom in
That made me famous
That did happen on that stream it's true
That did happen on that stream ladies and gentlemen
the best stream of 2019
the robot carnival
with
47 percent of the vote
After that is simpson's hit and run with 14 percent of the vote had a lot of fun in that stream
robot carnival
There it is best stream of the year. Apparently we're at the end of the night here
We have a couple more categories to do two very do very important categories
Because i've been doing this for such a long time. We have
the worst joke of the decade
And the best joke of the decade I did youtube
Six years or so before I did twitch
Those are included twitch is just about 40 to 50 percent of the whole time. I spent on these platforms
He was a tuber. So these hold a very special place in my heart. They really do even the worst ones even the shittiest
joke of the whole decade
I've been here for a long time and
I seriously cannot even
Comprehend this eleven thousand five hundred fucking people here. There's a lot of people
I've i'm shocked that there's this many people that think this stream is worth being a part of
Or the youtube channel from 10 years ago. So from the bottom of regardless of what wins worst joke and best joke of the decade
Thanks for making this possible
And let's hope 2020 is as fun as the 2010s because it was like it's been a fucking blast
Seriously, thank you everybody without further ado
Let's move on to the worst joke of the whole decade. Somebody just dropped 50 fucking subs
Barry saxie 50 subs right at the new year
Thank you. And that's a lot of that's a lot of subs
50 subs
uh
There were a lot of nominees for best joke of the decade clerky. Thanks for 20 fucking subs from clerky
Jesus back to back here
Thanks for making this decade something. I will literally never forget in my whole life ever literally ever when i'm 70 years old
I'll uh, i'll remember this shit. I really will thanks guys
100 community. What the fuck? All right. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait
We had a hundred community subs
Wait, what the fuck shit's coming in too fast
My name is redis gave a hundred community subs
One blondie 20. What the fuck?
ball boy five
Holy shit
po pooboo
What are you guys doing five from five five five five five five?
a hundred a fucking hundred from abe
What the fuck are you guys doing?
a hundred subs
From abe kashim unnecessary unnecessary unnecessary unnecessary chunky baloney 10 subs
Dr shrug five subs. Jesus christ this it's just won't stop poison type five
Corn, holy corn. Holy. Oh, that's a great name
10. Thanks guys
What the fuck is happening?
Poofy native 10 community subs. We don't we're at the worst joke of the decade guys like not best
Fucking everybody gets a sub. Apparently. Holy I can't even keep up reptio 10 subs. How many fucking subs are on this channel?
Uh
this um
this
This is you're just gonna fucking get kind of emotional
this fucking
8500 fucking subs
It's like a thousand two thousand last day
What the fuck are you doing?
This is madness
This is absolute madness
Poovo 20 more
This is a cool gaming moment
um
Holy shit guys
Uh, we're 8600 fucking subs. I want to make sure this is very very clear
um
the last 10 fucking years
has
Seriously changed my whole life
Honest to god like you guys have changed my fucking life
I dressed up like a dickhead, but
You've changed my entire goddamn life
From 2010 till now i'm missing this so many subs coming in right now. I can't even fucking read them
But just seriously know
That i'm gonna keep trying
Even if the jokes aren't even funny like i'm gonna try
I hope you enjoy being here. I hope you fucking like I think it's fun
That's all I care about regardless of the fucking amount of money that comes in on these streams
Number one priority is I hope you fucking think it's fun
Seriously, it's a lot of people coming in right now with subs a lot a lot a lot a lot too much for me
I can't even comprehend it
Cry on stream. He's gonna cry
No, no, I
Holy shit guys. What is going on? I can't even count them. How many subs to cry?
You've changed you've changed my goddamn life
I had no fucking idea what the hell was gonna happen. I had no idea what I was gonna do
I want to be like a vet tech
Just know where your money's going. It's i'm gonna go more i'm gonna go harder
I'm gonna go as hard as I fucking can
This is crazy
everyone even
Not good
I got you guys in mind. I really do
And this channel has grown
like 10 times
In the last year and a half
It's madness this channel has grown I I was at like 1500 viewers, which is huge
Which is a ton of fucking people. That's so many people
1500 to 2000. That's a fucking ton of people
Look at how many people here now. I can't even fucking I can't comprehend this shit
If you like this stream if you don't like this stream if you came here once or twice and you're like, oh this guy sucks
Thanks for fucking showing up in the first place and fucking trying it
If you love this stream
I love you back
Thanks for changing my whole goddamn life
fucking for real
Cheers to that without further ado
Here comes the worst thing i've ever done on my life. Here's the worst thing i've ever done. We got resident sleepers in the chat
Like president sleeper
And i'm not even upset about it. That's fucking that's kind of funny
That's kind of funny. That's kind of funny. Here's the worst joke of the decade
I love you guys
Hey, what's going on everybody, it's me demon lord saraxos here
Uh, you're probably wondering where where's germa what happened to him? Well, it's because I have taken over his soul
And I will only release it
After playing around a five nights at freddie
Here's the uh, here's the full ost of star wars and then intercut in the middle like a siren
Um
That would be a bad joke that's the worst joke in 2019 that's the worst joke in the last five years
That's the worst joke in the last 10 years. That's the worst thing i've ever said
Much
You can
Ah fuck this is bad
Really?
Yeah, but you could get in this one without the quest
Yeah
There's the first ingredient that's two eggs
Around this corner we got some butter
And then of course you cannot forget
Fucking you roll your sleeves up get your hands a little bit dirty and you add a little bit more butter fucking god. Damn it
Do you understand how hard you're trying to make one of the worst jokes I have ever heard. There's a bad guy right here
Yep. Well, this doesn't belong on here. It really the door actually is alive. Hey bub
It's me
dorvarine
the wolverine door
Oh
Oh that one hurt that one hurt me. I'm sorry. That one actually hurt my body as I was saying
The best part about that is all of those are from youtube from like 2013
But the worst thing i've ever done in my life in the last 10 years
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, it's it's not dorvarine
It's the pp poop it's a ppp's pants world of warcraft in chat joke
At least I had the decency to block out the people's names
Are we approaching?
10 000 subs
what
The fuck is going on?
9400 fucking subs on this channel
What is happening? What did I miss?
A hundred subs came in from fucking
My name is redis fucking again
Cry bitch. Hey, he slowed down. Come on
I can't even keep up. There's a lot of nominees on this list
And this is seriously a love letter to you guys
Like you're gonna make me fucking cry on goddamn stream. What?
When I first made my youtube channel, I didn't think this shit was ever gonna work and it
It kind of did I guess?
Holy shit drunk and crying on twitch. No, no, no, no, not quite
I can't keep up. I hope I use your money. Well, I really do
There's some projects coming up in 2020 that you don't know about that
That's where this money's gonna go
A huge amount of fucking money that I get on the stream is going right back in so
Early 2020 you'll see some stuff. Hopefully
um
No, not germa rumble that's just happening regardless
There's 94 fucking hundred subs on this channel
That's the most i've ever fucking seen and it's still going and I wish I could fucking say thanks to everybody
Here are the nominees for the best joke of the whole decade including twitch and including this fucking other hundred subs came in
from ap aperture city
Jesus christ, you guys have fucking gonna put me in it
You put me in a new tax bracket this stream put me in a new tax bracket
I'm gonna have to call my cpa after this stream
Hey, uh cpa. I just want to let you know, uh
Uh, I may have made uh fucking like 20 grand on today's stream
Holy shit
You gotta be fucking kidding me
Best joke of the decade on twitch or on youtube
Much love to you guys
Let's see the nominees
Life is pain. I hate my life is pain
Brush your teeth if you want not go to fucking jail kids
Try thunder for a clean machine
Boom boom
The grenade room
Coming in here realizing where I am and then somebody throws a grenade into the room and they have to leave
There he is. I found him. Oh wait, jerry. Did you just throw a grenade into the room?
I don't understand
I think i'm gonna die on camera
You think that's what you think you're fucking idiot
This don't do it, please don't do it
No, I can't take it I can't take it
Have a cigarette yeah, I'd like to smoke down here
Oh my god
I just found
a wild spay nest
On dust bowl and this is they pop up from time to time
But i'm gonna be really careful here guys this middle of mating season blue spays and red spays are gonna be mating
I'm gonna fucking die here
The green screen
Disney channel, but you're about to hear rich man and praise with cheering applause just for you
The original
This is why it's so hard to fucking deep batter a piece of ram because you don't you don't have the skin on there
Power supply
I'm talking about a real statement a see-through gold plate
This is what an old gameplay live let's play commentary was like in 2005 down here
Right, like and i'm gonna be like fucking silent. The webcam is gonna be in a wicked embarrassing place
I've got your favorite breakfast snack here waiting for you. It's
Here's your last chance, honey
What do you do with money is it is it is it like is it like a currency thing
What is it? I'm not sure
Is it like some kind of currency thing? I'm not sure
I mean, I don't know is this i've got a currency thing, you know, who knows
I'm not sure what else
Not a big deal
You know like not a big deal at all. You know what i'm saying?
Not a big deal at all. What is this? I want to watch this
Oh, that's what it was
We're talking about you getting clipped be burping it
Play at night we stop at night with the rats the giant rat that makes all
The rats we are the rats
Ladies and gentlemen the best joke of the decade
Starting with the bottom
the grenade room
The pop star the pop tarts joke
Can you hear me? Okay. Good
The tv commercials pc doctor cheers to you having a cigarette layers of fear some kind of currency thing
Not the top rope
spi
germa gets clipped and the top three jokes of the whole entire decade
were
the green screen
source
2008 hyper cam youtube video and at 30 percent of the vote
The rats there it goes a lot of shit happened this decade
the rats
Got got tweeted up by lil nas. I mean like come on
Another hundred fucking subs just came in from austin lantis
We're at 9,600 subs
You've got to be fucking kidding me
as this is
Almost double the amount of subs i've ever had
ever
Dodge there's a lot of people here dodge. That's true
almost
10,000 subs 9,700
Get the earphones out. It's real talk
in 2020
I really do hope that
You continue to think this channel is worth watching
I really do
The decades seen a lot of fucking people too
star
Was a huge part of those right like look like look at some of those most
important clips of the whole decade
Star was a huge part of that shit
one of my closest like I
One of my I respect him a lot huge respect to star
steve
Thank you
For all the fun shit that we did over 10 fucking years
italics
boo
mlc stealth
Vinny the vinesauce crew they didn't they didn't do so much for this channel
They've done a shitload for this channel. So fuck the grill master. He sucks
criken criken and and and criken crew like they've done so much
RT game crowd is fucking raided and hosted this channel a thousand fucking times
A lot of people have put this channel where it is now
and
There's been so much growth
Critical yeah critical the fucking podcast I was on the official podcast and did a lot
He's a good fucking dude
burger boy, thanks to burger boy burger boy was a huge burger boy created half of the videos
burger boy was such a comedy character, you know what I mean? It's just
There's been a lot of people that have been part of this community
And a huge fucking shout out mac
effectator
Mac is edited effectators edited so many of these second channel videos. They've been they've been a part of the whole thing
All the mods there's been some mods have been so much work
If I got you here, i'm gonna fucking show people out. I am
Kim forgot his girlfriend. Thanks to kim
I'll see her real soon
I'm gonna go see kim real soon. That's why we're ending soon here
Just keep rolling
What about us?
Yeah, the people that have watched my channel
That even thought I was worth fucking seeing or talking about or sharing with your friends
The growth of this channel over the last two or three years has been fucking crazy
I wish I could say thanks in a different way. I wish I could
Dr. Schmoyzen, I know that actor has been that actor so good and they were so accommodating
thank you to everybody that's made this channel as
Fun as it's been
I hope 2020s is fun. That's all I can say actor. Yeah, dr schmoyzen is a fucking talented actor
9,800 subs you said he was a technician. He is
Not a real doctor. He's a real boy. You can be an actor and a fucking doctor at the same time
Tons of money is coming in right now. I wish there was more of a way I could say thanks
All I can say to all the huge fucking ridiculous amount of money
The thousands and thousands and thousands of dollars that's come in this stream
I'm gonna try to do more stuff
Hope I spend your money. Well, thank you
For almost ten full years
Of this shit
Watching that last compilation was like damn. There's been a lot of fucking fun shit
Cheers to you. Cheers to 2020. Happy new year
Make 2020 a great year
I'll see you soon. My absolute. Thanks to everybody
Thanks auto
I
He's right there
Based chug the wine. There's not much left
This is a malbec too. This is good. This is good shit. I will see you guys in a few days
In let's see exactly
I'll see you guys on saturday on the fourth. Have a great 2020
We are going to train we're going to do the bits because i'm here. I'm not in the studio
Much love to you guys
Seriously, i'm fucking shocked at this shit
See you guys in 2020 if those of you that might be joining the channel for the first time
Maybe we'll see you again. If not, then thanks for sticking around right now
Maybe we'll see you in 2020
Stream archives too. Yeah, they've been saving everything
Much love to all of you. See you in 2020. That's the end of the stream. Let's do the bits from earlier
There were a lot of them
There was shit load of them big room to end 2020. That's true time for a four-hour bit reading
No, it's not gonna be that long. There were so many subs. Holy shit
This is 9800 subs. There's almost 10 000 fucking subs
Are you shitting me?
What the fuck is going on?
Holy shit, I can't even scroll
I can't even scroll
If you've gotten anything out of the stream
Holy shit
This is going to be the fastest
Bit this is going to be the fastest sub credits you've ever seen in your life
You kidding me? This is gonna be it's gonna be insane
Happy fucking new year everybody
Take care of yourselves. Take care of yourselves. Have a 2020 be great
Much love to you
Holy shit, this is unfucking believable. I can't even read them
I can't even read them. What the fuck?
Holy shit
Wow, this is fucking crazy. I can't even go down
I gotta pull out the mustard site
Cry damn it. I almost did during that compilation at the end
Here we go back to earlier phylactery lich 10 000 bits. Thanks for the hundred fucking dollars
It's a huge amount of money. Happy new year. Jeremy. Why don't you suck a fart out of 2008 2019's ass?
Maybe I will
Siroc. Thanks for the 500 bits
Hey, germa, I woke up looked at the time and said yo happy new year
Then I realized that it was 7 pm and not 1 am
Anyway as a member of chat
I am taking the worst chat trophy and i'll be trading for 20 pieces a 20 piece mcnugget at mcdonald's
It's worth it
400 bits four dollars from anonymous cheerer. Thank you anonymous cheerer. Just four dollars. Thank you
Uh algae advice drip. Thanks for the thousand bits
Thank you
They say hey, just want to thank you for the you and the community for keeping me company this past year
I suffer from severe clinical depression
And it hasn't been easy on top of that. My dad was diagnosed with cancer this year. So it's been extra rough
Though i'm a lurker
Thank you and everyone for keeping me company and bringing me many laughs to counter the pain and tears
Hope to make friends with everyone in the new year. Love y'all. Hope everyone has a great 2020
I wish you and especially your father the best
Cancer sucks. I wish your father the absolute best
It is our pleasure
To keep you company for this long
All through 2019
Thank you much. Love to you. Thank you so much for the thousand bits the ten dollars
Thank you to jerk mccurk for the 800 bits happy new year germa. Thanks for helping me get through the decade
Love you, bro. I could say the same thing to you and it will be real. Thanks. Appreciate it
Thank you for the eight dollars jerk mccurk captain clutch tm. Thanks for the 300 bits. Let's start the new year. All right
Happy new year. Happy new year to you, too. Hope you have a good one
Uh kelsey kelsey va. Thanks for the 500 bits. Please wish me a happy birthday germa cake and ice cream is on its way
Happy birthday kelsey
Have a good birthday. Take care yourself. Hope you have a good birthday on new year's eve. Damn
That's pretty great
But square thanks for the 20 dollars butt squire
2,000 bits from butt square. I made the original you are now cursed picture
And I have nothing to do with those coasters. I also made the two other you are now cursed images. So what i'd be suing
I don't know if you have a case
But thanks for the 2,000 bits
20 fucking dollars a lot of money. Thank you. Hey sad vega. Thanks for 250 germa
I'm not sure where but they probably are this probably a bot pulling images
From either twitter or discord if you put an image that said this is stolen artwork. Do not buy report it
They'd probably put it up on the shop. That's true. Yeah, that's true
Hey morning maple. Thanks to 500 bits
This is like a red bubble version of the daffy duck skit where he's fighting against the animator
Yeah, this is real life
You didn't thank elliot mills for their countless stolen fucking assets
I know what's wrong with me. Why wouldn't I do that?
The tombo thanks for the 500 bits. Appreciate that. Thanks tombo. No message
Whole of one zombie. Thanks for the thousand bits. Thanks for streaming really appreciate the laughs
You've raised the bar and chat has helped with some brilliant moments
I got to make the 5g gum joke yesterday. It was a blast seeing that evolve. Happy new year everyone happy new year
Whole of one zombie. You've been around for a long time. Thank you metro jelly
$15 from metro jelly bits for auto also. Sorry for making the dick phone case and scaring you you made that thing
Deleted a cthulhu syndrome. Thanks for the
$25 2500 bits get a bowl cut now, you know
I did get a haircut today and I was thinking should I get a bowl cut and I was like no
I have to have that for like a month. No
Not getting a bowl cut not gonna happen
I appreciate the 25 fucking dollars though. It's a lot of money. Thank you
Bala koala. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey jerma by this point you've probably seen this but apparently little naz x is a fan
The dude who did old town road you boomer. I can't fucking believe that
That's ridiculous. I seriously can't believe it
He's probably watching. Well, thank you little naz. I i'm shocked. Thank you old town rats
Yeah
Don't forget us when you're famous. How could I ever forget you guys?
You got me here in the first place. You serious?
And plus it was just a little fun tweet. It's not a big deal
Not a big deal. Also
Uh-oh, I lost my place
Where am I? Where the fuck am I? How did I lose my place? What?
Oh, there we are
Vilemi, thanks for the thousand bits Vilemi. I'm glad at least the chat agrees that the doctors were the best joke of the year
Well, it was nominated for worst joke of the year. So
Bad news for you bala koala. Thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars
German just want to say thanks for the last year
You and your community did a lot for me in the past 365 days
Just want to say thanks
Wish I could give more money, but my job fell through and i'm back to contract work
So I gotta be a bit more conservative with my money than i'd like
Anyways, excuse my rambling. I've been celebrating the new year. Just want to say thanks never under any circumstance ever
Feel obligated to give this channel money for any reason ever ever for any fucking reason ever
You being here and watching
Is enough for me. Thank you. Seriously. Thanks a lot
No one is under any obligation to pay this channel money. Tell that to the people that gifted 2020 subs
It was a lot
It was a lot, but no one's ever supposed to do that. I hope you know that we are encroaching on 10k subs now and
None of you have to do that, but you do a lot of you do
I said it three or four times
I hope you think it's worth it. I really fucking hope you think it's worth doing
Seriously, I don't want you to give subs to this channel and look back and be like, ah, that was fucking stupid
What a dumb idea. I hope you think it's worth it. Thank you morning maple. Thanks for 300 bits
The pottery was good bugleberry wasn't damn it. That's that's real. It's a real statement
Peaceful hailey, thanks for the 550 bits. Happy new year germa. Hope 2019 was good for you
Just want to say that you win the category of best streamer of the decade in my heart
You do so much for this community
The fact that you took pottery lessons for a bit is so much dedication
Most streamers wouldn't do that
You're an amazing funny person. Anyways, hope 2020 is the best it can be for you
Keep up the dedication. I will this stuff in the works right now that is gonna take months
But hopefully he's worth it
I think it will be we'll see
Thank you hailey reaper. Thanks for the 250. Hey germa. When are you gonna admit that bugleberry is terrible?
I'm gonna take him out back and shoot him so we can never see him again. Never that's not gonna happen
Uh erasmus. Thanks for the 275 bugleberry hindsight is 2020. Happy new year. Jean claude. Thank you
Appreciate that
Vilemi gave 5 000 bits. No seven fucking thousand bits 70 fucking dollars
Germa owu was the best noise of the year and no one can change my mind 70 dollars to say that jesus christ
Thanks for letting
Bullet casing. Thanks for the 5 000 bits not to be trumped
50 dollars from bullet casing. I have literally never laughed this hard at another stream
You fucking deserve this germa laugh my ass off. I'm glad you think that
I hope you continue to think that if not, then i'm doing something wrong
I'm doing something wrong if you're not having fun here
I'm doing something fucking wrong
And i'd like to correct it
Thank you
For the 5 000 bits seriously
Uh, yes is online 5 000 bits so much money
Jesus christ
Thank you for an amazing 2019. There's no other creator in the world that brings me as much joy and inspiration as you do
Much love to chat as well as for finding humor and literally anything
Here's to an amazing next decade. God bless you all
those are
Incredibly nice things to say about about anybody
I'm happy you say them about me. Thank you so much for the 50 goddamn dollars
Jesus small boss. Thanks for 500 bits. Hey germa. You're unironically the greatest streamer on twitch
I came home early to watch this and I regret it
That's pretty good
That's good. I like that one
Uh, happy new year. Happy new year to you too small boss. Thanks for the five dollars
Shoal shoal v. Thanks for the four dollars and 20 cents. Happy 2020 you idiot
Thank you shoal v
It's at this point where we got
An absolute ridiculous amount of community subs. I can't even fucking count them all
Just wait till you see the credits. It's gonna be crazy. It's gonna be the it's gonna be the most ridiculous credits of all time
Noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for 300 bits. I didn't have another dream about you last night, but that's good
But I had a trip to the er this morning because I had a giant splinter in my hand. What the fuck
And I watched a vod to help me through the pain. Thank you germa. Hope you're all right. That's
Doesn't sound good. That sounds like it hurts
But thank you noodle for 300 bits
Eco leech 1500 bits from eco leech. Thanks for the 15 dollars eco
Happy new year. Jeremy. You've been watching for about six years
Here's to another decade
Thank you so much for watching. Thanks for the 15 fucking dollars
Eco leech appreciate that
Bit slave. Thanks for the 300 bits. Happy new year germa. You helped me more than any other person I know
Before I was struck with depressio
And suicidal thoughts you helped me through that and kept me going
Now i'm happy
In the air force and doing a job that I love. Thanks so much for the help. I'm glad you got through it
Keep working on yourself
Keep moving in the right direction
Much love to you. It seems like you're doing great things. Thanks for 300 fucking bits
And thanks for being around for as long as you have
Of course, we remember we all remember
playing dead
Seriously bits life. Thank you. Good luck to you. We had
$100
10 000 bits from ape
Thanks germa for entertaining me the last seven years. I started the decade in middle school jesus
And now I get to build actual spaceships for a living fucking engineers
I'm telling you the boring parts in between would have been much worse without your brilliant stupid comedy
Those are really nice things to say about me. I'm glad you think that see if I can keep that
In your mind, I think about that a lot
You know it
Do people think this is funny and people into this?
I hope you are
Thank you
For the 100 dollars
And that amazingly kind fucking message. Thank you
21 thanks for the 500 bits. Hey yurmo over the years. You've helped me so much
You've helped so many people through some tough times
And I thank you so much for everything you do
It's been so great to see your channel and brands grow from old tf2 days
To where you are now your care and dedication to the community has me undoubtedly believing 2020 will have some more joy
Growth and prosperity for you in store. We love you in best regards
We'll see
It's been incredible. So
Even if 2020 is not
I've had a wild fucking ride and i'm glad to participate and i'm glad you guys got to join on the ride
It's been a lot of fun
We're gonna keep going
Ape thank you ape again for the five dollars and 50 cents best joke of the decade is the way you did your hair today
Thanks, man
Hey, sergel, but thanks for the thousand bits. I don't donate often and i'm definitely no 100 gift supper
But thanks for the year ps is sergel like circle not sergel. All right, well circle, but thanks circle, but
for the 10 bucks
Peak 24 gave ten dollars as well. No message just thousand bits. Thank you
Uh hip moss gave five dollars. No message
Skullsy gave 50 dollars with no message. Just a huge fucking money. Ishanji gave two fucking
102 dollars. How did I miss this?
Money was flying in
Jesus christ
Happy new year germa. Keep killing it in 2020. I'll try thanks for the fucking 200 bucks, dude. Jesus christ
50 subs from anonymous
Oh, yeah
15 dollars from banana joe
No message just 15 bucks
10 bucks from pif flavor of pea flavor
Hey, I just started watching this year and it was one of the best things I started doing. Thanks, dude
Also, this is the last germa tax you're getting
10 dollars or zero. Thanks for watching. Thanks for being here. I'm glad you found the community. I'm glad you like it
100 fucking community subs from my name is redis. Jesus man
You did it's like three times
OIS is for olivia. Thanks for the 372 bits
Zap bearer. Thanks for the 300 bits germans 2020
Expand banana 285. Thanks a lot expand banana austin the epic. Thanks for the thousand bits
We love you so fucking much dude. Thanks for everything you do
You guys do a lot for me a lot
so
It goes both ways in potentially my way more than yours
I get a lot of fucking money and a lot of people and a lot of
I try to stay grounded though
I don't want to think
Oh, there were 13 000 people here today. All right. Look at me. I I just
Just keep going, you know, whatever. Let's just it's another let's go another day
See you in 2020, right?
Thank you austin the epic for the another thousand bits 10 dollars emperor awful teen. Thanks for the 15 dollars
Germa keep doing what you do. I hope you make more merch so we can support you more and stop those pesky red bubblers
That's true
Hey dx. Thanks dx h. Thanks for 350. You're my favorite streamer. Keep going
We'll keep going there are the fireworks. Wait, what time is it? No, not 2020 yet pst
Ball bird. Thanks for the 500 bits austin the epic another seven dollars and 50 cents
I cheered three times because I didn't understand how cheering works
But again, thank you
Thank you
All right
Yeah, it's it's uh central right?
My name is redis another hundred fucking community subs on top of the
ridiculous amount
Hundreds of subs by my name is redis pizza star five dollars pigeon five dollars
Germa, you've changed my life ever since 2013 words cannot express how much happier I am different for the better
I am because of you
I'm glad you think that
I hope you keep thinking that into 2020. I hope you keep liking the channel. I hope you think it's still fun
because if it's not fun then
Like I said, i'm doing something wrong and hopefully I can keep making you happy
Jack ah, thanks for the 500 bits germa. You're one of the funniest and charming people i've ever watched
You always make me smile even to the worst dreams
Keep doing you i'll see you in 2020. We'll keep going
You lied about the domino's pizza. I couldn't get it
I didn't I don't want diarrhea in like four hours. I'm sorry guys. I don't want diarrhea. I'm not doing it
1500 bits from pubo
If there's anyone who deserves the support it's you
No one else puts this much effort into entertaining
Stupid our stupid asses. Happy fucking new year. Jeremy you psycho
Thanks people. We'll see you in 2020. Thanks a lot
Holy was so many fucking subs
Cthulhu syndrome. Thanks for the 250 play the rats now
No, not now
In 2020 I will fire king. Thanks for the ten dollars. No message. Thank you fire king fifteen dollars
So much money has come in today
Love you. Jeremy. Thank you rudy for the fifteen dollars
artesian albatross five dollars lobslob
Jay zanye west 105 fucking dollars
German just want to say congrats on how far you come you have somehow managed to keep me laughing all through 2019
I look forward to 2020. So do I
Thanks for the ridiculous amount of money jay zanye west
The arm op thanks for the 10 bucks. Happy new year. Jeremy first time subscribing and donating on twitch
I've been watching you for ages
Here's to another decade
Only complaint is that mouth cam face cam was joke of the actual decade
I've done mouth cam a bunch of times
Fucking mouth cam
Oh my god, taeyon. Thanks for the 250 my cheeks hurt you did this i'm
Happy and sad at the same time
Uh pair pair gave five dolls and links the falling down in the chair image
I put it on stream. It's embarrassing. Thank you
Wreckers d thanks for the 250. Thank you for influencing an entire generation of people with your comedy and personality. Love you, dad
Love you too, son
Thanks for taking anything from the stream go to bed
Argonator, thanks for the 250. Happy new year. Jeremy watched you most of the decade
Probably do it again
How about you play the old outro for old time's sake one last time and send it off with love. I will
I'll put on bloom blooms. Absolutely
Gnarly, thanks for 250. Wish I could give more but you seriously the best content creator on both youtube and twitch
I've been watching for five years and I cannot wait to see what you do in 2020
That means a lot. Thank you. I
I just i'm just trying to do stuff. That's I think is fun
If you think it's fun good if you don't then i'm trying to do something fun, you know, whatever it will
See if 2020 continues
right
Techno toast. Thanks for the thousand bits. Jeremy. I've been watching your content since high school
Like 2011
You're one of my favorite content creators ever. I love seeing you go higher and higher with your content
Can't wait to see how you evolve in the next year
Thanks so much for existing my man. Jeremy heart
so many fucking
Nice comments
So many people saying such nice things
Do I deserve it?
I don't know
I
Thank you
He's gonna do a villain monologue
Charlie is sad. Thanks for the
Hundred dollars and fucking ten thousand bits
I owed you this for a while because I said I'd donate if you did a fortnight dance on stream
Like since months ago, I tried to laugh at the jokes during the best of the decade, but I was too choked up
Thanks for everything. Jeremy. Love you lots
I me too a little bit
some of those
Some of those clips were
You know, it's a long time ago
I've been here for a fucking long time
Someone is fucking coming to get me apparently
Jesus
fireworks
Well, I really appreciate the
Hundred dollars charlie. Thank you
Hey 21. Thanks for the 250 nearly 10,000 subs and can't buy a decent haircut
Yeah, that's true. I'm killing the villain hair is nice
This was such a heartwarming stream and perfect way to cap off the decade. Thank you again. Thank you for being here
Vilemi
2,000 bits
Jeremy you deserve it and you know what to celebrate closing out such an eventful decade
Uh, why not treat yourself to chugging down a refreshing mountain dew throw?
Oh
Mountain dew throwback. Oh
No, keith king crimson. Thanks for the 250. Happy new year. Jeremy. Love you and links the the o the o double the o face
God
Hey cods. Thanks for the 1500 bits cods
Hey jerma, i've been watching for eight years don't have much to say other than thanks for the support over the time
Happy 2020 you too
Have a good one. It's been so much fucking huge like 20 12 20 dollars 10 dollars 10 dollars 20 20 20 20 100 100 100
100 subs 100 subs 100 subs 100 subs. This is fucking crazy
Mad thanks for the 1500 bits mad. Happy new year jay
Started watching you when I was like 12 or 13 and here I am 18 years old and transferring to college next fall. Good luck
Thank you for the past countless evenings you and chad have given me as an escape from my bipolar and dysphoria
This goes to you too chat. Love you all
If I had to pick a group of idiots to spend my few free hours with it'd be you idiots
Good night and happy new year
Much love to you mad
This community is fantastic. People are so fun here
We fuck around a lot. We do but people are so
Awesome here
I've never ever thought like oh fuck this place. No never not
never
It's like 10 years in 10 years
Thanks guys
I wouldn't pick any other group of fucking jokers
to spend it with
On near easier than you guys
seriously
cad b tv resident game developer
Great stream year and decade. Have a happy new year you too cad. Thanks cad. We are encroaching the end of the bits
Uh spine escape 250 you've been my favorite creator this past decade. Thank you so much for everything you've done and continue to do
Life wouldn't be the same without you in the community you've fostered
Has become one of the nicest i've been ever seen
I'm honored to be a part of it honored for you to be here
small request
Would you consider playing bloom bobs to play all the decade? Absolutely shout out to blordow, of course
Yeah, blordow has done all the art all the music
Huge shout out to blordow
And their awesome music their awesome art. It's been a part of this channel for a full decade
I agree support blordow
It's a really really good person
Spark not thanks for the 500 bits first time i've ever cheered on this site, but this stream was absolutely incredible
Thanks for keeping me and everyone else here entertained
All these years. Hope you have a great new year
Thank you spark nut for the 500 bits. Appreciate it
Jerma's been streaming for a full year. I've been going since
Since fucking august I won't stop
Hunter peck thanks for the 500 bits. I just need to say thanks jerma. I started watching in the sixth grade
And now I just finished my first semester at college. It's crazy to think about that
I'm proud to have donated 20 for the mcchicken stream and I am so proud
To have you part of my life. Thank you
I'm floored that you would say that about me. Thank you hunter
He paid for the mcchicken
Thanks for paying for the mcchicken. I really appreciate that
Hey kiddo, thanks for the thousand bits. Happy new year trans rights
Whoever whoever the fuck you are doesn't matter
If you're gay straight trans
You do you do the best fucking you you possibly can in 2020 doesn't matter who you are
Do you the best way you know how because you're the only person that knows
You are the only one that knows you
Thank you kiddo
Thanks for the thousand bits
Nimble pickle. Thanks for the 500 bits. I didn't think I would cry tonight, but I would be lying if I said I didn't
damn
Oh, it's been an amazing 10 years your videos and streams are always such a joy to watch your vids are always there for the worst
times of my life
And here's to the best
Let's make this next 10 years the best
Oh
Thank you. I hope forget about the next 10 years
I hope the next 50 years are good for you. Have a good 2020 and 2021 22
For real. Thank you. Nimble pickle. Good night to all and to all a good night. Yeah, that's right
Peepee poo poo sixty nine four twenty six six six. What a fucked up username
Thanks for the five dollars. Hey German long time viewer first time donator. How do you feel?
About giant enemy spider
Becoming a meme if people think it's funny
then
Sure, whatever i'm not gonna stop it peepee slap
Thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars every ounce of love in my heart to you germ
I've been watching you since 2013. You've gotten me through a high you got me through high school
Into college and starting my transition
Keep doing everything you're doing and I wish you the best of everything life is great
I love to play on life is pain
Good luck to you. Good luck to you peepee slap
Much love to you
Life is great
Apple shift. Thanks for 250 real shit, man
The best joke of the decade compilation at the end there made me actually tear up
It's my six month sub anniversary. I can't thank you in this community enough for everything
I know I always say it but I still could never say it enough. Fuck. I'm starting to
Oh
We got him not yet not not yet i'm still good i'm still good
I'm good
Have a wonderful 2020 and thank you for making my 2019. So yeah
Uh, here's to many more. Thanks apple. Thank you mission failed cry saved
Yeah, but
You gotta think about it right when people say these things
You know, it means a lot if i'm if i'm that much of a positive influence on somebody it's like damn
That makes me fucking happy. Like i'm glad you i'm glad you take something like something good
It's not all positive like life is not all positive, right?
It's like oh positive only positive only fucking positive only but it's not realistic
but if you have fun here and shit and you
You've made friends and stuff. That means a lot it really does
This community has fucking grown a lot and there's a lot of people that have made friends and shit and i'm i'm so happy about that
I people tell me like oh dude. I was in discord. I've made like lifelong friends in the discord and shit. It's like good
That's awesome
That's really awesome
more subs and shit have come in
The true michi. Thanks for the thousand bits
You know, I still remember when I first got on the stream
Uh chicky told me to visit him and we watched your stream together
I had such a blast with him
And since he's gone
Uh, I don't know since he's away. I keep sticking around here from time to time
And you put a damn smile on my sad face every time
So thank you
For everything man. Thank you so much for talking to him
And I thank you for being amazing
uh
Those who don't know
I haven't i've never talked about it because there's no there's no reason to
uh
And there's no reason to talk about it now
but there was somebody in the community that um was going through a lot of shit and had
brain cancer and
I hung out with them a few times and
They were really really awesome. They were really good person
Uh, and there's no reason to even go any further than that. You know what I mean?
And some with somebody put me in contact and it was
It was really awesome to hear the things that they had to say
They were really fucking good person
And i'm really sad to know they're gone
so
Yeah, I mean this is this is this is a big deal for me
to
Michi, I think was one of the people that put me in contact with him in the first place and something i've never talked about on stream
uh, so
But for real much love to you much love to chicky
They were going through a lot
That hit me right that hit me right in the chest it did
Thank you michi for the thousand bits and for even even putting me in contact
In the first place was with with chicky much love to them as well and their family
You know, sometimes you get real right? Sometimes you get real
I'm not going to pretend like i'm going to put on some
show
100 of the time this is real shit. This is real shit
It is
I came here for laughs. Yeah, but it's it's
sometimes you got to be real and just knowing that
If I made somebody happy at all and I mean this we're talking about this is like a year ago more than that
Thank you michi. I really appreciate the fucking thoughts and I really appreciate you coming in the stream
oh
Because if people really like I said before i'm sorry
I just fucking punch you in the face if people really get something from the stream and it's part of them
you know that makes me fucking happy and like that's
What else could I ask for? What else could I possibly ask for?
Oh, thanks for the 15. No fuck you who cares about money, right? Like if you guys are happy they're good
but that that hits home because
It's just just something to think about
I don't get very
uh emotional on stream
But for stuff like that i'm going to
And i'm not i just i'm that's just the way it is
We made him cry
No, no, I got a little I got choked up and there's a good reason for it
But we can move on from that
Fuck you. You cried
I did
I did I did. Yes, I did. I got a little emotional. Well, it's 2020
You guys don't even know I fucking got choked up like two videos before I got choked up like two videos ago
I got news for you
Change your category to just crying
Everybody I just gotta tell you
No, I like being real with you guys from time to time we fuck around a lot but sometimes you got to be real
but seriously rest in peace to chicky and
Much love to everybody in his family
He was a really really fucking good person
We will move on
We had 250 from j bong
The content you produce for this platform are miles above anything else man. My first stream I caught was undertale. That's a long time ago. Damn
Now I can say I threw a frog at your face in 2019
It's insane seeing your viewer go from one to two k people now averaging four to five k
Keep it up
I'm gonna try
We'll see this channel has gotten a lot more popular
somehow some way
Parasol 1500 bits. Thank you parasol
j zanye west nine dollars
Damn, thank you. J zanye west
Just take the rest of my bits. You truly deserve them for keeping it real and staying humble
If you ever do another green screen session, I'm hoping to see grandpa make an appearance
Lol, coffee cheetos chicken had to hear it before the end of the year
That's a good that's that's good good end of the year
Kaiju guts. Thanks for 300 bits. Can't even begin to explain how much you've done for me over the years. Here's to many more
Your dedication and hard work continues to inspire. Love you germ. Happy new year
Happy new year to you too. Thanks for the insanely fucking kind messages. Thank you
Thanks kaiju guts appreciate that
Cream corn. Thanks for 250. You never said the last category
How many people would suggest germa 985 to a friend also? Thanks for the great decade. What was it?
Let me see
Not 88 percent. That's pretty good
That's pretty good
That's not bad. That's pretty good
88 percent that's it's a b plus i'll take a b plus i'm a b plus streamer
Dr shrug. Thanks for the two. No five dollars. The ayaya bit made me take off my headphones
And take a quick walk around the house every time I hear it. I'm fucking sorry. I know it's the worst thing i've ever done
Stanktron
Thanks for 500 bits germa. Happy new year. I was not able I was not at the best state earlier today
But thank you for making me happy like always you genuinely made me laugh more than anybody in the world. No kidding
Thank you. Glad you put up with my bullshit. Thanks for the five dollars
No soup for you. Thanks for the three
Thousand bits thirty dollars. No soup for you
I immediately regret this because i'm currently out of a job
It's okay. I finished school. So maybe there's more coming your way when I get a good job
Thanks germ pleasure modding for you and your shitty chat. I mean lovely chat
One of our mods here. Thank you soup for the fucking huge thirty dollar drop. Appreciate that. Thanks a lot, man
Uh casu bearcat. Thanks for the thousand bits germa my fiance and I watch your streams and videos every night
We love you. Thank you for everything you do. We're so excited for what the future has to bring
There's some
I will tell you
Early 2020 there's gonna be some surprising things
That you see here
Some stuff you're gonna you're gonna question everything
You are going to question
everything
Somewhere in march of 2020
You'll be like what the fuck is going on
We just started working on it a few weeks ago. We'll see but thank you. Uh kaisu
Praised that son bro. Thanks for the 500 a bit say germa. My very first introduction to your channel was your pc doctor video
Little did I know this compact comedian would become one of my favorite streamers
Keep up the great work. Here's to another 10 years
We'll see i'll try there's been so much support tonight. Jesus christ
I can't fucking believe
there's
We're almost at 10k
99 73 are you fucking kidding me?
That's like guys. You have to understand something having
10,000 subs on twitch is like top
20 on the entire platform. That's like top 10
Top 20 on fucking all of twitch
Are you shitting me?
me
This dickhead really?
Are you kidding me?
No fucking way
my god
Make him number one
99 95
No way, no fucking way. No fucking way. No way. No way. Did it just happen?
Did it just happen? It just happened
10,000 9
10,000 99 subs 10 fucking thousand subs on this goddamn channel. Are you kidding me?
This is this is top 15 top 20 on twitch
What am I what do I say? What do I do? What do I say? This is ridiculous
This almost the 10 the 10. Ah, yeah. Yay
Give a speech
You want me to give a speech?
I'll give you a speech top 10 actually i'll give you a speech. Sure
That deserves a wink
How do I look right now? I probably got like boogers coming out of my nose
Do I got boogers all over my nose probably?
Life is pain. I hate that. Oh, that was bad. I don't like that
What's going on?
Get it off, okay. Um, anyways, uh, that's
Over 10,000 subs on the channel. I don't I never thought I would ever see this
ever
In the history of ever being on this fucking platform you guys have
Fucking crazy
Jesus christ
Oh my god
And we still have bits to do this but not just subs. It's been a shitload of bits
Thanks everybody do the sub credits. Not yet. I will it's gonna be crazy
What a fucking year
There this is what's ridiculous to me
There are 10,000
122 subs on the channel
That's so many people that's so many goddamn people
Just keep just stick around early 2020. There's gonna be some crazy shit
In before mixer contract. I ain't even got what i'm not going anywhere. What the fuck?
Superintendent chalmers. Thanks for the two no five dollars here. I just want to say thank you for these eight great years
Also since rats won best joke
It's also the year of the rat
I think you should play the instrumental version of rats birthday mix tape for the rest of the bits
Uh, not the rest of the bits. Maybe a little bit
Maybe just a little bit. I can't fucking believe this 10,000 subs on this channel
I'm kidding me. That's
Here we go. Is it gonna play? Where is it?
I don't hear it
Oh, it's because I ripped my headphones out when I fell off the chair
Uh, thank you xerox for the five dollars. The content you make is made me incredibly happy through the past couple of years
Of tough times and loneliness
Keep making amazing content being such a caring creator turbo heart
I'll try thank you nate
Cease for the 300 bits. Jeremy my roommate of five years introduced me to your content and our friendship wouldn't be the same without you. Thanks
Thanks to your roommate
Pink boo for the five dollars
I'm a bit sad that john junks the shitty gamer wasn't even in a nominee for best new character
But this is still a very entertaining stream
Glad you think so. There's a lot of people involved
There was about four or five editors
And made a bunch of those videos got them ready
the spectator cad
Uh jk productions had three people
To get it going in the last three days
Thanks to them
special, thank you
To we had a ra ra rasputin for the three bucks
Polka xd for the five dollars. Thanks for being there for me for nearly a decade without people like you and star
Uh, wait without people like you and star I would be a lot happier
Thank you without or with oh without people like I was gonna say wait what
Without people like you and star I'd be a lot. I would be a lot happier. Fuck. It is that. All right fine
Fervidal giant. Thanks for the 250. Thanks for a fantastic decade of non-stop laughs. You've had an enormous effect on a lot of our lives
Just want to say I love all you fuckers
It's a lot of great people here
Cosmorphia, thanks for the 1500 bits. I've been an avid follower throughout the hardest years of my life so far
You've helped me through tremendously. Thanks for the memories gerbil. Thank you for the memories that you've given me countless
Uh zion w asd. Thanks for the five dollars. Yo, happy new year guy
We've attracted a bunch of great people to this community. You're wholesome. It's nice to have people to talk to you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Thanks zion no vas. Thanks for the 250 germa is part of the one percent now
Uh
It's 10 000 subs like what the fuck is happening in my life
What is happening in my life right now that I have 10 000 twitch subs what's happening?
In my life. Thank you coke gaming. Jeremy. It's late. Don't you have a date?
uh
Uh-oh
All right speed speed lightning speed lightning web skull. Thanks for the five dollars germa despite being here for about a year
I think this is my first message in chat. I got free bits from a survey. Thanks for giving them to me
Squid king. Thanks for the five dollars. Yo, how's it going?
I got some of my grandma's apple pie wanted to say thanks for all the things you've done and people you've helped
Thank you squid freudian weapon. Thanks for the 25 dollars. So much money is coming guys
like thousands
potentially even like
10 000 dollars tonight. It's a lot
Freudian says it's been absolutely wild seeing your channel grow this past decade since watching your tf2 videos
Your streams are the highlight of my week
And I always tune in when I can your hilarious and charming guide. I never regret subbing or giving bits
Can't wait to see where you go in 2020. Best of luck. We'll see thanks for being around for as long as you have
Ten dollars from whoa. Wow me and the boys on hippie loved
This stream honk bunk a bunk. There you go
Finding monroe. Thanks for the thousand bits long live auto demis. Thanks for the 15 fucking dollars. Love you, dude
Have a great new year you too
The jewish bro. Thanks for 300 bits since the stream was super crazy. What are you gonna do saturday?
Uh, joel and I are gonna play keep talking nobody explodes
Also, i'm glad it didn't come into a bit that made me question your sanity that does happen quite often
Freezy burns thanks to 300 bits
It's just they smash the keyboard with a bunch of letters. Thank you for the 300 bits freezy
Stankton thanks for the 500 bits. Germa is in weezer. We've actually seen this before
Your fave is in weezer
We have seen this
It's an interesting image
It's a ghost party. Thanks for five dollars germa. Please play bloom bombs. I will
I will
Polka thanks for the five dollars the last decade's been one of the worst of my life
I cannot thank you enough for what you've given me throughout the years laughter really was the best medicine you can give me
I'm
I'm sorry to hear that your life has not been going great
But i'm happy to know that this community makes you happy
Thanks for sticking around
seriously
I joy boy. Thanks for the thousand bits germa finally decided to join your large community of loving fans
I just wanted to cheer for you and say that you are a legend
I don't know about that. I don't know about that. I've been watching for a short while love all your content
Please keep making the awesome interact stream ideas
Once again, keep it up. Thank you
15 dollars look at all this shit. Look at this
15 dollars from ink grim germa. I watched you for 10 years
Since I came to massachusetts. I was alone, but you always make me laugh. Thank you so much
Thank you for the 15 fucking dollars and the incredible support
chunky baloney
Chunky baloney gift 250. Hey germa. It's your suite mate from 15 years ago
This is real
Chunky baloney is my old college roommate. This is actually real
I can remember watching you play wow in your dorm room as a gnome shouting for gnome ragon as you ran around
Today you're basically doing the same exact thing
But with thousands of people watching you
You really haven't changed in that time that and that's honestly why you get 2000 subs in a night
You're a genuine entertaining person
That doesn't need to pretend to be anything that you're not and I think everyone here can see that
I can't pretend. I don't I don't know what that I can't pretend
I don't believe me. I if I try
pretending just
Oh kim is calling me. She's probably like where are you?
It's almost midnight
All right. Oh, I gotta let me I gotta take this. Yeah, that was kim. She's like, uh, I don't think anybody can get in here
Uh las vegas on the strip is crazy
so
Let's see if I can get out there
I'm gonna be taking a lift. Let's see if the lift. Hey lift driver
Can you get me to the strip in 20 minutes?
Get out of here. Get out of here. We're almost done lightning round
Uh, she actually said I don't think you can get out here. So I was like, okay do the bits tomorrow
No, no, no, no, we're almost done
Try thanks for the five and no, no, no, it's fine. She said I can't even get there anyways
So we're about we'll i'll see you in about 20 minutes
I'll be fine. Don't worry. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Don't worry. I'm good. We're almost done
500 bits from try rats rats with the rats here for another new year's pass. That's right beautiful jen five dollars german
You've helped me through many sad days
Kept me going through even rougher ones. Thank you. Beautiful jen. Have a great decade beautiful jen
The schmidt meister 500 bits at 6 30 here and i'm glad to catch your stream in if it's just the end
I hope this next decade treats you well
I hope the decade treats you well as well
schmidt meister
Nicholas, hey nicolas, thanks for the 500 bits. Thank you for the entertainment over the last eight years
I cried during the best joke of the decade video best joke was one where you and mala and star through grenades that made music
That's the uh pianists
Tristan thanks for the 25 dollars. Jesus german
I've been watching you on youtube since middle school and it's crazy to think that you've actually shaped my sense of humor
I regret not subbing on twitch
There are 10 fucking thousand subs
So don't it's all right. That's you giving me 25 fucking dollars right here. Thank you
Ketsu band. Thanks for the thousand bits 10 dollars been watching since 2012 so grateful that i can always come to your videos when things are tough
Happy new years. Hope it's a good one. Hope you have a good one, too. Thanks for the fucking 10 dollars a lot of money
Void five dollars happy new year here's to another decade here's to another decade
That's true ten dollars from red the mage sadly. I missed the stream
But i'm excited to watch the vod so glad to have you here for the past decade of my life
You've made so many people's lives better. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Miss lily t thanks for the thousand bits. I'm honestly not really sure what to say
I want to thank both you germa and the chat for the great laughs i've had especially the discord
Who keeps me going through life even if they don't think they are
Every time I come back to the community with a stream, I feel 10 times better. Thanks. Everyone. Love you all
We've got a great discord community
We have an awesome discord community if you want to join it it's available. It's open to the public
Death gamer. Thanks for 300 bits been watching you since elementary school back in 2011 a long time death gamer. Thank you
1500 fucking doh 1500 bits from
Doris
Or dar east you are the leonardo da vinci of entertainment. Holy fuck. That's a lot to say
Best streamer on the platform probably in existence. Hope you still love what you do and have a great next decade
I still love it
I still have as much fun as I did five ten years ago dub ski dude
Thanks for the 250. I made it in time to give bits
It's been so much fun mike and subreddit shit posts for this community and it's really kept me my creative side going
You're an inspiration in my you're my favorite human being just promise me you'll get a haircut and a tan
You're a goblin
maybe
Vr josh vr josh. Thanks for the five fucking hundred bits jerma. Thanks for such a great year
Can't wait to see what elaborate ideas you come up with in the new year
You're one of the most creative streamers i've seen there are a lot of good streamers on this platform
Thank you vr josh. You've been a big part of the community for the last full year and a half at least
Uh zooty thanks zooty for the thousand bits ten dollars glad to start the year and more subs from molly water. Jesus christ
Oh my god
Glad to see the start of the year finally subbed to your channel
Hope to be as dedicated and humble in my life as you've been in this decade. Happy new year to you and chat from new zealand
Thank you
Zapper thanks for 300 bits future gamer 250 blordow's brother has tongue cancer
Please consider donating
Uh, unfortunately, this is this is a true statement
um blordow
Has some fam his family his brother's going through a lot of shit right now and they're trying to
Uh alleviate some of his symptoms if you have anything
He's trying to raise money to have some
um natural juices and natural
Foods to help with his brother's recovery. So
Unfortunately, that is a true statement. That is true. Thank you future gamer for putting it to the attention of everybody here
And we're lightning rapid lightning rapid lightning rapid 250 from garfield the monday killer back from popular demand is garfield
Let's get some applause in chat, please stop booing
Uh, it's been quite a time hasn't it germa? I turned 40
Uh avengers did that thing star wars did that thing what a time to be alive
But wouldn't it be I wouldn't be where I am without you germa garfield owes a lot to you
I remember watching the fat guy engie vid all those years ago
I remember watching germa level three on new year's eve not so long ago when
You go to sleep remember garfield odie and john rbuckle think you're poggers
Thank you garfield
Icarus gaming 250 we're almost at the end germa early this year
I broke up with my girlfriend of one and a half years of realizing I was gay
I was really isolating for me since i've been talking with her every day until that point
But your streams helped me tear me up and keep company during it
You're a huge inspiration the things you said in these post stream chats got me to return to college
And find my path. I'm now getting a degree in english. You're a big part of that. Good luck to you
Learn learn learn
Thank you Icarus gamers for the 250 and the incredibly kind message. Good luck to you
Uh schauden freud
Thanks for the five dollars. I'm very new to the channel
But to say your streams have made my day or an understatement sometimes you're the only thing keeping me going
So I appreciate you being here. That's a really fucking huge nice thing to say about somebody. Thank you schauden frog
The virtual boy. Thanks for the 900 bits germa. I seriously think you're one of the funniest dudes ever
That's debatable. I've been a huge fan for a long time. Love seeing you grow and evolve
You deserve every bit you've gotten in my opinion. Thanks for all the laughs
It's a big statement. I'm fucking
Grounded to think that you think that so thank you
Expendable
Gingy thanks for the 1500 bits germa been watching what feels like forever always smile with every video
Life's been tough lately and it's always a breath of fresh air when I hurt my size laughing at your videos and streams
Thank you expendable. Thanks for the 15 fucking hundred bits
Thanks for the huge money. It's a lot of money
Spooky juror, uh james spooky. Thanks for the five dollars and 21 cents. Thanks for being you always keep it real
I saw your channel linked in a star video nine years ago. Thank you james spooky
It is time for us to show the subs. Are you ready for this? This is gonna be insane
This is going to be in fucking sane. Are you ready for the new year subs?
the
10,000 subs
Here we go
Oh
Oh, holy fuck try to read one
Uh, um, I can't fish sticks fish sticks gamings parappa. I can't it's not it's impossible
This is the fastest it's ever gone. Holy fuck
Holy shit, I can't read them snoozing copper. Thanks for the 260
Happy new year germa. It's been a great six years knowing you sometimes. I wish we could keep you a
Wish which sometimes I wish you could keep you a small channel forever
It's nice to have it small and comfy, but you seriously deserve all the best
Hope you grow even more. We'll see i'm
Completely shocked that there's this many people here in the first place
Thank you snoozing. Thanks for being here for that's fucking ridiculous. I can't even look at it
Incrim 500 bits germa just want to give you more bits. You deserve it. I came from vietnam
I was 11. It's been 10 years
Since I first watched you now i'm 21. I'm a junior in college now
You basically grew with me and I hope we can continue this relationship
smiley face
Thank you
This is insane. I keep looking over at the other screen and it's it's fucking insane
James spooky. Thanks for the 500 bits. I misclicked my last dono. Thanks again for being great
Here's me back in 2015 with you shorty
I am germa. I am slouching. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
I'll put it on screen. It's not that
I did fall down. Fuck
What am I holding?
Jesus christ
Uh, okay ice cream. Thanks for the 500 bits germa. I've been watching since 2014
You're one of the you're the one interest I come back to watching these streams is so enjoyable
And i'm european
So I usually watch your streams before I go to bed. Hope you have a good year you too
But squire 300 bits and there is there is a message here
bailiff smack his nuts
What the fuck is this?
Is not
I don't know that is
Mad max. Thanks for five dollars
I've been here since the worm stream with vinnie
Jesus christ
You've been a great entertainer for me and i've been i've been there bringing me laughs through my sobriety two and a half years sober now
Thanks to the streams
Keep at it
It's a marathon not a race
Thank you mad max. Keep at it. Thanks for the 500 bits
tylo 500 bits
Germans want to finally do a bit of giving
Started watching you middle school
I'm almost three-fourths the way through college
Here's to 2020. Thanks for being you. Jesus. Thank you tylo
Schmoodie five dollars germa uk viewer here. I never laughed so much at the stream ever. You're such a massive inspiration on me
I have pretty horrible insomnia
And you really help to keep these long and lonely nights a little less lonely
Thank you schmoozy
Really appreciate it
Peaceful hailey. Thanks for 300 bits. You're such a good person. Jeremy. Don't forget that and rest in peace to chicky
Absolutely
That's that's one of those things that I haven't really like I said, I haven't talked about it at all
Because there was never a reason to
That's kind of a personal thing that there was no reason to talk about it. It was just kind of
Me and this person had a small
um
Just back and forth relationship where we hung out a few times. I did there was no it wasn't necessary to talk about
Don't forget kim. I won't
Iota, thanks for the thousand bits first time donating. I'm glad it's a streamer like you
I've been watching you since high school
And now i'm working on a phd in mechanical engineering. Are you fucking?
brilliant minds
As well working on my transition
This is the best start to the decade. I could hope for the last video reminded me of what made me love you in the first place
Thank you iota for the thousand bits
There's so much fucking money that came in today. It's
flabbergasting
Apricot thanks for the 500 bits. This is all I have to give
Five dollars is a shitload of money. Anyways, so thank you
I've been watching you since tf2 days
You're one of my favorite people to put things out on the internet. Thank you apricot also a lot
Plastic spork 300 bits. Happy new year germa. It's been a lovely year with my boyfriend
If you ever wondered who the link was for that's who?
Raise why we met each other in your chat
And have been happy ever since so in a way I have you to thank for allowing me to meet the love of my life
Jesus plastics pork. I'm fucking so glad to hear that
That's incredible d flyers 500 bits first time donating. Thanks for all the laughs. You've given me. Thank you d flyers
Schmoozy again. Thanks for 300 bits. Also forgot to say i've been subscribed for about a year been watching for years
It's a long time to sub to anybody rock writing 500 bits more support. Jesus christ
holy fuck
500 bits from
Riso hey germa, I struggled with chronic pain and illness
For half my life
And had you to help me all the way you made a big difference through the whole thing
I want to thank you. Keep up the good work
I'm sure your projects will only go bigger these next 10 years
Thank you riso
We have almost made it to the end
of this insane
money drops
It's been a lot. Hey, oh my goodness
A v exe 500 bits germa, happy new year. Oh, I only started watching recently
But your streams have done a lot for me lately after starting hrt very recently
Thanks for being such a positive influence in so many people's lives
Good luck
Thanks for the 500 bits be the best of you you can possibly be I mean that thank you
Markey, thanks for five dollars. Thanks for the laughs throughout the years. Thank you markey for the five fucking dollars in for being here
T suck j t sock gay. Thanks for the thousand bits been here since tf2. You got me through some rough days
Happy new year a fucking another ten dollars
sir black mage three dollars
Germa missed most of the stream just coming at the end to support my favorite streamer
I'm not good at expressing my feelings through text
So my bad if this sounds stilted it does not
Thank you for personally for being a good entertainer for just an amazing person in general
You've had an amazing impact of my emotional health and my sense of humor. Thank you, sir black mage
Happy gay sounds. Thanks for 250 only been here for about a year, but it's been an incredible time
Thanks for the streams. Thanks for fucking supporting the stream with 250. Thanks for hanging out
50 fucking dollars from never trust to purple 5000 bits from never trust to purple
Germa, it's been a long time and watching feels like a lifetime words can't express the good you've done for me and everyone else
Thanks from the bottom of my heart for being such a positive force in our lives. You deserve every cent
I'm glad you think that I hope you continue to think that as we go into 2020. Thank you
For being here for 10 fucking years purple and thanks for the 50 dollars
Erasmus, thanks for 250
Surfer thanks for five dollars. Holy shit. Germa me and my good friend have been watching since 2012
Always love the content. We quote you on the daily 250 from genie boy. You're a genuinely funny guy, Jeremy
I'm usually serious and stone-faced around people
But after I met you in early 2017
And I watched you grab that auto five bit and followed you on twitch
I laugh more often as a famous actor once said a day without laughter is a day wasted
I would say that's about that much
How much you mean to me? Thank you from chile
2020 is the year of the rat. Thank you
Garfield thanks for the 250. Let's take another stroll down memory lane with gar remember that time
I single-handedly raised the bit minimum twice
Yes
It used to be 25 bits before garf stepped in the picture
I bet some of you new subs don't even know about that one
I don't know if i'm allowed to do this but since this is the last gar for graph of the decade
I guess it was worth a chart a shot
Garfield the monday killer is the reason why we have raised the minimum bits and here here you go here
It used to be a hundred actually and then garfield the monday killer
uh came along and
Gave a hundred and a lot and we had to increase the bits because it was uh, it was got one too long
But the monday killer strikes twice
Where's my keys 300 bits? Can I donate directly through twitch? I don't know. I don't have that available only through twitch or subs, unfortunately
Uh k decon or thanks for the five dollars jerma. I meant to give this to you for christmas, but it's a bit late here
Holy fuck. This is awesome
How do I get this on stream immediately?
Look at auto
It's auto. Thanks for everything
Thank you
For this awesome fucking picture
Kim is gonna love this
by the way
Kim and I did a dna test on auto because I didn't know what he was
We finally got the results back
He is 38 percent
Doxin he is 38 percent
something else
He is 10 percent
Shetland sheepdog
He is 10 percent chihuahua. What do you think the 38 percent is? That's not doxin
It's ridiculous. I can't even make this up
rat terrier
Swear to god
I swear to fucking god
He is a rat terrier doxin
Only auto would be rat terrier, right?
It's crazy
Clock working. Thanks for the five dollars. I've been following you since tf2
You're my favorite content creator. I'm happy to hear that. I hope you keep thinking that in 2020
Uh rag arnoi. Thanks for the 1400 bits germa. It's my birthday today. It's usually a bad time for me
But I laughed so much tonight
Didn't even realize it's now 8 a.m
And i'm gonna be dead tomorrow worth it though died to pinwheel
Happy birthday rag arnoi
Thanks for the 14 dollars
Gaming hash. Thanks for the 360 germa. I'm a high school student who's struggling real hard right now
This end of the year stream and all your streams make me really happy
I'm, sure if my future career choice is as I want to become a music band teacher for high schoolers
But I don't feel like I will be good at it
Very scared for my future
You'll be great
Care about it care about it every day
Cherish it love it
Care about it for real every single day
And you'll do fine
Really care about it though
Ladies and gentlemen, we are getting to the end of the stream last stream of 2019
There's been no music for about 20 minutes
But that's okay
I will see you on saturday
We still have a few more to do. We still have about 10 bits to do
People are just dumping money in and I can't even fucking react because it's a lot
It's a lot
One blondie gave 50 dollars
Germa you got me into tf2 all those years ago
You've been such a positive influence on my life and so many people's lives
Can't think of a better person to cheer to
You radiate joy
I just try to have fun as long if I have fun
That's I just want to have fun. I just want to fucking have fun
And if I have fun then I have fun and it's good to have fun
Thanks for the 50 dollars
It's a crazy amount of money to give anybody
Plain cheeseburger. Thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks
Germa you've been a huge inspiration to me and I have always you've always made me laugh more than anyone
You've turned many of my dark days into happy ones
From youtube or twitch. I love this community. I know it doesn't mean much coming from a random fan app. Don't hold on
Stop there for a second
Yes, it does
You just gave me
10 dollars
And told me that I'm I bumped you. I'm sorry
You just gave me 10 bucks
and told me that
That you like loved this community
That's a huge fucking deal for me. That's a big deal. I i'm happy to hear that like that's don't ever be
Oh, well, I I I I know it doesn't mean anything coming from a random person
We're all random people. We're all fucking random people
Don't think like that
By the way, we have the same birthday september 22nd. Fuck. Yeah, i'll be 35
yike
Leather jacket one of our mods
Five dollars take your private helicopter to the strip you 10 000 sub big shot streamer in all seriousness. Happy new year
I can't fucking believe that shit. I can't fucking believe it
That's crazy. That's insane
10 000 fucking subs
Are you serious?
Unbelievable now he's gonna get neon hair. I'm not gonna get neon hair. I look terrible
Fire king. Thanks for the five dollars german watching you and star
Says you were messing around in tf2 when I was 13. I'm now 20
I'm glad to see how far you've come wanted you to know you've earned this success
Maybe I don't
I'm not done. You know, like people say oh well you you look you you've been you're pretty successful. I'm not done
No
Not yet
There's still so much more to do
right
You peaked at the carnival. Yeah, hold on to that thought maybe not
Where are my keys? Thanks for 13 dollars. Happy new year's congrats. I wish I knew you back in the day like the others
I first saw you playing intruder with kraken
The first time and you quickly rose to one of my favorite streamers
Get me through a lot. You inspired me to continue writing and creative
Everything I possibly can in creating everything
Thank you for the 1300 fucking bits
That was a fun stream
Germa fucking germa fuck tf2 with the speed shit. I remember that thread. Oh, I remember that thread people were mad
Blaine's magmar. Thanks for the 250
This is the first year i've had to spend new years alone
Thanks for making it so I don't have to
I used to watch your casual commentaries
Thank you blaine glad to be some uh some company
Pin 250 i'm all alone tonight in a big new city far away from my friends and family your streams and content keep me spirits up
As I pursue my degree in civil engineering
Fuck. Yeah
All the best to you you too
Zalgis the sky thousand bits go to kim you dork. I will maxie kaspersky 15
I have nothing much more to say than I know every piece of content you create will always entertain me if not more
I hope it does
If you strike out seven times as long as you hit three home runs, you're uh, you're gonna 300 average
Thanks for the 1500 bits
Vinny bag of donuts. Thanks for the 500 bits not much, but thank you for a fantastic decade
Here's to another one
Yep
Tingy 250. Happy new year germa. I'm still a good bit out of it had too much to drink. I'll keep this short
Without you my two best friends peng and chilled. I wouldn't know where i'd be happy to have all of you
Happy fucking new year tingy. Thanks for being around for as long as you have aspada escalata 250
Germa here's to another decade of you being the funniest man on twitch
I you said internet, but I said twitch now get the fuck out of here. I'm going
I'm going i'm going to go
A digital haunt five dollars. My friend tyler's been watching you since 2013. Tell him that you love him. Love you tyler
Yeah, I love you. You're the best
Back in 250 good stream. Hope for the best. Love you chat. Don't go see kim. I'm going to see kim
Brack drabbins, but brack dabbins. Thanks for the thousand bits. Are you a furry?
Nope, but I will be at the furry convention in vegas
Uh in disguise, thank you for the thousand bits sir black mage. Thanks for the 268 hearing my remaining bits
You deserve them. Could you say cool one-liner?
Get out of town. That's not that's a terrible one-liner, but it's okay
Mysterious tv. Thanks for the 500 bits
Thank you germa for your incredible content for a majority of this decade
It's only up from here
I'm excited me too. We'll see what I can do
Plain cheeseburger another 500 bits hates me again want to say that if you ever need anything, just let me know
Also, I hope to meet you in real life one day cheers to 10 000 subs
Fuck yeah
10 fucking thousand subs guys
We're we're up there now
I told you this before but we're up there with some of the top on twitch
Let's go
Let's fucking go. I I ain't stopping in 2020
See you guys in 2020. That's uh, that's chicky in the middle rest in peace much love to you guys