Hey guys, remember Jerma promised to play Dead Space before his 40th birthday.
Um, that's true. No, that's true. I got a while. Still, uh, still fine with that statement,
by the way. Am I doing today? I'm doing good. I am doing good. I have been itching to play
Armored Core, but I decided I wasn't going to play it off stream. I decided I was going to
continue to play it on stream. We'll see after today. It's fun. I'm going to have to re-familiarize
myself with the controls because it has been a week and a half or so since I played it.
By the way, yes, there is a logo on my character and it's one that I made. I got kind of
inspiration. I saw, hey, look at these decals. Look at these decals. I'm going to make one.
Let me try making one. Mine's not as good as the others I've seen, but hey,
this editor is a lot of fun. It reminds me of the, uh, the 2k14 editor,
just way better than the new ones. Uh, I don't know what boss people are referring to,
but I don't think I've seen it yet. He's fishing for compliments. Yeah, I spent a little time on
it. So it's all right. What do you guys think? Bro, you're going to get filtered. We already
went over this that I, I, that's not here. That's not accurate here. Come on, give it a rest. Let
him fish. He deserves compliments. Oh, by the way, have I ever clearly stated that frozen red grapes
are the best snack in the world? Have I been on the record saying that yet? Did I, have I actually
been on the record saying that? Frozen red grapes is the single best possible thing that the human
body can eat. Like I'm convinced they are so unbelievably good. It's not even funny. Those of
you that have never had, remember frozen all the way through none of this half frozen shit, because
it takes a little while for them to freeze all the way through. Red grapes, wash them, you know,
take off the stem, get them in a little container, freeze them overnight. You open that, eat one,
don't just chomp right into it. Let it sit for a minute, bite into it. You know, it's frozen,
so it's going to be really cold. Just to make sure you know that you're into that. It's like
one of the greatest snacks ever. I eat them almost every day or every other day. They just, grapes
are so much better when they're frozen. I don't even really like grapes. They're good. They're
okay. But holy shit, you freeze them and it's, it changes everything. The whole thing changes.
Yeah. If you have sensitive teeth, be careful, but they don't. Oh my God. It's not like an ice
cube. They turn into this weird, like chewy jelly is the only way I can describe it.
If you know, you know, it's unbelievable. And all the people saying, ew, you just,
open up your, open up your mind a little, please open up your mind a little. You can say ew to
frozen grapes. Open your mind a little, please. What kind of grapes? Just, just red grapes. Green
grapes are okay with this formula, but it's the red ones, the smaller red ones that are way better.
Seedless, seedless grapes. No, they're not crunchy. They're chewy. You'll get it when you
understand. And I'm telling you, it's like going to be like a five gum commercial. When you eat
one of these, I just changed your life. Well, I didn't. That sounds like I'm taking credit for
that. I had frozen grapes a lot when I was younger. Something was like, you know what? I'm
going to do it. I feel like doing it. So I'm going to freeze some. So I, frozen grapes are going to
change your life. Not me. You see, I made this up. This is, I came up with this. All right. You guys
good? I'm going to play, um, Armored Core 6, stream for a little bit. We'll see if, uh, if I'm still
into it in another hour or two, maybe I just keep playing it. If not, after like an hour or two,
I kind of want to play coin game. I got an update a few months ago. They added a bunch of new
machines and stuff. I like playing it. So we'll see. I'm just going to wing it today. Uh, here we go.
Oh, let me show you my, uh, my unit. Wait, should it be a surprise? Uh, let's see. There we go.
Ah, take a look. Oh, see, I made this one. It sucks. That's how you can tell. I made this one.
I got inspiration from everybody that was making them. I was like, you know what? I'm going to try.
I made, I made 10 minutes. It took me like 15 minutes, 10 minutes. Yeah. I, I told you I was
going to do it actually pretty nice. I've seen some really clean ones. I think the teeth are a
little fucked up. I think I may have messed the teeth up a little, but it's okay. You can make
the paint have no wear. I kind of like the wear. Cool. All right. I'm ready. So is this the mission
that everyone's going to laugh at me for? Is this like the, here it is. Operation Wall Climber.
All right, let's just go. I'm ready. How's the audio? Are we good?
Oh yeah. On second glance, it sucks. You were just looking for the go ahead for me to make
fun of it. I get it. I respect that. What do I got for, I got two big cannons, right? I got it.
He's not paying attention. It's four buttons in a dodge. I'll be fine. Oh, okay.
I got it. Can you make more clay creatures? I want hobby updates.
I actually haven't really. I really haven't. I've been kind of busy though. I'll get back
into it. I will. All right. I got two cannons. I got the quad missile launchers on both shoulders.
I think I'm good. Let's just go. He's going to remember the dash. It's a X, right?
You need to try crocheting. The problem with me with crocheting is I agree with you. I would sit
down. I'd have on my thread. Like, okay, let's get started. I'm going to take the green and the
blue and I'm going to start to crochet. I guess I'm going to stand up and fucking walk in a circle
and then I'm going to go get like a water and then pace for five minutes and then sit back down.
I can't, I can't do it. All right, here we go. Destroy the city. Gatling cannon. I got it easy
up there. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. That's right. We're like a corporation. Oh, that hurt.
Can I reach up there? What's a heel? All right. I gotta remember the buttons. It's been a while.
How do you turn boost off? What's that? Okay. All right. All right. Now B is boost, right? Okay. Yep.
Left stick is that. All right. I got to get up there. All right. Who else is shooting over here?
You? I need full boost for this. What about Baldur's Gate three? I actually just barely
started to hold on. I can't talk right now. I actually just barely started to care about
Baldur's Gate three. Oh my God. What is even shooting at me? Oh, all right. Cannon's down.
What's left up here? Destroy the city. Gatling cannon and tetrapod MT. Where is that shit?
Not up top, right? Bro is never going to play Hylix two. Yes, I am. I promise at some point,
I mean, those things are weak. I just have to kill them. You also promised paper Mario. Yeah,
but for my 40th birthday, I got plenty of time. Oh, here we go. This thing. Oh,
I can't just sit there and stare at it. Okay. I get it. I get it. I get it. I'm going to be all
right. All right. I'm dead. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. All right. I haven't played
this game in like two weeks. The last time you saw me play this game was the last time I had
the controller in my hand. All right. It's all these fucking dickheads right here.
What was that? What just happened? It's got to keep moving. That's all it is. Keep moving. Keep
moving. Keep moving. Keep moving. Come on. Come on. Come on. All right. Uh, maybe I shouldn't
have the weapon where you have to stand still to use it. That's probably a bad idea. Yeah. The
two weapons I have on left trigger and right trigger, I have to stand still for two seconds
to use them. Bad idea. See? All right. That's better than what I did last time. We're good.
All right. Land already. There you go. There you go. All right. Here we go.
Shit. Okay. Damn. All right. Should I just go right for the guy and not like the 50 people on
the wall shooting me? Or should I try to clear everything first? Because there's a million
people on this wall. I'm playing it wrong. Oh, shit. Shit. This game is really hard.
All right. I'm doing this because these things stink here. Should I buy something new?
Just machine guns, probably? I'm going to try the machine guns. That's going to work, right?
Did that go through? All right. It did. This should be a little bit better.
Use the melee weapons. The melee weapons are fun. All right. I'm going to take this really slow.
That's a bad idea. Okay. So I should never be in the air or not in the air, but should always
be moving as fast as I can. Oh my God. All right. It's only this group right in front of the bridge,
right? There's people everywhere. I'm just going to clear everything wicked slow.
Activating combat mode. Do the frontal assault. I'm almost afraid to boot. I lose all my boost
before I even get over here. I'm going this way. I wish I could just snipe this guy up here. This
guy's ruining everything. What? This guy got homing shit on his bullshit. That's the boss?
Oh, well, that's why he's so annoying. Okay. I got a hit. All right. Where's this other guy?
All right. He's dead. What chassis has the most boost? Oh my God. I can't kill this thing.
Okay. So here are the 50 things on the wall. How do I fight this guy one-on-one?
Do I just don't? Just ignore these things? I feel like it's kind of hard to. Look at this.
Destroy them all. I guess I could just kind of fly up there. Ow. No, no, no. I have no healing.
All right. That was a little bit better. I want different items. I don't like these.
Nice bit, right? Okay. What, what is going on here? What is this thing? This is kind of good.
I want something that takes down the, what is it called? The shield? Maybe the big,
the big guns. I have to stand still though. And I get hit too quickly. Maybe I should get the
shield thing. I feel like when I jump up, I just see like, like 10 lasers just go right on top of
me. Maybe I could just block them. This is the back. What does this thing do? Laser cannon on
the back. Ooh, that's cool. Dual missiles. That's good. That takes a long time though.
That takes a long time too. It looks good. That's like an AOE. I kind of want to try this. This is
expensive, but I want it. Vertical missiles are OP. Verts are OP. Okay. It takes a long time to
reload, but I feel like I'm just going to be, I'm going to be a coward. Okay, here we go. Combine
it. Let me put it on. It does way more damage too. What about the, what should I get for the other
side? Can you doi doi doi? Yeah, for old time's sake. Sure. You know, remember, remember the good
old days. Use the sword. I actually agree with that. I genuinely agree with that. I love that
sword. It was very good. But what do I want on the right side? Something, something better.
Something a little flashier. What's this? Ooh, I want this. All right. This might be a terrible
design, but who cares? Shotgun? Shotgun, blade, little missiles, big missiles. I think it's all
right. Go in with no weapons. Just go in and use punch with my hands. I think I'm all right with
this. All right. It's time to try. Those were all just, I was just doing those too. All right. This
is the real one. This is the real one. This one's for real. This is going to shred. All right. This
is, I did my warmup. Here we go. All right. Check it out. Just, just go. Get out of here.
Get out of here. Where's the other? All right. What was shooting from behind? You see that?
It gave me an indicator that something was, what, what, what is shooting at me? There's people down
here. Okay. I'm just testing it out. All right. That's a shotgun. All right. I'm just going to
clear shit. Okay. All right. Everything here's down here's dead. It's not, it's not a race.
It's not a race. God damn it. Why do I feel like I have no boost? Do I have like a shit chassis on?
Okay. Let's go. I'm wrapping around this way. All right. That's good. All right. Good. Come on
target. It's dead. Where are they going? All right. All right. That one's dead. Fuck you.
Oh my God. This is correct. Oh my God. This is correct. I figured it out. This is correct.
Oh, this is correct. Let's get rid of these. Okay. Why do you have a Christmas laugh? That was just
like a comedy laugh. That's not how I actually laugh. No guys. When I'm watching like the latest
Will Ferrell movie, I don't go. That's just like a, Ooh, I'm excited because I'm doing something
fun right now. That's not, that's not how I laugh at jokes. Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh,
fuck off. Kill this motherfucker. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him.
Oh my God. I'm out of bullets. Where's my boost? Got him.
Okay. All right. Don't, I'm not going to fuck this up. I'm gonna take it really slow. Dead.
Okay. I'm going to take it very slow. All right. Now I take these out. We're good.
Use the jump pads. Oh, I forget what they look like. What do they look like?
All right. Here we go. Shoot somebody. What are you doing? I was trying to lock on to everybody.
All right. We're good. All right. I, I beat the mission. I did it.
Still one more. Oh, right here. Okay. Break in up there. Launching missile at target.
Let's go. I did it. That is fresh. Oh, be prepared for close quarters combat.
The deals. Oh, those went through. All right. I got it. I got it.
Who's talking. All right. This is, this is more of my speed here.
All right. And scanning. What type of pie should I bake? Um, a pumpkin. Get over. Oh yes. Pumpkin
pie. The best. Um, pumpkin pie is good. I don't know if I'd say pumpkin pie is the best though.
Pumpkin pie is, I used to hate it, but now I genuinely love it. I love one piece of pumpkin
pie. No more than one. No more than one piece of pumpkin pie. That's overdoing it. Is there
a boss up here that I have to, would you ever do infomercials? Oh, a hundred percent. Yeah.
I was thinking about doing that recently.
A supply Sherpa. Oh, is this going to give me full heels again?
That sounds pretty great. Have you seen Evangelion? I have not. I've seen pieces of it.
I've seen the final scene. I've seen the last sequence of that show. All right, here we go.
Uh, do I have a checkpoint here or do I get to really lock it in? I'm going to really,
I'm going to lock it in. Great. Oh, I thought you guys were all calling me rusty at the game
because I haven't played it in a while. This is what you're talking about. All right, let's do it.
Got it. Blind spot like right here. Oops. Get right up in there with the shotgun,
right in the guts. Stay right there. Get them, get them, attack, attack, attack, attack, attack.
Hey, hey, hey, what? Why did that not hurt? I know. I don't think I know how much shit I have left.
The air conditioner's blowing all my hair in my face. My hair is all over my, it's in my mouth
and shit right now. I swear to God. I need boost right now. I did it first try. I win. I win. I did
it first try. I win the ultimate game of, uh, can you play Armored Core 6 and you're a live streamer
and you sit here and play these games and you suck at the ball. I win. Rude? No, I'm saying,
I'm pretending to be you guys. Streamer can't do it. He sucks at everything. There's no way,
but I won. I did it. I was being you. Next boss. He's quitting. I'm calling it. I'm going to be
the next boss just because you're here. First try. I'm not going to say first try, but I'm going to
do it. You got stuck on the easy part of that mission. That's how it is though. It's like that.
Bro, you're going to get filtered like water on the next boss. You know, you've been,
you guys have been saying that this is the third boss now. At what point have you put me through
the water filter enough times where I am just, I'm just pure water. Like I'm going through the
filter. Sorry. Uh, there's new stuff. I have a lot of money too. I don't know what this is,
but I want it. Yeah. You trying to tell me I'm not going to buy this right now. I don't care
how bad it is. I like this too. New blade. I like that too. What about this thing? New training.
Yeah. I'll do the training. You get a parts for it, right? Ooh, go only melee build. I feel like
I've done the best with the melee because melee is just like, I kind of just don't even care.
I'm just going to go in and just swing. If I die, I die. That's kind of how I'm looking at it.
The next boss is the one. Apparently people have broken their controllers over.
Really? Okay. I have to get in the right mindset because I don't, I'm not going to like get mad.
I'm not, I, I'm not getting mad. This is going to be a, I'm just going to hang out and play
games today. It's not, I'm not going to put any bite marks into this. Um, whatever, whatever.
If I lose, I lose. And if I lose 10 times in a row, I lose 10 times in a row. I'm accepting
that right now. I'm not going to get angry. Okay. We're good. Just a little nibble.
Okay. Like I, well, who am I kidding? And I go like six bucks as he gets angry. All right,
let's do it. You want to do a poll? Mods do a poll. Um, do you know what? Do a channel point
poll. Let's do it. Let's, let's go all in here. Uh, will I show genuine anger at this next boss?
Like, will I, but what does that mean? We have to get some ground rules here.
Are we talking like, can I raise my voice? Can I say this is stupid?
What am I allowed to do? What's the condition? You, I think complaining is fine. Any negativity
at all. Kind of like Virgil, like the, like the Virgil rules. Okay. No complaint. But can I ask,
but here's the thing. Can I ask questions? Can I be like, I don't understand. Like,
why am I getting hit by that? Right. Like, that's a question. As long as I put a question mark at
the end of anything, I'm going to be fine. Fuck this stupid boss. Right. That's me asking a
question. This guy's such a piece of shit. Fuck you. These are all questions I'm asking. I'm not,
I'm not getting angry. I'm asking a question. I think that's okay. You lost the last time you
did this. I know. All right. Um, let me just do the training. Loophole Larry. He's already cheating.
People think I'm going to, are we just going to move to coin game in like 30 minutes? Is that
what you guys think is going to happen? Okay. Well, whatever. Let's see what happens. All right.
Range weapons to both hands. The double trigger. Um, you hold them both. Oh,
I've actually been looking for that. Yeah. This, this game is stupid. This game sucks.
I'm asking if you guys think this, I'm not saying it. Uh, I already knew that. Oh, right. I forgot
you could that. All right. I have to apologize to everybody watching. Um, I forgot that right stick
was lock on and I'd haven't locked down to a single enemy in 40 minutes. I forgot. Okay.
Generator installed to your AC greatly influenced the rest of your assembly from the selection of
usable parts to the basic performance of the AC, right? A generator that prioritizes EN capacity,
extensive use of aerial maneuvers. Okay. How do I get this one? I want this one.
I like the extended use. You have it right now, but is it on my actual character? Okay.
Fire control system installed X target tracking at close, medium, long range and missile lock
on multiple. Okay. Specialized for close range combat, allowing it to rely on land attacks with
its high firepower. Um, okay. So just saying like, go, don't fight things that this thing is a short
range. Like I completely missed that one, right? So that one is more medium short range. Oh, it is
nice Ahmed. Cool. Weapons and selection of parts used to assemble an AC determinants,
ideal combat range in style. Yeah. I didn't, we already know this. I do unlock stuff for doing
this though. So it's worth doing. You're reading the tutorial message. Like you were explaining it
to a kindergarten class. Have you watched mob psycho? Like you said, you would know.
I haven't seen the Smurfs movie either. What is that new generator? Uh, let me do all these.
Cause it's just going to unlock stuff. So just get them all out of the way. Reverse joint parts.
Yeah. Ooh. Okay. This is like a, this is like a hopper. You're like hop with this one.
This one's actually pretty good. I feel like I would love this one. Okay. Is mob psycho any good?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. No sucks. This is going to be one of you. Yep. Three different types of
weapon category, kinetic, explosive, and energy. So they do different things. They do very different
things. Cool. Look at that. I'm going to go like that. I'm going to go like that. Let's go ahead
and get, can bounce, produce heat when fired. When overheated, the weapon will be temporarily
disabled, right? Okay. So just don't overheat it. What is the overheat meter? Whatever those missiles
are on my right shoulder are awesome. Okay. That's I can tell now. Ricocheting will occur
when enemies have high defense, significantly reducing the damage they take. To counteract this,
try attacking at a closer range or switch to explosive weapons. I've been playing a lot of
sorcery. I read things like I'm narrating a story. And charge. Okay. You excited for the
Five Nights at Freddy's movie? No, not at all. I'm just being honest. Ooh, laser handgun.
There's two more. I'm going to unlock everything. I love upgrades. I love unlockables. I love
upgradables. Okay. Tetrapod leg units have high loading capacity and enable AC builds
equipped with multiple heavy weapons. Okay. They can switch to hover mode after, Oh, I have legs
now. Weird. Okay. I think I found the thing I like. How do I get this? Cause this is all I want.
I just want the, I want the floating machine. It's recoil. Yep. There's grenade launchers.
They absorb this kind of recoil, allowing these techs to be with their, Ooh, I can go back to my
missile launcher now. Ooh, I will abuse this though. I think unfortunately you can stay up a
pretty long time too. That's actually great. There's still the dash though. That's fine. Okay.
I definitely think these are my favorites so far. And hover mode allows you to maintain a high
altitude and turning in turn, making it easier to establish a line of fire and log on without
geographical obstruction. Yes. A hundred percent. This thing is great. It didn't go up even higher
too. Ooh, cool. Do the multi-lock with the shoulder. A new grenade launcher. All right.
What else? One more is tank ACs as well. It might be this one. I don't know. Heavily armored and
boast excellent loading capacity. In addition to lending themselves to highly durable bills,
they're also good candidates for high firepower assemblies. Tank type ACs are capable of,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. So it's just good. It just works well, I think. Oh yeah. This
is the one. I'm just playing Twisted Metal now. Those that know, they know. Those that know,
they know. And it was a great impression. You can drift. To execute a drift, move left stick
in the direction you want to face immediately after a boost. Hold on a sec. I'm boosting now.
Oh, okay. So it has to be like, like that. I mean, it's okay. I get it. Let's go. He hates this.
No, I, okay. I prefer the other one, but I do. I like this one. This one's fine.
This one's all right. This one's okay. Lock on. That's right. I forget it exists.
New vertical. Oh, wait. There's a new training. I'm going to do it. Advanced mercenary
certification. Adaptive assemblies. During real missions, you can expect enemy reinforcements
and other changes, right? Of course. Adjust to a wide range of combat scenarios. Sure.
Hold down right trigger and just fly. Is that not what I was supposed to do? Oh, I'm using my
regular loadout for a second. I forgot. I thought I had the other stuff on. Helps to remember what
I had on. All right. Now here comes a tetrapod. Ah, fuck. I forgot. Oh shit. Did it work? Okay,
cool. Shit. I didn't want to do that. Get over here. Ah, yes. Use lock on. I just did. Hey,
relax. Relax. Quiet. Congratulations. You have proven your skills by completing the entire
combat training regimen. Registration number RB23. Call sign Raven. All mind anticipates
excellent. Don't lock on. It reduces your accuracy. You guys should figure this out amongst
yourself. I'm getting mixed information in the chat room. Okay. Where's the one where I can't
be mad? Wait, does this go for the whole time I'm playing? Okay. So I'm allowed to be angry right
now, right? Okay, good. I got to get it out of my system then. Okay. What did I get? New stuff.
I want to try the bubble gun. I feel like I'm playing Mega Man. I got the new Mega Man power.
I want to use it. All right. I need help. Can I have some help? I want to ask another question.
Can I ask a question? So this is damage. This is the Sekiro bar. This is the, uh, what's this one?
That's the sustained Sekiro bar. And this is when, this is my overheat meter, which is pretty
high right now. So of the really important shit. Okay. Attack, power, impact, and ammo.
Those are the main important ones. There are no weapons that I have that overheat right now. Okay.
That's good. So realistically it's just damage, Sekiro bar, ammo, how heavy you are, and how much
boost you can use. That's what EN load is, right? Or do I have that backwards? Wait, no, no, no.
Okay. Boost speed, EN load, weight. EN is how much capacity you have. The weight limit for weapon
energy. Okay. Which one of these is boost? Attitude? Stability? Okay. So this is essentially
Sekiro bar defense. Boost is under boosters. Okay. I just want to make sure I know what I'm
doing here. All right. What about on this arm? What about the different laser blades?
This thing seems like it does way more damage. Oh, it only swings once, but I think I like it
better. All right. EN shortfall. What's that mean? That means I'm too heavy? Not enough energy.
This one's only four. That's one of the new ones I got, right? Get a better generator.
Oh, that's right. We have arms and legs. All right. Booster generator. How much money do I have?
This one's better. This one weighs more. Okay. This isn't the shop. I know. I know. I know.
I'm just trying to internalize a lot of this. Look at the thrust on this one. The upward
thrust is terrible though. Should I try it? Close range assist. Help. My hand is up in the air. I'm
waiting to be called on. What does this mean? Aiming assistance performance at close range.
Higher values improve aim when targeting enemies at close range. All right. So this is, I lose long
range assist. Do I care though? I'll try it. I'll use this other generator. I'll put that on,
whatever. This game is so customizable. How much money do I have? Look at all this stuff.
Medium range assist. I actually might want that. You can sell stuff you're not using.
Yeah, that's true. But let me just stumble. Let me just not look into that at all. Stumble through
the next few missions. Complain about the game. Not do any research on the chassis at all. Say
that the game is bad and that I don't want to play anymore. I think that's probably a good idea.
Let's go. That's the way. This is the way. This is the way. I've done that shit before many times.
I think I'm happy with what I got. It's going to be easy. You're too self-aware. Maybe.
These are baby missions. Why does your robot look so stupid? Hey, relax. Hey,
relax. I've said that a few times today. Hey, relax. All right.
Are you going to do a nun cosplay? No. Why? Why would I do? Well, I mean, I guess I could do
nun cosplay for the release of that new movie. The new horror movie.
The Nun 2 in theaters this Friday. I have no idea when that movie comes out.
Is that a real movie? Yeah. He's going to be a vampire for Halloween. Yeah,
we already discussed that. I only got four minutes. Did I just friendly fire kill that person?
4621. All right. Got one. I'll analyze it. Oh, cool. All right. More. This gives us some more
insight about V4 skills. Oh, it takes a long time to load that one. I like the bubble gun a lot.
I think it's fantastic. Okay. Some more evidence of a V4 situation. All right. Any more? I just
need to find a couple more, right? Not down here. There's one over here. Ow. All right. Give me,
give me, give me. Where are you? Cut it out. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, cut the crap. Okay.
Hey, cut the crap. Did I not get it? Oh, right. Somebody said you are so cringed.
Do I apologize? Do I have to say sorry? Hey, cut the crap. All right. There's one here.
You're a corn ball. Um, yeah, I mean, whatever, whatever. Oh, I can't go that way.
Got it. Bubble gun is the best gun in the game. Okay. So is it more? I think I got everything.
Didn't I? Did I knock everything? There's more in the hole. Uh, go into the pit. I didn't even
know you could go down. Where's the other one? Where's the other one? Where's the other one?
Where's the other one? Where's the other one? Where's the other one? Where's the other one?
Where's the other one? Where's the other one? There's two, there's two. Did I do it? Oh,
I did it. I got it. Okay. I thought I had to get them all. Two more optional ones. Um,
yeah, that was cool. I like how this is a snow level. Yeah, me too. What do we got?
Filter incoming.
I wanted to take one hit from the boss and just talk about how like bad the game is,
but I can't do that. I have to be real. People bet channel points on this. I have to be,
I gotta take it seriously. More upgrades. What was the, um, the ratio?
Was it like two to one, three to one, four to one for I'm going to get mad to not get mad.
It was four to one, four to one to get mad or four to one. Oh, it's been refunded. Okay. I see.
We'll do it when we get up there. I see. Yeah. I can now do OS tuning and arena by OS upgrades,
expend OST chips in your possession to upgrade your ACS OS from the OS tuning menu.
Really? Wait, control, quick turn. Oh, boost kick weapon bay. Wait, which one of these is,
uh, would you guys say is very important? Probably this one.
Boost kick. Oh, I don't have enough to do it. So that's cool. I'm imagining this is, uh,
PVP probably is multiplayer or something like virtual battles against copies of ACS created
using all minds, mercenary craft data from the arena menu. Well, this is how you get chips
invincible. Okay. It's one V one. So do you just go against people's creations? Is that how it
works? That's kind of cool. No. Yeah. Sort of do all those a lot of content in this game.
Let me do this mission first. Those are dev creations. This level, this level,
you buy the kick. No, I didn't. Didn't have enough.
This level is easy. You got it. This level is hard, but it's not the filter. Okay. Then let me try
you excited for the new saw movie. Okay. I saw, I saw spiral and I have to say, I can't. All right.
Does anybody care if I talk about spiral? Can I pause it? Can I talk about spiral for just one
second? I don't, I'm not going to spoil the whole movie. I'm just going to tell you essentially,
can I just talk about it for one? Look, just mute the stream for like a minute.
I'm going to talk about spiral or the book of saw. Okay. Um, are you ready? I'm going to talk
about spoilers for this movie. Uh, that movie did not need to be a saw movie. The only reason why
that's a saw movie is because sometimes people would lean over and go, Oh, just like jigsaw.
And they had a little bit of a soundtrack. That's that's it. Sometimes I want to say
probably three times over the course of spiral, somebody leans over and says,
just like John Kramer, John Kramer did this before like saw. And then they do the,
well, they explain the whole thing at the end of the movie at it. Like it's just, okay. It's just
like a saw movie, but it's like a soft like fan movie, by the way, they do say gas in saw too.
I watched it pretty, I watched it pretty recently. It's a soft type movie, right? But look, I love
saw. So I was like one of my favorite horror franchises, but you don't say this is a Jason
like movie. Oh yeah. Oh, Hey, by the way, everybody, all these people at this camp.
Yeah. All these people got killed just like Jason. You guys ever seen Jason? Like, Oh yeah,
I have seen Jason. Yeah. Just like Jason. Like do we have to say that in a movie? That's not a Jason
movie. Yes, you do. It's saw adjacent Friday the 13th. Yeah. But okay. But if Freddy Krueger,
all right. Freddy Krueger invades your nightmares. It's me, it's me, Fred Krueger. I'm gonna slash
you in your dreams. Right? Like we've, I've done that. You've seen, you've heard me do it before.
If there was a movie that came out where it was like Steve Stevenson and he murders you in your
dreams and he comes for you in your nightmares and he wears a sweatshirt. I mean, I don't,
it's like, what, just why is Freddy Krueger not in this movie? No, no, no, no, no. Wait.
Somebody's invading your dreams and killing you in your dreams. Just like Freddy Krueger.
I'm not in this movie at all. I don't spend one second. Yeah. Freddy Krueger. So yeah,
I'm looking forward to saw X because I don't know. It's all right. I don't want to talk about
sauce spoilers for the next. Like, do you guys remember? That's okay. I forgot about this until
very recently. Number one, I forget that there are 10 saw movies. First of all, after the third saw
movie, I don't remember a single one of those movies. What happens in soft four, five, six,
seven, eight, and nine. I don't remember them. They went from saw three to like saw 10.
The other ones in the middle were just like, ah, I guess we'll like mutilate people in the,
in the, you know, there's saw it's not saw, but it's saw. And I, I remember I look, I know what
happens. We're not talking all sauce spoilers. I know that after saw three, yes, it's and then
mm-hmm. And then it's a mm-hmm. And then that person, mm-hmm. I know, I know the whole thing,
but it's just funny to me that like, we have 10 of these movies and now we're even making ones
that are in like the sauce cinematic universe that have nothing to do with saw, but it's just like
jigsaw like traps. And that that's all that translates to the other movies.
Anyways, I've said what I wanted to say. That's not accurate. There is something else I wanted
to say that I had as a drafted tweet that is never going to be tweeted, but I'm going to say it.
I'm convinced the loud diarrhea I've had over the last few days
is what's causing all these colitis ads I'm seeing now. That's essentially what I believe.
Yes, you can unmute the stream. Yeah. And I don't, I don't, I don't have to explain that joke.
I'm not going to explain that reference. I do that too often. You're going to have to figure
it out on your own. All right. Where, where are we going here? Mute the stream? No, you guys can
unmute. We're not talking about saw anymore. Oh man. I can't. No, no, no. We're done. Where am I going?
They can't hear you. Well, that's too bad. Oh, wait. People were muted when I said that. Well,
just people, 2000 people just probably clicked the clip button. Like they had like fucking potato
chip grease all over their hands. And they like freaked out. They grabbed the mouse to go to the
click, the clip thing as fast as possible. And yes, I'm overgeneralizing that you're all eating
I know where it is. It's right there. I actually am. Yeah. You know what? Me too. Me too. I got
to wipe this off. Me too. Okay. I got to stay right near this. Whoa. Okay. I think this is just
they are where, where I killed it, right? He's actually doing like really well considering.
I know. I thought he was going to do much worse than this. God. I just love being a germamite.
Don't you? Yeah. Why'd you do that? There were people in there. Stop. This is going to pop out
of nowhere, right? You're annoying. Fine. That's fine. I got it.
Yeah. How are those for tricks? Are you talking to yourself? Yeah. I thought he was going to
teleport over here. What are the bubbles do? They do damage and they go close enough.
You're full of noises tonight. Just chilling. Good thing. I've got fucking liquid reflexes.
Whoa. Where is he? Where are you? Where is this guy? Oh, you're up there. Okay. Shit. I missed.
You guys are annoying. Like they're annoying. Where'd he go? Okay. Dad, what's wrong?
Oh, cause I said annoying. I called the video game enemies. Annoying. What is our charger sword?
Response. Let me check. Let me test it. Oh, that is way better than whatever the hell I was doing.
How did you not know? Uh, I think it's cause it said it had one swing.
So I just assumed that there was not a second swing, but if you charge it, you do too.
Is this a boss fight? I see him. I got it working on it. Oh, fuck off. Ow, ow, ow. I'm dead.
Okay. Well I get it now. Build might not be great here. Oh, I think I'll be okay.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, behind you. All right. So it's three of them. Are there a small, where's the smaller one?
All right. Four of them. Yep. Oh, come on. Go please. There's one back here.
Where are you? Where are you? I just saw you before. Where'd you go? Oh, right here. Nope.
That's the big one. Oh, they are so high up. Oh shit. Okay. Just the big guy, right?
Nope. There's another one. Where is he? There you are. Okay. Now it's just you.
Did that not hit? All right. There we go. Much, much better than last time.
Bubble gun helps a lot. It feels like it's pretty good. You don't have to be super accurate. It's
just kind of a lot of expenses, but whatever. All right. Have I made it? Is it time? It's time.
It's actually time. Perhaps. Okay. I got to think of only happy thoughts.
The lucky charms, marshmallows that turn into different like dragon coins when they hit milk.
That makes me really happy. I'm good.
Ah, that kind of hurt. That hurt.
Aren't you like 40? Yeah, I am. And I'm allowed to make funny little jokes.
Funny.
Okay. So I am being pinged by a mod right now. And it's like, dude, go do those arena missions,
please. Because the upgrades that you get there are going to make your life much easier.
All right. Let's do this. I don't meet the conditions to fight this person. Why not?
Oh, it's a ranking system. Oh, okay. All right. Let's go. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it.
Mod that mod. So these are just 1v1 challenging fights.
Mad stomp. Okay. Let's do it. Holy shit. You were so easy. I don't, I'm not even gonna,
you're not even gonna hit me once. Anybody else coming up here to fight? Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Say that now. Let's do all these. You get the emblems too. That's funny. They're very fun.
That was really fun. Wait, do I just get 17,500 gold? I can do it as many times as I want.
Like many other dosers, Rummy is utterly addicted to coral based drugs. And his perpetually addled
state. He has convinced himself that he is an invincible demigod. Even should reality intervene
with a costly defeat, he will forget about the setback entirely by the next day. Only death can
dispel his notions of invincibility. Geez. Okay. Blue collar worker who was involved in the
construction of the grid. He's now dedicated to establishing symbiosis with the coral and
building a future for Rubicon free from planetary closure. Inspired by father Dolmean's ideals.
Kick his ass. Lock on. I locked on. I was locked on almost the whole time. I am locking on. I am
locking on. Look, I just did it the whole last fight. Look, look. Come here. Aw. Maybe increase
the camera turn speed. You only need to lock on once. That's true, but if they go out of my line
of sight, I have to do it again, right? No. What? Wait, no. It just, oh, it just relocks. Okay. I
didn't know that. That's good to know. Thank you. Appreciate it. Lock on is a mode. Maybe camera
speed. I'm, I'm okay for right this very moment. I do agree that it could become a problem.
Locking on makes your aim way worse. Yeah. Seems like there's one mind to do lock on and there's
one mind to never do lock on. I don't know which one of you are correct, but just do it. I'm just
going to do it when I think I want to. That's a myth. Are we, okay. Are we in the stage of
From Software games where nobody really knows what actually is better? I feel like it would,
it's been a week or two. People should know by now, right? Or a bit. It does usually, usually
like a month or two. We'll go by her. I think we still need to wait a little longer to figure out
who's right. Um, I'll keep it on for now. Oh, that hurt a lot. No, no, no, no, no. No. Sorry. I'm
alive. Oh shit. I got really gritty at the end there. I almost had it. Went for a charged melee.
Yeah. Don't get hit. Where, where is he? Where does he start? Oops. Oh shit. No, please. There
we go. I did it. All right. I have a lot of chips now. So what are the good things to do?
Somebody held their hand up and they were like, Hey, can I, I, can I say something that you didn't
do in the tutorial? And they just went to the office. They got timed out. Excuse me, teacher.
I have a question. Go to the office. Oh shit. They did that 20 times. I finally called on that
student to send you to the office. I got a lot of money. What am I spending it on? Lock on is
broken. If you move the camera stick, lock on moves the camera for you. Oh, get the legs. Go
get the legs. That's right. Ooh. Should I do the tank? Nope. We're doing that. What should I sell
that? I don't care about that. I can just get back later. Do I care about anything on here?
Okay. Way more health, way more stability. I need more energy. So, Oh, way too much. How
heavy is the bubble gum? Bubble gun is pretty heavy, but I like it. I'm keeping it on. The
blade is pretty heavy too, or doesn't use a lot of energy. This one's good. I like this one too.
Disable one of the shoulders. That does work. I am going into, uh, apparently a really hard,
really mad inducing boss fight. Basically lock on is a useful at your weapons effective range,
but if the enemy is too close or too far for your weapon, it will be less effective.
You could also buy a new generator. Just need generator. It's the most important part.
Uh, let me go look and see what's even for sale. Okay. I need, I need a big bulky one,
right? This, this thing is 416. How much is this one? 170 for the middle one. Okay. What should I
sell? Yeah. I, and I can buy these all back, right? I can buy everything back. I'm not going
to lose any of these. This is not okay. How much do I need? 170. I want to keep bubble gun and I
want to keep, um, blade. I like the weapons I have. And now this thing is much more health.
Generators work by how much they have at full capacity, but also how much they recharge.
High recharge is going to be important for this boss fight in order to boost to dodge attacks.
Also, if you want me to, if somebody got banned and you want me to, uh,
unban them, that's not happening. Swap out the bubble gun. It's bad. Well, let me just see.
Let me see. I got a bunch of new stuff. Somebody said the chest piece is really important with
this too. All right. I'm going. Okay. Hold on. Where's my generator? Okay. There it is.
How was this one better? You don't have any back right equipment on. Is that bad? I'm still in
range here. No, I won't be. Bro does not get it. I'm, I'm doing fine. I've beat all the, look,
I might, it might not be perfect. It might not be exactly perfectly handled, but I have beaten
every mission so far and I'm going to beat this boss and I'm not going to get angry.
We're just going to go for it. I'm just going to play it. And if I'm, if I can, if I lose,
I can go back and, you know, re decide what I'm going to use. I'm not going to get angry.
This is it. Is, uh, are we, are we, do we have the, is the poll ready?
So I cannot get angry. I cannot complain. I think complaining is makes sense because
I don't have a face camera and it's not turning on. Don't let people decide your build for you.
No, I think I'm sticking to my guns here. You're gonna get angry.
We'll see. Okay, here we go. We kind of need to wait. I want to, so this, this is currently
8 million channel points saying that I will rage at this boss. I want to set the ground rules again
going, Oh, or what? Oh my God. That's fine. But me saying, Oh my God, this,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, right?
That has to be fine. Like, Ooh, I got hit by something. Oh, what? Totally.
Shit. And now I'm going to talk about how stupid this is, right? That's the difference.
I didn't even buy my chips. That's right. All right. Boost kick. Okay. How do I do that?
L during assault boost is boost kick. What is this one? Ooh, you can take away the missile
launchers and put regular weapons there. Weight control unlocks the ability to sortie
when AC is overburdened. I don't get that manual aiming. Turn more armor. Salt armor is good.
Second charge of assault armor. Quick turn fire controlled optimizes fire control. Oh,
don't even don't show these to me. Wait, repair kits. I feel like I should do this.
Either that or maybe speed dynamic deflection. This is just straight up damage mitigation.
This is just 3% less damage overall. I'm going to do the heel. I have one more.
I have people saying quick turn. I'm not going to use it though. All right. What? So I got kick
quick turn. All right. So it's unlocked. I don't, do I have it installed? Is it installed right now?
Press L and Y at the same time. You have to equip it. You need to equip it. Okay.
What does it do? Assault armor creates a pulse explosion centered on the AC.
Cancelling out incoming enemy fire and creating a damaging area. It's such a big,
like I just tasted a frozen grape and it was amazing by the way. I just like was in,
I just tasted one. It was great. Okay. So where is it? Frozen grapes just don't ever leave your
mind. Once you eat a frozen grape, it's there. It's in the back of your mind forever. It just
is. I'm telling you, trust me. Um, okay. Expansion. There it is. I think I'm happy
with this right now. I'm just going to, let me just see what the boss does. I'm not going to
get angry. We're just going to check it out. Let's go. I'm ready. Stay positive. Somebody
said, that's why I just talked about grapes. I'm not going to, look, this game is hard.
It's a very challenging experience. From software made it. This is a boss that they made. It's,
it's like millennia. We'll get upset. I am do emote only. Okay, fine. Emote only because I
don't want any help either. I got my bubble gun. I've got my super launcher and I've got my sword.
I choose this chassis because it looks like
okay. There are things being fired every direction. This is it. Okay. We're good.
Ouch. That hurt. Ouch. I'm going to try that again. Okay. Everything is good. We are doing cool.
One sees you. Who saw that by the way? And you didn't even see that.
Easy. Hold on. I like floating around like this. This is great. That thing is huge up there.
Oh, look out. Got it. They said to be patient. Everything is good. We're doing fine. Part two.
Waiting for combat. You're exposed to snipers from all quarters. Oh my God.
What's happening right now? I, uh, I'm still alive though. I just have to make it to the boss.
Okay. That's it. One more. Where are you? Oops. What? I'm on it. I'm out of bullets.
Good. I'm not bad. I'm going to get a checkpoint here. So I'm fine with this.
That's the watch points control center. Targets inside. How do I reload weapons? Can you spell
it out to me in emotes? How do you reload? Okay. It's Y plus the weapon button. Oh,
this thing can't be reloaded. That's just how much ammo is left total. Thank you. Appreciate
the help. All right, here we go. Something's going to blow the bridge up while it's running.
What is that thing? Is it a bubble gun? Oh, I see. You're very smart. You have a bubble gun as well.
He's an independent mercenary who survives. 621 kills you.
Where'd he go? I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. He flies around.
That was sloppy. It's the first time I've ever seen this guy. I'll get him.
He has bubble gum. Anybody else have this problem when they play games like this?
I forget what the weapon is on top left sometimes, and I go, wait a minute. I have that.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm seeing a lot of yeses though. All right, let's go.
Whoa, whoa. Wait, I can. What's going on? Oh, I can. I thought this was death if I fell in here.
Shit. I got staggered. Damn it. That's, that's not angry. That's an exclamation.
That's not angry. We already agreed that we, I could do that. Oh.
Ah, kind of a little. Hit him with that. Easy, easy, easy. Do not get hit by that.
Did I do it? Did I beat him? How'd I do? Okay. I feel very happy right now.
I'm not angry or anything. Things are well, things are going very well.
I thought that just kills me. That would have been really sad. Okay. Am I going the wrong way?
Oh, I was reading chat. I thought I did it. I was looking for all the pog champs.
Wait, can I take like a chip out of this? No. Ah, that was just part one. I see.
Hmm. He got through part one, but how will he do it? Part two is the scary part is a supply.
All right, well, let's go. What is it? It's probably a giant snake.
How do I do that? That was really loud. That was super loud.
Here comes the real boss. The ground's going to be lava. I probably have to do this level
in complete darkness, which is why everyone thinks it's hard.
Wake up. R.T. Thanks R.T. for the raid. Welcome everybody. Welcome. Welcome. Welcome.
We're playing Armored Core 6. I've not died once, so it's actually pretty interesting.
Welcome to the gamer zone. Oh, it's emote only. They can't even talk. Well, thank you nonetheless.
Yeah, it's weird. People are saying, dude, this is so hard. So I've been,
I've been playing this game with my feet the whole time. Like it's been going pretty well.
It's kind of hard, I guess, when you play like that. Oh, all right, here we go.
How could I have missed? Oh, is this thing out of bullets? It's almost empty.
Okay. So that was interesting. So the big problem is trying to dodge those. I didn't
know they were homing missiles, but now I do. I know they home and I think you just run them.
Where are you? I got an, oh, here we go. Here we, here we go.
Ow. My goodness. That hurts a lot. I didn't get hit by any of that time.
Whoa. Well, that hurt. What was that move? Question. Okay. 50%. That's not bad.
Happy Hob with a raid too. Two big raids back to back. Thanks guys.
Appreciate it. I'm thinking that I'm trying again. Welcome all raiders. I got to get this down.
Crap. If you get hit once here, it hurts a lot.
All right. I need shield breakers. This, this ain't cutting it. Ow. Yeah. I need anti-shield
and I need explosive. Yeah. We're changing it up. Oops. I'm not angry. I'm just a little
surprised at what just happened. Everything is okay. I'm just a little surprised. Oops.
I just wanted to get back out here as fast as I could because I wanted to change this stuff
very quickly. All right. I need anti-shield. I'm good. I'm good. I just was surprised that
that's what I just did. So what do I need? I need shield impact. There it is, right? All right.
Impact. Drop that shield. No, I'm seeing a lot of nay. Nay, nay, nay. No, no, no. Don't do this.
Isn't that what that means? Because people were saying the bubble gun is really good
against the shields, but I don't use it that effectively. I always burn it out.
Let me take a look. Hold on. Impact. What has the most impact? Probably some of these.
There's way too many yays and nays here. I'm just going to do the thing I just did.
I think that's what I'm going to do. I have to stand still for this, but
I'll try it. What do I want on the other hand? The sword is really good, though. I love the
sword of this so much. Grenade launcher, maybe? Let's do grenade, grenade. Okay, this is bazooka
and this is grenade launcher. What does this one do? Yeah. Yeah, fuck it. We're doing this one too.
That's what we're going for. It might be dumb, but I'm very surprised at what I just did,
and that's my own fault. Nobody else's fault but mine. I'm ready. I got two big missile launchers.
I've got two missile launchers now. Way better. Way better. I mean like a hundred times better.
Oh, I ran out of juice. Did I miss? Come on, do it. Okay, I do have to fight that.
I have to fight that guy again, don't I?
Oh, ow. Die. Got it. Where? Okay, we are good. Fight the boss. Well, the mini boss. Let me get
it right. I'm going to lose here, right? It's okay to lose here. There's the kick.
It's the first time I've seen that. All right, let's see. Maybe I can do it first try with half
health. I almost got it. Damn it. All right, he's a little fast. I wasn't planning on beating him
this time anyways. I had half health. These things are slow. I just need to get to the
checkpoint for the boss. All right, three hills. I'm ready. Let's go. All right, I got to get above
you. You're so quick. Shit, I'm never going to hit this guy. I am never going to hit this guy.
He's too fast. Shit. One good hit and this guy is dead. All right, we're okay. Come on,
that didn't hit. I haven't even hurt him. Oh, that was good. Ah, point blank. I'm right in
the face. Come on. I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. That hurt a lot.
He stopped bumping into me. He's bumping into me. He keeps just driving into me.
No. All right, this is a bad loadout against this guy. It takes too long to shoot this guy
with this loadout. I can do it. I can do it. I can do it. Look how close I just got it. I'm good.
Yeah, let him out of emote only. I want to see their anger. I want to feel it.
I'm just chilling. I'm doing fine. All right, my gun was just in his body.
Which ones did I kill? I wonder. Somebody said boost kick. Oh, I just tried it.
Probably does a lot of damage. Where'd he go? Boost kick scales with weight. Oh, shit. Oh,
the bubble ward. That's a good idea. Somebody shoot somebody at him. I didn't have any bullets
left. Shit. Okay, this is not going to work. I'm just understanding that right now. Yeah,
it's way too fast to use these weapons. Okay, so here's what we're going to do. You don't need
to quit. It's okay. It means I have to do it again. What are the problems? Okay, the problems
are they're too slow. So I honestly think this was fine. I think the bubble gun was actually doing
pretty good. I mean, I beat him with the bubble gun. I can't beat him with these two. I'm going
to keep it on. I need just something to like do double bubble. I think you might be onto something.
I'm going to try it. I'm going double bubble. Just need to buy the other one, right? Yeah.
All right, we're going to go double bubble. 90,000. I don't need this. That one's on.
All right, double bubble. This is fine. This can stay on. All right, what about this stuff?
I feel like I need to go to like armored core school for three weeks so I can get my doctorate
in armored core. I'm kind of too heavy. I think this is good. I mean, I kind of have... Wait.
I mean, this thing that you are so, so much lighter, but obviously all that capacity is
gone and I want the capacity. Apparently too heavy though. How do I drop some weight?
Get rid of one of these? No, I have a better idea. I'm changing my entire play style.
Everything is changing right now. Here's what I'm going to do. We're doing double sword. I'm doing
sword on left, sword on right, and then big missiles in the back. That's not possible. Oh,
it can't be done. That can't be done? Okay, well I'm going to do... That can't be done.
Try to stick with what I know. You know what? I feel like this thing is good. Get the weapon bay.
I don't have enough. And now I'm going to do this. I'm going to try this. I want to be able to move
around. Let's try that. I have to start the mission over again. All right, so do not quit
the mission. Just die, go to continue, and the continue screen has... Stop touching the camera
stick when locked on. Yeah, but you are talking about 30 years of me tracking with the right
stick. You're going to take a while to get used to that. See how this is. All right, so now that's
good. See how this works now. A little bit faster. All right, get rid of that thing. Did I hit it?
Okay, I forgot what my entire loadout was. I was just shooting as if I had the grenade
launcher on still. Okay, left trigger is sword. Did I dodge into that? My goodness.
Right trigger is just regular shoot gun. Left trigger is sword. Okay, that was very sloppy,
but it's all right. Now fighting this guy will be a lot better. I mean, I'm going to lose,
but it's fine. All right. Let's go. You're talking like you're reassuring a kid in a storm,
like those loud sounds. It's thunder. Hey, watch this. Ready? Flash. One, two, three.
Booger. That means it's four miles away. Feeling? Yeah. After you see the flash,
count one Mississippi tube, and then you'll figure it out. Lightning's not scary now, is it?
I mean, I planned on dying here, so it's okay. I want to go in fresh. Just kill me. I wanted to
get killed right there. I've been playing for three hours. I thought it's been like 40 minutes.
Time really flies when you hate fucking everything possible about a game and can't
stand playing it, and you're only playing it for views. Wow. I'm kidding. Stop that. I'm
kidding. That was very clearly a joke. Here we go. Where am I?
We're 619 and 620. Dead? Which ones did I kill, I wonder? Double.
That didn't even hurt him at all. Wow. There we go. All right. Now we're going to fight the real
boss. Real boss. I'm probably going to die in this one, too. Now we're cooking. There's the
supply. Don't quit. Don't quit. I won't quit. I won't. I won't. I'll make sure I get it right.
I know the last time I did that, at least a few of you had a bunch of papers on your desk,
and you just threw them in the air. I know. You were taking notes on my performance, and it was
like, all right, he did that like three times. Whatever. Just throw them up in the air.
All right. Here we go. I'm going to try it with this. Should be good. I did it. You need to
believe in the lock. Don't touch the right stick. Believe in the lock. I know, but I can't. I'm
trying. I promise I'm trying. No cam means you can rage in silence. I have actually not. You know,
you guys talked this up so much. This is like a filter. I don't think you guys should have said
anything, because I probably would have been like, what's going on here? Now I know this one's a
hard one. I'm just trying to watch the missiles come in. All right. I'm locked on right now. I'm
not going to hit any of the right stick or anything. This is going way, way worse than
last time. Oh, I'm already out of boost. All right. Here come the missiles. Oh, I'm dead.
Okay. That's 50%. Okay. Stop touching the right stick. That's a large ask. It really is.
It's almost making it harder for me. I mean, I'm not touching the right stick. It's weird to not
have my thumb on that though, but I'm going to keep it up. Did that hurt? I think that kind of
hurt. Ouch. I'm taking so much damage. Sometimes I feel like this game's like a war of attrition
that I will always lose. Better than last time. Oh, that happens when? Okay. We're at 50% again.
Different sword. Okay. What do I got in my hand right now? Let's go bubble.
And then this one's eight. I'll do this one. I'm all right now. All right. Let's go for it. Here
we go. Oh, okay. Bubble. I was getting better. I didn't want to do that, but it's all right.
Oh shit. I'm clear. I'm clear. I'm clear. I'm clear. Am I? That hurt. Oh, that was a big move.
What is this new move? All right. You have a gigantic sword now?
Flamethrower. Okay. All right. All right. It's not even a big deal. That hurts.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Okay. So phase two now has a gigantic fire sword. Good to know.
Okay. Just keep the pressure up. No matter what. Pressure. Only pressure. Pressure. Pressure.
Only pressure. Only pressure. Pressure. Pressure. Pressure. Pressure. Pressure. Pressure.
Pressure. What happened? Oh, shoot. I had it. It's okay. We're good. What the heck? I forgot.
I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. Oh my god. I'm just driving into it. I forgot
everything. I forgot everything. It was so clean. That first wave was so clean too. And I forgot
everything. I was so locked in trying to like fight that I forgot of the other moves. Oh,
that's fire. I forgot he did those moves. It's okay. It's all right. It's all right. It's all
right. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. I got it right here. Everyone
relax. This is it right here. I got it. I got it. It's just phase two happened and I took
two full health bars in damage because I stood there and went, what is this move?
That. Hey, easy. Easy. Am I locked on?
I forgot the moves again. I forgot them again, guys. I'm way too locked in.
I didn't mean to do that. I forgot the moves again, by the way. Like if I just, honestly,
I need to go write it on a fucking chalkboard and I'll be fine. Like a thousand times. Hey.
Oh my goodness. Okay. We're fine. All right. Phase two, the swing happens. Phase two,
the swing happens. Phase two, the swing happens. Phase two, the swing happens. Don't just keep
playing like it's going to just be phase one. Don't get locked in phase two. We're good.
Everything is fine. Everything is just completely good. We're good. Come on. Come on.
Back up. I couldn't back up. I couldn't back up. I couldn't back up. I was staggered.
I got it. I, all right. I am so confident that I'm going to beat this, but it's my confidence
that's causing a huge problem. I have to be not confident anymore. Right? Like I have to be like,
oh, it's not going to happen. I don't think it's going to happen. All right. I got it this time.
Here we go. Oh shit. That's not good. This is a bad start. I don't know. I took too much damage
there. Way too much. Do you have a sword in phase one too? I didn't know that. I wonder what the
actual way to avoid that is. There's gotta be like a, oh, it's the meta way. It has to be some
way to do it. I have no idea what it is though. Way too much damage. This, this, this one's,
this one's not, this one doesn't count. Yeah, this one doesn't count. This one doesn't count.
This one doesn't count. I tried to turn this like keyboard turning in world of Warcraft.
It's just an observation. Shoot. Oh, oh, peanut butter. All right. Pull back. Pull back. Pull
back. I thought it was me that did that to you, but it was you that did that to me. Why already?
What? Oh my God. I'm kicking his ass. I didn't realize how much I was kicking his ass.
I didn't realize this one was, I was just pressing random buttons. I thought this one was a,
just like, I'm not going to do it, but whatever. You know, if I had like 10% more patience,
I would be doing a lot better. Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to go in with this 10% more patience.
Let's try that. Is the character still in the game? Oh, okay. I was like, what the fuck is
happening? Shit. I wish you weren't so high in the air. You can tell when it doesn't work.
Oh, I couldn't even see it on the screen. Did that hurt? Kind of? Yep. That would have been
great. All right. Patience. Patience. Have it please. I accidentally just pressed up on the
D-pad. I don't even know how that happened, but I know it did. I didn't mean to press that.
Uh, that's why I'm going to take this one as a loss.
Oh shit. Okay. Um, so this is very, very, very difficult, but it's not impossible.
I'm not even sure difficult is the, I don't think it's even necessarily that's difficult.
It's that you are, you're, you're stepping on the gas. Your foot is all the way to the
bottom of the car and it doesn't stop until the mission ends. I think you just,
you have to be on point the whole, you gotta be on point the whole time. We're doing just fine.
Okay. Here it is. Not bad. Pretty good start. Keep it up. No. Back up. Here we go.
All right. Phase two, swinging incoming. Underneath it. That's exactly what I wanted to do.
How many swings do you have? How many times does he swing? Oh boy. I'm out of dashes.
Oh, you're doing way too many of those in a row. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up.
No. What happened? What happened? I got hit by like a hundred missiles. What the hell?
I hit him. I wish the lock on circle was like red. Sometimes it's hard to tell if I'm even
locked on. Can I change that in the options? Can I change that? I wish I could make it red.
I don't know how you reliably dodge those. It's just a hundred million of them. That one didn't
count. Should I stay back from the missiles? Maybe? I don't know. They just spam. I guess
like maybe just go. No. How are you supposed to dodge that? Okay. Just assault boost pass.
Aren't they homing though? Yeah. They're like, they're like on me. All right. I had him. I had
him beat. I just got to get back on it. Let's go. Start over. Does that kind of work? It uses so
much. Look, and it's happening again. I don't have any more boost. No, I'm doing it my way.
I wonder if I can, can I just outrun it? Maybe.
I just hit every button on my, I hit Y, X, A, and V at the exact same time.
It's just so much happening. I feel like I'm in a crashing plane.
Is that anger? What? No, that was not anger. That was me making a joke. That was a joke. That was
like a, I did funny noises. That's not anger. That's funny sound effects. You cannot be angry
and make funny sound effects. That's not how it works. I got them down to like 1%. I'm going to,
okay. Time to be quiet. Let's go. This is the one right here. This is actually the one right now.
Watch this. What hit me? I'm so confused.
So intensify, Raiden. Get clear.
Here comes the swing.
Do that quick.
Oh my goodness. I can't believe I didn't get killed.
Oh my goodness. You gotta be kidding me. Oh, it's okay. I'm not even mad about it.
I can't believe it. I can't, I can't believe it. God dang it. Darn it. Oh, darn it. That's
a big darn it right there. That was one HP. That's such a huge darn it. That's, that is like a,
oh gosh, dang it. Oh, that sucks. I can't even, it's all right.
Hey, we're good. Let's go. I'll do it again. I'll do it again right now.
I'll do it again right now. Recharge, recharge, recharge, recharge. Why can't I recharge?
Oh, damn it. I have to restart.
Okay. Now I'm just, I, I, I, I need to do one hit. I can't believe it.
Okay.
Oh, get in there. What? That doesn't count.
Here we go. More of this bullshit. Good start. I can't believe I didn't hit that.
I wish I knew what happened there. I was locked on. It just didn't stay locked on.
That's a complaint. I lose. No, I'm complaining now. That's a, that's actually a complaint.
I didn't press the right stick. I didn't trip the lock on off. I'm complaining. It's over.
Yeah, this is a complaint. I wouldn't necessarily say I'm angry. I would say I'm complaining.
I'm going to put a, this weapon, uh, is, is ass against this enemy because yeah,
give me a different, how do I do it again? How do I, how do I put a different weapon on?
This bubble weapon is cool, but like, how are you ever going to attack somebody?
Like he just flies around the whole map and at the range is like medium range. I'm yeah, it's ass.
Hey, I not, I didn't get filtered yet. I had, the boss had one HP 10 minutes ago. Don't forget that.
I ain't getting, no, this is bullshit. You take one of those. It's half of your entire health pool.
My eyes are itching. Yeah, this, look at this. Okay. This bubble gun,
you can shoot it for like a one second before it overheats. This thing fucking stinks.
You go overheated. Oh my God. This thing sucks. Asshole.
Okay. Come on. Come on. Shit. That, how did that even hit me? I dodged it perfectly.
Still not good. I don't, I have like no health. All right. You know what? Kill me. Cause I,
I want to take this bubble gun off. One, two, you shoot this thing for two seconds and it overheats
in the middle of a giant fight where there's just shit screaming at you. And like missiles are
shooting you from every single direction from every angle. It's hard to look at that tiny
little bar to see if it's red. I'm sorry. It just is. Get this thing the fuck out of here.
Sell it. Oh shit. I don't have anything. Is this even better? All right. No more complaining. Let's
go. I'm trying to be so patient. There's just shit everywhere. Oh really?
That's unfortunate. I need to get more heels. Probably. I feel like that's holding me back
too. I already have one health. If you don't get to phase two without two, it's over. Okay. Let's
pull back. I hit that. There's always one little straggle rocket. That's like, so you do through
all this. And then it's like like that. Maybe you just, I'm just going to ski. I'm not even
going to attack like that. Just drive. Does this work? Kind of. Oh no, it does not. Oh no, it does
not. Okay. Good start. Very good start. Exceptional start. Oh shit. Okay. Ski, ski, ski. All right,
back up, back up, back up, back up. Not bad. Not bad. Here comes the swing. Yep. What hit me? What
hit me? What hit me? What hit me? I fucking lose. Oh no. Oh no. It's just got such an insane cone.
It's like, it's like, it's like 300 degrees in front of this motherfucker. Again, like another
2% boss fight. Give me a break. Be more aggressive. I feel like last time I've tried to be
aggressive. He just kills me in two hits. Here, do the little sneaky, like, go on, do it. Do your
little, there it is. Oh, you got it. I'm literally waiting for it. What the fuck is happening?
Oh my God. He just almost double tapped me in one second. Holy shit. I got way too aggressive.
What? Oh, already? That doesn't look like 50% to me. Holy shit. What? Where did, he just like
scooped me up in the middle of his mouth. Oh my God. I can't believe I almost beat this guy with
one health three times. You shoot behind you? Oh, come on. That's absolute fucking horse shit.
It really is. Back it up. No, you fucking idiot. Stop flying directly over my head.
Get away from my head. Get, get out of here. Go back to your corner. You're like, you're broken.
Dude. What? I couldn't jump. What? Why couldn't I jump? I was trying to jump.
He was like glued to the ground. What the hell happened? I, I was pressing A. How come I didn't
fly? Was I out of, was I out of juice? Damn it. Fuck you buddy. I got like just caught up. That
was so fucking stupid. He flew over me and I couldn't stay locked on. Come back when you're
level 80. You don't level up in this game, do you? I need to grind side quest. I mean, dude,
I have come one centimeter of his bar of health, like four times. I can do it. I just have to get
the last hit in and just kill the guy. We're doing this right now. Like, holy shit.
Give me a fucking break. Key, I'm literally keyboard turning in World of Warcraft.
Okay. We're good.
All right. Come on. This is the one right here. This is it. No more bullshit. I can't see anything.
All right. We're good. Oh, come on. That's just so stupid. You just, sometimes you're just in a
spot where you're going to get hit by that. Sometimes you just don't, you can't dodge anymore.
This is un-fucking-bearable. This is boss number three. What does boss number 17 look like? Holy
shit. Have any humans completed this game yet? All right. This is a good start.
Huh? What? Oh, I got staggered by something. All right. Pull it together.
Come on.
What? Why are you stopping? I did not tell you to stop. Why are you stopping moving?
Oh my god. I just got, my elbow was stuck on my chair. Hold on. I gotta move this. This is in
the way now. Okay. There we go. That's better. I have free movement of my arms now. I might be able
to do it. Oh, I'm out of juice. I'm out of juice. I need to build juice right now. No, dude. That's
the exact thing I didn't want to have happen. Oh boy. We're good. I win. I win. Okay. How did I
think I was ever going to get through that without complaining? I'm telling you, I put my, these
things down. That's better. Phase three. Don't even say that. That was hard. Let me just bite the
controller real quick. Cause you hear it? I was going like this. It was like gripping it like
480,000 credits. Wow. That's pretty sick. Is he going to rage at the spider boss?
Probably. I don't think we should do any more bets on that because it absolutely is happening,
but we're going to move on to a coin game. I want to play coin game for like an hour or two.
I got over the hump. I can come back to this if I want to.
You said you could hear a strange voice in your head. I can see why that boss is considered a
with the difficulty really turns on. That was fun. I like it. Do you like the game? Yeah.
All the From Software games do this shit. They make you go through every stage of grief,
question your reality, question, question everything. And then when you finally beat it,
you go, that wasn't even a big deal. That wasn't even a big deal. That was nothing.
It looks fun to be fair. I would say it's very fun. How red are you? Actually, not really.
You probably can take on anything after beating that guy. That's encouraging. Hey,
thanks guys. Sweat check. Uh, I don't, well, you can't, I can't do a sweat check.
There's nothing to check. Check the messages.
Only him and the next one are really hard actually, in my opinion. So wait,
this is not the case of like boss 15 is not insane. Boss three is very difficult. And then
is that, Oh, okay. It is. All right. I see. I see. There's one guy. All right.
Boss four is ridiculous. Boss 15 is insane. The other bosses aren't. Okay.
So it is what I was describing. So have you guys beaten this yet? I'm imagining
virtual encounters are now available in the arena. We invite you to hone your technique.
Yes. I have four times new mercenary data. Ooh, I unlocked new arena. Well, that's cool. I think
that's a good stopping point though. I am a fan. I will probably stream it again. Just not right now
because right now I want to play coin game. Coin game got an update a few months ago that I never
played. I don't think it's anything too substantial, but there's at least another
arcade, I think. So let's go check it out. If that's all you want to see for armored core,
maybe I'll play it again at some point. But if I can beat that, then I think I can handle most
of the rest of the game. So let's go play coin game. Actually, let me get, let me go pee. I'll
be right back. And I'll come back with coin game. How does that sound? Sounds good to me. Um,
all right. Be right back.