Hey everybody, welcome to Octodad. As you can see here, I'm gonna be playing this game Octodad.
It's a crazy quit play credits play quit play quit play options credits play quit play quay op ops and play
Did I say clay? Okay
Walk to the alarm clock. No problem. That's not a problem. You got a problem. Take it to the judge
Where's the alarm clock? I have no idea where I did well then though. That's like a box of chocolates
I think it's over here. All right, you like cross-legged weirdo. Don't pick up the friggin desk turn off the alarm clock
How the hell do I do that? Press the middle mouse button or space? Okay
Click got it. I I don't want to get out of here move
Move out of the way. How do I make how do I change this mode? Oh you press it again. Okay the phase
My god, my mother will be so upset with me
Alright, so what I know about this game is you're supposed to go do things supposed to go like
Like yell at your kids and like yell at your wife or something
I don't know, but you're not supposed to like people know that you're an octopus
I'm not sure how that's possible seeing as how I am an octopus in a suit
I don't know how this works, but get up there climb
Yeah, oh my goodness. Look at this. I'm a dainty little ballerina get up here. All right
We're gonna go in this room first because this room looks like okay, it has a to-do list on it
Oh, hi, honey. Welcome back from the store. You bitch get your hand up there
Slime your hand over here and turn the faucet off turn dip your dirty hands wash those dirty hands. There you go
All right, turn it up. What am I supposed to on press escape to view clear off the red counter put dishes
Okay, I gotta put the dishes in the sink. All right, where are the dishes?
All right, I'm gonna do this in one. I'm gonna do this in one fell swoop. You guys ready for this
This is how we do it in the big leagues. Oh
Like that, I missed it. I missed a couple things. Hold on. Hold on put your hand down here
It's just as easy as that
Done. Oh geez. Let me just tell you that I am just fabulous
Get this get it. Yeah
I did it. I did it. Oh my goodness
I did it. Oh my goodness. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. My leg is on the counter. I'm all kinds of crazy
Clean out the fridge mop the floor. I'm off the floor right now, honey. Pick it up
You're about to like have relations with an octopus. I don't know if you know this or not, but that's a little weird
Just do some scrubbing. That's all I got to do. Just you know, just do a little bit of scrubbing. What's left?
There's a some over there did it
Interpreted as cleaning
What else do I gotta do dishes in the sink? I don't know where the dishes are. Oh my god
She's like watching me. No, that's not that was a bug like a six-pack of dr. Pepper
I didn't mean to do that. This goes in here. Okay. This is a dirty dish get in there shit
I just knocked it off. Well, hopefully that wasn't your cup, honey. You know what fuck this
We're just gonna drag this whole damn counter in there like that. Just get in get in
Done right you like apples. Hey, honey. I got an apple for you teachers pet teachers
I'm trying to make a joke here game like like get me in like the right spot get over there you slug bastard
Get this in the sink. Yes
Thank you, honey, you're welcome
All right time to clean the fridge out. Let's just open this up right here. Yep. Let's just get this open right now
Fridge is now open. That's what I'm talking about. Let's just get in the fridge. You know what fuck this. Am I doing a good job?
Hold on. I want to see
You can't see me
Let me close myself in the fridge, come on no just turn around now
I'm stuck get just start smashing stuff. Just go go go go clean it out throw that in the air
I don't care about that at all. Just scoop it up with your tentacle hand
There we go. Perfect. Go straight in
This is not cleaning a fridge out. This is not that was a pizza that could have been slices in there
I could have eaten down the bottom. We got like a big gross cucumber get out of here
We got some bottles of I don't even know what those are, but that's it. I did it. I win
Give me a kiss
Freaking out
Oh
I would like that banana. Please give me the banana. Did I ever tell you you look so
Beautiful in this firelight, honey. Let me just get his hand over here. Let me just say go. Yeah, honey
I like you know, I really love you. Did I ever tell you that you look your hair looks so gorgeous like this
Is this a new hair dye? Thank you for the banana. You are such a sweetie. You dropped it. No, I did what?
Oh, okay. We're done. Good job. I'm glad you have an animation to tell me anything
You stone statue return to the dining room. Bye