Somebody said,
Hey, I want to talk to your manager.
You're three minutes late.
I am the manager.
What do you got to say?
Wait, the title is... Oh, the first...
I liked my title. It was
having fun farming.
Alright. That's all I need to say.
I got the tweet out already. I was prepared.
Hi, how are you?
How's it going?
Tonight's going to be a comfy night.
And you can tell that
because I've got a raspberry tea right here
and it's hot.
If I'm drinking hot tea,
it's guaranteed to be a comfortable night.
It's just the way it is.
Raspberry tea?
This bro's farming L's.
Yeah. It's alright though.
Is it hibiscus?
It's raspberry zinger.
It's the celestial brand.
It's good.
I think it's hibiscus, rose,
petals,
some other stuff.
It's good. It doesn't need anything.
Don't put sugar in it. Don't put anything in it.
It's just good. It just tastes good.
Raspberry zinger.
House Flipper came out
with an update, as you know.
Anytime House Flipper gets
a major, major update.
I am there day one
playing it. Hour number one.
This DLC released
two or three weeks ago.
So I missed it by a little bit.
But it's alright. We're good.
Are you going to make a Family Guy house again?
Well, build your own farm.
Fake fan.
Every time I restart
House Flipper,
I have to go through and get all
the tools and get money again.
Because I just delete everything.
I don't even sync it with the Steam Cloud.
I always say, make sure I do that.
And then something goes wrong and I just have to redo everything.
Yeah, the farming DLC
came out. Also, not just farming.
Apparently, you can
build your own house
from scratch now.
Before, that was a big,
one of the only cons
of House Flipper
was I thought that, oh,
I can't make a house
and put stuff in it.
Now apparently you can.
I know, it's called House Flipper.
That's not flipping houses. That's not flipping a house.
But still, I like,
I guess there's some more freedom now.
I don't know exactly how much, we'll find out.
It's just a fun time.
Yeah, that's the goal.
You guys ready?
You guys ready to hang out?
In this gigantic collective chat window?
While a 37-year-old
moron tries to
fucking build a house?
Alright, let's go!
I gotta give myself a little bit of credit.
I have like 120 IQ.
My performance IQ is like zero.
So, I'm not stupid.
Anyways, he's a genius.
I mean,
I mean, you said that. I didn't.
You said that.
But, blinking?
I guess so.
Thank you.
Alright, let's go. Yeah, you're gonna see.
I know, I start every single
time. I just want to check the audio.
This is not the color that I would want.
I just was testing
painting and everything again.
The DLC came out three days ago.
Alright, so we're good. I got time.
Why did you make the back rooms?
I just picked the first paint that I saw.
Alright, we're doing farming.
This is it right here. We did this one.
We did this one. I don't remember doing this
one, but I think we did. I don't know how eventful
this one was. Well, let's go.
Farm Flipper. It's a new map. Seems kinda
big. Alright, that's the one that's available.
Let's do that one. Where is Molly?
If you're looking for the perfect couple,
visit our Joe and Lily
Inseparable since childhood, happily married and
good ranchers too. And yes,
Sury, they're doing so
good, yet the locals don't know what this
morning Joe and Lily found.
Their barn damaged
and their favorite cow Molly was gone.
The couple might be able to handle one of these
issues, but two at once
is too much. Let's go. What do we have to go
find the cow? This is huge
drama. So what do I need to do?
Alright, let's go. There we are.
I'll take care of that.
That's easy.
The roof is gone.
Plane?
I got it. Don't worry. Where is
Molly?
This is just a Nancy Drew.
The Nancy Drew plot. Alright.
They got two. Wait.
There's a lot of stuff here. Could always just go on the
front door. Wait, I can't go in here.
Why am I not allowed in the house?
Oh, should I remove the drain pipe?
What are you doing over there
with the drain pipe?
I don't know. Just figured I would move
it. It's kind of an eyesore.
Oh look, I found a cow.
The game volume is a little low. I'll turn it
up. Keep it as a souvenir.
Alright, let me
go. Hold on.
Where is it? I don't think the music has to be that loud.
How's this? Better?
The problem with House Flipper is some
sounds just explode.
Just be careful. We have to test
something. Some of this stuff is
so loud. So I'd just
be aware that it's the mixing
on this game was one of those things that was always kind of
off. I'll take out the sledgehammer
and it'll just be
I'll hit a wall and an explosion
happens. Oh, also too.
The limited
items in the Grotto Beast store are
leaving tonight.
Just to make sure everyone's aware of that.
Tonight at 12
at 11.59 PM Pacific
tonight, the posters
the
yeah, all three posters are
leaving the store.
The glow in the dark ghost shirt
and hoodie.
The glow in the dark one. The
original 40 shirt also
is going to be gone.
Is that what he just said?
I thought he said
there's a store. Yeah.
Yes, there is.
But anyways, yes, Grotto
Beasts dot net. I feel so
bad. Like, wait, what do
you mean store? It's like, oh, shit, you don't know.
Well, it'll be there.
Yeah, you can keep that there for a little bit.
Okay, so let me let's clean
the fly noise. It was kind
of weird. This is one of my favorite parts
of the game. This is going to determine how loud it is, by the way.
That's not bad. Usually this
is pretty loud. It is loud.
Oh, well, it didn't look that loud.
All right, we're going to clean all this up.
But that's the task.
It doesn't need to look filled with water.
Where did I get that from?
Wait, you can have like farm
animals and stuff? What's your favorite?
Vinny just used your likeness
on the screen. That's all right.
Vinny has expressed written permission.
Don't worry.
Yeah, Vinny has expressed
written permission to use my likeness.
Play the Home Depot
song. No.
Some of this still looks...
Is that shit?
Why would I use this? Like use as in...
What do you mean use? Oh,
I... All right. What?
Am I eating it?
Where is it going?
I probably shouldn't do that.
All right. Place a fence and gate. Remove
trash. Milk container.
Okay. Still dirt everywhere.
How is this still dirt?
Are all the windows down here clean? All right.
I think it's clean now.
Wait, window. Looks pretty good.
All right. I need a fence
and gate. So this
is in this room. So clean the dirt. Clean
the window is the way. There's one more window.
Oh, there's still tons of shit over there.
All right. That's three.
Oh, it's dirty up here. What's
the best way to find Mithril in Terraria?
Just take what you just wrote
and paste it
into a
search engine.
Wait, what?
How's the performing DLC?
What are you doing? What?
Germa, you haven't tweeted about GrottoBeast
once. I've retweeted the GrottoBeast
account, though. That counts, isn't it?
That you're a fake fan.
This dude's farming L's.
Can I put this up? How do I make this...
Oh, rotate. There we go. Shift
and what? I don't think I can move this.
Oh, right here. I thought
my game crashed. Yeah. I mean, the thing
is, I don't really use
any social media, like, ever.
Besides here and sometimes in
the Discord, I just
log off, dude. I just log
off. I just log
the fuck off. All right. That's good.
Wait. This is
still dirty. All right. Milk container.
All right. This is an enclosure.
How does this work?
Like this? There's a gate.
All right. Cool. Zero
percent. You just put a baby
gate there. Wait a minute. Hold on.
It wants me to put second floor
and then in this room here.
All right. Well, it wants me to replace the tiles
here. I can handle that.
Oh, he's farming L's.
Weren't we going to start banning people that said that?
I always had the impression that we were going to start
banning people.
That's what it says in the title. Okay. Almost done.
Just the first person? Oh, well,
we can make this kind of funny, though.
So let's wait for someone
to say it. And I'm talking like
half hour from now when everyone isn't doing it
anymore.
Just like ban somebody and just talk about, hey,
I've been live for like 13,
14 hours. And you
just ruined the streak. Nobody
said it. And we were talking about how nobody said it.
Like, wait, what? No, wait, nobody.
Not everybody said that?
No, I've been streaming for like 14 hours.
Sorry, but you get
banned. Place a fence and a
gate. How did I not do
that? Didn't I do it?
You have to build on the...
Dude, I thought this was
already here. I thought this was
way too filled in. All right?
I'm sorry. This is
filled in. It needs to be
way more transparent than that.
This is a white fence.
I thought this was a white fence, guys.
I did...
All right. Whatever. I was like, this shit's
almost done. All right. Now he
is farming elves. Okay.
Someone needs to fill this dude's noggin.
That's so stupid.
I wanted to make a big gate.
All right, cool. That's done.
There's still dirt somewhere. That's
done. Okay, here we go.
Garage door. I want
to put it here so bad. I want to put
it right there. It's the poop,
dude. What the heck?
Dude, this... All right.
Isn't this supposed to be here?
No, that's supposed to be there.
Okay. I need six fluorescent
lights. Guys, I'm not trying to make
this that wonderful looking.
I'm just trying to do the mission so we can unlock
the farming stuff. Crumb of a retweet
would be cool. It's only sponsors.
I just don't
use Twitter.
Like, for anything.
When I open up Twitter to... I didn't even take
a sip out of my tea yet. No, I'll tweet
out a Grotto Beast thing. You know, one of the things, once
the commercial was out, that was sort of
like the, all right, let's go.
There will be a Grotto Beast
tweet tonight. There will be.
Maybe back here? How many do we need? One or two?
Two? Ooh, cool.
Walk through that gate?
I'm fine. I got it.
This is the kind of gate that hurts your hips
when you walk through it. This thing
scrapes bone when you walk
through this. You get wedged in
and... Ow! Okay.
My hips hurt. All right.
Some water?
Probably in here, right? How is a cow going to fit
through? We'll see. I'll fix it if I need to.
If I need to.
Somebody also...
In offline,
like free stream chat, offline chat
here, there'll be like, oh,
exclamation point, tweet.
And since, since
like the end of February, whatever
it was, it's been that Wild Hearts tweet.
It's been like two
straight months of Wild Hearts ad.
It's just been two months of an advertisement.
It's been there every single day.
Every single day
it's been there for like two or three
straight months. They're getting their
money's worth? Yeah.
That's so stupid. Fucking Twitter.
Every time I open up the Twitter app, I like
just blow the
dust off. I need milk containers.
Oh, sell
the milk container.
Where are they? Oh, is this a milk container?
No? What is
a milk container? Oh, okay. That's
what I wanted to get rid of. So there's a
milk container somewhere in here?
It's not these, is it?
No, I like placed these.
Where's these? What is two milk containers?
Oh, it's these.
I thought I was looking. Okay. I was like, what the hell
does it want me to look for? Next to the door.
Oh,
boy. We just got a raid
from Squeaks.
What's up, Squeaks? And what's up?
What do you call your
audience? The Squeak
Maniacs.
Thanks for the raid. We just started
playing some house flipper. Those of you that are
in this community that have not
followed Squeaks, stupid
behavior. No, Squeaks is
awesome. What do I have to do out here?
Oh, oh my
look, there's chickens.
What? What?
Follow me.
What? Hold on.
Can I have like just a bunch of chickens follow me
around and help me? How many can I have
at one time? Cool.
Did you see the coffee bit Squeaks
did on stream a few days? Yes, I did.
It's classic. Pour
something out as if you're pouring it
onto your desk, but it goes into another container.
And then you pour that container out.
Oh, unbelievably classic.
You left it open? Oh, shit, I did.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Everybody follow
No, no, I'll lose them. I'm not
ready for this, but I am ready for like in a couple hours
to have like 300. Like, I'm just
gonna have like a chicken army walk around with me.
I'm back in here. Okay.
Stop following me.
Can I give a treat? What is this?
Really? What could I do?
Minus one sunflower. Is it bad?
Grass is kind of tall in here.
You guys hungry? Okay, I gotta
make sure no one's following me. I don't want them to be stuck.
There were three following me. It was
these three, right? Alright, we're good.
That's cool. I'm gonna
blame that on somebody else. They want a
different window up here.
Can I break this? What did I just
do?
This might be loud. I'm warning you.
This is actually, this is probably gonna be loud. We need to test
and see. This is the loudest object in the whole game. Just be
aware of this. Is there, do I have a ladder?
Wait a minute.
Use tool grappling hook? Where's
a grappling hook? Grappling hook?
Flashlight, jump,
crouch, run. Grapple,
it's in the wheel? Oh, wait.
Wait a minute. Whoa, drone.
Oh my god. Okay.
Hold on. That's pretty cool. That's
new. That wasn't in the game before.
Alright, I'm warning you. This is loud.
I'm warning you. Please turn your volume down.
We need to test and see how loud it is.
And I knew it. I knew it was gonna be loud.
Okay, I need to upgrade
to
more faster demolition. I don't have any
of my old points, but it's alright.
Okay, so we need beds.
Get a couple of these.
Buckets, whatever.
Maybe these are dirty. Okay.
How am I gonna fit three of these?
Dude, get rid of the huge
pile of shit.
That's not just poop, isn't this?
I don't know why I was thinking of that. I didn't
finish my thought. There's another squeaks bit that was
really funny for all the
squeak maniacs that are here.
When he had the thing
transcribing him talking
and he muted his mic and just started
talking shit. And he was just
transcribing everything he said.
Pretty good. They're already gone.
Oh, well, whatever.
So why can't I place this?
Do I have to break all this first?
Yeah, see, it's like, oh, it needs to be bigger.
How do I replace this?
Sell it? Yes.
Loud. Incoming.
Oh, cool.
That's good. Look at this.
Look at how clean it is and look at how nice
it is.
Dude, it's 3am and we shouldn't be mowing.
Alright, I did it. Look at that.
So much cleaner.
All the lights are on the ground.
Oh, I
didn't do shit on the ceiling.
Uh, whoops, forgot that
was the thing I had to do.
Back home. You've received the
architect tool. Congratulations.
You've unlocked a new tool. From now on
you can build structures.
I've been playing this game for six, seven,
eight years. It's been a long time coming
for this. From now on you can build structures. Use
the architect tool and place the foundation
on the ground, then select its borders
and give it a desired shape. Okay.
Finally press the E key to erect the building.
New tool. To plot a field
select a hoe from the tools menu.
Choose a field with Q plus
that middle mouse button
and click on the ground. Okay.
House building. Paint
gun. What's the paint gun?
What? Okay.
Most of these tools are new.
Just go back here. Okay. Paint gun.
Alright. Change size.
Well, this is way faster.
That's so much faster.
Okay, cool. What about the drone?
Alright, where am I? Am I the drone?
Can I fly the drone in the house?
You can. Okay, that's weird.
What happened? What the fuck?
That thing's a cheap piece of shit.
That thing's a piece of shit. Alright, what's the next
mission? 89 missions
to do on Happy Ranch.
Huh? Wait, I can just buy one?
Wait, what do you mean I can buy a
cow? Why?
I'm just looking out and there
is a cow here. Okay.
Well, follow me because you should probably be in the...
Oh, this is a bad idea. Can I make a
bed? I need to make a cow bed.
Can you fit in here? Wait, goats?
Pigs? Horses? Sheep?
They have different personalities.
Alright, if I have like
three alpacas, four cows,
and like two goats,
the neighborhood is going to...
Oh my god. Okay, we're good.
Okay, we need a spot for you.
This is not big enough. You need a way
bigger space than this. No, fuck my
bed. I don't care. We'll get...
You need more room. No, fuck this.
Loud incoming. Oh, I can't...
Hold on. 500 bucks?
How do I... It's $3,000.
I'm working on it. I'm trying.
Hold on, you gotta get out of the way.
You can't go this way. You have to wait.
This is like wet concrete. Watch out.
I got a new skill. Design interior
walls, yes. Okay.
Building modification.
Oh, that is so cute.
Alright, come on out. Edit inner...
Select two... Press and select
two points to edit inner walls.
Points? I guess that...
How do I... Because I can move the edges,
but how do I carve off internal...
I guess. Alright, well we're both in here now.
Click and drag. I tried that. It didn't work.
I can't break it. Okay. Building
modification. Okay, now...
So I want to do this. Ah, alright.
There we go. Okay, okay. I get it.
This is the... This is where you can come in.
And you'll have a little spot.
Alright, good. Let's make a door.
Alright, this is going to be...
I need a door. Yeah, like a garage door.
Got to be big enough. You're okay?
It's like a car
garage. I know, but it'll...
You put a cow
in your garage. Dude, just wait.
Rome wasn't built in a day.
Took Rome at least a few months.
Alright, what else do you need as an animal?
Pantry? Animal products.
Everything. Okay, what do
cows eat? Hey, right?
Cows eat carrots? Cows eat carrots?
It is Otto.
In case you get hungry, there's a carrot snack
right there. This needs to be much bigger.
It's going to be way more comfortable than this.
Yeah, this is not... I don't like it
either. Uh-uh. Alright,
that's better. Okay, E.
E. I need like barn outdoor.
Okay, walls.
Wall panels, right?
It needs to be kind of like
like a barn. Like this?
Like wood? Like one of these? These
look okay. That'll be nice. Like red.
It's going to take a lot to do this because
my skill point is literally zero. Change
size? Oh, I can't. You need
one acre per cow.
I want to open windows and stuff. No,
it's not going to be a concrete room.
I have to finish the inside
first. No, you know what? I need to do my
missions, first of all. I've...
What? How?
What? Oh my goodness. This milk?
Alright, I... Hey.
Um, I wasn't ready.
Needs. No needs right now.
Alright, I need to put like hay down or something.
No shot the HOA will allow this.
Is this shit? There's no way.
Alright. Okay, I need to...
I'm going to move you to the animal hotel.
I can't take care of a cow right now.
Look, I got all this shit to do.
Are you going to go to a farm where you can be
taking care of properly? Horses?
You sell? I didn't sell. I did not sell.
The cow went to the
um, like the animal, like
farm hotel thing. I think I can go back
and get that cow later.
Do I have to actually
get horses here?
How does this work?
Oh, okay.
Oh shit, it's going to roll into the...
Somebody's... Whoa! There it goes.
I actually just took out... That would have been bad.
Just...
Okay, wait. How many do you want me to take down?
Cut down tree... Oh, these...
Wait. Where are the... Where are the ones
you must cut down? Oh,
oops. Sorry about that. I want to try to use
the axe too. How does the axe work?
No, we just only use chainsaw.
Alright, put this down. Alright, lay foundation.
So you want me to put down a foundation
here. I need to build
a stable. Okay.
Let's go.
Alright, done? Cool. So now...
Oh, I'm so glad there's a guide.
Alright, so now we need to make a stable.
Knee, knee horse
box gate. You want the gray
tile? Okay. Do this first.
You should do this IRL.
I just want to make sure you understand that.
Like, I don't...
I would probably get seriously injured.
You want me to build a house?
Like, build this?
Huh? Yeah.
Okay, that looks good.
Somebody said caveman. I could make some caveman
level stuff, but not like this.
You need skill training
and safety.
Okay, so I need to get this.
This interior has got to be way better
than this. Three of these?
Is that not counting it? Why is it only counting
one? I don't think I can make it perfect.
Zero out of four?
Wait, why did it...what?
Alright, this is not
a me problem. I can't
get it perfect. Put the pillars first.
Try that.
Alright, that counted.
Jeremy, your problem solving skills suck.
This was one out of four.
I picked it up and put it down in the same spot
and it went to zero out of four.
The instructions were incorrect.
There we go. That's a dad excuse.
The instructions
were not correct. It's really not
hard. No, it's not.
I just did it. It's
kind of finicky. How come I wasn't doing this
too...okay, so the pillars definitely had to be
here. Because it would not let me go
in this exact spot before.
Before it was like I could only place it like here.
Am I missing tiles somewhere?
Oh, come on. Okay.
So this thing is
for here.
Oh, that was a lag spike. Wait, what does it want this?
Half box wall.
Wait, let me do that first.
Oh, please. Change
the music. This is the music in the game.
And this thing goes hard.
I'm keeping it on. No, we can't replace
every soundtrack with Doom
OST. Alright, so these are the
windows. Horse mats.
Okay. Four of these, right? Okay.
So what now?
Two of these go here. No.
Smash. I'm starting to understand
it. I think I can make my own farm.
Looks pretty clean. Where's
the door? I'll worry about that later.
Look, there's a door. Oh, that's
not a door. That's a giant
window. Where is the door?
Wait, where's the door? I need a
door. Sliding gate.
Hey, we're good.
Now, ceiling lamp.
Empty shelf with horse care equipment.
I don't know, put it like right here. How many
horse feeders for? This looks like
my high school?
What?
What are you talking about? Are you
a horse?
This looks just like my high
school. Alright, that looks good.
I'm starting to get it. So
it's a Minecraft house. Somebody
came into this universe with the Minecraft tools.
My game got
hacked by some like Minecraft player.
And they're just building in my game.
Okay. So now
I want us to see the
just in case we get introduced into the
gameplay mechanic.
Um, I think I'm going to buy it.
I got money. Let's buy the new house.
Cabin in the woods.
A remote getaway in the heart of the mountains.
An easy sell. Just needs a little love to
become the site of a joyful family gathering
once again. Or anything else you'd like it to be.
I'm buying it. Let's check it out.
This is the new house in the update.
This place is very dirty. Garden
con- oh, that's right. Alright.
It's time for the game to begin. What do I
got for- ooh. What do I got for
space in this lot? First thing is first.
Yeah, we'll change the music. Yeah.
I didn't want to hear it another time. Uh.
Hey, how's Doom
OST sound?
No, something else. Something else.
Something else. Ooh, it's raining.
Ooh, this is going to be so fucking
relaxing. I can't wait.
Stardew Valley music? That's not a bad
thing to put on. Stardew
OST. Yeah, it's like just
so, it's just so nice.
How's that? Good? I want to be
nice and in the background.
Okay. I'm going to plant my own trees,
I think. Can you?
Alright. Well, that's fine. First,
most important thing, we've
got to clean this up. This
yaw has got to be a grass
cut.
Stardew music
in the background.
I feel like I'm going to mess something up if I do it that
way. I'm going to turn these sounds down
just a little bit. Lawn mowing
simulator. Oh, I still want to change the auto
saving. How do I do that?
Click save. Three minutes. Yeah.
Like 30, 15
is good. Every three minutes
is a lot. Okay, here we go.
Ah, this is what I'm talking about.
This way we can get
rid of all the weeds. I should get some upgrades
for doing this. You like firehouse
subs? Yeah. Firehouse
is good. I've had it a few times before.
Let me move this back here.
I got a big lot. It's going to take me a minute.
Look at those mountains. It already looks
10 times better. Okay.
It's burnt? It is burnt.
Oh, no.
Yeah, it is burnt. Can I restart?
Yeah, it's all burnt up. Will that get
fixed, I think? I can plant some stuff there.
I'll make that. We'll turn
that into like some kind of pen or something.
Yeah, what does it replant? It's fine.
Can you make a koi pond?
Try. Where are the pigs? Hurry up and
spawn them in. Patience.
Yeah, usually I'm the one without the patience.
We need to prepare our pen.
We can make sure our animals are taken very good
care of. All right, that's good enough
enough. I want to see the- what's the damage
in the interior?
Oof. Oh, dear.
Oh, boy. All right, we're working
from top- we're working
top down. Looks good.
What is all this? Oh, no. Get rid of this.
Now, what if all the animals
lived in the house and I lived in the barn?
Like, they live in the house.
That's just an 80s comedy.
Yeah, that's all right. Yeah, I want
I want the pig to have an office.
What's going on with this thing?
Junk. Get rid of it. Junk. Junk.
This one's pretty good. It's kind
of dreary in here. Whose room is this
going to be? By the way, we can get
Whose room is this going to be? Should be the pig's
room? Who would want a good view like this?
A goat? All right, so this is going to be a goat
room. What do you think we'll paint?
Let's start from the bottom. Floor. Carpet?
Can we put grass up here? It kind of looks like
grass. Nah.
Farming. Whoa!
It really is Stardew.
All right, where do I want my, what am I growing?
Right here. All right, I want to make
a bunch of sunflowers.
So I need to, what was it? It was a
certain tool, right? Yep, here it is.
Corn's going to go here. No, sunflower will go
here. Make a corn maze.
All right, I'll do that in the backyard.
That's a good idea. I like that. Yeah,
I'll make like a tower defense
pathing thing over there.
You have to walk through and then go
this way and then there's a huge tower defense maze.
But first of all, sunflower seeds.
So where do I put them?
Is that it? Do I have to water them too?
Plants versus zombies map?
Yeah, I could do two rows of sunflowers
and then just, that's a good idea too.
All right, so if that's the sunflowers
then what would go right in front of it?
Pumpkins, carrots.
I think this is it. We've got tomatoes,
pumpkins, potatoes, corn
and carrots. Tomatoes, right?
Corn makes, we're doing a plants versus zombies
thing. This is in the game. What just happened?
Did I just plant corn here? Okay.
Let's have it come out a little bit further.
I also have to put a bunch of bad placement
because when I played plants versus zombies it was terrible
placement so we're going to have like two or three
pumpkins and then two or three corns and then
yeah, we'll make sure it's accurate. What happens
if you torch it all? Then it all goes away?
I don't want to do that. Got one row corn,
two rows sunflowers.
Does anything look like a walnut? Probably
the pumpkin I would imagine.
There's a zombie
in my lawn.
There's a zombie.
Walnut, walnut down here
and then we'll put
a couple more
we'll do a couple more corns like just kind of scattered
in a row like right here.
We'll see how that turns out. I just want
to see what it did.
We're thinking way too, hold on
I need to water this stuff. Maybe you don't.
Hey, it's a process.
We didn't get right to the
Best Buy. We didn't get right to
the mall a few years
ago. The process is we get
we will
we, we, we
I want all new stuff.
Now you bet your ass there's going to be a
like four by foot
four by five whatever foot
square footed, square pool.
I want a square pool.
I don't know is it five by five? Is it
eight by eight? How big is it?
Wait, getting ahead of myself. Four by five
is fine for you. Permanently ban that
person for an hour and then reduce
their sentence by 55 minutes and leave
them a stern message. All right, let's start
with doing one room at a time and
let me tell you I don't like that at all.
I don't like that at all and I don't like that
light. So if this was if I'm coming up the
stairs here I would probably say this
is a
could be like an office or something or could be
a bedroom. Floor is important. What do I want
on the floor up here? There are beehives.
Do I have to do anything with them?
Is there any like special interactions?
This might just be aesthetic.
I don't think it actually does anything.
Okay, one thing at a time. Let's go
to floors.
We'll just do wood. Doesn't matter.
I don't like wood floors though.
I really don't. Too much to upkeep.
You can fuck them up. You can scratch them up.
I don't like it. Green tiles are fine.
I don't mind this.
What does this look like? It's not a farmhouse
without wood. That's true.
I need some light in here. Something really basic.
Eater. There it is.
No, there it is. That's the exact
one that I want. Yeah, that is
exactly the one.
And I want this shit to be teal.
Yup. There it is.
Oh my goodness. Yes.
Where can I put this? I don't care
if my whole house looks like this.
As long as I got my square pool.
That's all I care about. Does it have to be
in the yard? I think it has to be outside.
Not enough room. It's not enough
room. Yeah, it said it. How come I can't
put it in there? There's plenty of room.
Look at all the room right here. How come I can't
It doesn't have to go up against a wall.
There's plenty of space here. Because it's on
the second floor. So, what? I can't
have a second floor square pool? Bullshit.
Let's pick all this up. I might just
put it in the kitchen. Wait a minute. This is not even my house.
We're doing the
switching. We're switching around here. The animals
are gonna live in here. We just gotta clear everything first.
Get a good look at exactly how
the whole thing is set up. Okay.
Clean up. I do work at a hotel
and the pool is on the 10th floor.
Yeah, that's also a hotel though. Alright.
Now, just clean up first.
I keep getting distracted and that's
gonna stop. Just clean up. I can't wait to see the
before and after after this one. It's gonna be so awesome.
Open. What's in there? This place
is kind of like gross.
I aired out a little. I want some more cleaning points.
This map is kind of low
on the list here. Where's this
dirt? See the minimap? Oh, right there.
Clean. On to the next room.
Beetle update? I have not gotten them yet.
I do want to get them. That's probably
a summer thing. I don't
think death feigning
blue death feigning beetles, I believe.
That's more soon
than it is the cold months. You think you'd still be
the house flipper guy if you weren't
me? Well, I don't know. I
wouldn't be me. So, I don't know.
Probably not. Have you seen the new Zelda trailer?
No, I'm not allowed to see the new Zelda
trailer until I finish my homework. Yeah, I need to finish
Breath of the Wild. There might be spoilers in there.
Alright, have we done all the interior rooms besides
the hallway? On the bottom floor at least.
You are never gonna finish Breath of
the Wild. How can you be so sure? I gotta pick up
individual playing cards.
Ugh. Take out the flame? You can't use a
flamethrower. Oh, wait, you can. Well,
I feel like the guy in the neighborhood that is going
way too far on Halloween. No, no.
You don't understand. Every window has to
have demon fire come out of it.
Every ten minutes. It's gotta
be on a fifteen minute timer. Well,
that was much easier. I kinda feel
bad that I can... I feel like this is
cheating. I'm cheating right now. This is
cheating. Where is this spot? How
have I not cleaned it yet? Where is it? I have
no idea where this is. It's apparently in here.
I don't think it's outside. Where is it?
It's a mug on the floor.
I think that's plumbing. Yeah, that's just plumbing
for the toilet. But I don't know if this is gonna be the bathroom
so I don't know. Maybe it's not. Maybe it's
over here. Really? Upstairs?
Where do you hide your weed stash?
Um, well, if you're
over twenty-one, marijuana is
illegal in Las Vegas. I mean,
hide it. Aren't you nineteen?
Get out of here. I'm gonna gas.
Alright, let's start taking some walls down.
Fix the fuse box. Fixed.
I have points to put in. What am I doing? Alright.
Faster. Let's do that.
More demolition. More strength.
And job requirements. Sound pretty good.
Ooh! Look!
It's going to start. Cleanup's going pretty
well. There's one issue there.
This is clean. This is clean.
Yeah, I got the Stardew Valley soundtrack playing in the
background to make it extra comfortable.
I think this is permanent. Yeah, it is.
Who puked up that high on the wall?
You have to stand up here
and aim this way to
puke up at the ceiling. We're going to get all new bathroom
stuff anyways. Yeah, we're
going to do that. Remove the whole
bathroom? I might once everything's clean.
Design does not happen until everything is
clean. So all the HGTV
Andes can hold on
a second. There's dirt up here. Okay,
this is kind of cool. Where is it?
I got it. Okay, thank goodness.
Where? Okay, it's the
painting frames. One more? Where
is it? Yes, thank goodness. All right,
we're good. Yeah, the grappling hook was added
three days ago. Changing this.
I might just remove this and we'll put something
else in. Yeah, I want a different staircase than that.
Okay, we build our
own rooms. Hey, my birthday
is 420. Can you get faded
and play back rooms on Roblox?
Uh, I don't
think so. There we go.
Much better. I might even take this wall down
too and just have a bathroom.
We'll see. You promised.
I didn't promise a 420 stream. No,
on 420, I'm going to be sitting
on my own couch watching old
Fraggle Rock episodes. I'm
going to be very busy. I'm going to be incredibly
busy. You're going to do that without us?
All right, stairs.
I want it so bad right now.
We need a way to go up and down.
Hmm. How are animals
going to use this? They're just not
on pivoting. The bottom floor is where
the animals live and the top floor is where
I live. And it's just going to be made out of gold
ladder. Yeah, I want there to be as much
real estate as possible to put other stuff.
Stairwell takes actually a very
large amount of space. That's the worst
possible place. Wait, where's the front door?
Where's the door? How do I get out of here?
How do I get out of this house?
Oh, okay. Uh-uh. I don't like this.
No, front door is right here. Yeah,
front door is right here. There. Because the bottom
floor is going to be the barn. Yeah, the upstairs
is going to be where I live. But there's going
to be, I'm sorry, but dad gets
to have one room down here. And I'll make,
I'll section it off right now. Garage?
I think that's fair. I had a dad room
before though. This needs to go over here.
This is, I'm claiming this is mine.
Either this one or this one. I like this one.
Get the color, right? Yeah.
I have no idea how to fucking swim.
I probably should remove this. I can
stand in here.
I'm happy. I don't even need to play the game anymore. I'm done.
This room is going to be immaculate.
Just wait. Check this out.
I'm going to get pool lights all over
here. Hmm. All right.
What should I, I want like lighting, like
really nice lighting. What do you think?
Tile? That nice kind of
clean tile look on the walls? Of course.
Oh yeah, of course. Roulette table?
Okay. Oh yeah, this is perfect. I'll put
that somewhere else in a minute. Wait,
I gotta make a casino? All right. This is
going to be a farm and a casino at the same time.
That's so stupid. All right. Don't
get distracted. So bathroom.
What should it be? What should the colors be?
Just like a light blue? Green?
These are pretty default, but they look
good. Marble? Marble sounds good.
This looks kind of good. Wait a minute.
Look at this. Let me see what it looks like. That's
pretty sharp. What about the floor?
That's a good floor. Make the floor?
That's a great comment. Bro, you just
made a baptism room.
No. This is
my personal sanctuary.
It's a barn, a church,
and a casino. Oh man.
I don't think
I don't think you can get permits to have a casino
and a church in the same space.
I don't think that's how it works.
I think there'd be quite a few people that would have things to say about that.
I would imagine.
Baptism chamber.
Everyone's saying fix the tub.
Hold on. I can't.
I think it's like this permanently. Unless I sell
it. Well, that's definitely the walls for sure.
I actually really like it. The outlet?
Yeah, this is a little
fucked up, but it's all right. Everything's going to be fine.
Nice. This is a saw death trap.
It's not done. If
you were constructing a house and somebody walked over and saw
the frame and went,
Hey, are you making a saw death trap?
The house is not done.
How are the sunflowers doing? Good
question. Ooh, pretty nicely
it seems. Pumpkins are not done.
I just got a bunch of corn. Oh.
I wonder, do I feed this to animals?
I would imagine. Plus six corn.
That's kind of cool.
Animals provide 50% more produce.
50% increased growth rate of crops.
Which one of these is better? Probably this one.
No, I probably won't do it.
Oh, it's done. Pumpkin?
Maybe animals provide more produce?
Whoa. I'm
harvesting all the sunflowers. I probably
make animal food. Seems pretty good.
All right. Back to what we were doing. It'd be so
funny if you could play. We gotta get a better door than
this. This thing sucks. All right.
I'm walking in. I want misters.
I want kind of scented
misters to be spraying
at an angle here and here.
Right at the door. I want to get coated
by like a nice gentle mist.
Some kind of fragrance.
Then I want to be able to sit down here and just
sit, inhale and exhale.
Let me do this. Carbon monoxide.
And by the way, I don't
want a window in here. This is for
me to come in, sit down
with some nice lights.
You're gonna get CO2?
I'm gonna be, what? I'll put a vent.
See?
That's not enough.
See? I'll be fine. I've got a vent.
It's not an interrogation room.
What interrogation room has
marbled blue
like pool walls?
What are you talking about?
I've never seen an interrogation room
on any television shows or any movie
that took place inside of an indoor
pool facility. All right. Move this.
Gotta get my towel in the right spot. See?
We're safe. I don't hate that
light. There. Are you happy?
There. Are you happy now?
No. I am not making
the SpongeBob kitchen.
It might look identical
right now, but I can assure
you this is not the SpongeBob kitchen.
But now I feel like it kind of has to be.
But what about my sanctuary?
But what about my
sanctuary? Oh my
god. Damn it.
Okay. Fine. Fine.
I'm making a second room where my
sanctuary is going. There's like two barrels.
Where's the door? So the door
needs to be here, right?
So let's say the window is here.
So the door would need to be here. That's
fine. Let's operate on the door being right
here. So the door is there. The fridge.
Where's the wall? No, the
door would need to be right here, but I can't do it like
that. Because if this was the window,
I guess that would make sense.
Then I need a little table right here.
It's blue, right? Everything,
almost everything in this room is blue. Does this
work? It's white. Put on
SpongeBob music? Okay, the oven is
blue. It's like a flat top.
I wonder if they have them in this game. Oh,
no. I can make this blue
though. I think this is close enough.
Is it a flat top or is it a
stove, right? Would it be like oven?
Like grill? Yeah, all they have are these.
This might do it.
Not quite. I think
it's honestly this one. Or one of the ovens.
I mean, it's this.
It just needs to be. Okay, we can't make it blue.
This is perfect. Top is like
a dark blue. How do I
do the top? Okay. Top
is like that. And then it's kind
of gray. Not that gray. I
think it's good like this. So where's the fridge?
Alright, now we need the hole here.
It's just kind of an open square.
Oh my god. They actually have
it. Not enough space on the wall.
Oh, it has to be exterior.
Shit. They might all have to be exterior.
Might be able to get away with it with something else.
Hold on. I don't know, like opening
or... It might be something weird.
Walls. Now it would be
glass walls?
Damn it. It has to be exterior. Yeah,
it's got to be exterior.
We might be out of luck here.
Half wall is okay. Just
do a drive-through episode.
As long as we don't touch anything, that
is accurate. So I need
to put a... Hold on, let me fix this.
Do half walls. Yeah.
Squidward would hate this.
Yes, he would.
What kind of... It's like a submarine
door, right? I'll put on SpongeBob
music. That sounds fun. SpongeBob
OST. An hour
of relaxing SpongeBob music.
Sounds perfect. Alright, the door
is... It's an open doorway,
right? Does it close? It's kind of like
a big arch.
I mean, if that was a little
lower tech, it would be perfect.
This one looks good. Turn the music up.
There you go. Do the vault door?
That might be something better. Hold on.
That actually might be the closest thing.
Yeah, whatever. Sounds good.
Maybe we can stick with the blue. Ah, Squidward!
So where's the fridge?
We're gonna fix this. Okay,
I can't hear anything. My building is
so slow. Your SpongeBob
impression sounds like Squidward trying
to do a SpongeBob impression. Thanks
for the compliment. Alright, we're gonna retile.
The floor is already done, but it needs to
be a little bit lighter wood. I like that bubble
sound. It looks like this one
here. Other way. Okay.
Thank God he's making
the crusty crab. Well, this is just
one room of the house.
What were the tiles they called?
Where were they?
There. Beautiful.
This stream is a vibe right now. Yeah.
I'm glad. I'm just
chilling out.
I feel pretty good. Alright.
So I need my sanctuary row.
I can't even say that word. Sanctuary.
Sanctuary.
Kind of ugly, but I can't fix it.
Alright. Can I get another picture
of the room? So the fridge.
Okay, so there's a door.
Alright, so if that's where the door is.
There's another door
here. Are there two doors?
There's a gas. There's another range
right here. There's another gas stove.
This one is beige.
It's like beige.
It's a little too bright.
So there's the window.
Okay, the fridge is right here.
It's one of those double door fridges.
And it's all blue.
It's kind of like this.
What? Two of these. Is it wider?
I can't make this blue.
Here we go. Kind of purple.
Okay.
And there's a bunch of, there's like a condiments table.
It almost, it looks like a little
wardrobe. Like a little bureau.
Whoa, this is way better.
This is a thousand times better. The fridge.
Okay. I need a low,
like one of these. This might be fine.
It's probably a lower one. Pretty good.
I'd like it to be wider.
Almost there.
It was lower. It needed to be lower, lower, lower.
I think that's fine.
This works. Can't make it blue though.
And there's condiments all over this.
Ooh.
What was that thing?
You can actually do a koi pond.
It was a thing that was hanging on the wall.
And it looks just like this image here.
It was a bunch of utensils and tools.
And they just look just like this thing.
I can't find it.
Here it is. Where?
Oh, yep. Here it is. Okay, cool.
This doesn't match, but it looks good enough.
Good enough.
It's kind of coming together. What's in this corner?
These are all horse tools.
Yeah, but it looks fine.
You need the door to Mr.
Crab's office.
So this is going to have to be Mr. Crab's office.
No, I'm not making the whole
Krusty Krab.
I'm not making the entire...
What about my farm church casino?
I have to make the whole
Krusty Krab restaurant?
It would take me two weeks to do that.
What about my pool?
Alright, so let me...
Okay, okay, okay. So this is to the kitchen.
The other door
is here.
It's not though. It's different in every
episode. I feel like the doors
in this room are different in every
other season. Alright, I'll make the whole
Krusty Krab. Fine. Fine.
You don't think I will?
You don't think I'll make the whole entire Krusty Krab?
Down to the last...
Touch. Down to the last...
Like buffing out the last scratch.
No, I'm not doing that.
Let me at least finish this room. Why is it so
loud? Okay.
Door here.
Door over here.
So this stuff is actually a little bit more
to the right. Is the door
here? Where does this door go?
So this is Mr. Crab's office
over here. Is he enough?
How big is Mr. Crab's office?
It's pretty small, right?
Isn't it just a desk?
There's a desk right there. It kind of is
this size. Turn the light on.
Okay. This is a
load-bearing wall so I can't get rid of it.
Here's a Krusty Krab map
you can look at. No, I can't play
that. I'm just going to look up
Krusty Krab office.
Oh, this is a good... Okay, here we go.
I can do this. So it really
is just a big desk.
It's kind of like a big... Is it like a treasure chest?
Like a suitcase? I think like a
toy chest will work.
A toy box. What about just like a box?
Huh? This dude's 40?
Not yet. Trunk?
Oh. Hmm.
Chest. I'm surprised I don't have one.
Turn this up. SpongeBob is only
four adults. I want some water.
I'll come back and we'll continue.
I'll be right back. See?
I'm back. Christmas music?
Yeah, you should probably change the title to
Making the Krusty... Yeah, somebody said it. Making the Krusty Krab
because chat pressured me to do it.
And then... And then dash?
I want out. Yeah, there's got to be like
a dash. I want out.
Alright, let's go. Well, let me get the stuff that I know.
I don't think I'll be able to find the exact
thing, but a wardrobe should
do it. One of the short,
wide... They definitely have it.
Really? It might just
have to be this big wooden box.
Okay.
Now, it's like a big throne, isn't it?
It's a very large
chair. Where is it? They definitely have a
version of it. That's pretty good.
Oh, and make sure you stay to the end of the stream
because I'm going to do a full
all-in SpongeBob SquarePants
laugh. You're not going to want to miss it.
Stay tuned. Yeah, that one's fine.
Gold, right? You can't see it.
Well, it's going to have to
do for now. These other two chairs are going to
have to be these. I saw them earlier. They're
kind of thicker here.
Because they're kind of hollowed out
barrels. I wish I could just go back.
Can I just go back? I'm missing that button or something.
There's no window.
There's another door? Where's the other door go?
It's wood on the walls.
We've got to get the aesthetic right.
Are they horizontal or vertical lines? Looks like they're
vertical. Kind of like this.
Yeah, I like that. The lines are vertical.
I'm looking at a reference image right now.
Wrong way. Fake fan.
Oh, this is the door
that we're seeing here.
Which means this has to be turned this way.
Alright, I'll do that in a second. What does that even mean?
So that back wall is metal.
Such a fake fan.
No, I'm sorry guys. I don't remember the
blueprints of the Krusty
Krab. Literally L.
What? Why? I don't know the
blueprints of the Krusty Krab.
Now I need a metal.
Like a steel. Okay.
Close. You are killing
my childhood right now. It's not even close.
I've seen a few things that
could work.
I'll try the one I was going to do. It's this one
down here. Oh shit, it's a double.
Shit, this is a double too. I don't want a double.
I need to see what it looks like.
This is not my final decision here.
That's better, right? I think that's
accurate. So this is Mr. Krab's office.
We can go and mess around with this
later. Very important.
How the hell does this
work?
Because this comes out to the restaurant.
And then Squidward's
station is right here.
And it's a big boat. I doubt we'll be able
to do that though.
It looks like a boat.
Can you do a Squidward laugh?
Why are there so many weapons?
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
How am I going to make Squidward's
cashier station?
It's a boat. How am I going to make a boat?
It's going to be some type of
furniture. Wait, what about a big pet bed?
That might work.
Sort of boat-like.
The race car bed could work.
Wait a minute. This is pretty damn
close. I wish I could change the color.
I wish I could make it bigger. Oh, I could do a bathtub.
Yeah, that's true. What color is it?
I need a fixture
first. Alright, let me get the back wall.
The back wall is kind of like a blue
and green and pink
and it's kind of a lot of different colors, but I don't think
I can do it. So we're going to have to just do
the best I can here. Just make it
kind of industrial. I could
paint it. Oh, it's a boat.
I think the bathtub will be fine.
Should we just use the ones we were using before?
These kind of work. I think this is actually
perfect. Alright, let's spend like
a hundred thousand dollars on this
because it's going to be almost the entire floor here.
Alright, before we do anything,
this is all open.
And there's a bunch of tables.
What happened to the farm animals?
I got bullied into
making Krusty Krab.
No, I wanted to make it.
I'm kidding. That's the nature
of House Flipper. You go in with a
design and then you do
something completely different and you don't
even start on the thing that you wanted to do.
I might get halfway
through the Krusty Krab and this might turn into a different
place. Alright, so this
is...
I'm thinking about pulling this whole
wall forward, having it be across
this way. Yeah, the whole thing has to come forward
because that will give a lot more room for the
other... Yeah, this place
can really breathe. Can you upgrade
swing speed? I can upgrade
the hammer, which I'll do that now.
So the hammer's better. Yeah, that's much better.
Can we get a plankton voice?
You want me to do plankton?
SpongeBob?
I don't know if...
That was a little deeper maybe.
Don't crash my
stream's joke economy right now.
That wasn't that bad?
Why was that that bad?
That was Mitch McConnell's voice?
SpongeBob?
You're right. Yep, that's true.
Pull this forward. I don't need to get into there
from here. No, I don't. I'll seal it up later.
You went from 2100
to 1790 with that one. That's
not fair. That's not fair.
That's not fair.
Why can't I move this? Alright,
so the door to get in is
here. No, where
is it? It's right here. Right there.
One more.
Your stock just went down. That's
fine. Hey, I pay out
comedy dividends. That means every
every few months I read you out
my draft tweets and there are always
bangers.
You find me a draft tweet that you didn't like
and I will
agree or disagree with you.
It's really that big? Why is this
so huge? This is
massive. Am I
crazy or something? Why is this still
not big enough?
Come on, dude. Really?
Which is better? This or Papa's freezer
ria? This is much better. I love
Papa's freezer ria
but how slippery is it in my top
25 games of all time?
Alright, do a little bit
more cleaning up. I need a wall.
Oh, damn it.
What is it? What is it?
What is this? What is going on here?
What is this? What the hell is this?
What is this weird paneling
behind this? Okay.
I can stay there for now.
Still, okay, that's much better.
I might want to move this over a little bit.
It's not quite all the way flush.
Say my leg. My leg.
My leg. Ow.
Did I get the part?
Now I can bring this wall forward.
I'd love to pick this up. I can't pick it up
anymore. That's a problem for like
this problem next weekend.
I want, yeah, speed for sure.
Alright, I just keep making adjustments.
Okay.
Go like this. Much better.
Okay, let's just get
this over with. Front door of the
Krusty Krab is
right in, it's right here.
Right in the front. The whole
floor is green.
I'm not going to read that. You're fucking
crazy. Why did you write that?
All the things to write down
into a chat room and press enter.
It's just an immediate response.
Immediate response. You didn't
even take one second.
It was like, oh, yeah.
The floor of the Krusty Krab is green.
I look over three seconds, not even, you didn't even take
not even two seconds.
My shit is green sometimes.
Alright. Really?
Okay. Not even a
second.
Why would you share that with the glass?
Does the Krusty Krab have a bathroom?
Alright, well this has to be sealed off.
Because I want people to come through
this, which is the front door.
This is all glass,
isn't it? Big glass panels.
Can I get a
exterior of the Krusty Krab, please?
Would it be under door?
Or like glass, right?
Do it again. Okay.
Same thing on the other side. Two big
glass doors to get in. It might have to be
these side by side. Why is this so fucked up?
Is there a double door?
It has to be at the last double door.
Oh, right here. That's
much better. Oh, it's way too big
though. It's way too big.
This could work. Jesus.
Something like this is on the other side over here.
This is what's over here. Shit.
The entire front is glass. I don't think
I can do that though. It's a place
holder for now. That's gotta be glass.
That's gotta be glass. Okay. I'm gonna sneeze.
I actually caught it this time.
Okay. Now the
foundation is almost here. Now the work will speed
up very, very much intensely.
Here we go. This is a vibe
tonight. I'm glad. That makes me happy.
This will start to look more and more like
your beloved Krusty Krab
very shortly. This is
a good street to fall asleep to. Yeah, that's
cool. I don't mind that.
Big problem. I
cannot put anything
on the top or bottom here.
This has to be blocked with the bathtub.
This is actually a pretty major
problem. Can I do the half wall on
the ground? I don't know if I
can do a half wall on the ground.
I cannot. A window theoretically
is a great idea, but I
don't know if there are very many windows that
can be interior windows.
I need a fixture though.
Mountable bathtub. Where's the actual
bathtub?
This one here, right? I need the actual
thing. Where do you buy those?
Baths and showers.
Where is it? It's the
little thing that has to go into the wall.
Call something else
installations instead of this.
Okay, here we go. Yeah. Shower.
All right. Bathtub. But it's on the wall.
I need a wall.
This could hide it. I wonder how well
this hides it. Let's find out. I think this might
hide it. Yeah, this one will hide it much better.
I wonder what the biggest one is. Installation.
Oh. Where's just like
bathtub? Bathroom.
Okay, fixtures. Oh, I wish they would
I wish I could see how big they were without
having to buy it first. That's
pretty good. I don't know
if I'm going to do better than that. Maybe
I could. I doubt it though.
Wait a minute. Guys.
Guys, I could have just
made my own fucking
building. Why have I
decided to turn this
residential house
into the Krusty Krab? I could have just made the
Krusty Krab from scratch.
Well, now it's too late.
But are there any empty
lots? I didn't see an empty lot.
I'm going to see this through.
I think this is going to be good. Trust in
this process I have here.
Trust in this process.
The price is broken. Portal 3?
Hold
on. Just wait till the tables get in here.
Wait till the floor is done.
Wait till the decorations are up.
How long has this been playing for? I thought
this was still Spongebob.
Leave this on.
This was pretty good.
This is nice. We're making progress.
Here we go. One, when
the floor is installed, you're
all going to be...oh my
god. That's the
Krusty Krab. Now that's
the Krusty Krab I know.
Me doing that accent is like
Cilantro for a lot of you. You either really liked
what I just did or you hated it so
much that you just, you just
want me to turn my stream off. Alright.
Floor going in. It is a green
floor. This looks pretty good.
Let's try it.
I need lights in here. It's a green wood.
I don't know if I can do that. Green
wood. I don't think so.
This is close. Tile though.
Alright. Better. I think that's
better. It's got some more texture on it.
Can you change the color of the wood? You can, but you can
only really change it to other wood
likes. You can't make it like purple
or green or...so does this
door go anywhere in the Krusty Krab?
No. This is the Krusty Krab right
here. I'm making my
sanctuary. No. That's my
room. Alright. Where are the lights in the Krusty Krab?
Do they hang from the ceiling?
Alright. Krusty Krab
restaurant floor. Yeah.
This is as close as it's going to be though.
What do we got for lights? It kind of looks like
I can't really tell. There's glass
back here though. I was going to have
ceiling lights. These are kind of
interesting. Nice untextured
source map.
It looks fine. Where should I even put these?
There are no lights in the Krusty Krab
guys. There are no lights.
Oh! It's a jump
map. It's not done. Yeah
it does look like a dev room doesn't it? Because I'm
currently developing it right
now. It's not done. I'll do that
later. Aren't the walls wood in the dining
area? I don't know.
No. The glass. There's
wooden trim down here.
This is all this metal.
And then it's glass?
Glass. So this is a bunch of glass
glass glass. Glass and wood.
Why are these lights so high up?
Okay. I need to do, fix this
wood here. Ground.
This one I believe right here.
It is. What is casting a shadow over
here?
This is supposed to be Mr. Krab's
office.
Does Mr. Krab have the green on his floor too?
I'm sorry.
This looks like
you know those game makers
that are on you know
you can just get it like oh download this
game making studio.
This is, you just downloaded
a game maker studio. But you just opened
up Unity for the first time. And this
is what you came up with for the first, and you have no
experience at all. Zero. And
and you're twelve.
Just like oh look at my room that I made.
Yeah. There's chairs.
And there's a chair. But hey.
You gotta start somewhere. And when you first
make this room and you get really into it
and you go wow that was actually really cool. That was really
fun. And you end up making something like this.
Which is a level up from that.
And then you end up making a room like this.
Which isn't done yet. L plus
ratio plus your twelve. I
think it looks pretty good. I'm going
on the fucking lawn.
You need to hold your applause
until the end of the stream. We're going to see
all the before and after pictures.
Oh nice rain. This has been
a disastrous one guy.
I don't think so. No.
It's not done yet.
I don't want you looking over my shoulder while I'm doing
game development. This is not
even in a technical alpha right now.
This is in a Unity free
trial mode right now. This is not
a technical alpha. So
I see tables and they look pretty
cool and I know exactly where I'm putting them.
They are they have yellow in the middle and red
on the outside and they are wheels.
They are boat steering
wheels. That's not awful.
Not awful.
I could say dining table couldn't I? This one's
pretty good. Look at a picture of the Krusty. I got
a picture of the Krusty Krab right here. I'm looking at it right
now. Tables. This place
looks nothing like the Krusty Krab period.
Fuck you. Hey
come on dude.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
Oh that's pretty good.
They have the one kind
of pole in the middle.
It's on a stand. I don't think there's
any of those here though. They're red
on the outside. Close enough?
Yeah it's close enough. And
there is one here. There's
one here. There's one here.
There's one here. There's one here.
And they sit on little
barrels. Is it too big? They have little
any mini barrels?
Maybe a stool will look like it.
Pretty good if I could make it beige. Pretty good.
Right here. There we go.
They all have two or three. I can move all these
later. Guys, contrary to popular
belief, the finishings
is what ties everything together.
It's all about
the decorations and the finishings.
Already right now
it has already started to look more like
the Krusty Krab. Just simply by adding
the tables. We're going to do a bunch of stuff
here to hide this. Where's
Mr. Krab's door? It's coming.
It's going to be over here. It's going to be right
here. And you don't...
I'll show you the finishing touches
in a second. Where are the bathrooms?
That's a good question. The bathrooms
are on the right side.
So the bathrooms
need to be over here.
Bathrooms are over here. How do I move this?
I cannot take down
these walls, so I'm just going to have to
improvise a little. We're going to extend this
a little bit further. The bathroom doesn't
exist. No, it's not going to work.
It might work if I do this.
Can I build
off of the house? I don't think
I can build off of the house that
exists already. Can I?
I can't. Wait, is that actually
doing that? Wait, I can
do that. Alright. That's a big deal. Hold on.
So, if
I extend this wall
out, then I can make the bathrooms
right here. So that wall here
has to come out and match the wall over on
the other side. So if I can extend this
wall, that would be great. Because
this is the back. Let's see.
Yes! Let me
get rid of all this shit here. I just needed some space.
Alright. And now
can I bring this wall out?
What is this weird, what is this wacky
wall right here? No!
I can't get rid of this exterior
wall. No!
I can't, really?
Oh, oh well. Well, this is
the bathroom. Okay.
I gotta clean it. Put a door there?
I don't know if it'll work, though.
Because this wall can't be manipulated.
Oh! Oh!
I actually can. Alright. Where is
it? It's like right here.
Hell yeah. Nice!
It's a little messed up because
it's alright, though. Bathroom.
Beautiful. Perfect. Okay.
Bathroom.
Get a few images. A bunch of
wooden stalls, isn't it? Krusty
Krab bathroom. Okay.
So it's still green. Honestly,
the farm update will probably make this a lot easier.
So it's the same green, same blue.
Which I didn't delete at all.
Somebody doing the
chimpanzee jumping thing.
SpongeBob music! It kind of looks like
you guys are dancing to this song.
So I don't even see the anger in the chimpanzee.
I just see, I see you guys
rocking out to this music.
It's lining up with the music. Okay.
You just came back after two hours, what'd you miss?
Um, well, I think
it was just about an hour or two ago that I decided to make
this a SpongeBob house. Alright.
Good, almost done. There aren't
any more rooms after this, so it's all detail.
Damn it, it's not enough. It's fine.
Okay, so now we need the green. The green is easy.
Was these ones, no?
It was the... this one looks kind of better.
Oh, this is wall.
Damn it. Wait a minute.
These are way better. Isn't that kind of way better?
Nice. That's actually
perfect, yeah. I
don't know, you shouldn't be able to bump into stuff
when you're doing this. It's going the wrong
direction. Shit, it's got to
go vertical. You're right, damn it.
There is a vertical one, isn't there? It's actually
kind of getting there. Why is there got to be grass
sticking out? Alright, stalls.
They are made out of wood.
There are three or four toilets.
They're mounted into the wall.
They're the little mounted toilet, and they have
a life preserver. It's pretty close, but
it doesn't have the life preserver. That's close enough.
We're good. Alright, so it's one,
two, three. So I need three of those
things. Suspended toilet.
Alright, so we'll go one, two,
three. Alright, now I need to make
wooden stalls.
Do they make them anyways?
They do not, but
the farming update
gave us the ability
to make opening
kind of stall-like doors.
Greenhouse wooden segment. Oh,
here we go. This can't be inside.
Can none of this be?
So what do I do? Wooden roof side
segment. Where would the
I have no idea where they would put them. Like the
horse stable thing. There we
go. Yep, this should do it.
Are you going to play House Flipper 2? Better believe it.
Let me make these better.
I can't move these. But they have
What is hanging? There's like a cloth
or something. Hold on. So it's the wooden
doors, and then
it's two pieces of cloth that hang
from side to side. So these
technically would be the doors. I could always
add more toilets here. What's better?
House Flipper or Buffalo Chicken Sub? Buffalo
Chicken Sub all day. I'm sorry. Buffalo
Chicken Sub takes the place. It's like number
it's like number six on my
most favorite games of all time.
We were talking about like you got like Diablo 2
Team Fortress 2
Neverhood
Buffalo Chicken Sub
with blue cheese on it
obviously. And then probably Resident Evil
4 is probably up there.
Vampire Survivors is probably there too.
I need more toilets. Installation.
Good. Nothing over
there. That's fine. Blue cheese is so good. Yeah.
If I could
not get weird looks, I would
put blue cheese on almost every single meal.
Look at how nice and
colorful. Oh, look. SpongeBob.
Wow. Why are you not
at Coachella? I don't think I could name
you one band that's currently playing
at Coachella right now. I just don't think I could.
Okay. I need
What are they? What do they got? Decorations.
I need some nautical stuff.
Hmm. Let's see. There's
a hand dryer. There's a nautical.
There's a barrel. Oh, no. I thought I planted
other stuff. The gorillas are at Coachella
right now? Are you serious? Oh, shit.
Okay. Krusty Krab. Let's focus on one room
at a time, please.
I just typed in Krusty Krab
Coachella. Krusty Krab
restaurant floor. I mean,
there's not much else in here. There's a menu
that's up here. There's the door over there.
Okay. There's the door to
Mr. Krab's office, which let me go in there.
I can't even look at this because it's such a placeholder.
I can't even look at it. How about Minecraft
Cherry Blossom Forest?
It needs to be a little bit wider. I gotta
type this door. What is this? It's called
like something. Sounds like a C, right?
So I don't have to scroll down the never-ending
where is it? What the hell is it called?
It's called KY.
Okay. I guess I can only do
singles. I need a painting.
Something that looks like a menu.
Could be a menu. Oh, I can also import
images. That's true. Okay. Krusty
Krab
signs? Krusty Krab
Krusty Krab menu sign. It's kind of hard
to get a clean image of this.
I can get the big thing that's
outside. We'll do that later.
We're not done with our
internals here. Ugly, ugly, ugly,
ugly. We need these
glass panels
all over here. It sits on there weird.
Okay. Not bad. Not
bad. I want to put another one here, but
I don't think I have enough room for it. What happened to the music?
Oh, I closed the window.
What should I put on? Terraria? Terraria?
Okay. We've done that before. We did a little bit of Startup Valley.
Morrowind? RuneScape?
Pizza Tower is a little too intense
right now. Morrowind sounds pretty good.
There it is.
The Elder Scrolls III Morrowind.
I'm kidding. I know everyone's going to freak out.
So this is just more of the restaurant,
but this is way too big.
This is the Krusty Krab. This is how
big it is. There's no way
that I...
Here's my plan.
I'm getting my fucking zone that I want.
I'm getting my zone.
It's going to be a secret entrance.
I'm making my sanctuary.
You can go to the Krusty Krab all you want.
Me. I'll be in this room.
Crack shed.
This is the room he goes into to escape us.
One more piece.
I want my tub.
Thank you. I want a different
trim. Yeah.
We need a wall.
Wall tile. I'm clean.
How about these? I need to see the whole
thing. It's too bright. Well, we can
change the lighting. A little too
much going on. A little too loud.
Yeah, it's a little too loud.
This might be pretty good.
Put it down.
Pick it up. That is smoky.
I like it. Look at how smoky
this is. Can't stand in the pool.
Nice.
Just wait till I get the ambient lighting
in here. You are going to shit your
pants. This room is kind of freaking me out.
I don't like it. It's like too much going on.
I need ambient lighting in here. Quick.
I need really cool
ambient lighting in here.
As soon as humanly possible.
Yeah. Yeah.
Dude, that's real subtle. I know.
I need, hold on. Star Wars?
I'm not comfortable in here
yet. This feels like
a fake
room for a prank show.
Oh, yes. Come right this way, Mr.
Hudson. Come over here. Come to our beautiful spa.
It's like, oh, okay.
Someone's going to do something.
Someone's going to fuck with me here. The walls are going to collapse
and a bunch of gorillas are going to
attack me in here.
This is a prank room. But it's not done yet.
Let me finish it.
I need pool lights.
Do they have pool lights?
I don't think so. Well, that's going up.
That's a Krusty Krab thing.
What color is this? I don't want it too bright.
This seems pretty relaxing.
It's too many.
Well, it says they were small.
Why is it so bright?
Put up fairy lights? Do they have them?
I don't think they have stuff like that.
Stop putting it away.
There's no water even in there.
Neons. I got to get this brick out of here.
It's pissing me off. I'm going to
buy like 5,000 of these.
So I just never have to buy them again.
I don't care if I store them in a fucking shed in the backyard.
Jesus.
If I touch the water,
everything goes away.
Hey, could you go this song?
Let me listen to it again.
What does it go?
It's so old.
That's a very old meme.
I am not trapped. I'll be okay.
Because I'm going to make an opening
over here.
The door will probably be right here.
Now, there's a door right here, isn't there?
Or am I making that up? Isn't there a door right here?
No, it's not.
Really? Okay.
House Slipper 2 comes out this year,
doesn't it? In like a few months.
I think that's when it's
planning on coming out.
4 to 3? Cool.
100% we're playing it.
So now, I've got to fix that.
I've got to add the green
here and then the walls.
So let's buy a shitload of the walls.
I wish the recently purchased was bigger than this.
Instead of having to go to
walls and then all the way down.
Because I know what I want.
Or I could just remember how to type it into the search bar.
Instead of just glazing over
what it's called every single time.
You guys like this one?
Floors.
It was the green.
Was it a tile or was it a panel?
It was pretty far down.
Crusty Crab.
Now,
that's it for the floors of the Crusty Crab.
We're getting close to being done with this.
Then I just have to finish the upstairs.
Do I want any weird lights in here?
Hmm.
I don't think I want any lights in here.
Besides the ones that are already there.
I'm going to put, uh, this should be it though.
Yeah. Alright. So I need like
probably enough.
Why do I always have to do that?
Change the roof? Yeah, well, I'll mess around with the
exterior in a minute. Alright, so the next time
I play this, which will be at some point
soon. I'm not, the stream's not over by the way.
Um, but we will actually
cows and horses into stuff.
He got me on this Crusty Crab thing and I'm
stuck on it.
Favorite childhood snack. That's a good one.
Uh, PB Crisps.
They don't make them anymore.
I don't know what was in them. I don't know
why they won't bring them back.
Those were my favorite snack. Probably ever.
They're gone forever.
Actually gone forever.
Mr. Crab's office is so bad.
Okay. Can I put wood on the ceiling?
Let me see.
As it said, panels, right?
Floor and ceiling? Floor and ceiling panels.
I can.
What kind of, what is it? It's a little darker than this.
This? Mmm, that's kind of
alright. Is that good enough?
I think it's fine.
Can you play less sad music?
This is a little somber, isn't it? Okay.
Um, how about, what's something we can put on?
Sims buy mode? I like that one.
Cool.
Alright. We need to make this area cool looking.
Relaxing Gran Turismo
music to help you relax.
Really? I dig it. I'm into it.
Let's see if it helps. What's the outside of the Krusty
Crab look like? Let's see.
Krusty Crab. It's really good. It's kind of
green. It's like
olive. It's kind of like olive
wood. It's brown?
This looks kind of green.
It's wood covered with algae.
Oh. I mean, it's still green looking.
Dude, this shit is green.
This shit is literally green.
This is not
brown.
This is green. This is a green
tinted brown. Show us.
Show us.
All these Krusty Crabs.
Krusty Crab exterior.
This shit is green.
This shit's green. That's green.
That's brown and green.
Look at all that green.
It's wood with moss.
Yeah, but I mean, it's still like, how am I
how do I get that to look like that?
This is going to have to be just brown.
What is brown? Shit's green.
I thought my game crashed. I was
supposed to be really sad.
That's brown with green on it.
I don't know why I think that's so funny.
I'm moving on.
All right.
All right. Windows jump
scare. Oh shit. Sorry. I didn't realize it was
turned up. Well, just do
this. I
need it. No, I'm not doing the exterior.
I do want to pull in that
sign though. The menu.
Mod linked it here.
Galley Grub.
How do I add this?
I think I have to pull it in.
Save this link.
So much shit on my desktop.
Windows sound incoming. Let me turn it down.
So here is what the I'm going to try to get the
menu into the game. And this is what I'm trying
to put in here. So then I go.
I think it's like a camera gallery.
I got a lot of shit on my desktop.
So I'm going to do this.
All right. Let's go. How big should it be?
Where does it go? I'm right there, right?
Is it bigger? A little bit bigger.
Is that too big? That's not bad.
Can it hang from the ceiling? I don't think
so, unfortunately. Yeah. And everybody
was telling me that this was not going to
even look remotely like the Krusty
Krab. And we're not even done.
Finishing touches is all that
matter. The bathroom is way too big.
I have to
do this room. This room is just a placeholder.
I got to get this a little bit
nicer looking. Playing with this is to
go like this.
All right. One thing at a time. What do I want to add?
Is there anything down the hallway in the Krusty Krab
here? It is hanging. Oh, there's an order
here assigned to. I want to see
if I can get some nautical stuff here because there's
let me see. What
do you like? Anchor? Like a ship
anchor. Like ship.
Oh, OK.
I know I can put one of these
somewhere. Bingo.
And where should this go?
In the office?
This needs a total complete
reimagining. I could go to the steam workshop
too. I could do the steam workshop.
Nice Gmod office. I
know. Is a mini safe. All right.
So is there anything else in this main
room that is not here that
needs to be here? The sinks?
I can't really put glass over here because it won't.
You need wooden pillars.
Hmm. Wooden pillars.
All right. Fix the hole
where the pillar is. Let me look.
OK, they I don't think I can put those
in. They go across the ceiling, right?
Well, look, there's a couple that are on the ground.
Looks like to the left and right of the door
the entrance. If I go like
this, they're kind of like
here and here.
It's got to be
the same on both sides. It's a little bit tighter.
It's like here. But for aesthetic reasons
I'm putting it here. Are you still going to add goats?
Yeah, I kind of
threw away the whole farming DLC
and yeah, that's
unfortunate. We'll do it again.
This is just wood, but I don't want to build that yet. All right.
So this needs to be like here, right
here. Should be thicker. Really
sell what it is. It's wood walls.
These are pretty good. They're kind of
selling. These are a little dusty.
Let's try these. Use farm animals
for customers. That's actually a
pretty funny idea. This in the corner.
Pretty good.
Is it going to sit a little bit tighter in here?
Together. You missed a spot.
Doesn't match, but I don't think it really needs to.
Bathroom is the way it is. This is
my sanctuary over here. That'll have to
do. This is the room I want to tackle now.
The door to Mr. Krabs office
is left or right?
Is it closer to the wall or is it more in the middle?
It's the one in the middle, right? Yeah. Build this up.
What about the barrels? We'll do some touch up.
And the door. I'm going to have to keep using
these weird sci-fi doors, unfortunately.
Hmm. These look quiet.
Oops.
I like it. It's cool.
Here's the fridge. But we keep that closed
because I don't want anyone to see.
Oh, we've got more logos. Hold on. I've got to put these
in. Okay.
It's one too. Okay.
You can't see anything?
Yip, yip, yip, yip, yip, yip, yip.
Yip. Yip.
I might as well. Oh, there's a raid!
Oh my god, I got to turn this rain back on.
But I don't want you guys to see this yet. Hold on.
I don't want you to see this. This is very important.
This is where my sanctuary is.
I'm okay if you see it just didn't want you to see this because it's a surprise
Hello, welcome. Welcome vine sauce viewers. Thanks a lot, Vinny. Welcome
This is a surprise for chat. So I'm sorry. I took a little bit longer playing house flipper. Thanks for the raid. Welcome
We are currently
Doing something very important. We are recreating one to one
Not a single detail missed of the Krusty Krab and house flipper doing my best. I think it's going pretty good so far
We're working on it. And then I've also of course besides the Krusty Krab. I also have my sanctuary over here
Which has been recently updated. I'm leaving this house. Please. Don't mind the poop chairs. They're temporary
Alright, hold on. I got some other things to put in here. This is much smaller. All right. Yeah, like right there
How am I gonna do this? I don't think that works. Can I put it on a tree?
Why do I feel like I'm walking through?
One of those like Disney
Experiences where it's the Krusty Krab. Oh, whoa, I can actually walk around the Krusty Krab. This is so cool
And then it's just a store in here. This is a huge gift shop with tons of toys and
plushes and
Stickers and and you can eat here. You can sit here and eat here
but hey, but those of you that just joined us and some of you that have been here or
Some of you that have been here for a while have not seen all of it. So of course, this is we're not done
This is obviously
Spongebob's office Spongebob's work area. He's the cook. We got the window here meet a little bit of cleaning up here
There's a lot to do here. But wait till you see mr. Krabs office
I'm telling you right now. You are about to be floored with how accurate this is
But here's the bathroom though a little bit of extra space
All the toilets work dude, the floor is really carrying it really is without this floor. It was awful
All right. I'm happy with this so far. I think this isn't going pretty well
Let's tackle this room because this I just I don't I don't love it. I don't love it. Okay
What was Vinnie playing tonight? What's Vinnie doing 90s stuff? Oh
Obscure 90s websites. Ooh
Sounds pretty good. Okay
We need a shelf over here
There's another grill that's there's a second grill right old virtual world
There's another oven right here. It's too big. It's too big. I can't put it anywhere
I would pay thirty five thousand dollars for that. I wouldn't so I need an oven or a stove
There's a second one. What color is it? It's like, um, there's a couple of barrels
Let me put the barrels in first because I think those those go against back wall
Yeah, these go like here this I think it's too good how the ceiling needs to be wood
Shit. All right. Well, I gotta do that right now
Don't forget the Krabby Patty poster
Can I get it? Can a mod link me the Krabby Patty poster? You know, the craziest part about this house is
There's an entire upstairs that has bedrooms and bathrooms in it and it's sealed off forever
Never to be opened. I think that's pretty clear
All right, I need to fix the walls over there
Plenty of these good make sure you add a secret ladder to the upstairs crack addict
Yeah, I'm gonna hide that though because I don't want anybody to see it. So I'm gonna hide it like over here
I'm not even sure I can get upstairs ever again. I'm serious. I don't think I can get up there
What where am I?
What the hell? Uh, oh cool. You can change the roof, huh?
Wait, I didn't process that at all. How do I get to the roof tool? Oh
Cool. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What's the what's the top of the Krusty Krab? What? Yeah, no one's gonna look at the roof
All right. Well, this isn't the wrong spot. So where am I gonna put this?
I mean that can stay but so I need to it's gonna be like away from my sanctuary
Right, that makes sense. The hell is the rest of the house put it above the pool
Yeah, I was just trying to but I don't think I can get up there. It doesn't like that. The pool is there
The bathtub up there I think it has to just be maybe wait, okay, wait, wait, wait, maybe in the corner
I can do it right. Okay, I can do it right here. I want this be hidden though. All right
What is did I do it again? I don't care. Nice. Grab your fatty only at the Krusty Krab. Oh, I'll take that one
Wait a minute. What is that? I'm taking this downstairs
What a mirror be better here a mirror on this side and a mirror on that side. That would be kind of fine, right?
That might be actually pretty good. All right. There are some boxes in here. I got the food over there
I got the two barrels. There is a window. I actually think this is pretty good so far. Oh, wait, hold on
Yep. All right, Krusty Krab only a crab fatty only the Krusty Krab. All right. Come on. I don't want to spoil
Okay, any more any more I should put in I think that'll do it. Yeah, that should be fine
That should tie the whole room together now. You can look it's not that big. It's a little smaller. Yes, not bad
This is kind of ugly, but the vampire picture of you behind. No, this is it. That's for my sanctuary
I need some lights in here that I need a nice light and I'll be happy
Something very basic. Yep mood lighting exactly string light. I think they do unfortunately. It's okay. We like the chandelier. Ah
Hey, I hate this picture. It's so stupid. It's too well lit for that photo to be in here
What about like candles candles make more sense? Oh, I'm gonna make I'm gonna make a blood-borne room
I'm gonna make a dark souls. I'm gonna pick a from software room pretty good
I'll put a bonfire in the middle now. I'm sorry. There's not enough candles in this room
Okay, now it's officially a from software room
Is this your grave?
Vampire German grave, how did it get darker? How did I get darker?
This shit's on your walls. Wait, is there like a coffin? Hold on. Is there like a vampire coffin?
Why would there be what I'm looking? Oh my goodness. There is
the crusty crab
I think the candles are going out. I think that's the problem. He's be bigger than this. I think that's a good size
Fucked up. Yeah, he wanted to be he wanted to be put into a casket in his sanctuary room. He's not in there
He just really liked this place. He's in there don't open that open have it have the casket open
I don't think I can I love it. All right, I need a door there or should there not even be a door
Just just waltz into this
Okay. Um, I need like a shitty door. It's like a rickety door
This might be nice to get the shit out of somebody too. It's an outhouse. Yeah, please wash your oh, hold on
I got another image. This is a good one. This is a weird question
Does anybody have any more vampire pictures of me? Like that's a weird question to ask
Okay, hold on. Do you want safe? All right. Okay. Look at this ready
Yeah, turn the stream off dude, but we're probably getting close once we start doing shit like this
God all right that one hat that's going it. I don't this this is
Why would why do you have this? Why do you have this already? Like why do you own this?
I don't know. I can't understand why you would own this image
The question is does is this what goes on top of the door or is this go in the room, too?
I'll let you see in a second. Is this this is like an advertisement for like who's in here
I want to put like a big floodlight on that. Oh, jeez. Hold on
All right. Let me add one more and this is not turning into the saw house again
But like this is just too much. How is this? I can't believe this is a real person's face
I honestly don't understand. This is a real human being no spoilers
You know, honestly though, I'll be honest I've come to terms over the years with
Just how truly fucking strange my face can look sometimes and it's I just it's funny
I don't even care. The question is where does this one go that it's not even if it's not even me. Yeah
Alright, I think I'm done. I think I'm done. I think we've gone. We've gone a little bit too far
Uh, I think I'm done and that was really I don't know. I wanted I want the before-and-after pictures
Oh shit, I forgot about this. Hold on. I want the before-and-after photos. We'll make sure to move your office here
Do one final tour. Okay, welcome and we maybe we're not done
I'll make sure I'll move my office here. Wait, don't forget about the garden. Don't forget about the full send spongebob laugh. Okay
It's I can't do it. Should these be in the room here? I didn't like that at all
I find me somebody that did what about the animal customers? Alright, let's get some animal customers in here
Where are they? Where are they?
Arming well, how did I find it before? Oh, wait, wait, wait. I think it's actually from a different menu
I think I have to do it from the laptop. Yeah. All right. I gotta move my office
Let me save this and we're gonna go back to my office. So back to the office save the progress
Could I've done from that menu? Oh shit. I thought I had to use I thought I had to pick up the laptop and move it
There so could I have actually just gone there? Oh shit. I own this the option was immediately beneath what you clicked
Yeah, but when you have tunnel vision like I do sometimes it's burning. All right. Well, let's see how that's going
Mr. Grabs room in development by the way, so we just have
Animal customers. I just want to see what I'm just curious. Okay. I don't even know if I can do this. What?
Why can't I move? Oh, look at the little pig you guys want to see? All right, follow me. Take a look at this place
All right. I'm ready. Here's a carrot. No, these are spongebob characters. That's Squidward. Oh, wait, hold on. What about the pig?
This is cute. I like this. What's wrong? Are you okay? Are you good?
Doesn't need anything and there are other there's other animals out here. Oh, hi. Hello. What is that?
What what animals making that sound by the way? No one's gonna eat here
You okay?
Be in this room the health department is gonna be pissed. Oh, can I put like feeding troughs in here?
Don't go in the vampire room though. It's not safe in there. Okay, I need
Where do I buy food? Oh, no animal care. It's right here. Okay
Okay
Imagine going to a place to like a restaurant and there was just like cow and pig feeding troughs inside
It's a salad bar. Yeah, that's true. I need water
Hmm. Oh, okay. They're eating. Okay. They're eating. They're eating. You just ate the whole thing. What? Oh, no, the secret formula
It's pig slough. Oh, wait, the big ones coming in. I only need some water like a watering thing
Here we go. All right, things are going good. Why are they farm animals in this? I'm so lost
Um, this is a new update and we're just literally playing it for the first time right now not the last like five and a half hours
What is that animal? Is it you I'll pack is really do just look like spore characters. Is it good? Oh you eat grass
Oh
Where'd it go? Okay. All right, that's it
I could get some more animals, but I don't think I I think I'm gonna call it you get a bunch of spiders
Oh my god, I can sleep here you
the way
Okay. Well, um, how do I get the before-and-after photos?
I think I have to sell the house, but I don't know if I want to sell this one
This one's too special to me. All right, follow me, please and you buy a duplicate. Um, you actually might be able to
Alright, it is my office now. Oh my god. There's a move button. Alright, I think that's it. That was a lot of fun
I'll probably play this again, but we'll actually make a farm next time
And not crusty crab just gonna hang out and play for a little while make the chum bucket next
Now thanks for hanging out I'll give one final tour those that didn't get to see every room we're gonna start
All right. It's time. How do I move move? What? Oh, this is not right
Something's not right. What are the horse? Where's the horse? Huh? Where's my horse upstairs? Maybe. All right, let's do the tour
Welcome to the Krusty Krab. I have we make our own fresh ingredients here
Apparently we don't because there's nothing's been planted in months. I guess but never mind
Here's the front door. I got a nice glass over here a nice. Well, there was supposed to be glass over there
Yeah, I don't don't mind the pigs and the cows and the animals and stuff. They're just hanging out. You can come in
Alright, so here's the Krusty Krab
Pretty good. I added some
Extra stuff and take it right here. See please wash your fins
bathroom
This is a secret exit which goes to the roof just in case you need to use it
He's the bathroom. There are no sinks in the bathroom. That's unfortunate. I'll fix that next time
Here is spongebob's room a shot-for-shot remake and put some stuff here in there. This is mr. Krabs office
The work in progress. Oh and of course the the vampire room
Or the from software room, whatever one you want to call it
Beautiful square pool pretty nice. What was that? That's shit. What is that animal? I swear
Okay, so there's that and then there's the upstairs which is the living quarters. Very cool
This still needs to be moved into I'm thinking of a big flat-screen television right here
Nice bath, maybe a little maybe upgrade the bath a little
Could be a little
Yoga studio, but you're very well behaved. You're very nice. You want some dress the horse
I don't know where the horse is horse is fine
Horse is not fine. Oh, no, you're good. All right, everybody's doing good. I'm gonna save it and I'm gonna call it
so I mentioned that I
Was probably gonna take a little bit of a break but not really
Wednesday this coming week stir and I are gonna play some games but besides Wednesday, I don't really have a plan
So Wednesday, we're gonna play hanging out stir and I and then maybe another stream later this coming week
but I
Only and I are gonna take a little bit of a break
Been doing a lot of grotto be stuff and we're
Incredibly happy that a lot of people have been getting their stuff
But a lot of work to do still up until I want to say a day or two ago
That's really kind of where I was for four or five straight days of off stream
When all the grotto be stuff, but I think I think we need to take a little bit of time together
But I'll see you Wednesday after Wednesday, maybe this weekend. It scares me every it actually scares me every time
But break as in there's only gonna be like one or two streams over the next week or so
Yeah, thanks for watching. This was fun. Pretty great update. I'm glad you can actually finally build a house
Adding additions to houses was always something I begged for
Five years ago, but you can finally build a house from the bottom up
But that's a huge deal. Can you please pet the baby pig? Yes
Come here find truffles
Did you find one? It's kind of looks like Otto with no hair. Have a tomato
You don't have to find any truffles. You can just relax. I love I can why you want to go in there so bad
What if what's in there? What are the wait aren't the ingredients to a Krabby Patty?
It's not meat right then it's something else. This is just fish crab. That's crab meat. It's a secret
Oh, it's human meat. It's veggie meat. I don't think anybody knows. All right. I'll see you guys on Wednesday
I'm gonna I'll hit up stir and see um exactly what we want to do
He mentioned he wanted to play orks must die free
So it might be a gamer stream on Wednesday. We also need to watch him play five nights at Freddy's
Imagining that will probably be part of that stream too. We'll see
This music was actually pretty relaxing. It was this is Gran Turismo
Gran Turismo
Okay, wait, let me make sure I save this
Yeah, it's safe. All right, and the music I did not forget the music
There it is
Yeah, also by the way, just to remind everybody one more time the limited items are about to leave the store in
15 20 minutes for grotto beasts. Yeah in about 10 minutes 10 20 at 11 59
The limited stuff is going off the store specific. That is the glow-in-the-dark
apparel
That's the original 40 grotto beasts and all the posters
jiggleberry
thoraxos and glue man those are all going off and I think the hats are going off too
the cards are still there though and we uh
For those of you that are still waiting for shipping updates, we are working on that right now for those of you that don't know
some of the early orders had some kind of issue a ton of orders have already gone out a
Massive amount of orders have been shipped and people have got it and we've seen a lot of really cool
Openings and unboxings and we're just really happy that people like it
But we want to make sure that the people that are still waiting for a shipping update
That they actually get as of tomorrow morning. We're meeting with represent
So we're gonna be talking about it trying to figure out a game plan, but it looks like it looks like they're gonna be
Starting to really go back and take a look at all those so we're working on it
We are those of you that are still waiting
The regular grotto be shirts are still up and they are staying there
Yes, like the logo shirt logo hoodie and obviously the cards
Yeah, the starter kit and the cards are all gonna be there
I will tell you the starter kits are not going to see a reprint
The plan is not to do a second print of the starter kit and it's still inventory
But that's something that is not going to see a reprint and we likely depending on how it all goes
We did a second print of the boosters already
So we'll see how that goes. We'll see how much inventory we have and
Make some decisions as that goes forward. Yeah, just want to give you some updates
What about a second edition?
What about the uncrusty grotto beast ad? Yep. I would expect that in the next few days
Yeah, just know that if you are still waiting if you had a March estimated ship
We are actively actively working on it
And thankfully it's it doesn't seem like it's a very large amount of people
But it's still even if it's a smaller percentage of all the orders or whatever it is
Wait, I don't we don't want that right? So we're trying to actively figure out how to fix it
Yes, the non glow-in-the-dark stuff is staying but the art prints are about to go away. Yes, Holly
Do I have that right? Is the non glow-in-the-dark?
What are you staying or both of those going? Okay, so it the non glow-in-the-dark is staying
so the one with the
With the ghost on it. Yeah regular ink is staying logo staying and the cards everything else is going
Is the glow-in-the-dark gonna be gone forever? We don't have a plan to bring it back, but I don't know
I don't we're just trying to get through this first period to make sure everybody gets their cards. Everybody's happy
That's priority number one right now. And with that we'll see you Wednesday
We probably won't bring it back because with the as limited as some of the stuff is
the cards we have inventory and
one inventories gone, that's
It's especially the starter kits. We're not doing a second print on those
Well, the music didn't get looped
Stupid and idiot loop the music next time people are counting on you to play it
What's my favorite color? My favorite color was the color of the pool
That I built and house flipper. Alright, see you guys later. See you Wednesday. Take care of yourselves. Have a great night. Call your mother
season