Okay, so what we're gonna do, you guys, we're gonna play a game called Simon Says. If you don't know how to play that, then you're just dead anyway. So are we ready? Everybody turn to me. The game's gonna start when you turn to me.
Now, Simon Says turn to me. Okay, Simon Says...
Ow, hold on.
Kill him! Get that son of a bitch!
Oh, hold on. I gotta... hold on a second, guys.
Simon Says, we're gonna jump.
That guy on the left! Okay, he did, he did. He's good.
Simon Says, sing a wonderful song!
Uh, sorry. That wasn't fucking good enough!
Well, I thought that's what... that's what you... they didn't do what I wanted them to do, so I killed them.
That's how you're supposed to play.
What? What do I do?
What does that mean, rebel?
What? Oh, the...
Oh, whoops.
Is there a disco here? What the hell is that?
Can we... can we have a disco party after this? I wanna play disco. I know I've been bad, but still.
Is anybody going to answer me? I'm trying to ask a question.
I want Warden again. Give it to me. Give me Warden. I'm not listening to you.
I'm gonna do whatever the fuck I want, because I don't care. How about that one?
What's a potato? What are you talking about? Are you talking to me?
What the fuck? He just killed me for no reason!
That guy first captured Shelby for no reason. I want him reported. I want him in jail.
Listen, everybody shut the... shut the fuck up, everybody.
Okay, so on the count of... I never told you to come down here.
Nobody said to come down here. You have five seconds to go back up the stairs.
Five, four, three, three, three. You made it, okay.
So everybody now on the... I want you all to come to the line and line up crouching.
If you are not crouching, then you are dead. That's all I gotta say, so get down here.
All my friends will shoot... Don't shoot him!
Okay, so when you line up... No, don't kill him. He just wanted to say hi and give you a hug.
Okay, so what we're gonna do here...
What we're gonna do is we're gonna have all these CTs please line up here with me.
Line up side by side with me.
Because you guys have been so good, you terrorists, will you cut to shit?
Quit shooting people in the face. What the hell, man?
Okay, what? Seriously? Seriously, I'm trying to talk here.
I want all the T's to come and give your favorite CT a hug.
Okay, let's do it. Everyone come give us a hug.
Yeah, I love hugs too. Yay, thank you for the hug.
That's a wonderful hug you're giving me.
What the fuck? You're supposed to hug people!
All right, so all the boys...
Thank you. I didn't mean to. It was not me.