Hello everybody. I already have my chat open. Hold on, let me do that. We fix that. That is a useful
thing to have open. Welcome to the House Flipper Unofficial Invitational. How you doing? Give me
one second while I do this. There are 10 people here. It's weird to talk in chat and not be in chat.
Hold on. Give me one. I didn't even. I gotta tweet it. I gotta tweet it. Give me a second. The House
Flipper Unofficial Invitational. No, this is unofficial. This is only my Invitational.
If you're wondering, I asked a bunch of my friends, a couple other streamer colleagues
to come into the stream, spend 75 minutes at the same time with the same house,
and see who makes the best house. Graded on five categories. Well, four categories. You guys will
get the last grade. Everybody should be getting started with their streams. We want to make sure
everyone's ready to go. All right, here we go. Who's here? We will. We will introduce them in
just one second. How much time do they get? 75 minutes. Are you playing Final Fantasy today?
What? Not today. Yeah, we're gonna play Final Fantasy in five minutes. No.
All right, I think we can get the crew here. Let's see if everybody's here. Hello? Is anybody here?
Hello, Mr. J. Well, that's a mod. All right. Is everybody here? I'm live right now. So if
anybody wants to pop in. Hello. Hi. Yeah, we got, we got mods in here. Everybody unmute.
Yeah. Yeah. Hello. How is it going, folks? What's up? Should I ping the other streamers to unmute?
I would say so. And it's 75 minutes. Starts right now. Wait, really? No, no, no, no. I'm just
kidding. I'm kidding. Oh, that's right. That's right. That's right. All right. Once everybody's
here. Yeah, you can unmute. You can undefine everything. We're going to go over it real
quickly. And I'm very curious. I want to get a little bit of a temperature check from all of you.
We're going to introduce every single person. Each person gets each person gets 15 minutes to
introduce themselves. Should take us about two or three hours to get through the initial intros
here. Cool. Glad I have this full PowerPoint presentation. You to me. All right. So welcome,
ladies and gentlemen, to the house flipper of unofficial invitational. What you see on
my screen right now is the house that all of these streamers are going to have to turn into
a beautiful home in 75 minutes. The timer is on my stream. I would be aware that streamers,
if you need to know, it's 75 minutes, hour and 15 from when I count down. Well, let's introduce
who's here first. And by the way, you get literally like a five second introduction.
So let's start. Whoever wants to go first. Go ahead. Just go. I'm Vinny. Hi. That's all I need.
He got it. Well, I was I thought we were going to hear a shit load of people just start yelling.
Does he get points for that? Does he get graded? Hmm. Yep. I think so.
That was some good philosophy. That was pretty good philosophy. That's right. Everyone's.
No, no. See, see, see dog. What time is it where you are right now?
It's well, it's 512 a.m. And I woke up at 430 a.m. For this. So I hope that goes into the kind
judging considerations that at an inconvenient time, I'm on peak performance.
Yeah. So I'll just go through it. Connery's pants. See dog. Criken. Doug Doug. It's Alex. Ludwig.
R.T. game. Joel. I almost just said Trotter, but you're you're a mod and Vinesauce Vinny.
These are your we did an alphabetical order. Yeah. Roll call attendance done for the class.
That's the attendance of ladies and gentlemen. And I mean, you know, for German 98. Yeah.
Whistler. I don't know. He's not here. He might just say he might just show up and just jump in
the call later. He has no pressure to be here, by the way. It's a content creator stream and
we're less than 15 minutes late. That is a crowning achievement. That actually is true.
It's true. There's the sheer fact that miracle we're all actually here at the same time is
quite shocking. It is. I'm just going to tell you guys this. When German presented this idea to us
and I'm going to go full in for this, all right, because it's going to be like my part of this
is going to be crap. But I get into this call and I'm expecting everybody's got their stuff lined up
so good. And I realize none of these guys have booted up the game. Yeah. So I have a good chance
of maybe making it into the bottom five. You know, you got this, Joel. I believe in you,
Joel. I don't know. You might be the favorite. It's possible you're the
fellow. I hope you crash and burn. Joel showed us his secret and it is
way better than anything I thought. I think we have a very. I hope you're a lecture about the walls.
So I don't know how to make walls. I will figure that out. He woke up. It's five a.m. He's like,
what the fuck does German want me to do? He wants to build a house. What are the tools?
Telling me about the technique, about how bad he will.
You're going to scroll at a good pace. Make sure you're five pixels away from the wall.
The ball won't build. And I'm like, wait, which tool is this? Well, I'll figure it out.
Yeah, it's by the way, this whole thing is horseshit. None of this matter.
Give it away. What? No reason to stay.
If you guys just all left right now, like it would be fine. Like there's no nobody wins anything.
Nobody loses anything except I have to ask you, Jerma. I have to ask you this.
This might be a stupid question, but are you wearing it like a toupee or something?
You look like you look like you. No, I'm not wearing a toupee.
Oh, this is my real fucking hair. Tony's shit. What happened?
Look more professional or something. This is Tony. Take points away for that.
Take points for copying Tony star. Thank you for bringing up points.
Let's go over it real quickly. You are all going to be graded individually.
You're going to give me a tour through what you thought?
You don't like my presentation voice? There's a lot of people in here who just left.
Is it a mod? You'll never figure out who it was with like streamer mode on.
OK. Sorry, Jerma. Which sea name was it? Good luck.
You are all going. Let me talk about what you're doing.
Yeah, that's an old one. That one was of 2018.
I mean, this is like a first trial run of this event. You guys supposed to be my friends.
We're listening, buddy. Go ahead.
I'm going to keep you going, Jerma. Yeah, everybody give it up for Jerma.
I'm here for you. Moment of silence for Jerma.
You are all going after 75 minutes, which, by the way, everybody here is streaming.
So everybody has their streams going. You can jump around, go see what people are doing.
Maybe one of them isn't. And then, you know, whatever, that's all good.
Well, maybe two of them aren't three. Doesn't matter. But go check it out.
You're going to be seeing their process. They'll be streaming it live.
They're all on this house and they're all going to be graded on five categories.
Creativity is number one. It's worth 35 percent of your total grade.
Creativity. Creatively bankrupt.
Based on a one hundred point scale, it's worth 35 percent of your total grade.
Complexity and structure is your second grade. This is worth 25 percent of your total grade.
How do you how did you handle the walls? What is your interior wall structure looks like?
Did you do any additions? How does your yard look?
Did you did you add anything in there? How does your yard look?
How does your yard look? The next one is cleanliness.
Cleanliness is worth 15. I see that over there. Somebody's put an image of me.
It's worth it. Cleanliness is worth 15 percent of your total grade.
So make sure. Look, I mean, look at this. You got this kind of dirty.
It's kind of fucked up. You're going to be graded on this one hundred point scale.
Maybe you get an F and clean. Maybe you get an A plus in creativity.
Use your time wisely. The next grade.
There's more. Philosophy is worth 15 percent of your total grade.
What does philosophy mean? We'll find out because I don't know either.
So we're going to figure that out as we go. The last grade is worth 10 percent.
It is chat's grade. The mods are going to put a poll in at the end of each person's individual tour.
That will be a very simple A, B, C, D or F. F is always 55 points.
You can't go lower than 55 points. Do we have any questions?
Have you revealed that you are going to build a real full scale replica of the winning house yet?
For the dollhouse, too. This is the location.
No, not yet. But that's that's that's a great idea.
That's actually a fantastic idea.
There's like grandmas on the left side of my screen. Is that all right?
OK, it escape. Go to settings. Go to gameplay options and
check the box that says I don't want to hear from the people, the buyers.
You should all do that.
Oh, I. Oh, wait, I think you're joking.
Well, they were just. OK, can I ask how many people?
That is funny, though, in my two page document that I sent you all four or five days ago.
How do you guys think I was making a joke?
I read I read it like I did. I read the whole thing.
I thought it was more like light reading, though. I thought I didn't realize it was
optional. I thought it was a creative writing piece.
I said you guys a two page document with detailed instructions.
It seemed like G.B.T. wrote it.
Oh, yeah. I thought it was like an Isaac Asimov, the foundation thing.
Like it didn't actually have any bearing on real life.
I don't understand the power.
We had to eat a horse in preparation.
I ate the horse.
Ladies and gentlemen, I read it so I could figure out all the loopholes.
Are we all ready? Oh, yes.
I didn't catch that.
I'm ready because you have seventy five minutes as of the third.
You're making me laugh as of three, two, one, go.
OK, they all muted. They can't hear me anymore.
I can hear you. I heard.
Oh, you're waiting.
That's not how muting works.
What? What happened?
I thought everyone was gone.
Oh, hi. All right.
Well, so they are on their own streams.
I'm very curious what they do.
In the meantime, I'm going to just kind of show you some things about house flipper
that, you know, we're just going to go take a look.
Some of you might not have ever seen this game.
Yeah, you should probably mute me
because I'm just going to be like an annoying presenter this whole time.
Somebody says Ludwig isn't streaming.
So he's cheating.
That's so funny.
But anyways, all right, let's go.
So I'm very curious about this.
This was just something to do for fun.
I never thought this was going to be like anything serious or anything.
But this is this is going to be a good time.
I'm very curious.
I could go peek in and see what they're doing, but I'm going to leave that up to you.
I think I think I want because I want to be very
surprised.
I don't think I want to see what they're doing.
I think I want to be given a fully completely secret tour
because then I can get my real assessment on the grades
because we have them here and I'm ready to give them to each individual person.
So let me let me do some stuff.
Let me let me see what I can do.
And I don't who cares about my time.
What the fuck do I care?
I don't want to peek.
So let's see.
What do I want to do?
I can just clean the yard and just hang out.
All right.
What I do want to I do want to ask this question of everybody that's streaming right now.
Who is panicking the most right now?
Right now, out of all the people that are doing this, who right now is like,
I don't fucking know what's going on.
Please somebody help me.
I bet you it's all of them because they have to clean.
Look at how fucking like dirty the yard is.
Hey, don't don't tell them this.
I'm going to want to see back here, too.
Don't tell them that.
Well, you think that's worth a 100 percent?
You think that's with an A plus?
If you miss anything here, they're stream sniping each other.
They really they really shouldn't be.
But whatever, it doesn't fucking matter.
I'm so curious, though.
I wonder what they all do.
They're stealing ideas from each other.
It's so funny.
I try to give the there's so many.
So I had like a two page detailed document about like how things work and everything.
And even I'm just sitting here going, wait, how the fuck do you build an edition?
Oh, so like 20 minutes ago, I was in there explaining how to do an edition
because I was like, wait a minute, why is this not working?
Oh, that's right.
You can't have anything on the other side.
We were we were like troubleshooting with each other like 20 minutes ago.
I didn't even tweet the stream.
There's like 10 fucking streamers here.
Give me a second.
Hold on.
I'm going to say live right now with the house flipper speed build with streamers.
It's not really a tournament.
You're wasting time.
I mean, the whole goal for the first hour of this stream on my end is to waste time.
So don't worry.
The timer is for you and for them to know how much time they have left.
Should I go in there?
Should I have the mods on mute and have me just be like, you got 25 minutes left.
It's a contest.
It's not a tournament.
Well, it's not even a contest.
When you're in school, you know, like a science class,
is it a contest with your fellow students?
No, you just get individually graded.
I don't want to give anybody an F though.
I feel like I haven't heard somebody's feelings.
Should I not give somebody an F?
Budwig is, I don't want to know.
I don't want to know what he's doing.
Give them all Fs.
They deserve it.
They all should have Fs.
Why is your camera off center?
I don't know.
Because I put it above this thing.
Oh, because I'm leaning in.
Okay.
Let me just live right now with the house flipper speed build in unofficial invitational.
Because does it even matter if I tweet something?
It's probably like only 50 people that see this through Twitter.
I was going to say the unofficial invitational.
I got time.
I like how I don't have to.
This is great.
We can just sit here and watch a clock for an hour and I don't have to do anything.
This is perfect.
I should do this more often.
Because I can hear in the other room, right?
A streamer freaking out.
Being like, how the fuck do I use this tool?
What the fuck?
This is this game.
What's wrong with this game?
I can't fucking pick this up.
They didn't read the instructions.
The birds are just chirping.
Ah, this is nice.
I feel great.
Look good right now.
All right, live right now with house flipper unofficial invitational with streamers.
I could add every single person, couldn't I?
Should I add every single person here?
You should.
Yeah.
I'm going to spend an hour.
I'm going to spend my timer is making a tweet in an hour.
Can I do it?
Can I make it?
Can I tweet my own event within the time that the event is taking place?
At this, there's two of these people.
I can't do it.
I can't look at it.
I hate looking at this.
It's in your title.
What is my title?
Oh, that's right.
We're good.
Okay.
At this is going to go over the character limit.
At seadog at italics.
Okay.
At who else is here at Ludwig.
This is what this is what people do.
This is the longest tweet of all time.
At people that aren't here.
No, that's stupid.
At Kraken.
No, I'm just I'm doing it.
This this I can't this is too many characters.
I can't even do it.
You have Twitter plus.
I don't even know what that is.
What is Twitter plus?
Is a Twitter plus?
Are you stupid?
All right, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Hold on.
Let me stretch first.
I swear to God.
I actually like need to hold on.
I got a DM.
Poke.
Okay.
Hold on.
Poke is in my DMS right now.
Poke is I think on his way.
All right.
Well, I think poke is on his way here.
You got you got an hour and five minutes.
That's so funny.
Add extra time for poke.
Well, it was 60 minutes, but we made it 75.
So technically we did technically that we did.
Yeah, we'll put we'll put poke on the end.
That's so funny.
He said he said it's not tomorrow.
Focus on your tweet.
Oh, my tweet, my tweet, my tweet.
I fucking love poke so much.
Okay.
What am I doing?
Oh, at C dog at it's Alex at okay at Doug Doug.
They're going to get a notification
and be like, why did Jerma just at me on Twitter?
Oh, because he just he just now put the tweet up.
Okay.
Hey at at poke at poke.
Okay at at Kraken at Ludwig at RT at Vinny.
I'm going to add somebody twice at Joel at Vinny Vinesauce or Vinesauce.
Yeah, Vinesauce.
All right.
I'm ready to put my tweet out for my big event.
That's everybody, right?
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Wait, I'm missing somebody.
Who am I missing?
No, no, no, there's one more.
No, no, no, I got Connery's pants.
No, I didn't.
I thought I put him first.
I put the other Connor.
Okay, there it is.
I'm ready to tweet it.
You guys ready?
Make sure you retweet it.
Make sure you retweet this.
Make sure I got everybody.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
There we go.
Hey, look at that.
I did it.
Yeah.
So anyways, if you don't know anything about House Flipper,
let me give you some quick education here.
House Flipper is a game where you clean houses.
You flip them.
You add interior walls.
So you're like, I can clean.
You try to make it look as nice as you can.
Walls can come down.
I hope this isn't loud.
It probably will be.
So I'm going to do this for a sec.
I probably should have mentioned that to all the streamers.
That the, actually, no, it's okay.
No, they probably patched it.
You tagged the wrong vine sauce.
What do you mean?
I did?
No, I didn't.
Great tweet.
I got it right.
All right.
How are people doing?
Who is in the lead in your opinion?
Who is like, wow, they know exactly what they're doing.
I hate this tweet bit.
I just did it.
It's over.
It's the entire Vinesauce team account.
Well, it's all right.
It's all right.
Let me get back over here so I can see what people are doing.
Okay, we're good.
It technically is the wrong account.
Oh, that's all right.
All right.
So let me just give you a quick rundown.
Everybody is doing what I'm doing right now.
They're probably very far ahead of what I'm doing.
I wonder how many people are just panicking,
just sitting around biting their fingernails going,
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I don't know what to do.
I will show you.
And I'm also here unmuted in case somebody has a question.
It's very important.
If somebody comes in here and is like,
hey, dude, can you please help me?
How do I do this again?
I want to be able to be here to tell them.
But House Flipper has many, many, many, many tools,
many things for you to do.
For instance, I can paint the walls whatever color I want.
I can take down pretty much any wall.
You can do wallpaper.
So let's just say for the instance this.
Yeah, like just panels.
I know a lot of you know this already,
but this might be people here that have no idea
that are here from other people's streams,
so on and so forth.
So I can.
Jerma, I have a question.
Yep.
Sorry, I scared the shit out of myself
because you came in here and I scared the shit.
You scared the shit out of me.
All right.
So is there a way to like bar window?
Like if I wanted like from the inside,
like put bars on the windows.
Like actually put bars on the windows.
Right.
Like so someone like couldn't get out of the room
if like through the window.
I don't think so.
Oh, but can they hear you?
I don't know.
Yeah, they can.
Yeah, they're lying to me.
I don't think you can put bars on the windows.
If you like bars on the windows,
I would say you probably should leave the bars
that are already on the windows.
Okay.
Because I don't think you can put.
You can sell the window.
You can put a new window in,
but I don't think you can put bars on it.
All right, I'll figure this out.
Thank you.
Yeah, so what happened to your eyebrows?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with my eyebrows?
I mean, my hair lightens up in the summer
because I'm out in the sun.
We're going to my garden, bro.
They're gone.
They're not.
What are you talking about?
My eyebrows lighten up in the summer.
My eyebrows are right here.
This grass in Vegas.
Well, I have sunflowers,
which I'm supposed to give you an update on those today,
but it's just not going to happen.
I'm sorry.
You have a unibrow.
I'm German.
Is that German?
This isn't cheating to just ask you a question mid-contest, is it?
No, no, no.
You're in fact the second or third person who's done so.
So yeah.
Thank God.
What can I do for you?
What can I do for your RT?
How do I fill in an existing hole in the house,
like in the concrete foundation,
like there's just gaps in the walls and I want to put wall in there.
Okay.
So you are going to hold right click
and you have build inlets or build walls and lintels.
Okay, I see build lintels.
That's for like a lower wall, is it?
Yeah, but lintels you can put up.
You can't put them down,
but you can build that build tool is how you cover up gaps.
Okay, but what if it's like a garage door or something like that?
Because I'm trying to...
Okay, let me see.
But so you want to...
What I'm imagining is you want to replace the garage door is what you're saying.
You know, I found a solution.
Yep.
It's grand.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Yep, you got it.
You'll be all right from here.
Okay.
Thank you.
Tech support.
I'm here for an hour to meet tech support.
That's so funny though.
No help, no help, no help.
You didn't help.
Oh, I didn't help.
That's fine.
No help.
Tech support.
Time is actually ticking.
I heard nervousness in that voice.
Okay, let me make some stuff.
Let me do the lawn.
All right, let's get the tree trunk.
I'm going to clean up.
I'm going to do a lawn.
I think a lot of people are sleeping on the lawn.
I tried to make that really clear.
I did say, guys, the lawn is important.
Look at the lawn, the lawn.
Only one person asked about the lawn and I'm not going to tell you who.
I did have one inquisitive response about the lawn.
I should have read this syllabus.
Yeah.
Won't your own house impact grading?
No, no, we're going to get tours.
People are going to share through Discord or through potentially,
if it doesn't work, I can just pull up their streams too.
What about indoor lawns?
I'm not telling anybody how to make anything.
One of the theories was if people had fun doing this,
if this was a fun time for everybody,
is maybe expand it and do it again another time.
Now that people have understand the format
and include themings that you have to go by,
especially with House Flipper 2.
House Flipper 2 is going to be so much more elaborate than this
that I feel like that could be a lot of fun stuff.
I'm very interested.
But if people like it, if people are like,
yeah, that was really, really swell.
I want to do that again.
Then we can start to do things like,
hey, the theme for this one is green.
I'm going to give you three words, green, bark, and food.
And that's it.
Good luck and see what people come up with.
This one was more, I'm just going to let people go kind of wild
with whatever they want to do.
And I might just remove F.
I feel like some, I feel like a couple people are going to be like,
hey, man, I just had no idea what the fuck is going on.
And I don't want to give him an F.
Maybe I'll take away F, bark.
That's fair.
Yeah, F is a little harsh, I think.
But no F can ever be lower than 55 points.
Just keep it.
That's, no, you have to, that's spineless.
What do you mean?
Is it harsh?
Don't hurt their feelings.
I'm going to try not to.
We're down to, they, all right,
they're down to, they've only got 53 minutes.
It's unfair to the people that try.
I'm going to laugh my ass off.
I'm going to laugh my fucking ass off.
If poke shows up with like 20 minutes left
and just like fucking freaks out and gets in the game
and makes a banger of a house.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, I feel like that's possible.
That's so funny.
All right, let's do some, let's cut some, let's cut the grass.
I don't even know if people know you had, there's a lawnmower.
There's going to be people picking up blades of grass by hand.
Everybody is inside at this point.
Okay, interesting.
D won't be insulting.
Put on some music.
We could put some music on.
I mean, we're just hanging out anyways.
Put on, I don't know, like Animal Crossing.
It's the easy go-to.
Ah, nice.
Only 51 minutes left.
Oh, that's like, I got a long time to relax.
I'll change F to 60.
We'll make it a D.
Yeah, we'll make it a D.
If I was going to give an F, I'm just going to give a 60.
There you go.
The F just doesn't exist anymore.
Play Hell's Kitchen music.
Yeah, I'll do that when there's like five minutes left.
When there's like five or ten minutes left,
I will play Hell's Kitchen music and just start yelling at people.
Let's let, let's let them work.
Let them actually try.
I don't want to give pressure right now.
All right, let's sell this.
All right, Poke is here.
All right, let me get, let me get Poke just quick instructions.
I said poke hop on the call.
I can give him a quick, I can give him a quick, quick rundown.
He's, he's got, it's still 50 minutes.
Look, I, these are individual grades, so I can know that I can know.
Hey, hey, what's up?
Hi.
Hey, all right, we're live right now.
There's currently 50 minutes left in the competition.
We started with, yeah, we started with an hour.
We went up, we went up to 75 minutes.
So you're actually not that, you, you still got some time.
Listen, I read it was tomorrow and I was at an aquarium.
I, I'm home now.
I'm here.
Well, the aquarium probably sounds fucking awesome.
It was great.
Yeah, but I don't want to, in the game, everything ready.
I'm ready to go.
I don't want to take up any more of your time, but the house you need to open,
you need to open, it's called Garden After the House Built.
That's the house everybody's doing.
That's the house you need to build.
Okay, which one?
So go to the laptop, go to browser, go to houses that you can buy
and make sure you've done the cheats to give yourself the half million dollars.
You're going to scroll down.
It's got a bunch of wooded windows.
You're going to get in there.
It's called Garden After House Built.
That's the one you're going to.
Garden After House Built.
That's the one right there.
Go, say go now and get going.
And you're only about 10 to 15 minutes behind.
All right.
Going in now.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right.
Timer's gone.
Good luck.
Bye.
All right.
Good to see Poke.
We got everybody now.
The aquarium.
Well, that sounds fun.
He's freaking out right now.
Well, if you see this and knowing that you've lost potentially 25, 30 minutes of time,
it's almost like, what do I even do?
I guess go through the windows.
Jerma, why weren't you invited?
I tried to give a tutorial of how to build additions,
but I feel like, okay, you know when a teacher,
when a teacher explains something and very clearly the whole class is quiet
and everyone's like, all right, can you show us again?
It's just like, oh, shit.
All right.
Nobody got that.
I have to, I have to do it again
because there's very specific things you can't do with the addition builder.
I wonder, I wonder.
This is House Lipper 1.
House Lipper 2 is not out yet.
Play Halls of Torment.
I actually saw that.
I wanted to play it.
That's definitely on the list 100%.
It's very pog.
Joel thinks he's almost out of time.
You're not almost out of time.
The Hell's Kitchen music hasn't started.
That's so fucking funny.
I don't know if, can we, mods, can you undefinite and unmute everybody for,
oh, no, no, just undefinite everybody for a second.
Don't unmute them.
Just undefinite them in here.
Can we do that so I can tell them to the time check?
We cannot.
We can't.
Okay, okay.
Well, sorry everybody, but we can only, okay, we can ping them.
Yeah, maybe ping everybody and just say, hey, 45 minutes, 45 minute warning.
This is going quick.
Oh, this is, I'm excited.
I'm so happy about this.
I'm having fun.
I'm having fun just like experiencing what I think
I'm going to experience in 45 minutes.
Come on, dig.
I can't dig this one.
Oh, is this a bug in this map?
Are they all freaking out about this?
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, alert, 45 minutes remaining.
What about a time extension?
We talked about a time extension.
The one thing that's important about this whole stream here
is everybody has to give a five to seven minute tour at the end of this.
And I don't want to extend it too far because the people that,
there's some people from EU, there's people with time constraints today.
And I didn't want it to be like, oh yeah, like,
so this would be like a seven hour experience for all of you.
I don't think anybody even knows that you can do this.
See, what I'm really looking forward to is somebody kind of thinking outside the box.
You know what would be outside the box?
Keeping the whole house boarded up and making an incredible garden.
That's where you get creativity A plus for me.
Don't tell them that though.
Don't ever tell anybody that.
Why is the game so dark?
Because it's technically nighttime right now.
I don't know why.
I guess I could just reset it so you can see better.
That's inside the box.
No, that's outside the box because the house is inside.
That would be outside the box.
Let poke bill for an extra 15 minutes.
That's actually fair.
That's fair because poke is not scheduled to do his tour until a little bit later.
So that's fair for me.
That's fair.
So let's just go browser.
I'm just going to just teleport around just to get it back to daytime.
Derma explaining things is so funny to me.
Can you please help poke?
He's freaking out.
Poke need help.
I can answer questions.
I can answer technical questions.
Tech support.
Yeah, he's panicking.
There we go.
So it seems like most people have started outside,
which is fair.
But how many of them actually put grass down?
And what is their philosophy?
And what the fuck is philosophy?
I don't know.
I just put it there because I wanted to have four grades.
So I have mods.
I do want to bring this up because so when we do chats grade,
we're just going to do it in just solid letters.
So it's only going to be A, B, C, or D,
because that'll be technically that'd be 95, 85, 75, 65 points.
So we can't do like a whole scale.
I don't think I mean, maybe we could.
How many how many things do we have in the poll?
We could do A plus A, A.
I don't want to do that many though,
because it's based on points.
So I think 95 could be fine if you wanted to do an A.
Poke is trying to sell the walls right now.
Hey, give him a break.
He was at the aquarium.
Okay, he was at the aquarium.
So how poke could really spin this.
I don't want to give anybody any help.
No help, no help.
But there is an animal DLC.
And if you figure out how to use it,
if you can go back and maybe see how to do that,
he could make an aquarium
and just show us all the fishes that he saw.
I don't want to give anybody any tips though.
Yeah, we'll just do A, B, C, D.
And it'll do the point system will be to be 95, 85, 75, 65
for your grade.
I have a whole spreadsheet here to calculate everything.
So don't worry.
Vinny's doing his best.
Ludwig is doing something horrendous.
I can't, I cannot wait.
We're getting down there.
Let me just at least paint one of the walls.
Because people are going to be like,
well, what about your house?
What about your house?
And I'd be like, well, it's not my.
So let me get it to look at least okay.
The grading scale, the grading scale has changed.
I mean, poke is asking if other people scrimmed for this.
I don't think so.
A is now 90 to 100, not 95.
I'm going on a boomer grades.
Sorry.
And A, when I was in school,
an A minus was 90, 91, 92.
An A was 93, 94, 95, 96.
And I believe also 97.
An A plus I think was 98, 99, 100.
Yeah, A plus is 100.
A plus was 100, 99, and 98.
I believe 93 to 97 was just A.
We're not Americans.
I am.
And this is my American school.
This is my American house flipper school.
We're going by American grades.
Sorry.
97 is an A plus.
I think that's true.
He's American.
Is that what do you mean?
Yeah.
Wait.
All right.
Anyways, what about an S plus rank?
Now I like S.
I think S is a great addition to have.
But there's no S in high school or college grades.
Can we say poke's viewers are messing with him?
Poke's viewers are messing with how many minutes he has
and he is mega panicking.
Poor poke.
He probably was like walking around like,
wow, oh, look at that shark.
Whoa, look at that fish.
And he didn't even know that that 75 minutes had started.
He's probably sitting there like, oh, whoa, this is so cool.
He probably went to lunch, probably had a wonderful lunch
and just had no idea that he was being timed at the aquarium.
You've ruined his field trip.
You called all these people into work.
People are telling me he has four minutes.
All right.
Communicate with poke that he has 37 minutes left and longer.
He actually has 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52.
Poke has like another hour to make his house.
Poke has another hour.
Dude, he is soaking right now.
What do you mean?
He went swimming at the aquarium?
What are you talking about?
You can't.
Does this place have a pool?
Poke gets an extra 30 minutes.
I think it's fair to give poke at least 15 to 20 extra minutes.
Poke's title is in all caps.
You know, it's going to be really fun.
One of the reasons I did this a whole event is obviously
I'm just kind of walking around and just,
I'm just talking to you guys.
Like I'm the judge, right?
I'm just waiting.
There's a lot of content for him.
I just want to go watch everybody's stream.
That's what I'm going to do tonight.
I think like lying down in like bed
or just like on the couch or something.
I'm just going to go through and just pick out everybody's
and just kind of just sit there and watch how they did it.
This sounds fun.
All right.
Let's put some grass down.
It is turf, I believe.
Yes.
Oh, wrong way.
It's all right.
I can do both ways.
There we.
Vinny has one room.
Vinny does not know how to spell refrigerator.
Do we need to give everybody an extra 20 minutes?
Do we have to give everybody an extra 10 to 20 minutes?
If people are down, I am willing to extend by another 20 minutes.
But it depends.
People might have something to do today.
They need it.
No, no.
It's way funnier if you don't.
An hour goes by pretty quickly as you see,
especially when you know it's counting down.
All right.
Here's what we're going to do.
We're going to stick to the plan when it's pencils down.
What we're going to do is we're going to get everybody in a call
and I'm going to propose.
How does everybody feel?
Does everybody feel like if we could all get a majority
for an extra 20 minutes?
We'll see.
If not, then we might just go for it.
We might get three or four people that are like,
look, man, I've got shit to do today.
And that's all right.
It's got to be unanimous.
Vinny doesn't know how to spell refrigerator.
You spell it.
OK, how do you spell it?
How do you spell refrigerator?
Is there a quicker way to paint?
Yep.
OK, so when you are you in, are you inside or outside?
I'm inside.
OK, so you're inside.
You have the painting tool, right?
You you can paint because you if you did you did
you did the cheats to make sure that you did all the perks, right?
Yeah, I got them all.
OK, so you can paint three or four walls at the same time,
but there is no faster way to go with paint unless you go outside with the paint spray.
Oh, fuck.
That sucks.
OK, so you need to what you can do up to four walls at a time painting.
But yeah, you do have to paint the walls individually.
You do.
Oh, that sucks.
OK, that's fine.
By the way, there is 32 minutes remaining as of right now.
I think it'll be fine.
Thank you so much.
Just want to make sure you are aware.
Yeah, so the question that Connor had is a very good one.
It is OK.
So for instance, like Connor is asking is, can you go faster than this?
And it's going to be slow for me because I don't have all the upgrades.
But if you have all the upgrades, you can do a few panels at a time.
You can do I think up to four or five.
So but that's part of it.
That's part of your process is what's important.
I mean, it's just it's it's with all the upgrades.
Should be able to get at least most of a wall.
All right.
Refrigerator.
Right.
How do I do that?
OK.
Refrigerator.
How do you spell it?
Re.
There's no D.
It's just Refrigerator.
Really?
But that's how you spell fridge.
That's how you spell fridge.
So why is it Re?
Why is it not Refrigerator?
Why is it Refrigerator?
That's weird.
Fridge is with a D.
Can you do can you do turf in the house?
No, you can't.
You can't do turf in the house.
Sorry, everybody.
What colors do I want to do?
I should just do like a congratulations.
You did it.
All right.
I'm going to put like just like party stuff here.
Uh, like party, uh, like decorations.
Christmas.
Here we go.
Welcome.
Yeah, here we go.
We'll put like this everywhere.
Uh, we'll do that.
We'll do, um, we'll put like Christmas stuff maybe.
Here we go.
I guess your eyes are sucking my soul out.
Hey, you need to relax.
All right.
Um, by the way, I, I feel like people didn't look into this,
but there's a grappling hook to get up here.
It's all right.
I, I know they were under, they're under a little bit of stress.
This is a chainsaw.
You can get trees down faster.
Build a wipeout course.
Ludwig found the flamethrower.
It's possible he just ruins his whole thing then.
Don't tell him.
Ludwig might accidentally click the button and burn the whole house down.
And then, sorry, he already did that.
Oh, no.
Ludwig cannot find a certain paint right now.
There was some interesting questions because, so, the question was asked.
Hey, this is two stories, man.
That's a lot.
And I was like, yeah, it is.
Oh, all right.
And they were like, oh, okay.
But here's the thing.
Take a look.
You want to build the houses.
You can make this a whole thing.
I wonder who's the most focused.
I think they were anticipating it was going to be one floor.
If you want to do one really great floor, that's fine.
Your complexity and your structure will be suffering,
but your creativity score might be through the roof.
I looked at Lud's stream and I regret it.
Here's a really important question.
Has anybody cleaned their whole yard?
Has anybody cleaned their yard?
Most people did.
Hoke is kind of cooking low key.
All right.
Let's let it out.
Let's let him cook.
Doug Doug did that first.
Ludwig is eating a brick on stream right now.
That sounds pretty fucked up.
All right.
I'm going to make my bathroom.
I've never seen Ludwig this focused.
How much extra time should poke get?
Poke should get at least.
When did he come into the call?
When did poke come into the call?
What was the timer when poke came into the call?
It was 50 minutes.
So 50, one hour.
So poke should get poke should get 20 minutes extra.
Give poke an extra 20 because that would be the same time.
I think, I think that's fair.
25 would be the same.
We have to do.
We have to deduce five minutes.
We have to deduce at least five minutes.
The, you know, we got to give a five minute penalty.
I wonder if anyone's going to do anything outside.
I feel like everyone's just like, okay, I got to build walls.
I got to do this.
What am I doing in this house?
Okay, I want to build this.
I want to do that.
But does anybody make like a nice fish pond out here?
All right, let me do my bathroom.
You mean deduct.
I don't want to read chat anymore
because that's funny what you just said.
So I have to say it, but I, because I can't, I can't be,
I have to be unbiased.
Somebody said poke is painting his whole house right now
with a paint color called intense rust.
And I, I kind of have to delete that from my brain.
I have to pretend like I did not hear that.
I just, I have to just know.
I can't know that.
All right, let me get a door.
That's a good bathroom door.
I guess I could have typed it.
This is funny.
I'm having so much fun right now
because I'm just imagining everybody else's streams.
Is that weird?
I'm sitting here just kind of hanging out.
I'm watching imaginary streams right now.
I don't know how many of you guys here are doing the same thing.
Or if you're jumping around to see what people are doing.
But I, I'm watching imaginary streams.
I want, do people even know how to do what I just did?
Like the door in the wall?
Like in the inlet of the wall?
I'm not even sure anybody knows how to do that.
Connor is watching a tutorial.
That makes me, that's so funny to me.
I can't wait to watch everybody's perspectives later.
20 minute warning.
The mods are paying in everybody in the channel.
Could do Sims build invitational.
I think the reason why this was doing it for me,
the reason I thought this was funnier instead of the Sims
is because first of all, it's 3D.
It's a first person 3D game.
And this game is very kind of oddly complicated.
So you really do kind of need to know a lot of stuff about this game.
I did try to give a detailed couple of pages of information to people.
But even still, like I feel like there's some things,
like how do you put panels on walls?
I don't fucking know.
I have no idea.
Yeah, the one minute warning.
Yeah, once we get to 10 minutes, the Gordon Ramsay music is coming.
All right, this must be a bathroom.
We need bathroom.
Oh, I need a fixture.
They don't even know that either, do they?
Yeah, you need an actual fixture on the wall.
You need the thing that the toilet can actually sit in.
You need plumbing.
Do they know that?
Yeah, you'd like need this in the ground.
Does anybody know this?
There's no way they know.
No, they definitely do.
Okay, part of the tutorial I gave them was to do the first couple missions
to understand this, like what this means.
We might need like a 15 minute extension.
Well, I guess if you do type in toilet,
you'll see this and be like, wait, do I need that?
And everybody's chats, I'm assuming are yelling at them how to do this.
And they have to assemble it too.
I can't wait to see half of the shit that's just not even assembled.
Complexity and structure.
Oh, that's minus my own points for complexity and structure.
Ludwig is doing the Kubrick stare right now.
Can I ask, how is italics doing?
How is italics doing?
Is italics doing okay?
It's doing great.
How is Doug Doug doing?
Connor Eads Pants came in and asked a very specific question
about putting bars on the windows.
So I don't even want to know what he's doing.
Joel is losing his mind.
Vinnie, it feels like everybody's going insane.
Do the houses have to be livable?
No, no, that was not part of the criteria.
It was just make the best house, the most interesting, the most just build,
build a house that you want to build.
Does anybody have an exterior wall yet?
Does anybody, are they all like this?
I'm going to laugh.
So don't tell me, I don't want to know.
Actually, don't tell me if every single person has a fucking exterior
that looks like this, I'm going to laugh my ass off.
Don't tell me.
I actually, I'm going to wait till chat like settles down
because I don't even want to look over here
because that is so goddamn funny if everybody has the exact same exterior.
The same exterior concrete like paint.
I can't look over at chat until it's safe.
Do you know who's going to get a lot of points?
Whoever has exterior paint on their house.
Can we get a quick recap of the rules?
Absolutely.
There are 10, there are 10 people here.
There are 10 streamers.
Each one started at the same time with this house.
This was all messed up.
The windows were all boarded up.
The lawn was all dirty.
There was trash everywhere.
Everybody started at the same time.
They all had 75 minutes at the same time.
One, two, three, go.
They're all streaming their perspectives.
They have to build the best house they can in that time limit.
Well, except Poke.
Yeah, except for Poke.
Poke was here later, but we're good.
Everybody's here now.
So we're good.
Everybody's building.
Everybody is currently intensely focused.
There's 16 minutes left.
We might come to a unanimous decision.
When everybody is like, I need more time.
I need more time.
If it's possible, we might get a unanimous decision
to add an extra like 15 to 20 minutes.
We might do that.
It's possible.
At the end of this, each person is going to individually give me
a one-on-one tour of their house.
So we have Discord here.
We are Discord.
I'm going to, they're going to share their Discord screen with the game.
And they're going to walk me through it one-on-one.
I'm going to, at the end of that, about five to seven minute tour.
I'm going to be grading them based on a few categories.
They're going to be graded on, and these are 100 through 60, the point system.
Nobody gets an F because we figured that's kind of mean considering if somebody,
you know what I mean?
I don't want to be mean to anybody.
So we got 100 point scale, 100 to 60.
60 is the lowest you can get, D minus.
So creativity is one of the categories.
Complexity and structure is a category.
Cleanliness is a category.
Philosophy.
What was your philosophy with this whole thing?
That's a category.
And then at the very end, you guys are going to get a grade too.
Your grade is worth 10% of the overall grade.
Creativity is worth 35%.
Complexity is worth 25%.
Cleanliness 15%.
Philosophy 15%, adding up to 100.
There you go.
Philosophy is the vibes, bro.
That's exactly, you got it exactly.
If you've got a fucked up house and you didn't do the walls right,
but man, the vibes are immaculate in here.
The philosophy was immaculate.
That's an A.
If nobody gets an F, doesn't that make D the new F?
Probably.
That's only 95%.
35% plus 25% is 35, 45, 55, 60, plus 15, plus 15, which is 60, 70, 80, 90, plus 10%,
which is your grade is 100.
Trust me, I spent a lot of time on this.
This grading system was, I sat there for at least 15 minutes.
No, it was actually at least, I actually spent time on this.
I wanted to make sure this went off like, okay.
So there was some time putting this.
Have an F, but just don't give it to anybody.
Stop wasting time.
I'm not being graded.
I am here merely as technical support and as a judge
and to help you along the way understand what I'm doing this for.
And the answer to that question is for absolutely no reason.
Nobody wins anything.
Uh, the grades don't give you anything.
There's no winner.
It's just get some people together and make some fun shit.
That's it.
You should just leave the call and play something else.
Just don't even grade anybody.
Just be like, all right, later.
Turn my stream off and just like delete the tweet.
Every streamer right now is puking blood with stress.
Intense rust.
I hope, I hope all the cheats were enabled for everybody
because it actually would be very hard.
The reason why the timer is okay where it is
is because everybody should have all the tools unlocked and fully upgraded.
Because what you are watching, I do not have the tools upgraded.
Will there be a winner's build off after?
I didn't really think that far.
If I'll be really honest with you.
Just trying to get more than five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten people
streaming at the same time was probably the hardest part.
If you guys like this, if after this, this is over
and we do all the tours and everyone has a great time,
then why the fuck I would do it again?
A hundred percent get different streamers, different people.
This is just like people that I know.
I obviously would love to open it up to more streamers
and more content creators and stuff.
That would be a lot of fun.
There were a couple of people that I reached out to that couldn't do it
that I would love to see what they would do.
There are a couple, there are two or three people that are not here.
So I would love to see what they do.
Expand the torture.
And also to like, I want to like,
obviously include as many people as I can.
But I think I told you this yesterday, the day before.
I'm actually pretty, I'm not that well connected on Twitch,
on YouTube as much as maybe some of you might think I am.
But I would love to open this up to just have more people for sure.
Should I just do the whole house this yellow?
We're getting, it's getting down to 10 minutes remaining here.
It might be time to change the music.
All right, let's get, let's change the music.
What would be Hell's Kitchen?
Like music?
Ten streamers had exactly 75 minutes to build a house in House Flipper.
Unfortunately, only one of them will get the golden jacket.
We've seen some drama tonight too, as Poke showed up 25 minutes late.
This is where the part where Poke is in the chair and he's like,
I didn't, I was at the aquarium and I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I, I, I got a beep on my phone.
I had to get there and I got there pretty fast.
But what we don't understand here is what was happening over on Natalix's stream.
And like it shows him just like fucking smashing his fucking desk.
I'm not doing this anymore.
I'm not doing this anymore, Jerma.
Who's getting eliminated?
Nine minutes.
Where's the re-sounds?
Oh, that's true.
They should be here now.
Yeah, where are they?
Eight minutes before we get everybody in here to ask
the very important question of how are we going to handle this?
You should add sound effects.
I like, all right, I'm going to get up like the violin sound.
Okay, I know what I'm doing for the next 10 minutes.
Give me a second.
Okay, I got that one.
I got the theme song.
Am I going to do this forever?
This, there's 10 tours I have to do.
I don't, I can't do this forever.
Okay, I'll do it for every single one.
I'll do it for every single one.
At least the first like three.
We've got seven minutes.
Poke is the only one with a little extra time, but that's all right.
We do have a schedule of who's going when.
We're going to have to move the schedule a little
because Poke was scheduled for 3.20.
But I think we're going to have to move Poke
because Poke's still going to be, actually, might still make it.
I think he must, this might still be fine.
Okay, any other Hell's Kitchen sound effect?
How many sound effects are there?
Violin?
Isn't this the same thing?
It's the same sound, right?
Yeah, it's the same sound.
There's only one sound effect.
Just put Gordon Ramsay yelling at somebody in the background too.
No, that's too much.
Need a boom?
I need like a boom effect?
Oh, it's this one.
How loud is this?
This is so fucking loud.
I have to turn this way down.
This is at like 0.0 percent.
Five minutes, almost at the five minute timer.
Five minutes, five minutes.
All right, how loud is this?
Let's see.
Careful, this might be loud.
I'm just trying to get it through where I can.
That's really, it's not.
This one, all right, that's good.
Right there is good.
All right, let's get them all together.
So show me what you got here, Talix.
Well, see, I'm over here and this is my bathroom.
The bathroom.
Don't you think it's a little dirty, don't you think?
They're not, they're not going to be able to hear that.
The boom is too quiet.
We have less than five minutes remaining.
All right, I got to get my, so there you go.
I'm going to get everything ready.
Let me make sure I have my camera set up, everything set up
because I'm going to have to be doing through sharing screens
and let me get that set
because I want to be able to get right into it.
So give me one second.
I will be back.
You're going to see the screen is going to go black
and then you'll, I'll be back.
I think, I actually think I'm good.
I think I'm ready.
The question is, is everybody?
So we're okay.
Let me just warn everybody here.
This is a really important warning.
They're all going to get unmuted at the same time
and everyone's going to be probably complaining
and like yelling at me and saying like,
hey, do this, I needed more time.
Like, hey, dude, my house sucks or like, fuck you.
There's going to be a lot of fighting, I think.
So just be ready for everyone to unmute at the same time.
It's going to be hell on earth here.
Who do you think makes the first complaint?
Who complains first?
I think that's a good idea to figure that out.
Who is immediately the first person that we hear
being very mad at me or very upset?
Give minus 10 points to the person that complains first.
We have to be very, very attentive to this.
Minus five points to the person that complains first.
And not just like, oh, wow, that was so hard.
I mean like an audible like, like this was annoying.
You know what I mean?
Like an audible complaint.
There has to be some care and shit.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
Don't, and don't give it away either.
I was going to put it as far as they're great.
Minus five points from philosophy because of that.
That's right.
See, you get it.
You get it.
You understand now.
One minute is on the clock.
Now, I'm going to wait to play this
because I want this to play while everyone's freaking out
and yelling at me.
Final 60 seconds.
Here it comes.
Count it down.
What did you say?
Get the clock ticking sound from 24.
All right.
Here we go.
We got to tell everybody pencils down.
And if you're in their chats, tell them to.
When I start saying this, tell them to.
We're going on the honor system here besides poke.
Poke is the only one that gets a little extra time.
So do not do this to poke.
But everybody else is on the honor system.
We got 15 seconds.
Here we go.
Who's cuisine reigns supreme?
We will find out very shortly.
God, that hurts my head.
I didn't know it did that.
Stop. What's going on?
Who's doing that?
I'm being like electrocuted.
Is pencils down?
Pencils down.
Oh, we're doing that in the discord to tell everybody.
All right.
Pencils are down.
I've never been more stressed in my entire life.
Me too, man.
This is fucked, Jerma.
I got to say, I didn't realize how quick 75 minutes was.
It is pretty quick.
It sounded so long during the prep.
I was like, that's like 10 minutes per room.
It's like 30 minutes per room.
From learning the game while doing it.
Hold on.
So poke is still going.
Poke has been given special time because poke showed up
30 minutes late.
So poke is still building right now.
He's got about 20 minutes left.
Let me let me let's let's ask the group.
How are you all doing?
Do you guys want an extra 10 to 15 minutes?
So good.
I'll take an extra five.
Well, poke you are poke you have like an extra almost 25 minutes.
Yeah, you're good.
Use a little bit of time.
No, just to put those final touches on just to make sure it's just right.
I would actually like no extra time because I think everybody else
has messed up and I don't think five minutes will help me.
I need like 45.
So I selfishly I selfishly think that the people.
Yeah, some people could use five to 10.
I couldn't.
I need three hours to be held back by the baddies.
Yes.
Is it OK if I like went over by two minutes?
No, definitely not.
That's minus 10.
No, it's not allowed.
Poke poke.
If I put German, what if I put your dog in it?
Will that give me two points back?
I just want time to finish the shrine, you know?
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, 75 minutes is 75 minutes.
We had the confines of the time.
We should play within the time allocated to us.
You have to remain at the confines of the tortilla.
That's correct.
The only thing is poke poke poke you poke.
You should get out of here because you have like an extra 20 minutes to build.
All right.
I mean, I'm down to take the L.
You just want to take the L.
I mean, I'm not going to lose, but I mean, I can take the L.
All right.
You're certainly going to lose.
There's no take.
You'll see, man.
I got some crazy design.
All right.
Like minus two, minus two.
You get were you guys as stressed as I was?
Did you ask?
Oh, yeah, I was miserable day of my life.
Yeah, miserable.
God damn.
It's not easy.
So I'm really happy.
Everybody had a really good time.
I'm really glad to hear that.
That's not what we said.
Great times.
So thank you.
Thank you.
Everybody thought it was fun.
All right.
So here we go.
So how's it going to start?
We're going to go to you.
You all should have the times.
You feel free to stick around if you want to watch.
We did some discord testing.
I am curious.
So feel free to watch.
But the only thing is it will only be me and the other person in a one on one in this call.
But feel free to react to it and watch what other people did.
So the first one, Joel, it is you.
So, Joel, if you would if you could turn on your your screen on discord.
You see this?
Also, if someone needs to go earlier, I'm feeling a little bit better than this morning.
So I can swap if someone needs to get out of here faster.
We can figure that out in due time for sure.
If anybody wants to swap with italics where he is currently.
I'm chilling.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
So let me get out of this because I need to be able to capture this.
So let's get this started.
So we have about five to seven minutes.
The times aren't going to be exact.
I just don't want to I gave us a time constraint
because I don't want the people at the end of this to be waiting around for like two hours.
So let's get started.
Joel, you ready?
I am going to open yours up.
I have your audio through here, too, just to let you know.
So if you're going to play any loud sound effects, let me do this first.
Probably a good idea to quick save for everyone.
It is.
How do you how do you do that?
Yeah, I'll do you quick.
All that for Joel.
Oh, no, don't don't do that.
Don't do that.
How do you actually quick save it?
Okay, we are ready, Joel.
Hold on one more second.
I want to make sure I can see everything that you're doing.
I'm going to try to go to German stream chat.
Okay.
So this is Joel's view.
Yes.
Let me make sure I can see your whole entire thing.
Hold on.
I got to get it in the frame.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me just exit my game so I can hear this better.
I can get rid of the timer as well.
I can hear like somebody swearing.
No, don't worry about that.
Don't worry about that.
No.
Okay, move this.
I'm going to get out of my game.
Okay.
You can begin.
You can begin your tour.
I am here and I'm ready.
Okay, Jeremiah.
So the extensive cleanup that I did of this.
First of all, before we go into the house,
I'm going to make sure that you see all of my nice cleanup that I did.
There's no trash.
There's nothing going on here.
Okay.
And as you can see, it's all pretty damn good.
You know, and don't worry about that, but whatever.
So my point is I did a lot here to make sure this was going to be percentable and good.
Now, first thing you're going to see is a crime scene yellow tape.
That doesn't matter.
Joel, could you just stand still for one second?
Because the bit rate, your bit rate is phenomenal.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, you're going to have to go to each room and freeze for like five seconds.
Okay.
But everything could lower the FPS too.
That can help sometimes.
If you're like running native, the bit rate kind of suffers.
So a lower FPS streaming helps.
You can always just watch my stream.
I'm also streaming on my channel if you want to pull that up too.
But this is one to one so I can actually react with you.
I think it's actually good now.
All right.
Did you make a change?
Good.
No, it's all the same.
Oh, okay.
I think it looks all right.
Okay.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Okay.
So you see the yellow tape that says crime scene do not cross.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Now, what I did here is I made sure that even though my house is floss,
I made sure to point them out to kind of get a bit of a, you know,
like be aware there are some issues here since a trip password in here.
Sure.
Now, as you watch the bathroom here,
I did an interior decorating here that shows that I got a sense of humor
in the, you know, face of terror.
So I didn't install a toilet, but I installed a hole here instead.
Okay.
Or a bucket if you prefer.
I installed a poop knife for the willing and a plate of brownies.
Now, if you might notice, there's a picture of William the foe looking at you.
Yeah, I was going to ask you about that.
There's only to encourage, you know, fecal content.
But as you can see, yes to that, no to that, you know, be careful, be aware.
So that on the right, that's somebody defecating is what I'm being,
is that what that is?
No, it's art.
Anyway, anyway, that's a bathroom and it's a big window out here,
but you own this entire area, so it should be fine.
Anyway, that's a bathroom, you know, and in here,
I made it make sure to do a little thematic thing here.
As you can see, there's an alien in here and you go in here
and you notice, wow, there's a lot of going on.
There's a bit of a sci-fi theme.
There's a UFO in the ceiling.
Sci-fi theme.
Yes, but check this out.
Oh, all right.
I like it.
I like the, I like the radio.
Yeah.
What is on the radio?
I don't like aliens.
So, you know, say no to alien abduction.
There's a little cow being abducted.
There's some corn for the alien.
And as you can see here, there's the guy from Toy Story, Gary.
And you know, I got a little Gleeby Deeby guy and a toilet too.
But this is going to be playing throughout your house tour
and going to irritate you.
So I'm basically telling you that if you're impervious to migraines,
this is great.
But if you're not, then, you know, whatever.
But anyway, that's just the bottom floor here.
Now, I want to guide you out of here
because I have something very, very good for you.
Now, there's two options here.
You can check out the Amazing Maze or the hidden Green Gobbler Room.
Can we, can we go to the PlayStation 1 Green Gobbler Room?
You got it.
There's the Green Gobbler.
And as you can see, picture Willem Dafoe.
You go in here.
Whoa!
There's a little shrine dedicated to the man.
So as you all heard, Jerma Chat, Willem, William.
It's, oh, fuck, I fucked up.
It was supposed to be Willem.
Is that, what is, is that, is that Jack Nicholson up there?
No, that's Willem Dafoe.
Anyway, he died this year.
And I want to make sure that everybody remembers.
He died of gas.
So over here, there's the poisonous gas storage
where Willem Dafoe was turned into the Green Goblin.
There's an air conditioning unit here that lets you smoke the gas
to turn into Spider-Man.
You and I, we're not too different, Spider-Man.
I'm putting down a complexity grade here.
What I enjoy, let me stop you for one second.
I do very much enjoy the Green Goblin room.
I think it was a very good creative choice.
What I'm very, I think I'm upset with here is the fact
that that's Jack Nicholson's picture up there,
not actually Willem Dafoe.
And over on the right there, that's,
can you get in close to that, please?
Yeah, that picture there.
This?
Yeah.
Just get in real close and just stand still for a second
because I want people to be able to see this
as it offers a little bit here.
Yeah, that's, I'm going to give you a little bit of points
deducted from that because this is one of my least
favorite images on the internet.
So I'm going to deduct a few points for you from that one
for your philosophy.
I do like the vision.
I'm a big fan of the vision.
Anyway, we've seen it.
I'll take it.
So you can see here, there's the gas from there.
And once you've ingested the gas,
the mask starts talking to you
and you can stand in front of the mirror and it goes,
you know, Spider-Man.
So the entire green goblin room.
Yeah.
All right.
I think it's how much more of your house is there?
Uh, a little bit.
There's just two areas left.
Okay.
Quickly show off.
So that's a green gobbler.
I like it.
Want to show this off?
Put a little reference to, uh,
I don't have any.
Please don't deduct points.
I don't, I don't know what it is.
The pixels are trying so hard to put that image on the screen.
It looks.
Whoa.
That just like actually scared me.
There's another person behind me.
Can I interrupt real quick?
If we made it daytime, it probably would have helped.
That's true.
How do I do that?
Uh, if you exit and reenter, yes, leave it a bed.
I don't have a bed.
I think it's also because you are technically sharing from, uh,
from across the world.
I think that's another reason, but we know we can see it.
Burnt post maybe.
Okay.
Just checking.
Can we just listen to the audio for a second?
I just, can I get just into,
this is going to be a part of your grade because philosophy,
um, yeah, I want to turn your volume up.
I want to hear that.
Listening to that.
I think I got it.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay.
Anyway, quick thing here.
We had some problems.
Uh, somebody died, but it's okay because, you know, life and death
is kind of synonymous with each other.
And through death, life comes.
So we're growing corn here from it.
Oh, a garden actually garden.
Okay.
Yes.
And we, it's also solar powered.
So it's, you know, it's environmentally.
Healthy.
Okay.
But anyway, speaking of gardens, I made sure to include a little
puzzle because we all like mind puzzles, right?
So here's the amazing thing.
All right.
Wait, wait, can you, can you actually sleep?
Can you like reset your game?
Like just go to a different house and come back to this one.
All right.
So just go to back to your office and then come back to this house.
Make this your office.
Make office here.
No, yeah, make, make this your office.
Yeah.
Move office here.
Yep.
Okay.
Put the computer down.
Now go just leave here and come back.
Because I think we'll fix some of the vision problems that way.
Main menu.
Yep.
Just, and just come right back in or just like, yeah, just go to the computer.
Yeah.
Just reload it.
Reload it and then continue game.
Yeah.
You should be good to go.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Don't worry chat.
I made sure to save.
Well, also you could on Joel's stream too, has like the HQ high quality version.
So I can still get, I can still see what you're doing.
Watch the game crash now.
No, we're good.
All right.
So back over here.
Okay.
As you can see, laptop, the statement you missed, kind of.
I can, I can, I see, I see the, I see the vision.
I see the vision.
Okay.
Cool.
So we're going to move on here.
And this is the, this is the amazing maze, by the way, right?
It's all the grass, but I, you know, I'm going to open your stream.
Okay.
Yeah.
And you're like, my God, I have solved the maze.
Okay.
Jerma, Jerma, this is for you, buddy.
Cause I know someone has a special day coming up.
You've solved the maze.
You've done the brain puzzle and ladies and gentlemen, happy birthday, Jeremy, happy 60th.
We are so proud of you, buddy.
Hey, have a racing cake.
Thank you.
It is my birthday in months and months from now.
I really appreciate it.
That's right.
Oh, that's it.
And that's not how tall I am, but you're getting points removed for creativity for that one.
Because the short joke is I think, well, 60th birthday, well on its way out by now.
We are so proud of you.
But anyway, yeah, this is a little maze that leads to your personal pleasure zone.
Okay.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, go, go back to the table for a second.
And what, what is this?
This is a, this is a cake.
This is a little racing cake, buddy.
You like racing cakes.
Okay.
I actually, I'm going to, I'm going to pull you back a few points on,
I'm going to pull you back a few points on philosophy on this one,
because I actually don't really like raisins that much at all.
So that's, that's a blunder.
You like the spider though, right?
The spider is cool, but the raisins, I'm not a, I'm not a big fan of raisins.
Well, thanks for reinstating all my points, buddy.
You're my friend.
I cannot wait to go back and watch you do this.
Okay.
So we have a final area here.
Wait, there's another area.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
More, more, more.
There's a final area here that I want to show off, because Jerma, you like Twister?
You know, timeless game, right?
Twister, which game?
Do you like wall Twister?
Yeah.
I guess it would, yeah.
You figure this shit out because I ran out of time.
Anyway, as you can see, look at that.
Otto!
That's right.
Please give me 10 points for being so caring as a friend.
Anybody that has Otto in their house gets an extra two or three points,
at least on every category.
That's right.
And I put some Bop-Its in because, you know, I'm sure you like Bop-Its.
These are real Bop-Its, by the way.
What is to the right?
What is down there?
Is that like an air conditioner?
That's a printer because we all like to print shit.
You know what's wicked funny?
My printer's actually on the ground like that.
And you get points, you get points for creativity for that one.
All right.
My printer is actually on the ground just like that.
OK.
Now, I could prove it.
Check this out.
There's a bunch of spi...
Oh, oh my God.
OK, there we go.
A bunch of spiders in the ceiling, but don't worry.
The spider infestation problem is mostly resolved.
Cleanliness.
Well, don't worry about that, Jerma,
because we're about to go a little meta here.
OK?
Ready?
Ladies and gentlemen, beware of the Boggler.
And there's a little star reference there.
So, you know.
He's not here.
Doesn't matter because, Jerma, it's your streamer room.
You got your reddish shelf over here.
You know, check that out.
You got your whole thing.
You're eating a chicken egg, a tomato.
And you love that kefir.
Sorry.
Sorry, dude.
Tomatoes.
I'm sorry.
That's...
Yeah, but whatever.
That's fine.
But check this out.
It's nice milk.
And there's a big milk bucket.
And as you can see on the floor, it's infested with rats.
Friendly rats, mind you.
OK, they look...
That's cool.
What's that poster?
Can you get in close and just re-sperm it on there for a second?
This is the...
This is the flavors.
What's your flavor?
You are a gamer.
So, you like Seeds of Victory.
Cashews of Chaos.
Cashews, no.
Nuts of Destruction.
Definitely not cashews, for sure.
What's that one?
Gamer snacks?
Gourmet trail mix.
I actually don't eat very many gamer snacks,
but I do appreciate the fact that you're trying to make people...
Like and subscribe.
Well, you can't do that on Twitch.
And I pretty much only predominantly use Twitch.
And that's minus points for complexity
because my spine looked a little weird there.
Try to get your room right then.
It's a one-one recreation.
Now, we are on to the last room here of the tour, everybody.
So, I wanted to have a theme, various themes here.
And one of them was an OSHA violation.
So, as you can see, OSHA top 10 violations.
We're going to be cooking guns
and we're going to be using a sink here
and enjoy this sink drink.
Are those plenty of sharpies?
What's on the ground?
What's all over the ground?
Are those propane tanks?
Explosives?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Okay.
Well, as you can see,
there's some accidents here,
but we've got shotguns.
There's a toxic hazard.
There's a chocolate and eggs being cooked up too.
Chocolate and eggs.
And here's where it gets...
Yeah, it's good.
But here's where it gets interesting
because there's not only explosives,
it's radioactive.
It's radioactive.
And to really sell this house home,
Jeremiah, I just want to tell you one thing.
What's better than a baby with a gun
and peace near a fireplace with explosives?
I think there are quite a few things
that would be better than that.
I think philosophy might have to take
a little bit of a nosedive on this one
just because that's very dangerous.
And there's also somebody's
severed limb over there as well, I believe.
Is that somebody?
It's good, right?
I mean, if it's dangerous,
I don't know if good would be the answer,
but dangerous is definitely up there.
But you could put points for creativity.
Dangerously fun.
I see.
I'm feeling you.
I feel you.
Okay.
I think I'm ready to grade you.
I think I'm ready.
Remember.
Happy 60th.
We are going to go for creativity.
Joel, I think you actually did a lot.
There was a lot of time and placement
that went into this.
I'm going to give you, for creativity,
I'm going to give you,
because of the amount of objects
that you placed,
the amount of individual objects
that had to be physically placed,
you're going to get a 94 for your creativity.
Okay.
94 for creativity.
I think you actually did quite a lot.
I think it was very, very wonderful.
I think you did a lot of good placement.
I love the corn.
I like the fact that you actually did a garden.
Your complexity is also going to be a little bit high
because your complexity is in...
There was a full thought-out maze
part of this house,
which gives you some points.
The complexity of, you know,
Jerma's not as tall as his door,
I mean, and like, you know,
Green Goblin, it's not that complex.
I do appreciate the fact
that you did put a gnome next to that
to be able to show that I am, in fact,
over, you know, more than four feet tall.
That's unrelated.
This is unrelated.
And if you feel that way,
that's not deductible on points.
I'm going to give you an 80.
I'm going to give you an 82
on complexity and structure.
I think it was still good.
I think you get an 82 on that.
That's a solid B.
That's a solid B minus.
Your cleanliness was very good.
I don't see any trash in the yard.
Could you do me a quick favor, though?
Could you go to where the...
Go to where the...
Where's the garage?
Like the actual garage.
Yeah, I need like the garage
because I need you to go to the left of the garage.
No, actually, no, that's clear.
That's clear.
The spiders are going to take some points off,
unfortunately, because it's, you know,
you didn't clean that up beforehand.
Also, I think that having explosives everywhere
could be very dangerous and make a big mess.
I'm going to have to give you a 75 on cleanliness.
Okay.
I think that's a solid C,
considering that there were spiders everywhere.
There were rats everywhere.
It's not very clean, necessarily.
I mean, it's pretty complex.
It's pretty creative.
But I'm going to give you a 75 on cleanliness.
I'll take that.
Your philosophy and theming,
I'm going to give you an 86.
I think you deserve an 86.
I think that was a solid B.
Well, I'll give you...
I'm going to give you a 90, actually,
because you did have a pretty good theme here.
As much as I, you know, the Green Goblin,
you had a pretty good theme.
All right, it's time for Chat's grade.
Chat, what is your grade?
You have to pick...
It has to be 95, 85, 75, 65.
Those are your choices.
Joel, I think you did a hell of a job.
Those of you that opened up Joel's stream
would have seen the high quality version.
We got to see a good PlayStation 2 version,
which I think actually added to it.
So that's why I gave you more points for creativity.
And I think we can see what they want to do.
Can we get the poll going?
Adding your own audio track is a huge deal.
Your own audio track in the game?
That's how you got a 94 on creativity.
What do we got?
What does Chat want to give you?
Wow, Chat is saying A.
95 from Chat for Joel.
Joel, that brings your total grade.
That is worth 10% of your total grade.
Joel, you are at an 87.6 is your final grade.
That's a B plus.
Okay.
That's a B plus for Joel.
87.6 for Joel.
I just want to let you all know
that I'm very happy to be part of this,
you know, opportunity to show off
and not necessarily show off
in a sort of, you know, narcissistic way,
but rather, you know, show everybody
that my hard drive is running out of space
for some reason anyway, whatever.
My point is I worked really hard on this
and I think it's pretty good according to you guys,
which makes me very happy.
But this was my little attempt at making a house here
and I can't wait to see what everybody else has done
because I mean, there's so many people,
there's so many talented people
and I guarantee you this,
if you think mine is the best,
that's not going to be the case because, you know.
Well, we'll see.
Yeah, we'll see.
We'll see.
But I just want to thank you all for, you know,
looking at my house
and I want to thank the Boogler himself
for giving such a high, high ranking.
Honestly, the lower bit rate actually added to it for me.
It really did.
Oh yeah.
Thanks a lot, Joel.
Joel, it was a pleasure.
Thank you for showing your house.
It was phenomenal.
Everybody say thank you to Joel.
I hope you had fun.
Thank you, guys.
Coming up, we have...
Yeah, but if we want to talk,
if anybody want to say anything about Joel's house
before we move on to Seedog.
Is anyone else going to get the points benefit
for PS2 graphics in the Discord preview?
His house is perfect for the PS2 graphics though.
It really is.
It couldn't have worked better.
I think that's why...
Walls?
Wait, what do you say?
Nothing.
I just spent most of my time painting the outside of my house
and I realized I should have just put in...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Lud, Lud, Lud, I...
I'm a stupid idiot.
Lud, listen.
I used the paint gun and I grappled too, Connor.
I had to grapple.
He's so wrong.
He's such an idiot.
I'm such an idiot.
He doesn't know how wrong he is.
I should have hung spiders.
I don't have a single rat in my house.
Ludwig.
He had so many ill references.
It was so tight.
You're going to get so many more points
for painting the outside of your house
because it's your only fucking person that did it.
Just go check out Doug's house.
All right.
Seedog, you're up next.
Are you ready?
Oh, by the way,
we can change the quality here potentially.
Under your stream quality settings,
set stream quality to better text readability.
It might actually increase the bitrate.
Oh, is that on Discord?
I believe so.
And if you're streaming at the highest quality,
stream it at 30.
Is this Nitro?
This is...
Oh, it's a community server.
Everything's listed up.
We got HD streaming.
Yeah, so if we can do...
When you do your stream,
do it at 30 FPS rather than 60.
Try to go with the highest quality
and do that text readable thing at 30 FPS.
Should probably also have...
Who's the other person streaming in the Discord?
I can't see it because the dot-dot-dots.
Oh, just only have me do it?
Yeah.
So if you want to watch,
maybe open up the person's stream
that's currently doing it.
That makes sense.
I think just watching through JermaStream, yeah.
Yeah, that's probably the best way to do it.
Okay.
So Joel, you should turn your screen share off, Joel,
because we're moving on to Seedog.
So Seedog, did you...
Oh my God, I'm muted this whole time.
Oh my God, I'm an idiot.
Oh my God.
I was talking to you guys for like five minutes.
We heard you.
All right, are we ready to...
Can you see me?
I can.
Let me just make...
Let's make sure it actually looks okay first
before we move on.
Looks good, yeah.
Tell me how many P's is that?
Hey, it looks...
I was offering 101 of 100.
It actually looks...
It looks pretty good.
It actually looks good.
All right.
This looks great.
Okay.
So the Discord screen sharing
is kind of giving me a seizure,
but that's fine.
I can still do the tour and my chat doesn't see it.
So I'm fine to suffer.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah, because it looks pretty good.
We're good.
Just bear in mind that I'm fighting that for you
when you're grading.
I got it.
I got you.
All right.
Are we ready?
How are you doing?
I'm doing good.
Do you want to see the outside first?
Is that where we normally start on these things?
Yeah.
You are free to give me the tour
however you'd like to.
All right.
So let's have a look.
Let's have a look how clean the garden is.
You know, we've...
I've gone for a minimalist approach with the garden.
By minimalist, you mean you removed everything?
Well, yeah, but that's what I thought it meant.
So you took cleanliness as
get rid of every single plant.
Well, yeah, because there's stuff that lives in dirt
that's dirty, like worms and stuff.
So I wanted to get rid of the grass that they would live in.
Okay.
All right.
Show me your process.
I left the trees
mainly because I couldn't burn them down.
Oh, I could have cut them.
I didn't really...
I left them intentionally.
So you tried to burn them down.
It didn't work.
Okay.
I get you.
I thought if God wanted them there,
the flamethrower surely would have kept them.
You know what I mean?
Here's the thing.
It is clean.
Very extremely clean.
Not a single weed around.
Very clean.
Exceptionally clean.
Even the back?
Not nothing.
Okay.
All right.
There is some patches, but they just grew back over time.
I did actually get rid of these initially.
But this grew back.
This grew back in the time that you were doing?
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, it did.
It did.
Very clean.
Ignore the wall.
Yeah.
Looks all right.
I would have liked some shrubbery if it was possible.
I would have liked a little bit of...
I left this one in here.
Mainly because I couldn't remove it.
So I did leave that in.
Okay.
So are you ready for the tour?
I am ready for the tour.
I love how you're spending a lot of time in the outside.
What the fuck is happening here?
You've got the green M&M thinking about societal collapse and falls.
All right.
And I love how there's like the ad of the person
who actually like where you got that picture from.
So it's good credit.
You got credit there.
That's actually very thoughtful of you.
You can credit the artists here on this channel.
Okay.
We have an image of me pointing to the enter.
Oh, that's you at the entrance.
It's me in a maid outfit.
This happens a lot actually on my streams and content.
So I thought it would be a fun callback.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I have other...
So you actually you did an exterior.
I will give you credit for that.
You did a very elaborate exterior.
Yeah.
Sorry to interrupt you.
I didn't mean to.
I just wanted to...
Oh, no, it's your tour.
It's your tour.
Please give me your philosophy.
I need to hear it.
You are essentially the guy that we all are here to impress.
And I noticed that in a lot of my favorite countries,
they tend to have pictures of the guy in charge on walls.
So I thought, well, why don't I mimic that and have the,
you know, this is the biggest mural be of the guy in charge.
Right.
But you...
I'm going to give Doki a little bit of points on this
because you went less like Rembrandt painting
to show how interesting and amazing I look to
more like the guy melting at the end of Indiana Jones.
I think that's a little bit of a point deduction.
It was the first one that came up on Google.
What did you type?
What do you mean that's the first thing that came up on Google?
What did you type into Google?
It's the Japanese Google.
It's different.
It's a different Google.
All right.
Okay.
I'm feeling it.
If you tried it now, it wouldn't work.
Okay.
All right.
So, okay.
So I will preface.
Actually, no, you know what?
I won't.
I won't preface.
I won't tell you.
Okay.
Having that dog in me.
We blocked this off because I just didn't want it.
I was tired of doors.
What?
You didn't even put a door?
No, no, no.
There's a door.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's another door.
Can you get into the house?
That structural integrity is going to see you at least at a C right now.
Well, no, no, no, no, no.
You can get in the house.
Wait, you can get in the house?
Okay.
Of course you can get in the house.
What kind of asshole would I be if I made a house without doors?
True.
You know, I've been living in Japan now for a while,
and I've been concerned with earthquakes,
and I just thought that these doors here,
they were just a hazard waiting to happen.
So I blocked those off.
Okay.
I don't even know what this is.
I'll be honest with you.
I just put it up there.
Okay.
Was this like the first picture in like the folder of the meme folder you have on your desktop?
I asked the viewers because I didn't have time to get them.
I asked the views to send me memes,
and some of them aren't great.
Some of them aren't great.
Connor, Connor, you asked for memes?
Yeah, I didn't know we could put memes in the game until I got in.
It's true.
That's true.
I improvised.
Okay.
But creativity is going to see a little bit of a hit on that one.
Just a little.
It's creative because I'm going beyond my means, right?
This is left by the previous contractor.
This isn't me.
Even though it's the color of the paint of the outside of the house, you didn't do that.
I didn't do it.
The contractor left it there.
Okay.
Got it.
I see.
We got you.
They leave stuff all the time.
Right.
So why are you laughing?
This is serious.
Because this is not even a house.
This is just walls with giant like pictures on them.
All right.
Let's go.
No, no, no.
This is so much more than that.
Okay.
All right.
I'll let you go.
What I have.
Okay.
First of all, I find that the concept...
First of all.
All right.
Okay.
Wait.
Before you go any further, is there furniture in your house?
Yes.
Okay.
There actually is furniture.
There actually is.
All right.
Okay.
So let me...
Actually, I'm laughing too.
I can't present seriously.
So in the house, I decided that because you were talking about creativity,
you were talking about complexity,
I thought why not merge the two concepts into one
and take some kind of ideas from some of the properties that I enjoy.
So I decided that, okay, well, I'm a big fan of fun, elaborate mazes that kind of...
You think you're going the right way, but you're going the wrong way.
I mean, it's the whole point of a maze.
But I thought it would be fun because oftentimes in modern house design,
it's all about knocking the walls down.
I thought, no, why don't we put more walls, just so many walls,
that it's actually just inconvenient to live there.
But in fact, I did leave these here because I'm not a monster.
I want you to be able to charge your phone.
And then I decorated it with some pictures that I found.
Okay.
So...
So it's an anti-open concept room, an unopened room, you could say.
Okay.
So the whole house is a maze.
It's themed after kind of the back rooms.
Yeah, I painted the entire thing yellow.
Hold on, why is calm Nintendo music playing right now?
I thought you did that.
I was about to go, holy shit.
I was like, well, creative.
Wow, why don't we turn this corner?
You got your own audio like Joel.
I put that in actually.
Are you familiar with the brutalistic styles of Svavitch?
No, but let's continue.
So we're in the first hallway.
Yeah, where do you want to go in the maze?
Do you want to go forward or do you want to turn?
I would like to turn right because I see a little bit of a structural integrity
complexity issue up here.
What's going on here?
This is part of the frights.
I left this here.
That's intentional.
Yeah, I left this here.
I remodeled the entire floor.
I had to knock down all the walls.
I had to border off everything.
I got rid of all the windows.
They're all gone.
And I left this here as a kind of a keepsake of the previous owner,
who was kind enough to sell me this house.
I wanted to just have something.
Also, it's terrifying when you walk in because, you know,
the fact that you could scrape your head, boom, like that, you know.
I mean, I'm going to let you slide on that one
because that was an unbelievable bullshit.
That was unbelievable.
I'll let you slide on that one.
So you want to turn right?
I would like to turn right.
Would you like to keep progressing forward?
I would like to continue to go forward.
Yes, I would.
I would like you to stop and go back.
Okay.
I would like you to quickly explain what is going on with the wall on the left here.
Go like turn around.
What's happening on here?
This is a structural integrity complexity issue.
No, no.
So the, as you can see by the minimap, don't look at it too much there,
but it's just purely just here as you saw them.
I saw the minimap when you said that.
Okay.
All right.
I'll keep my mouth shut.
You can see that the entire design philosophy is to restrict the space.
All the time, everyone is talking about how much square footage.
No one's thought about how much square footage can I have
and how much can I make it useless.
So I think it's a fun concept to just start restricting space in an awkward way.
So now you can't even put anything here.
It's just inconvenient.
You're wondering why is that there?
I actually understand that.
I get it.
I'm just trying to get a little more of your video up.
There we go.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I would like you to turn around again.
Over here?
I would like you to go straight.
Okay.
I would like for you to turn right at the end of this.
I would like you to go in this room and I'd like you to just...
Okay.
So this is...
What was this going to be?
I don't know.
This is the whole point.
It's just like to signal that you've gone the wrong way.
Oh, but you didn't put like a piece of cheese down on the ground.
Creativity points deducted by two.
Why would I reward them for going the wrong way?
They're idiots.
This cheese is not on the ground.
That's deducted by two points in creativity.
You can clearly see that it's not painted.
Thus, you must not go this way.
Connor, there's no cheese on the ground.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Is there cheese in this game?
Let me pull up the tablet right now.
There's no cheese.
There's no way there's cheese.
Yeah.
There's cheese.
There's no...
Connor, I'm sorry.
I didn't see that actually.
Sorry.
Okay.
My bad.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have argued you there.
Well, I don't even see what your pictures were.
All right.
Go back and let's do the rest of this.
You've chosen the right way.
Congratulations.
Okay.
Thus, signaled by the banana cocktail-esque wallpaper.
I painted this entire goddamn maze, by the way.
You'll see this.
Okay.
This is painstaking.
I don't know what this is.
Just a meme image.
It's all right.
It's just a...
Yeah.
Like I say, it hurts to be in your house.
Why does it hurt?
I feel like my shoulders are...
I have to go like this when I'm in your house.
That's the point.
That's the point of the house.
Okay.
You're not supposed to be comfortable.
It's my house.
Get out of my house.
Okay.
All right.
Keep going.
So here's...
We have another meme.
It's sky raisins and jalapenos sky raisins.
Keep going.
Keep going down this hallway.
I would like to move forward.
Okay.
Would you like to keep going forward or would you like to turn?
I want to turn right down this.
All right.
Okay.
And keep going just through here.
All right.
We have...
Why is it getting tighter and tighter and tighter in here?
Yeah, I did that on purpose.
I'm trying to make it as little room as possible.
Okay.
I don't know what that is,
but you just keep going through that.
That looks good.
Okay.
This is Yoda.
The Yoda.
You got to get some creative points for putting Yoda in this.
I don't...
Is that pizza?
Is it a cat with a pizza?
Is it a peanut butter?
You left another paint bucket on the ground, Connor.
Oh, no.
That was...
He got lost in the maze.
Oh, Connor.
Connor.
Your complexity and structure grade right now is a 65.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's there on...
It just is...
We're going to...
I got to get your grades up here.
These are Joel's.
Let's clear those because you're at a 68 in complexity right now.
Oh, no, really?
Yeah.
The thing about this part is that it's a skill check
because as you can see, I just got stuck on it there
and you have to actually clip through it to get through.
You see I'm kind of stuck right now, but there we go.
We got it.
Okay.
So now you're in.
It's a potential skill check.
Okay.
So now this is the second time you've used this image.
I just want to make sure that's clear.
Third, actually, but...
Oh, third.
It is third.
It's an illusion.
So you come through, you're like, well, I just came this way.
There's no way this...
Oh, did I go the wrong way perhaps?
Right.
Okay.
Are you good to continue?
We are good to continue.
I'm getting my grades correct here so far.
Okay.
I'm good to continue.
What is that?
You can use that.
What does that mean, use?
What do you mean?
Press E on that.
What does that mean?
Okay.
All right.
I get it.
Oh, I can change it.
I'll change it to me.
There we go.
Oh, right.
I think that changes things a lot.
That stretched me in a comfortable way.
All right.
Your creativity is...
I got your creativity so far at a 72.
That's a C.
It's above a C, C minus.
I think you can really...
It's high, right?
It can go higher.
I just want to let you know that your philosophy right now,
I'm going to give you a 95.
And the reason...
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much.
The reason why you're getting a 95 in philosophy is because
you took this concept of walls and maze
and you made it your entire house.
I've yet to see a piece of furniture, by the way.
You will see furniture, don't you worry.
So we'll go forward.
And we can go this way, but there's nothing.
You can just stand here and contemplate.
You can also get a good view of this meme,
which says, I'll allow you to read it.
I look at the blood ocean sometimes and think, for real?
That's where the government is sending me in a windowless submarine.
As capital punishment for the greater good of the human race,
there is something outside...
I'm going to have to give you a 70 on creativity.
I couldn't even tell.
I couldn't even read what's going on here.
Okay, so I'll give you...
I'm going to drop the point.
Actually, I'll give you 71.
No, 73.
I'll give you 73.
I think you think I appreciate that.
So I can go this way, right?
Yep.
We also missed a completely...
This is the main branch.
I'll just spoil it for you.
Okay.
You can...
There was another branch as well that you missed.
Oh, show me, show me.
Please do, please do.
Yeah, yeah, it's...
Let me just...
It's going to take a minute.
Actually, I got to go through all this.
Hold on.
We do have about a 10-minute time limit for every contestant,
but it's okay.
But it's all right.
I think we can go over for a lot of these.
It's fine.
As long as everyone's cool with chilling for another,
30 minutes or so.
Yeah, this is the other part of the maze.
It's very clean.
It's extremely clean.
I mean, it has to be.
The whole thing is yellow walls.
It kind of has to...
You have to get a 100 for clean.
Well...
No other life form can live here, actually.
There's so much asbestos and paint.
It's actually a lot of harm.
I'm going to do the skill check real quick.
Hold up.
Can you not even go through your house?
No, like I said, it's a skill check.
So anyone real game is going past this point.
Oh, okay.
That's actually kind of cool.
Yeah, I think you're...
I'll give you...
I'm going to give you a 75 for creativity
because given a skill check,
an FPS skill check to go through your house
is actually pretty...
That's interesting.
Exactly.
Yep.
So we have another meme image here.
Okay, near on butt.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Is that Bernie Sanders right there?
Is that Bernie Sanders on the left?
No, this is Hide the Pain Herald in RTX.
It wasn't Bernie Sanders.
I'm just going to take a point out.
Would you have preferred it to be Bernie Sanders?
I just thought it was.
That made me laugh for a second.
Bernie's changed.
I had to change it.
And so now I really take the concept of uncomfortable,
you know, kind of an alleyways to an extreme here
by making it literally just...
You know, it's the limit you can actually walk.
I'm actually surprised you did this in an hour.
I want to...
Yeah, this is crazy, right?
You did this in an hour.
Yeah, I did.
I painted all the fucking walls.
I'm a psychopath.
I hate myself.
Yeah, you painted all the walls.
You really did.
You painted every single wall this color.
Yeah.
That's dedication.
It took nine hours, actually.
I started 10.
That's why I came on the call.
I was begging you.
I was like, there's got to be a faster way.
Please tell me.
There's not.
There wasn't.
So I'm very curious about what's up here on the right.
And I'd like for you to go open this right door.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
We got a Pepe image.
That's pretty cool.
Keep going.
The maze gets even more uncomfortable now.
Now we're just...
All right, go through the maze.
Go through the maze.
Okay.
Very easy to get lost.
Here we are.
Now we're in the...
Oh, I got lost.
Damn it.
Hold up.
Which way was it?
This way?
No.
No, this is...
I'm going back.
Okay.
No, I know.
That's the wrong way.
No, you're going the wrong way.
You're going the wrong way.
It's such a complex maze.
It's so easy to get lost.
Complexity is easily 100, I think, actually.
Complexity.
That's just my rating.
Complexity might have to go up a little.
Okay.
So there's a stair here.
And the best part about this stair, when you go up it,
it's purely aesthetic because it's completely useless.
There's nothing up here.
No, no, no, no, no.
There is.
There absolutely is.
Okay.
All right.
I like the aesthetic.
It's not going to change your score or anything,
but I like the aesthetic.
Okay.
What the fuck is this?
Above me, Scoob.
You got a Scooby Doo.
You got a Scooby Doo meme in here.
Take your philosophy down by a few points.
What?
It's the part of the film.
Okay.
So we go...
Now that we've finished this floor,
it's to signal that you're near the end.
All right.
So I decided to go for a blank aesthetic for the rest of the maze.
Okay.
Also, I was running out of paint and time.
Just...
Sorry, let me close this.
You didn't...
Okay.
So you go through now.
This is where the doors come into effect.
I'm trying to constrict it with a new method now.
What did you fucking make?
All right.
It's a new way of constricting.
So go through here.
Was that Final Fantasy?
All right.
Final Fantasy.
What is going on in this picture?
Where is the furniture?
Show me the furniture.
Show me the room with the furniture right now.
This is the final...
Are you sure you want to continue?
We give you a chance to end it all.
Because it can be tough.
This is the...
And also, I couldn't build a wall here.
But this is your final get out.
If you...
And also, you get stuck at the doors.
So you...
I actually kind of like that.
You made the haunted house thing where, like, if you want to leave...
It's like, no, no, you can get out of here.
Like, I'm scared.
There's an exit here.
I get it.
Okay.
I like it.
Are you really sure you want to see what's coming up?
Because it's bad.
Yeah, that changes things a lot for me.
So, you know, it's true to life.
And also, it's safety regulations.
We had to have an exit.
Okay.
So let's go...
Okay, you also get clipped on the door.
So you have to open them.
It's actually kind of...
It's kind of a great thing.
Because you have to consider...
I love how there's two doors that go to the same place.
Yes.
I thought it was more dramatic.
All right.
Here we go.
Is this the final room?
Okay.
There is another room.
Of course, there's another room.
But this is the prelude.
It says...
I'll let you read this.
All right.
Sometimes the side...
If you can't even a chick, it's C-Dog VA.
Scrump, Dill, Dumpster's, Dump Truck.
This is your live reaction to that.
Okay.
I'm going to give you an extra point in complexity.
I took some points down for creativity.
There's also this plant matter on the ground.
I'm going to read down on Glen Lewis a little bit here.
This plant matter on the ground.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
They're in jars.
So that's extremely clean.
Because we're not...
There's no dirt.
It's all self-contained.
Do you see any of the dirt outside?
Because I don't.
That's extremely clean.
That is pretty clean.
Because we need some oxygen generation.
All right.
What's the last room?
Let's see it.
Well, there's actually another door.
You just put walls up and put doors on them
and made a gigantic fucking maze.
It's the room.
It's a philosophy.
I had a hundred points.
There's the furniture.
It's one couch.
All right.
I'm going to have to...
Here we go.
No, no, no.
It's the casting couch.
Look, Shrek is signaling what could be happening here.
All right.
I'm going to have to...
I do appreciate the maze.
The maze is very, very interesting.
Look, if you were to tell me
I got an hour and 20 minutes to do something,
I don't know if an elaborate maze
would be the first thing I would do.
I would focus on building a room.
You don't have any rooms.
I built the back rooms.
You've got zero rooms.
You've got...
It's all one room.
No, no.
This is one room.
This is two rooms.
This is three rooms.
So I'm going to give you...
Here's my grades for you.
We're going to get Chad's grade.
Chad, if we could go ahead and get Chad's grades.
Remember, it's A, B, C, or D.
I'm going to look at what they're saying.
I want to see how they're feeling about this.
I feel like A, for sure.
Well, actually, there are a couple of As.
I've seen a few Bs.
It's A. It's got to be an A, at least.
There's no way.
What is Chad's grade?
You can't give anything lower than a D.
Sorry.
Here's what I got you at.
I got you at a 70 for...
I got you at a C for creativity.
Well, actually, I'm going to give you 75.
I think that you had a...
I like the maze idea.
I'll give you 75 for creativity.
I've got you at a 69 for complexity because...
It's arguably the most complex house that you'll see all day.
I mean, the amount of walls and redecoration and painting.
It's extremely complex.
I got you at an 86 for cleanliness.
I've got you at an 85 for philosophy because I do think you did have a pretty...
You had a good theme here.
You've stuck with the theme completely.
So, Chad's grade is...
If I may ask, the cleanliness, I mean, I find it hard to believe it's not 100.
Obviously, I disagree with your ruling on this, but I just...
Where were those 14 points?
Where are they going?
So, the cleanliness problem was there was two paint cans on the ground.
And the issue with the paint cans is you had a good cover for the first one,
but the second one was there.
Also...
It was a skill check.
I'll give you an 89 for cleanliness.
All right. Thank you.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
I think that works.
And then Chad's grade is nobody can get lower than a 60.
Conor, I'm sorry.
They have given you an F.
What?
Yeah.
An F?
What? They don't like the maze?
They didn't like the maze?
What are you doing?
I could give them an F.
How do they not like the maze?
Oh, I liked it.
Oh, my God.
Well, fair enough.
I swear to God.
Your overall grade is actually not that bad.
Your overall grade is a 75.6.
That's a full C.
For somebody that woke up at 4 o'clock in the morning to do this
and learned how to play the game an hour ago,
actually great fucking job.
Seriously.
That's actually...
You did really well.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
I'll take the C.
Overall of a 75.6.
All right. I'll take it.
I'll take it.
Thank you so much for judging me.
I appreciate it.
Thanks for waking up early for this, Connor.
No worries.
We're excited to see the rest.
That was fucking funny.
Thank you.
No worries.
All right.
That was C-Dawg.
The next person we have is RT.
RT is coming up here next.
Oh, is it myself next?
I thought it was until later.
Oh, did we...
Oh, no, we did swap you.
I'm just making sure that I can get around to everyone.
Oh, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, we swapped out.
It's Alex is here now, right?
I believe that's who's here now.
He's completely deafened.
Yeah, it's Alex.
There.
Hey.
He's clear to go.
Are you good?
Are you ready?
You want me to go?
I mean, I'm happy to go.
If you just give me one second here, I can set it up.
I'm good right now.
Are you good, Alex?
Are you good to stick around?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
Yeah, and we're trying to keep these around 10-ish minutes.
I know some of these are worth going around to.
So, I mean, whatever.
It's all good.
Everyone should get 25 minutes now.
Everybody should get 20 minutes.
Wait, no, sorry.
You can't limit the rest of us to like less time.
We have to make a bargain, too.
Sorry, my Discord completely crashed.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Well, it's Alex.
Are you ready?
I didn't mean to just be like put on the spot.
It's like, right, I'm going home.
I've got nothing to show.
No, it's a fantastic home.
Oh, I actually cannot wait to see yours.
But it's Alex.
You want to go instead of because his Discord crashed?
OK, I can do that.
And we'll get you back in RT later.
All right, Alex, are you ready to put your...
Fire away.
...put your stream on?
Let me make sure you can see it.
Somebody, we need to stop Poke?
Is Poke still building?
Poke is still going.
Did anybody tell him to stop?
He's still going?
He's still going.
Yeah, that's...
All right, cut.
Poke, if you can hear us,
Poke in yours, you need to stop building.
Poke, you need to stop building.
Poke, you have to stop building.
Everyone's been trying to get a hold of him.
He's just going.
We tried.
We pinged him like three times.
That's so funny.
All right, so this is Italics.
Yeah, can you see everything?
We can see and we are very excited, it's Alex.
The time...
Oh, hey, Poke, yeah, you have to stop building.
You said 30 FPS, better text readability.
Yeah, it looks good on our end.
OK.
All right, it's Alex.
Welcome to my home.
I went for the detail oriented approach
and we have a completely clean yard.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Restart, restart, restart.
Can you redo it and take away the text readability?
Because we might not need to do that
because like we're both on the West Coast.
We're good, we're good, we got it.
Starting over.
We got it, we got it.
So smoother video instead?
Yeah, I think as long as you don't have to do the text mode thing,
you just have to check that box.
OK, how is that?
That looks better.
Can you move around?
Hey, all right.
Looks good on our end.
OK, looks good.
All right.
So what do we got?
Welcome to my plot.
We've got turf laid down on the entire plot.
You won't find any weeds.
First of all, that's a full clap.
That's a full clap.
I can't believe you actually did this in 60 minutes, 70 minutes.
This is a 100% clean backyard.
Wow.
And I'll show you the corner as well.
The turf changes as it gets in the back, but it's still turf.
OK, so there won't there's no like there's no little ugly dirt spots.
We have a nice suburban yard that we can have the kids go out and play.
That sounds great.
All right.
So you're starting off at cleanliness at 100 right now, by the way.
And we tried to get a little custom with the house
and get some give us some paneling, give it some paint.
Now, let me take you inside.
So I just learned how to play house flipper yesterday
and I was under the impression that this is a house flipper competition.
So I have OK.
All right. That's oh, that's pretty damn good.
I have to tell you that's actually for complexity sake.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. All right.
You're it's Alex.
You're you're I got to listen.
I got to tell you how complex this was.
You're like a world first documented ability to do what you're seeing here.
It's not on.
How did you even get the furniture to go upside down?
Hours of trying to figure out how to do it after we did it on accident.
OK. OK. All right.
I'm feeling it.
I put in the training.
I put in the work.
I put in the preparation, but we knocked down all the walls
and gave it some, you know, a little flair.
You got you got a nice little sliding door.
So far, you and Joel, you and Joel had different walls so far,
except you might be noticing every season the same paint.
Everyone's got the same paint.
That's because it's landlord beige.
You know, it's just that's the start with.
OK. OK. Give me some more.
We got some water flowing uphill because this is the house that is flipped.
OK. And we got like a nice little dining area.
There's a piano here so that you can enjoy an elegant presentation
with your friends while you're having some food.
Beautiful. Oh, you even got the seats.
Did you do this through the whole house?
Well, yes, but you're kind of you're looking at the whole house.
The majority of the time was spent making sure that
all of the little details like the exterior were taken care of and clean.
It's it's extremely clean. Look at that sheen on the wood.
You have the first person to show sheen on wood, by the way.
So it took a long time to get all of the like we have a second floor paint job.
We got paneling on the first exterior, actually put in some some windows
and some sliding doors and like a proper front door.
Got a nice little seating area with a big screen TV and some speakers.
Is that an award on the table?
Yeah, that's my award for getting first place.
Oh, that's confidence.
Yeah, that philosophy.
I'm going to have to give you a 95 on that right now.
That's honest to God.
That's a philosophy.
That is a vibe.
And it's you're up very high right now.
I just want to make sure you know that.
Thank you. I appreciate being recognized.
Sometimes overconfidence can be a little bit of a downfall.
So philosophy is going from a 95 to a 93.
Look at the fish.
They can fill it with.
Oh, you actually can go upside down.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, do it again.
I'm sorry.
I got to apologize.
We presented the house in the wrong way.
I want to make sure I win the house flipper competition.
It's Alex.
I don't know if anyone's going to beat you.
I don't think anyone's going to come close.
If you'd like to sit and enjoy the TV or check on the neighbors
outside through the front window.
Yeah, that was I mean, I don't I mean, what do I do about this?
This is this was Connor's grades.
Hold on a second here.
We got you out of creativity.
We got you out.
I got you out of 95 for creativity.
I got you out of 100 for complexity.
I've got you at a 100 for cleanliness, although this can come down from here.
Well, the cleanliness can't go down because this is I can show you the upstairs.
That's what I'm concerned about.
It took so long to get all these other beautiful details just so that
I had to choose my focus.
That's true.
Just try to get the downstairs as much as possible in a very short amount of time.
But, you know, you've got like at least a urinals.
Oh, yeah.
Just that reveal I got.
That flip reveal is going to be living here.
You know, the urinals get dirty after a while.
So you want to be able to switch to the other ones.
OK, I like it.
My I didn't do this.
The sink is leaky.
This is just fault.
I'm taking this back.
Is it water damage underneath them?
It's still under warranty.
OK.
All right.
What is it?
Can you go up or down technically?
I can.
It's clean.
Oh, but it's just it's twisted that way.
All right.
Yep.
The majority the majority of the time was spent.
All right.
This was this was phenomenal.
I will have to tell you this is probably up and also probably number one so far.
But there is no number one.
We scared off the moles outside.
OK, we dug up all the holes.
Oh, there's no tires.
There's no weeds.
It is a clean cut all the way across.
I was told the outside is very important.
Where's the maze?
Oh, yeah.
Open the garage.
I want to see in the garage and I want to see every corner of the garage.
You didn't just put everything in here, right?
You didn't just put all the chairs and stuff in here.
No, you can you can actually put two cars in this two car garage.
Actually using for cars.
I thought there was going to be a very short.
I'm going to I'm going to emphasize brevity in my presentation.
You've seen it.
This is it.
I have the house flipped house.
I think so.
Chat, what's your grade?
Go ahead and give it A, B, C or D.
I'm going to have to go ahead and say that for your complexity,
complexity carries this the whole time.
I think that you being able to flip that and turn it the way
that was an unbelievably huge deal.
I think that one of the reasons why hold on.
Oops.
OK, one of the reasons why you're going to be up there pretty high
is because of the flip reveal, not just the fact that you did flip it,
but the fact that I and everybody watching it was built entirely upside down.
It was built entirely upset.
Center here was put upside down.
That was a phenomenal, phenomenal presentation.
You physically cannot do it without being upside down.
And the way that you get upside down is actually so secret
that it isn't even on the wiki for this game.
We discovered it on accident.
What do you mean we like I I practiced yesterday
so I could understand how to play the game.
You know, I got familiar with it.
OK, OK.
I thought you meant like somebody in chat told you to do that.
No, I flipped upside down and then we spent an hour and a half
trying to figure out how to do it.
Oh, OK.
All right.
That's all right.
Here you go.
Here are your grades.
You got a 95 for creativity.
You got 100 for complexity.
You get a 100 for cleanliness.
This is a very good.
This is a very good grade.
Your philosophy is a 93.
The only thing that I'm going to do here is I'm going to bring it down to a 90.
And I'll tell you one reason why the whole house was built around
and going upside down everything.
And there's no second floor and there's no basement.
And the garage is empty.
That's fair.
But I thought that having quality individual rooms would make up for
instead of having like a bunch of things scattered around.
You know, I went through quality over quantity.
You did, which is why you still get an A.
And you know, I'll make it.
I'll make it a 92.
So chat gave you an A, which is a 95.
Nobody can get a 100 that this is the cleanest yard you'll see today.
That is that's a huge deal, dude.
Because seriously, like having a fully clean yard with grass planted.
Big deal.
This took almost one third of the total time.
Yeah.
Your total final grade.
Congratulations, italics.
You are currently the head of the class with a 96.5.
I'll take it.
I appreciate it.
96.5 for italics was a hell of a job.
And nobody wins.
Did chat already vote?
Chat did.
They gave you an A.
So you're at 96.
96.5.
Well, yeah, I rounded it up.
But by the way, now that I've gotten scored, I can share my secret.
Yeah.
If you have cheats enabled and you type,
you don't even have to open a window.
You can just type it into the game.
G-R-A-V.
That's how you flip it.
That's the graph cheat that we discovered.
Before you go real quick, can you just give the philosophy
on what is going on with the red and the kind of metal here?
Because that's one thing that I'm kind of reconsidering.
Well, we were going for something that had kind of a classic vibe,
but you'll notice that it does match the interior a little bit.
Like we have this wallpaper here with the skulls, like the Day of the Dead type of skulls.
Everybody's calling you a cheater.
Yeah, that didn't work.
We're all cheaters.
Hey, I didn't say you couldn't.
I didn't say you couldn't do these things.
If anything, he spent the extra time to figure that out.
So that's the grade.
You got a 96.5.
I'm just a magician sharing my secrets so other people can enjoy.
Instead of keeping it to myself arbitrarily.
All right, we're ready for the next person.
Coming up next, whose house is next?
I believe it is Vinny.
Vinny, I believe you are next.
Thank you, Italics.
Congratulations for being head of the class so far.
I appreciate it.
Great job, Italics.
Yeah, hell yeah.
Do we want to get some...
Anybody else want to say anything?
I mean, we could do that too.
I mean, I don't know.
I want to make it extend for too long.
But what does the class think?
There was no maze.
I thought that was part of the criteria.
What was the maze?
Yeah, I was...
By the way, it's no maze.
I think he's really flipped the house.
Hoke, are you still cheating?
I think cheating is not fair.
Yeah, cheating is on its land.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to say something, Hoke.
Thanks for saying something, Hoke.
That's ironic coming from the person
who got like 30 extra minutes to build compared to the rest.
I used only 20 of those.
A genuinely 20 of those.
I was at the aquarium.
He was at the aquarium, everybody.
All right, it's all right.
We gave him the time.
I do absolutely love Italics' home,
but he is missing a complete second story.
There's nothing there.
Well, but hold on.
I'll be sticking around for it.
I'm not next.
I love it, though.
Hold on.
But remember, we're talking about creativity
is 35% of your total grade.
I mean, flipping the house halfway through
and doing a big fucking reveal.
That was a holy.
My expectations were not going there.
I gasped, you know.
I actually was.
That was amazing.
Yeah, I was just waiting for the maze.
That was the prestige.
But it was incredible.
I loved it.
Why was the bathroom not flipped like the rest of it?
Oh, the bathroom is not upside down.
They caught that too, but I didn't say anything.
The science is in there.
The science isn't there for the plumbing.
They won't let you put pipes upside down.
So I figured something was better than another.
I tried to put something in the room.
I love how somebody said House Flipper Drama is insane.
House Flipper Drama.
House Flipper Drama is insane.
House Flipper Community is going to be in shambles after tonight.
Hey, well, guess what?
This is the House Flipper Community.
We're literally all here now.
All right, let's get Vinnie in here.
So, Talos, thank you.
Thank you once again.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Chad, thanks for the A.
You're a real one.
Thanks, Talos.
So Vinnie, same deal.
I'm live, charm.
If you...
Yeah, make sure, Talos, you turn your stream off before I open this one.
And then, Vinnie, did you do the...
You know, I don't think you...
Because obviously, if you were in the United States,
I don't think we have to do the thingy.
Let me know how this looks.
I'm going to just look around and tell me if this is...
It's 30 FPS, but it should be kind of smooth.
Looks good.
All right.
All right, I am ready for you to begin.
I'm going to take your grades.
Let me just change this real quick
because these are not your grades.
These are Italics' grades.
Okay.
I will tell you when we are ready to get the tour.
Sure.
Okay. Vinnie, please begin.
Sure. Well, first of all, Jerma,
thank you so much for having me.
It's really just a pleasure to be here.
I would like to emphasize that I did not cheat
while making my house flipper house.
Okay.
And so what you'll be seeing today is legitimate.
Now, the yard isn't...
Am I getting subquitted right now?
I think we lost some quality.
Oh, really?
It looked good for the first five seconds.
Are you on 30 FPS?
Yeah.
Are you? It looks like you're at 60.
Let me try taking a quick look here.
It says 30.
Yeah.
You want me to go down to 720p or try 60?
Dude, take it down to 720.
I think the better reading mode worked pretty well.
Yeah.
Like, how do you do that?
I think if you did this a box, it's like,
see, just show text better.
It's like a checkbox you can do.
Yeah, I don't see that.
Where was I on this?
It should be on the drop down.
See how this is.
Oh, that's better.
That's better.
How we feel on this?
This looks a little better.
Yeah, I think this is good.
Yeah, I don't see it.
It's weird.
I don't see it in the drop down at all, actually.
Very strange.
I think this is good.
I think this is clear enough, I think.
Okay.
All righty.
Well, anyway, like I said, so yeah,
the yard is your basic yard.
It's just kind of, you know, natural.
It's just, I left it natural.
I gave it a little koi pond.
Okay.
Nothing special in there, but I can tell you the feature of the house is,
you know, we got some nice paint.
Let me take you inside.
So as you can see, I've got furniture.
You do have furniture.
I've got a picture of my family.
I've got my favorite ducks from Animal Crossing.
So you see, it's like a proper home.
I have, there's Simon Cowell and Howard the Duck.
So lots of important people in my life.
Okay, so this is more of a personal touch.
It is.
It's rustic.
I'm going for the rustic feel.
And you can see we even got a nice accent wall.
We don't go in this room.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Go back.
We don't go in this room.
What do you mean?
It's just, it's not a room I would recommend going in.
Open that door.
I need to see the whole house.
Okay.
Leave the, leave and close the door.
Don't show me that again.
So in here we have the hybrid kitchen and bathroom.
Okay.
So there's a shower.
So there's a nice carpet here for the bathroom kitchen.
You've got a nice toilet.
You got an iPad right next to the toilet.
Good.
You may need that.
I use it a lot.
Put that on the dishwasher right there.
Got some cabinets.
Urinal.
So when you're cooking and you're busy on the stove here,
you can take a quick piss.
Use your soap and go back to cooking.
And the carpet is just a really nice feature
because it just makes it comfortable.
Because when you're cooking and you're in a kitchen,
you're moving around a lot.
So the carpet really takes some of the,
some of the wear off of that equation.
I do appreciate,
I do appreciate the like the throw up color
that you have for the carpet.
That's very nice.
It hides all the,
it hides all the potential kitchen mess.
So you know, you spill shit on the ground.
That's fine.
And piss stains and the like.
So yeah, really, I think it's just a nice thing.
And it's really an underutilized concept.
The kitchenette, bathroom combo.
And also the Grey Leno show is the greatest late night show
of all time.
So then, as you know,
so I'll show you the upstairs real quick.
So, you know, I didn't quite-
Go back, how many times have we seen this image already?
Haven't we?
Which one?
That one.
Is, no, that's just like a type of image.
No, the one on the left.
Oh, that's just me.
Like put through a filter a couple of times.
I just thought it would be nice to have that there.
Connor, are you, you're watching right now, right?
There's a version of my face that has this same face
on his Japanese Google.
Yeah, not on Japanese Google.
Sorry.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I do like the, I love, before you say anything,
I love the wallpaper.
I think it's very fun.
Oh, thanks.
It's cool.
Yeah, there's definitely a nice vibe to the room.
I tried to find sand flooring, but I like this better.
I have some photos.
I was going to do a little photo gallery of the evolution
of our image together from acts like six years ago,
five years ago, to the most recent thing,
because we're buddies.
You know, me, you and Kraikin, we're good buddies.
Yeah.
And so anyway, this is my alien, Nortz, and he's smiling.
Here's the gamer chair, the desk.
Back to the gamer chair.
There's a gun next to the gamer chair.
I'm just, I'm just asking a question.
What do you want to know about it?
Why is there a gun next to the gamer chair?
Why isn't there a gun next to the gamer chair?
Okay, fair, fair, okay, okay, fair.
Um, here's the bed and, uh.
Why is there mirrors?
Surrounding, surrounding mirrors.
Well, this is, I mean, this is the implication,
really, more than anything.
Are you a vampire?
I mean, some, some would say a sex vampire.
Who, who can't see the vampires,
can't see the reflection or something?
Why would you have mirrors everywhere?
Wait a second.
Uh, uh, this is clicking right now.
This is clicking right now.
Um.
Cool.
But what do you think it is?
Are you, are these all here for you to-
So anyway, down this way,
I'll show you another, uh, cool, uh, feature of the house.
So, you know, there's toilets pretty much in every main room.
But then here we have, probably,
I don't know, the grimace room, you could call it.
There was an accident happened here.
But, uh, there is a toilet and-
We'll go back to the wall.
Go back to the wall.
That, that, is that, that's Mr., is that Mr. Dink?
Yeah.
Well, he's purple.
And I feel like him and grimace probably had,
like, something to do with each other.
I don't know what, but I'm, I'm trying to find out the connection.
Vinnie, Vinnie, I wanna, I wanna interject for a second here.
I do have to drop a couple points on philosophy and creativity
because I'm saying, I'm seeing a theme that,
did you paint the outside of the house purple
because this grimace room existed?
And that was the first thing you did.
And then you said, shit, I can't just make a grimace house.
No, I started with the grimace room.
That, yeah, that's what I, okay.
Yeah, I knew the grimace room would have to be, like, really important to the room.
Okay.
And, uh, we got the summoning circle here.
Well, it's more of a summoning cube, but it worked.
And so, uh, yeah, I mean, that's pretty much it.
I don't have anything of note to show you back here
because I spent a lot of time trying to get-
Can you go to the garage?
This all rustic and nice.
There's nothing in there.
But can you go to the left of the garage?
Oh, Vinnie, oh, Vinnie, Vinnie.
Oh, Vinnie.
It's dirty back there.
It's pretty dirty back there.
Hey, Jerma, can you take a look on Japanese Google real quick
and check, um, for a photo of you, if you wouldn't mind?
Anyway, so, yeah, the Mr. Dink connection is really,
oh, really interesting, isn't it?
That connection between-
I actually do like the Mr. Dink.
Oh, I forgot to play the dramatic sound from Hell's Kitchen.
Hold on.
Ah, this, you've got lots of dirt back there.
I thought that was the YouTube video that I just opened.
Okay, that was-
Listen, I'm happy that you're here in my house.
I thought that was a different YouTube video.
I just tried to play the-
Okay, all right, here we go.
Vinnie, good shit.
I liked your philosophy.
I thought your creativity was great.
I love the fact that you have your multi-kitchen bathroom area.
Fantastic.
I'm going to give you an extra point in philosophy on that one.
Your cleanliness could be a little bit higher.
I'll give you a 90 because it was just that one area.
But, I mean, actually, never mind.
You shouldn't have shown me that room more than once
because I forgot it existed in this blood all over the walls.
You got a C in cleanliness.
All right, so here you go.
Jack, what are you going to give Vinnie's house?
A, B, C, or D?
Because right now, Vinnie, you're looking at a-
Somewhere around a B, it seems like.
No, no, no.
Hang on.
Here, I was doing this earlier.
I'm going to play an A chord.
Oh, it's a little out of tune, but don't worry.
I promised you that was an A chord.
Wait, before you do this, go to your volume and turn the music volume down.
No, it's okay.
Wait, if I say no to the host, does that minus points?
No, no, you're good.
You can disagree.
All right, what do we got for a chat grade?
Ooh, they're being pretty nice to you.
Thank you, Chad.
That's really kind of you.
Listen, I'll take a B.
That doesn't matter.
But I'm just happy that I have a house that has furniture in it
that isn't, you know, upside down.
Because listen, I wouldn't want to live like that, would you?
I don't know.
And I'm really happy that I can sit on my couch and chill
and watch a little tiny TV over there.
And then if I need to go to the bathroom,
I got my iPad here.
And then I can also cook while I'm in the bathroom.
It's really, really nice.
Saves a lot of time.
The iPad gave you extra points, by the way.
Be curious.
All right, what do we got?
We are at, you are getting,
the vote is pretty much locked in at this point.
Although a lot of people want to give you an A,
but it seems like the class is going to give you a B.
So listen, it is a tough act to follow.
It's Alex, you did something amazing.
House, whether or not I, that's a tough act to follow.
Vinny, Vinny, I think you might be pleasantly surprised by this grade.
You got an 83.8.
I'll take it.
You got a solid B.
That's a solid B.
I'll take it.
Very nice.
Very clean.
I like the philosophy.
Thanks.
Excellent.
If you could hit escape and go to your options
and turn the volume down on your music.
Turn down.
Oh, there you go.
All right.
Can we get, anybody have anything to say?
Yeah, I think you got robbed.
I think that was easily an A house.
I agree.
I loved it.
Thank you.
I quite appreciate the crime scene and all the blood on the walls.
Like, you know, it really adds something unexpected in your home.
You know, Jeremy, if we have a private room, do you,
is it really your right to barge in there and start looking around?
Oh, shit.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
If we have a private room.
I'm sorry, Vinny.
He didn't want that to be seen.
How come they didn't do like a New York City box apartment?
What was the maze, actually?
No, I'm sorry to say there is no maze.
I enjoyed your maze.
Yeah, no maze.
Yeah.
There was a maze category.
I also added an image of Japanese Google,
just in case you were confused in the chat.
You can see it.
Cool.
All right.
So we got, who's up next?
Yeah.
Thanks, Vinny.
It was an awesome job.
Thanks for coming out.
I'm going to get going, too.
So have a good one, everybody.
Good luck.
Bye.
Thanks, Vinny.
Take care.
Later.
Vinny's a good lad.
All right.
Who's up next?
I think it's either Polk or Ludwig, right?
Who's, any of you two need to dip?
You want to get it over with or?
I'm ready.
Oh, no, no.
Yeah, Kraken, it is you because you do have to dip.
Yeah, Kraken has to dip.
So why can I still hear this music?
Is this from my camera?
Oh, it's Vinny.
Vinny's still live.
He's like still doing it.
So we're going to tell Vinny to, all right.
Let's tell Vinny that he has to stop screen sharing.
Okay, there we go.
All right, Kraken, are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's just do a quick little move around test.
I think it looks all right.
Okay, we are ready for Kraken's house.
Take it away, Kraken.
Welcome, everyone.
Yeah, this is my house.
Yeah, first time in this game.
So, you know, learned a lot on the fly.
And I know the first thing you're thinking is,
yeah, you know, compared to some of the other yards,
this seems like it's a little bit messy.
This is kind of dirty, Kraken.
This is very dirty.
And you'd be right.
But also, what if I told you it was intentional
and that some of this trash was left here
with a very important message?
Okay, well, I'm going to have, honestly,
I'm going to have to start you out at like a 60 for cleanliness
just because of what we know so far,
but I'm willing to change it.
And that's all I'm looking to hear, all right?
Just, you know, open mind.
And that's that what you see here, huh, a fallout shelter.
Are you saying that maybe something like
this world that we're in is kind of a post-apocalyptic one,
per chance, and maybe there is like some mess out here
left from, you know, the fucking fall of humanity?
Okay.
Have you thought about that?
I have thought about it.
I'm also thinking about potentially you
forgetting how much time is left and just going,
oh, shit, there's a lot of trash outside.
I have to pretend I have to come up with a story.
Or maybe this was the point all along.
And let me welcome you inside too.
Are you familiar, by the way, with the whole,
you know, Barbie movie, Oppenheimer,
kind of, you know, double feature thing
that's been going on the internet, very topical.
Everyone's all looking forward to it.
I know that the Barbie movie is coming out.
And the Oppenheimer movie is coming out the same day.
Oh, it's coming out the same day.
All right.
Okay, I get it.
I get it.
That's the whole thing.
So I thought, what if we made a fallout shelter, right?
Because Oppenheimer, that was themed after Barbie.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, let it come.
All right.
We're still percolating here.
So welcome on in.
This is the first room we have.
And you'll see that there's each room in this house is themed
after a different, just kind of fun concept, right?
Something that I think Barbie would enjoy
or you'd want in a fallout shelter
should the Oppenheimer bombs fall, you know, at any minute.
So this is the first one.
Any questions?
Feel free to ask.
I have one question.
And it is, did you and Vinnie use the same wallpaper?
I don't think he used this one, did he?
I will say there's a good chance this wallpaper.
Yes.
No, we did use the same.
You'll notice there's more than one wallpaper in this house.
And that's because, like I mentioned, each is a different theme.
And so this is the neon room.
Okay.
We have a little TV here, like, you know, TV Mike from Willy Wonka.
What happened here?
And hop over this.
Well, this is the fish room, as you can see.
So we have a little fish here in the corner.
And that's it.
Now we can move on to this is the love room.
This is the love room.
Yes.
Yeah.
We got fairy lights.
We got some chocolate and...
Is there a reason why the chocolate and the lights
are not on a structure of any kind?
Like on a table?
Yeah.
We only had one of those nets for the fish.
Okay.
Turns out it takes a lot of time to keep adding, you know,
furniture.
And it's better to focus, in my mind, on the philosophy and the spirit of a room
than on the actual, you know, amenities.
So I can do something real quick for me right now.
Just very quickly.
Yeah.
Take out your mop and mop the floor for a second.
That's the floor, baby.
That's just what it looks like, guys.
Yeah.
This was by design.
I appreciate you checking, though, that my lovely floor was not dirty.
Okay.
Definitely didn't hurt.
Well, speaking of amenities, this is the snow room.
We have a friend and snow is cold.
So we have a, you know, a fridge, which is also used in fallout shelters
to escape bombs like in Indiana Jones.
So I love it.
I love the snow room.
Great.
Moving on, we have this is the neon room.
And over here in the corner, we have my little rat friends.
They have their water bowl and a nice little bed.
Of course, we keep our cool.
We don't want them to get out and make a mess.
So we take them out one at a time.
Something happened with the wallpaper back there.
There's some wallpaper issues I see.
There's also some structural complexity issues.
I think that are maybe bringing a little bit of the points down.
Go back in this room and look to the right.
Oh, you mean?
Yeah, I'm seeing a little bit of snow tends to blow, right?
And so I just thought it'd be kind of fun to show
that it gets around the house sometimes, you know, in the right mood.
Speaking of, look, we can fill the rat's cage with food.
That's a cute thing, right?
Look at that.
Honestly, first person to incorporate an animal like an animal enclosure.
We've seen a couple of rats,
but we have not seen an actual animal enclosure yet.
So I'm going to have to give you some points.
They have comfortable space.
Moving on, we have now we're entering the dog room.
Good dog.
Can I stop here for one second?
You started this with a philosophy of 95
because you told me at the entrance that this was a Barbie Oppenheimer house.
Did that change in your process?
Give me your philosophy on this.
Did that change halfway through?
May I counter you with this?
Does Barbie not have a dog?
I don't know.
Does Barbie have a dog?
I don't know either, but probably, right?
So this is the good dog room.
I was thinking of all the fun things
that Barbie would like to have in her playhouse, you know?
And so I couldn't find many props related to dogs.
So I do have a nice dog light down here,
but that's all we got.
So over here, every good house needs a toilet.
This is an outhouse that you put behind this?
Yeah.
Well, we didn't have plumbing working,
so I did have to just kind of drill a hole in the wall
and throw the outhouse outside.
We also have the piss buckets for the overflow.
Oh, those are pee?
You're not getting higher than a 60 in cleanliness.
This is not happening.
I'm sorry, Kraken.
We have buckets for them.
They're not on the ground.
I can show you the broom thing again if you want to confirm,
but they aren't, you know.
I'm going to give you some points in creativity
because that's actually funny,
but you're not getting higher than a 60 in cleanliness.
It's just impossible.
Just wait till you see the rest of the place,
and I think maybe you'll be changing your tune.
Okay.
Speaking of cleanliness, this is the plant room.
I know you said that you were excited
that there was a garden from one of the earlier contestants,
and I thought, what about if the garden was inside?
And also, in case the zombies come,
this is, again, a fallout shelter at the end of the day,
and so we have an ammo box and machine gun just for guarding the place.
You know what I think would really help stop an intrusion by zombies?
It's having full walls.
I think that would help
with maybe a weapon aiming from a different floor.
So I'm going to have to give you a little bit of a doc on that.
Now, what if I threw this out there?
Plants versus zombies.
I gave you a point in philosophy for that.
All right, great.
Moving on, this is the Mexico room.
We have kind of the Day of the Dead theme with this garland and little skull,
and then over here, a full-on spooky guy.
I just really want to make sure that each room here felt like its own world.
Its own world, just like the Barbie in the Oppenheimer movie.
Now you can see my vision.
Then I got back on track with the theme of the Oppenheimer thing
with like a kind of a like a generator, gas generator, right?
Some boots, which you would probably need in the wasteland.
Moving on, we have a cute cat portrait that I found on the shop
and just couldn't help but put in the very cute in my building.
Yeah, it's very cute.
This is the brooding corner.
I was really with the guns.
Everybody has like a gun with a chair.
Well, you would you naturally hang your gun up when you, you know,
are like kicking back and just reminds you of your own mortality like Oppenheimer does.
That movie I believe is going to be a bit dark.
So I thought a nice little brooding corner would be good.
This little spider over there though to keep it keep it light.
And then this of course is bringing us to the end of the tour,
which by the way, I don't know if you noticed this was a maze the whole time.
I was gonna say, where are the doors?
Somebody said, does Barbie not have doors?
The doors were made because as I mentioned, someone, me,
this is their first experience with this game and first built the walls.
And then later didn't realize the doors were a thing until after,
you know, using the sledgehammer tool.
But I think it adds to kind of the rustic feel of, you know,
finding your way through a maze, right?
You sort of did the reverse of, oh my God, mom and dad are coming home.
We have to clean up the place.
So you kind of did like, oh my God, mom and dad are coming home.
We have to build a fucking house.
Yeah.
And that's how this is what you could come up with.
That's kind of that's pretty accurate.
I also think though, there's some cool parallel, you know,
comparison of the rats, right?
Rats in a maze.
And then here we are in a maze.
And so that's probably worth a couple of points.
You know, is this 90s themed?
Is this 90s themed?
This room, yes.
This room is kind of timeless, I think, though.
So, you know, take that as you will.
All right.
Finally, though, we got to go to the we got to go to the upstairs.
See, because I want to see upstairs.
Well, feast your eyes on the point of this whole maze.
All about good vibes over here.
And so what is better than good vibes, especially at the end of the world,
at the the apocalypse of time?
We know toilet paper is going to be the most valuable thing.
So I just wanted to kind of pay homage to that and have kind of a nice,
you know, denouement, if you will,
kind of wrapping everything up here as you come to the top.
You did get a point in cleanliness because of the toilet paper there.
So there's one point in cleanliness.
You got a 61, a 61.
Great.
Well, I'll take that.
All right.
Can you look at the ceiling?
OK.
Look down.
I just was seeing what was on the ground.
If you had anything, was this default, the default floor on the ground?
Well, I think since I went through a lot of effort
putting up wallpaper on literally every other wall,
I really I kind of thought the ending being a more
minimal kind of, you know, good vibe room.
OK.
Would just would just kind of tie the whole thing together and
you know, I didn't want to overdo it.
Can we get chat?
Can we get chat to give a grade of this house?
What do you guys think?
A, B, C, D.
We don't give F's here.
All right, Kraken, I can tell you what I got over here so far.
I got you at an 80.
I got you an 85 for creativity because you really pulled me in
with the whole Oppenheimer Barbie house.
Yeah.
And I dropped some scores elsewhere because it turned out
that that was just a bait and switch.
And you you grabbed us.
And unfortunately, if your whole house had been a Barbie house,
it probably would have been a lot higher.
I just I'm just going to be completely honest with you.
Although the philosophy of you making individual rooms
and individual spaces that were completely disconnected
from each other did have to take you some time.
And you stuck with that philosophy.
So I'm going to you got an 87 for philosophy.
Wow.
Thank you.
You got 76 for complexity and 61 for cleanliness.
Chat has given you they're still deciding,
but it looks like they're going to give you a C.
Oh, all right.
Well, question.
Where is the rest of the upstairs?
Oh, wait, wait.
Yeah.
Where is the rest of the upstairs?
So rather than leaving a empty room that kind of felt unfinished,
I opted for let's just kind of box it in.
What does the outside look like?
Can you go out to the outside and look at the exterior?
Chat, you got 75 from chat.
Your total grade.
Actually, all right.
You got a 78.4.
That's a C plus.
Hey, almost a B.
All right.
I'll take it.
I will say you hit the nail on the head with the Oppenheimer Barbie house
kind of being abandoned halfway through for the multiple room thing.
That's exactly what happened.
That's what I figured.
I started with that vision and I thought, oh, this is going to be great.
And then kind of got carried away, I believe, with each of these rooms.
So, you know, you hit the nail on the head there.
And I think if I could go back, I would have just done.
Hey, honestly, your first thing.
Philosophy, you beat at an 87 for philosophy.
You were on the right track.
It's just timing and first time playing it.
I completely get it.
That's a good job.
It was very wonderful presentation.
Very wonderful house.
Everybody should be clapping right now, please.
Thank you, Kraikin.
Thank you.
Yeah, this has been a pleasure.
Anybody have anything to say about Kraikin's
a themed house that became unthemed after 20 minutes?
Yeah, I got a lot to say.
A lot to say.
You got a lot to say.
First of all, fantastic job on the Maze and Corporation.
Thank you.
Really.
Thank you, founder.
Why, when you knocked down the wall, Jerma said, whoa, at an empty room.
I just, what the fuck was that?
We just said, whoa, at an empty room.
What was that?
Well, I, because I didn't know the empty room.
It was very strange that he was able to hide this from me so well.
Actually, it's kind of strange that he built a wall.
Oh, we got maze drama.
He hid it from me.
All the mazes.
You two both made mazes.
You guys both made mazes.
Look, it was not empty.
There actually was another toilet paper behind the wall in case you lose the first one.
There's a second one.
I just saw it in my comments.
I apologize then.
Additional toilet paper.
Yeah, there's an Easter egg.
Your outside is very dirty.
Out of everybody, I know it's part of the theme, but you have the worst outside, I would say.
And I mean that in the nicest way possible.
Open the garage, please.
There's no nice way to say that.
I did clean this side, though.
Look, Vinny, okay?
Oh shit, you did clean that side.
I don't know why I cleaned that corner, but I did.
What's in the garage?
It was a very enticing corner to clean, I agree.
I will, Joel.
Joel is the only one really that actually utilized the garage.
That's true.
This is true.
Joel is sitting at an 87 right now.
All right, are we ready to move on?
Now it's either Polk or Ludwig.
I think it's...
Who do we got?
I'm ready.
Polk is ready to go right now.
And Ludwig will be right after Polk.
Polk, how are you?
Great.
How are you?
I'm doing fantastic.
I'm so glad you're actually here.
I'm so looking forward to your house.
I'm really happy you actually got to be here for this.
No, I really thought it was tomorrow.
But no, this is great.
Dates, times, it's hard.
It's easy to get it all messed up, right?
I checked the time.
I didn't go over.
I think I didn't cheat, so we're good.
We gave you time anyways, because make it fair.
Yeah, I cheated a little bit.
Well, Italic flipped his whole house upside down, so it's okay.
Let's open up your stream.
Can you just move it around for a little bit so I can see?
It's a little bit ready to turn around.
I think it's okay.
I think it's all right.
It should be good.
Let's just double check it.
How do you guys feel?
Can you give us a full circle?
Yeah, we're good.
Looks good.
All right, Poke, take it away.
What do you got?
Hi, and welcome to my house.
I opened my door.
This is my beautiful house I worked on.
This is my first time playing, too.
I had no past experience.
On the way here, I woke up my roommate.
He won on my PC, did everything for me, the tutorial, everything.
And I just took over, and here's what I got.
Let's take a look at the outside.
The outside is a little dirty, Poke.
It's a little dirty on the outside.
I didn't really have time to clean the outside.
It's not about what is out anyways.
It's about what is inside.
I think that matters.
Can we start with the garage?
Do we have to?
Kind of, because I want to see if there's anything in it.
Do you hear the sound, by the way?
I hear the sound, yeah.
All right, so cars can fit in here.
I mean, it's good.
It's clean.
You can fit cars if you really wanted to, you know?
So I went for like a lime green design, you know?
And if people look at, I mean, since the house isn't really done fully, you know,
what's wrong with having a few placeholders, you know?
Are these other houses?
Is this what the house could look like eventually?
Is what's on the exterior?
I don't know.
I mean, those houses look great.
Whatever houses these are, they look phenomenal.
I mean, it just messes with your imagination a little bit.
It's like an optical illusion.
So here's, let's just go in the front.
This is the front of the house right here.
Wait, this is the front door?
Yep.
You know, let's put some music on.
So I went with like a, I went with like a, like a airport, you know what I'm saying?
All right, so you made an airport in, okay.
Give me the philosophy on that.
I mean, when you're rich, you can really do anything you really want.
And this is for the people out there who just want to get what they want, you know?
And some people want a Willy Wonka house.
Some people want a fact, you know?
Some people really just want an airport.
I would want an airport.
Oh, can you elbow the city player?
I think there's something wrong with it.
I think it's skipping a little, okay?
Now, this is, we're all streamers here.
We're all streamers here.
And I made sure to make one of the houses really relatable to all of them.
This is the streamer room.
Now, I didn't have any photos on my PC.
I only had sponsor photos.
So these are just, these are the different sponsors you've had throughout the last year?
You have one of those banned lawn chairs.
The most uncomfortable, those things make sweaty red fucking marks all over your whole body.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to take some points off of that.
Really?
They make sweaty red bands across your whole body.
It's horrible.
But I'm gonna have to give you some points with complexity though.
Your score is very high right now.
There's a triple PC set, people have dual PC setups.
And here, this house, we have the triple PC.
These are all three individual computers?
Yes.
Okay, interesting.
Can you pump through like multiple games or are you trying to do multiple streams?
It's to stream the streaming PC.
Okay, what do we got on the wall?
So these are TVs?
These are all just TVs.
Ah, cool.
Now, here's the kitchen.
Raj's doors.
Or your doors.
Yeah, I mean, we all learn from Russ, you know, how to really protect yourself.
And why would you not want to like, like, you know?
Yeah, I thought I did, what did you, where'd you get the flashlight from?
It's music.
All right, wait, wait, turn, turn back around.
I, what, this is just a picture of, who's that a picture of?
Just some inspiration to get like, just get back to work.
Got it.
You know what I mean?
I do like the wallpaper in here.
It's, it's very creative.
Thank you.
So, can I see, what's the painting on the wall here?
On the, this, this side wall?
If you turn to the left.
It's a window.
Oh, that's a window.
Oh, that'd be beautiful yard.
Every house needs air.
Well, turn around, let me see the beautiful yard again.
Turn around, look at the yard.
Yeah, to the right, where, where that is.
Yeah, that looks, that's exactly what that looks like on the wall.
Now go back, go back inside and take a look out.
I just want to.
Oh, I mean.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Oh, you mean like here?
Yeah, it does, it does.
Yeah, that's what it looks like.
It's transparent.
It's weird that the lake is like kind of an optical illusion,
kind of like a mirage sometimes.
That's weird.
It looks good though.
Let's go upstairs.
Yeah, let's take a look upstairs.
What the fuck is that?
We don't want to go down there.
What is going on down there?
All right.
This is the realtors, one of the realtors son.
Oh, okay.
I like it.
I do appreciate it.
So the floor, Vinnie and Kraken had this on their walls.
So it's really nice that you actually made them rugs on the ground.
Yeah.
I think that's a pretty good philosophical reason to do that.
Thank you.
I couldn't find any lights.
Wait, that's a.
That's what came up when I searched for lights.
If you're wondering, these don't turn on either.
Do you?
Okay, poke.
Very important question.
Do you have a bathroom?
Yes, I'll get there right now.
Some music.
So here's the bathroom.
Oh, like behind you or this is the bathroom here.
Where do you go to the bathroom?
If I have to piss, where do I go?
Um, I fucking can't.
All right.
So what is there?
Is that a security camera?
Well, you want to have safety and that's the actual design of the room.
Is going that way.
What's in that room?
Yeah.
All right, you're gonna have to get an extra few points for that.
You have to get a few points for that.
You actually tricked me.
Okay, you get a few.
You get a few more points for that.
Uh, I'm going to bring complexity down a little because there's no room there,
but I brought your creativity up.
All right.
What?
What is it?
What's the say on the wall?
Room room.
Okay, so you've got and what's that?
Is that a photo of Ninja?
I don't have nothing on this PC.
So Connor did also by sort of.
I can't talk.
I can't even hear myself.
Connor did a similar.
If you stand that way and then open it, it won't hit you.
If you go.
All right.
Yeah, go just turn all the turn off the.
Yeah, because then we can talk.
Is that question mark to signify the Riddler?
Well, that's just to really, you know, I don't think the image loaded.
That would make sense.
It's probably an area.
What was supposed to be there?
What'd you say?
Honestly, one of the other photos, probably Ninja.
Okay.
All right.
Light the question mark.
It looks good itself.
Obviously, brutally honest.
I mean, I think it looks great.
No, what is the solar?
Oh, that's the solar.
Okay.
I thought it was a cell tower.
And honestly, this, this is for like the rich who just want to throw off burglars and stuff.
Imagine you came in and where would, you know, you'd have no idea how to get there.
It would throw me off because it did throw me off because I actually did not know if
it was a real room or not.
So you got me.
All right.
Is there anything else for us to see poker?
Is that, is that pretty much it?
Honestly, that's all I was able to figure out.
All right.
So I'll give you the grades, the grades that I have for you so far.
I really did like your airport philosophy.
The reason why your philosophy is so much higher is you have a 95 in philosophy
because I'm getting inside kind of your head a little bit here because you're you get back.
You're like, fuck, I'm 30, 40 minutes late.
I need to do something.
I'm going to do an airport.
And it's like, no, you know what?
Fuck it.
I'm going to change it from an airport to like an anti-burglar house.
And then you're like, fuck it.
I'm just going to put garage doors everywhere.
You, you were like up against the clock and you made it happen.
And the philosophy of you making that happen and adding these comedic elements
is what puts you at a 95 for philosophy.
Unfortunately, unfortunately, unfortunately.
Sorry, I was waiting for a sound effect.
Sorry.
Your, your, your cleanliness was pretty much zero.
It's very dirty outside.
It was filthy out there.
It looks like you took a little bit of less time.
And this trash, that's a trash bag right there.
Well, that's not a trash bag.
What is that?
Oh, I thought that I thought that was a trash bag.
OK, but anyways, that's it.
You got a, you got a 60 for cleanliness.
It was very dirty.
And I dirty enough where I can overlook it.
I would probably give you like a, maybe like a 65
because of if you just go outside and just take a look around.
This paint cans, this wood, the flamethrower ran out.
Yeah.
And like the scaffolding is still there.
Basement.
Everyone's saying go to the basement, go to the basement.
Can you show us the basement?
Chad, let's get a grade.
Chad is currently giving you an A.
So we're going to the basement.
Oh, optical right now.
Oh, OK.
Optical illusion is pretty sick.
Yeah.
I, yeah, I think you nailed it.
I think you knocked it out of the park.
It just was very dirty.
So that's going to hurt your grade a lot.
But Chad has given you an A, which is a 95.
Yes.
So we here's where you stand now.
You stand poke.
You had a creativity of 95 as an A complexity of an 83.
Now, the reason why I give the, I just,
the big paintings on the wall.
I mean, you said you even said it yourself.
You didn't even know what images you had on this computer.
So yes, that's I got to bring some points down for that.
So that's an 83 for complexity.
Plus having a garage door for every single door is it's,
you know, it took us a while, you know, to open them.
And then they're very loud.
But your philosophy was a 95.
Your cleanliness was a 65.
And Chad gave you a 95 with the grand total poke.
You're a grade in total with this music in the background.
You're probably going to be pretty close to being at the top.
If I'm honest.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
All right.
So you are at an overall grade of 87.5, which puts you, Joel had 87.6.
Oh, wow.
It was, it was the cleanliness is what killed you.
That's worth 15%.
No, I'll take that.
Damn.
80, 87, 87.5.
Nice job.
Thank you.
I loved it.
Yeah.
What did you do?
Is that as another sponsor?
I don't even, I don't remember this.
I think so.
Yeah.
It was actually.
All right.
What do we have to say about this one?
This is very good.
We have some thoughts.
I would not want to raid this house.
It would take way too much gunpowder.
Thank you guys.
I love the painted on doors.
It's so funny.
The garage having to wait for the garage doors every time.
Oh, my God.
It's torture.
Like the idea of like each of the,
the first two notes playing from each individual radio that is in every room.
Did you put that?
Did you put that in or is that just there?
Yeah, I, I, I looped up.
I just shortened the song.
Oh, you took that.
That's so funny.
Oh, my God.
If you were upstairs in that home and someone's at the door,
you probably wouldn't make it in time.
I don't think anyone is.
No one's by the way.
I love that you painted the whole outside of the house.
This experiment green.
This took half the time.
And it's, it's all splotchy.
Look how splotchy it is over there.
The inside of the house was the last 10 minutes.
I had no idea what I was doing.
That's so funny.
Can I give a point?
Can I like do a zero decimal one extra point friend point?
Because it's so good.
Okay.
Can I like, you know, give points?
Do you want, you want to, you want to step in and stamp on a point one point?
Because we're like, you know, we're like tight, right?
There's so much more.
I want to see everyone else's things first.
Let's, let's see everyone else's.
Okay.
Let's see everyone else's.
I appreciate you though, man.
Damn.
Thank you.
Everyone else is doing great too.
I want to see, I want to see Ludwig's.
Yeah.
Lud's up next.
Lud is up next.
So we're going to thank you.
All right.
Oh, thanks a lot, dude.
It was awesome.
We'll see it.
We'll see how it plays out.
All right.
Ludwig, are you, are you ready?
Yep.
So Ludwig, I do have to tell you very importantly, there is, you did get a minus two deduction
to philosophy right off the bat.
I'm sorry.
Because we, we had a thing with the, when I unmuted everybody,
the first person to complain was the one that was going to get minus two points on their philosophy.
And I think the first thing you said was like, fuck this.
This was stupid.
No, I didn't say that.
I would never say that.
I forget what you said, but it was very funny.
But I am, I'm, I'm willing, I'm willing to scrub those points being deducted.
Look, it's fine because I think I'm going to score 100 in philosophy.
And so a 98 is still an A plus.
Really?
Okay.
You, you'll double it.
Give it to that person.
So you're really confident.
Yeah.
Because most of my build sucks.
I mean, I do not have the expertise of other people.
I do not have the, the cleanliness of other people.
Okay.
But philosophy is what this whole build is based off.
And, and, uh, Jerma, I'm, I'm getting up there in years.
I turned 28 this week.
Um, yeah, happy birthday by the way, if everybody didn't know.
Thank you.
Uh, it's, it's, uh, it's stupid.
Uh, and if this was a low score, it'd make my whole year shattered.
But, uh, what I want you to focus on is history.
Okay.
History.
You know what they say about history.
You know what they say.
If you do not learn from history, it is doomed to repeat itself.
Got it.
You ever heard that?
I have, uh, many times.
Oh yeah.
That's me that said that.
And, and, uh, and so today we are going to do an homage.
Okay.
To H. H. Ohms.
Do you know who that is?
I don't.
Well, I'll, I'll show you.
I'll show you.
Cause, cause first and foremost, um, he's an American.
Okay.
You hear that music?
I cannot hear the music.
You don't hear like the national anthem playing?
I don't, I can put the national anthem on over here if you want me to.
No, you're fine.
You're fine.
Okay.
Oh, say, can you see by the dawn's early light?
This is our American garage.
Okay.
Uh, and, and it's where we are starting our story today to explain who H. H. Ohms is
because at the end of the day, this is a history lesson for you to learn to not repeat what was
done in the past.
Starting with the garage.
Already a good start.
Yep.
Starting with the garage here.
So H. H. Ohms, uh, was an American, uh, and I made this garage to dedicate, dedicate to him.
Um, oof.
Oh, you just blew it up.
No, it was a, it's an explosive entry.
It's like, oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me actually do a little bit of, you didn't have sound turned on.
All right.
Okay.
I realized now that I didn't.
I okay.
I still don't have sound on.
Okay.
I volume down.
Yep.
Thanks.
Thanks, Connor.
Stop talking to me ever again.
Thanks.
Sorry.
That was Connor.
Um, uh, can you even still hear it though?
I think it's sharing to my screen.
Hold up.
I'm resharing.
Reshare?
I'm stopping streaming restarting.
Okay.
Restarting share.
If you pull the actual game.
I'm back.
There you are back.
There we go.
We got it.
Can hear the birds.
Yeah, there we are.
There we are.
This is our American garage.
Red, white and blue filled with the American flag.
Of course, uh, we have our, our turrets, um, which is going to come in handy a little bit later when
we, when we learn more about H.H. Holmes, who again, you don't know about, right?
That is a brand new person.
I don't even know who that is.
Great.
Brand new person.
Love that.
So let's, let's talk more about it as we enter the backyard and you can see here.
Look at the walls, right?
Paint it all the way through.
Looks really nice.
Yeah.
Um, uh, do not enter.
Ooh, okay.
No, no doors.
No doors on the back.
It's nope because the house was a confusing design because H.H. Holmes.
Jeremo, this is where I should, uh, tell you he was America's first serial killer.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yep.
He was America's first serial killer and he operated out of Chicago during the Chicago
world fair.
He, uh, fell into some affluence through his family and through killing the leader of a
pharmacy and taking over said pharmacy and through that was able to create the murder
castle.
I love it.
This feels like a book report, Ludwig.
I'm going to tell you histories.
It doesn't repeat itself.
Yeah, go on.
Uh, we're here.
So the murder, the murder castle and, uh, uh, much like this project was developed very
quickly by many different developers.
Uh, and for me to emulate that, I took suggestions from my chat.
Okay.
To, uh, to create this.
So, so you'll notice the, the long, uh, winding narrow halls.
It's like a G mod map that hasn't put head textures put on it.
Uh, white all the way through.
Very clean.
Mind you.
It's very clean.
I will say you're starting at a hundred paint everywhere.
No spots missed at all.
None.
Yeah.
None at all.
Um, it's a maze house though.
It's, it's, it's, it's not a maze.
So that's, and that's, and I knew you'd say that because there's been a lot of
maze houses.
They haven't there.
There have been there, but there've been at least two.
The terrifying thing about HH homes is he would,
we love mazes.
Well, no, this is not a maze Connor.
I'm not, I'm not like you.
That'd be crunch.
Uh, HH homes use several different contractors to make his house.
That way no individual except for him knew the layout of the home.
He would then use it as a hotel during the Chicago world fair that people would
stay at.
And from the second floor, he would have a trap door to bring people to the first
floor.
What is that?
Okay.
That's from my hero academia.
What does it have to do with?
Did you hear what I said, Jerma?
Yeah.
But what does that have to do with HH homes, my hero academia?
Well, don't worry about this.
This is just to show the explosiveness of the trap door, bro.
All right.
That's pretty cool.
That's actually pretty cool.
Okay.
I'm going to have to get, we were starting a little bit high here.
Yeah.
You use the environment to make something happen.
And I'm going to, you're actually pretty high.
I thought it was just, I thought it was just a white house at first.
Okay.
Do you got me?
That would be embarrassing.
You got me here.
I'm actually here now.
You got me now.
Well, let me get you the hook then.
Yep.
The way HH homes would kill all his victims was by having them go through a trap door
into the basement where there'd be eaten alive by rats.
Really?
That's terrifying.
Yeah.
That's horrifying.
Your cleanliness just went down.
Horrifying.
10 points.
Well, it's a trap door.
It's the rat room.
They're located within the rat room.
But there are rats in your house.
So we have to be fair.
But it's in the trap door rat room where you're supposed to kill people.
So it makes sense that the rats are here.
What's that on the-
Whatever.
What's on the wall there?
Can we find us?
This is, if looks could kill, you know what I mean?
Okay.
So this is where, this is where, so you could be, is that a poker table, blackjack table?
What's over there?
What's the philosophy for that being in here?
I figured the rats would get bored.
And I wanted to put a poker table for them to play poker at.
Okay.
All right.
Jerma, this is, this is, I hope, an eye-opening
about the dangers of the past and how not knowing them could make them happen in the future.
And what I want you to understand-
Are you gonna kill me?
What does that mean?
I'm just teaching.
This is educational.
It's educational.
All right.
And I just, I want to teach you to just be wary in the future.
If you ever go to a hotel, make sure it's from a reputable source.
Okay.
Because you could end up in H.H. Holm's murder castle.
Oh, sh-
That's the end of the tour.
Oh, all right.
Shit.
Okay.
That's, that's the whole tour.
I spent most of the time painting everything white.
Everything was white.
We have a few questions.
Yep.
Yeah, please, please, go ahead.
Two, I have a few important questions.
Number one.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Where's the bathroom?
Uh, that's a great question.
The bathroom?
Let me bring it to you right now.
Right here.
Okay, so you did-
Okay, so this is a bathroom.
This is-
This is the toilet bathroom.
Got it, got it.
Okay, I do appreciate the fact that it's outside.
Can you go ahead?
Just give me, give me the outdoor look again.
I want to-
No trash, no, no bullshit's here, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no bullshit here at all.
You know, I cleaned up the entire yard.
Chopped down the trees in the front.
I thought they were a bit tacky.
Okay.
Some weeds grew back just because the game was open.
But, you know, they were, they were gone earlier.
I, I've-
So here's what I've got so far.
I like the fact that you did the garage.
A lot of people just didn't even-
You, there's only two or three people that even
stepped foot in the garage, it seems.
I do appreciate the fact that the garage is done.
So, Chad is going to be grading your house right now.
I'm going to give you my grades that I have so far.
And you can argue with me if you want.
We can go through it.
I have you create-
I wouldn't dare.
So creativity, I got you at an 85.
The fuck?
85.
Sorry, um, what, why?
85-
Why do you hate me?
I got you to creativity 85 for a couple of specific reasons.
One.
Okay.
I like the philosophy.
The philosophy is actually where you're going to get some points back here.
Because you, you took, you took a theme and you,
your whole house is a gigantic, I got a gigantic history lesson.
That's really interesting.
I gave you a 93.
I gave you a 93 for, for philosophy.
You also-
Okay, and that includes the minus two?
You have 91.
So it's a 95.
You have a 91 in philosophy.
Oh.
So I forgot to do that.
Just a moment.
I apologize on my turn.
I want to just point out that if you go to that basement, right?
That's like the garage, right?
And you flip it upside down.
Can you show them, can you show them what we have in the basement?
Oh, the garage, sorry.
Can you flip it upside down?
How do you, how do you flip it upside down?
How do you, how do you do that?
Flip it, can you flip it?
How do you flip it?
Ludwig, Chad is giving you, Chad is giving you an F on your house.
How do you flip it, Connor?
Flip it.
Oh, you keep saying flip it.
Flip it, flip the, flip the house, flip the house, do it.
Is it like a command?
Am I doing it?
G, GV what?
Oh, you're flipping the house to see what it looks like upside down?
He's asking me to flip it.
I don't know how to flip it.
Only Italics knows how to do that.
He's the only one that knows how to do that.
Grav?
Okay, look.
All right, close, close the garage door.
Close it.
Okay, sure, sure, sure.
Yeah, how do you flip the house?
Grav.
All right.
How do you do that?
You have to be inside.
Okay, I'm inside the house and then I type in Grav.
Okay.
Ludd, you had a great intro.
You had your intro.
You were like informed.
You were ready.
You had your history.
You didn't rattle by Connor right now.
What I'm trying to say is this is not an American room.
This is a hidden French room,
which is everything that America doesn't stand for.
If you flip it upside down, it's just the French flag of a room.
There's no stars in the room.
There's no stripes.
Where's the stars?
It's a French room.
Where's the stars and stripes, Ludd?
It's red, white, and blue.
Where's the stars and stripes?
And look on the outside.
It's a hidden French room.
You, I can't stand.
Look at all the stars.
It's red, white, and blue.
I can't get rid of this thing now, Connor.
You've stressed me out.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave you to it now.
I don't know.
I don't even know how to get rid.
All right.
I got my final grades for you, Luddwig.
And don't worry.
I don't think you're going to be disappointed.
Okay.
So philosophy, you get a 91.
That's an A.
That's an A minus.
And we had an awesome history lesson.
I really do enjoy the fact that you utilized the garage.
You didn't just go over there and into the house
and not do anything with all the pieces.
You used all the pieces.
Painting this took a long time.
That's why you also get pretty high score.
And I realized most people didn't paint shit
and then put funny objects inside.
Yeah.
So that was a lesson.
You're an 85 for creativity.
I want you to show you.
Look at this.
Over here is painted.
Look at that.
You know how hard it is to get there?
All right.
I'm going to give you a couple extra points for complexity.
I painted in every available corner.
Yeah.
Your cleanliness is only a 90 because there was rats.
And I know that's on theme and on brand and everything.
It's part of the story.
So I'll give you a 92 on cleanliness.
You got a 91 philosophy, 92 cleanliness, 80 complexity,
85 creativity, and chat's grade is a 60.
So is that the worst chat grade for anyone today?
That's the worst chat grade that can possibly go out.
And they must have it out for you for some reason.
I don't know why.
You know what?
I've deserved it from day dot.
And they saw through me.
So your final grade, Ludwig, it's probably going to be.
Let's find out.
If only the music played through, it probably could have helped.
But you did put music through.
I really thought I had.
The music would have really helped then.
It would have been huge.
All right.
I got you at 92 cleanliness.
I got you at a 91 philosophy.
60 is pretty solid.
I got 60, which puts you at a final score.
You are at an 83.2 for your final score.
That is a B, a nearly B minus.
How does that stack up?
You're kind of right in the middle.
I do appreciate the whole thing.
So here's the thing about theming.
So everyone else that had a theme, they didn't stick with it.
A lot of the theming was kind of all, you know, okay,
we're starting with this theme, but we're moving on to other themes.
Your entire theme was this H.H. Holmes serial killer house.
It was the entire thing.
It was a mistake, Jerma.
I should have just filled up 12 rooms with 12 different things
and threw the Green Goblin in and done a little funny voice.
I don't need to give you guys a history lesson.
It's your day off.
Yeah, you gave us a history lesson.
I'm glad you're learning you definitely would benefit from some funny voices.
I think he was rumored.
Two have killed between 20 and 200 people.
So I just have to give her through the rest of this report,
although nine were only ever found in here.
Oh, house flipper drama.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not talking shit.
I'm saying it's what I should have done.
I should have shambles.
I should have made a the fucking community's falling apart right now.
I'm not talking trash.
I should have made a poorly designed tacky house
filled with furniture that I downloaded offline.
You're making crash houses.
Oh, OK.
Well, it's it's an American house.
And it's very clean, right? This is a garage that you'd expect a French house
house red white blue and their star and I couldn't figure out how to get the stars on the ceiling couldn't figure out to get the
Stars on the ceiling, but here's the thing
you painted a
Connor the re Connor you too Connor you had points a lot of points in
them in cleanliness and in philosophy because
It's it actually is a huge pain in the ass to paint every single wall in this game
It's a huge pain in the ass. Even if the wall is completely one color
It's a huge pain in the ass to paint every single color
It's liberty blue. Okay, tell me that's not american liberty blue. Anyway, who made the statue? I don't want to
I don't oh
Well, I guess it's actually a good point
Uh, well, I don't want to take up too much of your time here jerma. I'm happy with my score. Uh jerma's chat
Sorry, I uh disappointed you but I I hope you learned a lesson. We learned we hey
I learned something today that I didn't know before that's all that matters actually actually true statement. Be safe out there
All right. See you at work. Did you learn that five to seven minutes is a lot longer than you thought it was
Uh, how long was that because it to me felt like an eternity. I usually go about one to two minutes
But who's who's next? Uh, we got coming up next is I believe it is dug. Dug. Dug is next, right? Yes
We've got only there's only two people left
There's all this dug dug in and connor and then we can give out our we can see our final grades. Oh, I
I'm in there. Oh, no, no, that's right. That's right. Yeah, that's right. That's right. That's right
Okay, because we moved you right we moved you. All right. So actually we'll do dug dug then we'll do rt
Then we'll do connor connor connor. You're gonna round us out. I'm ready. I think it'll be a good one
All right. Here we go. Uh, let's make sure we get us looking good. This is dug dug coming up here
I'm doing 30 frames at 1080. Let me know if this is all right should be good. Let's find out
Oh, that looks good
Looks good. All right dug dug. We are ready for your presentation now
Look, I enjoyed hearing ludwig's origin story as much as the next guy there have been some great houses here today, but
Germa i'm ready to take you to the happiest place on earth. Okay
Dugney land a legally distinct version of disneyland with everybody's favorite mascot dicky mouse
Uh now germa, what is your favorite ride at disneyland goofy? Oh, that isn't a character. Um
space mountain that
Is down for construction unfortunately as we walk into main street avenue
You're gonna notice lots of shops lots of different areas of dougney land. You're gonna notice, uh,
Goofy's castle as well as the epcot center
And all of those lovely houses around main street that we all know and love as you walk down disneyland. I mean dougney land
Avenue very beautiful. Um, the walls are fully painted. Wow. Okay looking good. Let's uh, let's start
Let's go to uh, dicky's toontown everybody loves toontown. Um, you have all your favorite character here's like goofy and doccy and um
Cow. Yep. Yep. So I love the cow. The guy. I love the cow is one of my favorite characters
Notice the cartoon flooring really evokes that feeling of like you've been transported into a cartoon world
And chat this might be a bit scary. We're gonna head into haunted mansion next
Oh, you're gonna notice that haunted mansion is actually yes, seadog
A maze and as we go in oh god, sorry. Sorry
Um, there's terrifying photos up on the walls. You don't know which direction you're going you're moving left and right where the hell is
Uh this oh look at how scary. Oh another ghost. This place is terrifying, right?
Really really gets you into the mood not even for children because of how scary this is
I genuinely don't remember where the ending is
Uh, it's an actual maze walking through. Oh, can I start to wonder can I pause you for one second?
Let me pause you for one second. You made an actual maze
Connor your maze was just like a curly queue with with pictures from your computer. It was very good
But this is a this is this
What is it slander? No, no, i'm just saying this is like the first real maze of the night of the four or five maces
What I will stand for the low mark have you dissed my maze come off of it. What is this? This is real maze
Look at the mini-map
Oh mini-map, okay. I just met doug doug for the first time like fucking a month ago
Oh
I literally am lost. I do not know how to get out of this. So we might need to stall for okay
Whoa another ghost watch out for that ghost. Wait. Oh i'm back the entrance. Okay, that's not a bit. I'm
Okay, hold on. We'll get to the end one sec. All right
As you continue along your haunted mansion it gets scary and scarier
Did the creators of dougney land even finish this maze?
Is there anything actually waiting at the end?
Is it going to be as scary as those ghosts have been until finally you go even farther and you reveal
jared fogel's bedroom with a children's bed in front of it truly a haunted ride that any
Man or child would love that's pretty fucking funny questions on a haunted mansion that I
Honestly, you're the first of all you're the first person
You're the first person that made a real maze. Look at the mini-map
Look at the mini-map go back to the maze and go into the mini-map
You had actual places where you couldn't really go and then you had to go through a different spot
You got lost in your own maze that that's a disaster complexity intentionally, right that
Complexity, I got you at a 98 right now, by the way
A 98 and let me tell you this is just I am lost one second. This is just haunted mansion
All right, don't even get me started on adventure land. Okay, here we go. Here we go
All right
So as you leave the haunted mansion, uh, you're a little spooked, right?
You need something to to chill out with maybe you want to go to tomorrow land
The future of tomorrow or whatever walt disney said and tomorrow land is uh, all of the highest technology that uh, we could find
Uh, there's
Oh, there's technological cubes. There's technological cubes. Look at these tech cubes. I think it's a cabinet
There's technological paintings, which I don't think anybody else had the walls fully tiled with some of the most cyberpunk tomorrow land stuff
You can find and a bed. I do have furniture in this house. Yes. Okay. I I do have a question
Yes, what is the philosophy of the placement of the technological cubes because they look a little scattered. Yeah, have you um
Seen the movie alien. Yes, it was random. I've just put them everywhere. Oh, okay. Okay. All right. Okay. Yeah, that looks fantastic
I love it. I love tomorrow world whatever you're going to call it in your royalty free copyright free version
Right, right. Right. Yeah, it's it's fair use because
Of the cubes, um, let's head back downstairs. I want to show you our backyard
Okay, other people tried to make prim and proper little boring lawns. Nobody likes that. Nobody likes suburbia
What you want is adventure land this outdoor has a mix of different plants and foliage
It even has a swimming pool that the deep end has a swimming pool
Adventure land is something for everybody. Look at this bonsai tree pretty cool, right? This is actually a pretty damn good backyard
There we go. Oh
I I'm I am I am I don't know doug doug. This is this is looking pretty solid
Uh, can I can I can you do me a favor? Yeah, could you go to the garage?
Sorry, you mean what garage I would like you to go to the garage the garage doug. Are you talking about?
Germaversal studios that place is a dump. My park is much better. Don't go anywhere near germaversal
I love how you just put it. Well, I want you to open the garage
Open it the standards at germaversal studios are very subpar. I don't even think they have a ride in here
I appreciate the fact that you hid the garage
Yeah, that park sucks. Yeah, there's not much in that there's not much in that park
Not much in that park certainly not the happiest place on earth now. It's very clean. It's very clean
The parking lot there's a parking lot. Yeah, I took out the garage door and put in a wall
Okay, all right
But why is there a door to the park how a car is supposed to get in here dog dog dog dog?
What's that right there in the lower left next to the door? Oh boy. Um that
somebody
Um miss did park their car in the wrong spot. The door is not the door is not even in the frame either
But that's again some rogue driver. Yeah, have you been to disneyland? Have you been to the parking lot?
These people do not know how to drive. Can I ask a question germa? I hate to cut in. Yeah, go ahead. Why?
Was the garage not the parking lot germa germa?
Excuse me. Hold on. That's true. Why was the garage not the parking lot?
Look, you have to build around what the people want some guy
Charges ford f-150 through my walls and made a huge mess
And so I built the walls around it and that became the parking lot
That's why there's this disaster here. None of this was my fault. Well, life gives you lemons
I do appreciate the parking sign though. That is very nice. I do love it. It is parking for a segue
Can we go into the body? Can we go into the ball pit? Oh, yeah. Yeah
So one of our most popular rides is ball pit land and if you've been wondering where the bathroom is, don't worry
Splash mountain has you covered. I was just gonna ask it multiple
Pools that you can swim and frolic in and if you need to go to the bathroom
We do have a urinal at the very end if you can kind of jump up
Yeah, I was gonna say are you are you peeing out of the water to get to that?
Um, I think if you jump across you could sort of time it in bursts
What about the if you take a shit you go in the pool so nobody is swimming in these pools
Well, I was sort of thinking maybe the middle one would be the shit pool and then splash mountain is the first and the third
Okay, I get it
So so only so one of these is used as a place to go to use the bathroom and the other ones could be used
As a pool that's that's i'm pretty sure if we put enough chlorine in these nobody's is gonna notice
So i'm gonna dock you on cleanliness for a minute. That's filthy. Uh, i'm gonna have to drop you on cleanliness
Have you ever been you know, like a wave pool those things are bright yellow. All right
Everybody just puts up with it. That's part of the amusement park experience
I am torn because you have philosophically probably
One of the best I would say one of the best grades here philosophically speaking
This is wonderful and i'm trying to figure out is this a 95? Is this a higher score?
Is this a 96 or is this I?
I'm i'm epcot you have epcot. We've got
Every other contestant has been spot checked on the corner next to the garage. That's true
Can we see the corner of the garage dog dog corner? Oh, oh, right. Right. Right. Yeah
See that as part of our adventure land expansion was left untidy. Let me back. Let's check it
Oh, um, I have no everybody neglected hooligans at this park
Everybody needs to get in there and kick them out. We're if and if the park is successful enough
We will purchase
Germaversal studios and just kick them out of here. This has gone on too long
I'm going to give you a 100 on creativity because I really think you deserve it
I think I think you actually deserve a perfect score for creativity
I think you absolutely nailed it. This took you had to bring in custom things here and I think you absolutely crushed it
On complexity i'm going to give you a 94
There was some there was some
Doors that weren't really in their own place
There were some walls that were constructionally had some problems the garage had wasn't anything there
There also was the problem with the dirt and then the debris
To the left of the garage, but I do think it was phenomenal. Do you have a second floor?
Uh, yeah, that's tomorrow land. So that yes, right that was that was part of the second floor, right?
Okay, so just making sure like this is all there was on the second floor. That's nothing behind
Okay, and the door if we see the tomorrow land door
It's a little also perfectly locked into place you see in the future of tomorrow
Doors are more of a philosophical concept very philosophical. I might add I love it. I think it was fantastic
I think you're going to get probably at least an a
Uh, we need to see what chat says what is chat giving for a grade chat is also giving you an a so you that is also
That is a full nine. That is a 95 from chat. Thank you. You've got a you've got a great great score here
Let's figure it out. You're gonna be a pretty high probably top of the class. I'd say pretty high 94 in complexity a
90 and cleanliness of that back area really gets everybody
Philosophy, I feel like you did a lot with your philosophy here. I think it's a little low
Hey, and you got to admit with the doors consistent consistent philosophy throughout. I'm gonna give you a 97 for philosophy. Let's go
I really think that it should be somewhere higher than a day
And then chats grade is also an a which puts you at a grand total of
96.0
Thank you chef. It's alex is currently at 96.5
Both 96s. You should both should be very proud of yourselves for your creativity complexity cleanliness
Wonderful wonderful job doug doug. That was fucking phenomenal. Thank you. All right, so we got one more
We have connor eats pants is the last one
Right, no, oh my god, why can I not think you know why?
No, get jared off the screen
Jared jump scared me jared jump scared me
It's because it's because i'm looking over at my sheet and because we moved you you're like not on the sheet over here anymore
So you're like out of my brain
All right. It's your turn rt. I promise I promise I promise I promise I promise. All right, let's let's get it
Let's get it. Let's get it
Um stream quality is a better text readability and 30 fps. Is it? Yes
Go he hates rt. He hates rt. It's cord crashing is going to be your worst nightmare now
No, you had the opportunity and the discord just all right. Let me take a look. Uh, can you move around?
It's it's actually okay. Um, I'm actually glad i'm going at the spot
I did because I think what my house here
There's going to be a little bit of anticipation because I actually gonna quote germa here
If your whole house was a barbie house, it would have been a lot higher. It was a view in criken's house
Um, no, i've actually produced a no
barbie dream house
Uh based on the old doll house toys
Um for you to play with today
Um, let's make our way on side. But first and foremost haven't just left this out here
What do you mean you haven't left it out here? Here's some strawberry ice cream take with you
We thought about it. Oh, we thought about it thematically
Oh shit, let's step on and holy shit
Was to try and get the classic feel of a traditional barbie playhouse, you know
So it's a bit plasticky feeling as you go through it, but the colors uniform have a little elegance of style
You have your nice windows. You have your lights
A little bit of air to kind of get in here retro tv kind of because you would you would have like kind of old toys
Based on this like kind of little old things that you stick in the house
When you play with one of these toys sets back in the day
You know
I tried to kind of really base it on kind of like the earlier ones from the 60s when mattel were making these way way back
So we've actually got open access back just so you can kind of get your hands in there
You know if you're playing with as a kid, you've got your kitchen unit. Of course, you can play with it, too
You also have a complete pool side
Beach area we've sanded down a lot of the garden here
But also some grassy patches just to try and make it look distinct got to get the barbie brandon in here as well
Sure
Okay, you get a lot of stickers of barbie in these old play sets too just to really kind of hammer home
What it is, you know, they're big on the brand and they were back in the day
We built our own little bench here assemble this so you can just have it like a nice little hold on pause for a second pause
This is all very wonderful. You've even got the little dirt. You've got the dirt
Under the bench in an artistic way on it and like because your legs are going to kick some of it away
No, we thought about that. Yeah, that's just like you you've shaped it. You've you've sculpted this
This is this is a sculpture. This is a sculpture you've made. Okay, continue. You're way too kind
You're way too kind
We have like a more little sticker of barbie here as well
Just so she greets you when you're coming in the door
You have a lot of these things just as you go about in the house
Uh, if we take a look upstairs
We tried again to just try and give this kind of an open feeling. We got all the essentials here is all the clothes
Um, you know because barbie famous for our fashion through the years
We really want to make sure that we have that as part of it
Here is classic kind of style bedroom
We went for a bit of an urban feel maybe in the back a bit
But also kind of want to keep it true to barbie have that in here
Was the were the walls not being pink a time constraint?
No, no, it was actually it was a deliberate choice
We wanted that kind of the contrast in background because it makes these walls pop more if you actually have a brick wall in the back
It's what in a lot of urban dwellings, you'll kind of get that look
And actually they incorporated that in some of the classic barbie dream houses. I'll have you know, my grandmother had one
That's true. Somebody look that up. Is that true? Somebody look that up if it's true. I'll I'll put it higher
We have a wardrobe room here as well. Of course, you know, you can go through your outfits
Um now we do have one bit now
This is classic and I debated doing it this way. Okay. Um
There is an extensive use of stickers in old barbie homes
Especially for details like toilets and that because you only get so much plastic in this set
So you really make use of yes
they make use of sticker elements for some of these features in the house because otherwise it would just
Ramp up the retail price and I want to try and stay true to the vision of it being a toy
And you know affordable in that sense. Ludwig Ludwig. This is a history lesson. It's not about a guy that murdered people
This is this is the majority of the house here
Um, we can hop back outside. We have working lights as well. We wired all these they work you have working lights
Are you the only one that made working lights in the whole game?
No, wait, somebody else did sure did somebody else have working lights?
I don't think anybody had working functioning electricity. I did. I just forgot to show it but oh, okay. All right
He's already killed me by now
He's all right. You've already died already
We can take now we can just sit by the pool with our lovely strawberry ice cream and just soak in the day
We have flowers all over the garden. Yeah, can I see the flowers?
Yeah, of course. We have a lot like that on the purple ones here
We have these kind of like this border edge guard of these kind of plastic pots
And I kind of want it's weird because i'm trying to represent this feeling a bit of plastic as we kind of go about the property
Um, because again, I like the toys were the reference point for this
Stock up on some more strawberry ice cream rt. Can you open the garage, please?
So I did think about the garage in official dream houses back in the day
The garage would actually be sold separately as would barbie's car. So it's not included
It's not included
I actually wanted to remove the garage entirely in the property because to kind of hammer home that idea of it being sold separately
um
Because it wouldn't be included. That would be a separate playset and we were focused on barbie's dream clubhouse here
All right
That that's a good answer. That's a good answer
Can you check the corner to the left of the garage? Uh, the corner to the left of the garage sure thing. Just one sec
It's clean. Oh you keep you get to keep the 100 on clean
No, don't worry attention to detail like, you know, like I want to keep the garden kind of nice pristine and proper
Um, I really like actually like kind of like adding the sand in this um as we were going about it, too
I just thought I added a bit just sort of a bit of contrast from like kind of just
Modern suburbia that you're getting here and like everyone just doing kind of grassy gardens
I thought it would look a bit more distinct and again
It's the idea of kind of dream clubhouse and thinking of the beach and things like that
Yeah, the the sand is bringing me to the beach. That's really wonderful. Wonderful. Wonderful. Wonderful
Thank you very much
Uh, I have to i'm fighting with giving you a 98 or a 100 on creativity. I'm trying to uh, 98
It's a 98. I think for creativity
It could be 100 that is very kind that is very kind of you
It's a 90
It's a
Oh
It's a 99
It's an oh my god. You're all right your creativity. I'm giving you a 99
your
Your complexity i'm giving you an 89 and it's not because it's not a complex house
It's because it's it's a it's a more it's it's it's a home. This is a regular home. It's not it's not a very complex home
This is a a home. This is like modeled after those old barbie toys
Which is exactly the old barbie toys. So you don't actually want too much clutter in there
Exactly. I've tried i've tried to kind of push over though and add as much details as I can like stuff with the lights and that
That's true. You know getting plants inside just to kind of make it look nice, but your philosophy
You've got a 100 that that this I think you've you nailed it on sticking with a theme
You pulled the theme the whole time. There's not a whole lot of structural problems
It's very very nicely made all the wiring works in the house. Everything works. That's a 100 for philosophy
That's a 100 for cleanliness. This is going to be you're going to be isn't really close
You might be ahead of the class. We're going to see what chat's greatest chat is
Chat is unanimously giving you an an a 95. Oh my god
So I think it's very possible. Let we'll do a little bit of the math here. Hold on a second
We got you at 99. You're way too kind chat. Thank you. Got you 90 for complexity
Which is 100 ask is there a difference in chat's grade if it's unanimous does that make it 100 or is it a 95 max?
It's just 95 max just to make it sort of point wise was easier to calculate
Nobody is going to get a 100 like it's impossible, right? Okay, it's impossible. Great. Great. Great
Impossible to get a 100 make sense why I didn't get it make sense why I didn't get it
Well, i'm not gonna for your other reasons, but uh, i'll get you at a
Drum roll, please ladies and gentlemen rt game is currently at the head of the class with a 96.65
One tenth of a point higher than his alex. Oh my god
I actually five tenths of a point higher than doug doug freaking dare you
That I don't want to be a buzzkill
But doug neeland does own the rights to barbie and we will be sending you a cease and desist. Oh, that's true
That's true
Look the two people who might beat me italics and the barbie house both cheating the law legally
Listen there can be a brand opportunity
Mattel is very powerful as I imagine doug neeland is our lawyers will talk right we can work something out here
We got a killer cut of the ten thousand dollar prize pool that germa put up we can agree to that
Yeah
Well, it was actually it was actually a hundred thousand
But I mean, I don't know why you I don't know why you said it was so low
But I am okay with this being the model house that germa recreates from scratch rather than doug neeland
A hundred thousand dollar prize pool. Oh, no, no, no
All right. That was fucking phenomenal rt
Uh, thank you very much. You're way too kind. Thank you everyone. It's
Is really good rt. Yeah, good show. Thank you so much. Everybody did a great job. Come on
Like uh, but the people's skill levels in the game and some people woke up an hour before and some people with timings trying to get
Everyone this was a lot of fun. Thanks everybody so much. We got one more. We've got con reeds pants house
I had a so I had a theme or something. I went for here. Okay
Let me know if the stream looks good if any change anything. Yeah, let me just turn you up a little
Let me take a look
I think you should be good good and stuff
Oh, let me check it while I load it. I am loading your stream, but it is freezing. Let me
retry
Okay, there we go. I can see it. Uh, you look you look pretty good on my end
I think let me get rid of these grades for rt. I'll tell you when you can go
So you said you you have a theme that you're going through you said I have a theme
I'm it's not exactly like a home that you well, I guess you do live in it
If you're like, I guess someone who's invited to it, but okay, it's not like it's not like a not like a family home
Uh, it's a it's an orphanage. Um, okay, it's specifically it's a hundred thieves cash app orphanage
Is what we've made here and if you're wondering about the windows the boards are supposed to be there
Okay, um, they're supposed to be there so that you know people don't leave
Um, but yeah, so that those are there for a reason but I I can show you the home check it out in the front yard
Again, it's an orphanage. So you can't really expect it to always like look so great outside
There was some digging that didn't look some digging that didn't get done there
You can listen. We'll get to it. We'll get to it anyways, okay
And the boards are uh, you're you're you're out of 75 for cleanliness right boards are there for a reason
Okay, so here we walk in and this is the main room as you can see it's uh red
We have a couch Connor. We made the same house and I was just sitting there chatting to people
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I could show you my house that I made. Okay. Well, I have a light switch
That's actually fucking hilarious. All right, go on go on. I don't want to interrupt you though
They'll let your lights work your lights actually are functioning. They work. Yeah, they work they work. So that's one light
Uh, this is the girl's room. Okay
Or, uh, this is the girl's room we can fit two
Um, we have things girls like in here like a barbie dream house
love
asan
Um this doll and taylor swift, okay
Uh, so yeah, the girls love it
Um next room over this is the boys room
We have things boys like like the main characters in michael bay transformers movies like shia laboeuf
and mark walberg
Oh, I know camaro because like bumblebee
um
So not nothing else besides like nothing else besides transformers. No, well, there's austin's show
But he's not on hundred thieves anymore. So they had to mark him out. Okay, he used to be on the wall. Okay, I see
Yeah, and that's just like a window
Was it like I don't know if there's crutch. Is it a window or is it a is it a pic?
Can you can you get closer for us? It's a window. I can't I don't know how to crouch
Uh, I don't think you can okay
It's actually I might not the kid might have actually put that on the wall next to him to simulate
Oh, I see. Okay. Okay. Anyways, that was the boys room. Nice. This was an accident
There's supposed to be like a door here. Fortunately, we won't get into that
Okay, this is the hundred thieves cash app kitchen juvie
We have brought to you by courage jd
And we have courage on the wall. You have a nice sink
This is where you get the juvie in it
I'm gonna get okay. I'm for creativity. I mean you may I i'm gonna give you so far. I got you at an 80
Okay, I got you an 80 so far. Well, we'll keep getting that up. Don't worry
Okay, this is the back door here is the repurposed from a sears that shut down
We kind of just took the glass sliding door. We like the blue
Um, but yeah, so that that's that uh, we could go. I don't know where we could go next
We could go upstairs next. Yeah, I i'd like to see the upstairs. That would be good again
It's it's tough to get funding for an orphanage. So they kind of make make what's going on with the window?
Hold on. Is there a window you got a window here on next to the door to the right?
Yeah, no like this one. Yeah, is that part of another window or is that a just half window lighting natural lighting?
Well, the sun is the sun is due south. So it's not hitting you this way
Well at this time of day, of course, but yeah, I mean hold on. Give me a minute
There's a sleep button. Oh, you can't sleep with this one. Actually. All right. So what what do you got?
Oh, you you are the first person to use the house
Yeah, I think that's worth at least a couple points in philosophy
And the sun's there somewhere
anyways, uh
Upstairs we have we have a couple different usages of the main usage of upstairs is the playroom
You'll see it in the corner, but okay kind of just having like the the owner's bed is right there
Okay, and we want to keep it like motivating for the kids. So like we have ted lasso on the wall kids love ted lasso
Uh, this is uh, this is the bath
What it's I see says, uh
I see the one that we first e to do something. Yeah. Well, it's where you close it says call dot. That's for the kid
That's oh, okay. I see. Okay
Okay, so this is a toy
Is there any is there a bathroom? What right here? So that's a wait. So that's a bathroom
There's no toilet. That's what they use. Well, I okay. Did you not even look in the room? I
did
you have
Bucket. Oh this is okay. That's right. The okay. All right. All right
I see. I see. I see
We're not trying to kill the kids. Okay. All right. So now
What's in that room? Yeah. Anyways, this is like where whoever runs the house would sleep. I guess like nade shot or somebody
Um, this is the this is the playroom now. I know this looks bad, but
Kids will be kids boys will be boys. Sometimes things get roughed up. Okay, that's the we're at we're at it
We're you you your score is unfortunately falling
After that it's unfortunately falling
It's a lot of a lot of a lot of dings if the kids are happy then i'm happy and that's what matters
I don't even need the score. Anyways, this is the playroom. We have a lot of toys for the kids here
Okay, um, well you can actually hold them. Yeah, you throw it and like they fetch it and then they come back
This is like a little doll
I believe okay
There's some weaponry. There's some security cameras you have okay
Okay, so we have we have sponsors can I see the garage could I see the garage
In the interior of the garage here. We have another toy. We've got like an outlet with a fork. Jesus christ
okay, um
I I think of course I have
Your philosophy had to come down a little
First you have the garage it will get there. Okay, so I wanted to show you this we do like this is still here
Uh, why is it not clean?
But when the kids turn 14, that's where they go drink
Juvie, okay, what's in the garage? I gotta see the garage. Oh, yeah the garage
This is uh where we get streaming setups. So if they're gonna be in the orphanage
They want to become streamers obviously and is there anything in the garage? Of course. Oh
shit
Okay
You've actually got a garage. You have a garage setup. That's shocking your setup. All right, we can't we have face cams
And that does a nice face cams and it's been the perfect place to see somebody's face perfect lineup. She's on hundred thieves
Yeah, I thank congratulations for making a garage. First of all, that's uh, thank you, of course
And what what why would you not utilize the garage? That's what's the computer? It was silly. Is that just a regular computer?
That's a streaming computer. Okay, they're melee players
Okay, cool. Cool. Okay. All right. I think I think i've got your wait. Hold on. What's in the back?
You did paint the exterior which is actually a huge deal
Of course painting the exterior is a big deal. So we're gonna have chat get the grade up for you
They can uh do it. I can give you what I what I like
Let's not pretend like there's not an effort made on the lawn because like as you can see the turf here
The kids lay it out. They mow it they try so you didn't do that. No, the kids do it
Oh, okay. So you didn't do that. Uh, well, I mean it's done. It's a part of the
Okay. Yeah, that's fair
All right. What do we got? What do we got for a chat score? Uh a b c or d you can't go lower than a 60
Um, i'm not saying that for any particular reasons or anything. I'm just I just wanted to make sure I said it
All right. I got you 75 for creativity
Uh, I I do I do I think it's a solid c. I do like the idea
Of I love what gets what gets a 75 for creativity like over like what what did like the what did like the maze get?
Uh, you're talking about connor's maze. Yeah, like just like just like just so I have like a comparison
Connors maze got a also 75 for creativity. Okay. Well that all right. That's yeah
I would like you to open the front door
Uh in the front the reason why the 75 is for creativity is because this space although clean and although nicely, you know decorated
It the the creativity there's a kitchen there in the way the kitchen's supposed to be it's a nice home
It's a nice house. You made it's a nice interior. I love the idea that you've replicated
Uh this this uh, this home this house
It's I believe I believe that's a good but creatively speaking
I think I could have used a little bit more a little bit more paint on the walls
Maybe not maybe not so much red
Uh, and I I would say that 75 is a pretty fair score for creativity on complexity. Yeah, it's not bad
Can I try I mean I I would like to vouch for my
For my comrade here and give a couple more on creativity because I mean that is a courage jd sponsored kitchen
You know avengers assembled if you know, you know
Uh, it's it's an end thing. You may not know it is the yeah, I I think I'm not that familiar with 100 thieves
Come on now. Let's not be too hasty with this sponsorships. You know, I mean there's no hashtag ad anywhere. I don't know
I i've i've it's actually a good point. I'm not ever puts food on the table for the kids is what I always say
Like it wasn't wasn't one of the easy to get a sign. Apologies officer in playroom. I'll give you
I'll give you 76 complexity. I'm gonna I'm gonna give you 64 for complexity because your favorite operating system is the nintendo 64
I figured that that was a good thing to give you. I think that was your favorite you called it an operating system
Yeah, operating system. Yeah, no, that's my favorite. Probably that is probably right and I gave you I gave you a 60
Unfortunately, I gave you a 60 for cleanliness just because it's uh, the wall all the boards and it was fair
boys will be boys and like a
A lot of the these kids a lot of the walls were kind of missing pieces
Uh, there's still that notices on the front. It's it wasn't really cleaned up properly
Uh, but I really shows the state of our orphanages really that I mean, it's not really
That makes sense. That's fair. I mean i'm glad I can bring awareness to it
Chat has given you a b chat has given you an 85 chat's rate is an 85. I'll take b. I got you
I'm gonna give you a 78 on philosophy because I think I like I like the I like you you
You fulfilled your philosophy the whole place was built on this one theme
You didn't make you know, whatever the hundred thieves, you know front door and then have a completely different interior
You did stick with the theme and the philosophy. So i'm going to give you a c plus for that one and look we can get you
I'm gonna have to give you your final grade now your grade
Is as of right now you got a 76 for creativity. I've got you at a 64
For complexity and structure i've got you at 60
I'm gonna give you 64 for cleanliness because it's also you know might as well because it's 64. It's your favorite console. That's fair
That makes sense. I'm gonna give you 78 for philosophy
And then an 85 for chat's grade which gets you to a grand total of 72.4
You got a that's a full on see that that is more than passing. That's very well
Is that higher or lower than the other connor, uh, the other connor got a 75.6 robbed that's fine
That's okay
I'm a winner in my heart. We're last place together. We're last place. There is no last. Okay
Very important very important when you're in school in high school ed in college
They don't like bring everybody up and say all right
Hey, this is the best people in the actually they do it's like the fucking dean's list. They do right
They do do that
Yeah, but they also used to say like 10 people got d's five people got c's and they would say in front of the whole
Class and then they'd slap a paper in front. He was actually traumatizing
This is kind of like that jerma in a way. You've done this to us. How about you show us your house jerma?
What do you have to offer? I was walking around just putting random paint on walls
I was answering technical support
We all had the same amount of time and you made a house and you've played this game more than us
Like what's what's what's your house? What makes it so you can grade? What's the philosophy?
You can grade my house
Let me get let me give the grade let me give the final grades up
We need to know what your your qualifications are my qualifications and even get yeah
Connery spans your overall grade was a 72.4
Let's get the final grades on here because I think people need to see them and we're going to do it in
Uh in order of top of the class down now if you got if you're there's no bottom of the this is cruel
But I how else do we do this?
How do we do this without it being big I bet you feel big
All right, here we go with a
96.65
RT game is your is your head of the class honestly in shock. Thank you so much deserved
It was a great house. It looked I was gonna complain but it looks so good
Thank you. Thank you. I was honestly shocked. I'm still gonna complain a second. I'm just kidding
Let's get this a little bigger so you can see
All right
at
96.55
Is italics. Um, I think we should just congrats massive congrats. This is so cool. Just rounded both up to 97
You know
There's also an a you remember teachers wouldn't round up. Oh
Well, we I mean we could round up but these are the exact scores with
96.05 we have dug dug
Clap so those are your those are your top scores. That's everybody that got an a effectively
So the people that got into high b, let me just write it 96. all right the high bs
Let me see. Yeah. Yeah, make sure you do your garages next time. Can you still see me? Yeah
You're still on the screen. I was just playing it myself. All right, let me see 80 who had
87.6 87.5
Okay with an 87.65 we have Joel
Congrats very good score. Very excellent score. That's cool. That's a b-plus, isn't it? 87. Yep
87 and above b-plus. That's correct with
87.5 we have poke. Yes, 87.5
You guys were neck and neck yours was fucking hilarious. This is great
Great, thank you. Wait, can I take that one percent he gave me or no? Oh, that's right. Hold on. Wait, wait
Wait, you you you did offer the friend the friend points
How are we gonna do that? I think he loses one and poke gets one right? Joel. What's your uh, what's your uh assessment here?
Yeah, well, what am I supposed to do? Well, sorry what you said you wanted you wanted to give zero point something points to friend points
Okay, how about this? How about this? Uh, I will give
As very generous and I just want to say, you know, thanks. Thank you that I can be part of this
I just want to say this I think poke gets a zero
0.5 extra friend point zero point five. So that would be no no change at all
I'll take it. I'll take it
And 87.55
Changing points
In second place if anyone below me wants to combine our scores to take first place as a tie
I think i'm open to that too
I'd like to give all my points to connor eats pants into help his orphanage because I believe thank you in helping the youth
Well, let's we're not exchanging them now. Are we look i'm the teacher you can't just give grades to each other
Just wait till I get it all on paper
I give my share, you know captain mike i'm standing on my chair right now captain my captain. I give it to connor
Teacher i'd like to give a full letter grade to uh mike over there like that is how this works
All right, here we go. All right. All right. Well then keep your own let's keep it
What if we were to rate germa's house all of us? No, that's what we're doing
Yeah, but I didn't even I wasn't competing. I was like literally walking in circles
Did you have 75 minutes to make it?
I had 75 minutes to explain to chat how this process was going and answering questions
How many hours do you have on you? You have more hours on this game than all this combined
I have two or three thousand hours in this game. I would I would demolish any of you in a challenge any of you
Let's find out we'll find out when we look at your house right now any of you so get through these get through these scores
We're gonna take a look when's house flipper two out actually
Yeah, uh, what do you guys you guys down for round two when house flipper two comes out? Yeah, of course
I'll be a part of it. I'll be in i'll be in it next time. Okay, you can feed him. Let's go watch me
What see see me with an a fucking plus see me with it, but who grades it then we have to get some
A third party i'll buy i'll grade for you guys. I uh you want to grade
Uh
Yeah more of a I feel like just my history lessons aren't appreciated. So
All right, we got your chat gbt history lessons. I mean lugwig you're lugwig. You're a red devil in the white city
I was an english major. What do you want from me?
As well, I forget that sometimes yeah, I went to college
English major gang love your score. Your score is like good. You had an 83.2. Ludwig. That's a b
I know I had the worst chapel though, and it really hurt it did it was 10 percent. They were so mean
Yeah, they hate you. Yeah, they hated me justice of this entire day is luther getting
Injustice you brit. All right, we have
Hold on hold on. Let me see. We got 83.2 is lugwig. You had a drinking corner for 14 year olds
That's true
You lose you lose quite a few philosophy points with the 14 year old drinking corner. I think that that's I think that's fair
Okay, we got uh
Yeah, doug did use a
Doug's maze room was a real maze. It wasn't just walls put up in random locations down gigantic
Always maze is a generous term to describe. What was at the end of that?
Uh, who's next after lugwig? All right. Now we've got we're down now. We're down to the seas. We have 78
Seven and this is not a bad thing. We got 70. It's no it's not it's not criken
We got you to 78.45. That's a c plus
That's good. And he's get degrees sees get to read degrees real shit
And no and remember remember philosophy wise remember we saw what happened when somebody went full-blown barbie husk. Oh, yeah, they won
That's true. I mean you
Your philosophy you you were there and I blew it these guys you were there. I was there
Oh, no, Vinnie. I don't know Vinnie Vinnie is higher Vinnie is higher. He's he's down here
Vinnie was Vinnie's at eighty three point eight. So he is higher than you lugwig. I'm sorry
Oh
Yeah, he's got it. He's really good. It was Vinnie's was really good. Yeah, both of ours were good. We're both
Yeah
so now we've got
Underneath you criken we have with a
With a seventy five point six we have c dog. Thank you
This was awesome
It was like a powerpoint presentation of like memes
It really was
Honestly, it was just you went through your computer and just typed in you typed into the windows search bar
Dot png and was just like what do I got on my computer right now?
Your house is what elon musk wanted to live in when he bought twitter just memes just comedy was legal again
I you know, I think I went the extra mile with the decoration and the sheer amount of walls
Um, it was just it was tough
I was I was it was a lot of walls
It was it was a lot of walls good maze. It's a lot too much walls
I think I by the time I realized I had 10 minutes left. I was like, oh i've got i've got nothing
They were all mustard colored, too. You had like a whole mustard colored house
Oh, it was I loved it. I loved it. I imagine summer. It's just unbearably hot because the air can't reach you
Oh my god, I don't there's no reason to be there anyway
In the house
It's on like the real estate listing. There's no reason and then a 73.4 which is a 72 a c still it is right
Or is it c minus?
Uh c minus that's connery's pants at a 72.4
Yeah, it's uh, oh c minus wait all all the c's got c's that's actually yeah
That's kind of thematic there. There are your final grades. That's a 1.667 gpa, right? Did I literally get last place?
Oh, yeah, you got dead last there is no last place. There's no last place. There's objectively
Corners were voted last. I feel like there's
Everybody with c to start their name off. Hmm all got c's. Wow. What's up with that? Huh?
Hey, you guys had your philosophy scores were high with okay
Some would say we never stood a chance philosophy scores
Your philosophy scores are my put your dog in the game
You do show us your house. Give me a second
It would be nice to see your house. I want you to boot up and show us your house and show us what you made
I'll show you my house. All right, i'll show it to you boot it up
I wasn't competing
Well, we're still gonna judge you on a few factors guys. What do you think for the factors? We should judge them on
Yeah, what what factors do you want to judge me?
It's the same criteria, I think that's okay. Okay, asshole. Okay. Okay. Sure great this one
Let's see. What do you guys think?
Punks i'm actually gonna show you something fucking. Oh, no. No, no, no, no
We're gonna get I want a real grade and you better give me a real grade one of the like pre-built ones
All right, are you guys ready?
I'm ready. Uh, have you shared your screen yet? Oh just oh you
You can see you can see my house so you pull up my live stream right now
Oh, hang on. Here we go. Give us one sec. Hang on and I want you to take a quick look
I want you to take a quick look. What's your channel? What's your channel name? Twitch.tv said german an effect. Thank you. Not that one
Okay, I
See the stream
Okay
Um, I think you got the wrong save. Can we go ahead and see that garage before you head out? Where the fuck is my house?
You sleep. What are you loading here? Jeremy? Can you go back to the home, please? Where's my where's it?
What about that garden after building the where's the crusty crab? The crusty crab was here. Where's the crusty crab?
What sure are you okay? Jeremy? What are you talking about? Honest to god? Why why is the crusty crab not here?
I swear to god it was here at like fucking 40 minutes ago. All right, you gotta be shitting me
Where's the crusty crust around jerma? You wouldn't mind. Uh, we got a zero for preparation
Yeah, the fact that this doesn't exist is good doc complexity
It is we are gonna add complexity. I think because he's made it up in his own head and oh, this is fucked up
This is actually fucked up. Where's the crusty crab? It's more philosophical. I sold it. Yeah, that is philosophical. I sold it
It's the cabin. No, it's not it's not
It would be the crusty crab it wouldn't be the cabin that's a mess right there what yeah, that's fucking awful
Love 60 for cleanliness, right guys. That is the lowest score of course the lowest possible score. Yeah, there's a bit back
Hold on the presentation on the class computer jerma, you should oh did you just have a 180 in your opinions?
I think you just did oh it just guys
It got silent
This is the wrong building am I am I wrong to say that i'm clipping through the roof. Why don't we take you through?
What's this? Oh
25 minutes. Yeah
It's this go ahead build away build away crusty crab
That looks pretty interesting doesn't it through the front door as you see this house is perfectly this sign is in the perfect location
Going through here. We've got the galley grub. There is your ordering station squidward sits right here
Unbelievably complex complexity philosophy theming idea of the bathtub being the thing that he sits behind
This is don't worry about this. This is uh, there's nothing you have to worry about that
Uh, this is uh, hold on
Why there's a futuristic space just wait just wait just wait just wait
Go look at what the crusty crab looks like it looks like this
No, it is pretty accurate to the crusty crab. I'll give you that. Oh
Crusty crab. This is where spongebob. This is the window in the corner
Well, you're the kitchen's pretty good. What's that connor said that again?
Okay, I don't know connor. I'm not seeing any mazes
Yeah, where did the kids sleep? Where did the orphans go? Yeah, where where's where's the where's like that weird?
Corner. Yeah, the weird corner. Yeah
That gave me. Oh, did you have working lights only three of you did?
Can you show us the uh, could you show us mr. Krabs's room again?
Uh, this is the bathroom. We don't need it. I said I I I was I got tired when I did this
And I was like I have to go tired
But it's always hard to make crusty crabs office. It was hard to do it because they forgot the freezer
Yeah, that's all right. Yeah, but that side door always be in the kitchen. Like I don't remember that in the manga
I'll be honest with you
This is up here. If you didn't know up in the car. What is up here? Oh, what?
How did you remove the stairs? What the fuck is this? This is a different base home. Oh
Uh, yeah, some of the houses you can remove the stairs some of them were made more way more customizable than others
Mr. Krabs goes into hiding. Yeah, the irs is after him and this was you made this in 45 minutes
Somebody hacked my computer and did this part
House looks like a gmod man on ttt. Can you go through the those doors? Yeah. Wait, what what is going on?
Oh, this is somebody hacked my computer into this
And yes, I did I I I did this in 45 minutes with uh shows the outside
Yes, you make a vampire shrine to yourself. Yeah fucking weird. I know
I wish I was a vampire too
I what's the idea behind the the weeds in the straw because
The house flipper actually grows grass and I haven't been in this house for like four months
What's the what's the deal with that balcony on the side of the house? Can you look at that again?
Which one left side of the crusty crab? Oh, um
So what's going on there? Well, you can I'll figure it out. I could figure a question doug
By the way, where are all the animals because they were like, where's the maze?
Oh, and you didn't even say anything about my oh, it's nothing's here. There was like a bunch of problems
No maze. Okay
Uh, where are the animals? They were like 15 animals that were like running around
Well, they gotta make the burger somehow. So did you remember to plan this whole tournament so you could show us this house
Can you can you a really really cool shot above that that gray thing in the back to see what's back there
Okay, you want you want me to just go up and take a look. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah if you could you got it
Are you for grappling hook? Yeah, there's a great. I'll do wait. Oh, you mean back here?
Yeah, there's like a trap door or something. Oh, that is weird. What is that?
Oh, what's going on here? That should be illegal
That I didn't put that there. I don't like that. I didn't put that there you want someone to climb down from the ceiling all your table
I don't think I put that there. I'm comfortable. Uh, we're gonna take points off for cleanliness. It's gonna be a plus in complexity minus in philosophy
All right, what's my grade the smell so bad? You have to escape through the hatch. I mean honestly, I thought
You guys want to go ahead first? Well, what do you guys think for creativity?
Creativity, it's definitely got to be high, you know, it's pretty high. I thought at least
Yeah, I think that's fair
I one thing that bothered me is that the sign wasn't on its own post because that to me is the defining feature the crusty crab
Is its own definitive sign and he just he just left it on the front like a like a like a
Like he doesn't have the mcdonald's arches game limitation. It's not even transparent. It's just a you know, like a white
Yeah, just png
Wait, jk to the you know plankton's home nearby. So it's really geographically vague where we are
Yeah, that's right. You're right
90 creativity on like established ip
Well, how much time did germa have on this house 45 minutes five plus about three and a half hours
You've clocked in like
65 000 hours
I I have barely played this game
All right, and i'm trying to get extra points here at them and i'm just saying
With the amount of time you you know from this game. You should have been able to shit out of mona lisa in no time
But no gary no spongebob. No nosferatu. You're not gonna make it in hollywood. No, it's brought to excuse me
That's a good point. No nosferatu
He did make the whole vampire. He does have a nose for us. Yeah, he did actually have a vampire room in fairness
Yeah, come on. Yeah, and so I in fact, let's let's touch on that for a moment
I thought because of the vampire room for me philosophy was the highest score. I put 95
Well now on philosophy
I don't know just because of that hatch to access the toilet because like what have you just taken a shit and someone like
Climbs down from the ceiling like what I know. Yeah, I put 60 that's some weird philosophy. I don't know
I do have work
You may be able to take a shit on the roof and have it drop down into the toilet though
Nah, the angle makes that impossible to be frank, but the detail detail not with my kind of firepower the detail though
No, but that's that's not that's that's nothing go look at the interior of crusty crab
Look at how the wood falls. Why is there a trough for cows?
They were like 10 barn animals that lived here and I don't know where they are
I don't know where they went. They're actually supposed to be lost barn animals minus
I think they're dead
I don't know what happened to the animals
Yeah, while we're doing the grade and I I think the mods are sharing that chat's vote has come in with an f unfortunately
That's both. No, that's bullshit. That's
Deserve an f but it is the majority of the votes
Okay, so that's 60 that's so let me do okay fine
Creativity, what do you got for me creativity? I think 90 a 90. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, it's established ip though
But barbie house, we gave a high but it's fine. That's fine. Okay. It's fine. Oh, okay
For an hundred thieves orphanage
Complexity I think I think um, it was there's some like cool elements like the door the sliding doors
Um, like even like the posters I think they're kind of cool
Uh, hey, but but if you open up look at the interior of the crusty crab
You wouldn't have put these here lugwig the troughs. Yeah. No, no, no
I'm talking about this these pillars with the trap door to the bathroom so that perverts can enter
Yeah, between it's either between the I don't think you would have done this
I don't think I think you would have just kept the tables as they were you told us specifically just now to look up images
Of the interior so I did uh, and they're all rectangular like the interior of the crusty crab is one big rectangle
That's true. You know, let's go with maybe 85 for complexity. Yeah, I think I honestly
70 what I think 70 you're just on the trap door that went up to the the room was kind of cool
And the beams were are nice until you realize it's just empty space
How about an 80 how about an 80 I can do it
Yeah, but we should divide the score by how much time was spent making the item 45 minutes plus four hours hours
Well, I think chad's vote went into account that because they gave him an f. I know I think I think
Yeah, sergeant go ahead. Okay. Yeah, I took longer doing this but I wasn't timed
I sat around we we watched like three or four youtube videos
We went off on like a food tangent
There was like at least two or three hours of that stream where I wasn't even playing house flipper
Little baby said what I could repeat it. So what what uh, what happened was I was watching videos
I was watching like three or four videos
And then we did like a whole nother thing that we were talking about food and stuff
Did you hear me that time? No, I heard you that time a lot. I'm clear
Okay, I think uh, I appreciate that the the one thing that we're gonna talk about deeply is cleanliness
Yeah, yeah, and how troll? Oh, yeah, the trough was for the animals that we I put this in the last second
What is dirty here every look at how everything is perfectly clean you made it you made a restaurant with a trough inside
I can put my hand on the wall damn scores
Look at this even the bathroom the bathroom is immaculate. Look at every single one of it and no shits in here
No piss buckets in here. These are all clean. I think it's not clean though
The fact that you're shitting in an open everyone you're shitting next to someone. There's no there's no look
You got a ventilation system here ventilation
Why are the toilet stalls that's not why isn't there any doors on yeah, why that's not clean at all because you can't put them
I I feel like it might show my eyes if some of the lower score makes this call
Rt, what do you think for cleanliness? Because you had the highest score
I'm just trying to i'm trying to think of in relation to the spongebob lore and the crusty crab actually is notoriously not clean
And mr
crabs is like
Deploying all kinds of techniques to just keep it vaguely afloat when it's filthy
It was even an episode about the actual germs and the establishment if anything
I think the lore should be taken into account in judging that i'm on board with that
But there's he just knows the trunks wait the lord didn't apply in the grading though because like mine was a messy orphanage
But it was not messy. That is true in the hundred thieves juvie
Orphanage would be messy. Yeah, and it also wasn't creative. Oh, but did you have fred in your playthrough? Oh, he's so cute
All right
Let's get a grade. Let's get a grade
Can our can our favorite spongebob character can our a grades all give us a cleanliness score?
Whoever got an a can you give out a score for cleanliness and we'll find an average zero
If you're connor, you're obviously a c grade. Thank you very much salty because I gave his maze mustard house of 76
I'm salty because I got worse than the maze mustard
That's true. Honestly, honestly after the night after the night and i'm all this drama in this community and this
You know cataclysm that has happened the only reasonable thing I can see happening from now on
Is if jerma individually goes through every person and pretends they are the winner and congratulant you won first place
So we all get validation from this so we can pretend and feel good. Maybe just a dm that I can screenshot
Yeah, I will dm everybody saying you did a great job
But ain't nothing better than the crusty crap that will be in
Well, and you can you can you can crop it you can crop that message and frame it on the wall
Based on that alone i'm leaning towards giving you uh, you know all the connor's got a c grade
I think maybe you deserve a j grade too below them. Yeah
All right, so what am I what am I getting for complexity for real?
Uh complexity was 80 80 creativity was 90. Okay, so now philosophy is your highest score
Okay, so what would you say is that is?
91 are you all agreeing on that? No, did we talk about the alien doors clipping through the wall or no?
Uh, we didn't grab it up. Yeah
Can you guys show the doors like look open the door and look at it clip guys like what are we doing here?
What are we doing here?
Actually, you know so go in the bathroom go in the bathroom and look at the alien door and go up
What is that there?
I mean like look up above the alien like it's events ventilation. It's a ventilation event
I don't want to start more drama in the community, but like this is really pissing me off
Oh
Said it needed to be said I have a monumental point on cleanliness. Here's a please wash your hand sign
There is no sinks in that toilet. There's only toilet bowls. Where are you gonna wash your hands?
I mean, they're in the water though. What about in here?
We're just coming to you. You can come in here like dip your hands in there
Is there any indication that the water is here? Like how do we look?
See and did you have teleportation powers in your house?
I think that gets at least I you didn't even know I had that okay
Wow, i'm picking up philosophy to 93 for that. I didn't even go in the teleporting pool
And that's why this is our final call whatever we have for that then we can get our grade gonna say 90
Chat gave me a 60. Okay
Philosophy and matt what I said 90 we have our we have our final scores then okay
So what do you want to do the calculation creativity 90? Okay complexity 80. Okay philosophy
93 93
Cleanliness 60 90 flat 90 flat cleanliness. Are we are you guys agreeing on that? That's what doug said
I mean i'm down to lower it. I think it's fair 88 go for it. 88. Is that fair? I can do 88
I can do 88. Okay, there is no check raid check raid 60. All right, so
Uh, that puts me at an 84.65. Yeah, I just I guess
Let me just let me just like sneak my way in here real quick. Oh, sorry dropped your cleanliness to 80 flat
80 where where am I sit here? Oh
Right above any right below poke. Honestly, that's pretty fair
Yeah, middle of the pack
84.65 that looks all right to me. You're doing an exam and the teacher just takes at the end
It's like I just better than you
Yeah, what about my dad still didn't still didn't even do like top five
That's right. The teacher didn't even get top five
Oh
How the hell did you do it so good? Tell me there you're fine
Well, hey jerma, you know, congratulations. You look like you have some potential in this game. So I would keep at it
Yeah, that was a lot of fun. Did you guys have a good was that did you guys have a good time?
I don't know how you guys did what you did in 75 minutes. You guys are amazing
Yeah, everyone was creative for like their own their own way, you know, that was really awesome. I want to do it again
My only regrets I didn't get to go earlier
So I wouldn't have to go after the yeah, I wish I went earlier too
Do this again we do this again, but we're giving two hours
Yeah, we can do we could do a two hours
Hey house flipper two actually they don't have a release date, but you can build your you can build your actual whole house
I think from scratch in house number two. Oh my god. I also think it's strict a strict. Um
Like you should be graded on your performance there your what do you presentation like it should be strict five minutes
Can't go over can't go under get some songs in there. You know, I think that's part of it get some songs in there
Little music
Yeah, I just realized something I just realized something this whole thing was a gaslight by jerma
Because he just took a bunch of people in here to see how they viewed him through a scope
Like how do you view jerma and it turns out it's you know me
Just viewing him through memes
But other people are thinking like how do I skew it towards jerma through creativity or whatever, you know
and i'm just saying i'm just saying I think this was a
Experiment for jerma to do it. I don't know. They just feel I mean it was
It was this was an experiment
That that is absolutely correct. None of you won anything
And we're all going to go about our day normally as well. Yeah, then nobody 100 grand looking at this. Yeah the candy bar
I'll be waiting for the check in the mail the candy bar 100 grand scale right here
This is some ig in scoring for sure. You know, you should advertise it like 10 million dollars next time
But it's all inside joke. We don't talk about that. Do it for like five million dollars
Yeah, well, I honestly this was actually an experiment. Hope you guys had a good time. I thought it was great
I thought everyone had everyone had a lot of funny shit. Um, I thank you for organizing it
Yeah, I thank you so much
Everybody's the one person by point one points. I would be oh my god. I'm I'm honestly shocked. I'm honestly shocked
Are you guys the great? I?
Forget it. Like I said in the very beginning all these grades. They just horse shit. It's just for fun
So i'm i'm glad everybody had a good time. I know i know don't worry
We spent like 20 minutes grading your crusty crab like number by number
If it doesn't mean anything, I mean I've I would have probably given myself like a 96
Well, thank you very much. Thank you everybody. Thank you guys honors each shake get rolled. Um, it was a pleasure
Yeah
All right. Take it easy guys. Thanks for sticking around
Thank you, bye bye thanks also the mods too the mods helped facilitate a lot of this so thanks mods. All right
Uh, that was really interesting
Uh, I think I had a lot of fun
Hopefully everybody else did
Technically speaking. I think it yeah
Maybe we could drop the amount that people can do a tour
Because some people was like eight minutes then it was like 15 6 12
I think we could probably make it so it's like you get 12 minutes and that's it but
Um, I had a blast. That was a lot of fun. If you guys liked it
I would love to do another one get some other streamers to get some more people involved
So just about at like the four and a half five hour mark right now. So I think that's good. Sounds good
I don't mind having no limits. Yeah, I mean it it
I wanted to give people the room to kind of just kind of go and meme and do whatever they wanted
So but yeah, I mean the the screen sharing was the technical stuff through it looked pretty good. I
Uh, the only thing is jolts looked like kind of that kind of chunky playstation 1
But the good part is you could watch it on jolts stream, too
So that was part of it to make sure that you could see a high quality version, but it was awesome
Jolts was great. I loved it. Um, yeah, I I would love to do this again. Thanks everybody for watching
See you soon. Uh, that's it for me. That's really all I had planned
I if is anybody else gonna stick around and stream that was there if they are we can throw a raid to them
If people are still reading, I mean if people are still streaming. Yeah, that was fun
Yeah, thanks everybody that participated. I know
Uh kind of taking a like a four or five hour chunk out of your day
To kind of hang out for a while is it's a lot to ask but I appreciate it everybody that was there
Raid the winner. That's actually a good idea. That's funny highest grade gets the raid
Or should we split it between three people is uh, so
Um doug doug
rt
And italics are the top three rt has our rt is ending of the top three who is not ending
He said rt is ending is doug doug still streaming is italics still streaming because italics technically was in second place
You should raid the loser instead
No, connor's house was fucking funny. It was great. All right, uh, is italics still planning on streaming as I do this
Let me do that. Let me put the actual shit up here now
Yeah, there we go
Let me ask him. Let's see if he's still going turn this down for just a second. I'll back in here
Uh italics are you here?
He is deafened and muted
The talics is not streaming anymore. It's how presenting. All right, so doug doug is the third up. So italics is ending
So go say hi to your number three your top of the class doug doug with his unbelievable
royalty free
Uh doug land have I been summoned? Oh, I was saying if you're still streaming you're ending, right?
Yeah, i'm probably gonna take off just because it's been it's been a great five hours though. Yeah
Uh, love it. No, thanks, dude. I uh, hope you feel better. Thank you. I had a ton of fun
Uh chat, hopefully you were wowed. Thank you for the a
And rt, I mean honestly, he's a great lad
Dude fully like all completely like i'm just telling you like the way that I see it
That your flip the house upside down house deserve to be up there. It deserved to be up there
Just did I was trying to I was trying to do something. It was a gimmick, but it was a memorable gimmick
It was very good. I can't do it again. That was that was the only time I got I gotta find a new gimmick for
For for house but for two
Uh, all right, dude. I'll uh, i'll talk to you soon. I'm ending now, too
All right. Bye germa chat. See you soon
All right, go go all of you go say hi to doug doug and congratulate him on being top of the class
I will see you guys in about i'm gonna be taking off for a little while
I've got some stuff I need to do. I got some work I need to do
So you'll see me probably on maybe sunday or monday. Keep an eye on the sus
I'll see you guys in like four or five days. Take care
Thank you so much for watching. This was a pretty wild experiment, but I think it was I feel like it was a success
I think I had a lot of fun
Hopefully it was worth watching for you and we'll try to set it up again when house slipper 2 comes out
Maybe get some other streamers in here get maybe more it was a good time. Take care of yourselves. Have a great night
Goodbye. Talk to you soon