Jesus, how long does it take for this guy to? Well, I got a coffee. I refilled the coffee. I got- I had the robe off.
I brushed my teeth.
Whatever. That- it came out really weird, didn't it?
Hey, hey, oh boo-boo. I'm smarter than the average bear, and I-
I brushed my teeth. I don't know what the fuck that was. Bernie. Yogi bear is not Bernie. No, it's- that's-
Oh, look at that. That's awesome. Fireman, but it's a snowman. What the heck? All right, let's go.
We're gonna play- I gotta change my title. This is wrong. It is not accurate. Let's put this on slime rancher, and then
slime
money game.
Slime money game. I don't know. Money. Money.
Yeah. All right, let's go. I am ready to begin streaming for real now. Hold this back. Can you see?
Can you see? Aha! All right, so what are we doing?
Last time I played, a few days ago, I had the chickens. I had the
cave set up, right? I got my auto feeder. Oh, yeah, I did a Rubik's Cube and shit. Yeah, I forgot about all that.
Yep, I got my strawberries.
This game's so good. Am I in just chatting? I shouldn't be. Did it not update?
Should be in slime rancher. Slime money game. Am I in the wrong category? I shouldn't be.
We good? I was the one guy. All right, whatever.
All right, let's go. The last thing I was doing, and now the thing I'm doing now.
Put a face cam on? No, no, no. No face cam right now.
Market looking like. No face cam. No, I don't do face cam. I don't do face cam.
I do face cam only when I'm like dressed with a bathrobe on, and then I take it off.
Oh, this is gonna be big money.
Let's do a money. Let's go around and sell the stuff. I got 50 rock ploys. Holy shit, nice.
How much are these worth? I have 3,200 bucks. I got a ton of money. I have so much money.
50. All right, hold on. I gotta do some shit here.
Refill the feeder. What do you guys eat? You eat anything?
You eat?
Okay, yeah.
Face cam or else?
That's very fucking threatening.
All right, let me go sell. Let me sell these. Ooh, 16. Perfect.
Look at this. Look at that money. Oh, so much. How about the tabby plorts? Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna have like five grand.
Very cool. All right, I can upgrade shit. Face cam. Why do you?
Why? What?
Why do you want a face cam on?
So, all right, so you want a face cam on so you get to see that you look in the corner and you get to see this.
Why?
Literally, yes. No, why though? But why? You've not given me an explanation why.
It's tiny and you get to watch me go like this sometimes.
I want an explanation because all right, you can have it on for 15 minutes, but now you can't see shit.
Just turn it off.
Now this can sit here. I'll give you 15 minutes of face cam and then I never want to hear it again.
Because we're creepers.
In the middle. No, it's staying right here. All right.
So now I want to feed these guys. I got I got to upgrade some shit, too.
Hide it in the health bar. No, this is fine right here.
Face cam is wicked cool, dude. Thanks, man.
Your face cam is a treat.
All right, let's collect the money from the cave. Now these guys like fruits, right? They like fruit and meat.
Oh, I had a new thing. I fucked something up before the scream ended last time.
Something got really messed up last time, right?
Oh, yeah, I have the hunter honeys.
Right, okay. I remember.
What else is over here? We have these exploding guys, which they eat
meat. Didn't bring any, but we'll just keep going.
Okay, fruit and meat.
These are the hunter jellies.
They get mad when I come over here. All right, so they eat fruit and meat.
So we need fruit. We need meat. These guys eat meat. All right, so let me go feed all these guys.
Why is he pretending to be interested? No, that's that's just a side effect of the face cam. Don't you understand?
Side effect of the face cam is you're watching me
Talk into a microphone while I bob my head around and say things like this. All right, so we have to go over this way, right?
You it's because it's a symptom of the face cam
Because I'm just talking normally and me just talking normally without like expression. It's just me, but I don't I'm like not interested
I have to go like this
Okay, so
We got 25 vegetables in there
What we got here?
Okay
Strawberries coming up soon
With the face cam on that's all the only way you can tell
Okay, these well, look at how cute these cats are so awesome. How much money do you guys think I'm gonna make today?
How about five hundred dollars ready? Let's do a test. You ready? What's my emotion like right now?
What about what's my emotion like right now?
Okay, so
Dollars that went up a little bit. I don't how was I horny?
$48 that went up a little you have no fucking idea. You need the face cam to tell you how it was
$48 that's not enough money. That's not enough money
$48 that's not enough money
My point the point I'm making is that's a symptom of the face cam being turned on because I'm just normally just hanging out
But I'm not enunciating enough for the face cam to be on
So acting
Turn the cam back on now, how long do they ask that I can keep that up?
I'm just talking like this you want emotion with the face cam
I'm gonna talk normally what the fuck is happening right now
When you turn don't ever when you turn 35, you just your voice turns into an old person. All right, here we go
So I'm we'll see how long I can keep this up because people want emotion with the face cam
How many do I need?
five
Okay, cool
Ten come out when you tend to it. So 10 or 12 come out each time
Take these fruits back over to where I was going
15 it's 15 15
We're gonna go feed the guys down here. They eat fruit and meat right 1 2 3 4 5
They're not hungry. Why they're not eating. What are these little cute guys? Why they're not eating. Oh, they eat meat
I had it wrong. I'm such a I'm such an idiot
I'm so stupid
These guys eat the fruit right? Who's in LA noir?
noir facial innovations
That's I'm gonna die
Good thing the face cam was just on otherwise. You would never know what my emotions look like
Get out of the cage
All right, stop
Stop exploding near me
stop I
Need to put an auto thing in there because these fucking dicks just keep exploding you little assholes
Tuck it up exploding dicks
Okay. Oh, I don't all right. So now
This is a hunter over here. I want hunter. What was the other thing? I want to do hunter. What?
Music box will calm them down. Don't I already have a music box in here? I already have a music box in here
Yeah, it's like what's going on here. It was hunter. What?
Hunter and cat right or did I want to do hunter hunter and honey is over there
So I need to put hunter cubes over there. I need to feed this guy
You want me get the chicken get a bunch of chickens come back over here?
I got six of these honey plorts who hold on these guys have making some
What about huddle hunter that be cool? I'm every kind of cool
Puddles don't mix. Oh, you just sell puddle blorts. That's all you can do with them
Yes, really it worth a lot honey ones are worth 52. I want to save the honey ones
All right. I need to feed. Let's get some chickens. What the fuck is this 1080 frame rate? It's a 1080 graphics card
So you go
Okay, elder rooster. Whatever. I need I need to get a rooster in here
And I need a rooster. I gotta go. Okay, remind me to get a rooster. These guys have these guys switch beam again
Yeah, eat eat eat eat eat eat eat eat
All right, you guys eat meat
What are you guys eat fruit and meat?
Let's get some
There you go. You know, I need to get a rooster. I will you get out
Get back in there. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. What about explosive hunter?
Everybody still haven't eaten
So I do cat hunter but I do know that's mm-hmm explosive hunter
I think I want to do explosive hunter at the rooster. I know but hold on a second
Wait until you get a new thing. Yeah, that's probably a good idea. I'll just sell this stuff
Here eat that
Get back in the cage, I gotta put a auto collector over here too. These guys are annoying I
Just I'll just do it. Just put it in like what's it? What am I doing?
Autocollector all of them. I just run run and put a ceiling on this fucking thing
Reminder get a rooster. I know I know get a rooster. Stop it
all of you eat up
When I get a rooster y'all better stop this nonsense
Hunter ooh, nice hunter plort honey plort
or eat the hunter I will
That's good. Okay. Everyone collected. What do you eat meat? Oh shit. Hold on
You already eat that bird
Got that bird already. All right. Well, whatever. I'd love just run around collecting things. It's so
It scratches so many itches in my brain
I could run I could run around in a circle in this game and just feed and collect stuff
I could do this for the next five days. All right. What do you go? We good? All right, I
Want to go explore cuz I want to find a new slime at a rooster. I'm gonna go get one right now
I'm gonna go go in right now. But first here we go power core mk2
I do anything with the chip with us with the check at $4,000
What else can I upgrade I do anything else with these guys I could do a solar shield music box
What else should I do here? I could buy another plot. Wait. Oh
Shit the overgrowth. Let's go
This is new. Oh, yeah, I remember I'm soft lock myself in here, right? Okay, so what's over here?
Nice nice nice nice nice nice. Oh this look at chickens and a rooster get a rooster
Well, there's no roosters over here, but hold on what plots?
What's this say II I built this area myself
I'm just dumping an entire coffee on my ground on my desk and everything
Just this just like makes me feel cool. All right
Remember get a rooster. I will what's down here another area
This is 5,000 for the docks. All right, I can't do this yet. Where does this take me? Oh
Shit, that's really really important. I don't have to run all the way anymore. That's awesome. Thank God
Oh, thank God. All right. First of all, it's not graceful. All right, let's go back
I want to put these things away. I'm gonna buy a plot right
Hmm right here. Where should I buy the plot? This is another way to go. Oh shit. Cool
Rooster rooster. I know I'm gonna get a rooster. I'm gonna build another den here. Hey, you know what? I'm gonna have this be for now
Whatever. I got a lot of money. I'm gonna do mk3. What okay to whatever it is. I'm just preparing myself
Yeah, I'm gonna upgrade. I bought the new area
MK to and go I buy a heart module. Why not? I mean just get it just get all this stuff
I have the money pulse wave adds a pulse wave feature to your backpack that pushes away slime. We need some space. Okay
Oops, get a rooster. Oh my god guys. I meant remind me to get a rooster not spam get a rooster. Oh
Take these out. Oh my god. What am I doing? Oh
I'm gonna save the hunter ones. I'm gonna I'm gonna sell the honey ones and the boom ones. Let's make some more money
I'm gonna pull out
So honey's worth a lot
Well off rancher. I back up to 2800 bucks feed the hunter. It's making me sad. I I
Will feed the hunter? Oh eat get it. He doesn't even want he's not hungry
And I'll give me some plorts
only one port but
My god one plort Andy
tell
USB plort
Make more jellies. I know but it's said this this really is a game
This is just my my ADHD cannot handle this but I'm doing fine
You know, I mean, I love this shit
This is one of those games where I can just keep I can lose track
Every five seconds and I could still be I'm still making progress doesn't matter. It's a perfect game
It's a perfect game for me. I could look right now. I wasn't even paying attention to the game
I have no idea what I'm doing right now. I guess I was picking up fruit from this tree
Making progress doesn't matter how weird it is. I don't I just not doing it. I don't even know I was doing it
Again, here we are. Like I'm gonna go sell
It's just scratching an itch brain. This is a brain scratching game
Where the hunter ports over here?
Let's store the actually. Yeah
Yeah, wait, who do you see somebody does? Yeah, you guys do. I okay. I'm gonna tell you guys right now
It's time to make some progress. I think it's time to replace these cats. I think I mean we're not doing pink blorts pink blorts
still
Six hours into the game. I don't know about that. I think it's time to replace them
I think it's time to let them free
Yes, finally, I think it's time we put um, like
More expensive ones in here. We need a rooster. All right, let me hold on. What do these guys eat? Fuck
I can't stop veggies and meat. No, you don't eat that
It's always a button to press
All right, we're gonna replace all these guys within with like bombs and stuff. Okay, cool. That's the next plan
I'm gonna put a bunch of hunters in here store this
Just walk over there dude. Alright, it's time to go and explore. I need to go. I need a rooster. That's important
so here we go, I'm going to that place I was before on this way and
That's chickens. We don't want chickens. I'm gonna pick up a rooster
Here we go. Eat the game already. I don't think you beat this game. Is there credits in the game?
There are okay
Finally well, I had to get myself ready
Hey, there is no finally in slime rancher
I have pink slimes and I have to replace them, but I like the pink slime
So I want to keep them around they are friends
Rooster I'll take you though
1080 omega low what get a rooster. I will thank you for the reminder. I appreciate it
Okay, I'm gonna get bomb slimes. We're gonna we're doing bomb slimes. I want a bunch of them
Cuz I'm gonna do bomb and something else and I'm gonna place the pink slimes with bomb slimes
I'm lagging. I shouldn't be frames a bed. I think I was like open
PS frames are dying. This is doing this before
Was doing it before it's just at the game
It's the game. Oh, okay. I mean his rides run. I'm fine
Okay, I want more bomb slimes. What are you?
You're a honey boom
Largo you give me
One boom. Oh, thanks for the toss. I'll take it with me
X hell dies big up
boom
Cool decoration. Oh, okay. Can I make that jump with the rocket?
Probably not highly doubt it. I want at least like 10 to 20 bombs
We're gonna put them
I'm gonna do bomb hunter
That's gonna be valuable shit
Very valuable shit. I'm telling you right now
I
Mean me more
We're just gonna go farm bombs and farm hunters
I'm gonna be a trillionaire. I need a rooster to
Give us fucking air shots
Nice nice, dude
Nice, dude. No rooster though. I have to go to the other area
Ice cream cat. Nope, we don't we don't we don't do cats anymore. We're not doing cats
We want hunters honey and bombs and we're gonna replace everybody
Everybody's getting replaced. No, I don't want a pink sign. What a where this this area is huge. Why?
No, oh, hold on
Rooster let's go eat. He's replacing us. Oh
It's 12 enough for now. I think probably I need hunters
What do I get hunters man ugly face off-screen already
Rooster wait, there's a key over here. I need a slime key
bombs bombs bombs
Very cool and that guy forever. Um, it doesn't I don't think I can even do that. We go all the way up
She was up here. Where's the damn rooster? I don't know. I'm just trying to collect booms limes
I'm gonna do hunter boom. It's gonna be awesome that
rooster
Help him. Oh, he likes it. He likes the water. Okay
Any more booms limes? I see you up there
Okay, I want 20 20 booms limes and I'll be happy
Come on, Gwen. Let's go
Are you at?
I'm gonna take a right up here and go all the way down here
Remember to get a rooster. I just got one. I have one in my inventory right now
Thanks for the reminder get another one. I mean if one shows up, I'll get it. I
Want to go this way? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Okay, that's what I want right there get Ross here. Let me see if I could find anything
That looks pretty good to me. Look down on all these guys and see what's here. Oh, there we go
I don't want those. I want hunters. I kind of want to take the skin off the honey slimes
I keep thinking they're pink. Is that all that's over here? Come on, really?
Smoking I want to go I can't go this way
Just like a climb this mushroom. I don't get up there. I'll take care of it
Got it. Nice. I guess I could jump on the mushrooms go up there. But hold on. I want my stupid thing to work
Okay. Ooh, what's that?
Yeah, I'm all the way down here. Where are all the hunters at one guy spam?
one guy spam
What I say one of the least 20 there it is nice perfect it's puddles here. Mm-hmm
You're gonna have a shitload of these boom slimes. Oh
What's this? Oh, well, I got a rooster here. I got what I wanted 23 boom slimes
All right, it's time to replace you guys
Boom slimes have to be out at night. Do I have to put these guys in the nighttime den?
Or can they go out in the daytime? They can just be anywhere. So what do I do with these guys?
I don't know. What do I do with them? I have to incinerate them. You throw them away
do
Throw them away
Keep them. I guess I could keep them just to have a generator of though. Hold on. I have room in here
Yeah, I've got plenty of room. I got plenty of room
Now I don't need to do that yet. But that that food is scarce if booms eat meat
Yeah, we're gonna run out of food. What do these guys do rock rock and cat and you eat veggies and meat
These guys. Mm-hmm putting them up here rock and cat
They're going away. I'm just gonna
Look be free. I'm not gonna kill them. I'm just letting them go out to like the wilderness
Cuz I have a feeling I'm gonna need pink or something for some reason. I'll leave one. I'll leave pink
As we have to this is rock we have rock cat. No get no. No, no, no, no, no be free be free
Be free, you know, don't come back here. Stay out of here. Go this way
There's food over here
both
Why can they they miss you? I know but they don't kill it. No
I can't I'll just shoot it into the fucking stratosphere
Then it'll find a home stop coming back here. They're gonna eat the fucking food. That was really sad. I'm sorry. All right
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. We didn't know
Check this out. Now. We're gonna feed hunter plorts boom hunter. There's an over here
How many do I have a five? Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good
Easy easy easy easy easy
Here we go
Hunter booms. Oh this angel lid
Shit, I need a music box. Settle down settle down settle down settle down. Do I have a music box?
How do I get them to stop doing this? They eat meat
Okay meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat
Boop-boop, I need more than that
Let's feed the hell out of these things. I'm not out and then they're gonna feed the hell out of each other
They're gonna all turn into hunters. This is gonna be a moneymaker
Pull it up you back in there jeez
Don't feed the rooster. Isn't that an old rooster?
That's an old rooster the old roosters can still do that
I didn't know that it's too overpopulated in here
It really is so overpopulated. I think we have to take some out
How many do we take out? I think they're fine. I need to eat. They need to eat more chickens at the music box
It's already on. All right. I am out of I am out of hens. I
Need to go on it on a hen
I gotta get a bunch of hens. It's not yes it is. Oh
Fuck eat eat and then multiply
How we doing good? I see a ploid in there. All right, they're good. I need more hunter ploids
Sell all this shit. What are they worth? Yeah, go 3300. Let's go. Let's take a quest
Do water at them to calm them down. I'm down in there
everybody relax
quiet
Be good
Whatever. What's the quest?
Thor what he got don't suppose you could also get a cup of sugar kicking around
You want a rooster for okay. I can that can be done. That's a little that's my only rooster though
I'll get I'll get more
No, leave you here I'll get okay we're going on all right, here we go. I need roosters. I have for those already. Oh
Jesus look at this over cropping. Oh
Shit
No deal. No deal. Oh my god over cropage. What do I do? I have to I have to auto feed this stuff
Okay, we had a lot of overcroppage there. So now um, I know you guys are hungry, but
You want everything?
Hold on
Yeah, I've auto feeder on this thing to auto feeder purchase and yeah, all right, whatever. Let's go fill it up
They these guys eat everything
20 and make sure this one has like 20
These guys are good. Okay, you're fine. Now now we're gonna go like this
There you go. Cool
All right
Fill this up to like 20 or whatever. Okay fruits
These guys only eat meat who eats the fruits in here more hens by buying the hen
Hey
Fight her
Is this auto feeder?
I auto feeding these guys eat meat. Everyone else eats meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat meat
I need meat and even more birds
When the final match for that song
Do do do the doon do the tailor boomer all the way with voodoo dr. Jekyll and Hyde and do learn bub to do it
Right play fighter
I want to hear that right now play fighter. What was it? It was the like director's cut 63 and a third
What what what was that play fighter 64?
Sculpted here it is. Yeah
This is dmca the game's like fucking 50 years old. This is it
That's cool
They don't they don't make them like they used to they don't make them like they used to
Remember how good video games were they don't make them like that anymore
Yeah, they do fortnight the person's somebody wrote do something funny
But they hit enter too quickly and it was do something if you and then they were just like do something follow. I was too angry
Alright, I need a rooster and seven of those flying things. I'll go get them right now. I need rooster
I need chickens a lot of them chickens chicken. This is a chicken run
Goodness shitload of community subs. What's going on here Lenny? The person just gave 20 community subs. That's a lot
That's a ton of community subs. Thank you Lenny
We had five from soda cat five from stormy chew and five from mega dial
Thank you guys
Lenny
20 subs, it's a lot of fucking subs. Nah, they don't make them like they used to
Don't swear my kid is here
It's this is what are you talking about?
The cam back on right now
No, I was I embarrassed myself and that's how I then I run away for like 40 minutes. That's how this works
chickens only chickens and and chickadoos only
and roosters
Yeah away from them. He's a mine
the roosters chickadoos chickens
Chickens only chickens roosters chickadoos
Another five subs from mega dial. Thanks
Thanks mega dial. It's 10 from you
And community subs
All right, I have a lot of chickens now I need a couple of roosters
Let's go dump these guys
Chickadoo, chickadoo, chickadoo, chickadoo, chickadoo
What's going on with the subs? Another
Mingus, thanks for the five community subs Mingus
And from queen luigi what's going on here? What are you guys doing this?
He doesn't care. No, no, no, I'm good. Thank you for the thanks for the 10 subs queen luigi. That's a lot
He doesn't care. No, I don't
I do I don't it sounded weird when I said that I don't
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you got me. That was weird semantics there. I was like I do
I don't I don't
I don't know why I did like a bernie. I do I do you guys give me a shitload of money. Okay, of course
I'll be nothing without the community subs and the subs and the long-term subs and the bits and the years of people watching youtube videos
Of course, I'm nothing without you
But thanks seriously. Thanks with five subs things with 10 subs
All right. I have so many chickens now. Let's go back. I didn't get a rooster though
cry
Okay
Relax. I need a rooster. I have so many chickens. They're gonna they're gonna fall out of the cave
Stony chick chickadoo this one rooster
Fuck
I wish how do I get back to town? Oh my god, there's so many
Are they all gonna fit in this pen?
I don't think i'm gonna fit. Oh my god, stop spawning them
Jesus, okay. Um, who the hell is they keep spawning?
I have to pee
Really bad just drinking coffee
All right. This is my last run around to get a bunch of that spawned and i'm getting out of here. I'm leaving i'm done
That's it. I'm leaving
I'm out. I'm leaving i'm leaving i'm leaving right here. I'm done
Go pee in a gamer bottle. No
All right. Here we go
This is it's gonna be overflowed
All right. Let's take 20
This has got a lid on it, right? They're not gonna leave are they?
You just eat that
All right, who likes meat?
You do you like meat?
All you guys love meat
So we're gonna auto feed
I'm gonna put hens in here
There you go now you have an endless supply of hens to eat
Looking good
I think it's time to do a small. Oh fuck. I forgot about this quest
One rooster and seven flying bugs
Rooster it's nighttime, right?
Rooster. Oh
Yes, you're dressed
And I don't even want to pick it up. What slime do you think tastes the best?
um
ice cream cat
But that's very rare. You don't ever get to see ice cream cat, but I would say that one
Excuse me. I'll take seven of these guys, right?
Where honey slime? Um
Oh my god, it's a rooster motherload
There's another one. Where's it? There's another one up there. You don't like honey. No, I do
I mean, I just think ice
Okay, if you gave me a choice to eat ice cream or like a spoonful of honey, I would probably pick ice cream
Wouldn't you?
I mean, I like honey
I would probably pick the ice cream. Okay. I need two more of these guys
Adam, let's go
I love honey. I mean a nice vanilla ice cream with like whipped cream on it versus like a spoonful of honey
I don't know
I gotta go back
Back. No wrong way. He doesn't care go back and save them
Go back and say honey on ice cream. Well, there you go. There's your best take. Okay. Oh dear
This is gonna get overrun
Okay, you wanted a rooster. I got one for you and then you wanted seven of these
Thank you
Hunter plort cool. That's what I want
A lot of carrots. Uh, i'm gonna throw this in here. One of you guys are gonna eat it
cool
We collect in here at 14 hens
activate
Hunter plort just recycle this back in here
Oh, we're really gonna be in the money. It's gonna be awesome. This game has viva piñata energy
Yeah, I mean, um
I I like this game more than viva piñata
I I just I don't know. I like it a lot. It's too many of them jerma
Um for now
I'll say i'll probably don't
We're gonna replace the cats over here with see these guys when they'll give them a bigger space
How's this going?
Got food in here 14
Okay, good. Let's store the carrots in case I need them for anything. Oh, I still have those like whatever store the carrots
Take some hens out
Because there are too many now
All right. Now we're good. I'm gonna put some
You call yourself a jerma fan laughable check, man. I'm fucking loaded on channel points. All right. I mean really
We'll do that
Into here. What should I buy?
These guys these being auto fed they are. All right, nice
Ooh, that's a lot
This has an auto feeder too, doesn't it? You guys want meat?
No auto feeder, but here you go
These guys love fruit and meat. So we're just gonna give them give them meat
Suck that up
You want is there even in here still?
Is this you call yourself? All right, what the hell are you guys up to?
What do you guys think you're doing?
What is this?
I'm gonna turn on sub only
You guys wait hell you guys
Hey, hey
Guys, you can't you can't substitute teacher me. Okay
Oh the teacher's not here today
We can do it. We can make like noises and like scream and we can sit on different desks and talk all day
No, you can't actually because i'm an adult and I control the room
So i'm not wait, there's not a sub here today, all right bring those hunter plorts back up
These guys look pretty good hunter plorts
You guys look pretty good
You smell like a sub
You mean like a fucking sandwich?
Hey
What are you talking about?
Is there a lid on this? How does he keep getting out?
Why can't I put him back in?
How do you keep getting out?
Get in
What how are they getting out?
It's too many. Hey, where's the lid?
Too many bumps make the net recharge. How long does it take to recharge it?
Settle down
Takes two hours
Do you have to sit here and babysit these guys for two hours? Stop blowing up
Feed them. I don't have any food
Like two hours in a game you mean like so in like a minute a few minutes
Is it on there?
I think it's on there
Yeah, it's on there. All right. We're good
How you doing at this point? I should just throw you over there
What do you mean? It's in real life. No, they're in they're in
All right. I'm just gonna get away from them. Okay, i've collected
All right, let's go
Collect all this shit too. Nice
Music box, it's already on
Look kind of like Willem Dafoe
I don't what are you talking about?
What the fuck is that?
Is the who the fuck is that?
Is this guy talking about?
Is it like an actor or like a author or something what the fuck are you talking about?
All right, I need to hunt the plorts
All right fill up this cage with more hunter bombs
oops
All right, there's too many in here
There were way too many in here. You're right. I need another cave
Oh fuck the lid's up the lid's off the lid's off the lid's up. I need another cave
I gotta get rid of you guys are gone. Bye. Goodbye. Goodbye. All these cats are gone
That was fun. It was fun where they lasted but I don't need them anymore
We're gonna separate this up
Yep, it was fun. They were cool. They were very cute while it lasted, but that's it
Sorry guys
I mean, but we gotta I gotta take care of this
Get rid of the rock ones
Read the instructions what you walked over an empty spot. What do you mean? Where?
Hope you're
Shit kill the rock ones. All right, we're gonna get rid of the rock ones
read
Next to explosive hunter. Oh my god. There's another one
relax
He died twice
Oh flop
flop away
Come here
Come here. I'll recharge you
Why are they so angry?
Give me the one that's turned off
Feed them. I need to separate them first
What do they eat? They eat meat only
oh
Fuck do you think big chungus is funny? Of course I do
Is everyone in the game stop looking at big chungus? What the fuck that's so funny
there
Everybody relax
Okay. Are you guys good now?
Give me these hunter ploys. Hell. Yeah. Oh look at all these boom plorts
Can you guys relax now? I need to put a few more over here fucking blew over my face again. Oh my god
How do I switch these guys over?
What's the safe way to do this?
Just feed them they've eaten two dozen chickens
There's food in here. They ain't wanting to touch
Let's just never stop eating stuff. Oh my god
Did I lose all those plorts?
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me
I wish I could make a just a big long one
Come here you little asshole. Oh my god
Wait, you know what? I'm about to just demolish it and just put in fucking something safe over here
I had like 40 bomb plorts too. I am so mad about that
Oh my god, how do you keep these motherfuckers? How do you what am I supposed to do?
You can't keep these guys
They're um, they're insane
I have too many
Did one of them die?
Get in there. All right. I'm gonna get two more from this
Okay, I think we're good one more from this over that side that's gonna be good
This is worth a lot of money. It's worth it
Okay, I think we're good. Does that look even looks about even right?
Okay good
I'll eat
Just don't kill me
Auto feed the hell out of them
Fucking fruits are on the ground. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Hold on. I have no food
Shit, I will eventually
um
Get a rooster. All right. Now I gotta I was supposed to make money from this and it's annoying me
Recreate the chicken sound for half a half a billion off. That's not even you're not gonna give me that
Okay, there we are now i've got money to get i'm gonna have to get a lot of money
I need more meat
Okay, we're good meat meat meat meat. I need meat
Just suck up these. Um
3,700. All right. What do I what do I want?
Get out of the cage. No, all right. We're good. I need to do
Hmm
Makes lives that don't want me. Yeah, but those guys pay off huge. I just made like 1500 bucks
Let's fill up these things look at how many of these oh shit. All right. I can this is a payday. This is a payday right here
20 put 20 in there
20 in here
Go to the infinite chicken zone. That's true. I could do that after I sell
Honey hunter is better than boom hunter
No, you're probably right
Boom is worth a lot of money. Okay, let me get this shit out of here
All right, 50 50 50 50. All right sell
Get the funny meme line. Mr. Albertson. I don't know which one
I must have 5k
Okay
upgrades
Power core mk3. Yep, and give me the extra heart
I'm fully upgraded now. Perfect. The wicked funny one, which one
5k andy one
All right. I need meat a lot of meat
Too much one would probably say let me fill up the feeding tube thingy
We feed up the feeding tube for these guys. These guys want fruit. I'll give it to you
30 these guys want meat these guys want fruit and meat
I don't have an auto feeder here. Let's get that fixed
Load this up with fruits. Where'd you come from?
Come back and check on you. Go ahead and feed this guy. He's probably really hungry
He's been sitting here for like three days without any food
Go ahead. He fell asleep before he could bite it. There you go
There you go
Good boy. There you go. Good boy
There you go. Good boy
There you go
Don't do that
There you go. Good boy
All right, now i'm gonna go i'm on a meat adventure now
Three thousand bucks time for a meat adventure. Hold on
Built the water tank works
cool
Oh, this game is cute. It's very cute
Let's get rid of these
If I land the shot right now, it's one billion off the debt if I miss it. It's two billion added
I'm just i'm not doing that. I'm just kidding a billion up
You're gonna fail no i'm just kidding the deal that was no deal that was a fake deal
I don't want cats anymore. I'll sell this
So we have just carrots over here. Okay
This is a meat run. I need a bunch of chickens
Chickens were this way. We're just gonna go on a chicken run
That's it
We're not doing anything else besides what the hell is this for? Okay, cool. I have another pen over here
I forgot to pee. I'll be right back. So I have a question if you guys are peed so much
That you sit there and wonder
How it's possible that could even be in your body?
Like what does it look like inside of your body?
so long
I just peed out what could have been measured as a 32 ounce gatorade
That was inside of my
belly
It's weird. It's too much you belly
I don't get it dude. Why are they titans?
We already went over that that I was
That was bait i've seen the whole series
All right, let's go
I love this game. This game is perfect
Explain one of the what you want. I'm not we're not going to talk about a show
That a bunch of people might not have watched
We only do that with star wars and like marvel stuff
Not taking money from fuel. I just think it's good
That's true
You little little pug champ
All right, let's go after this one
Hmm very very cool piss
All right back to slime rancher
So i'm just this is this is a hen run
Just gonna get chickens
I'm gonna get as many as I can
And you know what?
Yeah, it's just chickens only chickens chickens and hens and roosters
And you know, i'm gonna have to do I gotta yeah. Yeah. Yep
uh
Yeah
I need more than one
I need a second coop
I need another coop, but I really would like them to be next to each other
I'm gonna move this
Can I move this?
I want them right next to each other
Go exploring
Yeah, but I I want to make a second coop. I have a lot of meat eaters. I need two coops
Oh, I guess it's gonna be down here. Whatever get in there
vitamins
high walls
grass
All right. I need more. This is the best place for chickens. Oh cool
Oh, let's get a shitload of them
Any roosters over here?
All right. Um, i'm gonna explore here a little bit
I've not been in this zone yet. Have I?
All right. What if I want to go? I want to go over here, right?
It's a good place to go looking around
There's a cat over there. Oh
What's down here?
Oh lots of chickens
Yes
Oh
Nice just keep popping out
big cat
And there's a treasure chest over there
Um, he likes meat shit. Well, I can't do it yet
I can't do that yet. Not yet. I'll be back
Am I probably gonna get a key out of that guy?
Make that I don't think I can make that
make the gun
suck noise
Chickens chickens chickens. Okay
I need a couple more roosters. What do you get roosters?
Um, there's a door
damn it
Where is this all the way up here? Okay
Hey albion. Thanks for the 10
You know how I say, you know how we say it on this channel. How do we say it guys? What do we do?
Thanks for the 10
How do we say it here? Come on. How do we yes, i'm just you know, nobody's saying it
None of you are saying it
There it is. You got muted yourselves. Thank you
All right, this is enough for now. What's this beach ball? I'm taking this
We say thanks for the ten dollars sucker
No, we don't
that ball
I'm gonna put this in a side. Uh, we're gonna have a slime thing over here, too
All right, that should help generate some more meat
In fact, I need to feed some shit now
That's a thank you vin smoke for the five
community, so
All right, these guys will breed that'll be good
I can have like let's go feed people. I don't know. How many do we need in here realistically like three or four?
I got the chickens
So many are in here. Okay, cool
chickens over here more
holy shit
Need two or three. Okay, I got 25. Let's go feed people and make some money
And then I need to go find some new slimes
I need to go deeper into
Where?
I have here unlocked
All this how do I get over here? Just feed the big, uh grotto guy
Feed the big cat just feed that just feed the big cat like a hundred chickens
How many how many do we need to feed him?
50 holy shit, okay
Geez, all right. Well, i'm just
All right. I got 26
I think I could just run around and collect 50 in that area. Can't I look right around here?
You need it's got to be 50. You gotta beat it yourself
If the government already sells
How much is this? This is for the docs. It's
5,000
Wrong way andy
I'm going i'm just waiting for them to spawn
Hey andy
Like your mail
Yeah, I really should
Hey andy, how are you doing today might have well that but that's my name is not andy
You know what I mean? That's
uh
Come on chickens. Let's go
Like a 31
I don't care about this. I just want chickens
Just want chickens
Well, just here. There you go. I almost didn't make that jump. All right. Here you go. Here's 30 of these
All right, that's a lot
I just fed you so much. You better be worth it
19 more it's not worth it. He doesn't have a key
Oh god, he doesn't have a key
He what is it? What's going on?
I want to make a formal apology
I was the guy in the last stream who yelled at you to dump the water while not knowing the water was its own slot
I really hope you can forgive me and not quote ban that guy that guy being myself
I mean this is
You were timed out for 20 minutes. Now. You've just got yourself timed out for fucking 40
Ooh more chickens
I was that guy. I was that guy that said that you dumped the water
A grand formal apology. All right, keep grab these guys
I need
Uh this mother of this go back this way
He doesn't sound like he accepts the apology
Uh, i'm gonna move some roosters. There's too many roosters over here
There's way too many roosters. Okay
Do I accept the apology?
Of course I accept the apology but that I mean things don't come without punishments
I I I need
Seven or eight more
Come on, let's go
I'm just gonna go to sleep and wake up
If you rob a bank
I mean, yeah, of course like after you rob that bank you serve your time and like come on out
Go go to serve your time though. You call me fucking 5k. Andy. You're gonna get
You're going to fucking twitch jail for a minute. He already did. He already went to jail. That's right
So my boy I put him back in because I he annoyed me. That's not how that works
He already served. Yeah, he already served his time
And then he got out and said hey, i'm sorry about that. I wanted to just say i'm sorry and I served my time
Get back in jail
That's right. That's true
750 bucks double or nothing. No
Mean boy, andy
Punish andy
What are you talking about
Me what's mean boy
You
Oh, i'm gonna sell this can I hit it from here if I hit off the debt
Yeah, I should fucking bet. I should have bet. Oh man. I should I did I heard it. Did you see I heard I did it
I heard it. I said if I want to take a billion off the bet off the debt
Whatever i'm gonna get these hold
Okay, uh refill the food
and 20
21 that's fine
You guys want meat, but I can't give it to you right now. I'm trying to feed a big cat
So i'm gonna go to sleep and wake up and help with these new chickens. Let's go
The big storm. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Mm-hmm. How about uh, should I buy the rewards thing? I have money. What did that do?
fence upgrade
Yeah
path upgrade
What does this get me?
It's aesthetic. It's aesthetic
It doesn't do anything. It's just aesthetic. Oh, oh man, really
That was like two thousand dollars
Actually scammed. It's all right
Hey looking good
Looking good
You guys want some fruits?
I've got no you want meat only
Okay
chickens
You want?
I have a puddle in the other room
All right chickens, let's go. It's way too early to do that stuff. Okay
That's a lot of chickens chickens. Nope. I don't want fog fruits. No, I want you
chickens spawns
Aha
I believe I have enough to feed that cat the whole way
I definitely do. Okay, let's go
Let's feed the big cat get a reward
I gave him 30 already 31. I I definitely have to have enough for this
Yeah, I think this area looks cool
more
More here it is
Oh shit, can I make
What's in there
What was in there? What was in there? What was in there? What was in there? What was in there? What was in there?
This
Where the hell does this take you? Um, where am I? Where am I? It's an island
Oh, is there new other slimes here?
Oh i'm over here. Oh shit. All right, cool
um
He wanted one of these
I'll take a few of them. I have the puddle. I'll put them in there. I'll put the extras in there
Ooh
This is water and stuff. Cool. This is awesome. All right. Awesome. Cool
New island new island same old slugs though. You gotta be something on here new island same old slugs
Same old slugs. What's up top?
Oh, hello
I know what you're gonna give me. You gotta get a key from this guy eat away
And go that's the key. I'll take it nice. Okay, so I can open another door
What door should I open? There's two there's three that I had there's two or three that I can open
Oh, okay
Get the cave get the cave get the cave get the cave cave door cave door cave door cave door cave door
Keep going
cave door
What's this?
Ooh
gilded
Secret style gilded
All right, this is end game stuff
Can't go higher than that
All right. Well i'm gonna i gotta open a door. Whoa
No end game. All right. Yeah, that's cool though
So you guys want to go to the cave door?
Which cave door are you talking about? I didn't think I want pink slimes too. I feel like you did I wanted the forest
That guy wanted pink slimes
I know he did
He's like seven eight of them
Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here
All right, let's get out of here
Forest help them help them. They'll be fine
Ooh, what about down here?
Did I look over here yet?
All right, is the whole perimeter
All right, I need that teleporter. I didn't get how do I get out of here? Where's the port?
What's the port the teleporter?
How do I sleep at night?
very soundly
Where was that teleporter? Was it up higher?
Where is this thing? I have to burn in my memory where this is. Where is it? It's not on the map. Is it?
Where is it?
Northeast sea level like up here
Northeast sea level there it is
Yeah, what a perfect way to okay. Let me burn this in my man. All right
Thank you for that. Thank northeast sea level
That's so much better than just saying
blind up
up blind
Northeast sea level. Holy shit. What a perfect way to describe that
Ooh
What do I do? I don't need the puddle slimes
I want these
It's too many roosters to give up. All right now give me up
Oh
Where are they? They live in the water. Where are they? I needed one
I'm shit
Don't they live in the water?
I think they're gone
a tiger
Cute. Oh, well. Oh, that's cool. That's gonna mess me up though. I'm gonna yeah, I'm gonna think they're a different animal
That's gonna mess me up
Got the key. Let's keep going
Okay
Look at all these
Now we feed everybody make some money open the secret door
continue
Ah, this game is fucking phenomenal
Like is anybody in this chat not have this game is anybody here not own this
I don't you don't you gotta get the you got you gotta get on this man
Hey, yeah, you gotta get on this man
No, it's up to you
Ear pressure doesn't work on me
God damn it
I have to take
I gotta take one of the slimes from inside. That's 750 bucks. That's good money
Yeah
I'll just go get one of the pond slimes in here. Hold on
Is this too many roosters?
Feed them these guys should be getting auto fed. They are
These guys should also be getting these guys want meat. All right, these guys are hungry
Here we go. We're gonna get we're gonna feed we're gonna make money
some more food
Welcome to flavor town
Yeah, this is let's feed them some roosters. There's too many in here
It was dizzy bird
All right, I think slimes just throw these guys away I don't need them for anything
Another uh activate
All right, we need to feed the other ones, you know speed that up
Super feed
I have to sell this stuff. It's getting overloaded
63 of these shit. Okay. Hold on
It's so satisfying i'll come back
Okay, i'll be back
Okay
Sell sell sell
50 rock blorts which have gone down in value, but it don't matter when you have a lot of them
You can make some money
Dump it
Don't be don't be
I remember when I remember when dump it was funny
in 2016
I thought it was funny before you thought it was funny. I thought it was funny before you thought it was funny
I thought it was funny before you thought it was funny. I was in crypto in 2017. I thought it was funny first
What do I feel like that's the energy of like every reddit comment i've ever read
All right, uh boom it up
Let's get some rest
Now it's time
We're gonna give this guy one puddle slime because seven hair fit. That's a lot of money
That's a lot of money. That's nothing to like
Let's sniff out or whatever
What is it did a hunter die out here? Whoa you got out
Back in there. Where did you?
Hell yeah, where'd these guys come from?
What oh my god, what happened?
It's because these little shits get get the fuck out of here. How do I kill?
Where's the slash murder button get out of here?
Don't come back. It's a good haul
Pretty good haul
22 hunter ploys cool
Uh, I got four minutes. Sorry. I'm good. I'm good sell all these hunter boards
What are they worth?
They're worth, uh 54 nice
And i'm gonna go to the forest i'm gonna go open that door
Sounds good to me. What about chickens?
Do we have a good chicken?
Going good
What about in here? What about the gold? How much is gold worth now?
Or oh eight. Holy shit. Should I sell it?
Maybe I should sell it
Hold it. Hold it. Hold hold hold hold
hold
All right, i'm gonna feed these carrots to the people in here i'm gonna take some meat in here too
And do one more haul
Need some meat. I need chickens
I just oh
chicken
Well, it's chicken
Oh, all right. We got we got a we got a decent amount in here
It's like 15
Well, I don't want to take the whole population
Pretty good. You get in there
You belong in there
oh well
Okay
Let's go feed the guys in the cave and then i'm gonna go
To the next area
And get some new slimes and shit. This is gonna be awesome. I can't wait
Which means more money, which is like holy shit cool
And that direct sucked
I think that person just watched it
Quest oh shit, right, right, right, right. Hold on. I'll do it
Uh, you guys want fruit and meat fruits
Okay, and then you guys want hold on
What do you guys eat? You guys eat the meat?
Okay, give me the uh puddle
Hurry hurry hurry hurry
No, stupid. I don't
Oh plorts
I'm good. There goes 750 and
Hunter plorts, um, I don't want pink you give me pink plorts at this far end of the game
One hunter plor that's it
All right. Hold on. Let me let me clear this up. I gotta do some cleaning up
Let me do some cleaning up first
You're back
And you're gonna mess you you almost just screwed the whole thing up
so
I'm here
See you in hell
How we doing
Get the fuck out of here. You're gonna fucking ruin everything
Get the fuck out of here. Get out of here. Get out. Don't come back
Okay
Cool. Let's go
Collect the money from in here
Sell clean up a little bit maybe do a little bit of upgrades and then keep going
This it's distraction the game
What we got? Okay tons of fruits in here
No, why do I still hear the music? Can I just like crush these in my hand? I don't even want these they're fucking worthless
Fruit and meat. All right, you guys are good
Fuck there's so many of these
Oh god, damn it. There's so many things
What do you guys eat? Fuck fruits and meats. Oh my god, there's too many things. Give me these back
Okay. Oh my god, I need to harvest this
Now these guys have already eaten. I've already collected good
These guys have a bunch of carrots to eat
70 fucking things to take
50 40, I don't know. Oh my goodness. It's too many things. Okay, I gotta slow down
So
Sell these stupid pink worthless plorts
Fuck you
Okay
Beats who wants beats just store them and then go back in there with
All right. I'm almost ready
almost
now I need to
Be drunk. No, this is so many things to do
These guys are they got food. They're ready these guys down here
This has been sucked up. Thank you. I will collect that's 12
This has been collected too, right it has okay good. Thank you 28
It's gonna be a lot of money
Okay
You are just kind of hanging out
All right. I've done a collection
I'm good. I'm ready
It's time to sell all this
And then we're gonna go in the cave
Oh god, this is so much fun. It's so far. I love it just to how distracting this is
Um, okay. Hold on
54 a piece
Was this 48 a piece? Hell, yeah
Almost 10 grand and I ain't even done. There's like 60 rock ones over here
Holy shit, there's a lot
Yeah, I ain't even done
Okay, that's good for now. I okay. Hold on. Let's run
Get the bread. Um, what do you think i'm doing?
Don't buy the docs buy lab doc is a waste. Well, i'm gonna have like ten thousand dollars. Let's see what I want to do
All right
Ten thousand dollars
I'm gonna get more storage
Because why not I just can do it. What about personal upgrades?
Can't do anything. All right, I got 10 grand
I upgrade anything else here. I mean might as well just get all this stuff
I got money
the lab
Lab. I don't know what the lab is
He wasted it. Well, I eventually i'll put somebody in there
Okay, I need i'm going to the cave
I'm going to the cave. I'm going to the cave
Yeah, there's time. It's time for me to go. I gotta go to the forest and then go find the cave
I have a I gotta put my key in there. I got a key man
No forest
No, get the lab
I want to open up the door that was over here
Where's the um, don't somebody gonna eat these
The teleporter to that doc was over that way, right?
I can take the teleporter that's over here
All right, here's the teleporter because then this is gonna take me this way and then there's there was a door I could open here
There's a I saw one of those uh keyhole doors up here
This is not the cave
Wrong way that not that way wrong way. Wait, why do I have to open the other door?
Wrong way i'm screaming
You need the meth lab
I'm gonna go i'm going this is where I was thinking of going
This is the area that I wanted to go look at because I knew there was a door to open
wrong way jesse
jesse
Chad is malding
I'm not gonna touch anything. I'm not gonna pick anything up
I'm just gonna open up the door. There's a cave somewhere
Where was that cave? It's all about exploration
Isn't it this way?
I'll find it
Where is it? Yeah, look right here. This is what I wanted to do
I got a I got a key
This is the door that I I wanted to open
Oh
Cool. What's that? Whoa what happened?
There's another door here. Where's this this leads to down here
I'm assuming I have to bring plorts here
And feed the plorts to this thing to enough of them so the door will open eventually
So it's currently on pink plort the thing. I didn't get rid of all my pink plot producers
Let's do it
In the meantime
Uh, what should I get in the meantime?
hmm
7 800 I can go buy. Okay, I can go buy
That doc it's 5 000 probably leaves me doing an area
I'm gonna do that too
I think it's already done
Is that what that means pink is already done?
There is
It's saying it's an example. Oh, okay
All right, what do I want to go from here?
I'm gonna go this way
a little back seating
Well, I mean
They could I mean they might be back sitting but that doesn't mean i'm gonna listen to the person behind me when i'm driving a car
I'm down the one in the I have the wheel in my hand. You're a passenger
No matter how bad you want to go to wendy's we're going to mcdonald's. I'm the one driving the car
Can I get a smoothie?
a mcdonald's
smoothie
You know, I don't think i've really ever had one
Maybe like once
all right
Docs is set where okay, so docs is 7 000
I'm going i'm going for it. I got money. I've got money. Okay, I got lots of it. I got plenty of it
I'm going i'm gonna open up doc
I want to see it
It's five grand. But what about the lab? Well, I don't know where the lab is
Okay, this is
I'm saying i'm gonna go to mcdonald's. I know where mcdonald's is
And you say no, no, no, no, no, you're gonna bring us to george's hamburgers
I'm like, I don't i've never heard of that. I don't know what that is
Go there type in gps. I don't know. I what do I don't i've never been to joe. I want to go to mcdonald's
I want to go to george's hamburgers
I don't know where the where is where's this lab you guys are all talking about over here
Don't just go there. I don't even know what that I no idea what that is
To the south of the house
What are you going about?
The lab this is 10 000. I don't have enough money to go to the lab. Everyone go to the lab
Yeah, george's hamburgers is way more expensive. I want to go to mcdonald's. It's half price
All right. This looks good. We'll do another collection. We'll do another collection good
good
Let's feed the big guys
We need meat meat meat meat and more meat
Meat meat meat meat meat. We have enough meat
Probably not what i'm gonna take from you anyways
Ooh, okay
An elder
Perfect, okay nice
This should be enough food to get us to 10 000, which then i'll open the lab and everybody can relax
You all can stop
Screaming into your monitor to the point where condensation breath fills up all over it and you have to wipe it down
so this is
One of these is a boom hunter. It's boom hunter same thing in here. Let's just get it
It's already eaten
Ah, where's elden ring gonna come out?
hopefully, um soon, I don't know
I don't know
When was the last time they actually talked about it? I don't remember them talking about it for a long time
When they announced it
No means they've probably been working on it might get cancelled
That would be sad
All right. This is gonna take us to 10 grand. Let's find out
Be close
Not quite wait
Might get us there with this
Forget us there with this
Hmm
Yeah, this should do it 96 97 98 99
10 000
All right
I can go open the lab
I'm going for it
$10,000 purchase the lab
You've unlocked the lab a special ranch expansion that will allow you to create gadgets using slime science
What?
Go over to the barn to get started
What the hell is this place?
this barn
Has all the equipment you'll need to begin crafting gadgets using slime science
Gadgets are used for utilities to aid in exploring defensive turrets decorations and more
Did you guys actually make me buy the cosmetic?
thing
in order to fabricate gadgets
You'll need resources in your refinery try shooting a plort into the refinery. Remember any resource deposited in that cannot be removed
Or I can put a gold plort in there
um fabricate gadget
Oh, I don't have any plorts. Hold on. I gotta get a plort
I came here plortless. I
Here i'll put a boom plort in there or something. I don't know
All right. Here we go. The builder shop allows you to purchase blueprints. A blueprint is required to build any gadget
purchase blueprints
novice pump
novice
apiary
wild bees
Teleporter
Instead of two guys allow you to remotely transfer river between two points
Helper bot that can be programmed to buzz around your ranch perform tasks
med station
slime ball hoop
novice pump
cool
You buy that and then you make it over here
a novice drill
Cool, once you have blueprint the fabricator allows you to craft gadgets using resources to this binary. All right
Give it a try. I need
I don't have a route. What's a rad plort. I don't have a rad plort
I don't know what a rad plort is
What is this?
In order to place gadgets you need to enable gadget mode, which is t
Gadget mode you cannot back or shoot but you can see all the build sites in the world that you can place your gadgets
Have a look around
Oh
Oh, that's cool
This is really cool
Well, that got more elaborate once you find a build site approach it and place a gadget menu
Simply it's like the gadget you used to place
I'm really glad this is not taking inventory slot
That's a double that's a two or three clap from the devs
to the devs
I'm glad you didn't make a take-up slot. Like thank you. I mean, that's a huge clap
Okay. Well now i'm glad I don't have any money
I have no resources at all
I think I bought the slime lab
scoff
nose turn scoff
I want to go to a new area. What do you got for me? Uh mochi
That's I mean, that's fucking simple. That's free money. All right free money. Thank you
Go feed that fat slime. I didn't I already where is he? Is there another one?
Is it fat slime in the forest?
Go feed that fat fuck settle down
Jesus
All right feed I need to
All right, i'm gonna harvest a bunch of stuff
I'm gonna bring tons of food
We're gonna feed the big slime in the forest
Let's say
Let's say you
Um, how many do I need?
guy in the forest
Oh, let me do this first. This is actually actually free money. I need one boom one of those and three of those. Okay
Need one of those
Uh go into the cave
Whoa
Oh my god, it's overflowing. It's completely fucking overflowed
Oh god
Holy shit, it won't it's it's not it's not going up. It doesn't matter what I do. Oh my god. Um,
Hold on. I'll be back
Take some of those to the lab
Oh
Hmm
You're right. Okay. Hold on. Let me get the rest
Nice job guys. You produced more than anybody else
you deserve
fruits
jeez
I was gonna put 50 and 50 and why not?
Okay, suck it up again
Jesus. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I need uh anymore. I need to boom one, right?
you guys eating
boom
One boom. It's only one boom one boom. Whatever
Booms
Now I need one boom. I have 20 25 minutes. That's forever
Let's load this thing up
50 foster plorts and 50 tabby plorts
Good base, I think put the puddle floors in here, too
I'm out, right? Well, I gotta buy this stuff first
All right. Now i'm gonna sell the rest of those
I need money
All right, but heart module
um
Not yet
I'm back. Hello
Still I still cannot take all this
Such production from you guys, it's unbelievable
Okay
Okay, 50 50 good
Uh, I need a boom plort. I need somebody to eat meat
This is the best and worst game for adhd
because
I have so many tasks i'm going back and forth doing but I always forget one item that I need in the room that i'm going to
so
I didn't get the boom plort because I didn't feed a chicken to the guys in there
But I had to go in there to get the phosphor plorts
But I forgot to bring the chicken over to feed the guy to get the boom plort
I'm constantly forgetting one item
In every single room and I have to keep going back and forth forever
I need okay. Let's just do this now. Well, it's in the top of my head
I keep running back and forth
All right. I just need one boom plort
and
Thank you
For there it is. Thank you
uh
Okay
Got it that poor hunter slime is alone in the corner. I know
I know
What are the phosphors worth?
15 cool
Oh, we have a hell of a lot of them
Complete this get the food
Thank you
I'll really care about some mangoes because somebody's gonna want those eventually
um
Here have some carrots
And I have some pod fruits
and
pelvis
I have a stack of these mangoes in here. There we go over here
oops
I almost have 10 mint mangoes
Limes have favorite foods
They give double plorts
Okay, so if I have a boom slime and a hunter slime mixed together
They will produce double from either a briar hen or a roostro. Is that correct?
Cool honey slimes love mint mangoes
So there's a honey
Boom who who where's honey?
Where's honey?
I have honey over here, right honey boom
Boom tabby
Honey hunter. Okay, honey right here
You taught me these guys
Will eat this and then produce double
Know what you're saying?
Planted. Whoa
Wow, that's genius
At least plant one I will
Did I replace the um
strawberries
Just make a new one new farm
That really is doing double isn't it it is doing double isn't it what happened
15 and 14. Oh, come on. That really is doing double isn't it?
All right, i'll plant
Fucking happen. That just scared the shit out of me. I don't even know why
You just had your favorite food settle down
plant it
Um, I just delete this
I just delete this right?
Oh, what's this?
Oh kind of want to plant this in here, but no, he doesn't need sunshine
Careful, okay
Plant this in the lab. Um
I'm gonna plant it over here
Will the chickens come eat this?
Okay, here we go. Let's upgrade it
nutrients sprinkler
Scarce lime
There we go. Now i'm gonna be producing a ton of these, uh water balloons
Perfect. There's too many people in here. I think there's too many people in here
Maybe not. All right
Next on tap is I want to go
Uh, all right, that's going
I got an email
All right
I now want to go it
find
a pink blob
Let them breed free range
Is that for you? Is that for real?
All right, let them breed free range
No
One guy, okay fucking god
Breed free range
Of course, that's bullshit. Why would that be real?
All right. All right, let's go
That's going
Teleporter
I'm gonna go deposit all this shit into the refinery
And then i'm going to go
What should I do now if i'm not gone?
I'll sleep first
Hey, I need money to buy things here
Feed gordo
Uh, I gotta find another gordo where was he was there was one on the forest
How did I get to 300 pounds?
Um, what the hell are you talking about? What's with the saturns?
Isn't he what I haven't seen in like three years?
Gordo gordo gordo i'm going for gordo
i'm gonna be 20, uh key berries
And i'll bring 30 of these beats
And i'm gonna go find a gordo. Maybe hopefully it'll be enough to get a key
Very cool. All right, let's go
gordo
So we're gonna go through the teleporter. I'm ready
Teleporter into the forest
And then this way
We're looking for a pink
gordo
Northeast at sea level for gordo really
Just wait that way this way that way
I got plenty of food northeast sea level for gordo. Are you lying?
Okay pink gordo big pink gordo
Northeast sea level. I think that's a lie, but whatever
Where is he?
I should buy a lexus
No
I'm terrified of owning like an expensive car
Is that no i'm terrified. I don't want to have an expensive car. What is this?
Oh finally the map
I was wondering why this place was so dark. I couldn't see anything
um
Driving around a car. That's a really expensive car
Scares the hell out of me because I'm how many scratches did I get on it today?
Did it rain is it gonna rust?
Was it dirt on it? I gotta get it washed this car's worth so much money
I don't want to fucking have anything happen to it
It's i'm leaving into the parking lot alone
I that's terrible
That's a I don't want to put that that's leaving like a that's a thick two hundred thousand dollar gold bar
Just sitting in a parking lot. Nope
I don't want it
It would never leave my mind
I would browse around that car every night
Circling it looking for dirt or scratches that were on it like the previous afternoon
And I'd be like was that there earlier?
Was that there earlier?
That's it. No, was it there earlier? Somebody must have bumped me. I made that jump. Cool. I got a feeling something's up here
What's over here? I'm on the island. Come on. I need something
pink slime
big slime
Bucky slime
Damn it. Well, I can get whatever that is
Keshire
Secret style. Oh, that's cute
That's cute
Go north go north
um
That way can I make that jump from here?
Not that I really need to
cat boy
It kind of is isn't it? It is a cat boy. You're right. I wonder what he's gonna do that stream
Well, I can tell you it's definitely gonna be after the archaeology stream and the wonders of archaeology
On march 6th at 1 pm pacific on germa985's twitch channel
I guarantee it's gonna be happening after the archaeology stream
Go north. Well, i'm gonna go north
I've gone north
Who's up here?
bryahen sick
That's okay. I went in this teleporter. Don't go in that go around it
Not this way. I'm gonna get up here and go around and go up north
This guy do archaeology on march 6th
This guy will be doing archaeology
Check it out
Hmm. Can I make that?
Okay
north
What if I get a key out of this?
Okay, so it's archaeology cat boy then baseball. Uh, that sounds pretty accurate
I would say that would be completely accurate what you just said i'm afraid to go down
What am I looking for here? All right, i'm still going
30 webcam 30 webcams was gonna be
Like a week or two ago
But that's gonna be some of the time. What exactly am I doing here for those? What is that?
What are those are those bats?
Why are they all dying? What are you doing? Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop
Boom hunter. Oh, okay
What's over here?
Oh shit
Go to this room
Hold on. I'm trying to this motherfucker is invisible
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Stop, stop, stop. Leave me alone. I got time to kill
Got it. Okay. Now i've got a lot of food
This guy only eats. Oh, he only eats meat
He only eats meat. Damn it. Damn it
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it
No
I gotta remember where this is. Okay, this is all the way up here
Well, might as well just eat
shit well
That's in the top left. Okay. Yeah good. He's on the map now
Southwest corner of the forest for honey slime
Southwest corner like down here
Well, at least I know he where he is now
Is there anything else i'm gonna do over here?
boogers
What about boogers? What?
All right. I'm going to the southwest corner honey slime
Damn it. I can't I wish I had food to feed him
Southwest corner. What's that?
I think I can't open
Damn it. I'm going that way
Uh-oh
Shit, I think i'm in trouble
Can I get up from here?
Uh-oh
Um, I think i'm gonna have to go from here to here here to there
Okay, all right. Let me get out of here. All right
I can't believe that guy's meat. I went all the way over there. I went all the way over there
What the heck southeast corner frick, man
What the frick?
All right. So down here you're saying let's see if it's over here
Come on respawn my ear
southeast corner
Here we are
I don't I don't see a
See one
So, oh
There he is
All right, let's get up there. I think i'll be able to get this one. Okay. What does he eat fruits?
Fuck is it enough?
Fuck I need more god. Damn it. Damn it
Damn it. Okay
Need fruit. I need fruit and I need meat a lot of it
Stock up on fruit. Stop stock up on meat. That's the plan
Just take a hundred chickens or whatever. It doesn't matter. All right, let's go
Yeah
I'll take it
Okay. Now I need to go
Just back down here. All right. All right. I'm coming back with a ton of fruit and a ton of meat
I need to go. Uh, this is interesting to do interesting commentary, please
What do you want to say?
Hell a joke about what?
What is currently on the screen right now that I could like what do you want to talk about like a seinfeld episode?
I saw one time
I mean the episode where?
kramer and uh and george's dad are playing pool and they're like smashing the back of their poles into the
It's a tiny room. They're playing pool and they keep like hitting the wall and stuff
That was really funny
I mean
What?
We're playing slime rancher, man
All right fruits meats and oh that chicken
No
Wait, if I can get the meat i'll take it
I need a lot of it
All right meats
meats fruits
I thought that was one of those scary guys. It's like what's he doing? He's waiting for me to come back
meat
meats more meat
What do I need like 50 chickens?
I gave him 10 already
How many did I give him already?
Seven gave him four. That's it
All right. Hold on
Uh, let's do this gets fruit
Meats beets tomatoes potatoes get those mangoes. Yeah
Okay
Chuck them off. Nice
So let's get I already gave him 20 so I need what 30 fruit
That should be enough
Need more hens though
okay, so I need
more hens I'd eat like
30 40 hens
I'm just gonna take way more than I need
more meat
Um, hold on
I don't want that
46 hens. Okay
I need a lot more than that
I could take a couple roosters, but I don't really want to
I want them in one slot
oh well
35 36 37 38 39 40
41 42
Okay, hold on
43 44 45
Let's die. I want to make sure I even if I take them i'm taking too many. I don't want to
Screw this up and miss one
Use the elders
I only have a few. All right. I'm taking that's it. All right. I got I think I have enough
Tons of food now I can go back. Let's just do this. It's on the top of the brain right now
I'm going back and doing it right now. Let's go
I have one shit sitting on the top of the brain do it
I know exactly where I need to be in a way. I know exactly where I need to go. Let's move
Let me get a sip of this uh coffee
Six o'clock drinking coffee. Yeah, probably
Nobody said that but i'm assuming you did
Just make i'm just making it seem like you did
Answer for like the crimes i'm committing
Okay, honey's live first. He's over here bang a left. Let's go
I'm ready for my free stuff
Which is not free because it costs 30 mangoes which are worth
Probably like five to seven hundred dollars. So this is a five to seven hundred dollar thing i'm doing here
Oh, let's go might as well take him if I can get him. Here you go rooster
Uh-huh. Uh-huh
Here we go
Give me my skimmy stuff. There you go. Oh shit
Ooh
Wait, that's it
I don't really want the honey slimes. That's it. Oh, there's a key
Nice a key
Excuse me. Watch out. Oh
All right. I still have a bunch of mangoes
I got another key. Hell. Yeah
Let's go to the other one. He's all the way up here
Eat them all these hens
Their favorite food is worth double right? Oh god. Oh god
Is that a special honey slime or is that what they look like now?
Oh, I have the dlc
You can unlock different skins for the different uh slimes and I believe that's a royal jelly slime now
Just like how I got this dlc where this is a cat and now it's a tiger
dlc
Don't do it
I can't pick you up. Whatever
Uh, just have to jump around
I'm gonna recharge
All right
So I'll have two keys after this
I've been a good spot
Here in the bang left. There's a chest over here
Who's the main character? Do you think in this game?
What do you shot like a gun? Um, who's the main character? I don't know probably me
Okay, let's do it
roost rose
I have to deal with all these uh, I gotta deal with these guys again. Don't I?
I do. All right. Give me the water gun
Get out of here
Get out get out of the way. It's now safe
Sort of I think there's one left
No mercy
I mean kind of
Get out of here
All right. Let's do it roost rose first
I i'm too lazy to go get it. Whatever you want more food
Holy shit
He
Kind of want the hunters
Come here. I don't need anything. Just come here
And three boxes. We got another key and three boxes cool
Really what why why the hell is that?
Primordi oil
This is like oil
Hold on. What is this?
Um, jelly stone. It's for crafting. Oh, okay. Cool
No, what the hell was even in here?
That's it. These onions. What are these?
buzz wax
Um, should I take some of these? I can't take anything
Get all that shit get rid of the hunters. Okay jelly stone
Is there any more buzz wax?
I got it
All right. I'm good. That's one guy. Um, I can get hunters. They're not that hard to find
I've never seen buzz. Did I get all the buzz wax? Was there only two?
Am I missing one?
Oh, well, whatever. All right, so I have two keys now
And I got all this new stuff. So what do I want to go from here?
I want to go this way
I want to go up here, right?
Or over here. Let me deposit this shit first
I'll cash in. Yeah
I'm gonna cash in i'm gonna make some money for a little bit
and then
i'm gonna
Figure out what I want to do
At least try at least make a funny sound to have something for best funny sound of 2021
um
I'll try
Vanish that person to the cbt realm
All right prime morty prime morty oil, oh no
prime morty oil
Shit i'm gonna be in a lot of trouble really soon
All right store this
Now I need to make money
The weather in scotland. Why?
Why is that bot? You know, I didn't put that bot on here
It's been here since I think i've been streaming and I don't even know why I don't even know how I don't understand
It was a weather bot
Like can't you just type into google weather?
I don't even remember putting that on the channel
All right, we're doing a dump
We are dumping
all these plorts
Directly a sneeze is coming
Okay, like there's no stopping that one
I tried
Sneezed into the shadow realm you sneeze so bad that you just implode
Look at all these fruits
I'm not gonna say it. I want to so bad
I want to say it's so bad
You're all saying it's not fair. I can't say it
It's not fair that you can say it and I can't
It's not fair. I want to be able to say it
Nice. Yeah, I wouldn't be able to say it. Why not? That's not fair
47 mint mangoes
Mint mangoes
I guess i'll have some mint mangoes
Sometimes this month
All right deposit. I've been holding this gold plort for the whole game
All right. I am ready to start making cash. Now. Here we go
Deposit these because then yeah, i'm gonna need them and we're gonna feed a bunch of meat a bunch of fruits bunch of vegetables
And we're gonna go
J g went worth
Eight seven seven cash now
If you have an annuity and you need cash now
All j g went worth eight seven seven cash now
Eight seven seven cash now
What a dumb commercial
All right, uh, I need money
So I need rad plorts don't have any
That's a scam. I don't know nothing about it. I just remember the guy on the viking helmet on the subway
I don't know anything about the company. I don't even know what they I don't even know what they do
I remember the guy on the viking helmet standing up on the subway and going if you have an annuity annuity
No, and then the guy comes on he goes it's your money use it when you need it
right
That commercial played I think every 12 seconds
That was on every commercial break
You could not go 20 minutes without seeing that commercial
Think of how much ad space that is
Think how much money that probably is to have that ad play
Across every fucking network on earth every 15 to 20 minutes
Holy godness. It's a lot of money
All right. Let's start feeding people start making money. It must have paid off for them. I mean I
All right, start that process
Let's go feed
Uh everybody in here. We need meat
And we want fast feeding
fast feeding
Now I want to get my yep meat
It's time for the chickens to shine here. Let's go
Elder hen sure
All right. Don't want to take away everybody. There we go. All right feed
Fast feeding more hens. They have favorite foods. Fuck
Fuck
We're good, we're good somebody likes briar hens, who is it who likes briar hens somebody does
boom hunter
Boom loves briar hens hunters loves roost rose
Honey, okay
Boom loves briar hens
You guys love briar hens
So might as well feed you a bunch of briar hens one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
Ooh, that's quite the haul
You're not going to eat it if you're not going to eat it i'm going to take it
You're not going to eat it. I'm going to
They don't have hands here
Whatever. All right, let's feed uh fruits to the favorite
The honeys that love fruits
You guys love this shit. Don't you?
Make sure I get this right
Uh, honey slimes love mint mangoes phosphor slimes love kyu berries
Well, I know what i'm feeding you
Okay
honey slimes love
mint mangoes
What do you guys like meat here boom tabby what a tabby's like
Boom likes, uh, what a tabby's like stony hens. Look at that
Exactly what I have in my inventory
nice
The first time i'm gonna have a full stack of hunters
That's a lot of money
Some mangoes in the auto feeder. Yeah good idea
Meat honey where I don't have an auto feeder for these guys doing
I do it is their favorite get back in there
shit
Wrong one
What are you talking about?
These guys eat meat. I don't have any meat left, but I will go up here and I will gladly put kyu berries in here
Geez, okay
um
Do I I have to sell?
I gotta sell almost all this
I need money. I don't have any
Don't hold it. I need like five grand to do gadgets
How you doing over here you're kind of lonely
Lock the cave. Oh, wait, where's that?
Is that over here?
No, I think plorts are way more important for slime science than for selling. Yeah, that's it
I figured I was gonna just start dumping
just massive massive amounts of uh
Yeah, i'm gonna start dumping massive amounts of pink
into the machine
And then once that's done
Get rid of all the pink slimes because i'm not gonna need them anymore. Maybe i'll keep one
All right. It's time for a big sell here
Money is worth that. They're kind of losing value. Oh, hopefully I can make some cash from this. It's gonna be a lot
Good. Yeah. All right. I'll have a lot of money. I need to do research
Feels good every time. All right
i'm gonna go
over here
Because now I should have a lot of red, right?
Let's get i'm gonna whatever I pick up right now i'm literally throwing in the machine
Water plorts go for like 40s. Have you considered getting more puddles?
Maybe
Probably
Yeah, I think so
But maybe not right this second. How you guys doing over here? You have anything else I can pick up?
Okay. Yeah
Easy relax a lot of booms. All right, i'm gonna deposit these booms
We're doing a boom deposit. That's 20. That's probably good
some more
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I'm going
deposit
And then research a bunch of stuff
What was it really more useful on the beach?
All right. What can I do now? Let's deposit all this stuff
Okay, blueprints
Novice pump allows you to siphon underground resources for one cycle. I don't even know what that means
Gonna just get it
I guess
What does that mean?
Novice pump so this is allows you to siphon underground resources
fabricate
um
Fabricate fabricate fabricate fabricate
Uh, this gadget is installed permanently until demolished
Siphon resources
Why did I make so many because I had a lot of I don't know
I want to see what I want to see what it does
What does it do last for 12 minutes?
What the hell does this thing do? It's a little like r2d2 machine. What is it?
uh
slime science
extractors
Once placed on a build site an extractor will begin working collecting resources from the environment over time
Once it's full of resources an extract can be emptied
The best extractors can repeat this cycle multiple times before they finally break down
Each extractor can find exclusive resources if used in the correct zone
Pumps can find a special resource in the dry reef
Rills find a special resource into indigo quarry
Apiaries can find special resource in moss blanket and all extractors can find special resources in the glass desert. This is a pump
In the dry reef
I need to go to the dry reef
The hell is the dry reef?
So do I just let this run?
Oh, whatever
What else can I get?
A set of two teleporters that can be used to create your own quick travel link. Yep. I would love to see what that does
ink teleporter
inkplot deep brine strange diamond in a hexacom. Well, I don't have that
drone helper bot that can be programmed to buzz around your ranch and perform a variety of tasks
That's 2 000 bucks, but is it worth it?
drone helper bot
I need honey quantum hunter wild honey jelly stone or hex. Oh, that's a lot of resources. Okay
Well, what that's gonna do maybe should you get that apiary?
I was supposed to learn it
Well, this is a pump. Okay apiary honey plort
honey rad plorts
Drones are so worth it. Okay
Good to know
Um, I have the two keys now. All right. First of all, let's take a let's take another pee break. I'll be right back
See you guys in a minute. We'll continue
you'll
Monster energy drink right that monster photo
Okay, let's keep going
I want to get to a new area
Five stages of grief nile fuck i'm not gonna wear that catboy costume for real, right?
Entirely skip stage two stage three and stage four
What a weirdo acceptance. Let's fucking go
Do I eat rats now with a fuel in my hand?
Let's fucking go
All right, let's go for real. I am ready to begin exploring a new area
so
I gotta go
Over here
Or over here
I'm gonna assume it's over here
Uh, so yeah, let's go
Enable rat jam. I'm begging you
No, no rat jam
Nope
Not doing rat jam
Sorry, i'm not doing rat jam
Oh, I hope there's a gordo in here. I have two keys
Stockpiling them. Excuse me
Did your parents really name you germa 985?
Of course they did
By the way, that's my middle name
It's jeremy germa 985 elberton
the indigo quarry
Ooh, this place is cool looking. Oh, there's islands down there. What do I do first? I want to get new slimes
That's what I want to do
That's a pink slime not new
What does H have to say?
Is that new fruit?
Those are not new slimes
Not new slimes
I don't see anything new yet
These pogfruits
Oh, it's just pogfruit
I need new slimes
Where's the new stuff?
Oh radishes
Odd onion
Okay. Cool
new item
Pog slow mode
He likes veggies. Ooh
Okay, cool
There's a guy in here and he likes veggies
I got plenty of vegetables. I have a huge I have a whole beet garden, man
Oh, wow, this is interesting. It really is like a quarry. Okay, cool
So it's marked he's on the map right mark this guy on the map
Why is he not marked?
Mark him. Why is that guy not marked on the map?
Defeat him once to mark him. Oh
Well, I need to get a vegetable quick
I need new slimes
Odd onions. No
No, come on. Give me something new
He's not ready yet
I'm gonna I'm gonna feed him a carrot
And he'll be marked
Mark for us
Get out of here and
How did they all miss all of them did?
They all missed
every single one
treasure cracker
Oh
Is he on the map? He is
Is that a treasure cracker?
Oh, I can unlock that now. Nice. Give me some new slimes, man
Stop reading the bad chats
Is it a bad chat?
Oh big glowy thing over there puddle
ooh
Give me a lot more of these guys
I want like at least two or three puddle slimes. Yes, there we are. Thank you
Gonna be an egg puddle. It's gonna be an egg. Oh, I thought it's gonna be like an egg with a yolk in the middle
That one's so funny
I just want the slime puddle slimes
Over here. I mean, that's still very cute though
Very cute. Oh
Give me that onion. Give me that onion
Rad slime
Ooh, we got rad slimes now
Get out of my way
Okay
Wait, it's giving me radiation for holding on to it
I want like a full stack of these
All right, I got 14 of them
Cool 14 rad slimes
Oh, I want more
I'm able to get more. I want more
And 16
Oka oka
Here we go. Get over here
All right, I have odd onion and oka oka
And then bunching. I've got a new slime
Hey
Whole inventory. Yeah, I got it. All right
Teleporter. Oh shit. Come here
No
Don't die. I want a bunch of you
Are you biting me?
Shit
This guy's gonna be really excited. I want to turn everybody into poisonous slimes
I want as many of these as I can fucking carry
New slime just dropped. Yep
What do they eat?
Edgies
That's the only new slime that's here so far
We're gonna get an absolute shitload of them
I think more than 40 is perfect. We can just breed them
Oh over there
I'll get a full stack
Teleporter over here. All right, 43 seems like a good amount
Read their info
rad slime
Favorite food is oka oka
But the favorite food is oka oka. So we're going to grow
oka oka
Favorite food is oka oka. So we're gonna grow it
I think we're gonna replace the beets because what's the point right now? Do I really want to grow beets still?
When I have oka oka and it's a rad slimes favorite
I don't think there's a reason for it anymore. All right, let's go back
All right, it's time
I believe it is time
We are going to get rid of
one of these
rocks
or cats
Who gets to go away?
I'm also going to get rid of the beet farm. I'm going to replace it with a oka oka farm
Oh, these are here the end of the beats
You have other cats
That's right. I do I do have other cats
Other cats no other rocks. That's right
And that's where we can get our pink from as well
So cats it was great. You were the first you were my first real money maker
But it's time for you to go. You're all going to be free
I will give you one last delicious meal
And then you're all going i'm not going to give you any more food
And you're all going to go on your own
The rock's favorite food is beets
but
Oh, but I don't it doesn't matter
All right. Hold on. Let me one thing at a time. Let's go make a new plot
Don't fall out. I got more of my puddle slimes here hanging out in the pool
a little plot
Cool. Cool
uh, all right
I mean I
I want more rat. No, no, no. Okay. We're putting rad slimes in here
And we're gonna put that hunter over there like I mean
Make a rad hunter. So I do rad but no no
What's the most expensive thing right now?
What would give me the best return here rad? What?
Pure rad probably probably just pure rad. Yeah, I don't want I don't want hunter red pure rad is more money
Yeah, we're gonna put this guy over here. He'll be happier with this. He'll be happier over here with actual friends
All right. I'm only gonna hmm. I'm gonna put
How many should I put in one?
That too many
This thing's fucking exploding
All of them in here
That they're gonna stack on top of each other. Don't you think I mean if this is just a moneymaker though, then it doesn't matter
They won't get out
If I just put oka okas in here and just get massive cash
They're not they won't get out. Oh fuck. I have no money. All right, i'm gonna go plant the oka oka. We'll get rid of beats
Holy shit. All right. Well, here's the moneymaker right here. Let's just make some money make make some uh cash
Okay
Looking good and then what do I want to combine? All right, I gotta i'm gonna store these odd onions
Okay odd onions go in here
I can store the beats
What else did I got in here?
All right oka oka. We're gonna grow instead of the beats
Combine them
What do you mean combine them?
Wait, can you say feed a green plot to the green to the rads?
Okay, remove crops oka oka go you can't do that
All right. We got oka oka is growing now
You can fit more if you keep them small
That was my theory is just have a bunch of small ones and feed the hell out of them
And make fifty thousand dollars
No, no more booms. The booms have kind of pissed me off. They're really annoying and loud and they just hate you and just explode
Okay, so let's do this
I will have a full stack of
beats
essentially
Yes, I need them for anything good
All right sell all this crap
What is that?
Rad plots of 53. What are those 73?
That seems pretty good
crystal, ooh
Crystal rad that's what we're doing next. That's the next play
for sure
All right fruits
When is it gonna be time to replace the kiwberries I wonder meat meat meat
Okay
Is it weird that I kind of want to just do two oka oka farms?
Because I got the mint one which should have a huge harvest right now
I just i'm fucking loving this game
You hear how like chilled out I am. It's like man. I could go over here and get these mint
This must be a big harvest over here
A lot
Very cool. All right
Chickens honey's love the mints make a little bit more money meat
We're gonna feed meat
Uh, we'll do seven stony hens
Not these guys the other ones
Okay
You guys love fruits
But you love
Um good legs the mangoes these guys, right?
These guys like the mangoes how they doing
Oh, it's already feeding
Might as well just put it all in there and do super feeding
Oh fuck, this is gonna be a lot of money
Oh my god, there's like 50 in here. Holy shit. Hold on
um
Here you guys love oka okas
Oh my god, i'm gonna make so much money from this
I need to put a uh an upload collector
This is gonna be a huge money maker
All right, you guys like fruit
You and you like the kiwberries, don't you?
Make sure I get that right dear
42 of these
All right. I gotta start storing stuff
43 that's good
All right, let's fill this up sell all this
I wish this game was on switch. It's not that seems like a big mistake
Eat up get some booms
And we're gonna go sell
Go check the drill. Uh, yeah, i'll head over there in a minute
I could also make something else over there. Can I?
All right, let's sell and then i'm gonna bring my oka okas over here get an auto feeder
And we're gonna make trillions from these red plorts
I mean, it'll be wild
This thing's ready
Yeah, almost
Any booms over here?
I can suck up
Booms i'm going through face cam withdrawal
You'll get it like next month
all right
sell
Sell everything sell the rads
All right four thousand bucks
Here we go
Time to turn that four thousand into like twelve thousand
Really really soon
Here we go
green plorts
Here we more green plorts
28 what 30 green plorts and this is how you start
Just making an uncountable amount of money
They want more food
I might have to double it up more okas. Oh, hold on
There are more plots outside yeah, i'm gonna double up the orca orca production absolutely
Oops, yeah double up the orca production cats 42 of those
30 and i'm by the time I get back I can do another delivery of uh of orca
Okay, whatever is orca orca
Yeah, let's go
This let's see fifty three bucks
Look at that number just low
Here we go
Just like that back up to almost seven thousand dollars. Okay, cool
Now i'm gonna take one of these
And oh, hold on
Let's do a research dump
Okay research dump
Oh my god, is this the among us guy
That no, no, no, i'm not no that we can't have that guy. I can't have that. No, it's not me
I don't know. It's a it's a guy looks like me. It is nothing. I've never i've never seen that person before in my life
I've not I don't know. I have no idea who that is
I have no idea
I've never heard of that person before in my life
All right research dump this. I don't know who that is
This is the among us guy. Fuck
You want to know the worst part about that meme?
I didn't play among us
once
I've never opened the game
So i'm the among us guy
But i've never played the game
Wouldn't you think that that person would be a huge fan of the game?
He loves it so much. He wanted to really push this meme of of an imposter meme. I've never opened the game
Why did it have to be me?
There are people that play that game every day
Why does it have to be me?
Internet works in strange ways the internet. Why did I say that weird the internet works in strange ways?
Okay med station
hydro turret
number one slime stage
pink warp depot
Can I make any of this stuff?
Rhone not yet warp tech pink warp depot
No, no decorations
Curios extractors
I need rad plorts. Oh the pump right the pump over here
ready
Whoa
All right, I I should just put i'm gonna put a bunch of these down
Nice. Okay. I'm gonna just put a bunch i'm just gonna put them down
I can make a bunch of them do it in different volumes. Yeah, what happened when I press q?
Oh, that's an air blast. Okay
All right. Uh, I have some money
Let's go ahead and um novice gordo snare
Special snare that captures a gordo slime bait it with food. What?
slime lamp
med station
Um, i'm hold on I don't want to get overwhelmed here. What's over here?
What is over here? Oh, right. This is okay. What wait?
That's a little okay. That's a little shortcut. Cool
All right, oka oka
oka oka
I'm gonna buy the dock. Yep. I can go to the dock
Not ready. I'm going to bed. It's hydro instead of pyro because it's water
Yeah, that's correct
All right, we're going double oka oka
I'm gonna put it
Over here. Don't let me forget this because you know, I will holy shit. Okay
Uh right here
What did you buy the lab?
Why buy the lab?
Remember it easier that way
How often do I pre-record streams maybe four or five times a week?
Closer. Yeah, that's true. It is
That is closer
Oh
All right, we're going right here with uh oka oka
All right, let's go
I want to make tons of money
Remember did you hear that doom guy is in smash? No, it was somebody from xenoblade or something earlier
Whatever it was
It was a lie
Yeah, I mean we just watched it
We literally just saw that like we just watched it on stream
All right, let's go feed them. I'm here with the oka oka
Who's hungry?
Just wait till I have a automatic feeder set up with just a hundred oka okas in it
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you see what i'm talking about. This is gonna be insane
I
Got 30 last time what's going on here i'm gonna give him a hug that's dangerous, man
I'm gonna do a deposit
I'm gonna deposit the rad ports
Are we doing good?
Looks pretty good. Who wants the mint who wanted this?
You do
Oh boy. Um, oh god
Too many too many
All right, slow the feeding down the feeding's way too high
Slow it down. Okay. Um, i've kept way too. Okay. I'm gonna do a huge huge, uh refinery dump
This is gonna be a massive dump
Um, i'm coming back pressure cracker. Whoa, that's too much money
I just clicked it forty five hundred bucks. No, thanks
store it
Pump it in pump this in too
Come back with all honey all hunter dump all that as well
All right, uh, i'll be back
God
Wait, let's go this way
All right. What do you have? You have ten
We had most of the honey guys over here. Yep
all right, honey and
At least i'll have plenty of uh resources sell these
I think I want a bunch more in the
i'll sell
All right, i'll sell these and i'm gonna deposit these
Did I or should I just deposit all of them?
I don't know. I think i'm gonna deposit
And then i'll sell the rest
What this is not the way that I thought I was going
Okay, i'm gonna get my go to my, uh, oka oka fields
These are probably done. Are they?
Very close
All right. I am not going to do another honey or hunter deposit
I have hundreds in here
Okay
med station
Sure
Hydro turges might as well get it
At least all the ones that look like I mean, I don't want to do the ones that don't have any
Value all right drill
All right apiary. I want a few of these don't I?
I want at least like four or five of each of these utilities
honey hunter
At least on hexacom
Med station is rad pink
Hydro turret is
Warp tech
All right. I want at least like four or five of each of these. I need a pink
What's wrong with chad?
um
Man, I mean you could probably say that every day
It depends on what like I don't know what weird like chat drug they've injected today. I don't know
Okay, okay one
Although you probably say that about me, too
All right. How many times you guys come in here and I was like eating a burger king burger while doing something weird
It's like what did he do for drugs today? Like I could say the same thing about me
I'm gonna wait for the oka oka harvest
I need pink
Now if I can get crystal
Fantastic
These guys I might replace these guys soon
Yeah
Is it gonna be time for them to go pretty soon here? I think
Because I don't need two cages with these things
I could put like a crystal the crystal. Uh rads are going over here. I think
I think so
ready
gray teleporter
All right, let's make a shitload of money
30 oka oka's
Feed the 40 slimes 30 of these and make like four thousand dollars
Oh, yeah
Let's see
Oh 58 even more than that
There's a couple in the way 60. This is gonna be gonna be awesome. It's like four grand
There's more in there
so
Tell these two
Nice you're gonna crash the market
That's i'll be fine
blue teleporter
These are currently worth 28
What happened weren't these worth 52 days ago?
I'm gonna hold them
You inflated the market
Whatever. All right
I need pink
No, I don't I want to explore
I'm going to explore
I'm going over here this guy. What's this guy like vegetables?
I'm gonna go feed this guy a shitload of vegetables. What do I have for vegetables?
and go
I got 50 of these
I'm ready to go get another key or something. The beats are worth double. Ooh, so I don't need to take that many. How many do I need?
15 only
Is that all I need 25
We'll be safe, you're right
We'll be safe. We'll be safe about it
Uh get rid of these
I have too many chickens
I have like a I don't have a quest for me. What do you want?
You want four crystal thingies and then three of those
I'm not even gonna come back
In fact, i'm not even gonna reply to this person
It's for four crystal slimes
I get 250 and then should i've I used six hours ago
I'm literally gonna just not even answer the phone call. I hang up on her actually
Okay, uh ki berries. I'm just gonna store them
And sell the puddle ports
All right, 25. I got I still have a key the puddle puts with a lot of money
All right
Let's
Go let's move. Here we go
Is there a fast way I can get back over here or do I have to run the whole way?
Before we run
The raid song what happened?
Sing the raid song
who raided
You rated germa rated you talking
Okay, not the key
Excuse me
This might be my favorite game. We came out in 2015
How do I get in there? I want to get in
How do I get in five years behind?
Hey, it's not too late. It's time for you to I guess it's gonna be a key
And there it is really that's it
Go down it's a teleporter
I don't want any of these rock slimes. I'm just trying to get them out of the way
What's in there? Nothing really
What's in there? I thought that was a gigantic crystal
Okay, what about this one?
Okay, okay
And this is just a port
Is this two ways?
Oh nice. Perfect. That's really cool. All right, perfect
Very cool. Very cool. Very cool. This is great. I don't have to run here anymore
I can just go down into my little uh spot
nice
all right sell
Those oka-okas over there
Back go back plorts what?
Mr. Plort missed crystal ports
plorts germa the plorts
Those are rock plorts, dude
What are you talking about? Put a drill in here
Oh my goodness
I'm gonna put three drills in here. Is it drill or pump? Which is the good one? Let's do the one for in here
real
Real. Oh shit. Cool. All right
Those are all good to go
Can these be destroyed by animals or something or no?
I don't I don't want these why am I carrying these?
Okay, I am gonna stay here
So i'm gonna go over here
I want crystals
Is that gold?
Awesome the thing I turned around
I would not have seen that
All right, we're looking the crystal slimes are gonna look like the rock slimes, I guess but purple
Yes, where am I going over this way or over here?
I don't think I went over here
And open this shit
Get away from me
What about in here? I still have a key if I run into a door. I might just open it
Oh, yeah
Yep crystal slime
Give me give me give me before they turn
Still plort. No, give me this just the slimes just the slimes is enough
I want a fucking carrot
Crystal poison is what we're looking for
It's the most amount of money
Get out of the way here
Good I got 11 crystal poison
This is a good haul. I'm happy with this so far. You played subnautica. I have
Like I stream subnautica, didn't I?
All right, I think I can go back. I streamed it for like three hours and I gave up didn't I?
Yeah, no, did I do it more than once?
All right, let's head back i'm gonna teleport out of here and i'm gonna do the slime i'm gonna make
It's time to get rid of one of the pinks. I have to make a decision. I've made it i'm getting rid of the uh, the
Bugs, um, no, what am I getting rid of?
the cats
I'm back here 10 minutes will be up
Cats are gone. Sorry
Cats are gone. I'm gonna take some of these guys. We're gonna you know, what?
boom
Maybe it's these guys
Because this is just boom cat. I already have pink cat
I feel like the boom cats are not really worth having
Throw them into the ocean
How do I get rid of them from here?
These meat only meat only suck. That's true
Incinerate them. I don't have an incinerator
Okay, that works
All right, what you're bullying?
What i'm you? Okay
so
You want me to let's get this correct here. I'm seeing in the chat
Incinerate them what i'm doing is i'm giving him a chance. I'm giving them a chance
You incinerate implies pick up burn to death. What i'm doing is shooting him free into the ocean
So he's got a chance
No, and i'm i'm fine. I won't even shoot him into the ocean. Here's what i'll do check this out. Okay, ready
Go back go back go back go back
Go back
Don't even think about it. He was gonna explode. He was waiting for he was gonna he was doing the thing that you did in team fortress
We just sat at a teleporter as a spy
And found the direction where it was facing stood behind it and backstabbed like 12 people as they came out
Look, there we go. He can be free. You know, you can just live out here. No, we can't
Look, I they can live on their own island over there
I would do that to a point. We're in the chat in the team tf2 chat
We would be screaming at all capitals
Kill the fucking spy at the teleporter. Oh my god
You guys are fucking stupid
Heavy sitting there going naked
See he he's blasting forward and rocket shipping over there. This is i'm not murdering him. I'm letting them fly to a new island
They can populate it and have have a go free
Incinerate them look ready. Look at this. There's look at the islands over here
See look at that. He's going all the way over the mountain poof into the distance
He just did a rocket. He turned on thrusters and went forward over the cliff
He'll be fine
He's gonna land somewhere and just be like, oh i'm fine. I'm good
Plus look at how strong they are. They have powerful explosion abilities and he's a cat
Nothing's gonna hurt him
and then poof
blaster
Okay, now we get to do something cool shit
It was really fun. You guys helped me a lot
He did a great job
Uh, he is that I think he did explode. I think I got it wrong. I think he actually is exploding in the air
It's too much oxygen in the atmosphere and it just sucks up into when he blows up
That's what's happening. All right crystal slimes going in
Crystal slime we will feed rad plorts to crystal slimes
Correct
That's what i'm doing
or
Do we just have crystal slimes make money?
Oh shit
Yes
I'm sounding like a child. What just leave the crystals should I I shouldn't combine them
Crystal rads, that's what I was thinking gold. I I thought you can't feed gold to anybody
Your crystal is better. Is it?
You can't feed gold anybody
What do they eat veggies? Oh, this is perfect
Eat it a water
Okay. Well, hold on. Let me let me just check this out
Your crystal is based
um
I feel like that's boring though. What's crystals favorite food?
odd onion
Uh
No, I i'm combining them because then their favorite food will be oka oka
That's what's happening here. That's what i'm doing. That's what's happening
Okay, okay time. Let's go
Any more more more more more
Look kind of boring looking
I would do
There's still some I don't know, but I you can't make any money
You got to use the expensive stuff
How much are they worth?
75 pop 30. Okay. Thankfully that market came back
All right, that's where 75 pop. Let's get the other oka oka farm
onion ring
Let's go on back this way and start feeding
It's the wrong way
Oh, no
onion ring
Okay
Your favorite food is
oka oka
Eat it
And here we go
Pop pop pop pop pop pop pop no, no, no, no, no, no. No, I want you to eat that
More. Yes, they look kind of cool
It's easy. Why is it getting so huge?
14 crystals nice
Very cool. It looked like freaking mortys
Oh good. They do look like mortys
How dare you how dare you all right suck that up
What I i've read it. I didn't say it
Who in here needs to change still?
Anybody in there that hasn't changed
Still people that haven't changed. I think everyone's turned
Yeah, that's good
All right, let's do it
crystal quartz
More more more more
They look they they look really cool. What are you guys talking about? They look cool
Fuck, this is full again
Um, hold on
Crash the market. I know
Oh, uh, i'm gonna sell sell
So
Take a little bit more money and then i'm gonna buy the dock
That's my plan
Sell all this shit go buy the dock
I have two gold right now
75 each that's a lot
Hunters are worth a lot
Hunters went way up. Nice rads 31. Let's go
You have paper hands
Whatever
All right. Now i'm gonna buy the dock
First i'm gonna sell more of that stuff market's up right now
Go for it
And wait, I have to go back and uh get my haul from the drills
Okay, what do we got?
40, uh sell everything
I'll be over 10k in a second here
You guys have anything in there? No, you guys do right? Okay 70 71 honey
Oh
Damn it, I dropped one
No, get back in there. Fuck. Oh get back in there. I don't want this get back in there. Um, I hate that
Okay, sell all this and then i'm gonna go check on my
drills
Oh this okay
You're close
Am I close to?
Honey is up today. Hell. Yeah, let's go
This will be 10 grand
Honey is here
Come on. Kanye. Welcome to the stream
I'm a streamer. I'm a gamer. I'm not really I'd like to I pretend to be
Over 10k
Okay, I have a lot of money and i'm gonna go get the okay
this way
Already another oka oka haul
More money. I want to get to 20k
All right now i'll be getting lots of production
Nice, okay. Cool. Hi. I have no idea who you are
Um, I don't know who you are either. It's nice to meet you though
Welcome to the channel. My name is Jerbo985
We do all kinds of fun stuff here
currently on slime ranger
Really into it so far
Oh and suck that up
And i'm gonna i'm gonna no sell
Sell it suck that up. Am I streaming tomorrow? I am streaming tomorrow and we'll do it
Yes, i'm streaming tomorrow and we're gonna play this
I
Have a paper mario
Paper mario is a distant memory in my brain at the moment
When i'm done with slime ranger
Well, that depends
I'm gonna try to get into gta rp
probably
Maybe in like a week or two. We'll see where that lays. I still have to
Like apply and stuff and do everything
So if I can do that, well, maybe i'll try that
But I have no guarantees that i'm gonna play it or anything
I'm still going through the process to see if um, that's something i'm gonna do
Uh here you just
I'm gonna waste one
Ow, okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good rads
Sell everything
And then buy the dock
and then just
God, okay sell
Drills fuck. Yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna all right. There's still there's a lot of money to be made
i'm depositing this into the
into the bank
drills
After I deposit. Oh my god. There's another harvest
There's an omega raid
Omega raid, where's it? Where's an omega raid? Where's one?
All right drills
I need pink floor. It's shit
Okay, i'm gonna feed these guys and i promise i'm gonna leave I promise i'm gonna go into uh
All right feed the crystal guys. Okay. Okay
Okay now wait i'm almost done
This game is a gigantic loop
Yes, it is
It is a huge loop
It's just a loop. I know but it's a very satisfying loop
It's a loop that I am having a great time doing
Okay
teleporter
Is over here, right?
Oh this way
You got me addicted to this game again
I don't know. I'm not gonna apologize for that. This is awesome
What we got?
whoa
Indigonium indigonium and jelly stones
Whoa indigonium jelly stones
What's that indigonium jelly stone is a rock
um
Apologize to them to what?
Uh, I don't want to put a pump in here. I want to drill
It's a rock. How do I get that? I'm gonna have to
Will that stay here?
That's gonna stay here, right if I leave
It's a fossil. Okay, i'm right back
Hurry i'm getting hungry. I'm hungry
All right, i'm gonna clean this up and then i'm gonna stream again
And then we'll pick right back up tomorrow
And after tomorrow, we'll see how far I am and how much i'm still doing
Because maybe one more stream of this would be us get satisfied of playing. Maybe not. We'll see
All right. I gotta go back
slime fossil
Oh
Well, the idea is to make just a shitload of drills and put them in here
right one two
three four five
One two, three, four five just make like ten of them. I'm gonna make ten drills and put them in here
Unlock the advanced one first. Yeah, good idea
All right. Here we go. What do we got?
advanced drill
Last three full cycles. Holy shit. Okay, got it. What else can I do?
What's the difference between blue and gray?
color
Advanced drill I need pink plorts pink and rock plorts. I know where to get those
What's your favorite food?
Heartbeat I don't have any more of those
Maybe I do
Here you go
Hey, give me one back because I need to grow it
What are the docs? Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I'm i'm working working on something. Oh shit
31 nice. Okay, good. Cool
now
Like this
God, I got okay. Hold on
What's your favorite kind of pizza?
depends on the day
probably like um
I like i'm a big just standard pepperoni just pepperoni
I want this food now. So like hurry up
What do you guys like?
Whatever. Oh here just I want pink
I don't know. I don't like that crust pizza. I like thin crust pizza
crispy thin
With pepperoni, you know, this is really good garlic and onion
Garlic and onion pizza is really really fantastic. I would highly recommend it if you've ever had it
Just cheese, you know, i'm not gonna
Say that just cheese is not good
Sometimes just cheese is all you want
Good slice of cheese pizza is perfect a lot of times
Okay, let's go make a few of those
Four cheese
Yeah
Kind of like a white pizza
White pizza is fantastic
I gotta really be in the mood for white pizza though
All right to the lab
Deep dish pizza. I actually don't like deep dish pizza. I'm not a big fan of it because it's pie
It's kind of like a pie. I don't really like it
It's a little too. It's it's really heavy too tons of cheese
the cheese pie
I mean this is not
Kind of what I like
You've been to st. Louis. I've never been to st. Louis
All right advanced drill
One two, I can only make two of these right now. I need more pink
more pink
Oh
Whatever i'll do that later. I need pink
I'll just put these up for now
They're my flavored pizza. What do you mean?
Somebody mentioned this earlier
These things just stay consistently expensive
I should really I should honestly 2020 hindsight
That should have been a pond over there and I should have had like two dozen of these things
Okay, uh, let's teleport back
advanced
drill
That's just gonna go with the recycles. Well, well, well remind me of that. Yes. Uh, um, what?
Remind me of that yesterday remind me of this tomorrow because i'm gonna forget these are here
All right. All right. I'm gonna call it here. I am prepared to go explore another area
very soon here
Pause at this before I go
Or sell sell
Doc we'll do that tomorrow buy the docs. Well, all right remind me to buy the doc tomorrow
and to open up those, uh
Things I got back there
I got 15 grand. This is awesome. All right. Is there anything I can buy right now?
Treasure cracker. Is it time to get this?
I'm doing it
The van cool. All right. Awesome
I still have one key. I'm gonna go to the dock tomorrow
and
Oh, that's five grand. Would you want valve to make team fortress three?
Uh, no
Not unless they really wanted to
I feel like that would have to be a project that really wanted to work on
And we got half-life alex because they just felt like making it and that game was incredible
Whenever valve tries to jump on something that they think they should be doing doesn't turn out well
When valve does something because valve feels like they want to do it because it's something that somebody has a cool idea
Usually turns out okay
So let them let them do it do things that they want to do at their pace whenever they feel like it
That's how you get the best shit from valve
And I I mean obviously everyone kind of thought well, maybe they lost it. They don't have it anymore
I wasn't a big dota 2 fan. I know it's popular but uh, whatever artifact was
Kind of weird and messy. I don't I guess it was okay. I don't know
Can they make games anymore? Do they even want to make games anymore? And then half-life alex comes out and it's like well
Okay, never mind
I guess they can still do that
So I guess just wait for them to do something that they feel like doing game of the year artifact. I would disagree with you
They're contributing in other ways to the games industry. Oh, yeah, i'm just talking merely game development
just purely
Valve making a video game in-house
I mean you want to talk about like the business side of things. I mean they they kind of changed the entire world
With steam and everything but you know, that's a whole nother conversation for the german 985 podcast
With special guests next week
Otto, I don't have anybody. It's just me and the dog. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a great rest of your night
This game's awesome. It's fun. Just to play it. We're gonna do it at least one more day tomorrow
See how it goes if i'm still having fun then well then yeah, i'll maybe i'll keep going
Have a great night. Let's go through the credits
They were a shitload of community subs today
They are at one point there was like a hundred
In like a 10 minute span. So thank you guys
never expected
Never obligated but always appreciated right? Thank you. Take care of yourself. Take care of you, too
Make sure you're doing that
Uh raid somebody. Yeah, let's raid somebody. Let's rerate tonight. Let's see who's live
who's live on like the
guy that
Follows like 10 channels andy
We branch out should we branch out to somebody we've never rated before what do you think who's live
I'm i'm here to take suggestions
Seeing a lot of seeing a lot of names
Seeing a lot of names. Hmm
You know, what's funny about raids I always have so much trouble with raids because i'm just like who who who do I do?
Who is it? Who? Hmm?
What about this person? No, no, no, no. No, we did that person like a week ago like two weeks ago
What about that person that person's new? But do I know this person? Who is this person?
I've ever seen them before what do they do for videos? I'm about to send a bunch of people there. Who are they?
Who are you? What's happening? Sure. I'm just right. You know, let's just go this way networking andy
But this is not networking andy. I gotta pick somebody. I gotta pick somebody now. I gotta figure it out
Who is it?
It times up the credits are over the oh the the post credit scene is here
The post credit scene is here and like i'm in the i'm in frame right now. I don't know what to do
Slime sickle. Oh shit. Yeah, that slapsicles raided us like five times before hasn't he?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's let's let's return. Let's return the raid
Slimesicle has raided this channel like four or five times. So
Really appreciate that. Let's go go say hello. Then we got it done. Let me sure I spell this right
I feel like raiding channels on this channel is me picking food at a restaurant
I just don't know what to eat. I don't know what to pick
Why what do I order and then I feel like I ordered wrong, but then I get the order and I go
No, that was great. That's perfect. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Go save lotus lime sickle
Very very very very nice dude has raided this channel at least three or four times over the last few months networking andy
Call me whatever you want. That's fine
I'll see you tomorrow. Have a great rest of your night. I'll see you tomorrow around. Uh, let's around 2 30 pacific
2 30 pm pacific tomorrow
See you soon. Take care of yourselves. Good night