Um, yeah, I have one. Oh, did you just die?
What just happened did you just fall off the bridge
Seriously, I fell through one of the holes in the damn bridge. I'm like
Were you recording yeah, I
Say we just give you all this stuff back I had the enchanted it's all gone down there man. Oh
Jeez, I
Don't think I took a backup of this map. Oh
last time okay, I
Guess that's all we need hopefully
There's I there's a creeper out here though. All right, we'll take care of them. We got three doors
We got two creepers actually, that's that's the way to the creepers
Alright, so let's go the back door. I
Don't see anything
Okay, okay, we're good we're good got that one got that one we didn't shut the door though
All right, we'll shut the door after we kill this bastard
You're gonna blow up. What are you doing? I'm pushing him back. I'm doing like the sprint attack
He's like honest. He's chilling on top of the tree. Now. He's like he's like I'm pretty cool up here
He's like a tree frog. What is he doing? I?
Think with the
One point with one point two. It's like they're more scared to jump down. It seems like they are
Already, I'm gonna try and wow what he really isn't coming down. Oh
There he goes watch out
There we go. Nice got a nice little crit hit on him close that door close the door and onwards we go. All right, so I
For those of you that don't know I just ruined everything essentially. I
I broke a bunch of stuff because I fell in the lava with the enchanted bow and pretty much
I'm just a terrible person. So that's uh, that's that story
Hold shift from now on that's what we got to do. He's kind of like cross the bridge. Oh, I
Totally forgot about that
While holding shift if you hold shift that you won't fall through
And also for those of you wondering Leptor is away on vacation
So we had to continue on briefly without him
Yep, and he should be back pretty soon man though with the one block wide stuffs really scary
Yeah, I I couldn't believe I fell through that. I couldn't believe it. I don't know how to really destroy spiderwebs
Maybe a pickaxe is faster. They seem like they take a long time to break sword sword. Okay
You sir win
All right, you I guess whoa, they're awesome traps apparently laid
And we've got a mob spawner right here
So all I have to do is destroy it with the wooden pick before it spawns any any pesky spiders
And there's a chest in here, too. You shouldn't attempt this if you are not yet ready. I'm feeling it's going to explode
That's what I feel. So you so I should open it then look down here. Look down here. Oh wow
Frozen waterfall, that's pretty crazy. So all right, you know, you don't think you want me to open this
Here's what we should do
Okay, if one of us needs to stand like way back here where it's safe like as far back as possible
I have the most stuff so go ahead and open it and if it starts hissing run for your life
Okay, here we go. Oh my god. There's a lot of stuff in here. Is it hissing? No, but it's I'm scared
There's a ton of leather. There's a ton. I don't know. How do I take things really fast? There we go
Something's gonna explode with
Out of the chest, okay
What's going on? You're stuck in the you're stuck
Okay, that was yeah, if you shouldn't attempt this yeah, right, I think maybe they mean the drop down here
Alright, I got a bunch of leather
Alright, let's go back over here where it's kind of safe and like craft that leather into armor for you real quick
Yeah, make sure I don't waste it this time. I want to say the raw fish is just like one
So I think I'm gonna go ahead and eat one of those. Yeah, we got company. There's a there's a skeleton coming down here
Well with the with the update they're gonna stay in the shadow
So they're not gonna follow you too far while the Sun is shining bright in the sky. There's another one up there
I'll get him. I'll get this rat bastard. So do you want to go up? Oh, wow watch out behind you
Well, they just pulled out it's alright we're good. Oh, there's like a cup
There's like a bunch of spawners in here
Do we want to do this first or do we want to do like the waterfall thing first down there? Oh, well
I guess we're already in here might as well destroy the spawner. Okay. Oh watch out hit that guy
Yeah, leave him alone. He's my friend
Yeah, one of us has to like distract while the other one which has like destroys and if you want to destroy one
It's with your pickaxe. I don't have a pickaxe. Oh, yeah. Whoa. Yeah
That guy yeah, I'm getting close to being dead close. Okay
How's your hunger doing? I got 70%
All right here take take this bread and once your hungers full you'll start healing automatically
Bunch of a bunch of coal bunch of arrows in this chest bones
Do you still have a bow? I do. I guess you took the arrows already. Yeah
What we should do is like all these bones are gonna be really valuable
So I'm thinking just put them in a chest. Yeah, like make a chest over here
Do you still have the crafting table down here? It's still down there
It's down. Also, um, oh never mind. We got this heel pad out here
So if we start running out of food, we can like retreat and like heal up. All right
Hey, you want me to throw these bones down to you? Oh, sure
All right, where should I? Oh, it's creeper behind you creeper creeper coming up behind you
What where did they just fall? I just like throw it down then like the water. I think I see them
Gotta watch out for this guy though. Oh, wait, can I like shoot him with the oh, you got up
We got a zombie here, too. Don't don't waste the arrows unless you have to okay. He's in the water
So I'm just oh now he's up man. They're crafty. They're cunning. Yeah, watch yourself. Okay. I'm safe
I'm gonna throw all the bones down at you. There's a zombie coming for one of us and now a thunderstorm
What was that? It was like it was just thunder. Oh, oh, I gotta turn my volume down again. Get that son of a B
Right. Well, what does it mean? There's just a thing of fire just sitting here burning on obsidian. Where are we at?
This is um, there's like see I think that's just netherrack
Bunch, but I put all the redstone torches around it kind of freaked me out
I got a bunch of arrows. No, here's uh, here's seven more. Oh
All right. Here's what we're gonna have to do. See how the floor is made out of obsidian. Yeah
That's scary because there could be explosions here obsidian is resistant to explosions. So like, you know, I'm saying like the floor won't crumble
Okay, there's something explodes. So be careful when you're removing these redstone torches because they could set off
explosion
Yeah, so we gotta listen. All right, we're good. And that's that netherrack
So is this just that's it. There's nothing else here. I don't I hope we don't just randomly explode
I feel like there should be like another
Area or something. Well, what's with like the broken edges on these walls? You know what I mean?
See how like the walls are kind of cracked over here. Um, I
What's that mean? Yeah, that's I don't know that. Oh, there's another area good fine. Gerber fine. Watch out. That's lava
Can you get that chest without ooh
Golden sword, which is not the greatest thing in the world, but there's another one over here. Okay
Do you have a pickaxe? Did I already ask you that? I do not have a pickaxe
It take mine. I've got a lot more stuff than you so break break the other side
I'm really scared. Someone's gonna explode in here
Here we go. I'm like trying to stay as far back as I can. All right
It's a very long hallway and a sign you can have that back
You want me to go first? I guess man obsidian hall
Well, nothing can get through us in this hallway shivering sands one record. So there's a this is a whole nother area
It sounds like well
Apparently you drop down. That looks kind of sketchy. I don't know about that