Oh, fucking leaked. Oh, Monka, Omega, Monka, Omega, Monka, Omega. He leaked it.
I actually leaked it. Oh, Monka, Omega. He leaked it. Just sitting there. Oops, wrong screen.
Okay, I'll see you later. I'll be back. I gotta have my two minute intro. Hold on.
All right, there we go. That's better. Hi guys, how are you?
Okay, welcome. If you probably could guess today, we're going to do the UFO arcade update.
Just dropped a couple weeks ago in the coin game. One of our old favorites from earlier in the year.
Today was mystery stream and there you go, mystery solved. We're going back to coin game.
They've added, this is a pretty significant update. I'm looking at this right now. So
they added 15 new games. This is not just two. Oh yeah, we got a new update for you. I don't
like three new games. It's 15. I don't know how different or good or we're going to check it out,
but that seems like a lot. Jerma hates me. What are you talking about? I don't. What? Why would
I, why did you say that? Bird game two out of 16? Well, no, that's what we're doing. And if there's
time left over at the end, depending on how long the update takes us to get through, depending how
many prizes I want. And we're also going to play elf bowling because I'm like three people in the
pre stream chat wanted me to like that. That's, there's maybe four people in the chat before the
stream started. They're like, Hey, play elf bowling Christmas flash game. Cause this is the last stream
before Christmas and I'm not streaming on Christmas. So sure. I'll play elf bowling for like 10 minutes
Oh, also I want to show you guys the power of the pre stream chat because this mystery was already
solved for people that were here like 30, 40 minutes ago. I'm going to give you a poll.
I'd like you to look at that poll because this is what you could have chosen. I want to see what
happens. Please vote for what you think you'd like to see today. Please vote. Let's see what happens.
Oh, it didn't work. Why does that not work? Nothing on this one. How?
What I do is how, why is this broken? This is, this is not the poll. This is the poll. Why is this
poll being like, it's whatever. Who cares? Point is you could have, there was coin game. There was
GTA five casino update and there was Nancy Drew on here. You could have selected one of those,
but they chose coin game update and that's probably what I would have chosen too. So
good choice. Let's do it. It's available. It's ready for us right now. I'm ready to get addicted.
All right. A bunch of kids just drove by in a bus screaming out the window. That bus was going
fast. Slow down. Let's go. Let's go. All right. Here we go. Uh, I think there's a new game mode
too. Is there? Oh shit. I have a saved game. Load this one. So we played this in July.
Can I do this? Is it? No. Survival mode isn't here yet. This will delete. Yeah. Let's go.
I bought everything here, right? That wasn't that long ago. No, it wasn't.
Felt like a long time ago though. Hey atmosphere, thanks for the five community subs.
No, that was kind of a long time ago, July. It was like five months ago. That's a long time.
Are we in? The mouse is wrong too. Yeah, it's fine. Mouse curse is misaligned. It don't matter.
Now it has to be aligned now. All right. How's the audio? I got 96 bucks.
Was it UFO? All right. You pawn. Yeah. Okay. I got a hundred. What was my like stats? Happy birthday,
kiddo. There it is. The boom box. I spent all five months ago trying to get where to go. Okay.
I just got really scared. Put it in my inventory. It's like throw it in the trash. All right. Let's
go to the, you can drive cars, right? Why is the game so slow? Holy shit. Somebody's trying to kill
me. Like I am standing in the road. All right. Let's go. Let's go check out the UFO. Wait,
I need money. Don't have to call. Why do I have a gun? Oh, right. Okay. It's a rubber band gun.
I need money. I gotta call. I gotta call my uncle for money, right? How do I get money? Total money
spent. So I spent $41,000. How did I win 80,000? Oh, there's lottery tickets in this game. Holy
shit. I forgot. I completely forgot about the lottery tickets. All right. Well, let's go. Let's
I gotta, I, how do I call uncle, uncle Phil? How do I ask for money? I only have $96. That's not
enough. I gotta remember how to play. Just fast travel. Can I do it like this? Bus passes. How
much is a bus pass? A doll of 50. That's actually not that bad. All right. Where am I going? I want
to go to the UFO point one. Click here to purchase. Thank you. Got a bus pass. Now we're going to go to
one. It's very loud. Why is that so loud? And nothing else is. Sound effects. All right. That's
probably better. Here comes a bus. How do we, uh, this is a trash car, but that's not a bus.
Where's the bus? You are here. Where's the bus? Oh, okay. There it is. All right. I want to go to,
I want to go to one. I want to go to UFO point. Is this going to UFO point? This is going to
Barry's pond. No, we're at Barry's pond. How do I choose where I want to go? I don't want to give
my bus pass. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I'll give it. I'll give it a
give it. Let me in. Okay. Where are we going? Beach front. Oh, okay. I get off. It's a bus.
I never, I never took the bus. You just get out when you want. Right. Okay. I never took,
I took the subway guys. You got, I lived in, I lived, I lived in Boston in my, in almost my
entire life. So I took the subway. It's not the same thing. I took the T like the, the T stops,
the MBTA buses don't exist in Boston. I don't even, I think they do, but not like you think
the CBTA watch out, watch out. All right. Where I can't, I can't see that far. Can I stand up?
Press E. Should I get off now? No, we're not there yet. That's Larry's arcade. I want to go to the
UFO. The UFO is the arcade, the new one. I don't know what I have to also call my dad for more
money. All right. This is home. My home is the gas station. How does that make any sense?
There's a long bus. Like I could have just walked there. I have to go to the money grabbing machine.
Right. Well, let's see what I can play with 94 dollars. This is just actually a real bus.
Next stop. What's after home? Mountains. This is taking me all over the whole city.
You're going to get motion sick. Why am I going to get motion sick? I don't think this is even
in the game last time I played. All right. UFO peer is coming up next. Nobody's getting on or
off the bus. This is kind of depressing. The newspaper behind you says Jeremy. No, it says
Jerry's. All right. Coming out. Here we go. UFO peer. How does a bus work? Uh, it drives around
in a circle and lets people off at designated stops. You can then get on the bus or get off
at any of those designated stops. As long as you have a ticket to get on. This is half life too.
It kind of is. This is how long it takes in half life too to go. The only difference is
we're not getting the voiceovers. Fuck the Drew crew bro. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You don't come to the Drew crew turf and talk like that. What? Jesus. That actually scared the shit
out of me. I was just here. We did a full circle. Where's the UFO? What is the point of taking the
bus if we just went around in a full circle? Can I get off? He just called half life two,
half life one. I did. No, you get on. This is like a train in half life two that you,
or is that half life one? That happens in both. That happens in both. Yeah. What are you talking
about? It happens in both you fake gamer. There it is. Oh, look it. It's so glorious. Look at how
glorious that is. It's awesome. All right. Let's go. Wow. I can't wait to go in there and spend
some tokens. UFO. What does this say? Raceway and fun center. All right. It's done. It's ready.
It's ready for us to enjoy. Let's go. Oh, wow. Wait, this go-karts in here too? This is go-karts.
Holy shit. It's awesome. What are the new games? Butterfly catcher? Oh, you got to do the thing
you do when you go into every new arcade. You don't spend any money. You just walk around and
go, oh, look at this one. All right. What about this next one? Mermaids from space. It's coin one.
Nice. Ski ball. Clock tower. Whack a mole. What's this one? Oh, down a bot. I know this one. This
one's good. Iceberg bounce. I think we've played this one. Maybe not. Just toss it. Ooh, ticket
redemption center. I want to see the prizes of the UFO one. What do you get for prizes? Alien
plush green. Aliens. A pet moon rock. That's pretty sick. We're going to get all the planets. I hope
Jupiter's on here. Lava lamp. Fun capacitor. Plasma ball. It's one of these things you put your hand
on. Light sword. Oh, there's lightsabers in this one. Oh, my God. How many? Hover board is 100,000
tickets. Okay, it's 100,000 tickets to the hover board. I want a lightsaber. I want I want the blue
lightsaber. I want the hover board. And I want the thing that you put your hand on. Get the hover
board. All right, I will. I also am going to turn the sound down again, because it's I'm going to
hurt somebody. All right, that sounds good. Let's go. Wait, what else is in here? This thing. This
thing sucks. You can't win this thing. It's the do-goo. This one's actually rigged. They've made
videos on this one. It's actually impossible to win unless the person that's operating it wants
you to win. Hold on. There's a claw gate. Isn't there upstairs too? Popcorn Pete. Hey, kids,
I win an official popcorn Pete plush toy. Collect all eight cards and win a Pete plush.
Ah, look at this. There's a popcorn machine too.
Fucking game of the year. You want to know what my game of the year is? This. Dude, where's my cow?
Oh, what is this one? Wormhole. Let's check out the back. DeVito Do? DeVi-Devo-Devotted Do.
I'll take one. Give me it. Give me another one. Give me more. Give me more Danny DeVito Do.
It's so loud. I tried to turn it down. How loud is that? Is it so loud that you can't even stand it?
It probably is. I'm gonna give it a ceiling. That should help. You let me know. This is a
test to see if it hurts. Tell me if it hurts. Pretty good. I'll take another one. Oh shit.
Let's do it again. I'm making a tower. How many can I put on one tower? Oh my god.
That's like six. Imagine seeing somebody do this. I feel like you draw a crowd at this point.
I think that's the end of the tower. Oh my god. It's not. It's almost as tall as me.
I'm wasting money. Oh shit. I am wasting money. You're right. Oh, that's it. Hold on.
Whatever. We got six. Who cares? Oh, money machine. Let's go. Just like at the carnival.
This isn't a restroom. I'm not going to the bathroom in here. Quick. Get the bits. Get the
hundred. Oh. Monka. Omega. All right. Let me out. I'm thrown out of here instantly. Throw it like
onto the track. All right. I'll get those later. Let me go upstairs. I want to see what's upstairs.
What is up here? Laser zone? What is laser zone? Welcome to laser zone. It's five bucks.
It's laser tag. All right. What else is over here? Okay. You just can go down to the go-karts.
And that's what's that. All right. Let's go. Let's do laser tag first.
This is a pretty substantial update. How do? What is going on? I can't. I'm not.
You gotta go. Go for the base. Go for the base. Go for the base. Here's the actual pro tip when
you're playing anything. Any laser tag. Sneak around back to the base. Usually it's a dome.
That's all the way in their corner. And just hold down the trigger. Just at the base. You'll be
number one on the leaderboards every time. Don't even fight anybody. Do not fire at any other
people. Use all your ammo only for the small little light dome that's in their base.
It's funny because people will just ignore you. I just died. You'll get 100% ignored.
Where's my ammo? How do I get ammo? Ammo? Where's ammo? Oh, recharge station. Here we go.
All right. Let's do it. But yeah, a typical laser tag game is about,
I don't know, it'll be 15 minutes. You could spend a full 13 and a half minutes as long as
you sneak into the back of their base. You'll have like 60 million points. And when they print
out the scorecard showing how awesome everybody was, you'll be, you'd be like insanely, you'd be
so out of reach. Let me do it now. Well, these people, there's no, I don't think there is a base.
No roughhousing. I would have just got yelled at. A whistle would have just gotten like blown.
It is still so loud though. I have to like do it manually again. Where are they? Are they dead?
Got them both. Game over. Oh, I got a two. All right. That was, that's a 2.0 K.D. That's not bad.
I just got 400 tickets for doing that. Holy, that's a lot. I'm doing that again.
This time I'm going to try as hard as I can. I understand the game now. Let's go. It's time to
be the very clear adult that shouldn't be in there that's killing everybody. You know what I mean?
That's like tagging everybody. There's some dad that's just going overboard and just like,
got you, got you, got you, got you. Oh, I got you through the wall. Yeah, you're dead. It's like,
Jesus, come on dad, fucking relax. No, no, you have to go back. Sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint.
Got you. Call your hits. Yeah, this is, this is annoying older kid or dad that's going too hard.
This is also the dad that when he comes out of this, he has a full band of sweat on his head.
Do a laser tag stream. That actually might be like kind of funny.
You'd have to find a place that would allow you to do that though.
Back to spawn. Literally spawn camping children. It's also the worst when you realize,
so when you play laser tag and you, it can be very disorienting. There's fog machines,
loud music, there's lights everywhere. Somebody on the other team could just be standing behind
you, walking behind you the whole time, going like this to your back. And you just have no idea.
It sucks because then you'll go look at your score, which a lot of these places,
they'd like, I said, they do a printout and it shows you like your, your accuracy and,
and it looks like times hit 680. And you look at the person next to you and you're like,
what did you give times hit? Oh, four. Oh, what the fuck?
How many tickets is that? Um, guys, this is where you farm. The tickets is right here.
We're getting that hoverboard. All right. Well, I'll, I'll come back.
18 KD. Nice job, dad. Let's do the, uh, go-karts. Nice. See, look, little Doug.
You know what always scared me about this? Anytime you went to a place that had go-karts,
the staff for some reason would just be walking around, like on the track and shit.
And I'd always be so scared to drive fast because somebody would just be walking by. It's like,
Oh shit. That person, that, that's it. They don't care. It's just a staff member.
I see him like 300 feet away. They're like moving. Yeah. They'd be like,
there's like a guy smoking a cigarette, like right there. This is how you drive.
No, this is not an indicator of how I drive. And it always was so annoying because the somebody,
when you knew you were on your last lap, you'd see the worker come and close the gate and you're
like, no, don't close the gate. And you have to go the other way. There's a separate way you have
to go to put the carts back. Still in last place. I don't know if this was a competition five seconds
ago. Am I on one wheel? I wish I had a controller. Oh, that was a tight turn. And that was tight
turn. He had a red shell. How have they not made a game that was, you know, those VR experiences,
how they're all stupid. Come check out the VR experience where you get like a little laser gun
and the polygons are five times bigger than they should be. Why not have a Mario Kart style
VR experience where there's like 12 seats, everyone's in a car and it moves around this
feedback and you're actually in like a Mario Kart style race. That exists. Oh, I want to play it.
Where do I play that? I have to come in first place eventually here. Not now though. I just
want to check it out that they literally do that in Japan. Are you serious? Japan seriously is
that one place on earth where they seem to just do everything better than everybody else for some
reason. You know what I mean? Oh, yeah, we have arcades here in America. Yeah, yeah, we do.
Oh, they're really fun. Sometimes this you can play Mortal Kombat 3. Oh, no, you can't. Sorry,
both of the coin slots have been taped over because the machine's broken.
You want to play the new Halo game where you can shoot as Master Chief?
Go, good luck. There's always four people sitting in there and they're part of the same four friends
that came and they're not leaving that booth. They never get out until they like they beat the game.
I feel like this place is in Japan where I can put on a headset and eat food but not in real life,
but I still get full of nutrition and stuff. Also, very, very, very important. When are arcades
going to implement the old school Super Nintendo Mario comes up and says it's time for somebody
else to play? Remember that shit when you went to used to go to GameStop? We're like,
why don't they do that? Those of you that don't know, in every GameStop, in most video game stores
or boutique stores, whatever, there was always like a Super Nintendo or PlayStation 1 in the corner.
That was just a demo. You could just play it was various games. If you stayed on that for more than
15 to 20 straight minutes, Mario would come on. It would go to a black screen. Mario would appear
and go, thank you. Next person in line, please. That, yes, it did. That happened. And that person
would have to leave. Otherwise, it would look like a total asshole. Yes, that happened. Yes, it did.
It's real. Making that up. You're paying money though to play that one. Yeah, but I got money.
I want to pay too. Will they have more than one machine then? All right, let's do this one. I'm
going for it. How much does this one cost? Two bucks. That's a lot. First fucking try. That's how
we do a first try jackpot. I'll take a first try jackpot. Thank you. Everybody show up. Everybody,
that's me you're talking to. That's me you're talking to. Let's do it again. These are my tickets.
Get the fuck out of here. Again. I'll never get it again. Spin again. Yeah, it's like laggy.
Again. Again. What's the jackpot at now? Fuck, he's going to chase that high all night.
I'll take another jackpot. That's two. He's just lucky. I don't think he is. I don't think he is.
I think he's got the skill to be able to get a... How many tickets do I need? A lot. I'm going to
trip on these. Is money laundering going on in here? No, there's no money laundering. I don't do
that. Here's the problem with this machine though. You'll get so frustrated playing this machine.
Typically, this is how you do it. You put your money in. You wait. Okay, go around.
Go around. Gah, I missed. But you'll do this 10 times in a row and get so frustrated that you
try to catch it instantly right when you activate and put your money in like this.
Fuck. Let's go again. Okay. I am unstoppable. What? Did I get two in a row? I did it. I
didn't do it. I did it. Security? Why is this guy going to explode? What's going on? Why is
this person going to explode? Get this person. This person's a bomb. This person's going to explode.
What the fuck? Get out of here. Get the bomb out. Get him out. What about my tickets? Again,
it's a sparkler. Whatever. I'm going to get kicked out of the casino. I'm going to get
kicked out of the casino. No, I can't do that right now. Did the game crash? Let's do it again.
Hey, Jeff. Thanks for the five community subs.
I can't lose. I can't lose. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let me count. Let
me see my winnings. Get it out of here. No. Look at the jackpot keeps going up. I'm going to...
You think I'm not going to get that hoverboard? Are you serious? Let's go count the tickets.
Out of my way. That's 4,000 tickets already. You don't think I'm going to get 100,000?
Oh, what's this one? How much money do I have? 94. Cool. Let's start over here. Right here. This
sounds good. How do you play this one? How does this one go? Just toss it. You throw the ball.
Cool. This sounds fun. I'm going to do it right now. That's fine. Let's go. Oh, I'm going to be
obsessed with this. I'm going to be... I just toss it forehead. You don't think I'm going to
do this one again? Absolutely. How many do I need? How many points do you actually need to win the
super jackpot? Oh, shit. Again, I did it. 270 tickets. Again, I'm going to try to get more
than once. It's only 200. Yeah. I mean, come on. What's this jackpot? Oh, I almost just soft locked
it. Yeah, that was close. Oops. Oh, God damn it. I actually, I didn't, I really didn't mean to do
that. I went too high. What? Like you've never done that before? Please. I got it again. I mean,
no. You've never accidentally tried to throw something in one of these things that just
bounces back and hits you in this chest. That does happen. That's never happened to you.
You've never been playing like the football game or the throw the thing, toss the thing,
and you go a little too hard and it bounces back and hits you in the chest. You know,
the throw the football through the holes. You've never hit the, you've never missed the one you're
trying to hit the little one at the very bottom and it bounces back and hits you in the face.
I got it again. You're taking the, I'm an idiot too far. I feel like we've been to different
arcades. I'm sorry. Those of you, everybody, everybody over the age of like 28 in the chat
right now. This is like probably eight of you. You remember playing the throw the ball. You had
to like throw it hard because the shit was broken half the time. Throw the ball into the hole and
it wouldn't go in. So you had to throw it kind of hard and it would bounce back and hit you in the
stomach hole in the sign. Oh shit. You're right. Hole in the sign, hole in the sign, hole in the sign.
I once bounced a basketball at the top of the cage in the hoop game and smashed myself in the
face and started crying. Thank you. Thank you for explaining how this happens. I don't think I can
make that. Oh guys, I don't think that's possible. Is it? It might be possible. Oh,
it's going to be possible. Shit. Stop wasting throws. It's all right. I got, I have $84.
Yeah. I'm the guy that walks into the arcade with a hundred dollars.
A little higher. This is going to kill me. More power. I'm holding it down as far as I can go.
I might, I might have to come back to this.
Give a shot. Put a bowling ball. No, because that's dangerous and stupid. I'm not going to hit this.
Aim. Like that's no, it doesn't do anything. You can't bounce it.
What happened? Where'd it go? Oh, all right. I'm never going to get it. I'm never going to get it.
Leave. Maybe I'll try it later. Another day. All right. What's next? I want to play it though. All
right. Is this one. I, this one's fun. This is when you throw a bunch of a ping.
That's going to happen every time in it. Now there is strategy with this one. What you do is
you scoop up all of them. There's usually about maybe 20 or 30. You get as many as you can hold
in your arms and you just toss them all up at the exact same time over here. And you just, that's,
you'll hit most of them. Game. It's going to do that loud song again, isn't it?
All right. Here we go. Come on, get them all. Ah, do it again. I get it. Cheating. How am I
cheating? Get the ones in the front first. Get it. That's it. I got them all. That one wasn't even
hard. Bonus round.
Shit. Okay. That's gonna, I gotta get it. You gotta do bonus first.
First part's not hard. Get it. Get this last one. Get the last one, please. Get the last one.
Bonus round. Go with the front row first.
It's loud for me. So what's the strategy? Middle out? You think? Like middle out. Middle out?
Just throw fast. All right. I'm just going to spam them. Spam. Spam. Spam. Bounce. Bounce. Bounce.
That shit's impossible. This is not even possible. I don't think it's even possible.
It's gonna take insane long. It's not even possible.
What about off the edge? I mean, it doesn't really do much.
Okay, one more time. That's it. Final attempt. And then moving on to down the bot, whatever it's
called. Bonus round. There you go. You can't do it. It's not possible. Whatever.
I'm getting a lot of time today. Okay. All right. Let's move on.
Nice. All right. Here we go. Here's one of the games I'm talking about, guys.
If you've ever played this before, you whip balls at these things.
Oh, I got to get this better. I can do this better. I can do that better. 500 or go home.
I think. Yeah. 500 points or go home.
They're already down. They can't go down anymore.
How's that worse than last time? It got, it fucked up.
Aim for the one that has red light. Yeah, that's what I was doing.
Oh, this is going to be worse.
Now you got it. Okay. I got it. I got plenty of money. I'm bad. All right. Sure.
It's not, that wasn't bad. That wasn't bad. That wasn't bad. 380 down as many as possible.
The light is bait. Is that true? Is it light bait? The light is bait. All right. Light is bait.
I'm going for just a full on hit. Every single, I have to, if you hit every single throw,
you'll get 500. That should work.
God damn it. Shoot between them. It's, it's just my sensitivity.
Oh, don't go for the top ones. Bad idea. Let's try to, it says that I need more sensitivity.
I'm going to get, ah, I'm going to get stuck here. I'm going to get stuck here. It's okay.
I'm going to do it. I need to get at least 400 or something.
Oh, all right. I keep getting stuck in the same spot. Go for doubles only. Let me see.
That's not reliable. Now doubles ain't reliable. Check that.
Doubles ain't reliable. Now doubles ain't reliable. Unfortunately doubles just kind
of happen to try a second row. Maybe it just farm doubles in the second row. Maybe we'll see.
Okay. You can do, we're only going to do the, the, the bottom and the, okay. We're going farming
doubles. I'm just a psycho. Do you have to be? All right. Let's try it for real this time.
And I'm moving on. We're going to skee ball next. What? That's, that's too hard to do that. I need
more sensitivity. All right. Last one. Finally, actually last one. I'm just going to go try as
many as I can. This is bait. It's fine. Here we go. I don't, I don't care. I don't care. I don't
care. It's, it's the sensitivity. It's got to be higher. I can't move. Just no, no, get me out.
Get me out. Get me out of here. No, if I increase sensitivity, I'll stay there for like another three
hours. Sure. Is there sensitivity? I don't know. There is no sensitivity. Well, let's go. This is
just original skee ball. I think this one's in the old game, but this one's a, it has a, yeah,
this one has a space theme to it. Skee ball is one of those games that you seriously get. I get
oh, Jeremy, that's never happened to me in an arcade before. No way. I, when I play skee ball,
if I, if I, that never happens to me. Yes, it does. No, I've never rolled a little too hard
for it to hit the back and go forward. What are you, what are you, what are you for? No,
Jeremy, I've never walked over to the side and placed every single ball in the hundred. No,
Jeremy, I'm such a good boy. Not everyone's as bad as you, boomer. You guys are describing
a technique that I did maybe when I was 11. I wasn't a boomer when I was 11. 50 points.
I can do better than that. I can do much better than that. 11 year old boomer. Everything's a
boomer. Guys, I'm drinking a coffee right now. It's pretty good. That's boomer coffee.
I drink my, this coffee's better. Oh, okay. Uh, guys, I drive, uh, I drive a Honda Civic.
That's a boomer car. Oh, okay. Guys, I buy a Charmin ultra soft toilet paper. That's a boomer
toilet paper. I use it per day. Okay. Hope you're having a good day. I am. Hey, thanks.
Hope you're having a good day too. I gotta get at least 100 before I leave.
What's my favorite ice cream? Mom's bacon cookie from Baskin Robbins. It's the best ice cream ever
and I think it no longer exists. I tweeted about it and they deleted it off their menu.
That tweet, by the way, had like 600,000 impressions on it. Why would you get rid of
that ice cream after, after somebody that literally has hundreds of millions of people
viewing their Twitter? How could you do something like that? Impressions. Well, how many impressions
did that get? I don't know. Who gives a shit? You know what impressions means, guys? I'm going to
give you some, some fucking influencer lingo here. Those of you that don't know, that is actually
how many times people may have even just scrolled by and not given a shit about the thing that you
said. Yeah, but they, but they still, they still went by it. Okay. Fucking boomers. Am I right?
I have to get a hundred. Come on. I can't find mom's bacon cookies. I know it's actually
unfortunate. It actually is. He's trying to be probably, probably was like seasonal
and I know I'm going to say this, but imagine having seasonal ice cream.
Is that, is that real? It's, it's not like pineapples are not in season. You know what I mean?
It's ice cream. Seasonal pizza. I have to get a hundred. Why can I not get a hundred?
Pumpkin spice lover is suffering. I don't, I don't know. Okay. I guess I do get it. It's like a
marketing thing where it's like pumpkin spice during the fall. Ooh, warm and spicy and it's warm
in your belly. Ooh, okay. But that pumpkin spice comes out of a bag. It's a powder that comes out
of a bag. It's not like, Oh, good thing these pumpkins are in season. My fresh pumpkin brains.
That's what you know. Get in there. I'm going to go aim down and yeah. All right. That's the
that's just, I'm going to aim down right there. A little bit higher sorting algorithm noise.
Oh yeah. I know what you're talking about. The things they, yeah. Oh, you're killing me. Yep.
Oh, I have to listen to it now. Then it goes like, Oh, I have to hear it right now. Let's go.
This is going to be loud as fuck. Hold on. Sorting algorithms. Yes. Ah, louder. No, it's like,
it's too, this is the best part. It gives the best part. Everyone quiet. Here comes the best part.
No, no, not this one. It doesn't, it goes. I'll wake my favorite one. No, fuck that one. That one
sucks. Dumb. Where is it? Here it comes. I think this is the one. This is the one. No, no, no, not
this one. It's a, it's one that's in two different sections. It's the one coming up next. Show it on
stream. Okay. I just want to show you my favorite one. It's all others are not even close. Not even
fucking close. Give me this. Where's my source? All right. Here it comes. Can you see it? No, you
can't. People are going, dude, I don't, not that one. Not this one. Boom. Next one, please. Not
this one either. Fuck this one. This one. Ready? Here it comes. This one. Yeah. Here it comes. The
best part. It's the best part. Oh, that was the best part. All right. No, no, fuck that. Let's go
back to this. It's really that sound. That's so fucking funny. I have to get it in a hundred
before I do anything. I can't know. It's lower octave. Stop getting tens. I'm trying to get a
hundred. I'm never going to get a hundred. Jerma, I just joined and the first thing to hear is
sorting algorithms. Why? Um, hold on. My, my, my, I'm, I can't even, somebody just complained
about the sorting algorithm. I, that's, I can't, I can't hear that right now.
You've complained about it before, have I? Oh, that's my favorite sorting algorithm. Skeeball.
See, here is the peer, the packets of data. Give me a hundred. Oh my fucking God. What was wrong
with that? I can't. It's, I need a new machine. It's definitely the angle. It's the angle. No.
Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I got it. I got it. I got it. You don't think you've ever
hit a hundred in real life. Yep. You got to go up. There's actually a strategy. If you,
here's the thing about the hundred. When you hit the hundred, you just, you get into the zone
and you get two, three or four hundreds in a row. And then for the rest of the night,
you'll never hit one more. In fact, it might not happen for years. I have to hit this. Like
this is not this difficult. More than that. I'm not, I'm just going to, but the thing is I can't
keep the same angle because the game forces you down. Nancy drew waiting. You had a chance to
vote for Nancy drew and you soiled it. Why can I not do this? Why can I not do this? Good. Done.
I did it. What happened to that? Jesus. You suck. It is not easy to get it in this game. It's not
easy to do. I think this is so easy. It's not. That's it. That's not easy. Oh, okay. At least
I heard the noise. Let's go. I cash in the tickets. See if I can get a lightsaber.
What do I have? 4,397. Let's go. I tried here. All right. We're almost 10% of the way to the
hoverboard. I'm just going to farm that. You know, I'm going to farm that. All right. What else we
got? We're doing full circle and then we go in middle. That one looks cool. This was already,
this was a 500. What? I'll take it. Mermaids from space. Mermaids and face coin pushers.
Five tickets, 10 tickets. You collect these. Anything else I need to know? All right. Let's
go. Multi credit. How many credits to load? 10. How many? I have 120 coins. This one is,
I love this already. Oh, I wish, this is why I wish this existed. This one, exact one.
All right. I got bonus. What did I do? Coin pusher. Pog. Yeah. Now this is content.
This is the content that you came to this stream for. There it is. Where's the 100? There's 100
right here. I'll get it. Here it comes. Usually it's quarters and takes forever. Yeah. Oh,
it's still going. Still going. Yeah, that was good. That was a really good one. Right side now.
Look at all this delicious stuff on the right side. Watch this. We're going to get an avalanche
right now. That's a burger boy tactic. Yeah, it is. Burger boy tactics work, guys. People want
patience. No, no, no, no. Just, you have to use the burger boy technique. Once that 100 goes down,
we're going to the left side. Just kill it. Kill the whole thing. Is this burger boy technique
or is this bored rich kid? I don't know. Last push. Oh, 1,290 tickets. 1,300 tickets. 1,400 tickets.
Wow. You just got yourself 1,400 more tickets there. And credits. Get in the center. Oh,
shit. You're right. Look at all that in the center. 1,400 tickets. Cool. I like that they're green so
I can pretend that it's money. Again, last one. Last one. We're going right in the middle. Yeah,
the bored rich kid. There are people meticulously crafting their next shot with the quarter that
they have. Well, this dickhead over here is just spamming them. That doesn't even matter to him,
apparently. This is going to be a lot. Look at this huge wave coming in. Spamming is not smart
because all the coins land on each other. Yeah, I know. In fact, I'm doing it wrong. You've got
to wait till it comes in here. I've played these before. The best technique is seriously this one
right here. You wait until it's all the way out. Put one down to make it so it's flat. Guaranteed
flat. Sometimes you can get two. No more than that, though. Maybe three. Come on. That was a good one.
Get this left side. Don't neglect the right side either.
Burger Boy wouldn't have wanted this. He's not dead. This is not what Burger Boy would
have wanted if he were alive. This one is actually mindlessly fun. All right, let's go mindless.
Look at that wave coming in. This is what Burger Boy would have wanted. There it is.
I got some extra credits. Hold on. Make these ones count. All right. Yes. Good.
I got extra credits. Left side right here. I got one more shot right in the middle. Knock it down.
Look at that. It's so close. I get to keep going. This side right here. All right, that's probably it.
No, I get to keep going. Don't have to spend any more money. I beat my last record. 1,400.
Oh, shit. Any more? That's it. 16, 57. No, no, no. They're still pushing.
Mom, the creepy old man won't get off the coin game. Well, son, here's the thing about the creepy
old man. The creepy old man comes in here every day with $100 and allows the arcade to continue
to stay in business and lets them turn a potential profit for them to put another clock tower in the
game, in here, in the children casino. All right, here we go. Wait, I want to cash these in.
What am I at? 12, 14,876. I'm almost at the lightsaber. Lightsaber's 30.
Now, don't even look at these middle games yet. This one's still at 500.
Almost. You gonna run out of money? It's all right. I'll get some more.
It's 500 every time. This is the best way to farm tickets.
Building is on fire. Oh, I'm out of money. All right, I'm out of money. All right, back to the...
I need more money. Back to the money. Get that sparkler away from me. Yeah, I told you. You guys
thought I was going... acting crazy. Go play the check-in game? Not yet. Not yet. I still have to
experience all the new content. I don't have any money. Where's the money machine? Upstairs? All right.
I don't think I ever got the jackpot in the check-in game. I did not. I did? No. Yeah, no, I did. I did.
That's right. I did. Top right corner. No, right in front of the door. I did it twice? Yeah, it was
like five months ago. I don't remember. Top right. I got 75 bucks. Let me out. Where were we? Oh,
that's right. Butterfly drop. How does this one work? Collect... collect all six to win the bonus.
What's the bonus? Oh, you have to put... it's like the hockey one. I remember the hockey one.
This one's actually kind of hard. Get all the infinity stones. Oh, all right. This one...
those are about 50 tickets. This one could be pretty... this one could be pretty lucrative.
This one's bad. I mean, it's not the greatest game, but it doesn't mean it can't be lucrative.
Oh, shit. I missed. Oh, shit. This one sucks. Oh, this one sucks, but I have to get the bonus.
Get away from me. You're using the net upside down. I didn't even realize that till right now.
Depending... seriously, depending how lucrative the bonus is. I mean, we need to see it once.
How much is this? Two bucks? Holy shit. Is this even possible? This one sucked. Just, I know it
sucks, but we... we have to see what the bonus does. I'm already two in. Shake the table. No,
you can't shake anything unless you get thrown out. There it is. Okay, there's orange and pink.
Got them both. All right, now we need red, blue, and yellow. That's it. All right, we can wait for
this rotation because there's a... this is red. I might... I can get the blue. Got it. All right,
now red and yellow. That's it. Here it comes. I broke it up a little. I'm sorry. If this bonus
is less than 500, I'm never gonna play this one again. Don't worry. You don't have to worry
about that. Bingo. Yeah, I just need blue. Is it... where do you see 200? I don't see 200 anywhere.
I need red. All right, you guys didn't think there's gonna be 2,000 tickets for the bonus
here. That's a lot. That is a huge amount. That's a ridiculous amount, actually. So, I mean,
it's a lot. I feel like I could probably win the spaceship light machine thing four times before
I do this one. All right, let's move on. That is a good... that's a good grab, though. That's 2,000.
More than 2,000 tickets. All right, other side. We have... ooh, wormhole. This one looks cool.
Two dollars before credit. What, do you drop it through? Let's get a good look.
So you just... oh, it goes all the way around. We gotta count seconds here. Okay, let's see.
From this... from when I click the button. One, two, three. All right, it's about three and a
half seconds. So how long does it take to go around? Let's see. Jackpot, for instance. Ready?
One, two, three. All right, so ready? Check this out. I'll get it right here. Oh, I'm in the wrong
place. One, two. All right, it's right there. Do it again. You start counting at one. Why do you
start counting at one, not zero? No, because I'm not a weirdo. Zero, one. No, it's one, two, three.
Not zero, one, two. See? That's the terrible ones. Zero, one, two. No, it's one, two, three.
He's not a programmer. Who counts like that? Nobody counts one... nobody counts zero, one, two.
I'll try it. I'll try it. All right, I'll try it. I'll try it. That's the correct way. Zero is
a void. It's not even a real number. Zero. No. Zero, one, two. It's close. Zero, one, two.
Two. That's literally untrue. Zero, one, one, zero. Zero, one, two.
So it works sometimes. Zero, one, two. All right, maybe I'll change the way I count numbers now.
Give me my tickets. That kid's gonna... look at how many burn marks are all over this kid.
What? He's got like... you're messed up. We're gonna find where your parents are.
Leave him alone. Well, what do you want me to do? He's holding it so close to his face,
he's burning his face. Here we go. This is the one I'm talking about. Cow machine. First try,
get it. Oh, yeah, I'm gonna clean this whole machine out. That's why you don't play this game
ever. That's why I don't... this thing grips as hard as your grandmother. Your grandmother
has a real soft grip. You got to distribute the weight. I get it. Don't grab the head. No,
no, no. You don't grab the head. You got to grab right in the chest. Right along the chest or
distribute the weight. That's not the chest, but I... no. I gotta get chest. There it is. It's lined
up perfectly. Just got to get it right in the... right there where the weight is distributed.
If this ain't it, this is impossible. Look at that distributed weight.
Come on. It's... what? No, no, no. I want to play it. I want...
How am I supposed to do this? It's right in the chest. Right in the sternum. There it is.
Get it over there. It's... you can't... it won't... it can't move. So how is it even possible?
I didn't get anything. It's rigged. No, it's a motion problem. Get it. All right,
that's a pretty good grip. It's impossible. You need to just toss it over here accidentally somehow.
That might be it. All right. Accident. Nice. Pretty good accident. I got one. Cool. Let's
get another one. Let's get one so we can give it to somebody here. Throw it on the racetrack.
Why would I waste a perfectly good cow throwing it on a racetrack? Why would I waste it? That's
the one. That's a perfect grab. What? That doesn't even make any sense. The cow just struggled and
got out. You have to actually throw it in like it did last time. Quick, get the Pikachu socks.
They're right there. I already got one, so it doesn't matter, but I'm gonna try.
Stop moving around so much. Settle. Settle. Settle. Why is it not settling? Throw it in there. Toss it.
Throw. Throw. Throw. Throw. Throw. Throw. Throw. Throw it in. Throw it in. Throw it in.
That's two. Oh, that was almost a free one. That was almost for free. Do it again. He's addicted.
Addicted to mega milk. Oh, I see. You're doing it. All right. I see what you mean. He's
addicted. He's addicted. I want to try to get one for free. We need a good bounce on the free one.
This is a cute game though. Go for the closest one. Well, what I'm trying to do is I'm trying
to make a pile. Derma's going to be here for four hours. No, no, no, no, no. More like four minutes.
Get it in. It's almost there. Grab it from the butt and then I should be able to toss it in there.
No, didn't get it. I just have to grab it. No, I have to push it in the head. I'm going to push
its head down. You know what I'm saying? Maybe it'll bump it in. Get it in there. Yes. Another one.
I want more. I wonder how much these sell for. Oh my god. I did it again. Another one. I want more.
I got to move some of these over this way. Let's try this guy right here. Right in the head. Got it.
I'm being such an asshole. Get your presents, man. I want to fill it to the brim
and then sell them. I want to turn. Wait. You just have to wait because I'm currently
getting all of them. These probably sell for like a hundred bucks each at least.
I'm on a roll. Yeah. What happens if I get them all? Can I get them all? Will they just stack up
over here and I can open the floodgates and have just a bunch of cows fly out? Some of them are
impossible to get though because of where they're located. Is this why Derma decided to move to
Las Vegas? For claw machines? So you're holding up the line here. That's all right. Get the first
one you tried. This one is ready to go. Just need to get it right in the chest. Right here.
There it is. Go around. There we go. Get the blue one in the back. Blue? That's not in here.
That's the background. Mario says it's time for someone else to play.
And then you just skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, skip as fast as you can so you hope nobody saw it.
They did. They all did. Is there something else buried in here?
What? The mod's doing a good job stopping copy and pasting trolls.
Yeah, good. So see you later. See you next time. Is it just, is it so much to ask to want to fill
this up and just turn around and just flex? Throw it in. I tell you, it's almost, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Ready? Watch.
There it is. Oh, I'm so excited. I'm almost as excited for sorting algorithms.
All right. I'm gonna get one more in there. One more and then I'm gonna open it up and
then I'm gonna turn around and be like, have at it, kids. And they're all gonna be like, yeah.
You're gonna make a, you're just making a riot? No. What? Does it count as a win if I pick the
one up that's right there and drop it over the sensor? I'm sure it does. I just have to get one
more in here and that's it. Look, I went over the double dare line. Okay. I put enough milk in there
to win the family challenge. Hold on. But I want to do more. I just want one more and then I'm done.
I won't have to play it again. Just want one more. I want to go so far over it that it's just like a
joke. Like, holy shit, man. What overkill is this? You did it. You won. But I want to make sure that
no one else gets to win as much as I did. I want to be on the leaderboard over there. All right.
Good. It's in a good spot. Cow leaderboard. Come on. I did it.
It's as many as it could possibly go in there. Let's go in. Let's see what we can get. I wonder
if I win. Did I win? Oh, wow. I won. See the real evil mastermind here thing to do.
Beat it. Whip out some super glue in like super glue. The door shut.
So it's like, there's prizes right there. We can't get them. The prizes are right there.
You evil, evil man. Jeremy, you need to let go. Oh yeah. I said I was going to stop after that.
It's all right. Yeah. That's a cartoon villain scheme. All right. I'm out.
Let's get our prizes here. Oh, no. The prizes are right there. I can't get them.
Oh, what are you doing? What the hell is it doing? Can I go in and reach my hand in there?
Wait, hold on. I have to just jostle. I have to just move. Yep. There it is. Okay.
No, no, no. Don't pick it up. I want to get out. I want to get out. I don't want to pick that up.
All right. I can try this one. This one's like right here. All right. That's it. That's it.
It's not softlocked. I can pull these ones out. Look, there are a couple. There are a couple that
are softlocked, but I can get them. See, I just have to pay money. No, I don't. Jeremy,
what are you doing? I'm just trying. I don't want to waste the money. I might as well try to grab one.
All right. That's good. They're both ready. All right. I beat the cow machine. Cool.
Uh, what do we have? Oh, there's more in the middle. All right. Hold on.
Why don't we have tickets? Get all of them. You don't really think I'm going to sit there
and get every single cow in that machine. Why on earth would I do that? Let's check my inventory.
Good. One, two, three. All right. Cool. I didn't despawn. I have them. Oh, I want to get a Mr.
Potato Head. How do I do this? All right. Right. It's from the middle. I can get one of these. I
just have to win. I have 20,000 tickets. I need 80,000 more. Do this one first. Okay.
You can only count to three. I don't have coins. What are you talking about? Oh.
Hey, I have something for you. This is for you. Come here. This is less dangerous.
Get over here. I have something. This is for you. This is for you. It's less dangerous. Here.
Oh, he fell downstairs and he hit his mouth. Oh, I'm sorry about that, kid. I'm sorry. He's running.
Even though when a kid, when like somebody cries, it's like, it gets louder. Yes.
You're mocking him. I remember when I used to cry. I would do this thing. And a lot of people do
this when something happens. That's so traumatic. Something like, Oh, I bumped my hand and it hurt.
You start instantly crying insanely hard, but you said no noise is coming up.
So you have this face like this. Should I turn the camera on for this? So you have this face,
right? That looks like this. Like princess bumped my hand real hard. Ready? Like, and then crying
happens. Sometimes it's, it's really delayed. Here comes an edit. Who cares? Nice hair hippie.
Ban that person for life, please. And you can always tell like, Oh, oh no, you like bumped your
knee. Oh shit. Oh, here I, oh, oh, here. I see that face and like it's, oh, it's, you know, it's
coming. You have good here. Hey, thanks. Three in a row, three in a row, three in a row and I get,
and I get a thousand subs. Oh, too bad. All right. Three in a row, three in a row, I get a thousand
subs. If I don't get three in a row, then I, I don't say that part. I don't want to say the next
part. I don't want to say the next part. That's too unreliable. Ghost pepper? No. Got it. Three in a
row and I get a thousand subs. Not three in a row. I eat a ghost pepper. Oh, all right. Double
or nothing. If I get another, I get four in a row, I get 2,000 subs. Okay. Five and five or
nothing. If I, I'll eat 10 ghost peppers on stream or 10,000 subs. Oh shit. Oh, gambling.
God damn it. I should have just, I should have just stopped there. That was a lot of subs. He's
going to chase this high. Oh, there they are. They're the subs. 10. Nice. I just got 10. 10,000
subs right there by cold war hall. Oh my God. 10,000 subs. You actually did it. I lost too.
That's a lot. 10,000 subs. Gifted. Holy shit. That's, how much money would that be? That's 50.
That's insane. Imagine that. Don't imagine that because that's never going to happen. So don't
worry. Dude. Oh dude. Coke. Coke. No, don't, I can't say that. If I say that, that's like,
I don't want to like slander a company. Oh, another 10,000 subs from you guys. That's
20,000 subs. 10,000 from Antfork. Thank you. Holy shit. Zero. One. Two.
Still good enough. You can do a little slander. Oh, Jerma sucks. Thanks to the 5,000 community subs.
You guys are really doing, you guys are going hard. Three in a row. I get 50,000 gifted subs.
If I don't get three in a row, I will, I will try, I will try my hardest to eat a one small,
a four by four piece of plywood. I get, I did it. I don't even know what that one was for.
I don't know what that one was for. That one's for something too. That one's for, that's another
50 million subs. I got a, I got a lot of tickets. Ghost pepper plywood. Jamie, thanks for the 5,000
community subs. Appreciate that. All right. I have 25,000 tickets. I'm, I just have enough
for the lightsaber. Let's do this one. Trick with these, you got to stay in the middle.
Stay right in the middle and you have access to all of them. Say, I know some of you,
some of you gamers that play this, you'll go like this. Oh, I missed. Oh shit. Stay in the middle.
Check this. All right. What's the, what's the score? I didn't see he was green. What? What?
Here we go. Oh, he lost his touch. Oh shit. I lost my touch. All right. Here we go. Here we go.
This is the one. This is the one coming up. All right. If I get, I get three in a row, then I,
I sub to a ghost pepper. And if I get, if I don't get three in a row, I eat 10,000 community subs.
I meant, I, whatever. I'm going to eat these subs now. That's the best tickets,
pound for pound. We got one more game to play. Tiny. Thanks for the 8,000 subs. Appreciate it.
Loose Cane. Thanks for 5,000 subs. Thank you guys. Seriously. Wow. A lot of fucking money.
My God. 5,000 subs. What? What the fuck? What are you doing? What are you thinking? What? What?
Hold on. How many subs was that? 50,000 community subs? Oh, oh, what? No way.
Who game? Whoa. 50,000. That's like 10 times. That's 10, 10 incomes. What the heck? All right.
Somebody actually just did it. What? Somebody just gave 50 subs. All right. That's enough. You did,
you just covered, you just covered everybody. Thank you. Raggle flaggle for the actually 50
community subs. Appreciate that. That's actually 50,000 community subs. Thank you for that. That's
a lot of subs. A lot of them. A lot of people dodged. Come on. What an asshole streamer. What?
That is actually a lot of money. Seriously. Thank you. Why am I an asshole? Because I was
doing the what? No, that happened before that. I, I, I cut that joke off right now. And I was
thanking the person for real for 50 and the five. I was, I was doing tuber. You guys know the drill.
He's doing a fake reaction, but it didn't even happen. Grimmy sensation. Thanks to the five
subs. What's seriously, uh, waggle waggle. What's your name? I want to get it right. You just gave
us a ton of money. Raggle flaggle. 50 community subs. Thank you. We need to get all the SpongeBob
cards. I know this one. Oh, this is, I love this too. Can I get two? Uh, I gotta get in the flow.
I have to get in the flow, get in the flow. I'm going to do like a hundred dollars in this.
Peculiar. Pangolin. Thanks for the five community subs. More subs. What? I got two. What? What
happened? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Back up. I got him. I got Mr. Potato. It's over
there. When did I get that? I didn't get, did I get all eight cards? I didn't see it. Did I get
another Pete? Holy shit. I don't even know what this is. Wait, what are you, what are you linking?
Link, link, link, link, link, link. Where are my teeth? Why did you take my teeth out of that?
I don't understand. All right. I got, I like, this one's fun.
Show the picture. I don't, I'm playing a game. Look at that eye. Those eyes are real, right? Link,
link, link. I know. I see it. You guys can't fool me anymore because now I just assume everything
is fake. Here, I'll put it on screen. Here. You want to see? Here you go. Here's what everybody
is laughing about in here. There it is. All right. Those two images have the same energy though.
Now what? No, I'm not putting that one on stream. I hate that picture. That picture scares the shit
out of me. I hate that one. I'll keep this one here, but that one is, I hate that picture more
than anything. That face you make when you get 50,000 subs. No, this is the face you make when
the shower is too cold when you get in. What? It was running for like two minutes. What the fuck?
There you go. No, I'm not putting, I'm not putting that image on screen. I'm sorry. I'm
going to give everybody nightmares because it's scaring me. I hate that picture. That is, I hate
it. I hate everything about that picture. It's the worst picture in the world. No, I refuse to put that
on stream. Nobody deserves to have to see that. How many tickets do I have? Free, free play.
I want to get the card on the right.
Get in there. Here they come. No, worst possible opportunity.
Come on, big push. Oh yeah. What was it? Why was I faking that reaction?
No, I'm not clicking any more of these. I'm trying to win a hoverboard. Get that card in there.
Show the fucking picture. Jesus. Jesus Christ. Why do I click this? There's so many in here.
Do you see how many photos are in here right now? No, I'm not going to link the Dunkin Donuts
gift card. We've seen that. It's funny. Okay. I'm serious right now. You, this is one of those
images that you're never going to unsee. You're going to look at this and it's going to,
you're not going to like this because I don't like it. And it kind of hurts my head. So just warning,
look away from the screen right now. If you actually don't want to never have this image
get out of your head for the rest of your life. All right. I did it. Oh, it's on my other monitor.
Get it off. You look like a bug. I got a bonus. I just want this card on the right and I can be
done and I can go scratch lottery tickets. What do you mean wrong one? No, that's just an edited
version. That was not, that one's not even as bad. That's like a typical scary image of like a scary
monster. That's not, show it then. Nah, I'm superstitious. I don't, I don't show pictures
of demons. Get in there. I haven't hit one. How am I this bad? Come on, give me that purple card.
That's all I want. Get it. Oh, yeah. Oh, spooky. That's spooky. Where's the 2000?
Did somebody steal my 2000 tickets? What is this bullshit? All right. I was at the hoverboard
30% of the way to the hoverboard. Let's go. You ready? You know what machine I'm going to use.
30%. Wait, does anybody know if I have to get them all here? Or can I get them from another,
I almost said restaurant. You don't? Okay. Well, I'm going to do this. I'm going to get like
10,000 more from this. Do this 10 times. What? I don't have any money. God damn it. All right.
We're going to go to the other arcade. I'm going to refresh my memory on the other games.
It's time for lottery tickets? No, not yet. Not till I have my hoverboard. Do I have to take the
bus again? Go play the bass game? Yeah, I could do that too. Wait, I want to mount and do. Oh,
sorry. Not add whatever it is a Danny DeVito or something. Oh, that's not either. Whatever.
What was last time you guys drank a Mountain Dew? They gross for some reason to be Mountain Dew.
Just regular Mountain Dew tastes like there's too much syrup in it. It's almost like you
melted a bunch of lemon lime popsicles and put it over ice and added a little bit of water. It's
something about it. Did they change the recipe? Why don't I drink diet? Because drinking diet
anything is not really that great for you. The shit that they put in diet soda is really not good
for you. They put like aspartame in that shit. You don't want to be drinking that. We've come
up with a chemical that tastes sort of like sugar in a way. It also can cause a bunch of diseases.
This is not in my car. That's fake news. Fake news at aspartame? A recent published review
of all available evidence including hundreds of studies concluded the studies provide no evidence
to support an association between aspartame and can't whatever. No, that's the fake news. Is it?
Did I just get fake newsed? Fake newsed? Did I just get fake news brackets fake newsed? Did I? No.
Did that happen to me? I can't trust anything. What happened? Aspartame is one of the most
controversial sweeteners in the world. It is claimed to cause health problems ranging from
headaches to cancer. On the other hand, food safety authorities and other mainstream sources
consider it to be safe. Who can you believe? The truth about aspartame. Is aspartame really dangerous?
Is aspartame a carcinogen? What are the long-term effects of aspartame? Dizziness, depression,
headaches, Alzheimer's. Does aspartame cause inflammation? It's too much info. Your body
cannot process artificial ingredients well, so substances like aspartame and
monosodium glutamate may trigger immune responses. That's too many angles. Too many people. Too many
studies. I have an anti-study. I have a study that's, but what about my study? What's going on?
It's too deep. Fake news. Fake news. MSG is safe. I know, but there's, I don't know. Here's the thing.
I've heard the story about MSG that one guy was mad at some restaurant and he made like a hit piece
on it, right? Something like that. I remember, right? Somebody was like, I got a headache.
It has to be from the MSG and not the pack of cigarettes I smoke every day. Of course not.
I don't know. It's too many things. There's too many things to know. Too many things to read about.
Long story short, eat a banana. Why is there a giant surge protector out here? It's for the robots.
Uh, what does it say? Islandville Power Authority authorized personnel only. Bananas actually cause
you to die, unfortunately. Guys, I guarantee you there's a study for every single substance that's
ever been invented of why you shouldn't be eating it or drinking it. Studies have shown that if you
eat too many bananas, it's going to cause you a potassium overdose. Okay. Is cheese the reason
why you got a bad score on your SATs? Click here. I have enough for a ticket, right? I remember
reading, uh, so everyone's seen that ad and there was a, there was a, somebody wrote an article about
this one particular ad. You guys have probably seen it. It's the doctors found this one food
that you should never eat. And the image is a bunch of tapeworms and worms in an intestinal track,
right? And this person wrote an article about how they clicked on it and they went searching
for this doctor. It was actually a pretty interesting read. I forget what the article was,
but go read it. It was pretty interesting. Is aspartame bat poop? I hate that ad. Advertisements
just make no sense. We live in such a strange world where somebody can just buy ad space
and just write just total dog shit and whatever. Doctors found this one thing that makes you live
over a hundred. It does? Yeah. Okay. What is it? Uh, subscribe to this magazine that has nothing
to do with anything that we ever told you. What? I want to know the fucking nutrient that makes me
live forever. Oh, well, um, well, I don't even know what you're talking about. What the fuck?
What is that even talking about? I can't believe you can just say anything. Ads work, unfortunately.
Wait, I remember this one. Wait, let's get out here. Out, out, out, out, out. I want to get out.
I want to go to the carnival again because there's other games here. What happened to the audio?
That was fast. Where is the audio? Oh, there it is. Hi. I'm here for your games. By the way.
Nevermind. No, I don't want rides. No, no rides. Get them out. I don't want them. I've already read
all these. I want to play the carnival games. There we go. A coin pusher. No, this is just for
prizes. This isn't for tickets. I'm leaving. Was that here before? Was it Ferris wheel here?
Yes. Oh, okay. I have to wait 20 minutes for the next bus. No, I don't. It comes immediately. Ads.
Ad companies are so fun. Not, not fun. Like funny. I mean, I didn't, I didn't finish my sentence
because this guy was driving erratically. Uh, they, first there's a pre-roll ad and
people have found a way. Ad companies have found a way to make it because, you know,
they know you're going to skip. So they just front load a ton of info in the first five seconds
and they've paid for 30 second ads, but they just front load everything in the first five seconds.
In the last 25 seconds don't even matter. It's just, they just added film time. Skippable ads
are cheaper. That's true. Still have to pay. Still going to pay for that 30 second slot. It
might be a little bit cheaper. Is it going to be Germacraft today? Uh, no. Where's the bus? Oh,
I have to call the bus. Whoops. We want ads. We already went over this. There's no reason
for you to play ads on this stream. And there's no reason for anyone to give a shit about ads
that's ever streams or ever maybe on YouTube because I say, I don't know. If I run an ad,
75% of you are not going to see it. Half of you have ad block. Half of you may be subbed.
If I run an ad like 20, I'm just making like 400 of you's lives miserable. I'm pretty close
to the edge there. Run it in stream. See, that's the way to get around it. But that's,
I, why would I do that? That's the quickest way to delete a bunch of people that are currently
watching. All right. Where are we going? Uh, Larry's arcade, right? I need a hundred thousand
tickets. Next Barry's pond. All right. I'm going to get off at Barry's pond. I have a lot of cows to
sell. Actually just play Raid Shadow Legends on stream. Do that. There are, there are no pros to
that. There's only cons. I can't think of more than one potential pro to that. That would be
a funny stream for maybe five minutes. And then I'm playing Raid Shadow Legends on stream. I
use other door. You played numbers go, Jesus Christ. What is this? What? Hold on. Somebody
just left a car. Who left a scratch ticket out here? I want eight bucks. Where's the other door?
Where's the use the other door? Oh, they're talking about the on the left. What the that's
all right. Let's get it in there. How much is one of these worth? Five dollars.
Oh, that's not worth it. I'll go get him. I'll go get him. I'll go get him. I'll go get him.
He's right here. He's right here. I'm sorry. I'll never do that again. I'm sorry. I'll never do it
again. Whose house is this? Run his head over. Holy shit. Wow, we found the psycho. It's me? No,
it's not. I didn't say that. Whose house is this? My house now. Is it? Is it my house? This goes
from being a fun arcade game to being really scary. Who's this dude outside shining a flashlight in
our windows? They're casing our house. Okay, I can't get in here. Where's my house? There's no door.
This game has slender energy. You're robbing a house for arcade money.
I don't even know where the hell I'm going. I guess we're going to check out that house.
I was supposed to go to the other arcade. Is it? Can I go in that house? Look at the map.
All right. Where am I? Bus stop. What is that? Home. What about my? Oh, shit. About my limo.
I really am a rich kid. Did he go over the edge? He just drove off the cliff.
Oh, well, sorry. Where's the basketball? I know you can play it. You have to. All right. I forgot.
Here's my achievements. Cool. Here's my fucking gamer fridge that I have behind me.
Why do I have a giant map of the town? That's weird. Sell your gamer fridge. Who the fuck is
this? Angel duck. This duck food? Come get your food. What the hell is going on? Oh, the duck eats?
How do you pet duck? Can you pet duck? I want to pet the duck. Force choke.
He's all right. Is he? Yes, he's fine. Mommy's little angel.
Ducks don't sleep. Wait. 105th annual swan goose show. Swim contest. Best feathers. Loudest quack.
Featuring special guest. 2028 grand champion. Gary from Islandville. 20 dollar autographs.
That's Gary. He's famous. Mainland arena. May 5th. 25 dollar general admission. He's famous.
Wow. You actually have a duck. That's so cool. All right. Don't overfeed Gary. I was going to
put food in the blender. I can't microwave his food or my food. Can I eat that food?
This is awesome. Pawn Gary. You can't. Why would I pawn Gary? We're just like hanging out together.
I'm not force choking Gary. We're walking around together.
You're hurting him. I'm not hurting him. Look, we're hanging out in bed. Oops. Sorry, Gary. Wait.
No. I want to hang out with you. This is my room. Cool. Can I use that? This definitely was not here
the last time I played. You have an entire house. I can't. Can I go to the bathroom?
That's a nice shower. Turn off the lights and go upstairs. Okay. Put Gary in toilet. Now,
that's something I'm not going to do. I need to turn the lights off. Was the lights switched
from here? It should be right here. What happened to it? Oh, hey. Excuse me. Excuse me. You're
blocking the way. Go up or down. Come on, Gary. Where's the light? There's no lights. Oh, here we
go. Ooh, Gary. Gary. Fuck. All right. Bye, Gary. It was fun hanging out with you. That's kind of
a cool thing. You have a house. You missed a room. Double D. What? Double D. Where? Put Gary in your
inventory. I can't put Gary in my inventory. He doesn't go in there. In the bathroom. What do
you mean? How could there be another room in the bathroom? Don't hit Gary with the flashlight.
Gary, what are you doing in here? What do you want? Hi. Yes. Yes. Move. We need to give you a bath.
How do you give a duck a bath if they're in your... Give them a bath. No, ducks bathe themselves,
guys. Yeah, ducks bathe themselves. They bathe themselves. You don't wash a duck. You don't like,
oh, I put you in a bathtub with soap and water. No, no, no. A duck just goes to water and they
smash their face into it and roll and they throw their head up in the air. I've seen it. Where's
this other room you're talking about? They put their head underwater. They swish their face around
and they put their face in the air and they go... They go like this. You never seen a duck bathe
before? Here's the duck's arm, right? This is the duck's arm. No, this is the duck's face. Yes. Hi.
How are you? Good to see you. This is the duck's face. They go under. Let's say that this line
in here is the water level. Yes, and we're talking about you. Yes. When they go under...
Okay, he's funny. When they go under, they... Yeah, go ahead and do it. When they go under,
they go boom, under the water, up and they go... They drink the water on their heads. They go...
They go... Very good job. That's exactly what they do. Yes, you're... Oh, yes, you're...
Good. Okay. Yes, you just wanted to kiss me. Okay, good. I see. Yeah, he's doing very good.
Where's the door that you're talking about? Do I not even have cable?
Wait, are you... We watch... Oh, we watch TV together? There's nothing on TV, Gary. It's his
favorite show. Hey, what? Did he just try to turn it back on? It's back... Gary, it's back on.
Your favorite show is back on. White screen. Don't you like it? Yes, I love this show. Hey,
I was... I was watching that. Gary, to the left of the fridge. Oh, there is another door here.
You can't go in this door. Thanks for the bait. All right, I gotta go win more tickets before...
I need 30... I need 70,000 more tickets. I can call my limo driver, right? Why would I take the
bus? Who are these people? Wait, did I just get... Did I just get like a luxury Uber? Shared luxury
Uber or something? Happy birthday. Whose birthday is this? They... They partied themselves out of
existence. The fuck up. Birthday sucks. All right, I don't... I don't want... I don't want it. I don't
want it. I don't do it. I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it.
Oh, I forgot. I remember these. Some of these are new. Some of these are new.
What is this? This is new. This is letters. Some of these are new. Oh, I remember this sand game.
This sand game is fun. What happened? Oh, you can't touch the middle. You can't touch the middle. I
remember. This one's fun. I think... I remember I tried to win this, but it's almost impossible to
win. Did I actually just try to rage quit the game? No. No, no, no. I need 70,000 more tickets.
This is not... Not efficient. Get out. Dunco? New. Dunco. Wait, have I done this one? Is this one new?
No, I remember this one. Yeah, I've done this one. Here's some Dunco donuts. Because you're
a rabbit. I'm sorry. What's the over-under on that? Is that like meme dead at this point,
and maybe everybody hates it, or people still think it's funny? I'm not sure yet. Oh, they got
stuck. 1,000 tickets and a free prize? What's the free prize? I don't remember there being a free
prize. We'll have to check that out. I think it's the cards, right? Bonus. Oh. All right, we've got
to get these three. We've got to get three tickets. There we go. Bang, bang. What is it? I need all
the cards. I've got to get them all. What does it say? What do I have? Okay, I need red and blue.
Red and blue, and then I'm done. Give me a red spawn. You get a Dunco mascot suit?
No, you get the plush. That's pretty cool. Oh, that's all right. It's going to put these down,
and I'm going to get the blue card. Give us Dizzy Bird? I'll do Dizzy Bird in a minute.
Get it for Gary. I will. We're going to do this in another time. We're going to do...
Okay, good. This should be enough to get the red card as well. I need a black card. Oh,
shit. I need more than that. Anything but the bird game. But I already beat the bird game,
so it doesn't matter. Go to the right... I know, I know, I know, I know. I was trying to get the
blue card. Oh. He knows he can't do it again. Yeah, I know I can't do it again. That's okay.
It's like what we talked about before. Like Jump King, right? Oh, do the Jump King DLC.
It's really hard, and it's crazy, and you could like it. No, I know I'm not going to do that
ever again. I've seen streams and streamers and clips of people on those DLC levels,
and I know what I'm capable of. It's not that. It's not that. You spoiled it.
Look at this card. It's right here. How can I not get the one all the way to the left?
I got the dunko card. It took XQC 60 hours to beat the game. Yeah. Oh, I can feel...
I can feel that pain. I just can. That's a lot of time. That's a lot. Can I get another push,
please? All right, we get a black card and we need a red one. Jeremy, can I have some tokens? No.
Get your run. Just kidding. Here's 50. Go play Dunky, whatever a thing is, as long as you want.
Okay, we need the red card. Spawn a red card so I can stop playing this, please.
Spawn a truck? I don't think those are in this game. Give me another card. There's a red card
over there, but it's not going to count. Oh, I got it. All right, card. That's not bad.
I don't need a green one. I need a red one. Spawn another one. Let's go. Card. Card. Left machine
is a red card. Yeah, but it only counts for the machine it's currently on. I need one red. Gotta
just get this thing to spin. Spin. Bonus. Oh, yeah. Super bonus. Is it seven free spins times two?
10 free spins times two. We need 20 times three. I'll take that. That's not horrible.
That's better. That's much better. No. No! This is time. Holy shit, this is times two, guys.
This shit's times three times three. I imagined that was times three. I want red.
Jeremy, please. Jeremy, I'll click it in like an hour. Land on bonus again.
Damn it. Fuck. I need a red card. Oh, my God. I'm seeing Omega Lulz. So let me go ahead and click
it. Is this the one you wanted me to click on? There's like three links in here. It's all the
different TV channels. All right, I see it. Okay, cool. You know, when you see Omega Lulz in your
chat, you have to react. Daily News 10. Find out what wrong with these five foods you eat every day.
Worms. Elephant roars like a dinosaur. Crisp Pratt accidentally gives away
travel trivia prize? What are, what is this? That's Crisp. He's trying to react to them.
I don't know how you guys do this shit so quickly. Yeah, I saw the McChicken one.
The best fast food sandwich. I don't even know what these images are. There's too many of these.
Like 20 minutes has gone by and you got this. There's like seven new photoshops in the chat.
I can't keep up. The Junior Chicken is better. Oh, excuse me. No, it's not.
The best fast food. I'm trying to move with my mouse. The McChicken from McDonald's. Just plain.
Just the way it comes. Just McChicken with lettuce, a little bit of mayo.
It's the best. Just when you're hungry, you can eat like six of them.
And look, I'm not, this is, I'm not counting like, Oh, what about Chick-fil-A? What about Popeyes?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not having that fight. Everybody knows that Chick-fil-A is better
than everything. Like I know that. I, I know that. Okay. I already know, but I can't, you don't eat,
I can't eat, you can't eat Chick-fil-A every day. You can eat McDonald's every day. Why would you
want to do that? But you, that's like the worst thing I've said. That's a terrible statement.
You don't want to eat McDonald's every day. You, you technically can. What I mean by that is,
this is what I mean. Chick-fil-A is sort of, it's a treat in quotes because it's not everywhere.
There's a McDonald's every one mile. Some places across the country have maybe one Chick-fil-A in
50 miles. So it's, yes, you, you, what are you going to drive to Chick-fil-A fucking 50 miles
every day? That's what I meant by that statement. Good thing I have clarified that. Red card. Red
card please. Just eat McDonald's every day. Chicken's unimpressive. Yeah, but it's, it's easy.
Go left. No, I need to get to zero. All right. Okay. I gotta, I have to move on. I can't do this
all day. I have to move on. Where are my tickets? All right. Here we go. Good, good, good, good,
good, good. Yes. Fuck you. No, don't do five. All right. We're at a good spot.
Give me a shitload and give me a red card so I can get out of here. Red. It's not red. Yellow.
Give me a red card. That's a yellow card. How many times am I going to get yellow and blue?
Red. Oh my God. I just want the red. This is how they keep you here. Bonus. Oh fucking yeah.
Yes. Yup. All right. 20.
All right. We got 11. Don't want it. There's no way there's a seven this close. There it is.
Do I know for a fact that the cards don't carry over? No. I mean, there's three different machines
here that have three different numbers on them right now. I assume it has to be like that.
Red, red, red, red, red, red, red. Yeah. Guys, we did it. You and I, we did it.
And there's two. I can get two ducks. Make it three. Put a third one down here. Too good to be true.
Too good to be true. Well, let's get it. We get Gary two. That's actually not an untrue statement.
Bonus. All right. Here comes the first duck. We're going to get two or three ducks.
All right. Come on. Got it. Thousand tickets and a free prize. Where is it?
Wait, I already got one? This would be number three.
Where do I get the free prize from? Is it? What happened to the cards? Oh, they reset. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. All right. We don't even. Hold on. This is important. Here's how we
wait one second. Because, uh, red, green, black. Okay. Hold on. Just, I'm just going to see what
happens. If a yellow card drops, then I'm going to wait. There's yellow and blue over here.
Well, first, let me go see, make sure I can even get this prize. I'm owed two. I'm technically,
I'm owed two prizes. Yellow and blue is right there. Let's see if you guys are right. See if
it carries over. Might be the final push. Let me get my prize. He's a dunko addict, just like grandma.
Holy shit. That's a lot of tickets. A lot of tickets. A lot of tickets. Let's test it. No,
they all reset. They reset. Where's my free prizes? Where are they? Oh shit. All right. I've got,
how many tickets do I got now? 37,000. Almost there. We're at 37%. All right. I'm going to do
this one. I'm going to try this one again. I like this one. This one's fun. As long as you pay
attention. All right. I'm trying to go too quick. Slow it down. The trick to this game is you let
it bounce once and then you do it on the second return. If you wait longer than that, you're not
going to get it because your brain can't keep up with it. You can only keep up with one turn.
It speeds up at that last two. Is this a rerun? No, it's not a rerun. I just wanted to come back
here. I have to, I'm just trying to get some, ah, it's not a rerun. There's a new arcade that
we went to. 15 new games. I'm just checking out some of the old ones, some of the new stuff that
they put in. They put some new stuff in. I'm just checking it out. If there's some stuff in here
that's new, there's, I'm just checking it out. And you play some old stuff to just when you're
checking something out, he's re, I'm re-recording. Why did I think that was going to be too,
what the fuck am I doing? This is what, that nerd neck. How do I get out of this? Oh, it's C.
Hold on. What? Oh, I remember this one. This one's fun. Here we go. Ready? You are slow. I got it.
Oh, oh, oh, what's happening? My graphics card's dying. My graphics card's dying. This, this dream
might turn off. Are you guys seeing that? Are you guys seeing that? Green artifacts are all over
my screen. No, you guys, it's not pulling it. Uh-oh. Oh shit. It's only this game that's doing it.
Fuck, yeah. Dead. It's like, the graphics card's fucking with me. Is it actually? Oh, it is my,
okay. Uh, he's in the matrix. I know what it is. I fix it. I fix it. I fix it. Quick, eat the red
pill. No, but the blue one's probably blueberry. Hold on. I actually have to, my monitor just turned
off. Oh, my cord was loose. It's okay. I fixed it. We're good to go. My monitor's just fucking
turned off. Come on. What are you doing? Stop. Why is my monitor doing this? Does my cable suck?
I'll do it. Oh, stop it. Ha ha. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. What are you talking about?
I gotta pee. I'm gonna take this again. Where are the balls going, Jerma? Where are the balls going?
I don't know. What's more efficient, this or the spinny jackpot thing? What do you think?
I gotta pee. Go to the bathroom now. No. All right, let's go. Streamer shits himself on stream.
I don't have to shit. I'm not gonna, I don't, I'm not gonna disappear for like 30 minutes.
Who shits for 30 minutes? I don't even start with this nonsense. It really depends.
How much time do I have? Yeah, it depends on how much time I have. Do I have,
how many, how many hours do I have before I have to do something? It's in. I wish I could just put
in like 10 credits worth. You know, this one's not even winnable unless the person who,
you know, these machines have to take in $1,000 sometimes before they do anything.
There'll be a PlayStation 4 up there or a Nintendo DS. How much is a Nintendo DS?
Like what? 200? How much is 3DS? Like 150? 200 bucks? All right, so let's say it's $200.
For the Nintendo DS to be able to be won, like it depends on who owns the machine,
but for the most part it's usually at least two or three times the amount of money has to come in.
So these prizes on the top row that's a Nintendo DS, wow, it's $2 a dollar to play this.
600 bucks has to come in sometimes for this to happen and you also have to win. You also have
to win the actual game of skill once they allow you to be able to win. It's not RNG. No,
play my favorite game here. Inside of Secrets. That's illegal. You know what's funny? Why is
that legal? It's not actually a game of skill if you put, is that supposed to be legal? Why is
that legal? It's not technically gambling. Not even close, not even close, not even close.
I love this game. Hey, it's my first stream here. You're top 10 underrated streamers. Oh, cool.
Welcome. You missed some of that. What? Too much. Oh, I have to get green once. I love green.
Did I get green? I got, how did I get green? What? I wasn't even looking. Why would it give
me a bonus? Jeremy, you've been playing the chicken game since July. Please stop.
I did it. Yeah, he said it. I've seen the video. You know how hard it is to avoid some of these
videos? Hey, click this link. What is this? It's called, okay, cool. I don't want to watch this
right now. I'm busy. Imagine getting that message for six straight years. You have to apologize for
that. Wait, what? Wait, why? Why? I have to apologize? I have to apologize.
We need a public apology. All right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. What do you want from me?
Well, I can do an impression. I can do a shitty impression of Larry David, but I can't do like,
oh yeah. I can't say that. I'm like, apologize again. I'm not even, I don't even understand.
I was, I was like mocking the meme and now I have to apologize for mocking the meme.
No, no, no apology. Nope. Not gonna happen. No, I'm going, I'm buried. I'm getting buried with this
one. I'm getting buried. They're going to be burying me in like another 75 years. And the
elves impersonator that I've hired to do the talk at the end of your life thing, you're going to be
like, oh well it seems that this boy, I'm not apologizing for it. I'm not apologizing for
saying it. I'm not apologizing. I'm not apologizing for saying I, oh, you said the meme thing. No,
no apologies from here. I'm going to sleep with it. Apologize for what? I, if you weren't,
if you weren't here like two minutes ago, somebody said ayaya in the chat and I did like a,
like a look, it's the, it's the thing, it's the video and people freaked out and now they demanded
apology. Apologize. I actually uploaded a video to my main channel and it opens up with me with like
music playing like guys. I just want to say a couple things. I'm, first of all, it's a hard
video to make. I'm really sorry. I said ayaya. I did like a thing where I pretended to be the
video for like, like at most six seconds and everybody tried to burn my house down and they
screamed at me and they called me a bunch of fucking names and idiot and stupid and they,
and they, they, they're screaming at me, but I'm the one that has to apologize now.
So, uh, here you go. Uh, I guess I'm, I guess if you're bad, if you're mad about that, then
sorry to hear that. It's an emoticon. The passive aggressive apology, the passive aggressive
non-apology. Apologize now. Apologize. All right. I have to get the fuck out of this
before I put on the video and sing to it at the same time, just to punish you.
Oh, now everybody wants me to do that. I'll do it. Do it. Do it. Oh, I'll do that. Do it. No,
do that. Do that. Do it. Do it. These are the people that just demanded an apology because
I said the word out loud. Unbelievable. Pick a side guys. It was an empty threat. I'm doing
this one more time and I'm moving on. Oh, it's glitched up there. All right. Goodbye. Please
tickets. Do it or you're not going to get any gifted subs ever again. Enable the, I enable
that emote for punishment. No, no, I'm not going to enable an emote. What was I thinking saying
that out loud? I of course saying the word, saying the A-Y-A-Y-A-Y-A out loud to a large
amount of people in this chat apparently is as if I turned on the webcam and was just naked
going like, yeah, look at this. Wait, look at me. What? Compact empty threats. I got it.
It's worse than that. It's not. All right. That's it. That's it. I can't, I've already beaten this
once. I don't have to beat it again. This actually is a rerun stream. If I stay here,
play the video. I'm not playing the video. No, no. Okay. Just delete the last five minutes.
Just pretend the last five minutes on stream didn't happen. You know what I mean? Like we can
just get over that. That the last five, the last five minutes did not happen. You know what I'm
saying? The last five minutes didn't happen. The most polarizing moment. All right. 40,000 tickets.
I almost just did it. I almost just went, I almost just went, I almost did it again.
Oh my God. Can you believe that Trevor lied about what? Give me those headphones. Give me
those headphones. All right. I'm good. I did it. Out, out, out. It was fucking easy. All right.
Let's go to Bass. Pull it. And we're going back to the other casino.
Do it. Oh, you got yourself 10 tickets. What is cuckoo clock? I've never seen cuckoo clock.
Let's do cuckoo clock. This shit is impossible. I don't know why people even play this.
There's no reason to play this. Yeah, I said this last time. Get me out of this. What a dumb game.
And for some reason, also, every arcade now, there's got to be some weird deal with this company.
Whoever manufactures this shit, because it's one of the only games at most arcades with this
10 of them in a row. 10 of them. And there's always people playing them. Every machine is
loaded with people waiting in line. Are they paid actors? And they're like, it's like six bucks to
play this. So they're just playing for free. And then you go, oh, I think I want to do that. And
they go, oh, I guess you're gonna have a turn. I almost won a thousand. And you spend 30 bucks
here and then you leave and they made 30 dollars. All right, let's go. Cash out. 40,234 tickets.
Let's go back to the other arcade and have some fun. But first, let's listen to the fun song.
Remember the funny song? Here we go. It's time for the funny song. Where's the funny song?
Never mind. I can't. No. All right, let's go. Limo driver, please take me to the other
casino, please. Uh huh. Let's go to the UFO. Just scream at us already. Jesus, I've been waiting
for hours. What? Scream at us? Why am I screaming at you? I didn't even play this one. Are you
serious? I didn't play the clock tower. What does this one do? Ball drops. Oh, it's this thing. You
have to. Damn it. All right. 500. I hate this thing too. Why is it always the worst ones that
take up the most amount of space? This is a small apartment. You could live in the spot that this
thing takes up in the casino, in the arcade. Why does it have to take this much time? I mean,
this much space. I got to at least win the 500. I wasn't even ready. That's not fair.
That's unfair. Why is everybody doing question marks? What? You could have had 500. I mean,
it's hard to control. This one's this one. This one's a waste. I could get so much more tickets
playing the spaceship or anything. All right. Hold on. Two balls. There we go. I have infinite
money though. No, I don't. I'm empty. That should be a thousand. Oh, why? I need money.
All right. I gotta pee. I forgot to pee. Let's pee first. I'll be right back. One of these days
might be funny if I'm like, oh, I'm going to go take a break. And it's been like three,
four hours on stream. I go take a break. I'm just going to go pee. And then I come back
and it's a new video feed. And it's just me IRL like going through the McDonald's drive-through.
And I come back and we just go back to what we were doing. Maybe you'll see that someday.
All right. Back to it. 40,000 tickets. I need a hundred. We know how to get that. We know how
to get that. Oh, no money. Solve that real quick. No, wait. That's not money. That's tickets. Where's
the it's where is it? Take over here. Don't even eat the food. Why would I not eat the food?
He's becoming delirious. Now check this out. We're going to get the other 60,000 tickets real soon.
Friendship ended with German. Now Drew Crew is my best friend. I'm part of that crew. Yes,
this is just a money printing machine. From what I understand, when this game actually releases,
when it truly launches and it's actually in 1.0, there's going to be another game mode called
survival where you cannot just print money. You need to do jobs and stuff. I think they really
want it to be an interesting, weird survival game from what I understand. All right, let's do it.
Here we go. Kids gambling survival. Hey, well, you gotta hand it to them. No one's ever done that
before. No one's ever made a kids gambling game. Actually, I have. Oh yes, they have like every
game that's come out. It's been like in the last five years. It's been like a gambling game
just specifically to make kids gamble. What am I talking about? It's all of them like you.
But they're not survival gambling games. Oh, you're right. This one is how you get the tickets.
I'll be there in less than 20 minutes. All right, start counting now. I know people are going to be
like, dude, you're going to be here for 10 straight minutes. Yes, at least. Let me see. Three hours and
37 minutes at three hours and 47 minutes. We'll see where we are. This machine is going to get
nerfed. It probably is. It probably is. This is how you can get tickets quick here. It's 500 every
potentially if you can really time this correctly, 500 tickets every three seconds.
These machines are easy in real life. These machines are rigged in real life.
Evacuate the building. Evacuate. Evacuate this one too many times. This machine is smoking and
setting off the fire alarm. Sparkle Kid? I love Sparkle Kid. Sparkle Kid's awesome.
Yeah, even a robot can't win these. Yeah, because it'll make it move one light forward or one light
backward regardless if you hit it or not. They've tested this with programs.
No, this is not balanced. I spent three hours grinding Dizzy Bird for payout. That wasn't half
of this. Sorry, you gotta get with the meta. At what point do you think somebody that worked
at this arcade would come over here and be like, what's going on over there? What do you think?
They would just not even give a shit. Who cares? And just like go back to what they were doing.
Oh no, I'm becoming more ticket than man. Are you getting paid to stop them? Are you getting
paid to work here? I'm out of money. Holy shit. All right, this is a lot. Let's see.
That wasn't even 10 minutes. That was what? Four minutes? That's 8,000 tickets in four minutes.
Yep, I'm gonna do the money machine like five times in a row. Move on from this lame ass place.
It's time for the Drew to solve the case. I appreciate the effort on that. Go-karts or
Riot? I will. I'm gonna bring my hoverboard onto the go-kart track. They won't be able to catch me.
They'll try. Let's do it. If you hold down a while while playing it, it'll automatically
start another one so you can get them faster. If you hold down? What? Hold down A.
Oh my god. Oh, oh, the cops are outside. Oh my Jesus. This game is a disgrace.
Drew with your face. What? I didn't read that right. I haven't gotten it in like five seconds.
Oh, that was lame. Stay at this cool arcade. Buy a hoverboard after you are paid.
That was... Come on. I haven't got one in like five. Come on. It's washed up. No, I'm not. No,
I'm not. Don't say that. Two, three, four. Out of money. I want to do this in real life.
Am I allowed to stream in an arcade? Probably not unless I get permission.
How many was that? And we're not even at 10 minutes. What'd I tell you? What was that?
8,000 first one. 6,500 for the next one. That's 14. Almost 15,000 tickets in 10 minutes.
Easy. I'm gonna do this twice in a row so I don't have to leave the machine.
Yes, you can. Oh, that's cool. All right. Can you actually do that? What's Icelandic for
degenerate gambler? I don't know. I don't know what it is. What is it? Get back in there.
This game doesn't take our fancy. It's time to party with Nancy. Play it three more times.
I'll stop at 200 bucks. Guys, I got like 10 years of streaming to play Nancy Drew.
And that's how long it's gonna take. He thinks he has 10 years. I got plenty of time. All right,
one more time and then I'm gonna sit there for like at least 10 to 15 straight minutes. He's
addicted. Yeah, I'm addicted to getting cool shit. I want to get the hoverboard. Once I get the
hoverboard then everything's fine. A raid just came in. A huge raid from Boxbox. Boxbox. Hello
again. Welcome, everybody. Thanks a lot, Boxbox. I'm playing arcade games right now. Boxbox,
I gotta raid you. When do you stream? Every day? Right now? Well, you can't be streaming
right now. But hey, welcome, everybody. Thanks a lot, Boxbox. Seriously, that's a lot of people.
Unfortunately, you came to a stream where the person is just doing this.
I'm addicted. I'm already addicted. So there's not, I can't say much besides this.
There it is. That's for Boxbox and his raid. What's that? You want two jackpots?
You want two jackpots? Oh yeah, you'll take two jackpots. Sure thing. How about three jackpots?
You want three? I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. You're in follower only mode. Oh
shit, turn it off. Turn off follower only for like 10 minutes. That's two jackpots in a row.
Here comes three in a row for you guys. There it is. All right, holding it down is like,
it's crashing the game. It's too late. Just turn off, you can turn it off. Turn off follower only
for like 30 minutes. That's too long. I got it all. He's playing elf bowling later. Stick around,
raiders. Imagine falling asleep. What? They left for another Drew Crews streamer.
Is my money going up? How do I have? Come on, I'm washed up. I've got to, I can't just suck like
this. I have to do, we just had a huge raid coming. Come on. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. This is not good.
I actually did lose it. No, I'm washed up. Oh, I'm really washed up. I might as well quit.
Never quit. Don't ever quit. Ski ball, ski ball, ski ball. I'll do some ski ball after I spend
200 on this. That's three in a row. Yeah, what's the most I've ever had? Five in a row. Wish me
a Merry Christmas. Hey, have a Merry Christmas. Hope you have a good one. Hope you get everything
you want. Hope Santa doesn't get stuck in your chimney and suffocate because he can't get out
and he can't reach his cell phone. Because how would you be able to reach your cell phone if
you got stuck in a chimney? You can't reach down in your pockets. You would just suffocate in the
chimney. I really hope that doesn't happen to Santa at your house. Because then Santa's lawyers
might come and find you and they might be like, well, your chimney was not at regulation. Chimney
is about 15% too small. And you'd be like, I don't know. I mean, you'd lose everything.
I'm speaking of suffocating.
Again. Help me. I can't reach my cell phone. I can't reach my cell phone.
No, no. Yeah.
I can just do it by feeling. I can close my eyes and do it. Use the force.
Don't make me put it on and get sued. I'm putting it on. Who cares? Come on. I can do it.
I can't do it. Come on. Come on. Just think of, just think of Uncle Ben. Wait, that's Spider-Man.
Yes. German confirmed force sensitive. You think so? Really? I think I am. Let me try. Let's see.
What the fuck, dude? What the fuck is going on? I think I should go to the academy.
First joke. Everybody hated that. Why? Why? What? Spoilers, but you can have force powers.
Oh, the game crashed. Why? Why was that the worst joke ever? Was it?
To apologize. Sorry again, guys, for a force. The Star Wars bed.
I actually can't see. I can play. Why can I play like this? What? I turned into a caterpillar.
Oh my God. My chest hurts. I have to win one. Oh, it fell off. Okay. Do I have no money?
Oh, it actually moved me. Hey ACDC Freak, thanks for the 5 community subs. Hold F.
Oh no, those are out of reach. Every last drop. He's going to force, he's force grabbing them.
14,000 tickets. Holy shit. 70% of the way there, boys and girls. All right, now I'll ride the
go-karts. No, no, no, no. The box box wanted me to do skee-ball. I'll do that. It's been like,
it's been like, it's been like 30 minutes. Box box, are you still here? This one's for you.
Right in the 100. Come on. Box box left an hour ago. Whoa, what was that? Why does that sound like
I smashed a window? Riven players don't deserve. What? I don't know what that is. What's a Riven
player? Mist Riven is a good game. Oh, quick play sorting algorithms. Oh, hey, by the way,
okay. Box box viewers, those of you that are still here, I want to ask a question because my viewers,
whoa, they fucking yelled at me and called me an asshole and an idiot for this. Listen to me.
How many times have you, as a box box viewer, right? As somebody that's maybe not,
never been here before, how many of you have accidentally in skee-ball or in throw the ball
that the thing knocked his head down? How many times have you thrown a little too hard and it's
come all the way back and hit you in the chest or something? Apparently, I'm a psycho. How many
times have you ever done something like this? Like ready? Like, oh shit, I fucked it up and
it's coming back. That happening to me makes me apparently a serial killer. You killed God yesterday.
Oh, sorting algorithms. All right, get me out of here, get me out, get me out. Let's go back to my,
let's go back to my, no, go-karts, go-karts. I'm gonna try to win go-karts. That's normal to be a,
yeah, I know, that's what I'm saying. All right, what do we got? Session one, 221, gonna be 221.
All right, let's go. Ready? See if I can beat 221. Do I have to pay for this? No, I do. Let's make it
clean. I have to get in first place. Were these people on the track before I got here though?
That's not fair. They had a head start. Session six. Get out of the way. Who threw this can over here?
Oh, yeah, I did. I don't think you can even get in first place. I don't understand this.
You know what I'm saying? There's no drivers to be in a position above me.
This is pretty good. It's a pretty good time. No major screw-ups. Whoa, wait, how did I get
positioned? Oh shit, I'm in fourth place. Third place, let's go. Out of my way. I'm a 34-year-old
man. I need to break an 11-year-old's go-kart record. Out of my way. I don't know how you
do it much better than this. Third place, how? I can still get third place. Experiences.
What about my experience? Go free camp. I have to hit W, A, S, and D.
I don't understand. Why are there so many green bean characters? I don't get it.
Why am I the only human? I can't turn the mouse. He's using his feet to drive.
He's actually using feet to drive. Why can I not move my...
I was in position number four. Wait a minute, that's a cheat. Can I... Wait a minute. Hold on,
preset the whole thing. I can cheat. If I go that way and then come... I can drive over this and
just... Okay, let's try it. It's not positioning, it's just lap time. Yeah, so who cares? Let's go.
What if I... Wait, hold on. What if I do this? How smart is the game? Smart. Can't tech that one.
Yeah, I'm stuck. All right, I'm not... I'm not gonna win that one. Who cares?
Sorting algorithm. Here it comes.
Um, how many club remixes of that song do you think exist?
Too many. I would... I would agree with you. Oh, shit, here we go again.
Don't worry, I'll get him back. Watch. No, don't come back, because they're on the way out there
like I'm thinking about clicking the X and then this guy just did fucking three jackpots.
I didn't do three. Jeremy, you dropped 3,000 subs.
Whoops. You lost three. Well, I... I gained like 30,000 subs today, right?
That's... Okay, that's fine. All right, 73,000. 73%. All right, what can I play that won't...
What if I turn the volume down and we just... And I do that and just win?
What do you think? Dipman just gave 5,000 bits. Thank you, Dipman. 50 bucks right now. Bang.
Coming in hot. And Dipman says, I got pulled over for speeding today and the officer let me off
with a warning because he was in the Christmas spirit. Thought I'd pay it forward. Merry Christmas
and thanks for five years of laughs. Slow down. First of all, slow down. You're not gonna go that
fast. Second of all, thanks for the 5,000 bits, the $50. Yeah, it's the spirit of feeling good,
spirit of giving. You know what I mean? Spirit of giving and receiving because I really hope that
under the tree come the 25th that I get another couple of mugs for my heated mug set. Just
throwing it out there for if anybody that might be listening. A duck. I would actually love a duck
pet. No, but seriously though, Dipman, that's a lot of money. Thank you. That's a huge amount of
money and just slow down. You're not gonna go that fast. Why do I have all this gas? Why do I have
10 gas? Here's what we're gonna do. I'm gonna go in the money machine twice and I'm gonna get 25,000
tickets and then I'm... Look, we'll put on like Yoshi's Story OST or something. Just hang out.
Go home and bring Harry. You could go for a DeVito Dew right now. I'll get one.
I'll do the coin pusher game again. I will. I will get my last 500 tickets from the coin pusher.
Bye, Jerma. I'm gonna go watch Star Wars. Well, as somebody that's force sensitive,
then I suggest that's cool, you know? What is worst Jedi ever? Let me see. What the
fuck is going on? I think I should go to the academy.
This just popped up on my monitor because I closed the tab. Here. Oh, oh, okay. I turn this off.
Turn this off. I don't want to listen to that anymore. I don't know. Put on fucking Chrono
Trigger. Put on Trigger OST and just play it. Okay, sounds good. All right, turn this off.
What? Why is it still going? Why is it doing this?
Mute. There we go. Now I can't do it without the siren. I can't do it without the siren.
There's no sense of urgency. 73,000? What do I need? A lot more. Are you doing it with the song?
Am I? I don't mean to be doing that. Do a text to speech. No, I'm not doing text to speech. What
am I trying to get with the tickets? I'm trying to get a hoverboard. Damn it. Can you tell me a
joke? If you do more channel points, maybe you can. Let's see if you guys can figure out my
favorite song is. What's my favorite song on the entire Chrono Trigger OST? What is it? Anybody
know? Frog is all right. Frog is okay. It's not Frog. Joke or riot? No, they were going to say
a joke. They were going to tell a joke. Not me. We're waiting for them to tell the joke. They said,
do you want to hear a joke? It was in channel points. Please play Chrono Trigger. It's one of
the best games ever made, so I wouldn't know. It's the epoch theme. Epoch. Epoch. Whatever it is.
Don't crash. That's the best one. Nah, I picked these up. It's gonna crash. When are you gonna
do a Chrono Trigger stream? I'd probably treat that the same way I did Mario RPG, which is
a day that I feel like being nostalgia. I'll beat it. It's another game that I've probably beaten
at least five to ten times at least. Oh, it's starting to really hang.
Any good RPG recommendations, chat? I just beat Divinity 2. Chrono Trigger. Yeah, I haven't saved
the game once all night. Holy shit, this is bad. Excuse me. Knock, knock. Who's there? Who, who,
who? Who let the owl in? That was pretty good. 83,000. I gotta save the game. Acknowledge me,
I grinded for these points. Hey, what's up? All right, everyone can breathe.
Play the epoch theme. It'll show up. You are manually breathing now. That doesn't work,
it only works in Jump King when I'm aware of every single thing I'm doing.
Did they add new things to the game? Yes, this area that I'm in right now is a brand new area
as of a week or two ago. 15 new games, 100,000 tickets for a hoverboard, and you get a house now
and a duck. Be cool. I don't like this one. This one's sad. Where is it? Where's the epoch? Battle
theme? Pretty good. Where's the epoch? Come on, where's the epoch? The epoch's the best. Oh,
that one's good too. What the hell is it? It's got, it's called like the wings of time or something,
right? Wings across time. There it is. Let's go. This is the best song. This is like Actraiser,
is it? Dev in chat? Really? No, why do I believe that? Dev ain't here. Hey, it's me. The thing is
that's like the boy who cried wolf because remember when I played Dusk and everyone was like,
dude, Dev, Dev in chat. And I'm like, okay. Yeah, whatever. That was real. And then started tweeting.
Remember like they started tweeting that I was bad at the game and stuff.
You are bad at the game. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm gonna have to defend myself here.
If you play a game like Dusk on these, on the, they arguably the actual hardest difficulty in
the game and you beat it, what do you want me to do? Close my eyes and do it? Back to the music.
We're close. Just throwing chairs at us. Eat a ghost pepper. Oh, by the way, I also figured out
after the fact that the boots was just a joke. You guys, they don't do anything. So yeah,
I'm glad we had a fight over that for like an hour and a half straight.
Shit. Okay. Come on. I have to, this has got to be the one. All right. I promise. I won't play
this one again. I promise. I promise. I won't play this one again. I promise.
We will finish the rest with games that you guys want me to play. Oh, it's starting to take over.
Promise me you'll get the boots. Maybe another playthrough years from now. That's three in a
row. All right. I'm going to, I'm definitely close. I gotta go. I have two more chances.
All right. That's good. I'm happy now. Last chance. Get it. Sorry. All right.
I'm not playing this one ever again. All right. It's time. We can get rid of the OST.
That was just to pass a little bit of time while I got 10, you know, 15,000 points.
I don't think these sliders do anything. Is he, well, I can end it on dizzy bird.
Do the coin pusher. We'll do coin pusher. All right. I'm at 92,000. I need
Jeff's about seven and a half thousand more. Good. I want to try this one again,
but I need money. I want to try that one again. I thought that was a music playing.
Am I? I thought I, I thought I auto-played a video that Dev is actually here.
Dev Oatid is actually Dev. Dev Oatid. What's up? We really like your game. It's great.
That is awesome. I rarely get to watch anymore. Keep adding cool stuff. You, I know,
I know you've already got three arcades. That's so, it's too addicting and too much fun.
You know what I mean? Which, which again, what was the coin pusher game that I didn't do?
It's good as it is. It's great as it is, but I'm a sicko and I need, I'd want more, more.
He's demanding more, more, more, more. I'll do laser tag because people didn't get to see it.
We'll go spawn camp. We need more Arthur. He's going to do one more of these Arthur.
Just one more. I swear this will be it. Don't you say that game sucked? What are you talking about?
Wait, I'm sorry. It's, it's hard to follow like what, what, what, like we as gamers
don't and do not like and do not like. Do we not like Red Dead Redemption 2?
I wasn't, I didn't get the memo on this one. We do? It was okay. It sucked.
I gotta get on right. All right. It's time to spawn. Oh, I got three shots now. Give me another one.
Am I crazy or did the dev just subscribe? That's a good question. Maybe. All right.
Let me, let me get in here. Let's spawn camp the same person. How'd you guys, why are you up there?
Stop body blocking. Dick. Can I recharge here? Come with me for a second. Come with me for a
second. Okay. I have an idea. I'm going to bring him over to the recharge station and just get
points. Not a thousand tickets. That's a lot. Dev is through crew. Pretty good actually.
All right, stay here. Damn it. He's running away. No rough housing. Yeah.
It's got moon means. What's that even supposed to mean? No gravity or something. I don't get it.
Move, move. Time. Moon aim suck. Mars aim is great. Oh, right. This is stronger. Gravitational pull. I get you.
Thousand points.
Game over. 1550. Nice. 16 KD. All right. What am I finishing up with? Coin push. You're right.
Somebody wanted to do coin push. That sounds fun. We'll do that. We'll do the SpongeBob one.
Or Bird. Duck. Chicken. Um, Dunko. The mermaid one. Yeah. Mermaid one's good. Let's do mermaid one.
This one's actually, yeah, this one's fun. This one's brand new, by the way. I think this one
actually came out like last week. Here we go. This thing's primed and ready. Spam. Yeah, let's spam.
Wow. All right. Stop burger boy technically. That's not helping. We need some nuance here.
Here we go. Watch this thing go up. Hey, welcome to Twitch. Enjoy your first, like, three hours.
Holy shit. That's loud. All right. I gotta turn it down. It is way too loud.
But didn't I already? I did turn it down. Uh-oh. Is it broken? 800 tickets. Let's go right at the
middle. Bonus. The death is a sub, but thank you. Welcome. Your game is very charming and fun.
It's a nice change of pace. It's just, you just can play arcade games. Just hang on.
Give me another bonus. Let's see how close we are. I thought, what, I didn't leave tickets on the
ground. We're 394,000 tickets. Dizzy bird, please. I will finish with dizzy bird. I promise. Let's do
this one. The audio is bugged. That's all good. 360. That's pretty good tickets. Let's do it again.
Two more times. That's it. If I get to 400, then I win. I feel like I was very accurate that time.
Not going for doubles. It's hard.
That's the one. Yes. 400. Oh, I'm very excited about this apparently. Okay. It's almost time.
It's almost time.
That was it. Those of you that know, you know. If you know, you know. That just went through
the credit went through and it instantly wasn't a jackpot. Those of you that know, you know.
It's hard for me to explain that, but you know. All right. Let's go back to the mermaid.
This should get us there. Let's go right in the middle.
No, it's here. Can you play the story mode? Holy shit. That was a lot. No, no.
The story mode is no, it's not accurate. I want to try it when that comes up.
This might be the biggest win from this machine up on strength. Oh, they all went flat too.
You'd love to see that. Easy, easy. Spread it out. There it is flat.
In 10 seconds, somebody prepare the bottom jewelry. Somebody do it.
Come on. Oh no. I didn't get a bonus. Come on. Right here.
More credits.
1200 tickets. We'll do, uh, one more time and I'm just going to spam in the same corner.
We'll do half or yeah, 50, 60. It's not going to move at all. Meaty if it falls.
That was cool. That's not a lot of tickets though. I'm not satisfied with that one
because look at the left side now. All right, we'll do one more. One more real one
and I'm going to dizzy. Uh, dizzy bird.
Disney bird. No, dizzy bird, dizzy bird. Look at that left side. That comes over here.
How ridiculous that is. I need to get it. Look at this shit. There we go.
Push it. This last one comes because it really does. We look at all these 10s and 20s and 100s
and then we'll cash in and go dizzy bird.
Okay. My cat is addicted to watching me play. It's kind of odd. I wonder why.
Well, I'm addicted to playing this so I'm not a cat or anything, but it's fun.
These are the best arcade game in real life. Uh, I'm not sure I agree with that. All right.
What am I getting completed after the stream is over? First thing I will do.
I promise. Sushi. Okay. All right. More 20. All right. Make this tactical. Look at that left side.
Tactical. Ah, that's it. We're out. We're out. So where are these tickets on the ground? Everyone
says it exists. Where are they? Oh, all right. I wanted to help. Fucker. You got it before I did.
No. Oh, now it's going to be old news when I get it. Thousand tickets. Hello. I would like
a hover board, please. What color? Blue. Blue. Thank you. Okay. Bye. How do I ride it? I'm going
to ride it. Whoa. What the fuck? This thing's fast. I can't ride this. Yes, I can. I can ride
this. Right. Is it not a vehicle? Is Dev still here? Is this a vehicle? Can I ride this?
Wow. Don't look over there. Not yet. Oh shit. I can't ride this. It's not rideable. Oh no.
I can't ride it. Yes, I can. I'm riding it right now. How much does it sell for? I don't know.
Oh no. I saw a kid riding it. There was a kid riding it in here already.
He gets the working one. I don't mind it having batteries. Where's my limo? I don't see how much
it's worth. We have stuff in here. All right. How much is it worth? Uh, that better be 19,000.
What about this other stuff? What are the, uh, what are the ear pods worth? Get rid of these.
How much are the ducks? How much are the ice cream ducks without the stick? 52? Nah. I know
what you're worth. All right. I got all my stuff. Ooh. Cheesy poofs. Push here for cheesy poofs.
Sure. How much are they? $1.50? You're losing $1 per poof. That's okay. My company is operating
at a loss. That's normal. My company have buy cheesy poofs and sell to the thing next to me.
I'll just go get a loan from a bank of $500,000. Pay myself a salary of 50 grand.
Burn the rest of it. That's what you do, right? I didn't even touch it. I didn't even come close.
Now I want the lightsaber. Now I want the lightsaber. The hover board doesn't work.
I want the lightsaber. Go get the lottery tickets. Um, where can you even get the
lottery tickets? I don't remember. Is it here? No, it's not. Where is it?
Gas station. There we go. All right. All right. Do I think the lightsaber works? No,
the lightsaber different doesn't work, but it definitely makes like a
zoom. Guaranteed. Y'all know that's true. Hey, everybody's saying, dude, what the
fuck? This is not a Christmas stream. It is now. They're happy. Merry Christmas.
Are there any new machines in here? I remember this part. I got the ticket back. Whatever.
No, I'm not going to sit here for an hour or two like I did last time. I promise.
I just want to see what it was all about. I just want to see what it was all about.
One more fish. Come on, fish. Spoiled brat.
All right. I'm going to end it with dizzy bird and then I'm going to play
elf bowling for like 10 minutes. Let's go dizzy bird time. Get the fireworks.
Yeah, I did the fireworks last time. No, you can't do this twice. I know it's my birthday.
Happy birthday. Really? I knew the surprise was coming. Unbelievable. I can't believe you guys.
Why wouldn't you surprise me? I'm going to do this until I have no more money.
What is it? Two bucks? All right. No, I'm going to do it 10 times. That was one.
That was not even close. How did I get a penny? Yeah, where did a penny come from?
That seems out of place. That's too far. That's too hard to gauge.
That's too far to gauge. You need the one that's close. It's in the same spot. Great.
At least I get a bonus. Right there. Right there. How many was that? Four?
This is the one. This is the best one to do. It wasn't even close. Not even close.
Not even close. That's okay. I've already beaten it. All right. Three more. This is
memory. I'm serious. I'm only doing this 10 times. What the fuck do I keep messing up?
It's all right. Two more. Last one. Incoming. Where's the light?
Are you fucking kidding me? I almost got it. There it is. The final one.
I'm leaving without you. I'm leaving without you. What is going on with you?
All right. That's it. That's Dizzy Bird. That's the end. Now we're going to move on.
We're going to drink a Mountain Dew. And that is it for the game.
Until the next update. Whenever that happens. Now we're going to do elf bowling. Where's the trash?
There is no trash. That was good. That's a pretty substantial update.
You got a whole new arcade. You got a house with a duck in it and everything. That's pretty cool.
Yeah. I'm going to transition to elf bowling. I have to end the stream the same way I ended
the last one. Hey, somebody just fucking hit me. I was just told somebody was Bowser.
I'll take one. I'll take two. All right. We got two of these. Where are they? Here.
Okay. Well, pick it up. Watch out. Put it in the golf cart and drive around. I don't think it'll
stay. I'll try. Damn it. I kind of want to do like 20 of these in the golf cart. Can I do that?
No way. Not one will barely fit in here. Is it facing the right way?
Drive. Drive. I drove the cart into the water last time too. Yeah. That's what I have to do.
There's a fail. Well, I can't drive over this for some reason.
Come on. Why can I not drive over this? Is it patched? Yeah, we're good. I'm still going.
Still going. Still going. Still going. Still going. Go. Keep going. Keep going. Go. More. More.
I'm not pressing any buttons. There it is. The end of the world. Oh, I didn't save the game.
Remind me that if I play this game again, I don't have any more gas and I need to walk back to...
Can you die? No, I can teleport. I can teleport. All right. Elf Balling time to end the stream.
Merry Christmas, everybody. If you've taken off, we'll see when I get back. I'm going to be taking
a few days off for the holiday. Please continue to nominate and discuss the end of the year stuff
that's not turning off. I will see you guys on Friday the 27th. If you celebrate Christmas,
happy Christmas, happy holidays. Whatever you happen to be celebrating, happy holidays to you.
I'll be back on Friday. And now let's do Elf Bowling. And if you were curious, yes,
it's already here ready to go. It is. I didn't know they were naked. How do you play? Oh, like
that. X. This is the first game I ever played. Is it really? I feel like it's at times 10 speed.
Why is it sounds so fast? Strike. Let me get to in a row. There it is.
It's my processor is going too fast. Did it just, did it just cut off somebody's head?
I don't remember doing that. It just ripped his head off.
God, that was three strikes in a row. Elf Bowling Dev in chat.
No way, because I don't think this game came out like 30 years ago.
Sorry, something came on the screen. I had to try to throw something. I don't know why.
How old is this game? I don't know. When did the internet come out? 1997? 1996?
I think I could probably get at least four or five strikes in a row if I try hard.
I gotta use my right hand. That's a spare.
You thought the game broke when the elf's head came off.
This game was completely showered in controversy, if you don't know.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe the original version of this game was a virus.
Right? It was, wasn't it? The original version of this game was a virus.
Hold on. I need to confirm. Can somebody look it up?
It's definitely sped up.
Let's do quit. Elf Bowling, let's do Elf Bowling 2.
Elves in Paradise.
Okay, I need to be clear. This doesn't show his elf dick, right? Tell me that's not true.
I don't want to get an elf dick. Okay, there's probably an elf dick in this.
It's shuffleboard. Don't pull your fucking underwear down.
All right, I'm out of here. Don't pull your fucking elf underwear down, don't you fucking dare.
Don't. I gotta go right up this way.
It wasn't a virus, by the way. It wasn't?
There's an elf dick. Play something else. I don't think there is.
300. They made a movie based on this?
If you have received elf bowling or frogapult games on the internet.
Spam that again. I can't. I didn't see it.
It's awful. If you've received elf bowling or frogapult games that have been circling the
internet and no one has, they must be deleted before Christmas Day. They contain viruses that
is to go off on Christmas Day and will delete your hard drive. That wasn't real?
It was a hoax. I don't know.
How am I supposed to know? I was probably like 12 years old.
It still is. You have less than 24 hours to delete this.
I don't want to play this anymore. I'm done.
How is this elf bowling 2? Elf bowling movie IMDB link.
Is there a trailer for the movie? I can watch that, right?
That's not like against the rules. I want to watch the trailer.
Yeah, let's watch the trailer for elf bowling the movie.
You're dead. This is the last round.
All right. I'm done. Forget about polar bowler.
All right. That was fun. You thought I was going to do that for less than 10 minutes?
More than 10 minutes? No way. Not a million years.
I want to watch the elf bowling movie trailer. Elf bowling the movie.
All right. Let's watch it. Please rate your ad experience.
Oh, shut up. Yeah. I hate it.
All right. Elf bowling trailer. 10 years ago?
This trailer is in like a terrible 480p trailer. This is okay.
Let's go. Yeah. Okay. Ready?
Put all them creature stolen toys in me cabin.
First of all, I just got to say an episode of Mickey Mouse Clubhouse
has which is about the same amount of animation quality.
Could it be that a long, long time ago, Santa started out as a pirate
and wound up kicked off his own ship? It's him.
And what do you lads do in this wondrous place?
See for yourself. It's a magical and mystical marvelous world.
It doesn't even fit up. It doesn't even fit up.
You're going to call me the Madagascar Penguins?
Are we sure this is not an iPad ad for an iPad game?
The Elf Bowling, the movie.
This is like a chick flick, except instead of smoking babes, dude,
it's a bunch getting a fat guy.
Is this movie in public domain? Can we watch this movie on stream?
I would. Wait, what? There's a second movie? No, there's not.
No, no, that's not real. Is it in public domain?
No way. Who owns the rights to Elf Bowling, the movie?
The Wikipedia article for it has been marked for deletion.
That's the nail in the coffin right there.
That's so funny. Well, we have to watch it before it gets deleted from the world.
If it's not on Wikipedia, then it doesn't exist.
Buy the rights to the Elf Bowling movie.
It's probably way more expensive than you think.
I would not be surprised if the rights to Elf Bowling and Elf Bowling, the movie,
all Elf Bowling intellectual property is less than two to three hundred thousand dollars.
It's probably like five hundred thousand dollars.
Imagine doing a Kickstarter for like a million dollars.
And the goal of Kickstarter is for me to get enough money to
buy out and own the IP of Elf Bowling. But what would I do?
It was six and a half million dollars to make that movie.
There's no way I could afford to buy Elf Bowling's IP.
To watch it on stream. To watch the movie on stream.
Buy it to put it in the public domain.
God.
Anyways, that's going to wrap up the stream.
I'm going to get some food. That was a lot of fun.
Hopefully you guys have a good Christmas.
I'll see you guys on Friday.
For... I don't know.
I don't know.
What the hell? What the hell?
Nancy Drew?
No.
No, no, no, no.
Yes. No.
May we'll see.
We'll see if it depends on how good my Christmas was.
If I had a really great Christmas,
then maybe we'll do Nancy Drew post Christmas stream.
If I had, if I didn't like my, if I didn't have fun on Christmas,
then we'll do The Surge 2.
I got to stop saying I'm going to play The Surge 2 because
I don't want to do that.
Anywho.
Let's do the bits and the subs and everything.
What about Disco Elsium?
Ah, that's another thing I was thinking of.
We'll see.
See you guys on Friday.
Have a great holiday.
If you haven't yet, I want to make sure I keep reiterating this.
Go to the Discord and check out the nominations channel for the New Year's Eve stream.
Nominate something.
If you see one of those categories, go to the discussion channel.
There's a pinned message.
Discuss it.
Nominate.
Nominate stuff.
If you want.
It is currently available.
It is going to stop the day that I come back.
Friday the 27th.
As of probably, I don't know, Friday night.
As of the stream turning off on Friday.
That's it for nominations.
And then the voting is going to start the next day.
Literally the next day for three days.
You will have three full days to cast your vote.
And then, obviously, on the 31st, we have to go over them.
I'll be talking about it every single stream leading up to the 31st.
The day I come back is the last day that you can nominate something.
Check it out.
Let's do the bits.
Be good.
Yeah, I hope Santa is good to you guys this year.
Let's go back to earlier this afternoon.
We had Dark Soul.
Dark Soul, thanks for the 250.
I'm here from Gap Gaming with your first paycheck.
We're really looking forward to sponsoring more streams,
but keep in mind these bits confirm your agreement to our exclusivity deal.
You can only wear Gap brand clothes on stream,
and you must now refer to your viewers as Gappers.
Thanks, and have a great stream.
Imagine doing that for $2.50.
Add four zeros, and maybe I'll think about it.
25, 250, 2500, 125,000, 250.
All right, that's $2.5 million.
I thought it was a little bit less than that.
All right, never mind.
Hey, Dark Soul, thanks for the 250.
Hi, I'm here from Gap Gaming.
Wait, what?
Why is it happening twice?
It's not, it's the same one, but I don't know why it doesn't make any sense.
Hey, it's me from Gap Gaming again.
Hey, a triple, triple zero Neo, thanks for the 250.
Chicken Game or Riot, I did.
Played it a few times, actually.
What about Community Night?
Yeah, Community Night got screwed up,
because I was supposed to go in front of the green screen
before the third one happened,
and I ended up having to push the green screen until further notice,
until I start to go to the physical therapy,
and it got a little botched.
So that's still going to have to sit on the burner for another couple weeks, probably.
But I'm no longer going to wait.
I'm not going to wait anymore to do Community Content Night 3.
So it'll probably happen at some point in the middle of January,
first or second week of January.
That's that.
But thank you, triple zero.
We did play the Chicken Game.
Martin had a meme, thanks for the 2,000 bits.
$20 from Martin had a meme.
Thanks for the 2,000 bits.
This was the game where you had your scratch ticket stream idea,
and I'd like to one-up that by saying you should buy a bunch of scratch
and sniff cards and smell them on stream.
Well, the scratch card thing got fucked up,
because I didn't know that Nevada doesn't have a state lottery.
So I'm like, we're going to scratch $200
worth of scratch tickets for every death in Sekiro.
And it's like, oh, sorry, turns out there are no scratch tickets in Nevada.
They don't exist.
There's no such thing.
There's no state lottery in Nevada.
And I was like, all right, well, maybe I'll have somebody send me
buy $300 worth of scratch tickets and send them to me from like Massachusetts.
Nobody wants to fucking do that.
Hey, can you buy $300 worth of scratch tickets and mail them to me and I'll pay you?
It's like, leave me alone, Jeremy.
Go to California, fly to California.
That's a lie stream.
No, that's not fair.
That's not a lie.
I can't, I couldn't do it.
I don't know that Nevada, I've only been here for a year.
I didn't know that I couldn't do that.
It's not a lie.
If you attempt to do something and you get legally, you can't.
Okay, sure.
Sorry, I didn't.
Sorry, I didn't get on an airplane to go to California to buy scratch tickets.
Isn't California right across the border?
Um, yeah, it's like a four hour drive.
That's, that's an eight plus hour trip to go get scratch tickets.
That's not long.
That's a long ass time in a car.
And it's not even, that's not just eight hours.
That's four hours plus to get there.
That's without traffic in California.
Once I get into California, I'm, what am I just going to drive to the border?
Take a step over the border and find the first gas station and buy $300 worth of scratch tickets.
The first gas, they're going to call the police on me.
Wouldn't that turn around and drive back over the, that's,
is it weird that I'm scared to do that?
Imagine if I got pulled over, like going over the border to Nevada.
Sir, I see that you just pulled into a gas station.
Yeah, I did.
Can I take a look inside your car here?
Uh, yeah.
What are these scratch tickets doing here?
I know it's not illegal.
It's not illegal to scratch scratch tickets in another state.
I'm just, it's not illegal.
Look, I'm going to, let's, let's be, no, I did.
I did not drive three, four, five hours across the border to get scratch tickets.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do that.
How about this?
The next time, it's going to be a lie.
The next time I'm in California, this is a lie.
Why would I even say this?
The next, the next time I'm in California, which I go a few times a year, stuff like E3,
Twitch con, you know, the next time I'm in, I'm in California, I'm going to buy
300 fucking dollars worth scratch tickets.
And, but then I'm going to get searched at TSA.
They're going to be like, what's this guy doing?
Why is, is, is this guy so addicted to gambling that he goes to a,
on a trip to Los Angeles and buys a like 50 scratch tickets and it's in his bag.
He's going, where's, what's his, what's, where's his ticket to Las Vegas?
This dude's going back to Las Vegas with like 75 scratch tickets.
I'm going to get searched.
I'm going to be like, okay, what are you doing here?
Guys, you know, if you walk off the airplane in the Las Vegas airport,
there's a slot machine right when you get out of the terminal,
they're going to be like, what are you doing?
Mail them to yourself.
Yes, I'd like to send a package please.
Oh, okay.
I welcome to welcome to like the UPS store.
Welcome to the USPS office.
Welcome to FedEx store.
How can I help you?
Yeah, I'd like to mail a hundred scratch tickets to myself.
Oh, you're insane.
Sure thing.
It's your money.
Where do you live?
Las Vegas.
Okay.
Just buy the stamp.
You don't have to tell him what you're sending.
Yeah, but I'm fucking crazy.
I know it's in that box.
And I'm going to be like, there's scratch tickets in there.
Like, I don't know.
I'm a weirdo.
Oh, yeah.
Here.
I'm just sending out a package.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That's it.
That's all our conversation has to be.
Yes, scratch tickets in there.
What the heck?
What am I doing?
Okay.
Yes.
Have a good day.
You're an oblivion NPC.
I just have to say everything I'm doing and walk in there.
Well, cool door.
Interesting door.
Howdy.
How are you?
Hi.
Wow.
Scratch tickets in this box.
How much?
Howdy.
How are you?
You're a math problem.
That's not an oblivion NPC.
That's a shitty, that's a bad let's player.
Yeah, that's pretty, that's pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Anyways, scratch and sniff cards.
But you can't smell them.
How could, why would that work?
I can't.
All right.
I'm gonna, let's go.
Let's go.
We got, we got.
It's four hours to Los Angeles.
All right.
It's like a five hour drive.
How dare you prove me wrong and embarrass me on my own stream?
How dare you?
Road trip stream.
No, I'm not doing a driving stream.
Are you crazy?
Desert bus.
Don't.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not gonna do a driving.
If I go, if I go anywhere, it's not gonna be on stream.
All right.
We gotta move.
We gotta go.
We gotta move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move.
It's Christmas.
Come on.
People got places to go.
Where were we?
All right.
Martin had a meme thanks to the 2,000 bits.
Scratch and sniff would be pretty cool,
except you guys can't smell it.
That'd be unfortunate.
Hey, Jay Bong.
Thanks for the 250.
What's up, Jerma?
I haven't been able to catch your streams for three days.
Gonna spend my time dealing with a huge sprained ankle.
No, knowing how to ice skate plus sketchy rental skates
don't look a good combo.
That hurts.
My ankle plumped up like a mango
and I'm bed bound for four to seven weeks.
Oh my God.
That's a long time.
The doc said it was a grade three sprain.
At least I'll be able to catch your famous yearly Christmas stream, right?
Should we tell him?
There's no Christmas stream this year.
It's the New Year's Eve stream.
You ever had a deal with a sprain ankle or sprained limb on a first timer?
No, not really.
I've had minor sprains, you know, minor twists on the ankle
or, you know, on a wrist or something,
but never something that put me in bed for like seven weeks.
Have you ever broken a bone?
No.
Well, no, that's not true.
I broke my collarbone when I was two years old.
I fell off a chair and shattered my collarbone.
I don't remember.
I don't know it.
I don't remember it.
I just know what happened.
Wimp?
Jesus.
Weak bones.
That's two.
The very first fall joke.
Thank you, Jay Blondell.
I've never had a...
I hope you get a swift recovery to you.
I've never had a broken bone like that or a sprained ankle.
It sounds like it's not very fun.
I cracked my skull open when I was four.
Beat that scrub.
I did that too.
I actually talked about that on stream when I was talking to Joel.
So you can't...
There's no one out there.
You and I are the same.
Sorry.
Hey, Yosher.
Master, thanks for the 500 bits.
Jerma, can you sort these bits for me?
Please lend me some of your processing power, Jerma IQ.
Sure.
Did you get some of that?
I released some.
That's what I was doing, the sorting algorithm.
You didn't get any?
Well, they went for you.
Can we do sorting algorithms one more time?
I'll do...
No.
Thank you, Yosher Master, and enjoy the Jerma IQ power.
Thank you, Nickly Bob for the thousand bits.
Thank you, Bob.
Ten dollars.
It's really nice to relax to your streams after work.
Thank you.
Glad you can hang out and relax.
Glad you can chill.
Cold War Hall gave ten community subs.
Thank you.
Ampharic ten community subs.
I think we caught them, but seriously...
What's this?
Oh, let me mix...
Let me see.
Okay.
I want to see how bad this is.
Because I literally...
People would...
Like I said, people wanted to burn my house down for this one.
Let me see how bad this is.
I've never looked over and seen chat tell me how much they want me to fucking...
You know what I mean?
How bad was it?
Why'd it give me a bonus?
Jerma, you've been playing the chicken game since July.
Please stop.
Ayayayayayayayaya.
I did it.
Yeah, he said it.
Ayayayayayayayaya.
That wasn't even that bad.
You guys overreacted.
Holy shit, you overreacted.
Wow what an overreaction to that.
I can't believe it.
I- you what an overreacted.
Okay.
What's that music?
Hey sad.
Vega.
Thanks for the 250.
So when can we expect the 10 Ghost Peppers to be eaten on stream?
or the 50,000 USD excluding tax subs i think i mean if you all right you want to go there
uh there were at least two or three times where i got 50,000 subs if i eat the 10 ghost peppers
then this 50,000 subs i'm not gonna eat those so like literally i just like like let me just put
this in like complete full quotation mark it doesn't matter how much money comes into the
stream ever i will never eat even one bite of one single ghost pepper ever on this stream for any
reason end quote ever ever ever ever and i mean ever and i mean ever and i mean ever and i mean
ever and i mean monka omega i mean ever monka omega why am i saying that today i'm not sure
why i'm into saying that now i started the stream with that didn't i why am i doing that
it doesn't make any sense i don't know hey turbo sucks five community subs we caught it thank you
hey knit cat thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars here's your 15,000 subs coke gaming it's not from
coke gaming that was a little satire parody joke that you just said don't get me in trouble but
thanks to the 1500 bits appreciate it thanks to the 500 bits five dollars no message just
five dollars 500 bits thank you jamie thanks to the five community subs i think i caught these but i
may have been focused on pressing the button when the light lights up over and over again so
thank you jamie 2803 five community subs appreciate it tingy five community subs loose cannon five
community subs and then we had the monster drop from raggle flaggle there was a 50 sub community
drop from raggle flaggle which is insane thanks to the five million subs appreciate it uh we i
remember catching these cvfd thanks to the 500 bits thank you for uh ot showing that freak on
stream thank you for ot oh thank you for not showing that freak on stream and i did
so i i sorry see ya cvfd i did i showed it thank you for the 500 bits so appreciate it
raf rod thanks for the 500 bits you ever tried uh zevia it's carbonated water and stevia leaf
extract it's really good no i just drink water at that point i just drink water i know some people
oh try this it's seltzer water with two two drops of watermelon juice whatever now i'll just drink
water that sounds like water yeah no not white claw but no i never had it i usually if i'm gonna
drink if i'm gonna drink carbonated water it's gonna be probably some type of soda not just soda
water it's gonna be something else to it but it gives me it makes me burp and shit it gives me
i don't it's been a heartburn future gamer thanks for the 250 speaking of ads i have a distinct
memory of going to the movie theater in between movie ads an ad playing in which a lady had bugs
coming out of her bleeding eyes it was super fucked up and i was 12 when i saw it i have no
clue what it was trying to sell but it scared the shit out of me that sounds horrible what hopefully
that was not during a disney movie that sounds insane thanks for the 250 though that's uh it's
fucked up c4g thanks for 250 thank you for enabling peepo happy i love this little guy yeah
of course everybody loves peepo happy the great it's a great little character thank you
furikus or ferikus for the 500 bits never for any reason at any time ever for any purpose do that
again apologize right now germa disgust it's the ayaya thing it's i you know i don't i can't believe
it i'm going to scream because he said the thing that's like a a meme that everybody's seen and
no he did it again no i didn't i said it normally you're not gonna hear me do that again look it's a
if you see this no no get rid of that get rid of that i can't even delete it get rid of that
don't do that don't do it if you see it you've already seen it dark soul thanks for the 250 i
swear to god if you have a mock kinero mosaic again i'm going to fucking sue you do you hear me
if you kiss the webcam with lipstick i'll accept your apology nothing less what is what is kinero
mosaic is that the is that this was that a show is that the show that the an is that the anime that
the clip is from i don't know that's the anime it's from i think you got you guys there are some
things that i don't realize how uh just how polarizing something is until i do it and then
i see that my all my tires have been slashed i will keep that in mind not apologizing by the way
gonna keep it in mind not an apology gonna keep it in mind by the way i'm sorry for doing that
at least don't be mad at me here i'm gonna lipstick on it yeah atmostarfish thanks for
the 500 bits appreciate it no message just 500 bits boxbox came in with a huge raid boxbox thank
you again that's like at least the second or third time that you've raided this channel i'm gonna
have to come and hang out i want i want to raid boxbox boxbox has shown this channel so much love
do sorting algorithm but no seriously thank you you've shown this channel a ton of love so i
really appreciate it to catch you in your streaming one day thank you though seriously
acdc freak thanks for the five community subs thank you acdc to stream 10 hours earlier
forehead jamona cucumber thanks for the 250 i was watching your latest nancy juror stream in which
you mistook some puffins for penguins saying they eat penguins to which i quote loudly responded
they're not penguins they're puffins you knob i wanted to say sorry about that i didn't mean it
love the streams well i didn't hear you i just wanted to apologize for saying that into my
screen well you did just say it right now yeah okay i see what i feel you thank you though thank
you damona cucumber for the 250 appreciate it hey inc thanks for the 250 inc inc six seven six seven
hey germa just want to say that you're my favorite streamer and you're currently getting me through
pretty bad times whenever i'm feeling shitty i just throw on a germa vlog and it makes things
that much better thank you inc i'm sorry that you're going through some shit right now
hopefully you get through it hopefully you can take care of it much love to you thanks for
watching the stream and thank you for the two dollars and 50 cents 250 bits have a great night
hopefully we see you soon butt squire thanks for the 500 bits gta online got an update about two
weeks ago that added arcades so it'll be a really good follow-up game to the coin game are you
serious also i know how much you like casino did they actually add that they added an arcade and
gta 5 online i'll play it eventually i know i will uh we had cyclops parker gave looks like
10 15 subs one by one one two three four five six one two three four five six seven eight nine
10 12 just one by one just sub sub sub sub sub thank you thank you cyclops parker for all those
subs and speaking of those subs let's switch over to the cleanup section of this movie theater let's
put them on the screen right now roll it all the community subs there were a lot of them tonight
all the regular subs all the long-term subs thanks a lot guys wait you got gifted a sub
all right let's see those emotes thanks a lot guys for your ridiculous support that you give this
channel on a day in a day out basis thank you we will finish up these bits we had 250 from e word
word to each word word are you gonna play halo reach again or are you gonna wait for halo one
to come up because halo reach sucks uh i don't know i was i was soiled for me may i don't know
i've never played halo and i played for like an hour and then it was just
maybe it's better that way we'll see hey have gone thanks for the 250 hey germa and chat
merry christmas i've been playing some of the classic lucas arts star wars games recently
and they still hold up pretty well you ever considered playing the dark forces last jedi
night games on stream also california has a state lottery drive into this town it's only about an
hour or two from vegas i know i didn't i didn't know he doesn't know i didn't know uh classic
lucas arts games though i remember there was a game it was it was an old old old not what was
it called you you like rogue not rogue squadron what was the old star wars pc games republic
command no no no no no maybe it was dark forces it was one where you had to it was sprites
and you had to peek up behind corners and shoot with a blaster what was that one it was old as
shit rebel strike it might have been rebel strike it was very old you had to peek up around corners
and it was very very very sloppy maybe one day dark forces looks familiar too galactic battle
grounds yeah maybe we'll do a star wars night try to get like five of these games six of them or
something oh no i how did i forget this how did i forget this i how i don't know how i forgot this
i just guys i have a 3do now we're gonna do 3do i have it i own a 3do now how did i forget to
tell you that omega lol why well because i wanted one we're gonna play gex also there's like two or
three uh full motion video games that are on the 3do that you can't get anywhere and i want to and
we're talking about original hardware this guy's a retro gal you bet your ass
gex is awesome so i'm gonna start collecting 3do games no i didn't spend 700 on the 3do
no go gex plumbers don't wear it's a porn game right i can't do that one let's finish up the
bits we had bowser jr streams that would be an interesting stream thanks for the 500 bits
hi germa i've been watching your streams for a while now it's been really helpful with some
hard times i've had i want to show some thanks and love in any way that i could keep being an
amazing person can't wait for more streams to come stay tuned hopefully you enjoy what is to come
got stuff planned i'll help you enjoy it like i did say previously but i will say it again i hope
you can get through whatever it is is causing you bullshit in your life thank you so much for
watching we also had 250 from martin had a meme they say can you explain this asking for a friend
sure uh sure yeah i'll put this on stream this is a this is very very old image what you have here
uh yeah we can explain this i mean maybe i can't even explain this but i'll try i guess uh i'll
try to explain this and in the best way that i can i don't know hold on is this is this the
this is how is this still here it's been like three weeks uh it's like you got like toilet paper and
there's like what looks that i bet that looks to be some type of oh there's a i like a lotion
on your desk i'm gonna be completely real with you here um first of all let's get the image on
the screen i need to defend myself here i think those are dog vitamins that sounds like bullshit
but those are hold on where is it i believe the i believe that is actually dog vitamins
what lotion container looks like that guys have you ever seen it that's not lotion that is dog
vitamins they don't have necks that huge look at the shape of that container i don't know look
why is it guys my room is a mess if you think if all right i'm gonna be let's be very real i'm
gonna use code words here if you think for a second if you think for a second that i'm like
lying out in my bed on my back no no i use what explain the toilet i don't know look at what else
is up there look at all this is a bunch of trash nobody even does that it's a meme it's like a
jokey meme from every comedy movie back in like the 1990s that nobody does that those are dog
vitamins dog i'm gonna look this up dog vitamin pump where is it where's the dog vitamin pump
what brand is that enhance there's dog vitamins you have lotion in the mirror that's not even
what do you think i just have like three huge containers of lotion in my room sitting around
for every scenario that could possibly come up i gotta have just by the bed gotta have it by the
computer i have to have it next to me it's a dog vitamins come on i got i gotta find it or no is
it dog vitamins or is it a coffee flavor pump that's not what it is who cares what do i really
care about my messy ass room look at the ground you guys don't think that every time i made a
video i looked at what was in the viewfinder and said i don't care look at this fucking dirty
ass room he's deflecting no those are dog vitamins i'm serious they have to be is a poo stain oh okay
that's funny what do you mean what are you talking about where's that where's a shit stain no that's
like a crumpled up mcdonald's bag that's not like shit stained diaper that's like a crumpled up bag
that's not like a diaper with a shit in it what are you talking about that's a crumpled not on
the wall dude that that's just that's like some wallpaper that's been torn off i don't know i
opened the door too hard and i scraped the door guys i don't know you're talking about an image
from like eight years ago i don't know what that is i scraped the door probably like 12 years ago
anyways where were we oh right i don't remember oh right here we go no where did i somebody like
oh is martin had a meme 250 can you explain this asking yeah yeah yeah
ec long thanks for the 300 bits hello jeremy have been subscribed to your
youtube since 2013 haven't been able to catch the streams that often but i love your content and your
humor you've brought years of joy to me and it means if it means anything my son's middle name
is jeremy and part of that is because of your influence over both my life and my wife's
stay amazing and hopefully i'll be able to see you around twitch more what an what an honor what an
absolute honor i can't even believe that thank you so much for watching if that much influence
you can have your for some reason to have your son's middle name to be jeremy i don't even know
what to say to that that's incredibly touching thank you i hope you stick around and one time
it is unfortunate i know no no no no no no no it's no i don't want you i don't want you to go
i don't want you time to go we had one more we had very nice gave 250 bits
i'd love to see you play rock of ages on stream it's 250 on steam right now well you did just give me
250 so i will just buy it because i mean you you why not have a fantastic holiday if you celebrate
christmas merry christmas if you celebrate any other any other holiday have a good one
we'll see you on friday now go out there and and see some thing have some fun i don't know
be safe don't do anything stupid don't do anything i wouldn't do and then think about it like what i
would you think about what i you know just don't do anything just don't be don't be like me no
yeah wait no no no no that doesn't work that way don't do anything just be smart and be safe done
thank you i'll see you guys on friday good night guys much love to you my birthday my birthday
happy birthday to sticks renegade happy birthday sticks renegade you that's a great birthday right
before christmas week of christmas what the fuck happy birthday happy birthday anybody has a
birthday happy birthday all of you good night