All right, throttle, handbrake, jump jets, grab rider. All right, so let's go, all right?
I guess so. I did not expect that to happen immediately once starting this video. What
is happening? Hi, everybody. My name is Jerma. Welcome to Road Redemption. This is a game
beat. My game is crashing. Jesus. Okay, hold on a minute. I need a second. I need to like
prepare for this. Well, I got like a gun. How do you shoot the gun? How do I shoot this
gun at this guy? Oh, well, I took a fucking beam in the face. I want to shoot this guy.
Oh dear god. What? What? How does? I thought. Oh, I did. Did I not die? I must not have died
from that. Okay. How do you shoot the weapon? I need to figure this out. Is it? There we go.
That's how you do it. All right, I figured it out. If I could only hit somebody with it,
that would be fantastic. But apparently that's not as easy as it looks. Especially when I'm
playing with a controller, which I probably shouldn't be doing. But I am going right here,
right here, right here. I'm going to get this guy. No, I got him. I won. I did it. Get out of my face.
Can I make, can I like jump over this? I got you. I got you. You let him fuck up. Let's go for a ride.
What is happening? How are we still driving? We're not on the course, isn't this?
My chest is going to cave in.
Oh, I only have 25. Put this down for a second.
All right, let's actually try to like win rather than just like throw up from laughing,
which is kind of hard to do. All right, I got this. I'm going to actually try to win,
not instantly die. This game is hilarious though. Without question. Get out of here.
Oh shit. I'll get him. Road rash. Road rage. Hey, what's up buddy? You want to get road raged?
You want to get, no shit. I was trying to hit you. I'm trying to hit this guy
and then I'm going to hit this guy too. Screw you buddy.
How much money have I made? I've made $150. That's good. That's a good amount of money to make for
just ramming into this shit. You know, it's a good day to make $150. What the fuck was that?
Did you see that? Hold on. I don't even care. I need to go watch it. No.
I want to go see the guy riding the car. Please tell me I can get back up.
I need to get back up there. Come on. Punch it. Punch it. There we go. That's what I'm talking
about. All right, there's no way I'm going to find that guy again. So I might as well just turn.
Okay, that was very loud. Apparently. I can drive up here, huh? Can I really drive up here?
Okay, I guess so. All right. We're going down the mountain. There's all the crash sounds.
Am I even driving the right way? See? There it was again. There it was again.
Somebody is riding a car. I need to figure out how to do that. That's really important.
If I can figure out how to do that. Okay, can I drive? Shit. Nitro. Nitro is kind of crazy.
Just nitro again. Nitro. It's okay. I'm still alive. I can still do this.
Let's go, you son of a bitches. Total carnage. Oh, boy. Did you see how much stuff just got
crashed? Did you just see? Oh, my God. Seriously. This is like tactical intervention. I'm having
more flashbacks. Drive. Drive. So I have to attract cops? I already have like. Oh.