Hello there. How you doing? Good morning to you. Oh, good morning. Good, um, good afternoon.
Whatever time it is where you are. How are you? Hope you're doing a fantastic day.
It's midnight. Good morning. Yeah, I don't know why I said good morning.
Good morning. Oh yeah, but it's like, it's like time zones exist. It's morning somewhere in the world.
Always. It doesn't matter. It could be, it could be 10 o'clock at night
for you and potentially one o'clock in the morning for me. It's 10 30 a.m. in Australia.
That's who I was talking to. It was good indeed. 16 hours ago. But welcome back. We're doing more
Mario Sunshine shoe eating stream. That's yeah. Well, I'm glad you made it. I, how did you know?
I've got like four different shoes here on plates and shit. This is, that's kind of weird. How would
you know that? I was gonna eat them all. Damn. One day, here's a list of ideas that I say that
I'll never do, but I would like to because I'm just right now, which is I'm just spit balling
this to you. What have I had like six or seven shoes custom made out of edible licorice or
something and they looked very real. I paid like a lot of money to have these shoes look really
fucking real. And I ate them on stream and pretended they were Willy Wonka like lose a bet
at some point in the stream. Now this is, this is exclusive to you guys because if I ever not,
I'm never going to do this. If I ever do this, you guys will know. But an hour goes by in the stream
and I make a bet with you guys and I'm like, oh, you know, fine, whatever. If I lose this bet,
I'll eat fucking 10 shoes. And everyone would be like, what the fuck? And I lose it. And then
here we go. The camera goes on. You're supposed to eat shoes on March 12th. You can't put that
there right now. That's not even real. Why is it to be 10? I don't know. Why not? Welcome back. I
have 26 shines in Mario sunshine. I'm having a lot of fun. Game's great. Evidence. Hold on. What?
I said, I wait, I said I was going to do this already. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on. Did I actually say this like four months ago? Wait, wait, wait, wait, what?
This is like back, this is like a year ago. I said I was going to eat a full shoe on stream. If
sans was confirmed and shoot, uh, he was last yesterday. Oh no. Why did I think this is,
why did I know this was going to happen? I mean, smash.
Well, I, what do I say? I said right here, March 12th. And so the shoe eating stream will be
on, uh, March 12th, 2020 market on your calendar. You gotta be fucking kidding me, man.
Yep. All right. Mark it on your calendar. Uh, Freddy dread gave 50 subs. Holy fuck, dude.
Thanks for the 50 subs. Freddy dread coming in. Yeah. All right. Well, fuck it. You know what
I'm doing. Never lied about eating the shoe. No, did I? Uh, last time I looked at my calendar,
it was not March 12th. It was March. I don't even know what days don't there's no such thing
as a day anymore in my brain. Only like weeks. All right. So it's March 5th.
I got plenty of fucking time to get a full shoe on stream. We had a wink. We actually did.
Welcome back to Mario Sunshine. I'll give you a look. Those of you that have not been around
the last, uh, it's gonna say few days, but it was actually less than 24 hours ago.
40 blue coins, 26 shines and zero regular coins. Uh, where do I want to go? I'm just,
I'm obsessed with collecting, but Freddy dread, that was an absolute shitload of subs.
Thank you for the ridiculous amount of subs. You did it again. You did it a second time,
like two, a minute ago. Oh my fucking God, Freddy, a hundred community subs from Freddy dread.
Jesus. Thanks, dude. That's a lot. You're supposed to do, you're supposed to do pachinko. Yeah. I
said I would, I said I would do it today, but I didn't say when. Did I? Yeah, I did. And then
Austin Atlantis gave five community subs as well. Thank you, Austin Atlantis. I'm doing it. I'm
going. I wish Nintendo would stop making bankable games and just make pachinko machines. Well, you
say that, but over the next 10 to 15 years, uh, all of those, all those Betty white machines
and all those, like, look at the cute kitty cat slot machines are going to get replaced by Mario
Sonic and like solid snake and shit. Time stamp this, mark my words. Like the Elvis machines,
gone. All of them. The Alfred Hitchcock slot machine, all of them gone, replaced with
Super Mario slot machines. Garin fucking T. How am I feeling? I'm feeling all right.
I'm feeling all right today. No, I'm sorry. I'll get it when it comes back. He's lying.
Now, if you missed it yesterday for some, I don't know. I have like fucking mystery pain
around my whole body. Right. And we already talked about it, but like, yeah, I got my like tongue
started hurting yesterday. It was just weird. And it like kind of freaked me out for like 10 minutes.
But oh my God, I missed it again. I guess this is the equivalent. If I, uh, if I was sitting there
waiting for a bus in real life and I'm on the phone, like talking to my mom or something and
the bus pulls up twice and I don't get on it. I got to get on the fucking bus. I got to get home.
I got to go home. Freddy dread. Holy shit. 200 bucks, 20,000 bits from Freddy dread,
a hundred community subs and $200 in bits. This is one of my favorite games. Thank you,
German. My man. This game's awesome. I've never played it. This is fucking crazy, man. Thank you.
I go. I got to get on the bus. I have to get on the bus running behind the bus.
No, stop, please. Please. No, no, no, no. I'll get on. I'll get on. No,
we're going to wait again. I have to memory a fucking four year old. Just get on the boat. Now
Nocturne, Nocturne, I have to turn a hundred bucks each shoe. Wait, I got to get on the bus.
Just wait a minute. Okay. Uh, Nocturne gave us a hundred dollars. Remember I told you how red it
was yesterday. Read it and it's a ton of more money now. Like right now is hundreds and hundreds
and hundreds of dollars each shoe, March 12th. I don't, and Hey, don't fucking, I'm going to,
I got to trust you guys not to talk shit about this. Cause if I get a custom made edible shoe
for March 12th, you bet your ass that you better not be telling anybody about that.
You got to be in on the joke. All right. How many do I need? Eight. But thank you both of you.
Seriously. Leather is edible. If you think for even one, one second that I am going to eat
a real shoe on stream and like die. You're crazy. Oh, this sucks. All right. I know how to do it.
I know how to do this. The ultimate joke. You got to get in like right here. All right. Now right
there. Okay. Nice. What the fuck was that? I got it. Okay. These are the worst ones. I got to make
sure the final one is one of the really easy ones up top. I need to see where am I going? All right.
There's one. I got to get the ones up. I want to get the ones up top last. The star definitely
goes in the middle. I am certain of that. Okay. There's only two more. I thought I just fell off
the edge and I was about to, I was about to be very, okay. There's the one all the way in the
end there. I got to go for that one next. And then there's the last one is the one all the way to the
right. I got to get that one. All right. Make it easy. Let's go. This is the camera. Just
fucking camera was just like a straight into the machine. I couldn't even see.
So have we determined, is it impossible for me to do this? Get in the corner right there.
Mario's kind of quirky. Yeah, he is very quirky. What are you doing? Get in there, get in there.
Come on, push it. Ah, this is going to get Jeremy floored. Wait, what? Why is that happening? All
right. No, no, no, no, no. Why, why is that happening? What the hell is that? I, why can I
fly with it? Why is it pushing me? He's got the fucking thing. All right. Hold on. See, it's like
shoving me to the right. I'm not pressing. It's just like, it's tossing me over there. Dude, what
the fuck? Dude, dude. See, what the fuck was that? I have to jump to this one. I have to jump to
that one. I have to. It's got, I have to do it like this because it doesn't, even if you,
this is really weird. Even if you jump over it, the game just decides it's just, it's going to
throw you like I'm not pressing. I'm in trouble. Holy fuck. That was close. Let go of the nozzle.
Oh, God damn it. Get in there, please. Don't you fucking even think about it,
but get in there, man. What the fuck? Somebody gave so many subs. Somebody had so many.
That's a hundred subs. I'm almost out of fucking water too. Hold on. Who just gave a hundred subs?
Austin Atlantis gave a hundred community subs. I took it. That's like a trillion dollars.
Holy shit, dude. Thanks for the hundred subs added to those. You got one. Nice.
I'm almost out of water. I'm so paranoid. Oh, that's it. All right. New strategy is go for
the one on the left first. Cause that one's the, that one's just the hardest one to get.
Start crying right now. Cry now. There's more subs. I got it. I got it. Okay. I got it.
Another 25 from Freddie Dredd. Holy shit. You guys are going fucking crazy. I got the whole
left side. I got the wrong thing selected. How does that happen? What? Huh? Did I just go through
the wall? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What? I thought you
couldn't do that. There is no wall. I thought there was a, wait, there's not a back wall.
What the fuck? I'm trying. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. There's a, there's a glass back wall. Isn't there like an invisible wall? How do you
not fly out? I, I can't believe I got the hard one too. What? There is in some places. What the
fuck? Don't miss the bus. What the hell is that? I thought, I thought I was going to just slide
down like I always do out the back. You mean you tell me I can fall out that way? I hit also. All
right. Hold on. It's all like, okay, I'm missing the bus. Yes. I, but I'm taking my eyes off the
screen. But you have to remember I'm not, I'm waiting at the bus stop and somebody's driving
by the bus stop every few minutes throwing $500 off the window. And I'm like, wow, do I get on the
bus? I got to try. Get on the bus. Hold on. Let me, I gotta get that money. Hold on. Fuck the bus.
Then like 10 more minutes go by. Like another person just like, Hey, hey buddy.
It like throws like $200 off the window. I'm just like, holy shit. That's fine. I gotta get that
money. I got people driving behind the bus. Just tossing fucking checks out of it. All right. I'm
getting on. I'm getting on. I'm getting, I can't believe I can fall in the back. Hold on. Wait a
minute. I'm so tilted from what just happened. I'm so fucking mad from being falling out the back
fucking window. I can't believe this is even possible. You can't fall out the front. Why can
you fall out the back? Let me on the bus. Oh my goodness. Why did I say I would do this level?
This is like the joke meme level that nobody does. They spend five minutes on this level. They go,
nah, I'm just going to play the fucking actual video game. I don't care who did it.
Guess what? LeBron James can dunk. I don't go, you know, I'm going to dunk first try too. Let
me get that. Give me that ball LeBron. And I go, I go to dunk on LeBron and he fucking does like
the most embarrassing, just like smash the ball out of my hand. And he, it does, it's so hard.
It does so hard that it's like, boom, boom, hits me like right in the nose. And I'm like,
oh, my nose like blows up with blood and shit. And I have to go to like the hospital.
I don't care. Wait, you met LeBron. You're getting dunked on. This is fucking so stupid.
Stop grabbing the wall. Let go of the wall. Why? What are you doing?
Okay. I figured it out. I don't do, although that was, you can fall off the fucking edge.
Don't do that. Okay. That kind of doesn't work. This is so fucking ridiculous.
It's going to work if I get it. No matter if the game is horse shit, I still made it work.
Just throws you to the right no matter what. All right. I got to get the ones on the right.
Okay. I got it. Don't fuck it up. One more. I'm preparing. Here we go.
It's not over yet. It's not over yet. It's not over yet. It's not over yet. I have to get in there.
Do it again. Do it again. Just relax. Do it again. Do it again. I don't want to, I'm holding the
ball right now. I got LeBron's in front of me and he's laughing. He's like, oh, you're going to try
it again. Yeah. In a minute. All right. Whenever you're ready, man. Whenever you're ready to go.
Wait a second. I'm just trying to figure out which way to go. No. Hey, I mean, I got like a
bunch of meetings to go to, but can you try to slam dunk already? Just shut up. I'm going. I'm
going to go when I'm ready. You know, you know who I am, right? I know who you are. All right.
Here I go. You can't slam dunk, Don. I did it. Phew. I'm glad I don't have to do that again.
He's just a guy that slam dunked LeBron. Yeah, I did. I did. I miss winked. Oh shit. I did.
And a ton of money. All right. Let me get hurt. Oh shit. I did it. I just did it again for fun.
Another one. Wait, what did it say? All right. Now I can, it's been 30 minutes. Can I actually
play the fucking game now? 10 more. Oh my, wow. How much, how much money came in? That's a lot.
Oh, we had, we had the hundred subs. We had 25 from Freddie. We had five from Labster,
10 from Javelin, a hundred dollars from Core Monster. Congrats on not beefing. 10 more from
Atlantis. You guys are fucking crazy. Thanks. That's a lot of money guys. Thank you. I want
to go over here. Did I get all eight here? No. Oh, I know. I got them all. I did get them all.
I did get them all at Gelato Beach. I remember this one. All right. Well, you can't back out
for some reason. Why can't you know back out of this menu? Press Z to see the levels you read.
Oh, imagine if your memory card got corrupt. Oh, there's a hundred coins. I don't, I'm not,
I don't need to do that. All right. I got five. We don't have the lowest. Eight at Gelato Beach.
Five. I think I have, oh, the park. I only have one at, in a park. All right. We're going to the park.
I got to go in the cannon though, right?
I don't know why they didn't add that. That should be the noise he's making.
Here we go. The beach cannons secret. It was a middle school joke. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Shut up. I'm just kidding. Shut up. I'm just kidding. All right.
What are we going? Let's get him. Pepehans. He hates me. No, I don't. How long you've been,
how long you've been watching this channel? Don't, I've already told you guys that 98%
of everything you hear on this channel is fabricated. Okay. Pick it up. Stop running
your fucking head into it, man. Pick up the bomb. That's, this game is really fun. NA aim.
Let's go. So what's in here? Wait, is this another one of those levels?
It's one of these. I do appreciate the, uh, wall paper. Okay. There we go.
I just blanked. I just like blacked out for a second. I don't know why that was. I just blacked
out. I forgot. I'm blacking out. All right. Here we go. I'm good. All right. I'm fine. This is not
that bad. Oh, kids. Where am I? What happened? Wait. Oh, I'm fine. All right. What's going on
with that fucking control scheme? All right. What the fuck's going on with this fucking control
scheme? Am I getting pushed with air? Why does this feel so strange? What's this air pushing me?
I'm being pushed in weird directions. All right. Right. When that thing go now,
I got to settle the fuck down. It's fucking air pushing me.
There's air. There's air pushing me. All right. What the fuck is going on? Why is this so strange?
There's air like moving me like left and right. All right. Break the crates is your emulator.
No, this isn't the original. You know, why would you go up there?
There's copy protection on the disk. That's weird. All right. Here we go. I'm going to count
right when the last one falls. Maybe one, two. Okay. It's two false seconds.
Here we go. And one, two, one, two. Okay. Two. Holy fuck. Holy fuck. Hey, this one's for free.
I stopped doing the TikTok thing. I don't know why I'm doing that. Turn up the game volume.
Nah. Yeah, sure. How's that? Better? Apologize. This is my red coins of the pirate ships.
Cool. Nobody has a name called tag me when Derma's upset. That's just. See, now you're just
gaming the system. Now, you know, you're just getting all these tags. The chat is devolving.
It's all right. It's all right. All right. We got to get up there. Do I ride the teacups?
That's kind of fun. Red coin. All right. Get on the pirate ship. Oh, okay. So any more red coins on
these ships? Okay. Uh, across. Oops. I hit my head. Whatever. Blue coin. I'll get it in a minute.
Nintendo is watching. Oh, well, that's good. Uh, Nintendo, when are you going to put this game
somewhere else besides a GameCube disc? It's probably one of the top three Mario games you've
made. They all they left out. Oh, well. Oh shit. I didn't. That was like, no, we, you port, no
switch port, no e-shop. Where's the GameCube e-shop? Shit. That's another question. Well,
that was still got it. And now from here, I'm going to go. Oh my God. I mean this way.
And I missed it. And I fucking missed it. How? Oh, it's, it's just exhausting.
Hold on. My hands are sweating. Do you know who would make a trillion dollars if you made a
controller? Is there like any anti-sweat controllers? All right. I mean, first,
let me stop speaking so I can play a video game. Why do these things have to be made of this hard
sweat plastic? Why can't this be made of a cloth or something? Like I want a cloth that I can change
out. Like you do your laundry, you do, I give a fucking pillowcase. Why can I, why's there no
control of pillowcase? I'm doing this so wrong. Just go across. What? I don't need, I don't need
the boats anymore. Wait, can I get in here? That's a 5,000 IQ coin. Oh, I'll get another one.
You need gamer gloves. No, but that's, that makes it worse. All right. We got a good view.
What the fuck are you doing? Get out of my way. Blue shell fucker. I hate you. Oh, fucking Nintendo
Wii, Mario Kart. It's coming for me. All right. I gotta get up there. I think I do have to go on
the, that I have to get on these and then just not miss. Can I do it from here? Hmm, maybe. Can I
walk? Hold on. I think I just do it from here. As long as I'm not stupid about this. Oh, why is
this game running at 12? Dude, your PC sucks. I'm not on the sheet. This guy move. This guy don't
move, does he? Well, shit. I have to like hover over there. Okay. We'll go back up.
Can I just shock him and then ground pound him? This camera is going to make me
throw up. Okay. Now I can get those. Or can I? I need water or else I'm not going to be able to
get up here. This is going to be bad. Okay. I think I can grab these without needing to fill water.
Let's see. Come on. Grab it. Okay. Do it again. Where are the other five coins though? All the
way up. This, this, this level might be the worst place for the camera. It's just in a building
every five seconds. God damn it. I can't see anything. Just, I want to get in the, I want to
get in the fairy go round, whatever this thing is called. Holy shit, Nintendo. I'm terribly sorry,
but this ride is currently under maintenance. Wow. Nintendo. Wow. Whatever. I don't even need to
say it. I need to get over there. I think I can just get there. Can I put you out? I got to get
rid of you. I'm trying to hold the thing down. It didn't hold it down hard enough. So I move.
It's frustrations settling in. Mad at children's games. Somebody told me I was going to get really
mad here. They were like, I can't wait until you get to level seven. Sucks. And I was like,
what is he talking about? This is Super Mario Sunshine. Grab it. I can't even be more like
your brother. He's not here right now. He's at school. All right. How do I, there's two more
coins. Where the fuck are they? Where's my, I can't spend my blue coins to get a red coin scanner
all the way up. Do I have to, I got to go over there. All right. I'm going for it. I'm going to
be smart about this though. Or are we? We'll find out. Can I punch them from below? If I, okay,
if I electrocute them and push them, can I, will they, do I get electrocuted by them if they,
if they're over me? Well, he's going to shock me, right? I thought they shocked you. All right. Now
I got to get on that thing. Pack them from below. I don't want to talk to them. They're electrified.
I didn't like that. What are your thoughts on Mario Kart 9? Um, I don't, which one is that?
There's been so many of them. All I know is Mario Kart 64, Mario Kart Wii, and then all of them
are the same game in my brain. The ninth one. Yeah, but which one is that? How many have there been?
How many Mario Karts are there? Is eight? Nine? Double dash? Yep. I know, but how many are there?
Is eight deluxe? Is 14? No, no, no, no, no, no. Mario, Mario Kart. How many Mario Karts are there?
Mario Kart 8 deluxe for the Nintendo Switch. Yeah, it is eight. I wasn't even looking at the
fucking screen again. God damn it. I'm like looking up shit on Google. How do I move this?
Can I like push this? Pull it? Can I grab this? Stomp it? Open that. Hey, I think you're in need
of a pair of my special sun shades. Oh, well then again, maybe you're not ready. You need to spend
a bit more time here. How much more time do I need to spend here? I've been here for like,
I've been here for like four days. How about you? I brought this baby to view the sunflowers,
but this looks unsafe. I didn't think Yoshis were bad creatures, that's for sure.
Wait, this is, there are actually Yoshis here? That's not a Yoshi.
That's like hermit crab. Whoa. Oh, they're draining the fertilizer from the ground.
They're drinking all the fertilizer in the water. Hey, wake up. All right, bring another one up. Back
to life. Plant, plant, plant, plant, plant. Here we go. Point, point, point. What? Fucking
speech is fucking. I hate that. Fucking speech is fucking. Nope. Don't think so. Why are you
doing this? Is one life worth more than another? I don't make the rules in Super Mario.
Nobody's dying. Don't you guys know? They're going away. They're all on vacation. Over here.
What? What happened there? Oh, you didn't spin around. All right, do it. Hey, why are you not
over here? Aha. You can't do anything about the sand. Can you? Oh, I got to be quicker than that,
huh? It's bringing you back to life. Yes. That was not even that bad. I see people on speed runs
do that. I can't do it. They do it like backwards into the thing, you know. Beat Dark Souls 3 on
stream, but you can't beat a single Mario game. I'm gonna beat, I'm beating this right now. Look,
don't you see on your screen? All right, let's move. Hurry, Mario. I can't imagine what the
poor princess is going through. Mario, please save her. Hey, Moni. Hey, you. Give me that Yoshi egg.
What the fuck? He was in my way. He was in my way. Wait, Moni's dead. Go on.
This is what was supposed to happen. Give me that fucking egg. Oh, he missed it. Good. You're just
as stupid as me. You really are a Mario clone. He's trying to hit the same jump, but can't hit it.
He's like, oh, whatever. He's just about to ride that Yoshi too. He needs bananas. I don't want
to get those. Stay right here, Yoshi. I got this. Here's your food. Ooh. You want some water?
You befriended Yoshi. Make him eat with B. Holy shit. I didn't even know Yoshi was in this game.
Yoshi's... Wait, I'm orange? Okay, so you can... What am I going to be? Juice.
Look at how long his tongue is in this game. All right, I get another one, right?
There's an egg over here. Okay, there it is.
No, that's such an old joke at this point, but it's still funny.
All right, let's go get some food. And that's... Ah, this is cool.
Whoa. Juice. What does the juice do? It's just like water. All right, let's eat a bunch of food.
All right, let's be orange. Now, where do I want to go? Anywhere, huh? Let's go back. Let's go this
way. But Yoshi can't come in here? Red coins on the water. Why can Yoshi not go in there?
Three minutes and paying attention to cutscenes. He's no dogs allowed. Yoshi's not a dog. He's a
lizard. Hey, Kazzy, thanks for the five minute resubs, Kazzy. Appreciate it. All right, so we
have to do... We have to go this way. Lizard. He's a lizard. He's a lizard. He's a lizard. Is it better?
This level. Pepe left. Do I have to do the race thing again over there? Is that what this is?
Did you do pachinko yet? Yes, I did. What's this? Collect eight coins before the timer runs out.
Well, okay. I'm pretty good at this.
Stop the car. Stop the car. Jesus, man. What are you doing? You don't go around a rotary
ten fucking times. What's wrong with you? Oh, God. It's baby Mario or baby Bowser. Wait,
there's a shine in... Wait, what? I can't believe there's a shine over there. Come here. Give me that.
Right, so I was just about to turbo... Yeah, shoot. Turbo nozzle. All right, how do I do this?
Turbo nozzle. This is a Yoshi up here. All right, there was a thing. There was a shine.
Where was it? Through these doors? There was some door I could go through. Which one?
Run just ran through doors. Is this thing fun? Holy fuck, this is kind of cool. Holy shit,
this is fucking awesome. I'm so pissed off. Another one. What the hell are we doing over here?
Wait, where is he? Where is that? Give me that turbo nozzle.
He's up. Where is he? He's like over here. Up there. Which side? This side? No, don't make me do this.
I'm sorry. Stop. Nobody say that for the rest of this room. I don't want to hear that ever again.
Is he not up here? He is up here. I need the hover. Maybe I don't.
He's blind. He's blind. He's blind. He's blind. He's blind. Found him. Really? Aha. Right in the back.
Get him. Hey, you. Get back here. How much more do I have to hit you?
Ah. Ow. Oh. Can this fucking hit him? Why is this not hitting him? Earth is happening.
Are you seriously moving all the way over there? Mom, my game's broken. I can't go this far. Shoot,
I was supposed to rocket jump. This game makes me thirsty. This game makes me want to pee.
This game makes me have to piss. It actually was the original title of the stream,
but people were upset by it, so I had to get rid of it. Damn it. Oh. All right, I made it.
Does it wink? Chain? Chomplets? Unchained. I hate this place. I hate this place. This place. I hate
this place. Why? Best level, worst level. This level sucks. Does it suck?
Um. This place looks like a modded Call of Duty Zombies level. Hey, Mister, I think you could spare
us a hand. This dear lady's pets have decided to go on a little rampage. No, no, no, no. Not
the bees. They seem to be acting normal. So we have to put out the, uh, the chomps. All right,
that's not bad. That's not bad. What's wrong with this place? They're lighting on fire again. I'm
trying, I'm preventing it from happening. Maybe I should clean the area first. Come here. Do they
have to go back in a cage or anything? Is it, is it, I'm trying to get them back in their pen or
something? Try cooling its head off. I just did. Okay. Do I have to get them all in a certain time
limit or something? How many are there? Two? Three? There's one other one right here. Okay, now what?
Ow. I, well, okay. You can, I grabbed their tails and throw them into the pens. Do I have to open
them or something? Or into the, throw them in, where's their water? Come on, come here. Go in
there. Am I killing it? Okay. I think that's what I need to do. Do the other ones. All right. Let's
go. Let's do the thing that everyone said. Do it, dude. What are you stupid idiot? Do it.
Now there's two more. I don't hate this place. Am I going to hate this place? I don't hate this
place. Wait, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here. I didn't get it. Now
stop, stop, stay right there. Don't move. Okay. One more. I just saw you. Where are you? Over here?
Right here? Right here? Like that. There you are. Come here. Come here. I used to do that all the
time versus Bowser in Mario 64. You would do that and miss and then you'd fucking fly off a cliff
and smash the controller into the ground and it would explode into like 5,000 pieces.
What? Am I saying mama? Come here. You have to go this way. All right. Got a clear shot.
Eight ball, corner pocket and go. Yeah. That was like a wicked annoying thing to say. I'm aware.
Eight ball, corner pocket. Yeah. I know that was, that was annoying, but whatever.
You guys just have no idea how exhausting it is to pretend every day. I brought this up yesterday.
It's, I'm just exhausted. What's it been an hour? God fucking tired. Remember to pretend
in every video game, one hour of pretending is actually like two to three hours of being
normal. I'm exerting 300% more mental fortitude. Man, I'm just fucking tired. Let's go back in.
Oh no, it's a race. I feel bad for the people that don't know that's a joke.
And they're just like, what the fuck, man? It's me, Paintissimo. And now listen, see that flag over
there. Hmm. That flag up there. Are you ready? Three, two, one, go. Three, two, go. Oh, I fucked
it up. I just, first time I've been on the level, guys. I don't speak cursive. Actually, cursive is
out of the, you'll be right, cursive is out like this. If I was speaking cursive, if it was out
like this, every single word, every single, everything would fall right into each other.
Every single word, there would be no beginning of any senses. That's correct. Oh, the crack's
kicking in. Crack's kicking in. Crack's kicking in. Crack's kicking in. Three, two, one, go.
Smelly a little. Kick head. Don't do that. Just run. Oh, that was not so bad. You're quick. Yes.
I suppose maybe I underestimated you a small bit. Perhaps you try again after you have practiced
more until then. Bye bye. Go to the hotel. Go to the hotel. I don't know what that is.
Don't stop spoiling the game. You're spoiling the game for me. I don't know what that is.
You just ruined it. How am I going to enjoy the game ever again now? I want to do this again.
Goopy Inferno. Oh, all the way.
No flood. Just my skills as a platform gamer. Can we talk? It's really tough being mayor,
don't you think? I've never been a mayor. I have no idea. It might be really easy for all I know.
All right. What do I got to get up there? Fine. Um, okay. Okay. Well, there's uh, all right. So
maybe I want to hear a coin. What are you going to do? Animal Crossing New Leaf. Um,
I'm just gonna play the new one. What's going on? Nintendo. Nintendo. I need you to. Thank you.
Can I get up there? Can I climb the tree? I can go over there. I'm just gonna.
I have to jump on these guy's heads. Oh, you're hurting him. So do I have to just bounce?
I don't know. That almost worked. Almost. I'm not done with this. I'm, I'm having a fun time at
face when Mario isn't there to save you because you are Mario. Who saves Mario? I mean, like,
guys, Mario is not invincible. I mean, just because he has a series of video games doesn't
mean that if he gets hit by a car, he's not going to break all of his bones and shit.
I have to bounce on these. So I'm going to try if I could do it. It'd be nice. They go all the
way over there. Right on these things. None of them are made out of water or anything.
Wink. All right. Fine. Here's water. What about down here? What's this? Well, I figured it out,
but where do I go up from here? How do I climb this up? Oh, wait, I can move this thing.
Why is it doing that? What? I rumble. I don't have any more coffee left. Disaster. Well,
I know where to go. Dude, we're going to get some fucking dunks. You know what I mean? We're
going to get the fucking dunks. Let's try this again. Watch out. You got to slam dunk on LeBron.
No, I can't. No, stop. Oh, wait, there's a coin. 46 blue coins. Nice. Again. Here we go.
Remember, there was a blue coin billionaire. What do blue coins do? Uh, I don't know. I'm
thinking you spend them on stuff. But I don't have a lot. I don't know. I didn't play this game.
Can you grab on to the- why are we- I'm trying to grab onto the- why can I not grab on?
I'm trying to just climb up to the top and just grab the top.
I have to jump off it? I can't just grab? I have to jump up into it. Shit, I just said the fucking
Voldemort name. Wait, why am I all the way back here? Oh, because I had game over.
I don't want to do that. I want to do something else. Where am I going? Where have I not done
everything? Park. Harbor. I haven't done Bianco Hills, the whole thing. You have the Yoshi.
Where the hell was the Yoshi? Over here, right? Whoa, what's up there? Wait, what's a bell?
I'm gonna clean this bell. No, I won't. All right, bell. This thing is dirty as hell. Nice.
How does one get inside? I see. I see. I gotta go in one of those things.
Whoa, right there. Can I get up there from here? Bang a left? I need to get all the way down. I
need to get up- how do I get over there? It's gonna be a weird way to get there.
All right, a bang of right? No, it's up there. I gotta use my mind's eye. All right, here's- this
is it over here. What the fuck? What's going on with this one? This funny streamer is unaware.
You think I'm funny? Thanks. Do you really? Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Funny looking. Still
counts. I gotta clean that thing. I'm going over there. All right, let's get up there.
So how do I do that? I can probably- can I just rocket jump from here?
Maybe. Is it just that simple? It might be that simple. It's so easy. That's kind of high.
You forgot to put it down. You gotta bring it down for me. Okay. All right, do I go back in the pipe?
Yeah, I'm gonna go for it. Get pineapple on roof. Get pineapple on roof. I'm up here though.
Roof, pineapple, roof, pineapple. No, I'm already up here. No, I'm not. It just put me back to the
beginning. All right, fine. Pineapple on that roof. Roof, pineapple. Sure. Tongue glasses. Roof,
pineapple first. Hold on. Important. Roof, pineapple. All right, just throw it up there.
Bounce off this guy's head. Throw it up there. All right, I can do this. Hey, you- what?
Your taste changed. Yoshi. So what was the point of me getting the Yoshi up here?
I walk somewhere with him over like the- on the tightrope. It went right through it. It went
right through the rope. Can I get up back up here? All right, pineapple. Eat the pineapple.
Eat the pineapple on the roof. You guys on drugs? Roof, pineapple. There's a roof pair.
Wait, you're talking about the- wait, that? The giant pineapple decoration? Not an actual pineapple
from like the shop. You're talking about the roof decoration. I didn't know you could eat that.
That's a decoration. That's a decoration. That's not- oh, eat the fruit on the roof.
You should have said eat the decorative pineapple. That's what you needed to say. You said eat the
pineapple on the roof. No, no, no. Eat decorative pineapple. I would have got it immediately.
Arena Beach. The manta storm. Where's Yoshi? He didn't get to come with me. It's kind of unfair.
What's going on up here? Why are you guys inside a pipe? I heard this is a great hotel. I can't
wait to see my room. What a cool looking sunset. Spectacular. Two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight. Eight coins. Good. Look at the sunset. Fine. Let's go. Uh, you probably should do something
about that. Your stairs are killing people. Uh, okay. Well, what's your problem?
Oh, please tell me my nightmare is over. You can save me. I don't know why, but just look at the
very- just look- you just look very capable. Listen, it all started around noon. This giant
manta-shaped thing showed up. It was this paper, thin, floating silhouette. It came and covered
the hotel grounds in this electric goop. Then, oh, the horror in my beautiful hotel, my poor
building. It sank in the middle of that awful ooze. Why me? I've got the staff cleaning up,
but where's my hotel? What am I supposed to do? I can't just sit back and, uh, it's- it's back.
That gossamer ghoul. Do something. Holy shit. This thing's pretty big. This song's kind of banging.
All right, what- can I shoot it? You can clean it. It's cleanable. Here it comes. Okay, what does
that mean? Get out of the water, Mario. Mario, don't you know? This is shut- spraying the water
causes it to divide. Is it- is this thing even here? I tell you, this game is Spining of Isaac.
This whole game is Spining of Isaac. All right, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump. Out,
out, out, out, out, out. Get coins. Save from the trees. God. All right, we're getting crunches.
Yeah, we're getting crunchies. I don't know why. All right, where is he? There you are. They're all
stuck on- they're all stuck on the top of that thing. God. I need water. Oh my god, the crunches.
I gotta turn it down. I can't hear these crunches, man. Give me that shit. Where's the water?
They are dividing into smaller units. I know. Die! Wait, are they co- are they going back together
again? They're reconnecting, aren't they? Give me that. I need more coins. Trees. Get out of the
water, Mario. I need that tree. All right, let me get a look. No, no, they're everywhere.
This is- holy shit. Get to work. I've- oh no. Okay, I'm gonna start- I'm gonna start over here.
Come on. They're all in the ocean over here. Okay, here we go. Over here. I gotta get in there. Oh,
look at that shit. All right, we're doing good. Not bad. I'm not breaking these boxes. Holy shit.
Now they're all after you. What? Oh my- get in the tree, Mario. Mario, get in a tree.
Just spray from afar. It's working. All right, back to the ocean. Ow, you fucker.
Okay, easy, easy. That was crazy. All right, now turn the volume back up. Now that we can actually
hear. It's not crunchy audio. You did it. I did. Yeah. That was kind of fun. I'm just not even
gonna look. Should I just throw it behind me? I mean, I'm like half court. Let me just like-
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey, look at this. Look at this shit. Look at this. You ready? Okay, there.
Okay. Wait, you didn't hear it? But it didn't swish? It's a swish.
It bounced. I missed. I missed each time. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Redo, redo, redo. That means I'm-
Oh god damn it. Shit, it wasn't even that fucking hard.
I just got in. It doesn't go in and come out. No, I want- Fuck man, why is it so hard to find this?
Basketball swish. Why is this so difficult to get this? Somebody make this video and you'll get
like 10,000 views. Just make a swish sound if I put it on YouTube. You'll get like 100,000 views.
Okay, that finally found it. Never mind. Thanks for uploading that. God damn it. I'm holding on
to this. I don't fucking care. I'm holding on to that. Right. Oh, here's a swish. It was a
basketball fucking bouncing and hitting a rim and shit. Because I can't hear it. I just have-
Right now I have the game audio in my ears. I can't have both because the way that it's-
the game is captured. Whatever. All right, let's go in the hotel. It's Mario, right? Yeah, Mario.
Listen, I have a feeling you can help me out again. Do the hotel as well. It's full of
ghosts. Is this a Mario? Wait, is this Luigi's Mansion tie-in or something?
So we- well, could you maybe look- just come inside. I can tell you're a miracle worker.
Don't be so modest. When did the original Luigi's Mansion come on? They turn into platforms. Oh boy.
This is going to be interesting. The place looks familiar. This is the Mario 64 place.
This looks just like it. Hey, can I go in here? Do I need the thing to run through
the doors? Maybe I should talk to the guy first. Hold on. Fire. Wait, I can actually open the doors.
Nope. You're invading somebody's privacy. There's nobody in this hotel. I'm the cleaning person.
None of these open. All right, dude. Well, I can't help you. You gotta help me.
Give me the key. At this rate, I'll never get back home. Can you do something, please, Mario?
Well, I'll try. No guarantees. Toilet? Oh, they're dirty toilets. Wait, these are not dirty toilets.
They just look like that. Oh, what's this in here?
Shit decal. This place looks like a fucking bowling alley. Why? No, it doesn't.
Um, all right. What do I do here? Is it like a fire flower or something?
Do we go up higher? Okay, well, we go higher. Oh, there's another. Okay. Well, it was confusing.
That should not be in the game. That shouldn't be in the game. That's like unfair and it messes you
up and makes you think that there's coins and shit. That's unfair. They should take this out
of the game. Are they all closed? Oh, look, it's Pac-Man. Hold on. Anything else over here?
Oh, you have that in you though. Doesn't that mean you have that? That's so joked. I got joked.
Well, let's go in. See what happens. Three, two, one. Here we go. The secret level. Oh, great. This is
gonna be fun. I love the background. That's the kind of shit that I want in my office. Those lights.
What are they called? Uh, light brights. Light bright. Oh, I can break these. I gotta be careful.
I don't want to break too many of them. What's the watermelon for? I think I may have just made a
mistake. No, I'm okay, right? Bounce and just make it take us low. Okay, that's sand. Uh, it's gonna
fall. Let's go. Waiting too long. You're probably asking yourself, why are you leaving that?
Because I could have, see, I could have been bad. Uh, which way? Okay, there's the psycho way.
I'm thinking about going the psycho route. Psycho route is get to the second one here and then jump
all the way over to the right side. I'm doing the psycho route. I almost had it. It was close. It
just went a little too far. Oh, I can get it. I can get the psycho route. I can do this an
infinite amount of times though. That's the one good thing. Get that camera in a good spot.
All right, so just, but, uh, I can't reach that. That platform, that move? That shit move?
That shit moves, right? I fucking seriously, I went like a tiny bit too far. I was trying to
be so slow with it and you pressed a stick a tenth of a centimeter and come on. It was such a pain
in the ass to get over there with the psycho route. Saved it. I almost fucked it up. All right,
there we go. All right, I just have to jump. Don't walk over it. If you walk over it,
you go all the way over the edge. Just be careful. Get that. Holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit.
I'm getting tuber. Sometimes it just comes out. I have, you have to like, it's okay. You know,
when they tell you, when, when you fight any fighter, like the karate or a taekwondo or
something, don't they say you need to expel air and force out of you? You know, you have to like,
the same thing is with video games. When you throw a punch in karate, you need to
exhale. Same thing when you're playing a game, you want to make a jump. That's correct. Tennis
is another one. Yeah, this is true. This is true statement. I'm not making that up.
Pitchers do it too. Yeah. And so don't streamers. Oh, I hurt my chest. Streaming is karate. No,
no, no, excuse me. That's a false. That's, that is what we call a false equivalency.
I never said that. I didn't even read what he said. I lost it when I heard this was a four star
resort. I mean, come on water damage in the restrooms. That is so low class. It's not some
weight. What's this guy doing? Ooh, pineapple. My apologies, but the casino, excuse me. What would
the word something about that words? Exciting me is not open for business quite yet. I need
a pineapple. Uh, these free pineapple, pineapple, pineapple, pineapple, no pineapples over there.
No, let's go upstairs. This level is unironically so good. It's, it's pretty fun. I don't, I don't
mind. I miss Lammy. Like I'm Jammer Lammy. You miss I'm Jammer Lammy. I beat the game
multiple times at coin. I'm leaving it for later. Where's the pineapple? Oh shit. Nice open free.
This is free. This shit's just for free. Hey, that sparkle, could it be a shine sprite? Um,
yeah, move out of the way. Hey you, no one in the pool without proper swimwear. I mean, what was
that? Hello? I get a really creepy vibe from this weird painting, but you want to know what I find
even creepier than that? Imagining how you got in here. You need pineapples? Fucking Nintendo.
Uh, oh, okay. Creepy. Creepy. Cool. Uh, hi guys. Eek. What's wrong? The coin's fake. It's not even
moving. That's a bad, terrible. I knew it. See? I'll get it. Stop running around. I want to talk to
you. Stop running around. Suddenly a ghost came out of the closet. I'll handle it. Double tap
right there. All right. Anything else in here? What about over there? Make the picture. All right.
What about you? Everybody has like their own personal pool. Do something about these ghosts
and get out of my room, you weirdo. Oh shit. There we go. Where the fuck am I? This is ridiculous.
This is crazy. I like this level. It's fun. I think the bed's made out of ghost. Wait a minute.
Where did you come from? I'm calling for help. Oh, but hold on. Uh, hi. Another room, I guess.
Streamer wet the bed. I did not. Well, where did I put that thing? Hey, have you seen a pineapple
anywhere around here? Let's look. Pineapples? Anywhere in here? Pineapple? I don't see a
pineapple in here. Hey, whatever. It's super coin. Yeah. All right. Hold on. Do you have
pineapple? Hey, found a, uh, another room. Cool. I found a pineapple. Nice. Cool.
It's a friend. It's just for fun. Pineapple. How do I move this guy out of the way?
Oh, there's more than one pineapple here. There's pineapples everywhere.
Is it going to eventually work? Can I open the door? Is door locked? Wait, what? Wait, what?
What? What? What? Why is the door locked behind me? Why? Why would the door lock behind me?
Are you kidding me? Oh my God. Oh, the door locked behind you. Oh, for the love of fucking God,
I have to do this whole thing again. Mario, you're a moron. Make sure to lock the door behind you
from the inside, Mario. From the inside. Yeah. Good. How do we trust you with all this bullshit?
Get out of my way. Okay. Give me a pineapple. Okay. Got a pineapple. Excuse me. Bye. Here you go.
Oh, Yoshi. Make them pay. All right. I got Yoshi. Now we go up. We eat the ghost in front of the
door. I guarantee it. If that's not what I have to do, I will... Why is this door open? Oh, hi there.
My door's open and there's nothing to be suspicious of. How about a game of Jax? Ha ha ha. I thought
they were ghosts. Oh, sorry. Oh, yeah, right. What are you doing up here? All these ghosts
are causing us trouble. They're everywhere. Why can't someone come along and suck them up
with a vacuum? Why are you looking at me like that? Yoshi is just so good. What a little good boy.
You know what I mean? I'm going to get lost up here. That's a guarantee. He didn't get the coin.
Sorry. What does it take for Yoshi to die? Yoshi doesn't just die, right? You run out of juice.
Is that for real? What? Eat him. Okay. What the hell am I... I think everything's clear.
Can I go in the middle somehow? He's dying. Oh, he is. Of course I get stuck in the door. Okay.
I need another pineapple. Wait. It might not be a pineapple. Check. It is a pineapple. Come on.
I got to unlock the pineapple. This should be a banana at this point. I don't need him anymore?
All right. I guess I did clear it all. What's the goal though? What am I trying to get to?
Oh, look at this. Hey, remember me? Pineapple. What was the point of this? Oh, okay. I need a
Yoshi. Please don't... Is that still there? Don't disappear. It doesn't disappear, right? Fruit
doesn't disappear. It stays. Come here. Let's go. All right. Eat a bunch of fruit. Let's move.
How come Yoshi doesn't die in that water? What's up with that? It's too shallow. If you step into an
inch of water with Yoshi on the beach, he dies. Is he a slug? I don't understand. Salt water?
Kill you. So, we got a... There's a blue... The blue sofa looks suspicious. Doesn't it? Nintendo.
What's the point of any of this? The door? The crack that I'm missing? I think so. Or the walls.
Anything on the walls? That's it. Okay. Well, can I go back up? Can I just leave? Throw the door.
Can't open? We need to go back up. Is there another... I think there's another tile thing.
Get in there. I don't know how that's possible to fall. Like, I'm gonna buy a lottery ticket
tonight. Okay. Is... Over there. Is there a crack tile over there? Yep. And I'm seeing quite a few
Pogchamps in the chat, but I need to correct you. I gotta have... I'm gonna cloud this because I
should. In the time it took me just to do that, I could have walked around the whole level two or
three times. Take that. Hey, have you lost your mind? You can't just barge into a lady's room.
It's just not done. Get out. Shoo, shoo. What's that? Anything in here? Paintings? Yep. Anything
else? You wanted me to leave, lady? Are you sure you didn't want me to exorcist Puke around your
whole hotel room? Oh, sorry. What's this charge of $750? Well, there was exorcist Puke all over
your room, ma'am. You don't understand. I didn't do that. A strange little man with a mustache
thrown in on a dinosaur and he puked all over the place. Okay, lady. Just pay the fucking deposit,
please. No, I'm not crazy. It happened. Am I missing something? Wait, like up here?
I'm back. What was it? Nothing down there? There has to be something down here. What would be the
point of you coming down here? Just don't. Blue coin? Fuck. All right. Is there another tile that
I didn't do? Ah, over there. Fruit fly brain. Fruit flies are for their size. The electrons
and neutrons in their brains are actually a thousand times their body weight. So if I
am a scaled up fruit fly, then see, that's a mistake on your part. Ended up back down here.
Okay. Did I go there? Is there one over there? There is. Wait, yeah. If I was a scaled up fruit
fly, you guys, I would be able to control shit with my brain and be able to move objects with
my thoughts. You think I'm that intelligent? You're flattering me, but thank you. I got it.
You're giving flies way too much credit. Why does it still want me to go that way?
I'm going in there. It so badly wants me to be over there. Have I done almost everything here?
Six. The shell's secret. I see flies move stuff with their brain all the time.
I've got to get in the shell. Oh yes. Oh yes. I don't need to listen to that. I know what to do.
This place is cool. I like this place. This level is pretty pog. Shut up. Shut up.
I, I, you, you can do it. I can't do it though. I can't, I can't say that. You can say that. I
can't. Am I your parents? I've got to go in there. Oh shit. Fucking Nintendo.
All right. I'm at about enough of this. I'm trying to skip this part. Wall jump.
Uh, whatever. Don't talk about that. I think I can just make, I'm just going over here.
Right. Can I make this? I got to go over there. Uh, I'm going up a little higher. What's this?
A yellow button. Press it. I don't, I don't care. Uh, okay. I got to get over. Can I land on one of
these, uh, ropes? I need to go from here to there. I got to go the other way. I need water too. Can I
can I? All right. Go water. All right. Let's go. People just like, oh, he fell again. No,
that was intentional. It was an intentional fall. We're going to go with that way.
Just walk. Just walk. Camera is, why are you doing this? Stop moving around.
Kill this thing. Oh my God. What's going on? Get off me. Get off me. Get off of me. Why is it on me?
Please let on something. Please let on something. Please let on something. Please let.
So I'm going to move over here and we'll go from here. I did it.
Doesn't look that bad until you get up. Where am I? Seven lives by the way. Be careful. Oh,
I could have just jumped off. Is there a one up anywhere? All right. This doesn't push you off.
I got another whole another rotation. No, I got to be on this end.
No, I got to be on this end. I got to be on this end now. Okay. And then, right. Okay.
I got scared. We ran into the wall and got scared. I didn't want to press jump again.
Karma, please hit the nails. Does that do anything? I'm gonna laugh my ass off if this
makes a bridge over here. So if I, am I going to get a one up from doing this?
That would be really, really annoying if I did. It's just two coins. I'm not doing that again.
There. I did it. I don't have to do that ever again. All right. Let's try this again. No
hesitation. No hesitation. Just go. Ready? And now I'm going to do it right now. And here we go.
You missed nails. I'm not going for nails. This is not nails percent. What is this I'm going to do?
Run up this? Um, I can slide. Run up? Am I sliding off of this thing? Can you slide? Let's test it.
You slide off. You slide off. Um, okay. Did the wall, I have to, you have to wall jump off the wall.
Or can I run across? Do I have to wall jump and then into the, can I just jump over?
I mean, the camera zoomed right up my ass. So I couldn't tell what the fuck I was going.
No, I don't care about the nails.
Fuck the nails. Fuck the nails. Fuck the, I don't care about the nails. The nails can go to hell.
Okay. I'm not touching a nail for the rest of my life. Even in my own home construction projects.
I'm never going to use one. I'm not going to pick my hammer. I'm not never hammering a nail in.
I got here so quickly too. I was like so focused. Hammer, you missed the nails.
How's about that? I almost jumped off.
I almost jumped off. I would have been, I would have taken a, I would have gone BRB.
I would not have sat here for that. I would, I didn't, I wouldn't even want to see the chat.
I would leave for 10 minutes. All right. Stop zooming in. Okay. So if I just run up and jump,
just go fuck it. Go. Holy shit. Okay. How we go up and then shit.
Okay. So I have to wall jump off here.
Holy motherfucker. Oh, that was very, very bad, but I did it correct somehow. I don't,
that was incorrect. So wait, left wall into back wall or back wall into,
left wall into back wall, I think. Right. Or back wall into left wall or just back wall into,
just go. I landed on an invisible ground.
This one's moving too fast. Look at how fast it's going.
What the fuck? Okay. Now we just jump onto the, just don't, just forget about that. The ground
is moving. That doesn't matter. You got to do a, oh, I feel so bad. I feel so bad right now.
You know what I mean? Like I just, I, I feel just, I just feel very bad because that's so,
oh, I, I have to do it again. Oh, I feel, I feel very bad. Oh, it's okay. I'll get it.
Okay. You have to do a slide, a side jump onto it because you can't make it. Oh,
you may have hit the nail too. And then I was just, you've not hit the nail. Fuck.
Okay. Here we go. And sometimes the side jump, I can't get that shit to work.
Sorry. I just had to, there was just a, I just had to let some air out of a balloon for a second.
I thought I had it. Oh, you got, it's like, look, if you give up a home run,
you got to pitch the next inning. You know what I mean? If you give up a fucking grand slam,
you can't just like be like, I gave him a grand slam. I'm going to give up every grand slam.
Every hit is going to be a grand slam. You got to, you got to get out of your head. Here we go.
What was that face? Now I'm just rushing. It's such a far away to get up there.
Grand slam. Here. Boom. Here. Double.
Oh, I had it. I had it. I did it. Like, I had like, it's like, you're waking up from a nightmare.
You don't even mean like you missed the last jump. It's like a nightmare. Wait. Okay. This is not
that bad. Getting up here. It's when they start turning on you. You lose them to a kid's game.
That's fine. I'm okay with that.
I'm landing on you. Panic jump. It was right on the edge. I thought, why would you jump? I just
thought I was, I don't know. I don't know. That's why I need a boat flex connected to my fucking
thumb. Oh man. Oh, it's all over from here. Oh, damn it. I'm so, I keep, you know, okay,
you don't keep seeing it in your head. Like I just, I saw the last thing and now I got to run
up that the last one. Oh, I may never see that again. I got so close. And what happened there,
sir? What was that? I hit my fucking head on the ceiling. Oh, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep,
I ain't doing that. I don't care. I'm going to do Bianco Cove. Fuck that, man. Let's get him.
Rage quit? No, I didn't rage quit. I'm still in the game. Get back here. See, that's the part
of the game that I like. You know, the kid shit. Oh no, ouchies. Like, look out, he's jumping.
Like Rube Goldberg machine Mario levels. I mean, I'm not into them at the moment.
Where'd he go? Yep. And you're the expert. This is a telltale game. What is this image?
Okay, that is just a screen grab of me going like this. That's what I, it's still the worst joke.
Yeah, I know. I'm completely and totally aware of it. I know it's the worst. Trust me when I say
I'm very, oh, we have a Yoshi. Where's the pineapple? What is going on? What? Oh, sorry.
I have autoplay on. Audio jungle. What's it doing? Audio jungle. Audio jungle. Turn it off. It's off.
I turned it off. I need a pineapple. Anybody got a pineapple around here? We just got a pineapple.
I need one. Very, very, very, very badly. Put it back on. All right. Let's see what we get
for autoplay for woosh sound effects. There you go. I can't hear them. So you tell me. I have no idea.
Pineapple anywhere. So what is this? Red coins? Nah, I'm fucked this. I'm out of here.
All right. Wait a minute. I want to, let me, I'm going to go back to this town here. This place.
I don't know. I can't hear any of these. I can just see that they're titled. The runaway Ferris wheel.
Turbo stop. It went to a political podcast. This thing's going too fast. It's going way too fast.
This is too fast. Why are these? This is called bad joke. Bad joke. It knows. It knows. It's self-aware.
I just can see the titles. I don't even know what's playing. We're going to get so many of these.
I just water just hit me in the mouth. How I just spit in the air. I spit in the fucking air and it
landed back in my mouth. That's what happened. That's it. That just happened. There's no water
in the air. Las Vegas missed one. All right. We're going to get up to the, uh, the teacups
or whatever the hell it is. There we go. All right. Up to the teacups. Oh, pineapple. All right.
That's where the pineapple is. Remember that. Remember where the pineapple is.
Dude, we're getting fucked up here. Where are those? Where are the teacups?
I just dropped my fucking Wemo.
That one was intentional. I got that one. I got, I got that one in the bag. I got that one in the
bag. All right. What do I do? How do I stop this? How do I stop this? Oh, there's a guy down there.
Oh, no one can ride the first wheel. This is so lame. When is it going to be fixed?
As you can see, it just spins and spins and spins. Sorry, but this ride is not working well at the
moment. Well,
Did I get hit by this? There's a turtle up here.
And they had to hire a new one.
I have to jump over the, I can't, can I not just, can I seriously not grab this?
I have to be able to touch it, right? 20 minutes later. Six hours later. Several bad puns later.
One hour later. Two hours later. Three hours later.
I gotta go the other way.
Okay, turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off.
Turn it off. Turn it off. What? Or what happened?
Okay.
You
It's funnier than you are
Yeah, it's what I could shake my keys in the camera, too
You want me to shake my fucking keys into the webcam? All right, I gotta go. I'm gonna go all the way around
It's all me it's all me
Okay, I can't I'm not playing this
Not playing this this is just a bunch of this then this is titled this is title sound effects pack number five
50 non copyright sound effects good for improving your YouTube videos. How is Mario? I
Found I gotta get up here. I have to get up here. I
Found it
Kill
There it is
No wrong button. Fuck. Can I not fill it?
No, no, no back back back back back back back back back back back back back back
Grab this please. Oh my god
Okay, I'm I have to go to the bathroom I have to go to the bathroom I gotta go I have to go to the bathroom
I have to go to the bathroom. I have to go to the bathroom
And I'm fucking coming back and I'm gonna I'm gonna read I'm gonna get my stream back together
I'm gonna get my fucking screen back together because it's off the rails right now and I have to get it back
The broadcast has eaten crack at this point
No, I didn't I didn't just shut up my computer I didn't you know, I'm still here
It's a bunch of people's freaked out
Grab it. Okay, I got it. I
Swear to God, it's be you fucking moron
I'm going to the bathroom
I'm
Have to go now. I have to go now. I have to go now. I'm gonna go now. I'll see you guys
I'm gonna pee I'm gonna go pee. I'll be right back
You
Okay, I'm ready to play Super Mario Sunshine again
Bounds are gonna be off. I'm going to the runaway Ferris wheel as you see on your screen. We've got to catch that Ferris wheel
That first wheel guys
Okay, I got I got it out of I try to get it out of my system downstairs I got out some some drink
I just relaxed for a minute. I got a little bit of water on my face and I looked in the mirror and I was like
Okay, like let's go. Let's go back to normal. Let's play the game that I'm supposed to I'm supposed to be playing and focusing on
That's Mario sunshine
Hey
You don't know normal like I can pretend to be normal at least like once a month. I break this
All right. I want to let go. Okay now don't screw it up
Watch one of these clips
Is there a better way there is a better way to do this
Let me talk to you first
Watch the spot. Let me just hope FBI. What is it? SpongeBob narrator? Hold on. I have to change my
Like it hit by this there's a turtle up here
Help a clock. All right
All right, that's what they were laughing at that I could see some of the titles but I couldn't hear what they were
Twitch account or something
He got into the discord. He just kind of screaming. All right. Okay, I gotta get back to this. We're going back to Mario sunshine
All right, I gotta go I'm gonna go all the way
No, okay, we're going back to normal I need to go back to my one more one more one more
Oh
What last one then I'm gonna play the video game
I
Okay, last one this hurts German stop it went to a political podcast
What
Drop the Wiimote. Yeah, I saw this one queuing up. Let's see. I just dropped my fucking name up. Ah
I'm gonna this hurts my fucking chest and stomach killing me right now
Like that, I can't I it's unhealthy for me to like laugh like this right now. Oh
Okay, this one's the best
That's the best one by far by far
In the game I just okay I just unplugged my DVI cable accidentally
Okay, let's fucking go I have to play the game
Oh shit, this is timer. Let me very Phil. I'm gonna climb over this place
Okay
Jingle keys now jingle keys now. I can't wait. I need to cool down for a minute. That's to be a cool down period
Wait, what the fuck? That was just I was kind of misleading to my brain. I'm
He's he's he's no, I can't let me leave let me get to like like another star first
Just wait till a little bit later
My rib cage is gonna explode if I laugh any harder
All right. So the problem was what ago and I gotta go this way
No, I gotta go this way
I gotta go the other side now and knock him off. Ah
What was that son, I don't know I wasn't paying 100% attention I
Gotta go around and kill the other guy
This was a Trey Parker. It might have been it was the self
Holy shit. Oh
My stuff I gotta move
You're gonna drop viewers, that's okay. It's alright. It's a home man. Fuck
I'm like, I'm so fucked up right now. God damn it. I gotta go
All right, don't fall. All right, I killed two of them
I have enough room to go this way and then why I got stuck on the other one
So now if I go like this
They come up I go up
Nope, I go like this which then puts me around this way, right?
Nick Nickelodeon
Nickelodeon not Nintendo. No
Nintendo what the fuck not Nickelodeon
We're playing Nickelodeon sound effects today
Move them. Okay, they're all dead. Now I go like this Nintendo, please
Stop. I just I'm just gonna jump it. Okay. No, I'm not. I think I can I just gonna go I just have to
There and then it's is it it's a right I press a not B a right day a a a
Get out of here. Oh my god
Ray, all right. Where now? What is it on top of me? Where is it? I don't want to die. Don't die
Shit I wasn't even looking
What is this? It's kind of far away
Fuck it. I need to get out of here. I gotta ride the roller coaster. All right ride it. Oh, I'm gonna die from this one. Oh
Man, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead
No, I'm fine. See look you can get on now
Then we can run yes, they can just jump from here. I know it seems so I'm so panicky because I have two hearts
And I laughed out like 500 packs of cigarettes like I've smoked 500 packs of cigarettes
I'm gonna get points. How could this be a Super Mario level? There's no coins anywhere. Where are the coins?
There's no coins anywhere not a single coin
You come here probably have one you got him three hours ago. I jump on this guy's head
Give me a coin. Oh my you've got to be kidding me
None of you have a coin the big one will have like three has to be right
Well, it's a bit. All right, that's good enough. Okay. Now we don't have to hear the alarm sound anymore
All right. I have to climb this again. Don't I?
first of all, I
Don't have to do
What's the best way to just just to do where I was before I just go into one that's open
I
Just jumped into an open one, which one of these how many this is gonna be really hard to do this
I'm trying to get on top of the when I press right trigger
The camera is lost 45% of the time the worst enemy Mario sunshine
Fucking Nickelodeon get on top so you can jump down. That's where I was going. Everybody said don't go that way
I was getting screamed at I was going the other way. I was gonna climb up
All right, that I'm just going the other way. How the fuck did that happen? I don't understand. I
Can't you can't wall jump from there. It don't work. Okay
Get me the fuck up here for the love of God
All right
Shut your car door. Just hold on a second and I don't think I supposed to be doing it like this
Salvaged take your keys out of the ignition. What's your damn seat belt on? Don't drive around with a seat belt. What are you fucking nuts and
Again
Yoshi go round secret, uh, what's the Yoshi go around?
The entrance is yeah. Yeah keys keys keys. No, no, no, no
All right, so what's where's the secret
You know where it is look at that only the orange Yoshi on the ride disappeared, what does it mean mister?
Well, that would mean I probably need to come over here with an orange Yoshi
Cool, but where is it any Yoshi?
Wrong idiot wrong idiot wrong idiot. Whoa, that was a blue coin
Wrong lie. You lied to me, but you don't like it
God call it. I got it. I said
Um, yeah, Daffy laffy from grandma's too
I mean, where's a Yoshi? I need a pineapple. I know where the pineapple is, but where's a Yoshi egg?
When I see a Yoshi egg in here somewhere
At the very beginning is it at least I killed that guy and I'm both
No, it's definitely no. I can't go back. What about around the water?
Oh
He's redeemed shit. That's a banana. Chad is actually the baby now. They want the keys. I
Told you there it is. What do you want? You want a
Alright a pair. I guess I want those over here
keys keys keys keys keys
Give us keys right now
No, you're not getting the keys
No keys, you're not getting them now. I have to run around like a dickhead and look for this one fruit on this whole map
It's in here in this pool or something. No, that's a banana
That's in a really weird place
I thought I would not have come here. We're gonna make you orange. You are orange already. Let's go
He didn't die from the other water. That was shallow. What now I need I know what that is
So if it's all water, why can he stand in the pools?
I mean, that's not shallow. It goes up to my fucking knees as Mario and he's like three and a half feet tall
Where's this fruit? It was like on this tree
Okay
You fucking little gremlin
You are taller than me and you can't stand in
That water I don't are you just are you going in head first and holding your head underwater?
Nice pink. This is great. How do I make it? I could eat that
All right, you're now orange
Please don't go over there. Don't go over there. Watch out
It's knee-deep water Yoshi. Don't go over there. He's made out of cotton candy
Yeah, okay
Doesn't matter doesn't matter which one I start on does it probably not it's just Frogger. Is it Frogger? It is Frogger, isn't it?
What the hell wait, okay, holy shit, I didn't mean to do that the camera just fucked me up
Okay, oh it moves I know what to do. Oh
My god, I can't believe it. I can't fucking believe it. I can't believe it
Well, I knew what exactly it was. Well, I don't even need to why did I even do that?
I just freaked the fuck out for no reason. There was no free. I'll never do these
I'm never gonna be able to do any of these fucking the depth perception. Just keep the camera here at all times
Don't ever move it. There's no reason to ever move the camera from here like fucking Diablo
I'm in trouble. Oh my no, no, no, I
Had it be to fuck this
Fuck it. Give me a break. Ah
Climb it. Okay. I'm pressing the up button you fucker. That was the wrong thing to jump on
Can I compensate this? Okay. We're good. We're okay, right?
We're okay. We're fine. Just don't move. What do I do? We're good. This is the one
No, it's not. It's this one. We're good. Now this time don't be a fucking idiot
Do it right do it right no snow don't jump over there do it right do it right we're okay
We're okay. Everything's okay. We're okay
Everything's fine. We're okay. We're gonna be fine
You
Don't have to rush you don't a you're not you're not a you have to go that fast man. I'm so incapable
You don't have to go that fast
I gotta go as fast as I can but it don't drop right now. Oh, I'm so bad at fucking video games of Mario, especially
If my patience is out of a fucking goddamn
Love weasel, you know what I mean? Like if I'm gonna I'm just gonna come trying to steal your eggs
And even if there's like 40 spiders in there, I'm just going to do eggs. I idiot why why why guys?
Um, I fell I didn't fall
Okay, so I don't understand what the fuck I'm doing. Oh, I know what it was. Sorry. Sometimes I forget
people holding their foot down on the gas till it hits the bottom of their car and
Flying by at 90 miles per hour. It's a little distracting
Sometimes I forget
Sorry, like pushing your gas down until you you hit the bottom of the car. Oh
Safe I did this the first time and now I'm so anxious. I can't fucking do it again
Every time what am I doing? That's so wrong. It's gotta be a side flip. I didn't do a side flip first time. I did it
Hey, okay
You fucking weirdo. It's time for you to stop being such a weirdo and do this
You fucking weirdo. Oh my god
So misleading long jump that doesn't exist in Mario Sunshine. They deleted it from the game
Shit your diaper. Hurry up. That's the blue button to leap
What that's not true. Is that a lie?
They like wait, is that a lie? That's not a lie Z
That's not Z. Is it? No, it's not. No, you got to just go right at the top. I gotta count. Here we go
I'm gonna count ready
One one two
Three it takes like three full seconds to get to the top. Here we go. Fucking weirdo. Don't worry. That wasn't embarrassing Jeremy
It's a don't it's okay. I had a diaper full of slime like three months ago. It's alright
I think I'll be fine
Five months whatever it was shadow Mario in the park. This one's kind of just for free isn't it?
Here he comes. Have you ever grown a beard? I physically can't do it. I don't have enough hair
That makes any sense. I don't have enough hair. It grows out like straw
Darn it. I'll remember this
No, I can kind of grow but it's blonde
so
Like here look, I'll show you but for instance, I'm gonna get I'm getting a little close just let you know. Let's see
It's all the black there's tons of blonde hair in here that you can't really see
so like
It looks weird because there's a ton of blonde hair in there
It's like black and blonde
You
Is weird is weird and even if I do grow this out it looks like
It just it doesn't look it's not you don't want it like I don't want it on my face
I like having a little bit
Maybe after a few days of shaving. I think it looks okay. But once you go four or five six days after shaving I
Look like I look like a fucking mutant or something. I look horrible
Okay, what what's left what's left in this video game only three at the Sienna
Serena Beach
three eight
five
Two at Pianta Village. Oh, yeah, that one sucks
What the airstrip? Holy wait, I've only gotten one from the airstrip only ones really is there only one there?
There's only one okay. I was gonna say holy shit. That's kind of bad
I'm gonna go to the beach. This one is the one with the house, right or I could go to the harbor
Yeah, I'm gonna go to Rico Harbor. It's two or three there that I can get
Well, I haven't been there in a long time. I don't remember where the hell it is
This one right here
No
Which one is this one?
Where's that coin pop up? Oh, okay. I've 54 coins
What do I spend these in the hut? I hear a star
How do I hear a star? Oh shit. Okay here I can get this
All right, you got it, right? I got 55 of these things. All right to go to the hut
Like the marketplace is there somebody at the market or something?
boathouse
across from the cannon across from the cannon across from the cannon
Down here and over there over here. It was in wait in front of me
In front like what like in right in front of me?
Literally like literally right in front of me turn around I
dig right here
Like this guy
wrong
spot with the M
Behind you am I getting fucked with right now people about people
There's people trying to tell me where to go and the people telling me the wrong way, right?
Look to the left
This is so much information flooding the chat right now
Rico Harbor building now. It's on the pier
Right here
Well, you can even you can go in this building
Okay
It's up my ass and around the corner
See when people say suit like that and that's like what I see and then I see left
Remember that there's a stream delay where you're getting what I do
Five to eight seconds after I do it
So when I turn left to look left and you say left
I did that five and a half six six seconds ago
And then by the time you say it's right in front of you
I'm actually looking at where the boat was because if five seconds have to go by
Wait ten blue coins
Let's go five shines
I've been hoarding these. Yeah, let's go. No refunds. Wait, should I not do this? It's two seconds ready?
I wonder if I'm going to say one right now
Six seconds. That was six seconds before I saw one in chat ready. Let's do it again on camera. So ready?
I want you to say
I'm gonna say a word and you have to say the second you see my mouth moving
point six seconds
That was five point like eight seconds time it on stream. How would I do that?
47 stars
Congratulations, they do nothing
Pull up a clock that how is that gonna do anything?
It's whatever you see I could have a clock that's counting down and you would get the countdown five seconds after I start the countdown
Put chat on screen. I
That's I don't know. I'm busy
Red coins in the water at Rico Harbor. All right, I'd rage quit this one. I'm back
I have to get perfect timing here ready. Nope. I like caravans of red ones. Okay. We're good. Okay
I'm back. We're gonna get it
Holy shit. This thing is hard to control. I got time but damn this is okay. This is hard
This is very hard to control
Use the middle squid
Wait, I thought I was getting I wasn't getting lied to yesterday
So I have people who actually you really were going faster or slower
Holy fuck. I thought everyone was just making that up. I thought people were just making that up
Yeah, I could ever tell I could ever tell who knows who knows what's what's accurate and wasn't accurate
I don't know. I could I could be you guys could just messing with me. Oh
Okay, we're holy shit. How am I still alive?
Mario Mario fix the camera Mario Mario
This is a great music video you're making but I would appreciate if I could get a better view of the of the game
Guaranteed you will not finish this level. Oh, yeah
Guthrie one three three seven write that name down. They're getting this up like in a few months if I feel like it
Guaranteed follow the yellow brick road. Where's six? There's one in the air somewhere. Where is it?
Right there. There's one in the air right here. I got a minute. I have a full minute guys. It'll be alright. I
Swear to okay. It's almost like it's almost like this like an evil part of my brain that
Magnetizes me to do stupid things like I it's like hubris. You know what I mean?
It's like I'm magnetized to screw something up because I just told you that I was doing fine
evil shadow
audios desync
Like I just need to stop talking about how things I'm doing are going
Like when I'm cooking this hamburger sure does look like it's medium rare medium. Well, well
Why is there a fire here now? Well, I burnt it. I burnt it. What's that smell stink smells like smoke. Oh
shit
Okay, like I gotta get off at this exit. Yeah this one right here
But why am I not what why am I not going off on the exit?
No, slow down. I just slow down. Oh, is that even possible?
I could probably do open heart surgery on myself if I just didn't say that
It's just going pretty well. Oh
My god, it's so hard to determine where that fucking coin is
Guarantee, you won't beat this Mario's made it at Dippin Dots. That'd be like kind of cool
Is it like let me guess the eighth coin is like hidden somewhere in a stupid place
Going this way. I'm not missing it. There's the last point. Let him suffer
That's so mean. It's going too fast. This is going too fast
Why did I jump on the pink one? Get over here
All right, we're good. Sound is out of sync. Is it ready? How am I? The audio is ahead
The game audio is ahead. Sorry. What are you telling me when it goes?
The audio is ahead. I don't know how this goes
Good. We good? Are we good? All right, let's do the next one. This game is fucking so good
Videos ahead now
Pachinko? I already beat Pachinko. Not fixed. Oh, Shadow Mario revisited
How about this? Ready? This might be good. How's this? Ready? Check it out. How we doing?
I'm too dumb to do that move. Me? Should I get this?
Thanks for waiting. You're a hell of a guy. Oh, what was the person that guaranteed I wasn't gonna beat that level?
You owe me a hundred dollars, right? It's always a hundred dollars. Every time. Not this time. This time you little shit
Frizzy and cut it there. Go ahead. Imagine playing a Mario game where you suck at jumping
I'm doing the like put my tongue on my teeth thing. Let's say, you know, somebody's pissed if they're like, nope
No, no, no, no, no tongue on your back right tooth
pressing
That's a real angry face. Hey, you know, maybe hey
Maybe it's like if some of you guys write show feet in capitals every 12 minutes. Yeah, you
Know that you know, maybe it'll happen at this point
I mean like, you know every like every eight minutes like six of you just write it in all caps and I
It's you know, it's probably at this point gonna have it's gonna happen. Keep that keep doing it
Keep yeah, I'm sure it will eventually it has to write. You mean you're saying it every every scream
Hundred times it's good. It has to still it's gonna happen. Keep doing it. I do everything here
I did that one seven eight. We're gonna go up here. Yeah the onto but that's the uh, I'm going here
$50 from yes is online
5,000 bits $50 $50 $50. Oh, that's secretive casino. Ooh
One of the casino. Thanks for the 5,000 bits dude. Seriously, they just like the what they say coin
Point point why coin put this on a 10-minute delay
I'm not like queuing up from pub G. Why would I do that?
Mark right this way, please into the casino. What no way
How much does it cost I play I?
Won three coins
I'm about to get hot but that's usually when I start losing
Sorry, you
The games are all rigged. Where's the manager? I want my coins back. It's rich
It's a real can I play this one?
This is the first time I've ever seen water-powered slots. That meant look at the sevens. Oh
Kevin
Kevin, ah, we got one more one more
But I win five coins
But what else is there? I won't play again. I can't play again. Can I play it was roulette?
What do I want? I'm looking for. Holy shit first try
Hi, we want them to boo
Again more coins. Oh, man. This thing's pretty hot. Let me get sevens. Yep
What is this a mystery prize?
Really, which one I'm gonna say right in the middle. Yeah, they this one right in the middle. Oh
It's you just flip it over
Closer
What are you doing what okay good good cool I won Oh
Super rock and what did you win the ability for you to get really really angry at a Mario game?
All right
This move
Does it does move
I think it's just watch out. Just watch out. It's all right. Watch this
That's room
Well, I can never ever ever believe I get on top of one of these I think so
No, I'm gonna go right one, two, three
Oh my god, it's moving
The black background the black background just the
Was warping around I thought it was going moving the black background and then done the 3d plane
I thought it was rotating. I thought it was moving up. Oh
It's all right. Come on. God damn it. It's cuz my camera was pointed straight down. That's a wrong wrong wrong
Fuck it. I'm not gonna need to do it again
Hurry up. I I jumped I tried jump. I just didn't I I I hit the jump
He just like fucking walked off. I best have done it too late or something. I don't know fucking hell
He's so it's a stress inducing
I want that
Jeremy why would you you're okay. I don't get fucked over by the cube. What way is this fucking turn it?
Holy shit, it was hard to tell. Oh
Don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't where am I? Oh my god, come on
It's just such an awkward thing with that background. I got it. I can't but how I had it to that was the end
It tilts around and you have to walk back up. You got to go back all the way over
I should get it this time
Okay, well it wasn't happening that rotation
Oh
Up
Holy shit, I almost blew it. I want some flashy see some flashy, right?
Sorry, it wants me to keep going back to this
All right
We got over there
Seven here. We gotta go back in here get is
Five here. Let's go to the beach. Let's go back to
Go, where is it?
Beach episode. No, but the the one with the casino in it that was the with the casino in it
What am I doing? Go back in there?
Right cuz I only have four here
Right. Is there only four here five. Did I get all seven?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. There it is. King boo down below
so how many
stars do I have to have before I
What's the
What about the game completion for shines?
70 70 you need seven shines in each level. I think I'm getting there
Okay, so down below
Boo, big boo down below
Anything in particular to go down or do I have to just go up and then down?
Um
All right
I'm not gonna just I'm not gonna say if I don't be saying the word. This is gonna dump gasoline on the spark
Hey
We gotta go down
Yeah, we have to go down the bowling lane. I always wondered what the fuck was back there
You know, I mean, you know when you break to something newer
your
Your bowling lane that doesn't work
Like it's like, oh, I just think not working that guy goes all the way in the back where the pins are
It's like holy wait, what's back there? Oh
Nevermind, but you kind of want to see what's back here
Kill these guys or I'm an M right there
Killed them all I don't need to
Elevator take me back down talk to that guy. I can't seem to attack these motherfuckers. I'm just gonna talk to this guy. Oh
Okay
King boo is a slot machine boss. All right. Well, this is cool. This is awesome
Then it what have we got? You didn't get shit boo. Sorry, just stop it for spinning
Well, I guess now I get a turn
This guy's fucked. So I help this guy
Alright, we're good. I don't need to be lining this up with anything. Do I?
pineapples pineapples pineapples
Ineffective. It's just laughing at you. You sure
It's like sweating. Oh, what about this one? He seems to dislike spicy things. Now's your chance
My chance to jump on his I just put him out. I think I just put him out
Just helped him. I sprayed him with water. Yeah
Yeah, he's I've helped him
All right
Spin it again. Is that nothing? He's a big waters, too
Spin it. All right hot pepper. Stop this for spinning and then go what behind him pull on his tail
Throw another one at him
Throw more fruit at him, I guess
Well, how all right, how would it change if I throw a fruit at him and he goes?
Oh, that isn't effective. But when he eats hot peppers all of a sudden now it hurts him
What kill these guys? Are you waiting for them to die fruits? All right, here we go
But what's the point do I need to stop this shit? It's just kind of annoying. What's the point of stopping it?
All right, we're gonna go up here and then I'm gonna throw this at him
Yes, sure. Let's go. I thought I just got thrown out
Yeah, I kicked out of the casino. I'm currently stun locked
This is how it ends. I need coins
Hey, look at that
Thanks for the coins
swell swell swell
He's turning down the audio a little loud. All right, he's dead
uh
Anus music
He said it because I only have one frame of reference for this so that leaves us with
There's more in here. What about that six scrubbing sirena beach
Not this again
Didn't I already do this?
Mario we got trouble that electric group is back where everywhere
Uh, oh by the way, you have three minutes
For what
You have to get everything or just like 80% or something throw barrels. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop
Whoa, what what what? All right. All right. What the hell? Where's my star many? Thanks friend. Oh shit
Many thanks. You saved me two free coins. Are there people down here? Wait, can I get two more coins?
Thanks mario
Yeah, nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice
The easiest four blue coins i've ever gotten in this whole game
All right, where's the guy that owns this place?
Where's the owner? That was great. Now. Here's a shine just for you
52 shines and counting and going right back in game fucking sucks last night
No, that doesn't work here. That doesn't work here. That doesn't work here
Shadow mario checks in
So episode seven is shadow mario every time it seems right makes sense. I guess
Go get him. I'll never believe it. We oh, this is gonna be an annoying chase, isn't it?
Get in there. Oh, he's gonna be going through weird doors and through ceilings and
All right. Let's go
Do that on purpose. Oh wait
They are they are fake
Which one's real?
Why is it not hitting him? Are you a little?
Yeah, I got you gonna die in the shadow mario level. Nope. He's still alive. Anybody else see the
other mario
Thought I did
All right. I think we have seven in most of these places
seven
nine
seven eight
two
Two and okay, that's the other pipe. So I gotta go
It's up there. Okay. I need the rocket. Give me the rocket. Can you throw it up here to me, please?
Just throw me the rocket toss it to me. I'll catch it. I swear to god. I'll catch it
No, dude, I don't want to throw your phone that far. I'll catch it. Just fucking throw it
Oh god, can I just hand it to you? I'm just gonna walk over to you and hand it to you. Just throw it dude god
Okay here one two three, please don't break. What are these guys doing over here? Are you slacking off?
You're slacking off. What happened to the phone? Uh, it tumbled down the stairs
Is there a case on it? No
Dummy, right?
All right. Let's go get the here. Here we go. What the hell is
This weird like picnic basket flag is this
Oh, right. I forgot about this. I was like, yeah, i'll come back here. Fuck this
I gotta go under and then up. All right
Hoopy oh
I remember I was like, why is it moving? Why why why is it moving man? What's going on? Why is it moving?
Wait, I was supposed to press jump. I was supposed to jump. Oh fuck. Oh, no. I'll come back later
Get out of the way. Hey
Don't look at me
Leave me alone
Get out of here. Stop
Oh, what the heck i'm gonna come back later
Dear what the fuck am I right now? It's the wrong. No, this is the only thing I can do
Okay, can I rely I can walk on here
The goal is up there, right?
Should I just shimmy and
This feels incorrect
Oh, okay that you went over the fucking banister mario
This is definitely the wrong place
Easy easy easy
What dammit calm down? I that was a good guy like
David or cheese just struck out in the bottom of the ninth inning
Game four of the 2004 fucking alcs. You know what I mean? That was what that was. That was what that sound was
That was like an old man screaming at the tv mad because there was a strikeout a plus b is a long dive jump
and
Why?
Why did that why was I never told?
Why is why it's been 16 17 hours in the game, why don't you know this
Because it was funnier. What do you mean? It was funnier, but
It looks big as fuck today
Okay, that was fucking stupid
It bumped into me. I jumped up. I didn't press any buttons
The thing when when it swayed back to start to fall bumped me and knocked me up turn the
It's gallding right now to the police station. I don't know what that is now. I can run through the doors
We do this first here, but it's all gonna be okay
I only have one health for one life. Whatever
Okay, where am I?
um
Is safe. Holy shit it is
I tried using the new jump and it didn't work out for me
unfortunately
spin jump and dive
The problem with me though is reliably spinning the analog to like do that. I could just I you know me
I might just walk the fuck off the cliff
Wait
Okay
Why am I still alive?
That doesn't save very much time
You have to show you you have to spin jump every time there. You can't just regular jump or dive or anything
You have to actually spin jump on every mushroom. I'm kind of glad that happened because I only have three
I have one
One up, you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm
What's the downside of the game over? I'm just having to run all the way back here. I'd rather be able just to start over again
All right. Oh same strategy. I'm doing that again
It didn't have enough momentum that time
So we're not gonna do that strategy again. We're gonna just do it the normal way. I didn't have enough momentum
All right, here we go
These are cool to have on the level like have those on the level. They serve a purpose
um
I did it. I just I spin jumped. Uh
I'm going the wrong way. How am I supposed to know what the way I i've never played this game before
Are they like five different holes? I don't I don't know how am I supposed to know that?
These are the only ones I can reliably get to right now
There's one over here and one over there
Where's the third one?
This is dangerous. But what is it for blue coin?
I can I go I can't jump in there. It's right there
Can I go that way see if I can go all the way around
All the way
Now there's one back here
This is a hole
right like it
It's not a hole
This looks like a hole to me
No. Oh, there it is
I can also go back here
Well, i'll try this one
Where does this bring me?
Please leave me alone
You two are fucking with me right now. Just
Look some other way
Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get away from me and then
Oh Jesus, what the fuck?
Which way is he going?
Holy shit, he's right behind me
Okay now
This is what do I do?
I just had to walk
The wind shit is gonna be over here, isn't it?
I didn't know there's gonna be a springboard
Do you see how fucking much I jumped off that?
That was like a boing
I don't care about that
I can just make this as a jump, right?
I of course I can
Is this a spring? Is this a spring?
Oh god. Oh man. This is
No, no, is this not is that not this? This is not a tight rope
Oh, why can I?
Okay. Thank you
The camera
This place sucks
I'm trying to like point dive
No, I don't want to do that again. I had to juke like four people
Do the speedrun skip? I'm going for it
I'm gonna go for that because that's the only way I ever liably know my brain will try to do this
I'm going for the speedrun strategy. You ready?
Check this shit out
Which way was that?
Hey, remember which way was that? This way?
I'm going for it. I'm getting up there. I ain't going the real fucked up way. No way
I'm going for it. I'm gonna get this shit
Check this out
You'll be reading about me in fucking newspapers after this one
I I he went over the edge. Oh my
I
I he he decided to to parkour over the edge instead of just
getting
I'm doing i'm gonna be able to do it that way
But um, he just sometimes decides that he's going to jump over and across instead of just grab
He just sometimes is like maria's like, you know, I feel like pole vaulting over whatever thing you're is in front of me
I'm just gonna jump the fuck over it. Yeah, you'll be reading about me
I will say though
They were so scared to have this game be just the cleaning game
They were like, oh my god
No, we have to get rid of that thing and they have to do shit like this for like at least 20 levels
Get over them barrio you motherfucker open up your fucking books and get the video game history streamers
I want I want you to open up the fucking book and I want you to see next to next to germa 985
I want you to look at accomplishments
And I'd like you to fucking open up this page
You want us to laugh?
There's no achievement center in there. It's like two. All right, get up. What's this guy's problem?
What was the goal with this level?
Just to get this
Is that it?
Now anytime you watch a streamer play this game and they get to this part and they go holy shit
Um, this I hate this
Tell them to use the fucking germa 985 dive technique and they show them a youtube video jump clip of this
And they'll be like wow. Okay, that's so much easier
Oh my god, you're gonna link them to slap five times all right, what's next chain chomp's bath give him a bath
Oh, we're gonna have to coach him into the bath
All right. So where's the bath?
Hey, you've got another problem over here. This thing's bigger than all those pups put together when it's chained up
There's no problem. But of course
When that thing's loose, we're in a heap of trouble. Oh, yes that beast's owner always burnt hands. It's pitiful
So where we have to where let me get that first. Hold on
Are there any goopers in chat tonight? I'm sure there's at least
All right, let's find out where this is
I see it. Okay, it's all the way back here
Oh, they have signs. All right
All right. You ready? Let him go
Three two one, let him go
All right, let him go
undo the nail
Well, actually go this way. What the hell?
Actually keep going this way
Keep going
All right, he's going really mario. You gotta be fucking shitting me
Come on
You're going you're taking a bath
No
He's in the same spot. He was in the last time
If you aim you stand still and then he runs away pound his nail back in proud fucking nail back in
Oh, you gotta be kidding me
I'm almost out of water
Hey, hey, hey what wait, what do you mean? He was nailed in
I need water just he can go fuck off somewhere for a little bit. I need I need fountain
Didn't nail it all the way
Start over you rage quit the bath level
He was going no, he's got I
Now I understand the hell is going on. Yes. Hi. I'm here to take care of him. Okay. Bye
All right, let him go
This is the calm level. This is not the calm level
Go get up there
He's really stinky. I'm sure he is
All right, let's stop him
What's this? What's the shotgun again? You have to be I have to be holding it, right? I mean just just go
Just let him go. He's gonna walk around in a circle. Anyways, come here you motherfucker
Get in here get in the bath. I got in the bath
That's like a
nobody's gonna
Stay in there. What the fuck you lied to me. This is a spongebob episode. God damn it
Get in here get in the bath
Get in the bath
Gary get in the bath
Thank you for the five community subs, mr. Dask
Thanks a lot. Are you available? Uh, not too many requests. I had to stop saying that just stop saying the secret of the village underside
I just saw a a big blue diamond thing show up. That's five thousand bits
That's fifty dollars. You guys you guys have been doing
The last two days has been like money central
And it was goiki
Goiki thanks for the five thousand bits fifty bucks. Is it better to have pogged and lost or to not never have pogged at all?
um
That's better to have pogged and lost. Absolutely
Even as old folks are starting to get excited about this
Oh before I forget I am not the mayor if you're looking for him. He's probably by that yellow mushroom
All right, so I need a yellow. Uh, I don't know what if they are like a
Papaya, what is it?
Is that you know the mayor looking for a papaya?
those of you that are uh
Those of you that have been around the channel for a while, you know that papaya is a b uh c tier
fruit according to me
Mom, it feels like it's getting close to fluff festival time
With papaya, where is it?
Your c tier
Yeah
You think so?
I'll have you know
That I have i'm a b plus
it's according to all the
data collection places
stream stats
I I have a b plus
in for best streamer of the year
Did it go down to a b minus? It's still fine
Why did I do all that for?
I just love going to find one fruit to bring back to give the yoshi egg
Give me this fucking thing. You could be a plus if you streamed as bugleberry. I don't think that's true
Okay, so this is secret now
What is it? What am I looking for?
Something I shouldn't wear. What if I go with the yoshi? No
mushrooms
All right. Okay. So
I gotta go down does it matter probably go down the hole that yeah, i'm gonna go down the hole that I went down before
This one, right?
Uh, okay
This music is kind of really loud
It's just playing the same loop over and over again
I found it
Yoshi, are you all right?
Yoshi
Oh, uh
I I didn't know what the fuck that was another one of these goddamn things. I'm gonna
Oh, that's gonna be look at how look at how much there is
Why are there people here?
I'm a chuckster
You better be careful when speaking to powerful the yontas some will chuck you straight up
But most chuck you backwards when it comes to tossing folk. I'm well, i'm a chuckster
I'm a chuckster
He almost threw me off
Rick, are you a chuckster?
Oh
Okay, this one goes up holy shit
I like this one. This one's great. This one's this one sucks, but it's I like it
Wait, can I push them? Hey, throw me over this way
Um, I don't think how how could you get less accurate than what I just did?
I think I can influence a little bit
a little
Throw me no. No, no. No, can I back up back up? I came out of it at a weird angle
Hear me. It's a school night. I don't go to school
Come on, throw me more throw me more further further
Why are you not hitting this?
truancy, yeah
Somebody somebody tell the time to get the truancy on me
I I haven't been to a class
In 17 years somebody called the truancy on me. No you because look at the there's a wall there
Here far I bounced off the rip. Oh my god, whatever
Thankfully, I can stay here forever
actually forever and by the way
Can I just?
Nope
Throw me throw me real far
And go
Good. I need you all the way. Okay, you now have to be
I need you all the way in front of me here and I gotta get this right
Right there is all right. No, it's not good enough. That's good. It's okay. I think so
higher higher
He almost threw me to the all right you guys any of you guys ever played little league?
I used to play little league and we had these there was like two or three fields that were right next to each other
You'd have the one outfield would be there would be another outfield. It'd be two or three of them right next to each other, right?
And there was always that kid
That hit a home run every other at bat
And sometimes he would hit it over the fence and it would go into the other field
Even while they were playing a game
They would do it all it would happen all the fucking time. It would fuck up so many plays because like the big strong
eighth grader
Could hit the ball almost to the pitcher's mound on the other field
That's just so so dangerous
Now i've sealed my fate, I don't care if we're here all night i'm all right with this
I don't have a problem with this
Okay. Now this guy throws
So hard he throws
As hard as he can so I have to hold back
Say good night to me. Good night
Okay, so now i'm
Wait, i'm not up there
Okay, so
Twist am I going through a fucking portal? What's going? I hope throw me
Okay, there we go. So when I watch what about these guys?
Why I don't I don't get this. Why are they all here? Why are you all here? I don't get it. Why are they here?
Wait, is this just a mess? Just just a mess with you. I get it
throw
Um somebody over there
you
Which way did you throw?
Which way is this person's throw?
Do you definitely throw over there? Right? Is that a
It's gonna be right on the line right here. All right, come here. That's lined up. I think
It's gonna be on the other side. Yeah on the other side
What are you doing? I I don't I don't know I was overthinking that just throw me
I thought he I had to get thrown to the other side and then
Paws sick
Paws me that way, please. Well, he's a chuckster. Yeah, he is a chuckster
What happened
He threw you to your death. Ah, I need to get I don't miss this
Don't rush it
If I rush it i'm gonna throw off the edge
The problem I have with that one when he throws your way up high is if I hold back too much
Then I just go right back down. But if I don't hold it at all or I do it too little
You really fly
Come on
You can control yourself in the air
I know
But if I hold if I do back too much, it's it's a really
There it's a lot of finessing in the air when you can't really see where you are
Hold forward. I will go over the cross. I will go across the whole map if I hold forward
And what is this doing this for? Well, has he tilted I was facing straight ahead
Game sucks streamers sucks. I'm going to bed
Wait, it can't be both. Okay
You gotta pick one. You gotta pick one and stick with it. Um
What why
Okay, I did this like six times in a row doing the same thing
And now all of a sudden it's not I did i'm god. I got it wrong
This I can't get like more straight than this
But i'm not gonna do it again. I didn't holy shit. That was close. All right, just do it quickly quickly go go go go right here
Okay, here we go. This is it. I can't tell i'm not ready yet. I'm not ready for this not yet
I'm not ready for this. Is that no, that's not right. I got a little bit more to the left
right there
Line's gonna be right between my legs. I love having a big fucking rectangle in the way
It was as if I was standing like at a full like 40 to 50 degrees to my right
I saw I I saw good do it now good now. I agree with you
I wasn't
What the fuck there's so many there's only so many pixels that mario's body can turn
You know what I mean? Like it there's only so much he can finite movements he can make
There's a whatever. There you go
These things these things are getting fucking deleted
On sunday, by the way, you're never gonna see one ever again. This has got me so paranoid that it's not correct
What the fuck wait, what what the fuck oh my god
The angle's bad
It's too far back
Didn't I go over it
Where did I fall then?
I undershot it
Right. He's gonna push me though if I uh, oh
All right, let's go
Fuck you
I can't tell this is too. No, that's that's too far to the left to the right. Just go straight
What do you think i'm doing? Is that it?
I mean, I can't get it any better than this. I don't think can I ground pound out of this a line?
Yeah, that's I tried last time. How's that? I think it's a little too much too much to the right. That's perfect
I don't think so. I don't think that's correct. It's good. Go do it. I'm gonna do it
If I get thrown 500 feet to the right and this whole thing is stupid wake up mario
Is the angle between your camera and his camera?
Who else has a fucking camera?
Yeah, I I had to actually wake his ass up. You're kidding me
What do you think we think we're good? I can't tell the chuxters position is more important than yours
Okay, here we go
Close enough
What the fuck man? This shouldn't be this ridiculous
Just do it. What the fuck?
He's gonna walk into me, isn't he?
God damn it. That's not he's not in the right spot. He's not he's got to turn. I think that's it
Jeremy did you join? I did it. Holy fuck. That was horrible. Is that it?
Yata's in need remember you are not a chuxter. That's fine. That doesn't bother me
I just went away for a bit and now look I can't believe it another fine mess and it's all a doozy
Some of the villagers are trapped in that burning ooze to go save them 10 people three minutes
youtuber voice
You know the drill 10 villagers are trapped in the slime. You must hurry. Well, stop talking and get the fuck out of my way
dingus
and
Somehow I got my I hit my head
You trapped you good. You're not gonna light back on fire, right? I don't think so. This ain't that bad
Two here six. Okay, we're over here
seven
eight
Anybody where where where where where anybody anybody anybody anybody in trouble trouble?
Who's in trouble anybody over here?
You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good
You're good. Everyone good
All right, I got plenty of time plenty of time plenty of time
There we go plenty of time. There we go
10 out of 10
Thanks sweetums
Oh, they all have coins
Yep
Uh-huh
Shit
You saved me. Thanks a lot
That's a free shine. I'm gonna have two shines after this
You know people happy
Two shines after this people three shines after this people happy
fucking winks
You know what I mean
Oops, the mayor's waiting. No, who did I save which well you who got who got saved over here?
There to get these
Did I get both of you? I don't think I got you two. Let's find out. No, I didn't
I need to stream but I need to stream to this
I almost just said I need to stream but the sleep is so good. I need to sleep but the stream is so good
Oh, well, that means a lot. I'm glad you like this stream
Thank you
All right. I'm done. Let's go talk to the mayor
I got one. I got almost all of them 10 of them eight of them. I got most all right
Hello
Give me my shine, please
You're so styling now I got the sunglasses
So, all right, it just made everything darker. Well, what do I what do I do with it?
Can I do any it's probably like the next level or something?
All right, where was that mirror?
Who is it there?
What is this dude?
Not up there
Over the bridge
Turn your brightness up. Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna take this off
Where the hell is this guy?
Ridge
At the start when I just over there isn't just the start of the level take these fucking sunglasses off please and smash them
Oh
He's all the way back here all the way
Well, I'm like all the way all the way back after the whole thing
Oh god, because there's like a fucking playpen right here. Why can't you like walk your ass over the bridge?
I have to come all the way back to like the fucking spawn get over here
The last thing I have is um, seventh level, right?
I'm at summit 60 shines after this i'm just trying to jump in the fucking pipe mario like you're really gonna keep doing this
All right, where's the police station? It's like a little corner somewhere over here, right? I'm going there like over here
Where is it? Where is this police station?
No, not that way
Where's the fruits?
Okay, so
Where am I going?
What's wrong with you?
I'm unforgivable. I have had it someone ruined my wall
Oh, i'm sorry to hear that. All right, let's go
Here we go
Bye golf. Well, I understand
Whoa?
Was I supposed to jump? Holy shit
But how that was almost a
Hyper oh mega choke at the end. I would have been so sad. I almost panic jumped off the edge
I almost oh mega choked that would have been so bad. Okay. I want to go do the
Turn this stuff in but do I?
Or do all right. I got a question for you
so
Oh, what is the
We did like six and a half hours yesterday six and a half six to six and a half today
what's the uh
We got like another how much long we got like another six to seven hours
What do we think?
Another will there be is there another stream?
Two to three hours. Okay
Unless you want to 100 percent
Depends on how many you do
Two to four hours. Okay, depends on how much you choke. Well, that's cool. I can
Well, hi
um
I need yoshi over here
You could finish this in an hour if you wanted to
I'm i'm not sure I want to rush through it
I don't I don't think I just want to what do I have 58 60?
I'm not sure. I want to just
Finish it quickly hurry up and be done
I'd like to try to at least get another
like 10 to 15 stars
At least get to like 70 80
I mean i've played this game before it's not like i'm like, all right, let's finish it. Okay. Bye i'm done
Oh, I got 60 stars and beat the game and uh turn it off and delete it
So I think we'll call it here. This is a good stopping point. Okay, also it's it's getting it is getting a little late
Not for me, but for a lot of you other guys. Yeah, this is got we six hours
It'll be about six and a half seven with the bits. Yeah, this is a good place
I think it makes sense
We'll finish it tomorrow and we'll do uh
We'll keep doing it until i'm kind of done. Even if I beat the game
I might still try to get a few stars and just play it
I've never played it before. Yeah, i'll see you tomorrow
tomorrow, uh
Same time around probably three
Three to three thirty something like that like but we're not gonna be it's not gonna start more than three thirty
Did you do the hotel level most of it? Yeah, but i'll see you guys tomorrow around three-ish pm specific
Sorry, I said the noises were funnier than you. Well, it wasn't accurate. It well, I mean it wasn't inaccurate
I'll see you guys tomorrow to show you eating. Hey, just don't talk about any eating anything
What are you trying to do?
You're not supposed to be leaking that info, but well, uh, we'll see you tomorrow
Thanks for stopping by guys. If you check us out tomorrow
We're gonna be playing more mario sunshine until I beat it until i'm done and full
And then we'll see what we're gonna do after that
Thanks for watching. See you tomorrow. I had a blast as always
This game is something i've never experienced. So it's really fun to experience it brand new
For the rest of you, let's go back earlier today
Let's rewind
E jangler
He's an e jangler. Thank you oat horse for the 500 bits march 12th drew crew shoe crew stream, please make it happen
I don't know maybe
hobby hobby club podcast thanks for the five dollars
Derma charlie chaplain died eating a bunch of candy shoes
What we had a hundred community subs from freddy dread
a hundred from austin atlantis
and
Freddy dredd two hundred dollars in bits nocturne a hundred dollars in bits of just crazy shit
Core monster a hundred dollars in bits
You guys give a lot of money today and yesterday
Thank you. Mr. Kool-Aid. Thanks for the 500 bits. Hey jerma. Here's some bits to get you a coffee
You must be exhausted from all the pretending. Yeah
I am
God, you know when you pretend as much as I do you gotta
You gotta give yourself a little bit of a boost
Thanks to the five dollars did
Tag me when germ is upset. Thanks for the three, uh, 300 bits happened a couple times today
On some of those secret levels couldn't contain my frustrations, but it's okay
Sometimes it happens all straight a couple what it was like twice
It was when I was when we were doing the secret levels and I talked about how
Well, I talked shit about a whole world here right I thought one of the whole level yeah I did all right nails
fucking nail
Yeah, that was not even a meltdown though. That was a
ADHD issue that was not a meltdown
You can't this doesn't count
but
Thanks with three bucks. Thank you lizard to be both for the 250
I'm spending today making an archive of all my mom's beanie babies for her. Thanks for giving me something to watch while I do that
Where's some money?
Beanie babies. That's pretty cool. I remember those things
That's very nice of you. Thanks for the 250. Hope you got them all sorted
Wind are thanks for the five dollars
You sniff sniff. Oh, yeah, jerma weed. That's the good shit. Anyway, jerma. I love the streams was also curious if you've ever heard
uh of
A king gizzard and the wizard lizard. It's a really awesome band that you might enjoy
If you haven't you should check them out
It is a great album called in your mind to get introduced to them seeing a lot of pogs
Oh, yeah, i'll check it out
Thanks with five dollars
I'll give it a check
Espada escalada. Thanks for the 250 had the same exact bad facial hair pattern. I feel your pain
Yeah, but I love to have a decent beard or something. Maybe but i'm not sure it would even work on me
I've kind of got
I'm not sure it would a big lot of facial hair would work. I like the way that I can make my face look now
So good, uh cell juniors. Thanks for the three dollars. I like this stream
I like that you like this stream. Thanks for the three bucks
Smelly boy. Thanks for the 250 after this. Are you willing to give paper mario a chance?
maybe
after mario sunshine though
I would like to
Get away from the game cube in the wii for a little while
And by a little while I mean a week or two
Just because we've done a lot of game cube and a lot of wii
The majority of the streams have been game cube or wii games for almost the last two weeks
We will come back to it. There's still tons of shit that I have
We'll see what's wrong with that. No, nothing wrong with that
I just like to I like to mix it up a little bit
If mario paper mario is long
That's fine. I'm i'm
The streams of yesteryear are not the streams of today year
obviously
Uh me streaming mario sunshine three days in a row four days in a row
Is something I probably never would have done a few years ago
I never used to play the same game
More than one or two streams. I would just abandon it because I just didn't think people would stay interested
And I don't think I would stay interested
so i'm
it's not like
It's not a big deal
Sorcery sorcery was a different case because sorcery was it's one of my favorite things ever
Streaming sorcery 10 to 12 times and that's just one of my favorite experiences
Yeah, but I never write off any game. I never say that i'm not going to do something. So
There's definitely a chance
CDT thanks for the thousand bits ten dollars jerma. I've been a fan since 2012 and I watched your pyromaniac video specifically
a long time
I'm turning 22 today and I want to thank you for being one of the positive influences in my life
It's a very long time that I forget that a lot
That next year
is
10 straight years
Doing this
2021 will be 10 full years
Doing either youtube or twitch
without stopping
There's been a couple of times when I haven't been around for a couple weeks two or three weeks is the maximum
I think i've ever not been around
But i've been around at least every week or two
10 years
That's crazy to think about that
Oh, there absolutely will be an anniversary stream and I knew you from the servers. See somebody's here that knows me from the servers
Gigantic air quotes
But uh, yeah, thank you for the 10 bucks cdt
Glad to have you around. Thanks for sticking around for so long
Toadside picnic. Thanks for the 300 bits jerma fellow mass hole here
Do you miss the chaotic yet inexpensive atmosphere that is market basket? I do miss something very specific from market basket
Market basket had uh, probably the best
Ginger ginger ale they had a golden ginger ale. It was market basket golden ginger ale brand
It's probably the best ginger ale i've had nothing can really replace it
unfortunate
You know, you know
I could probably order it somehow but it'd be weird
It'd be weird. But yeah, I I used to I did get stuff from there
Thanks to the 300 bits
Let's put on
The e-credits
We can switch this don't you love how I haven't had this highest tip bit leader top sub thing to work
I've never got it to work once
People just are waiting for that to happen. This never happened once. There's just no one. No one's getting there's no top sub gifter ever
Like am I ever gonna get this fixed it kind of worked the first week. Yeah, and then just stopped
Well, it's those people in the chairs. That's what you don't understand. It's always that guy in the chair
It's always the slug and it's always the
Animorph someday we'll know
Someday we will know
We will
That day is not today. Unfortunately
Anyways, as always thanks again guys
We'll hopefully see you tomorrow
for the
Holy shit. That's a lot of people for the conclusion of mario sunshine
However long that takes
That's fast
There are three or four more bits to do
as these
Insane credits roll out from the hundreds of gifted subs
And hundreds of regular subs
It's not just the gifted subs
Thanks guys never the new year's stream. That was ridiculous
I think that new year's stream. I think there were two to three thousand subs on that stream
That was out of control
He fucking loves us
Of course I do
What do you think this is?
Bulbaswag disney. Thanks for the 500 bits. This is one of my favorite childhood games
I'm, so happy you're finally jumping and diving
I've been spamming it every once in a while the movement mechanics is one of the best things about the game also spray water on
the birds
Again bulbaswag five more dolls here that one spot you found to get yoshi over there on that island is completely awful
If you want to cheese it here's a video
You can get yoshi out of bounds super easily into that island
But like it's not necessary or anything just a trick heads up from me your pal
Getting yoshi over there is awful
Maybe i'll give it a look use noclip on the emulator
Goosely charmed thanks to the 250 hey germa first time donator wanted to share something that happened at work
I was running late to a meeting and it was my turn to present
I airplayed my computer screen and some audio of a guy talking started playing
I was so confused for a few seconds until I realized I had paused a video of yours
And it had started auto playing all I can say is thank god you were being somewhat normal
And not crying to farting and screaming
Anyways, love the stream. Oh, man
what's the over under okay, if you took every single stream i've ever done and
Calculate how many hours that stream was all of them together and then rolled dice to see to pick a time spot
on that gigantic hundred
Two thousand five thousand plus hour video
What's the over under that it would be something fucking ridiculous or something fucked up that was happening on the stream?
Wouldn't be 100 70 if I was a psycho
Which I i'm not i'm not
Imagine if we did a coin
cost rng stream where it's every stream i've ever done
And every 10 minutes we pull the fucking lever
And it picks a random spot in like 2 000 hours of 4 000 hours of streaming
That would be kind of fun
Do that for the anniversary
That's a massive video file
I don't think that would be possible
Yeah, that would be a video file that was thousands of hours long
I don't think that's possible
I have a 50 terabyte but I would have to get an external hard drive. That was a petabyte or something
I'm gonna hold on to that because that's so dumb that it might be worth doing
Let up a generator that takes videos from the archive channel and gives you a random time stamp
Yeah, i'll look into this
I'm actually gonna for real look into this
Put all the streams in a playlist and roll the dice to choose a stream to do then roll again to choose the video
and time
It's possible. It's very possible
Yeah, i'm gonna do that. We'll do that
Put it on the list
anyways, we had um
30 30 dollars 3 000 bits from atlantius
Thanks for the 30 drop dude
I wanted to ask if you're planning on doing some kind of live in in-person show
I'll be willing to go to vegas and watch you perform in some way
It hasn't really come up
Something about that is very very funny to me
If I somehow got to rent out one of the theaters
On the strip or something
And for two nights only
I did just a terrible show
Like it was an hour or two long
That would be so bad
And make a fake almost infomercial esque
Commercial and trailer for it
And play that for a couple weeks before it happens and start selling tickets and stuff
Make the tickets two hundred dollars. Well, that would be a real asshole thing to do
Eclers in the crowd
Put a bunch of plants in to fake laugh at stuff and only see I only only sell 50 tickets and have
Hire a thousand people to come and crack the fuck up at everything and get cameras and film a live special
Have two people in the audience be actual real people
And the rest are just plants
Don't tell any of them
No, i'm gonna at that point. That's just an elaborate prank on two people
That's stupid
Now put it on the list
Thanks for the thirty dollars though, dude. Thank you going for the 500 bits
My favorite part of the stream is when you do bad at gaming
Hold on my favorite part of this stream is when you do a bad gaming moment and you just get mad at mario
Like why did mario just do that?
Why
There are some things that he like jumps over the pole and shit without me pressing anything
He does sometimes he does things without me doing anything
Mario is trying his best
And who is controlling him?
I am directing him but he is in control. I am directing him with an analog stick
But he has to run
If you put an earpiece in my ear
and said up
Right down up up if you just I would I would run up
But I still have to run it's my legs
Is he here right now?
Like i'm on one of those tv shows
Or i'm telling you there's a ghost that lives in my house
And I start going oh
Jeremy
Is he in the room right now?
Yeah. Yep. Explain it to me
Hey blackout. Thanks for the thousand bits and that's our final
Hit of the night
Move over here
Thanks for watching everybody
Uh blackout says for ten dollars thousand bits. Thank you blackout. Jeremy listen to your stream at work
Uh, I work at party city and today you made me laugh while talking to a customer
I had to yank out my earbuds stop laughing. She must have thought I was insane
Thanks for the content, man
I know you say we shouldn't feel obligated to donate but i've used your stream to make my workdays far better too much
to not donate keep it up for riffing your earbuds out
Yeah, you just be like i'm watching uh
I'm watching tv or something. Well, you can't you won't be that doesn't make any sense. You listen to a funny podcast
I appreciate that though. Thank you. I
No one's ever obligated to give this channel money. Some people give a lot
Some people give some some people don't give anything at all and all that is completely fine
That's all perfectly fine. All of it
Don't feel obligated to give a cent to this channel if you do i've really fucking appreciate it if you don't thanks for being here
Thanks for watching
You contribute as well
If a thousand of you guys two thousand three thousand of you are not subbed to the channel, but you watch the stream
That does it benefits the stream?
immensely
I will never give you money and you should you that's that's totally fine
Don't worry about that. You don't have to ever
When will we know if germy's in financial trouble?
If I do a raid shadow legends ad on my stream
That's when you know
Something's wrong
Can I watch this stream while i'm nude? Yeah, go for it
See you guys tomorrow
Have a fantastic rest of your night. Thanks for watching mario sunshine. We're gonna finish it tomorrow
Good night
Bye. Take care. See you soon