This guy looks like he's waiting for a bus.
Get out of my way.
Yeah, fuck you.
This is the same person talking.
I didn't even do that. I didn't even do that. Why? I did not press any button to hit him.
He just hit him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So what's next?
Alright, this really does sound like...
This sounds like somebody was just at a bar drinking with their buddies.
And held a microphone in front of someone, one of their friends.
Which is like, hey, can you...
Can you do like a fucking shitty pirate voice for me?
Be brave, son of a bitches.
Alright, this swear guy is seriously driving me crazy.
Be brave, motherfuckers.
This is all he does.
There's a guy on this boat that's just saying a variation of the same insult.
Be brave, pile of shit.
He's telling us to be brave in the same sentence. He's calling us names.
Which one is it?
Be brave, fuckers.
We're sinking.
We don't die today, you bitches.
Well, first I'm going to stab him.
And then I'm going to butt him.
And then I'm going to butt him again.
And then I'm going to stab him.
I guess a cup of drinks would make me think that it's all out.
Why does he keep telling me to do the fear skill?
Who do I have to...
I did not mean to shoot that guy.
Didn't mean to kill that guy.
I really didn't. I'm trying to do the fear skill.
Nobody seems to care though.
Apparently that guy...
Nobody cares about that guy.
Everyone's cool.
All right, we're good.
Look, a guy sleeping on the dock.
What do you know?
Hey, who's got a gun here?
You're going to put a gun on me?
Are you crazy, man?
That thing put somebody's eye out.
I'm tired. I'm going back to bed.
I think I'm good.
Wait, you got a gun still?
Oh my God.
You're going to kill somebody with that thing.
I'm sleepy. I'm going to bed.
I'm not tired anymore.
You think I'm tired?
No, I am tired.
No, I'm going to wake up now because you got a gun.
This guy's crazy.
I'm tired again.
No, I'm not tired.
You think I'm tired?
Fuck you.
I'm tired again.
Oh, hey.
I don't want to fight these guys.
I'm riding around like a dinghy boat and these guys are shooting like 300.
Oh my God.
There's no way I'm going to be able to fight these guys.
I just like 2%.
I did like not even 1% damage.
We're like instantly getting killed.
I can't even turn the wheel.
You need me.
No.
What?
Who's saying you need me?
Why is that the fucking reverse of beer?
Yeah.
No.
Oh shit.
There's a prisoner in here.
Get me out of here.
That's not a very secure prison.
Excuse me.
Just go the other way.
Could I use half a crown now?
I don't even know what that means.
You just said a nonsense statement.
Just please go out the door.
I'm sorry.
I'm on my way.
Get on your way.
Go.
I'm going to block this side of the door so you have to fucking go this way.
I'm sorry.
I'm on my way.
Go.
Turd sniffer?
Did you just call me a turd sniffer?
They're all like bumbling all over each other and like saying excuse me and like oh I don't
want any trouble.
Whoa.
Oh.
God.
Dude.
I can't beat this.
I can't beat this like hen house.
That's all I hear.
Literally that's all I fucking hear right now.
It's making me want to die.
Go.
Did I get out?
What is that nightmare?
You cannot be serious right now.
What?
Wait a second.
Don't even tell me.
Is this lady?
What?
No.
Yeah this is a lady pissing into a bush.
God they keep tempting me.
Stop tempting me with this.
Come on.
I like don't want to do this.
They keep putting them in the perfect spot for you to push them off the giant scaffolding.
Do you have any idea how hard it is to not do that?
Look.
Again.
And this guy.
This guy's pissing.
No he's not.
What is this guy doing?
Oh he's throwing up.
He's throwing up into an invisible ground.
I don't know why.
Wait was that the guy I was supposed to talk to?
Mind the sodding cannibals.
You guys notice something?
Anything seem a little off to you guys?
At all?
Just listen.
I found you cowards.
They patched him out of the game.
The last clip you saw was like two and a half days ago.
They removed.
This is all new dialogue on the boat.
Anytime you go on the boat now it's this.
What were the patch notes?
Did they say like oh we removed these scream swears be brave guy.
We apologize for his uncalled for insults.
And he has been removed.
I want him back.
Where is he?
He was an integral part of my crew.