Hello, good afternoon everybody. How you doing? Good to see you again. It's always good to see you.
So today we're going to play a game that's been highly highly recommended to me in the discord
channel and here. I don't know why. The game is called Frog Detective and I mean it does it the
frog is in the title so I have to play. I got this thing going since like 2012 where every single
video game with frog in the title I have to play it at some point so that's what we're doing today.
Does it have candy in it? I don't know. This game is only like an hour long so the other plan is
once we get through frog detective is we're going to do a part two of community content night.
Somebody told you we're going to split it into two and we're going to do it next weekend and
here we are. Community content night part two will be after frog detective one.
Let's go over those of you that weren't here a couple days ago. We talked about the schedule
coming up here. It's going to get a little weird. I have some old friends that have come into town
and they are going to be here for a week. A full week. So I've got to take some time to
show them around Vegas. Some of them it's their first time for being here so
old Boston friends coming in. On top of that I have sort of the final stretch of my
medical mystery that there's a couple appointments coming up this week.
Next week is what I mean. So it's going to be interesting but not next week like the week
after next. The first week of February. So there's not going to be a stream tomorrow.
That's where it starts but as of Tuesday we're going to start early on Tuesday. Very early
because I got something going on later in the evening on Tuesday. But as of Tuesday we're
going to go five days in a row. We're going to go Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday
and then after that after the five day super stream you are not going to see me for at least
six days. That's what I'm going to be taking the week off. So I figured if I'm going to take
six days off I want to stream like six days in a week. You know what I'm saying?
I don't just want to disappear. But that's the plan. Nothing tomorrow, something today
and then we do five days in a row. He's never coming back after that one. What am I going to
do for six days? I don't know. Knit a sweater. Do a knot tying class. Go work on something cool.
Eat a good breakfast at least one of those days. When I'm gone I want you to eat a
fucking really good breakfast. I'm talking like greens, tomatoes, beans and shit. Have like a
full good spread and think about me while you're doing that. Be like he fucking told me to do this
shit. Tell me to have like the beans and tomatoes and some nice like green sauteed eggs. I want you
to think of me when you do that. What do you mean? What are you? Beans for breakfast?
Hold on a minute. What you what you guys don't what do you mean beans for breakfast? What the
fuck? What's wrong with you? What are you talking about? Like that's English. That's English style.
You guys don't have English style breakfast in England? This like 12% of my audience is from
England. How come I'm not seeing more yeses? England isn't real. That's an English style
beans, toast, eggs, tomatoes, sausages. Come on that's an English style breakfast. That's
what my mother used to tell me. Was she lying to me? No she wasn't. Kim says that too. I got two
people versus you of like 3000. Sorry guys. Anyways we're gonna play frog. Just gonna chill
for a little bit. Play frog detective. This has been very very highly requested. I don't know why
but it was. It's true. Yeah I know. Let's put it on. I don't know anything about this game. It just
looks kind of like a cute detective game. Just okay all the Drew crew that's here.
Just imagine. This is Nancy Drew's of frog now okay. Can you see it? There you go.
Why does every game have to have a crew? Why can't we just play video games? Why is it why is my
stream in my community every game is a different country? Why can't we just why do I have to have
a crew for every game? This game fun? I already know. Okay all right let's see. Do it. Yeah I
know it's gonna get spammed. Do it. Use the mouse to look around. All right super frog detective.
W A S D is moving around. Okay it's me. Well the phone's ringing. This is not even
fucking 90 FOV. Fucking refunded. Hello. Who is it? It's the supervisor. Hi supervisor. Hey how's
life? Yeah pretty good I reckon. How are things with you? Me and the wife just got back from
Indonesia. Oh well tell them I dare you to come Bali. That means welcome back I think. Thanks.
Anyway what are you calling about? Oh right. I have a case for you. Who? It's a pretty spooky
one so hold on tight. I'm holding on. It's a little sloth who owns an island just off the bay.
Martin's his name. Says he's been here in a ghost for about two weeks.
So get this. He hires a team of ghost scientists. I'm not gonna do this whole stream. What's a ghost
scientist? I don't know. Anyway he hires some of them right and they can't find anything.
They've been on the island for two weeks. Whoa! The ghost is still at large so the head scientist
there a monkey calls me up. They need help and they want the greatest investigator I have.
So I said to them I'll send my best investigator but lobster cop wasn't available. This game like
30 minutes. Well this is this is precious game time real estate. We're running out of time.
So I'm asking you the second best investigator. I fully understand lobster cop's abilities far
outweigh my own. Yeah but you're pretty good. So are you up for it? I don't know it sounds scary.
I should be very brave. I believe in you detective. That's what I need to hear. Thank you supervisor.
I get okay. Wahoo! Can you give me a summary of the case before I go? Auto voice. Sure thing.
The basics are there's a slow... wait is this kids game? How old do you have to be to play this?
Well okay what's this what's the cutoff ceiling for age for playing this game?
Because I know like there's like cute games right? Oh that's cute game for kids
but if you're over the age of eight like it's don't even play it right like is this one of them?
There's a sloth who's hearing a lot of spooky ghost noises around his island.
He calls a bunch of ghost scientists but they're stumped. It's up to you to solve the mystery of
the haunted island. Why did you just tell haunted islands at me? Because that's the title of the
case. Time for you to grab your magnifying glass and get going. See you later supervisor. Good
luck. Thanks. I'm not a cutoff age for video games if you like it Jerma. Ah yes I thought this is a
mirror. Ah yes my trusty magnifying glass can't solve mysteries without it. Now I can right click
to see up close. But I can't do the thing. I can't do the thing that they do in every single... what
was last time you ever you saw magnifying glass in any form of media? It wasn't this. The magnifying
glass is not... they don't use it anymore. Nancy Drew. No no I'm talking like I'm talking... all
right let me rephrase that. Media that has been consumed by more than a million people
right? Like when was the last time you saw? Not don't... Nancy Drew's doesn't count.
Sherlock Holmes. Time to solve a mystery. Do they even use magnifying glasses in Sherlock Holmes?
Grace Ruxner presents Super Frog. I'm gonna say that like a thousand times this stream you
know I am. Frog Detective Adventure. How far away does Super Frog live? This is kind of loud. I'll
turn it down. It's on an island starring the detective Mark, Larry, Moe the Mouse, Bernie,
Fresh X, and the rest. Case one. The haunted island. This is just like cutouts. Okay the haunted
island. I'm ready. So I have to solve the case. Do a Kermit voice. Well this is a really small
island. I don't think it's gonna be that hard to figure this out considering... like do you have
one camera that's pointed at the island? That's all I need. Just even if it's low it's not even
HD. Okay what do you want?
Of course I remember. I don't remember.
Who should I talk to first? You're talking to me already. Okay who should I talk to second?
The other way around. I'll check it out. Thanks. What would you like to know? The resident. May I
ask who the resident of this island is? Oh that would be Martin. You can find him hiding in the
forest. He thinks the ghost can't catch him there. Hmm very interesting. I'll investigate.
But what would you like to know? Nothing. I'll come back after I did some stuff. See you around.
What does it say on this thing? Hmm maybe a man in a suit. Was playing this the compromise?
The compromise you have with the Drew crew. What is that? Wait can I pick this up?
Patrick. No it's not. Okay what is it? What is this? There's cookies? Macaroni. Yum it's not mine.
Hey uh you're that detective right? The one that uh monkey keeps on going on about.
That's me. I'm so glad they finally brought someone else in. I know nothing. I really shouldn't have
taken the job. Why did you take it? Oh I'll be honest. I thought it was a secret agent job.
That's what I thought. Why would you think that? Job listing said ghost scientist. That didn't seem
like a real job to me. I thought it was uh like a cover you know. One that only smart people could
figure out like me. It still could be a cover. Maybe they're testing you. Oh no no no no you're
right. I better look competent. I'm only joking. Sure. Can I ask you some questions about Casey?
What else do you want to know? What do you know about noise coming from cows? I mean I'm not
great at this. I'd be good at other jobs. Just letting you know. But it does seem like the noise
is coming from this hole. From a natural creature. They seem to be otherworldly somehow. They have a
weird and distinct tongue. Sometimes it sounds like a bird's call. But only sometimes. Oh that's
not good information. Yes I'm very good at finding things out. If you know what I mean. Bernie I'm
not a secret agent. Uh-huh. What else do you want to know? He's not paying attention beyond the
impression. Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding we figured it out. I'm not paying
attention to the story at all. I'm just making sure that I sound like Bernie Sanders.
That's it. That's all I cared about. I don't know anything. I don't even know what he just said.
I have no idea what's happening right now. Okay let's let's pay attention. Let me let me figure
this out. About the hole. And this too. This is making me dumb. This is making me. I'm thinking
dumb. You know what you think about noise coming from cows? Like I'm not even processing that
information. It's just I'm losing IQ points when I do detectives. Frog detectives. Okay here we go.
What do you know about the noises coming from this hole? I mean I'm not great at this. But I'd be
good at some other stuff. Just letting you know I don't have a problem with you. It just seems like
the noise is coming from the hole. I'm from a natural creature. I know all kinds of creatures
in my life. They seem otherworldly somehow. They were weird. All right. All right. I have to pay
attention. No more voices. We're done. Birds call. Only sometimes. Okay birds call. Do Obama?
I'm not sure that I can. I'm willing to give it a try. On the next film. Wait wait wait.
All right. Why do you want to be a secret agent? Secret agents get the best stuff.
Like for example you've got a cool magnifying glass. I want one of those.
Okay. Sure you're not. Yeah. Bernie Winks. Hey. Oh hey hey. Look at me. Look at. Even if I can't be
secret agent. Things I give up. I would love a magnifying glass. All right. There's nothing
I want more. You want a magnifying glass. You just give them mine. All right. Nothing. That's it.
I was saving my points for that. But now you can save them for something else.
Like making one of my emotes black and white. Which just makes it harder to see.
Thanks for the channel points. Hey. It's me Larry. Hey. I did not do it.
Huh? The noises are not coming from me. I didn't. I Larry did not make these spooky noises.
That's suspicious. What? Are you even listening to me? I said I didn't make those noises.
No I heard. I just. I don't like being accused like this. I'm not. Oh you're not accusing me?
That's such a relief. Can I. Are you going to ask me a question? Yeah ask me the questions I
mean. What can you tell me about the noises? Firstly I am not the one making them. I'm not
making the noises. Yeah. But I know where they're coming from. What? They're coming from the cave
in the forest. Why haven't you told anybody? Nobody listens to me. They say stuff like well
Larry if you won't listen to us we won't listen to you. Which is so weird because I do listen.
Maybe they. I'm a really great listener. So how do we get into the. This is just evil Bernie.
Evil Bernie Sanders. How do we get into the cave? Well I need a few things. To get through there
you'll need some sort of explosive device. Is that safe? We're dealing with ghosts here detective.
None of this is safe. Anyway I'll need a few things. I looked up an explosive recipe in one
of the old chemistry books. I need toothpaste, some wool, a chunk of pure gold and some pasta.
Oh so the normal explosive ingredient. There's a standard explosive recipe. Yes.
You want to get into that cave? Bring me those ingredients. I'll do my best.
Ask me then the question now. You have to do a. I'll try. Not next. Let's make some dynamite.
Not yet detective. We still need toothpaste, some wool, a chunk of pure gold and some pasta.
Okay. All right. I need. So I need. Oh yeah. So give me that. How do I get that pasta?
I need this. Yum. It's not mine. Take it. What are you doing? Howdy. What are you doing in there?
But there's a storm. It's not raining yet. Besides it's not actually that unsafe
to swim in the storm. Everyone keeps telling me to get out of the sea. But it's safer in here
and it is up there. Why is that? No ghosts in the water. Ghosts can't swim. How do you know?
Uh, Martin said you don't look happy in there. I guess I'm not. Sorry to hear. Thanks.
Ask you why you're so sad. Well, it's kind of silly. I really want a magnet. I told you it's silly.
Why do you want a magnet? Well, go on. My dream is to attach a magnet to a boat and, uh, hold on.
Oh, why? Boats are fast. I'm not fast. I hold on to the magnet. I'll be really fast too. Nice.
Right. I don't have any idea where to find one though. And even if I did, there's, there's no way
I'm getting out of that water here to that ghost is found. That's interesting. Is there anything
you need to know? All right. Let's process information now. Time to process info. All right.
Why did you want the magnet? So I can attach it to the back of a boat and zoom along. All right.
So you want a magnet so you can zoom along. Okay. If it's sweetens it, I can give you this big shell
in return for a magnet. I thought it might be magnetic, but it's not. Let's process info for
this like kids game that I'm not going to be able to complete because I'm doing, I'm doing like
precedents and presidential candidates. Oh no. God damn it. Okay. How was I supposed to know?
What am I? Scientist. Okay. Is there anything else you need to know? All right. We need to get a
magnet so we get the shell. We need a magnet so we can get the shell. We need pasta to get the
bomb. We need a magnet to get the shell. There's so many, there's a million people here. All right.
What is this? Is that a magnifying glass? Stop right there. Stop it. Stop right there. Why?
My shells. My shells. Don't step on my shells please. Oh, I won't. We can't be sure of that.
I guess not. They're very fragile and very small. Be careful. Aren't we all? I get, please just,
please be careful. Don't touch them. Don't step on them. Okay. You're still going to stand like that?
Yeah. Why? I'm alarmed. I'm on alert. I am protecting my shells from dangerous feet.
Wow. Sorry. I just worked up about my shells. I don't mean to be rude, but what shells?
I can't see any shells. That's because they're small. But me, very large. I have very big hands.
Shells are small. Hands enormous. How small? Too small for your weak magnifying glass.
Wow. So I'm sorry. It's the truth. It's the truth. It's just the truth.
I had to get this one specifically made for my tiny shells.
Fine. Can I ask you some questions? Ask me questions. Just be careful. Don't touch them.
Don't get near them. I will one. No, no, not you. No, no, no, no. You're from the fake news.
Somebody else, please. Me? Okay. Why don't you just get a bigger shell?
Ha. You fool. Hey. Hey. Sorry. It's just that there's not many big shells around here.
If I could get one shell. We got to get the shell to get the magnifying glass to get the pasta.
All right. We need shell. We need magnet to get shell to get magnifying glass. Okay.
Okay. All right. All right. Ask me questions. We got it. We got it. We got it. What about that
cave? This guy's a partisan streamer. Do you know anything about that cave? Oh, what? No.
No, I don't know. It might not. It could be a cave. It might not be a cave. It couldn't. It
might just be a small dark place. That doesn't need to be a cave. Who knows? Could be anything.
Looks like a pile of rock. There's a cave. Well, I guess we'll agree to disagree.
It's literally a confirmed cave. A potato, potato. You know, you do, you add to me.
Okay. Let's make sure we, let's make sure we do Trump correctly. The only way I'm telling,
listen to me. The cam has to go on for this because Donald Trump is one of the only voices
where you have to actually move around. Like I am. Okay. Like my hands come up in the air like
this and cross like this and I close my fingers. I don't know. I just that you have to move around.
I, I'm very, and I'm very limited. Like I, I, this doesn't do anything, but I don't know why
you just have to do it. You're a gobbler. Get out of here. Okay. Really? Yeah. Fair enough.
Ask me questions. Just be careful. I changed this one halfway through. Now it's somebody else.
Okay. I haven't paid attention to anything. Now I know. Okay. All right. All right. All right.
Right. What's the first step though? What's the first item we need magnet? Oh God. We need
potion. We need potion to get shell, to get magnet, to get boat, to get fucking pasta, to get.
All right. Let's, we gotta get for the first one. Hi. Hello. You okay? Yeah. Are you sure? Well,
I have just never talked to a detective before. I've heard so many nice things about you.
I don't want to be embarrassing. If I am embarrassing, that would be very bad.
You're not embarrassing. That's very good news.
The conversation isn't over. There's still time. I have to be careful. Oh, well, it's okay. If I
ask you some questions. You have questions for me? Questions, yes. You seem very nervous. Why?
Oh, because of the detective thing. I told you. I'm afraid of detectives. Maybe when I was a kid,
I had a bad dream about a detective. Something like that. I don't know. Sorry to hear about your
dream. What? What? What? No, it's because this is close. I know why people are fucking mad right
now. Because this is getting really close to the thing that everybody fucking hates. I know. And
now everyone's like, no, don't shut up. Hey, I'm available. And you can feel and you're like, no,
no, no, no, no. If he says, if he says this with this voice, and he says an A and then a Y followed
by an A followed by a Y followed by a second A, I'm going to leave the stream. All right, fine.
Eric, I didn't have a dream about that. Why are you afraid of me?
Sorry about that. Fine. You've worn me down. Damn your extreme detective skills. I'm nervous
because of Mystery Monkey. Mystery Monkey is a huge fan of your blog, so I don't want to make
a fool of myself in front of you. I just think Mystery Monkey is super neat. I don't want to
be embarrassing in a case I mess up everything. Oh, well, is there anything I can do to help you?
There's a dance competition coming up tomorrow. I want to compete and show Mystery Monkey that
I'm really good at dancing, but I don't know what style of dance will impress them.
Would you ask Mystery Monkey and find out for me? I can give you this mouse wash mouth wash in return.
Sure. Questions, yes. I'll take them. The cream of the crop. The cream of the crop.
If you could do me just one favor, man.
Fucking God damn it. All right. That bottle, what do you got in there? What's in the bottle next to
you? That's my mouth wash. Give it to me. I'm having to give you to find out what type of dance
style. All right, we're going to go Mystery Monkey. Okay, do it in Randy Savage is one of those voices
that if you go all out and you really go on, you really your voice will be hurt and pain for three
days after you do it. Guaranteed. I don't know how he did that so often. He must have had a voice
made out of his vocal cords are probably made out of fucking iron. Like it's just so much pressure
coming out of your throat at the same time. So much pressure. That was a fucking legend.
All right. All right. All right. We need to go. Dude, we got to talk to the monkey. I'll come back.
I'm getting that bottle. This is supposed to take 30 minutes to beat this game. I've already beaten
the game once. All right. Where's you? What kind of dance do you like? I forgot his voice.
Questions, yes. What would you like to know? What is your favorite dance style?
Hey, so you you like dancing and dance styles? I don't understand. I like dancing a lot if that's
what you're asking. Yeah, kind of. What type of dancing do you like the most out of all dancing?
Well, I basically have one move. Yeah, but yeah, if you saw someone dancing, what scenario would
you most likely be? This is such a good dance to me. What? I guess what I'm trying to ask is
what dance style do you like the best? I have to pay attention. I think break dancing is so neat.
If I saw someone break dancing, wow, I would swoon. I would even go so far to say if I saw.
I did Randy Savage for one second and like it hurts. I did it for one second. It's all right.
I can't do any more voices with the rest of the screen. I'd be deeply impressed myself
if somebody breakdanced that I would want to hang out with them at all times forever. That's great.
I got look, I got a lot of proven that could be whiskey, but it's not. It's water that's been
poured over coffee beans and then drained into a glass. Still water, technically. All right. Sorry,
touch change question. That's OK. I'm not sure it's important to the case. All right. So now
let's go get the mouthwash. Got a monkey fact. Thanks for injuring yourself at the beginning
of the stream. I feel like I've done that like five times already. I've hurt myself
during a stream and I'm just like, well, ouch, see you in six hours. Oh, a broom.
Got a broom. All right. So what? Look, it's you. Can I pick it up? All right. Here we go.
I want that mouthwash. We have some questions. Questions. Yes. I'm going to do a fake Randy
Savage. Hey, I talked to Mystery Monkey. Oh, my gosh. Did you mention me? What did Mystery Monkey
say? Does Mystery Monkey hate me? So embarrassed. I didn't mention you. That's just Joel. Yeah.
Doesn't Joel do a really good? This is just a bad Joel. He does like a perfect Randy Savage.
I could never compare. Yeah, I couldn't. Mystery Monkey likes breakdancing the best.
Joel basically is Randy Savage. That's fucking funny. Breakdancing? I think I could do that.
I got to start practicing now, though. Good luck. Thanks. Oh, here's the mouthwash before I forget.
Cheers. All right. Got the mouthwash. Now what the hell do we need to do with this?
Oh, dude, fucking stream is going to be bopping real soon. It even looks like the same character.
That's what's fucked up. Somebody link that gif. This is the same character. It's the same dance
and it's the same person. So I need Char. We haven't talked to you. Who are you?
Who are you? Who are you? I didn't mean to startle you. I'm Frog Detective. Oh, okay. Don't sneak
up on me like that. I was visible for the entire approach. Well, fine. I guess I just don't look
so smirky. Okay, I'll do my best. Sorry, I'm so cranky. I haven't slept in two weeks. I'm Martin,
king of the island. You're a king? Well, when I got here, there was nobody else on the island
except for me and Finley. So I thought I was fine to declare myself as king. Finley? I don't think
Finley cares about that sort of stuff. Finley mostly cares about the dance competition.
No, I meant to ask who's Finley. Oh, okay then. Can I ask you a few questions?
Go ahead. Not questions for me. Dance competition. You mentioned dance competition. Can you tell me
a little more about that than you said? It's tomorrow. Anything else? Oh, the best dancer wins.
Okay. You got questions for me? This accent's changing every fucking half second. I'm being
ripped through like portals. I'm being ripped through like accent portals. I can't pick one.
He's moving from country to country to country. Who's Finley? Someone's playing with the slider.
Yeah. You mentioned your friend Finley. Who's that guy? Finley lives on an hippie island and
comes to visit me every few days. The last time I saw Finley, she was talking about this song.
She wanted to dance to her day competition. Her moves were pretty amazing. Not like me.
She'll probably win. I haven't seen her in a while, but she's probably still prepping for
the competition. It is tomorrow. Not that I'll be in to complain to her with what the hell's
broken situation going on. Got questions for me? What about the noises? Can you tell me about the
noises and where they come from? I'm not exactly sure where they come from, but I know they're
coming from a ghost. How do you know for sure? I have a book about ghosts. It's called The Ghost
Guide, Food-Proof Ways to Detect a Spirit. I've read most of it. Anyway, in the book it says
that most ghosts can't be seen. Get this? I haven't seen a single one yet. The proof is all there.
Got questions for me? The American accent is seriously like, do you have questions for me?
You got questions for me? You got questions for me? You have questions for me? You guys have seen
that video? It's one of my favorite videos. It's a dictionary talking about accents.
On some websites you can have a definition of a word, right? It's stand. You guys have seen this
video? Stand versus stand. British versus American. I've told this already. There's a lot of new people
here. There's a website where you can place different accents for different words. One of
the words is stand. The person clicks on the English speaking version of it and it's like
stand. And then they click on the just American English and it goes stand.
It sounds like so bad. Stunned. Stunned. Did you find it? You found it. Good. Yeah.
It's like just one of them just sounds so elegant and the other one's just like,
whatever. Read the YouTube comments? Stand. Stand.
It's funny every time, man. I haven't seen this video in a while. It's funny every time.
Stand. Stand. One more time. One more time. We'll move on. Stand. Stand. What is the only
comment? But yeah, that's like, that's so funny. One year ago, a year ago. Yeah,
we've talked about this is one of my favorite YouTube videos. Just having 82,000 views
is just, it's criminal. This should not be, this should be at like 820 million views.
I think I, yeah, I showed you guys this like a year ago, but you know, I thought your favorite
video was the hog calling contest. It's changed a little bit over the years. It's changed a little
bit. Wait, hold on. That's a re-upload. Oh, well, whatever. All right. What about your nerves?
You seem super nervous. Is there something I can do to help you? It's just the ghost getting me
down. I haven't been able to sleep. Kind of annoyed too, because I usually love hearing
stories about ghosts. Read all about them on the cyberweb.com. But now, I'm living one.
I'm sure we'll get to the bottom of things. Bottom of the grave more like a...
What? That made more sense in my head. I guess I mean like we'll probably die before the mystery
is solved. That's pretty dark. Dark, just like the conclusion of this tale. Sorry if I'm being
dramatic. You know I'm a good detective, right? I've solved every case I've taken on,
except the mystery of how to put on a hat. I don't like hats. My head is a strange shape.
It really is. The point is, you're safe. I'm going to find the culprit. The best thing you
can do is sit and wait. Everything will be okay. I don't feel okay. I'm finding it hard to calm
down. I understand ghosts are scary, but there might not be a ghost. You really think it's not
a ghost? I don't know for sure. Oh. Let's try a visualization exercise. What's a visualization...
Exorcism? It's a thing where we pretend. Imagine you're on a beach surrounded by calming waves.
You can feel cool breeze on your face. The waves slowly move in and then out. It's a safe beach.
What beach is it? This beach. This isn't a safe beach. There's a ghost here.
No, the ghost is on holiday. Oh, okay. Where is it? On a road trip. Cool. Can we visualize
that we're on a road trip instead? But the ghost is on the road trip. Great point. Continue.
Anyway, the waves are coming in and out slowly. There's nothing to worry about.
No ghosts around at all. The ghost is on a road trip? Yep. Nothing to fear. A nice sandy beach.
Just me in the ocean. How do you feel? So relaxed. Great. Me too. Thanks so much, detective.
That's okay. I want to give you something as thanks. Perhaps a piece of my crown. A chunk of pure
gold. Wow, that's so kind. It's really heavy. It better be. It's made out of pure gold, man.
Why? I like gold. Okay. Got questions for me? What? Weirdly, weird sexual voice?
What are you talking about? That's half the fucking sounds you heard on the radio.
All right, I got a pure gold. Okay, what? I got this potion. I mean, he doesn't know. Remember,
do not split up when searching for ghosts like Scooby-Doo. Who took my sunglasses? Give them back.
That's me. I did that. Cool. Note, some fall noises need some tomatoes or soup. Who is ghost?
I'm not qualified. This might come in handy. Got a magnet. Oh, that was easy. That was really easy.
That was super easy. That was the easiest thing I've done all day. I got the magnet. Okay.
Science line, don't go in. Okay. What are you going to do? Fucking kill me?
Hmm. I should have listened to the sign. All right, we got a magnet.
We got a magnet? Okay. Always with the question. Is there anything you need to know?
I got a magnet. I brought you a magnet. What? A real one? Are you for real? Yes. This is a
dream come true. Thank you so much. No problem. In return, I'll give you this big shell.
I don't need it anyway. Great. Thanks. Wow. A real magnet. All right. Now we take the shell
and we go over here. I think this needs a new voice. Always. Always asking questions.
Ask me questions. Just be careful. I have a big shell if you want one.
How did you do this? Somebody? How did you do that? It's a long story. Oh, in that case,
I don't care. Just give me the shell. Don't care. I hate stories, especially long ones.
Okay. Anyway, I totally want the shell. Can I swap you for the shell? Very quickly.
I have this magnifying glass. Look at the tiny shells. They're very small. I won't need it now
that I have this big shell. Cool. Thanks. You're still standing weird. I'm still on alert.
Here's the magnifying glass. Now get out of here. Wow. What a crowd. Biggest crowd anyone's ever
seen. And then we go over here. Who wanted the magnifying glass? You did. I've got something for
you. Best deal in the history of all magnifying glasses. Every magnifying glass. It's the best
deal ever. Just sometimes. Do we have a voice? Oh yeah. Questions. Questions. Questions. What else
do you want to know? I have a spare magnifying glass if you want one. Interested? Are you kidding
me? There's very little, there's nothing I want more. Here you go. This is the best day ever.
All of my dreams are coming true. We got Medicare for all. We got magnifying glasses. And remember,
I was the first one that put forth the magnifying glass bill of 1981. Best day ever. Is there
anything I can do to repay you? Do you need any help with your secret agent business? I'm not a
secret agent. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. I can give you my lunch. Oh, what you cooking? Pasta as always.
I always eat as cheap as I can. A little bit of olive oil on your pasta. That's all you need.
Some of these people put tomato sauce on their pasta. Too much. Too expensive. Pasta is all.
If there's one thing I love apart from a thrill of secrecy is pasta. Anyway, my appetite is
satiated from the deliciousness of this magnifying glass. That's a weird way to word that. Whatever.
You like my pasta or what? Yay. It's all yours. All right. What do we need? All right. We have,
we need one. Wait, wait, wait. Is this enough? I think we have everything. I forget. Oh yeah.
Right. It's evil. A little more evil. More questions. Ask me them. The questions I read.
What else is new? Didn't you list the ingredients for the explosive device?
Toothpaste, some wool, a chunk of pure gold, and some pasta. Ask me the questions I read.
We need wool. How do I get wool? Larry David and Bernie Sanders are the same person.
Didn't they like meet and they just kind of started going like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
They just like kind of were yelling at each other for like a minute or two.
I fucking love Larry David. If you've never seen Curb Your Enthusiasm,
just do, just what are you doing? Like do it. What are you doing? All right. So what, what now?
I need, oh, you got wool right here. Hey, how's it hanging? Fine. I guess bored mostly.
Why are you bored? That's suspicious. Suspicious? Why? Surely you can't just say I'm suspicious.
There's no rule against it. I'm not being suspicious at all. I guess not. Sorry for calling
you suspicious. That's okay. Why are you bored? Isn't hunting ghosts supposed to be exciting?
For the first week? Sure. Not now though. I've been at this post the entire time.
I'm shedding everywhere. Gross. I know. You mind if I ask you a few questions?
Ask away. Shitting? Why are you shitting so much? I haven't had a trim in ages. It's just so yuck.
Split ends everywhere. I'm usually getting cut once a week, but it's been two weeks now.
Yuck. It's so gross. It's totally fine. Thanks for trying to spare my feelings. There is wool
everywhere. I think everyone is so grossed out by it. Surely that's not true. Maybe not,
but it feels true in my heart. I think most people like wool. Used for so much stuff. Like what?
My jumper is made out of wool. Wait, are you for real? Yes. That's weird. It's weird that
you're wearing my hair. Wool is pretty gross too. That's why I keep mine short. I don't think wool
is gross at all. Okay, but what if I wore a coat made of your slime? What? Ew. Gross, right? Sure,
but slime is kind of gross anyway. And I'm not saying that as someone who is very slimy.
I am saying that. Wool is worn by most people. It's the first time I've heard someone wearing
a wool. I think that makes you the weird one. Plus, I'm pretty sure the shirt you were wearing
is wool. Wait, wait. What? I'm wearing another sheep's hair? I'm pretty sure, yeah. Gross.
I'm happy to take your wool away from you if you'd like. I mean, your own wool is not whatever.
Oh, yes, please. You'll need something to clean it up with. Like a broom or a fire or something.
Okay, cool. I probably won't use fire. Okay. I can't believe I'm wearing wool.
What if it's Barney's? What if I ask you some more questions?
Can I ask away? Hey, I got that broom. Ready to clean?
Yeah, it's amazing. Thanks, detective. Can I keep this broom? Absolutely. Can I keep your wool?
It's still weird, but yeah, knock yourself out. What? I mean, like, take all the wool you want,
not physically knock yourself out. Are you stupid? Phew. All right, I'm ready.
Is this the Witcher? All right, here we go. Four questions. Ask me them the questions I mean,
those ones. Can you list the ingredients one more time? Toothpaste, wool,
chunk of gold, and some pasta. Thanks. Do I not have toothpaste? Wait, that doesn't count?
That's mouthwash. Where would I get toothpaste? There's more. Wait, bug. There's a bug. Oh,
wait a minute. Holy shit. There's a small enemy spider. Howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy,
howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy, howdy.
Yep. Right. You brought my toothpaste shipment? No, I'm the detective. Oh, okay. Can I call you
T-D-T-T-T-TEC or whatever? Yes. Nice. I have some questions. Is that okay?
Take it away, detective. Why aren't you wearing a lab coat like the other scientists?
It's my day off. I've been working so hard for the last two weeks. It's very important to take a
break and get some sun. You're right. Not about the sun, but taking day off. Yeah, I didn't
pick a great day for it. Sorry to question you on your day off. Take it away, detective.
Well, I'll tell you something. Arthur, hope you don't mind me saying, but you have wonderful teeth.
Oh, thank you. Thank you. I'm so glad someone finally noticed. How do you keep them so pearly,
White? Which Dr. Tight Smile's 101 tooth whitening cool paste for teeth, of course.
Dr. Tight Smile's 101 tooth whitening cool paste for teeth. I get a shipment here every three days.
I go through the stuff so quickly. I'm down to my last tube. Well, where can I get some of my own
toothpaste? Do you have teeth? Well, I could give you my tube, but I would need something
else to keep my mouth fresh. I think about it. Can I ask you some of these questions?
Take it away, detective. Mouthwash. I have some mouthwash for you. Amazing. Thanks.
Am I able to use your toothpaste now? I almost forgot. Here you go, detective. Take it. Do
what you will with it. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. More questions. Ask me the questions, I mean. I've slowed down a little. I'm trying to
be more like my friend over here on the other side. He's a little more toned down than me.
I'm trying to be more like him. Let's make some dynamite. Let's see. Oh, you got everything.
Yep. Amazing. Shall we make some dynamite? Yes. Let's do it. Nice. I'll cook up some
dynamite and we can get exploding, baby. Punished Bernie. Well, this is it. Yep. Time to blow this
cave up. Larry, explosives are dangerous. Sorry. Time to carefully blow this cave up. Thank you.
No worries. I'm nervous. Me too. And I'm not even coming into the cave. You're not?
I don't like dark spaces. I'm a sunny boy, baby. I'm not a baby. Sorry. Anyway, good luck.
Look after yourself in there. Thanks, Larry. Let's do it. That's like super animated. I'm surprised
that was like fully animated. Everyone is Bernie. Oh, let me just tell you something. Okay. Oh,
my pasta. My pasta. I got pasta here. Okay. Thanks. Everyone is Bernie. Well, that's not
true. That's not necessarily true. Oh, FPS gameplay. Every one of them is from Alabama.
That's not true. There was that one guy that was from every country on earth.
So, I mean, that's not true. Stream will be popping. This is the bird. It's Finley. Oh, hi.
Uh, who are you? Are you a ghost? What? I don't think so. Are you sure? Hmm. Yep. That's great.
You're not wrong. So, um, who are you? Finley. Who are you? The detective. Howdy. Wait a minute.
Finley. I know that name. I'm pretty well known around here. Around local dance circles.
Fuck. No, I can't. I can't do Irish. I can't. No, not Irish. Not Irish. Not Irish. Anybody.
Anything but Irish. Anything. You're Martin's friend. Ah, yeah. What are you? What are you
doing here? Oh, practicing for the dance competition. It's tomorrow. How long have you been down here?
Uh, geez. Like two weeks, I think. I didn't even realize.
Wait. Two weeks? Have you seen any ghosts around? Nah. Just me down here. Does Martin know you're
here? I don't think so. He never comes down here. Really? Why not? He thinks every dark
space is haunted. Oh, he reads all those ghost books and thinks there's a ghost in every
square. It's good for me, though. Perfect spot to try. You've been dancing for two weeks, right?
All right. Yeah. Aren't you tired? I mean, I
picked naps. These mushrooms are super nutritious. Gross. Mushrooms are disgusting.
That's your opinion, detective. No, it's a fact. Okay. Okay.
Anyway, Martin's been super spooked out because he's been hearing weird noise down
the island. Any idea what that is? I've been listening to my radio while dancing.
Let me tell you, it has been crazy. This cave has lots of holes in it. The sound from your radio
could easily travel up to the surface. I bet it's super warped, too. You know you've been trapped in
here, right? The cave's been blocked off by rocks. Really? Really? Really? Really? Okay, here we are.
No, yeah, right here. Right there. I think this is it right here. That's so funny. Yeah, you could
have died. Then I'd actually be a ghost. I didn't even think of that. Yeah. Anyway, let's go. Let's
leave. Oh, look at me. Finley. Hi, Martin. Hi. What are you doing here? I was in the cave.
What? How did you get in? It's been sealed up for weeks. Two weeks, to be exact. As it turns out,
there was never a ghost. It was Finley in the cave the whole time. She was so wrapped up in
practicing she didn't even notice the cave got caved in. The noises from her radio powered up to
her surface and sounds really scary. But my ghost books. I was so sure it was a ghost. No, just me.
Ghosts assure you you should never trust books. Don't ever read one. Always use the internet
instead. Yeah. Books are, without exception, actually inaccurate. Yep. Wait. Hold on. Hi,
apologies for the interruption. I hope you're enjoying the game. I won't keep you for long.
Well, I agree with the detective on most issues. There are contexts in which books can be very
useful and informative. It's important to check the validity of the author's sources
and to check the book is up to date. The internet can also be a useful place to find information,
but make sure you're getting your information from a trusted site. Thank you for your time.
Enjoy the rest of the game. So anyway, as I was saying, books have no place in society.
Sure thing. That makes a lot of sense. Thank you for opening my eyes to the usefulness
of the internet and the uselessness of books. You're very welcome. The useless snake.
So just to be clear, you were practicing for the competition this whole time.
I'm in it to win it. I'm still not entirely sure what this dance competition involves.
Dance competition. Best dancer wins. Who else is competing? That's a good point.
Just us, I guess. Don't forget Moe the Mouse. Who? One of the ghost scientists. The what?
Don't worry about it. I think we need more entrance. I know a few hardworking friends
who could use a good boogie, but they won't be here tomorrow. Well, let's move the competition
to today. Before we dance, I just want to say thanks for solving the mystery, detective.
No problem at all. I had a lot of fun. Help. Larry figured out where the noises were coming from.
Larry? Is that the lobster? The one that talks over everybody?
Well, I give my thanks to Larry too. Shall we boogie?
Let's go. I beat the game. Holy shit. Frog Detective's fucking got some monster moves.
He needs some space. Hey, he's just flexing on everyone. Yeah, he really is. Like everyone's
going to get out of the way. Who has the best moves though? Let's see. What a mystery.
Tier list. Okay. I think we've practiced enough. Wait a minute. Who's judging? Wait,
this is the best part of the whole game. I'll do it. All right. We have to decide. Let's go.
All right. All right. Okay. All right. No, no, you can't pull out the robot. No.
And next. All right. I like it. All right. That's the best one so far. That's the single lady.
That's robot two. Nope. That's all right. That shit face. That shit face guy at wedding.
When the wedding circle forms and everyone starts dancing and they're like, you go in,
now you go in. And everyone's like clapping along and there's some really cool shit. And then
somebody just stumbles into the middle and they're fucked. And all they can do is just move their
arms around people like, yeah, awesome. But in your head, you're going, holy fuck man. Somebody
sit down. Somebody's got to sit that guy down and give him a water. It was Larry. It was Larry.
No, no, no. There's no poll. It was that like single ladies. Yeah. Yep. I didn't, I didn't
did no votes for that one. Sorry. This is the election. What was the plot of the game?
I don't know. I was concentrating on doing voices for 85% of it. I don't even know what we did.
We went to an island and we solved it. There was a cave that was noise was coming out of it.
I don't remember anything. Hopefully you guys can do new game plus pog. Oh, well, that's cool.
This is the last case that we saw. Okay. Cool. I wonder what happened there. All I know is that
on this picture, there's a giant enemy crap. No, fuck that. I'm not doing that one again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't want to keep that. Okay. When we do the community content,
and I just know I'm continuing to perpetuate the meme of the giant enemy spider because there are
like 10 giant enemy spider remixes tonight. So I, all right, we're going to, there's a lot of remixes
already.
Frog detective, crime solving agency. Frog detective speaking. How can I help you? Detective
supervisor. Great work on the haunted island mystery. Thank you. I tried really hard.
I don't think even lobster cop could have solved that one. I think you're underestimating lobster
cop. You're probably right. Anyway, as I saw you busted a groove at the dance competition.
Yeah. Where'd you see that? It was on TV. Every channel, every channel in HD. Cool. I didn't even
see any cameras. Well, you certainly impressed the public. My phone has been ringing off the hook.
Mostly the calls are about your dancing, but I did get one call about a case. Have you heard of
warlock woods? I haven't. Well, there's some very strange going on things around there.
They need our best investigator on the job. Lobster cop was not available.
Can you handle another case detective? I can handle anything. The detective will return
in the fucking star wars episode two, the case of the invisible wizard. Oh no, that's the wrong
franchise. Captain America will return. Star Wars will return. Well, whoever wouldn't know
star wars will return. That was cute. It's already out. It's out now. Play it. Don't play it right
now. No, but no, no, no, no, no. We don't have time for that. We don't have time for that. How
long is it? Yes, we do. It's another hour. It's 30 minutes. All right. All right. Let's do another
one. Let's do let's do frog detective chapter two. Let's go. All right. Let's do it. Yeah. All
right. Let's do it. Guys, I already I think I already own it. Do I? Case of the invisible wizard.
Done. I already got it. It takes like an hour to be. All right. Then fucking whatever. Fine.
This is cute. We got time for community. This community content is not going to be as long as
the last one. It's like half as much stuff because it's like a part two and it's catching us up to
like last week. Oh, look at that. I do. I have it already. Yeah, don't worry. This one is what's
it called? You're going to hear a loud and I'm really sorry about that. It wasn't even that loud.
Dude, hyper hype in the chat, hype in the chat, hype train. What the fuck is going on?
Hype train started. I disabled hype trains. So don't even try. They physically are turned off
on this channel. Looking for a game to capture. Found one. Found one. Frog Detective 2. I got to
change the game, right? This is not accurate. We're in Frog Detective 2 now. The case of the
invisible wizard. This is cute. Isn't that cute? Speed run it. Can you? Can I speed run this? I
don't know. I don't want to speed run it. I want to take my time and have some fun. All right. Let's
keep going. Here we go. Frog Detective 2. New voices. It's a new game. There's going to be new
voices. And unfortunately the voice actor from Frog Detective 1 did not move on to Frog Detective 2.
He was in the middle of other projects. So that's the biggest gripe that I think a lot of people
have with this one. I've heard. So hopefully that it's still, you know, hopefully people still think
it's any good. I don't know. Let's find out. Frog Detective Crime Solving Agency. Frog Detective
speaking. Hey detective. Hi supervisor. Why did you hang up on me? Huh? We were talking just a
moment ago about a new case. The one at Warlock Woods, right? Yeah. I hung up because I got too
excited about solving another mystery. That's understandable. What can I, what can you tell me
about this new case? It's a doozy detective. Hold on to your hat. Supervisor, you know I can't wear
hats. Sorry. Anyway, what, what, what, what, what the fuck do you want me to do about this?
All right. I told you what happened. All right. You want, you want me to mute his sections and I,
hold on. I know that voice actor. You want me to call him and see if he'll like, he'll come
into like a discord call and like read it. Well, it costs a lot of money. I know that actor. Okay.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Let me, let me see if they're on discord. They are.
They're online. Well, you just, just hold on. Wait until I get them in a call. A couple of days ago,
a new resident moved in. A shy kind of gal. Doesn't like to be the center of attention.
Anyway, she settles into the new house and doesn't go outside to greet anyone.
The residents of the town feel like they need to welcome her properly. So they organize a welcoming
parade. Great idea. Absolutely. But someone in the town seemed to think otherwise. Last night,
the parade decorations were destroyed. What? I know, right? So rude. Nobody has any leads on
the case. They don't. I'm waiting for them to fucking reply to me. Jesus guys. I can't just
turn it off. I'm waiting for a reply on discord. Everybody needs to relax. Holy shit. That's where
you. All right. Hold on. Are you fucking around now? Jesus fucking Christ. Hold on.
Hello? Hey, what's up? It's me. Oh, hey, what's going on? How are you doing? I'm doing good. Did
you get my messages that I sent you? Yes, I did. All right. Do you, are you cool with doing this?
Yeah, it's okay. All right. So I'm going to mute the frog sections and then you can come in.
And I mean, it might be delayed a little bit. It's okay. No, that's fine with me. I'll do that.
That's fine. Cool. Real voice, by the way. Real voice, by the way. Are you ready? Yeah, I'm ready.
Okay. Oh, oh, sorry. That's me. I'm the detective. I'm aware. Warlock Woods is a magic town. So it's
not the easiest place to get to. You'll need to take an enchanted cart to the end of the line,
then travel the rest of the way on foot. Too easy. You'll need to question everybody to get to the
bottom of things. Do you think you can solve the mystery? Great. Hop to it. Oh, I forgot to mention
the new resident of the woods is special. She's invisible. Oh, that was loud. Hey, can you,
are you eating something? Yeah. Can you put, can you put just, I've got a little lot of people
here watching. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Oh, that was loud. And a wizard, an invisible wizard. Cool. Um,
what's the relevance of her being invisible? Nobody knows what she looks like. So they're
really excited to find out. That's the parade and the decorations and the celebrations.
They want her to be un-visible? De-invisibled? Uh, uh, visible. Exactly. Anyway, how do you
have everything you need? Um, I have my shoes, my jumper, my pants. I think I'm missing something.
Your magnifying glass? Of course. It's on the table next to the die. Why did I say diaper?
I was gonna say diaper. Yeah, you're not very good at reading. What the fuck am I,
how was that, why was I going to say diaper? Unprofessional. Shut the fuck up,
dickhead. That's very rude to say. Am I getting paid for this by the way? Thanks supervisor.
Good luck detective. Ah, my trusty magnifying glass. I can't solve mysteries without it.
What, he's calling me now? He's calling me, you're calling me now? Should I answer it? Hello? I'm
sorry. Okay. It's all right. Yes, I'll, I'll pay you by the way. I didn't mean to fly off the handle
like that. I'll turn it back down. Same thing, same deal. Okay. Let's go. Ah, my trustworthy
magnifying glass. I can't solve mysteries without it. Well, maybe I could, but I wouldn't want to.
It's missing background white noise from his mic. No, no, don't give me that idea. Please.
Fuck. God damn it. Hold on. That's fucking stupid enough for me to think it's funny. Just wait.
He has push to talk on. Yeah, but hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me one second. This
is worth, this is worth it to me. Bear it back. Okay. I just had to, uh, need to just fix his mic.
Something's wrong with his mic. Sorry. There we go. Look through your magnifier with right click.
Yes, yes, yes. We know how to do this. Let's go. Are you ready? Lobster cop. Uh oh.
It was a wink. Is it Larry? No, it's not Larry. Ah, it's the famous frog detective.
Perhaps not, but I'm sure you will be soon. I hope so. What brings you to my office detective?
It's actually next door, right here. Oh, I thought that was a cupboard. Oh, that's my office.
I've been putting all my cleaning supplies in there. Yes, I'm looking every time you do it.
They even say, this is my office. And then you say, sure, this is your cleaning frog.
And then I say, I'm a crime-solving frog, not a cleaning frog.
Excuse my ignorance detective. I wasn't trying to offend.
Make him louder. Turn him up. It's, can you talk for me for a second?
That's not, it needs to be a little louder. You're too quiet. Let me turn you up a little.
Say something. Is that better? A little bit, say it again. How's that? Is that sound better?
No, it turns, your mic is fucked up. You don't have any, hold on, wait, wait, wait,
check to see what mic you have plugged in. I think I have this one plugged. I think I'm on,
it says, larger tech webcam microphone 920. No, no, no, no, no, wrong mic. You have a better mic,
don't you? No, I don't. You don't have a better mic. Aren't you a voice actor?
You don't have, you don't have a single. Let me try plugging this one in. Do you think this one's
better? Hello? Is that better? Does that sound better on this one? Or should you go back to the
other one? No, go back to the other one. The other one, other one, other one. That's a little better.
Why do you sound so different on this one? You're on, you're on Skype on the phone.
All right, fuck it, whatever. We gotta, we, I mean, we can't just do this all day.
This is, that's fine. So I'm going to put you, I'll just put you, I'll pump the phone through.
That's fine. You know, you want to just come over? Just come over, just come over. Like I'll do my
best impression of you as best as I fucking can. Two hours? Two, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Now,
like right now. Get here now. I don't have a car. Just drive here now. I'll do my best. Okay.
I'll be here in two hours. Be here in fucking 10 minutes. I'm getting another phone call.
What the fuck is calling me now? What? Stop, hold on. Stop, stop. Hello? Oh, Jeremy. I'm so glad I
got to get a hold of you. It's me, Bill Blueberry. I heard you were looking for some voice work.
You're looking for some voice actors. I can do voice work. Okay. You'll be here. I gotta hold
the phone with my mouth. Are you, are you going to, how, when, when do you think you'll be here?
Is he gone? All right, he's gone. Fucking Blueberry calling me. Doesn't he? I hate this shit.
People know I'm fucking streaming. So aggravating. Like why would you call me during the middle of
the stream to like try to get on the stream? Like get the fuck out of here, dude. Anyways,
I'll do my best. Excuse my ignorance, detective. I wasn't trying to offend. I'm a very busy boy,
a head full of mysteries. Sometimes I forget to be polite. If I was polite all the time,
I would never have time to soften it. Hold on. I can do better than that. That's a better,
better voice, right? I got a better voice than that, don't I? He's just like, oh, look at me.
I understand. Maybe that's why I'm not as talented as you, lobster cop.
Perhaps, but detective, you must keep trying. Never give up. I can give you some tips if you'd
like. Wow. Yes, please. Tip number one. Pay attention. You should make sure you are looking
at things and paying attention to words. Yes, quite right. Tip number two. Everyone is a suspect.
Even you. I will suspect myself much more from now on. Good call. Good call. Tip number three.
Carry a notebook. Oh, I'm not really big on books. They are without exception factually inaccurate.
Detective, don't be foolish. A book you write yourself cannot be factually inaccurate if you
are writing facts. I suppose you're right. I don't have a notebook though. Well, it's your
lucky day. I have a spare notebook on my desk. You can decorate it and use it all you like.
Wow, really? Yep. There are stickers you can use too. I bought them all with my crime solving money.
Cool. I'll let you get to it, detective. Head into my office when you're ready to decorate.
Okay. Thanks, lobster cop. Thanks. Thanks, lobster cop. It's fucking hard to do.
I hope he gets here soon. We can decorate the office? Oh, stickers. Which stickers should I
pick? And where should they go? Oh, this is tough. This is tough. Oh, schmock. That's good.
No. Wait, this is kind of off. Worm dick. All right. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry. Sorry for the worm dick. Done. Done. Clap for me. Clap for me. Clap for me. I fucking
demand it. Clap for me. I fucking demand it. Clap for me. I fucking demand it. I got a notebook.
Open it. Oh, there's a new mechanic. Notebook. Magnifier. Invisible wizard. That's a lot of pages.
Notes. Number one best detective has lots of fans. It's super cool. So many trophies. I hope I get
a trophy one day. You don't have any trophies. Liar. There's no chairs in here. It's okay.
You can stand right there. Right in front of the mic. Right here? That's a little too close. Hold
back. Okay. Is this ready? Good. All right. I'll get you some. You can sit down right there. That's
fine. Sick. Sick. Sick. Sick. Sick. You know what to do. You know what to do, man of the hour.
Say it. Say the line. You came just in time. It's time to solve it. Oh. Are you all right?
Are you okay? My leg. That was my leg. I know. You all right? No, you're fine. You're fine. You
okay? Yeah, I'm okay. This was slippery. Why is it so wet? Because I sweat a lot.
Okay. It's time to solve another mystery. Did it. Does this look swollen? Yeah.
Really swollen. Oh, shit. Super hot. What? Are you good? I am 100% fine. Nobody worried about me.
It's not swollen. I just had a full job of peanut butter in my pocket and it slid down to the bottom
of my pants because I have a hole in my pants. Oh, okay. You're good. Snacking on the go.
You're making it worse. New characters. Hold on. We got new characters. He didn't shit his pants.
Does Jerma Wink even work? What the fuck? It didn't go through? What a scam. Warlock Woods.
Oh, my stars. It's you. It's me. The famous lobster cop. I really thought you'd be a lobster.
I know I'm frog. Yeah. Why is your name lobster cop? I have to tell you something.
I'm not lobster cop. Why not? I don't know how to answer that. Who are you? I'm the detective.
Frog detective. I see. Is lobster cop not available? Unfortunately, not. Well, I think you'll do just
fine. Thanks. I'm Susan. Hi, Susan. I'm the one that contacted the agency,
which I think you'll find excludes me from being a suspect. Oh, I didn't know that would work.
You should know these things, detective. I'm sorry. It's okay. I think you should still question me,
though. Getting into Eeyore territory, but remove all doubt. Okay. Question me all you like.
Oh, the wizard. You got a balloon here. Do you know the wizard? I'm sorry. I spoke up before you
did. Do you know the wizard personally? Nobody knows her personally. Well, not here at least.
Not me. Right. But I had a lot to do with the organization of the parade.
And I was the one to start the investigation. You mentioned that. Worth bringing up again.
So you were fine with her moving to town? Absolutely. That old house has been empty
for years and it's really nice. Someone wants to live there. He's a lot of fixing up, but I'll
look nice soon. I think plus it's always exciting to have a new neighbor. Sure is. I put up a sign
I made for the wizard, but it got knocked down last night. Feeling pretty sad about it. If I'm
honest, I know you're here to solve the mystery, but I just need to tell someone how I feel.
You can talk to me about it. Thanks. I'm not a professional sign maker, but I worked really hard
on that sign. Really. I struggled to understand why someone would knock it down. It feels so
heartless. And now I'm not sure who to trust. I thought everyone here would be thrilled to have
a new neighbor. It's a tricky situation for sure. Some people are protective of their communities
and think new people are going to change things for the worse, but that's almost never the case.
New people make places better because they bring new perspectives, especially in small communities.
Hopefully it's just misunderstanding or a mistake. I'd like to believe people are good.
That being said, I'm treating everyone as a suspect. Not me, right? Even you, especially you.
Especially me? Oh, I know. Sorry. Not sure why I said that, but you're not off the hook just yet.
That's it. Detective, could you please find me a hook? I could hang the sign back up with it.
Oh, okay. I'll do my best. Question me all you like. Okay, I need a hook. Small,
fucking enemy. It's wider. Square. All right, Susan. Motive. Maybe she didn't like her sign
destroyed at the parade out of embarrassment. Something to fix the sign. It says she's not as
suspicious. This makes her much more suspicious. Upset about the parade being destroyed. Worked
really hard on her sign. What do you sound like? What do you sound like? What do you sound like?
What do you sound like? What do you sound like? Hello, little frog. I'm Ralph. Why are you yelling?
I'm just making sure you can hear me. I can hear you. You don't have to yell. You're very
small. Might be difficult for you to hear. I'm small, but I'm also very close to you. Being
small isn't the same as being far away. Are you sure? You can hear me at this volume? Yes.
Weird. I'm the detective. I'm here to solve mystery. Really? Yes. But you're so small.
I'm of average frog height. Can I ask you some questions about case? Questioning me, huh? What
happened to your eye? May I ask why you have an eye patch on? That's Ralph's business. Oh, it'd be
really good for me to know why you have an eye patch. Sometimes a boy just wants to wear an eye
patch. That shouldn't make me a suspicious. You put it on for fashion. Kind of. Detective,
I don't want to get into this too much, but I watched a movie last night about pirates,
and I loved it. And there's another three left. Three whole movies. Can you believe it?
Sequels? I've never heard of a movie having a sequel before. A giant enemy. I know, right?
Usually sequels are reserved for video games. Yes, it's extremely normal to have a video game
sequel. Especially for games with large audiences like the Toad Investigation Series. Yeah. Anyway,
I was watching a pirate movie last night. That's where I was. And for that reason,
I have decided to wear an eye patch. Okay. I'll leave it at that. Thanks. Questioning me,
what about the wizard? I can't wait till there's a wizard so I can do a fucking wizard voice.
You know how that is every time. How do you feel about the wizard moving in?
It's nothing against the wizard, but I've been living away. I've been living with my friend
Carlos for a while now, and our space is big. I would really like my own home. I'd been eyeing
off that old house for ages, but maybe I'd move in one day. But the wizard, not there first.
I see. It's my fault, I guess. I shouldn't hold it against the wizard. Hmm. This house is twice
as big as all the other houses. Maybe you could renovate it and turn it into two houses. You could
split it down the middle, or have one house upstairs and one house downstairs, like an apartment.
That's a pretty cool idea. I like Carlos and everything, but I'm a private boy.
I understand. I don't have any renovation supplies, though.
I'll see if I can track some down for you. Thanks for your help, detective.
Maybe if I do a good job, I'll get my own building, sure. I'm excited to see it.
Dude, three houses. Two houses stacked on top of three houses? A motive in true pirate fashion
wanted to cause a ruckus, needs building supplies, loves pirates, eye patches cosmetic only,
a private boy, wants to renovate, thinks I am too small. I am not.
Why don't you get it out of your system now while you have a minute. Nice.
Hmm. What? Huh? Who are you? The detective. Oh, I thought Lobster Cop was coming.
Huh? What? Did you say something about Lobster Cop? No. But I heard- Can this frog read my mind?
Why are you speaking like that? Like what? Like this? Whoa! Is that what telepathy is?
Can you hear this frog? You're saying everything out loud.
Wow, this frog has a temper. Anyway, who are you?
I'm Noddy. Okay.
I'm the mayor of Warlock Woods. Okay. Did you ask me to come?
No. I would have asked for Lobster Cop instead. I really need to emphasize I can hear you.
Stop listening to me. Okay. Can I ask you some questions about taste?
I guess so. Tell me what you want to know. How do I change your voice to something that's
not as awful? Well, okay. I'll take that as a- I'll take that criticism.
Can you tell me about last night? Nothing.
Oh. But I can tell you about the wizard.
I know basically everything there is to know about her.
That's great. First of all, she's a wizard.
Uh-huh. And she- get this. She's invisible.
Great. And she just moved in. And now we're going- and- and she's a wizard.
We're gonna take the wizard and we're gonna- they're taking over all of our- all of-
they're 1% wizards. Fucking back to Bernie.
I think you mentioned that. No, I don't think I did.
He only has one voice. It's- it's just different spectrums of Bernie.
It's like this. It's like this. It's like this. It's like this.
This is like this. It's like this. Everybody has to sound like Bernie Sanders.
All of us. Doesn't matter what we do. Doesn't matter how close we can be to each other.
We're always gonna be Bernie. Right, okay. Sorry.
It's fine. Anyway, tell me what you want to know.
That's a real voice. That's real. That's two hours straight of doing this.
That's- that was what that was. About the wizard.
How do you feel about the wizard coming to live here?
Oh, heck, how do I answer this? Well, I'm happy she's here,
but that house has been empty for ages. And I don't- didn't know she was coming,
all right? Nobody told me, you see. Not Bernie.
Look, I- oh my god, it's not Bernie. Do I- okay, do I sound like Bernie right now?
Do I sound like Bernie right now? I want to tell you something about-
I want to talk about this. Do I sound like Bernie Sanders?
No, I don't. My- my regular speaking voice has nothing to do with it.
When I talk normally, I go from sentence to sentence and everything is perfectly normal,
as you understand, as you hear now. I have absolutely nothing in common
with the way that he talks or the way that he enunciates words, okay?
God damn it. I think so.
She kind of came- wrong. He's doing it on purpose.
She kind of came at me at a weird time of night, and I- well, I thought that she was a ghost.
Oh, yeah, it was a bit messy. Oh, I tried to vacuum her up.
Hmm, with a vacuum. I put it on the highest setting.
Just really went to town with the vacuum. I think I really freaked her out,
and now she won't come out of the house. Um, please don't put me in jail.
You're not going to jail. Jail isn't real.
But you prob- you should probably apologize.
Okay, sorry, detective. I mean to the wizard.
Right, yeah. That's why I was helping with the parade, to apologize.
But she hasn't been out of the house. Also, the parade is ruined.
I see. This makes me sound really bad.
I swear I wanted the parade to be lovely.
As the mayor of the town, I booked a live band to play a song.
But as you can see, the stage is gross and ruined now.
The band is on their way, and I have no time to fix it.
They're a very famous band. I want to be as professional as possible.
Offer the voice actor a beer. You want a beer?
No. I- I offered him a beer.
What the fuck are you- Well, if only I had a rug or something to use, I could cover up the mess.
But the town is in disarray. I don't have time to track one down.
Oh, no. Thank you for your concern.
If you happen to find anything that would work, please let me know.
Will do. Do you have any more questions?
Hmm. Now, we need a rug. We need a rug. We need to fix the sign.
We need building supplies. He's not a drunk like some people.
But is that- is that- is that a shot at me?
What are you talking about? I haven't had- I haven't had a drink of alcohol in, like, two weeks.
What are you talking about? I drink alcohol, like, once every two months.
Maybe. He's sloshed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Okay.
Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
Hi. Hi.
A customer.
Welcome to the Carlos All Things You Can Need shop.
Are you Carlos?
Yes. Just like the name of the shop. That's me.
How cool is that? The shop has my name on it.
So cool. My company also has my name on it.
What's your company called?
Frog Detective Crime Solving Agency.
What's your name? Crime?
Oh, no. I'm the Frog Detective.
That's not really a name, though. More of a title.
Oh, I suppose you're right.
My shop actually has my name in it.
Cool. I'm jealous.
Thanks. Here in Warlock Woods, we are all our own biggest fans.
Being conceded is a societal construct. We have rejected it.
Hence why my shop is so popular. I sell portraits, among other things.
Wow. That's great.
My office neighbor, Lobster Cop, has a picture of himself right above his desk.
You know Lobster Cop? Holy heck. I've been a fan forever.
You know, he solved the mystery of the Haunted Island recently.
I don't think so. It was actually me that did that. That was me.
Wait, really? It was all over TV. The dance competition had a lobster in it.
Oh, you must be thinking of Larry.
You mean Small Larry? No, this was a regular-sized lobster.
Uh, no. Larry's regular-sized lobster.
About the Larry I know.
Oh, well. Agree to disagree.
I really did solve that mystery. It was me, detective.
That's really cool.
Thanks.
So you're like the second best detective, I suppose?
Yeah. Did somebody just put a germ of Pluto with a bloody nose?
Oh, no, no. What?
Yeah. Do you mind if I ask you some questions?
Okay. What would you like to know?
Fucking Bernie. What do you need?
All right, it's over. I gotta stop the read now, normally.
You can go home now.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Get out of here. Get out of here,
because I can't pretend to be three, five, eight people anymore.
I'm staying.
Okay, you can stay.
Just here in my shop.
What about when you're closed up?
My shop doesn't close. My shop doesn't close.
It's 24 hours. What time do you close?
Oh, fucking, I'm doing it again.
What if somebody's a portrait of themselves at 4 a.m.?
You're open all the time?
Of course. I sleep and eat and look after myself.
My customers simply wake me if they need to buy something.
Where do you sleep?
I sleep standing up. Here's the training.
I'm the most committed shopkeeper at all of Warlock Woods.
Also, the only shopkeeper at all of Warlock Woods.
I'm the only one, Froggy.
Do you ever take breaks?
Sometimes, but I really like it here in my shop.
It's where I feel most at home.
The extreme shopkeeper lifestyle isn't for everyone,
but I take so much joy from my work.
Me too. Although, I must request that you look after yourself
and close the shop if you need a break.
Okay, I promise.
Anyway, did you say anything last night?
Nothing particularly interesting. Why?
She cried.
I think I need to question you a bit more.
Go for it.
What would you like to know?
Why do they always pause and go like, huh?
What do you want, huh?
Hi? Hey?
Frog voice actor.
Is he okay? Are you okay?
He swallowed an almond. He's all right.
What do you know about the new wizard that just moved in?
Who?
The invisible wizard that moved in literally next door.
Wait, really? Somebody moved in?
Yeah.
That place has been empty for ages.
I got to say hi.
Oh, the parade was meant to be for saying hi.
Get him some water.
He needs a parade? Parade?
The parade that everyone has been prepping for.
Oh, he's been working so hard. He needs a water.
He's been working so hard. He needs a water, doesn't he?
Get this guy a water.
Do you want a water or do you want a beer?
I want a beer.
God. Beer.
Oh, how nice. Can't wait.
It was destroyed last night.
What?
This conversation is a roller coaster of information.
I have literally no idea what's happening.
You weren't involved in the decoration.
You okay? You gonna be all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
You weren't involved in the decoration at all?
Nope. Should I offer to help now?
Wait, who is he? He needs a break.
He's like, what did you do before you came over here?
What did you eat? Like, you ate a bunch of shellfish?
Are you like allergic to something?
Jesus Christ.
He's not...
He's...
No, he's not.
How old are you?
All right.
Let's go.
No, it's for the invisible wizard.
She just moved it next door.
People saying he's not old enough to work.
Yes, he's like 38.
Why am I asking an imaginary person
if they're old enough to be working for me?
So, I'm done.
Oh, dear.
The party hats.
Pardon?
Every time we throw a parade, everyone has a party hat.
Mine was ruined at the last parade.
He is real. I know.
I've been too busy working at my shop to buy a new one.
Oh, no.
How embarrassing.
I can't show up to the parade without one.
Do you think it's too late to order one online?
It'll be tight.
You're right.
Oh, what should I do?
Don't stress.
I'll track one down for you before the parade starts.
Oh, my fucking stomach.
Oh, this is fucking...
This is killing me.
Everyone's going to point it out now.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you, detective.
In the meantime, I'll figure out a way to repay you.
Unfortunately, I don't have any frog portraits just yet.
Not a problem.
What would you like to know?
That's all.
Can you please check on their leg?
Is it still swollen?
Oh, my god.
This is so fucked up.
Okay, we have two or three more characters to introduce.
And they're all going to have normal ass voices, by the way.
Ahem.
You're the detective, right?
I'm Mandy.
Hi, Mandy.
Be careful where you step, detective.
There is mess everywhere.
I'm used to mess.
Lucky you, I'm not.
My shoes are brand new.
I can't get them dirty.
Why don't you change shoes?
Detective, are you joking?
I can't wear flats with this look.
Proportions would be all wrong.
Besides, these shoes are enchanted.
Oh.
I'm one of the few actual witches here in Warlock Woods.
Most folks here are just fans of the spooky.
Which is fine and all, but it means a lot of the cleaning work will be mine to do.
I never should have learned that tidying up spell.
It shouldn't take too long for me to clean up this mess,
but first I need to find all my pies.
I haven't seen pies.
Same thing that happened everywhere.
Someone thought it'd be funny to knock them all over.
Vandals.
So annoying.
I spent ages making them.
Oh, I see.
Well, do you mind if I ask you some questions?
Tell me what you want to know about your pies.
Do you need help finding your pies?
Yes.
Detective, seriously.
I seriously need help.
Straight up.
I can't see anything right now.
These glasses are so dark it's unreal.
I'm such a dingus.
Holy fuck.
It's nice.
Nice.
That's a cool...
Nobody says that.
This town is literally cloaked in eternal night.
I do.
No, you don't.
That's my thing.
No, that's my thing.
Don't stop talking about other people that say that.
That's my thing.
It's a German 985 channel thing.
It's my thing.
Let's talk about the people that do that.
Oh, this person does it too.
No, it's my thing.
They can't do it.
Why do I think sunglasses would be a good idea?
They weren't a good idea.
However, I don't regret it.
They make me look amazing.
Do you think I look amazing?
Thanks, I do too.
Worst purchase I've ever made in terms of practicality,
but it brings this look to a new level.
I may be a dingus,
but I'm very stylish dingus.
What were you talking about?
My outfit.
No, no, no.
Before that.
Pies.
Right.
You offered to help pick up my pies.
I'm missing quite a few.
If you could bring them to me,
I'd be happy to clean them up all up
and give you one as payment.
Pie.
Okay, so sounds like fun.
Neat.
Thanks, detective.
Tell me what you want to know.
I need a pie.
All right.
So we're going to put another circle here.
Mandy needs help finding her five pies.
Okay, we can just run around and find them, right?
I'm going to knock them over.
Schooled me about fashion, fair enough.
Real.
Ask her about the wisdom.
All right.
Oh, can I?
Where were you last night?
Doing heaps of pushups and getting ripped.
Just kidding.
I was on wizbay.net where magic happens, TM.
How are you doing?
Bidding on some new shoes.
Oh, you just got those ones?
Yeah, but the ones I was bidding on
would go super well with this blue dress I have.
Wow, cool.
I know.
I didn't win though.
Who got shoes?
Not sure.
All I know is their screen name.
Someone called DizzyWizzy109.
Sorry to hear it.
How did you feel when you lost?
A bit defeated.
I went for a midnight stroll to cool off,
but then I saw someone in the distance.
It was a pretty, it was a pretty froggy night,
so I couldn't see much,
but they were carrying a large box.
I couldn't see what they looked like,
but they definitely weren't from here.
It felt like they were waiting for someone.
I didn't think too much of it and went home.
Did you hear any noise after that?
No, my house is soundproof.
Ever since Mary has taken up singing,
it's kind of a necessity around here.
I only saw the mess in the morning.
Interesting.
Tell me what you want to know.
Fucking easy.
This is gonna be fucking easy.
Oh, look, DizzyWizzy109 is in chat.
Nice.
All right, we're gonna find somebody
with that screen name.
Is this the last person?
This is it, right?
Where's the, all right, what do we got here?
Let me like take, ooh, lost pie.
I got a lost pie.
Nice.
I need five of these?
I have not absorbed a single piece of information
this game has ever put forth.
I know, and that's my fault,
because I've just been fucking all this up
with voices and stuff,
and you can't even pay attention.
I'm sorry about that.
I have no idea what's going on.
This is the only task I remembered.
Two pies.
Oh.
Hey, Reindeer.
Reindeer.
Hi.
Hello.
Wanna hop in?
A little bit.
But I'm on a case.
Oh, cool.
I'm Victor.
Who are you?
The detective.
Is that your real name?
Maybe.
Cool, cool, cool.
Are you here to question me
and investigate stuff?
Because, like, I'm not suspicious.
How do you know you're not suspicious?
Well, I think I didn't do it.
You think?
Yeah, nobody knows anything
for certain these days.
So why are you here swimming?
I'm visiting my friend Naughty.
Oh.
She's the only person I know with a hot tub.
Do you remember the fucking voice from last one?
Well, I heard they were gonna be delicious pies
for the parade,
and the timing was perfect.
YouTuber Jim Carrey.
Now, just because I opened it up with, like,
Hello!
Do not!
That was Jim Carrey.
It was.
All right.
But just because I did that doesn't mean
the character is Jim Carrey.
Where do you live normally?
Over near Pumpkinville.
Nice spot.
I was thinking of taking a holiday there
at some point.
Yeah, it's fine.
Yeah.
Um, so, can I ask you a question about anything?
Yeah, whatever.
Otto3, questions.
All right.
What'd you do last night?
Do you need anything?
Where were you when the parade was destroyed?
Well, I had been swimming all day
in Naughty's hot tub,
so I was super wrinkly.
Yep.
And it was hard for me to get inside the house
because of my wrinkly hooves.
Uh-huh.
So I waited for about a half an hour
for the wrinkles to de-wrinkle.
Yep.
And then I went inside to Naughty's house
and snoozed on the couch all night.
What time was that?
All night.
No, I mean, what time?
That is not the time.
What time do you close?
What time do you get back into the house?
I gotta stop doing that.
I gotta stop fucking...
I can't do No Country for All Men every half day.
Before the parade was destroyed,
it wasn't me.
Probably wasn't me, I mean.
Can't be sure.
But 90% probability that it wasn't me.
Questions, you have them.
Stop talking in voices.
For fuck's sake.
One guy.
Did you know about the invisible wizard
before you get...
What if I started going, even why?
Not really.
I knew the parade was for her,
but beyond that, I know a lot.
I'm begging you, do that.
Talk in tongues.
Just going nuts.
I think a lot more people would leave
if I did that one.
Annoying that they never threw a parade
for me coming to visit.
I'm super cool.
Have you been here before?
So many times.
The first time they even threw me a parade.
Okay.
I take the parade thing back.
Just pretend I didn't say that.
Sure.
Detective, I'm really bored of this conversation.
I'm sorry if that's rude,
but I have a new policy of being honest with people.
Were you dishonest before?
Yeah, I guess.
I wouldn't tell people when they were boring me.
I don't think that counts as dishonesty.
What am I supposed to do when people are boring?
I don't know.
Leave the stream.
Find somebody else to watch.
But probably don't tell them.
It would hurt their feelings.
I didn't hurt your feelings though, did I?
Well, I have to admit I was a bit hurt.
I have a very exciting job and I'm a frog.
I like to solve mysteries.
I don't think I'm boring at all.
Well, Jerma was hired to voice act this entire game.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah.
I'm full of energy today, if you couldn't tell.
This game sucks.
All right, actually ban that person for five minutes.
I want them to sit there and think about it.
It should be like...
And then they can talk again.
Plus, I've solved my fair share of crimes.
What crimes?
This one.
You've solved the crime already?
Yeah, Ralph did it.
How do you know?
Good point.
I haven't decided that bit yet.
But it seems likely that he did.
What was his motive?
His what?
Motive, the reason for destroying something.
Oh, I think it's because he has an iPad on.
This is a great stream.
You guys are smoking crack.
You guys are smoking.
Don't smoke crack.
That's not good for you.
I don't think that's a motive.
That doesn't make any sense.
Wow, who's the rude one?
This conversation...
I'm just...
Let's go.
I just...
We're just sitting here going back and forth saying the same three sentences.
I mean it.
I just get so grumpy when I'm hungry.
Why don't you eat something and get out of the hot tub?
No, I just...
I must continue to soak.
You could ask someone to get you something to eat.
Like who?
There is nobody here.
I am here.
I have to get him something to eat.
Right there.
I go being rude again.
If you happen to find food, I would love to have some.
In the meantime, I would like to apologize for being so rude.
Please take one money as an apology.
Nice.
Wait, give item?
Lost?
Should I give him a pie?
Is this...
Should I not give him a pie?
No, no, no, no.
No, he doesn't deserve it.
He doesn't deserve it.
No, it's not.
It's not your pie.
Am I going to give this pie back that was on the ground
and then this person is going to sell it for money
and the person is going to eat something that was on the ground?
Very rude.
Rude because of hunger.
Maybe just rude in general doesn't live here.
Okay.
Smoke and crack.
All right, we got...
How many pies do we need?
We need five.
What do I have?
Two?
How much does this stuff cost in the store?
That's too expensive.
How am I going to ever afford this stuff?
Six dollars for a sheep?
Hello, wizard.
All right, I haven't talked to you.
Hello?
Hello, frog.
That was there.
That was a fucking softball.
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Mary.
Nice to meet...
Same person.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Did you like my song?
Yep.
I've been practicing all day and all night.
Oh, are you okay?
He's getting embarrassed from this.
Turn on mic distortion for one of these.
All right, fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
I guess it's...
How's this one sound?
This is a pretty good sounding one.
Not a bad one.
Okay.
I'm tired.
Maybe you should get some sleep.
Maybe.
You sing very loudly.
I'm why everyone's soundproof their houses.
That sounds expensive.
Yeah, but that's not really my problem.
I think I sound very good even late at night.
How late?
I love to sing at 3 a.m.
Wow.
That's when my energy is the highest.
That doesn't sound very healthy.
My health is my business.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Maybe I should listen to some soft sounds before bed.
Welcome to my hair salon.
That will be 100 money.
Just joking.
Anyway, who are you?
I'm the detective.
Oh, cool.
Can you question me?
Do you mind if I ask?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Oh, boy.
I love questions.
What do you know about the wizard that moved in?
Wrong voice.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't actually hear you.
I was asking about the wizard.
Oh, yeah, there's a wizard.
She just moved in.
Why?
I'm a detective.
Right.
This is part of the questioning, right?
Yes.
Cool.
So I didn't do any crimes or anything.
And I have the right to remain silent.
Yeah.
But did you want to remain silent?
Literally never.
So like, I heard that Ralph was super weird about the new wizard moving in.
Also, I heard that Mandy was in a bad mood the night the parade was destroyed.
And I heard that Naughty, like, attacked the wizard one time.
And that's all, actually.
Does this make me a snitch?
I think so.
Rats.
Oh, boy, I love questions.
What were you doing when the parade was destroyed?
Oh, boy, yeah.
Sucks that the parade was destroyed.
Oh, we're doing questioning.
What was I doing?
Not much.
Just singing outside.
You were outside when the parade was destroyed?
Yeah.
Did you see anything?
What did you see?
Detective, have you heard of extortion?
Yes.
That's great news.
Is it?
Detective, I would like to extort you.
I don't think that's legal.
I am above the law.
Oh, why are you extorting me?
I would like five money for a train ticket.
I don't have any money.
Well, you best get some soon.
It was her.
She did it.
What do you need a train ticket for?
He's getting bored.
No, just shh.
I want to go to Froggy.
I just broke this shit.
I'm sorry.
This is actually the knob.
The knob slipped.
I want to go to Froggy Wood and become a star.
Oh, that sounds exciting.
I know, right?
Sorry about the extortion thing, but I don't really have many other ways to get there.
I figure if you get the money from me, I can finally go and live my dreams.
Do I have to do this?
I'm not doing that.
What will you give me in exchange?
He's getting bored.
Fuck.
Hold on.
I'm not getting bored.
What kind of information?
A phone number.
Who am I calling?
I can't tell you that.
All I can say is that they were in the vicinity when the parade was destroyed.
I don't think you'll be able to solve the case without this phone number.
Hence the extortion.
Sorry.
It's okay.
We all get extorted every now and then.
Yeah.
Anyway, come back to me when you have my money.
Oh boy, I love questions.
Five dollars?
Do Robo Bernie.
Oh my god.
Perhaps the wizard is a better singer than her.
Bernie.
Robo Bernie.
I can't.
I can't have this be three hours of Bernie Sanders.
With like sprinkling.
Sprinkle in like a baby voice and like Donald Trump and then some Obama.
Like I can't have three hours.
I can't have three hours of Bernie.
We can't do that.
All right.
I need to buy those pies.
What about the corn chips?
Whatever they are.
Should I pick these up?
Oh, there's a pie.
Four hours of Dean Dingus.
Finally some good fucking food.
God damn it, man.
All right.
What have we got?
I need two more pies.
What was that?
You see that?
I can't go in it.
Wait, I can go in the houses?
Hello, is anyone home?
Sounds like somebody's inside, but I shouldn't intrude on.
I'll come back another time.
Hurry up and investigate.
What the fuck do you think I'm doing?
You're a detective.
Yeah, and I'm I'm detectiving.
What do you think I'm doing?
This is the wizard.
Yeah, I know.
I need two more pies.
I have no idea where they are.
Wow, wow, wowie, wowie, wowie.
What?
Look, idiot.
Look, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot.
He's stupid.
Look, he's stupid.
In the water?
There's nothing in the water.
Found one.
It's a lost pie.
I need one more.
There's a huge deer in the water.
I can see the deer in the water.
Yeah, I know.
That's a little strange.
One more pie and then we can do a turn in.
Can I take the balloon?
Got it.
And go.
All right, let's do the turn in.
Five lost pies.
Streams like this are why I need a therapist.
What?
All right, what do you want?
Uh, here are your pies.
All five of them.
Well, all of them?
I think so.
Yeah, that looks like all of them.
Wow, you must have searched far and wide.
Yes.
Wowie, thanks, detective.
Show this stream to the doctor.
You mean you're going to show this stream to your doctor
and say something's wrong with me.
I got something wrong with me here.
Not me.
I don't show this one to my doctor.
Here's one money.
That's it.
You didn't promise pain.
Wait, why one?
I gave you five pies.
Oh, I'm not okay.
I'm not very hungry.
You can hold on to it.
What?
Nonsense.
Take one and eat it later when you're hungry.
All right, now we give the pie to the elk.
Got a pie.
Pie to the elk.
Elk gets out of the water.
That's a good deal.
One dollar for five pies.
Done.
No, my doctor would probably shout bald at me then subscribe to you.
What?
I've got something for you.
Questions.
Take a pie.
That's real and true.
Are you still hungry?
Yes, very.
It's making me really rude.
For example, I think your jumper is outdated.
Victor, I'm not the most fashionable frog in the world,
but I like this jumper.
It's my favorite.
You're right.
It's retro, not outdated.
I'm simply very hungry.
Here is a pie.
Seriously?
Score.
Yep, please enjoy it.
Oh my gosh, that was amazing.
And I feel so much less rude now.
Really?
Yep.
You have beautiful eyes.
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
It's true.
And I think that color jumper suits you perfectly.
You're making me blush.
I should give you something in return for this pie.
I have a spare party hat I'm not using.
Maybe you could wear it.
Alas, my head is simply too weird.
Well, hold on to it anyways.
Might come in handy.
Thanks.
All right, got a party hat.
Party hats for somebody who wanted one of these, right?
Who wanted the party hat?
Can you please call Bugleberry again?
No, I fucking blocked him.
I blocked his number.
Bugleberry is worse than a telemarketer.
I get more calls in the middle of dinner from Bugleberry
than I do from people trying to sell me shit.
Or take a survey.
All right, who wanted the party hat?
Not you.
You?
You wanted supplies.
Who wants it?
You want a party hat?
Who want a party hat?
Need something to fix her sign?
Want supplies?
Want some rug?
All right, Carlos wants a party hat.
Paul Bugleberry, he's crying.
He's not crying.
What would you like to know?
I have a party hat for you.
Carlos, I have something for you.
No way.
It's a party hat.
Yes way.
That's epic.
That's honestly the most epic thing I've heard all day.
Thanks, detective.
Hold on, sorry.
The word epic was said like four times in a row
and I got a headache.
Not a problem.
Incorrect, it was a problem.
And you solved it.
Just like a true detective.
Oh, thanks.
You've made a fan out of me.
Here, let me pay you for your work.
Oh, no, no, that's okay.
Detective, I insist you take a payment.
One money should do it.
Three dollars?
Carlos just subscribed.
Thanks for the sub, Carlos.
Appreciate it.
Thanks for the sub.
Welcome to the stream.
Oh, I also found this rug out back.
Not sure what it was for,
but I figured you're good at solving these puzzles.
All right, now we got a rug.
Read his sub message.
I just did.
Bugleberry just messaged me on AIM.
He's coming over.
Don't let Bugleberry over your house.
He's never going to leave.
He'll find excuses to stay.
You'll be there for four hours
sitting there watching TV
and you know that he's not going to leave anytime soon,
but you want him to leave,
but there's no reason for him to leave
because you said it was okay for him to come over.
So you're sitting on the couch,
both just watching fucking random videos
or YouTube videos or TV shows.
It's like, we're not doing anything.
We're not going anywhere.
I don't want you to be here anymore,
but I don't have a reason to make you leave.
And then out of nowhere,
you're hoping you don't hear it, but you do.
You hungry?
Let's order some food.
It's like, oh, that's at least another fucking 30 minutes
before the food to get here.
And now you're going to be here for like an hour.
There's a two hours now.
Or we're going to go somewhere instead.
I don't want to pay.
I don't want to do that right now.
I'm going to make a tuna sandwich in the fridge.
No, I'm all good.
I'm good.
I don't want food.
Oh, what was the last time you ate?
Fuck.
Okay.
You've been here for four hours, so you know.
It's been at least probably six hours.
I'm not hungry.
Not really.
That was a real wink.
All right.
Rug.
Bugaberry is a positive role model.
Tell me what you want to know.
I got a rug.
Scam wink.
All right.
Let me just get like 10 of them out of the way
because I'm going to get scammed.
Great news.
What is it?
I found you a rug.
What?
Holy guacaboli.
This is great news.
Thanks for tracking it down.
This should do the trick.
Wow.
It looks just like new.
Hopefully the band won't notice the mess.
You just tanked the wink market.
Yeah.
Now it's worth like one cent.
I don't think they will.
They're in a fish tank anyway.
Why?
One guess.
They're a fish.
Bingo.
Wait.
Do you mean to tell me
you got the most famous band of all time?
The Market Buddies?
Yep.
They're on their way.
Wow.
I saw them live once and it was blown away.
I just shorted it.
Oh, you just shorted?
Did you?
Oh, wow.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
Sorry.
Oh, you shorted the winks.
Wow.
Winks are now a million points.
Fucking idiot.
I can't wait.
I'm excited too.
I can't wait for the parade to begin.
I better get back to work.
Did I get any money?
Before you go,
I should give you something in return.
One dollar.
I have some building supplies left over
from when I made the stage.
Is that enough?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Real wink.
So this is if a real wink comes in,
I just stare and then people realize,
oh, no, no, no.
Oh my God.
They're worthless.
Now they're not.
Now I can't even get a wink for buying a wink.
Now I go.
This is when I go to court and shit.
I get sued.
And it's a fucking mess.
Get out now.
It was simply a favor.
Don't be silly.
You worked hard to get me this rug.
I insist.
Wow, thanks.
Got one money and building supplies.
These voices are making my teeth fall out.
I'm going to be really honest with you here.
I think that's just a coincidence of you
not going to the dentist for 10 years.
It happened now.
Like your teeth started.
It had nothing to do with me.
I hear the supplies.
The wink is a scam.
Dump it.
Dump all your points.
Dump all points.
Invest in highlights.
Oh, no.
You guys are just throwing it all away.
Hello, small frog.
I managed to track down some building supplies.
Oh, great.
What exciting news.
I'd love to use them if you're okay to hand them over.
You guys are really selling all your points.
We just like banged all these out in a row.
Holy shit.
That was one, two, three, four, five.
Excellent.
Thank you so much.
Of course, I must pay you for this.
Oh, there's no need.
Really?
I won't hear it.
Please take a money.
One money.
Thank you.
Also, I think you've earned yourself
the title of honorary pirate.
Wow.
Really?
Me?
A pirate?
Yes, you have the treasure collecting skills
of the finest pirate.
For this, I must award you a special prize.
Here, take this hook.
Got a hook.
The hook goes over here.
We did this all in a row in 10 seconds.
Why am I not reading highlighted messages?
Because there's a million of them.
Wait, when did I say that I read out loud
all highlighted messages?
I don't.
That's impossible.
Because you devalued the wing.
So you guys are just devaluing
the highlighted chat messages.
That's what you're doing.
The more you do that, the more devalued they become.
Dermot lied about reading highlights.
Hey, what?
Dermot, you just said, all right, I'm moving on.
Look at this chat.
What a fucking engaged chat, by the way.
Look at this.
This is the third worst chat experience.
What are you talking about?
I would put this as the first best chat experience of 2020.
Sorry, I didn't really know why I said that.
All good.
Enjoy the hook.
And move over here.
Dermot, this is inhuman.
I didn't do anything.
I did Bernie Sanders for three hours.
Look what I got.
Okay, here's a hook.
You're back.
I found you a hook.
Oh, my stars.
Thank you.
I can fix my sign right away.
That's okay.
It's welcome.
I would like to repay you for this hook.
Let me guess.
One coin.
I got it for free.
Nothing is free in this world.
Just kidding.
Our society is really progressive
and often things are actually free.
As a sign of my gratitude,
please feel free to use my house whenever you need.
I can just use your house?
It's fairly simple, but beautifully decorated at least.
I have a phone too.
Great.
I'll be sure to use that.
I now live here.
Thank you, Susan.
I've worked really hard.
When's community content night?
Give or take maybe like 12 minutes from right now
because I think we're at the end of the game.
Anything in here?
Should I use the phone?
Yeah, there'll be a pee break.
Who should I call?
Oh, I don't have any numbers.
Okay.
Well, how much money do I have?
I have five money, which is what...
Who wanted...
You wanted five money.
Five money?
Oh, boy.
I love questions.
Five money.
Hi, Mary.
Hey, Detective.
How's the extortion going?
I think I've got your five money.
Well, for real?
I didn't think the extortion would work so quickly.
That's excellent news.
I'm really good at being extorted.
I'll say.
Anyway, do you have the information for me?
Totally.
Last night, I saw the postman drop off a parcel.
It was around the time the parade got destroyed.
I couldn't see who he was giving it to,
but it was someone here in the town.
Barney is the postman's name.
He's a chill dude.
I don't think he'd mind if you called him.
Have his number.
May I have it?
Absolutely.
Got phone number.
Thanks for giving me this money.
I'm really excited to see Froggy Wood.
I'm excited too.
And then I have to wait until the parade's over.
Of course.
See you around, Detective.
Now we call Barney.
Who knows Cam?
Everybody always talk shit when we repeat a joke on the channel.
You guys are going to request knows Cam.
How dare you?
I'll actually fucking dare you.
Who should I call?
Call the mysterious number.
That's a small phone number.
He's driving.
Hi, it's Barney.
I have you on speaker.
Hi Barney.
Hi.
Who am I talking to?
Lobster cop.
Wow, really?
No, I was tricking you.
Rats.
Who is this noodle?
I'm the detective.
I'm calling about an incident that happened last night on Warlock Woods.
I didn't do it.
Do what?
Whatever you're calling about, it wasn't me.
Are you sure?
What did I do?
Last night someone destroyed a parade,
which was being set up for the new resident of the town, the invisible wizard.
I was told you were in the area when it happened.
Oh yeah, I was there.
Didn't destroy anything, if that's what you're asking.
Was just delivering a parcel.
Who were you delivering it to?
What was your name?
Lola.
I don't think there's anyone in town called Lola.
Must have been someone who lives there that the dress was drawn to parcel.
Oh, I can't remember exactly what house it was.
Sorry.
Do you remember where the parcel was sent from?
Oh yeah, I deliver a lot of parcels from them.
It was from the Wizbay.Bet headquarters.
That sounds really familiar, like the two of us on the phone right now.
You just are a little older sounding than me.
Where have I heard that name before?
I know Mandy's buys a lot of stuff from there, but this wasn't for her.
Do you know what was in the package?
Some sort of shoe, I think.
Maybe two shoes?
Her shoes?
Did you get a good look at them?
It was pretty dark.
I have no recollection of really seeing anyone.
Not even if this guy's a terrible mailman.
Yeah, 6666 viewers right now.
Fucking parade.
Oh weird, Warlock Woods is pretty dark,
but I haven't had much trouble seeing anyone before.
Me neither.
It wasn't much more dark than normal either.
All I remember is a blue dress with stars on it.
I'm pretty stumped on this case, Barney.
Do you know if there were any clues left behind?
A signature on the delivery slip or something?
I didn't get them to sign it,
but I remember someone dropping over at the entrance to the woods.
I tried to call it, tell them, but they'd stumble off before I noticed.
At the entrance to the woods, you say?
I'll check it out.
What did we just have?
Fucking community subs?
How many subs just came in?
One, two, three, four, five, six community subs from Great Canadian FK Club.
Thank you.
Thanks, Great Canadian.
Appreciate it.
Accidentally crashed his van into the decorations to roll away without realizing.
All right, well, we have a new motive.
So now we have to go look for this package, wherever that is.
I don't know.
What about, didn't they say it was in the beginning of the town?
Did I not leave?
I mean, I know it's that person's username, right?
The eBay, whatever it was.
I missed it?
This must be the thing Barney was talking about.
Hmm, they're glasses.
Oh, they have a name engraved on them.
The Invisible Wizard.
Well, this is my only clue left.
I think I should try and return these to the wizard.
You should be in the old house near Carlos's shop.
Use your fucking eyes.
Use your glasses, Jeremy.
Don't anger me.
All right, where's the wizard's house?
Right here.
Hello, is anyone home?
I found these glasses.
All right, it's an invisible wizard, but not really.
I'll just find you again.
Was that real?
I don't know, man.
This is fucking scaring the shit out of me.
Oh, this is seriously fucking scaring the shit out of me.
It's fucking crazy.
This is scaring the shit out of me.
Door opened?
Fuck, okay.
Fuck, Jesus.
This is fucking scaring the shit out of me.
Ah, who was there?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
I'm the detective.
Oh, thank goodness.
You're here to solve the mystery.
Yes.
Okay.
Well, I don't know where my glasses are.
So solve that as soon as possible, please.
Thanks in advance.
I found your glasses, I think.
Are these yours?
Oh, I can see again.
That was so quick.
You should get a promotion.
I don't remember calling a detective to solve this mystery,
but I must have done so.
Otherwise, why would you be here right now?
Yeah.
Well, no.
I'm actually here to solve a different mystery.
Which one?
I don't mean to ruin surprise,
but the town was setting up a parade for you.
I'm sorry to tell you last night.
I'm sorry to tell you that last night,
someone destroyed it.
Wait, you're the wizard doing the wrong voice?
Oh, fuck.
You're right.
Sorry.
However, I've noticed that your house is littered with the decorations.
Where were you last night?
I was out in Whismay.
I got some new shoes.
I picked express delivery.
They arrived last night.
Oh, you're Lola.
Yes.
Back to my alibi.
I went to pick up my shoes from the delivery guy.
And then I dropped my glasses.
Needs echo.
Oh.
And that's all I have to say about that.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I think someone else must have destroyed the parade.
Perhaps one of my enemies.
You have enemies?
Um, yeah.
Who?
The guy.
People think it's Bugleberry.
You're losing viewers.
Evil guy.
Sorry, what?
Enemy.
An enemy, evil, a giant, evil enemy.
Evil guy?
Yeah.
Are you making this up?
No.
Evil dude really is my giant enemy.
Don't you mean evil guy?
Evil guy.
He's posting, he's posting cringe.
Shut up.
Quiet.
Quiet that person.
Your enemy?
Yes.
Where can I contact evil guy?
Oh, he's not able to be contacted.
He's very mysterious and he's not available right now.
Or ever even.
Anyway, he must have destroyed the parade.
Case solved.
We did it.
Well done.
Wow.
Too bad he's not able to be apprehended.
But at least we can continue with our lives.
Lola, are you being dishonest?
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
It was me.
It was an accident.
I swear it.
You destroyed the parade, didn't you?
You posted cringe, bro.
I didn't know the parade was for me.
That's so nice.
And I've ruined it.
When I dropped my glasses, I couldn't find my way home.
I was bumping into everything.
It was horrible.
Don't, please don't post cringe again.
What happened when you got home?
I had some chips stuck to me so I ate those.
And then I just hid.
Why didn't you tell anyone what happened?
I'm so embarrassed about it.
I only just moved in and already I've made a big mistake.
Can you guys even fucking hear that?
Why is that not working?
This has been, this has not been working the whole time.
No way.
I recorded it.
Dabba dabba doo.
Why are you not hearing this?
I'm so fucking mad.
I played this like, I've been playing this sentence
for the last like 15 straight minutes, like every few minutes.
Because I sampled it.
But why, I don't know why it's not working.
That, that's annoying.
That's annoying.
What the fuck happened?
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, that's annoying.
Whatever.
Oh, that sucks.
I thought I had it set up correctly.
What a pain in the ass, whatever.
Fucking joke sucked, ruined.
I sampled myself saying something
and I was, I thought you guys could hear it
and I was just not paying attention to it.
It was fucking hilarious.
I'm a very shy lady detective.
I make myself invisible so no one can see me.
That must have been why nobody saw you.
Yes, I suppose.
Did it become non-invisible, un-invisible visible?
You insist.
Ta-da.
You're a frog like me.
Yes.
I'm slightly disappointed.
What?
Well, it's just that I had a good joke prepared.
I know how it feels.
We're the same person, you and I.
Exact same fucking person.
I'll do it anyways.
Okay, so imagine that instead of a frog,
you were revealed to be a lizard.
Oh, no.
Okay, so you've just been revealed.
Okay, pretend.
Okay.
It's me, a lizard.
Wow, so you're not an invisible wizard after all.
You're an invisible lizard.
That was way worse than mine.
I don't even say that that was on the same level
as the joke I was going to make.
Don't do minus twos for something I didn't say.
You know what?
Fuck you guys, I'm out of here.
Yeah, it was a good joke.
I thought, me too.
Detective, are you going to tell everyone?
Was that even a joke you were going to make?
No, no.
Why is it not playing?
It lights up and I can see it playing.
It's just not being broadcast through to you guys
for some crazy reason.
More, if you tell everyone what I did,
they will be upset.
I think they'd forgive you right away.
What if they don't?
I want to make a good first impression.
When we go outside,
can you please tell them that it was evil guy?
That's a lie.
A white lie, perhaps.
But who is it harming really?
Evil guy.
Evil guy isn't real.
This is a moral dilemma, Lola.
Just like in my favorite episode of Parriot.
Parriot.
Parrois?
It's your choice, detective.
Let's face the music.
Or the routing settings in your GoXLR.
Yeah, I thought I had it set correctly.
I guess not.
Frog Detective 2, complete.
Now we're moving on to Community Content Night.
Episode 2, week 2.
Hello.
Hi.
My name is Lola.
Hi, Lola.
I'm a frog, just like me.
We're so glad you could make it, Lola.
You guys are standing way too close together.
Sorry that there's been so much commotion
trying to get the parade ready for you.
Somebody destroyed it last night.
Barry, don't tell her that.
We're sorry that somebody destroyed it, Lola.
The detective has been trying to figure out who did it.
Well, detective, have you solved the mystery?
Hope it wasn't me.
I'd be surprised if it was any of us.
I wouldn't, looking at you, Ralph.
What?
Ralph didn't do it, Victor.
How many times do we have to tell you?
I just don't trust that guy.
Rude.
I'm not rude anymore, Ralph.
I had food.
I don't think that's how food works.
I didn't do it.
Well, I guess we'll find out in a moment.
Go ahead, detective.
She did it.
Who was it?
It was, it was Lola.
What?
It was an accident.
Lola dropped her glasses last night
while picking up some shoes she bought on Whizbay.
Oh my gosh, those are the ones I really wanted.
They look amazing.
Lola can't see without her glasses,
so she had a lot of trouble getting home last night.
I'm doing the thing that you,
I'm doing the mother, the parents,
reading the story in bed when you were a kid.
And they're getting, they're losing interest,
and they're falling asleep,
and then they start to do,
we talked about this before.
She bumped into just about everything.
I'm so sorry, I feel awful.
I realized what happened
when I had lots of chips stuck to me.
Do the Earth Explodes joke.
What?
I ate them, they were delicious.
The parade was for me all along,
and I didn't realize it.
Lola was very scared of your reactions,
so she hid in her house out of shame.
Oh, Lola, it's okay.
You should have told us.
We completely understand.
Yeah, Mary destroys stuff all the time.
Yeah, I really do.
Plus, Naughty tried to vacuum you up,
so I feel like the parade being destroyed
is kind of fine.
I thought she was a ghost.
That's what they all say.
Hee hee.
We're all really excited you're here, Lola.
We don't need decorations anyway.
I really thought Ralph did it.
Victor.
Victor apologized right now to Ralph.
Ralph, sorry I said ayaya.
It's not okay.
This is a real conversation
that I have with my chat once a week.
I am also sorry.
I really didn't mean to destroy the parade,
but I should have spoken up when I did.
I'm a very nervous lady.
Plus, what a terrible first impression.
Not as bad as my first impression.
What did you do?
I ran over Mary by accident.
Ha ha, yeah.
That was really painful.
Ha ha.
Should we get this party started?
Another party.
Let's go.
Are we going to pick another dancer?
Okay, why does this feel like something
that I would see on British television?
What's happening right now?
The song, too.
The music.
What everybody's doing.
The way that everybody is and looks.
And special thanks to the super hot team.
Hash house.
House house.
Geeks.
Chad.
Ben.
Papa.
Naughty the dog.
Ben.
Papa Ben.
I'll get it right.
I just got an achievement.
It's called Snitch.
I live in my house.
Okay, where?
Right here.
Frog Detective Crime Solving Agency.
Frog Detective speaking.
How can I help you?
Detective.
Supervisor.
It's me, the supervisor.
I am aware.
Great job on solving the invisible wizard mystery.
That was quite a head-scratcher.
Sure was.
I was shocked that the culprit was the wizard herself.
Yeah, the mysteries I solve are never what they seem.
It's always a misunderstanding or an accident.
No one is ever malicious on purpose in my mysteries.
I'm so glad that crime isn't real.
Didn't you get extorted earlier?
Yes, I think that's a crime.
I suppose that crime is real after all.
Your office is called Frog Detective Crime Solving Agency.
Yes.
Detective, why do you believe that crime isn't real?
Community Night sucks.
Frog Detective forever.
You just did...
We did it all.
We did every Frog Detective that exists.
But there's no more to do.
There's no more to do.
I was exaggerating.
Plus, despite my job title,
I never really seemed to be solving crimes.
That's going to change in a moment, I think, Detective.
Oh, super duper.
Just got a call about a doozy of a case.
That sounds exciting.
It is, but it's also the most challenging case I've ever sent you on.
I'm confident in your abilities,
but you might need backup on this one.
Like who?
I'm going to send the lobster cop to help you with the case.
Really? Lobster cop handles such advanced cases.
Won't I just slow him down?
Nonsense, Detective.
You've shown you're a very capable mystery solver.
I think you're in the running to be the new number one.
You're making me blush.
You'll be a-okay.
So where am I heading next?
I can't say over the phone. It's too sensitive.
Wow. Head to the train station.
I've left a ticket for you there.
The train will take you to where you need to be.
Good luck. I want to meet this character.
Good luck, Detective.
Do you think you can handle it?
I can handle anything.
All right.
Frog Detective will return in episode three after the detective has left.
Is somebody breaking in the room and stealing something?
All right.
He looks like he's made of ice cream.
I would love to eat Frog Detective in an ice cream bar.
He's definitely lemon lime.
You know those shark bars, the shark popsicles?
I feel like he's a creamier version of that flavor.
Isn't that a character on Sesame Street?
The detective will return in
Cowboy County.
Corruption at Cowboy County.
What happened to community content night?
I deleted everything accidentally.
I just like there was a ton of it.
I just fucking hit.
I pressed the backspace button on it with everything selected.
Sorry.