Rats, we're rats, we're the rats. We pray at night, we stalk at night, we're the rats.
I'm the giant rat that makes all of the rules. Let's see what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into.
So sue me for being thorough. I want to know that you know what the plan is.
Look, seriously mate, how many artifacts do we need to steal before you trust me with these jobs?
Well, I just want to make sure you know what's happening. We're going to get the treasure, we're going to get out of there.
And we also have to...
We must get it. That's the most important thing. So be on your A-game. We go now.
I got to drive the car today because it's my birthday.
No, don't let him get in the car. Please don't let him.
Come on.
He's driving. Whatever.
Bloody hell.
Oi, more importantly, since when did we have a rat problem?
We don't. Get in.
Let's go. Speed it up.
Yeah, that's the speed I'm looking for. That's the type of fastness I want.
I don't even know where you're going at this point. We've been driving all night.
It's my birthday.
Hey, you... You're just... You're running over a guy right now.
Are you fucking serious?
I mean, next time we do this, I'll get my nan to drive.
Excuse me, sir. Yeah, you over the dancing. It's actually $10 to dance in this building. You're going to have to give me some...
Oh, I'm going to die!
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, may I have the attention of the class?
My name is Dick Dastardly Richard, and I'm here to take the treasure chest that's in the back room.
Go get it, boys. I'll follow you in.
And let me tell you something, clerk. If you so as move a muscle, I'll make sure you stay buried in that ground there.
Alright, let's go.
Alright, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme. Is the treasure in there? Is it in there?
Yep. It's all here.
Oh, yes. Now that's what I like to hear. And now we are invincible.
Not so fast.
You stand before Gerard, guardian of the treasure chest of the Mayan temple, and I will make sure to grab...
Hey.
Oh, fuck this. I'm off.
Hey, what are you doing?
We're the rats. We pray at night, we stalk at night. We're the rats.
Alright, yeah, that's cool. I like rats, nothing bad with rats, but let me tell you something.
Over my dead body are you getting this treasure.
Rats, rats, rats, rats, rats, rats.
Wow, look at that flock of birds over there. That reminds me of my favorite movie, The Movie.
That's your favorite movie, too, right?
No, my favorite movie is Frozen. I like Elsa and Anna. Okay, now I kill you.
I'd kill you.
Wow, that's great pick choice for a favorite of this movie.
I wonder if I have to think that now.
Now I get to be the giant rat.
Cool, surprise.
So you're trying to tell me that inside of this building
right here, there is a giant rat,
among other things, the giant pickles.
Did he say pickles?
Or am I putting that in there by myself?
Whatever, Sergeant Pickles is gonna go in here
and check it out.
We're gonna make sure everything's okay.
And give me some candy corn, too.
That's a weird request, I know, but just get it.
You guys are gonna drop it.
We're gonna be in big trouble.
So quit blushing around.
I hear somebody coming.
Somebody put it down, put it down.
Hey, get in.
Hello, sir.
Welcome to the Rat Cafe.
There's no rats here.
It's just hamburgers.
That would be real nice if that were true.
Except it isn't.
You're a rat, aren't you?
No, no, why would that happen?
That's not us.
We're just, we're just people.
And I'm gonna be taking you in.
And wouldn't it be funny if this were real?
I'm just kidding.
Be careful though.
There's apparently a giant rat around.
You have a good day, officer.
So, you figure anything out in there?
Nice, clean.
It's back to the drawing board.
Well, that's great.
I don't know how to draw,
so you're gonna have to do the drawing.
Sergeant Scritchy Scratch of the Cat Police reporting in.
You are now relieved of your duty.
Absolutely, Sergeant.
You've got it.
We'll be taking off now.
Thank you for your continued work.
Thank you.
Your duty will not go unnoticed.
What's that on you?
What?
Are you wearing a rat on your shoulder?
Why would I be wearing?
What the fuck?
Get in there.
They're gonna just...
Boss, we got big problems.
The Cat Police are here.
Are you kidding me right now, Cat Police?
Get us the fuck out of here.
Drive the car.
Get us out.
Let's speed it up.
Get us the fuck out of here.
Come on, get us the Cat Police.
You kids, don't leave.
I'm the police.
Good job, Cat Police.
You did it again.
You saved the world.
And that's what we do as Cat Police.
We make the world a better...