Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 Gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Cow Mangler Soldier. And I gotta apologize right off the
bat because I did say a long time ago I was gonna get this gameplay, and it never happened.
And I've done I think every single rocket launcher besides the Cow Mangler. And I am
sorry about this. But here it is, it's finally here. We have it, it's done, it's ready,
it's ready to watch, it's right here in front of us. So anyways, what do I think about the
Cow Mangler? I do have very, very conflicting opinions on this thing. And there are some
pros and of course there are cons to go along with it. And the biggest pro out of anything
with this weapon is obviously the fact that you can turn off buildings. If you don't know,
right clicking with this weapon allows you to do like a super charge like Super Saiyan
Kamehameha. And you take out a sentry gun or dispenser or a teleporter. Makes it totally
disabled, it cannot function, cannot do anything for four seconds. Now that's amazing. Especially
if you're playing with a group of people and you all happen to be on Skype or Mumble or
any of those voice chat programs. Because if you can call out when you're doing it,
and you say over the microphone, you say something like, hey, I'm gonna take that sentry down,
I'm about to do the right click, go after it, you have no fear of being shot at. It's
just fantastic. The person can turn the corner. Let's say it's a demo man or a heavy. That
sentry goes down in two seconds. So it is a very good item if you are in direct communication
with your teammates. Other than that though, the cons and the biggest con in my opinion
is the slower reload time. I cannot get over it. If you're like me, if you're an impatient
like me, it is very hard to get over the fact that it takes another like quarter second,
like point two or three seconds to get that other rocket into the chamber. It's actually
another reason why it's taken me so long to get this gameplay. It's cause I just, I get
in one-on-one fights with somebody. I burn through all my rockets and then it's like
ch-chunk, ch-chunk. And by the time I get one or two back, I'm just instantly dead.
But if you can handle that, if you can handle the little bit lower damage and you can handle
the reload time, it is definitely a rocket launcher you should look into. And you could
say that this weapon does not need ammo, but to be totally honest with you guys, I don't
think that's an issue anyways. Cause how many times have you had zero rockets in your rocket
launcher? Cause running over any weapon or picking up ammo, it's really not that difficult
to stay above like eight or nine rockets in the chamber. So I don't see that as a big
issue. So now while the second gameplay plays in the gameplay plays, that's a great word.
So while the second gameplay is in the background, there's two gameplays, both of them on King
of the Hill Harvest. I want to talk about something insane that I'm going to do. And
I've been alluding to this a little bit. I did, I talked about it in my live stream last
week, but live stream, here we go. Here, here comes the announcement. I have no idea how
I'm going to explain this. I'm going to try as best as I can to explain this thing I'm
doing. But anyways, this weekend, this coming Saturday, I am going to be doing a live stream
and it's going to be like unlike anything you have ever seen ever in your entire life
for any team Fortress 2, anything. What I plan on doing guys, I plan on doing a game
show. Now what does that even mean? Like a game, what do you mean game show? What I want
to do is I want to set up sort of like if you've, if you've ever seen deal or no deal,
that's really the only small piece of explanation I can give. Here's what I'm going to do. So
this weekend, I'm going to have 50 pieces of gift wrap. I'm going to have an entire
piece of my backpack, 50 slots as gift wrap. And what we're going to do is get everybody
into the live stream, do a trivia night and have that be up on the screen the whole time.
So all you're going to see is you're going to see 50 gift wrapped items, which could
be anything. And I mean literally anything. I've been working with this for so long, trying
to get items. There will be unusual hats, there will be strangers, there will be regular
hats, there will be strange parts. I am going to go all out with this. And what's going
to happen is I'm going to ask a trivia question into the stream. And the first person to answer
that question correctly is going to get a chance to pick one of the random gift wrapped
items. And whatever they open, they get to keep it. Now, if that happens to be an unusual
hat or a normal flare gun, that is theirs to keep forever. And that is what I'm doing
this weekend. Everything is going to be live. Everything's going to be uncut. It's going
to be just crazy. And I'm really hoping to get a really big turnout there. And to be
honest, the only thing you'd be missing out on is free, cool, crazy game show items. So
this weekend, Saturday, May 5th is going to be the huge game show live stream. It's all
going to be taking place on Twitch, twitch.tv slash jerma985. I want to do it on Twitch
because I don't want ads. I don't have a partnership. I want it to be totally uncut where everyone
can see everything. So come on over to Twitch this Saturday, 6pm Eastern time. Tell all
your friends, tell all your family members. But no, it's going to happen this weekend,
guys. I hope we have a lot of fun. And those of you saying, oh, Jeremy, don't, you don't
have to do this. You don't have to give away unusuals. That's not what this is about. It's
just about having fun as a community because that is what this is. So if you're concerned
about me losing more items, do not worry about it at all, guys. You guys know that it's not
a big deal to me. We can take care of this. I have a lot of friends, a lot of people helping
me with this as well. So do not worry. Just come, enjoy yourselves. We're going to have
a great time. So come on down this weekend, Saturday, May 5th to the Jerma Game Show extraordinaire.
Nice game show voice. But yeah, this is how I'm going to wrap the video up, guys. So thank
you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all next time. So
take care, everybody.